Tonight's Gaki no Tsukai is a half-hour show full of unreleased material that you can enjoy if you missed the recent special on meeting up without your phone!
Can I really say this?
Then by all means.
Matsumoto talks honestly about himself.
What are you doing?
Our opponent, Hamada
Who is the celebrity who appeared in front of Downtown?
Takizawa Karen's Natural Explosion
Lunch time, which was not shown in the main program, is also open to the public.
Meet up without using smartphones or other devices.
The team that gathers 5 people first wins
The losing team will be severely punished
Here are the gorgeous guests who participated in the tournament.
Matsumoto team and Hamada team with 10 regular members
The first subject is a big electronics store
Let the game begin!
Who came together first, Matsumoto's team or Hamada's team?
Where did Matsumoto's team go?
Along Meidera street in Shibuya
Okay, Shibuya!
Yamada Electric
Matsumoto team's destination is here.
And where is Hamada's team going to?
Big Lo in Shinjuku
It's in Shinjuku! It's in Shinjuku!
Is there any chance that Hamada's team will meet up with the others in Shinjuku?
And where is the leader of the team?
Anybody?
Hamada's choice is Big Camera in Akasaka
No way! This is definitely the place!
Do you see the one in red?
There's someone in red, even though there shouldn't have been a red one.
It's not good enough for you to be here, but you are here.
I don't care if you're here.
I'm getting sore for a second.
What the hell is this guy?
I've seen this guy many times.
Enemy leaders joining together
Here's a previously unseen scene that we couldn't show you in the special
I've known you since elementary school.
And why are you standing where you're standing?
You're standing over there.
Don't stand there like it's a given.
I honestly think that's the worst part of downtown.
What do you mean?
Let's get this over with.
Nearby?
That's the worst part of downtown.
That's amazing.
And one other.
What's that?
What? You're all alone in this place?
Mr. Furuichi
Are you walking here alone?
I'll introduce you.
This is Hamada in front of us.
Hello.
What's up with that?
It's work, right?
Surprise!
Actually, this is such a coincidence.
In the end, both enemy teams go to the same place, but
No one joins together as a team
The next subject is "art museum"
Matsumoto team's destination is
Ueno, Ueno
Ueno
Let's go
Matsumoto, Hosei are expected to join us at Ueno
I wonder if they have the uneducated idea
that an art museum equals Ueno in the first place.
Matsumoto with his sights set on Ueno
Matsumoto was doing this in the car
The crowd of people going back north, none of them talking much
All they hear is the roar of the sea
Listened? Listening?
Are you listening above?
I'm only listening to the ocean rumbling.
Is it there? There it is. There it is.
I'm one of them.
I'm alone? Me too?
Driver? Can I ask you to sing, Mr. Driver?
Matsumoto with the driver
The Tsugaru Kaikyo Winter Ceremony was in full swing
You know so much about it.
Hamada's team is going to
Roppongi
Was this the normal recording section of Roppongi?
Museum of Art
Roppongi
Chance for three people to meet up in Roppongi
Kawaguchi goes to the National Art Center, Tokyo in Roppongi
Ah, Pierre!
Yay!
Hamada Team Kawaguchi and Taki have joined together successfully
And here the time is up
It's a lie.
The only result is Kawaguchi and Taki meeting.
The next subject is tall buildings
Skyscrapers.
Sunshine 60
This was an option a long time ago.
Sunshine, right?
Sunshine in Ikebukuro?
Yes, Sunshine
While Downtown bring up Sunshine 60
Hosei
It looks like Endo's going to Shinjuku.
He was looking at a building in Shinjuku.
He likes buildings.
Okay, let's go to Tokyo Metropolitan Government.
Let's go to Tokyo Metropolitan Government.
To Tokyo Metropolitan Government, for Endo
Will he come up with the same Idea?
Will the other three show up at Sunshine 60 or Tokyo Metropolitan Government?
On the other hand, where do the five members of Hamada's team go?
I'll just say what comes to mind
How about both of you say what you're thinking.
Roppongi Hills
Roppongi Hills, Tokyo
Isn't that very high?
It's tall.
Is there another one over there?
They choose Tokyo Midtown
There's another one called Midtown.
And then there's the Mori Building?
What is Hamada's decision?
Chance to meet up at Tokyo Midtown
Kawagushi and Taki arrive first...
Ehhh, that?
Huh?
What?
Aaah!
Oh.
Hamada!
Yay!
Wow!
Yes! We did it! Yes!
Hamada has made it!
Against Matsumoto's team
How is Hosei's aim for finding Endo?
Anyone? Anyone? Anyone? Anyone?
Someone's running!
I knew it!
Aim for Endo
Thank you very much.
Merging with Endo, on target
Meanwhile, Kato and Iseya, who are enemies, also meet up with each other
You lie!
Time is up here
You know what I mean when I say "tall building," right?
It's the Sunshine 60.
Oh no, it's old.
Who's old?
The showdown is paused
Lunch time for each player at the same point
Matsumoto-san, is all alone in Ikebukuro
That's right.
Yes.
So he'll be eating alone
Matsumoto is the only one.
He's alone.
Here's a scene from lunch that didn't make it into the special.
Matsumoto
Here we go.
He went to a ramen restaurant near Sunshine 60
Waiting for you
It's kind of a sad place.
Hamada and his friends in midtown...
It's so stylish.
The three of them get along at an Italy restaurant.
Looks delicious
A little hard to see
Can you seeing normal Taki?
No, no, no, I don't see it.
That's about right.
roughly
It's about what it might say.
Is this a drinking place?
There are many ramen shops here
But it says 'noodles and sake'.
It's 'noodle shop'
Oh, this is says noodle shop
My eyesight is getting really bad.
Oh yeah, your writing is perfect.
I think I just wanted to drink. I guess I've already made up my mind.
On the other hand, Isea and Kato...
They were talking about love for some reason
Is there anyone you've met so far that you think is your type?
Is she your type?
It's a very big one.
Kazuko Kurosawa
Moriyama-chu?
yes
You're very particular.
What do you like about her?
It's amazing what she's like on TV.
She's funny.
I love it.
It's interesting that there's a psychological negativity in there.
I can see that.
And what about the three, Hosei and Cocorico?
I have non-alcoholic beer for now.
Thank you for your hard work
We're not done yet.
Just a quick break.
You've been thinking about it for a long time.
You're not going out at all?
I'm not going out at all
You're not going out?
Kawaguchi is very busy lately.
I love you and I have a secret
I love you and have a secret
It has started
Taki, have you seen it?
I, I ,I'll watch it.
I felt so rushed
I don't have any friends.
there's nothing wrong with that
I'm with my dog, all the way.
The dog is my friend
Dog is my friend
It's starting to get pretty dark.
While the team of friends are spending time side by side
And Matsumoto?
I hit the jackpot.
Delicious!
Can I ask you to look at this?
He's eating ramen by himself.
I'm telling the truth.
It's like a fighter's early days.
Each one finishes his meal as he pleases.
The game is now in the second half.
It was super tasty
The next subject is a famous bridge
Famous bridges
Which bridge are the 5 members of Matsumoto team aiming for?
Nihonbashi is a bridge, right?
Nihonbashi, right?
Nihonbashi, I shoot there a lot.
Matsumoto is sure to go to Nihonbashi.
Why is that so?
He'll go to something old, like Sunshine.
Maybe...
Aiming only at Matsumoto, Nihonbashi
I think he's going to say it.
Nihonbashi just because it's the beginning of Japan.
It all starts from Nihonbashi.
That's right.
The road to Japan starts at Nihonbashi, right?
Rainbow, Nihonbashi, Katsudoki
I don't think Karen would say Katsutoki Bridge.
And Matsumoto?
Matsumoto is a little old.
That's why Katsutoki Bridge is so important.
Big chance to get everyone together in Matsumoto's Team at Nihonbashi
Meanwhile, Hamada's team, which already has 3 players, has
The three of you have to watch out for the joker...
That's right, isn't it?
That's the special rule this time.
If you encounter a Joker Ebisu
Members are disbanded on the spot
Mr. Ebisu says Rainbow Bridge is K
right?
The most *pan* I could think of was the Rainbow Bridge.
Nihon-bashi bridge
So I personally would say Bay Bridge
Both are off, big chance for everyone except Tanaka.
I think this is it.
Matsumoto arrives at Nihonbashi
Takizawa is in trouble.
I wonder if we'll ever see her again, even if she's in Deluxe.
Takizawa is headed for the bridge...
Maybe I'm amazing.
Matsumoto is here.
Matsumoto
Yes, that's right.
It's the only place.
That's good.
Matsumoto-Takizawa splendid meeting
And Iseya too
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Slow, slow, slow.
What a surprise, the three of them meet up at Nihonbashi
As for Hamada's team
Hamada's team arrives at Rainbow Bridge
Will they meet up?
who who who
Isn't that Ryo-kun?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
As I called
Hamada's team is now joined by Kato
Well done!
Now both teams are split into two pairs
In other words, reaching for the whole group.
All everyone wants to know now is where Joker Ebisu is going.
They want to know where he went.
Let's see...
Wait, wait, wait.
eh
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You've got to be kidding me.
The joker is on the Rainbow Bridge.
eh
Yay!
Woohoo!
Sorry about that.
The four members of Hamada's team have been disbanded.
The next subject is a big park
Hamada's team is again aiming for the big park by themselves.
How about we get to know little bit more of each other
You're going to be the interviewer
that''s right.
You're trying it right now.
You don't get many opportunities like this, it's Matsumoto.
I don't have a lot of questions.
I'm a pretty much no "No Good" questions guy. So anything goes.
So how do you think you've lived your life so far?
That's No Good.
the only one
That's NG
They say there are only two.
Then where did you get your clothes?
That's not what I want, that's not what I want.
Actually, there's a scene that we couldn't show you here.
I'm sure Matsumoto's already been fulfilled.
I'm sure it's already been done.
Do you still have any big dreams?
I mean a dream that hasn't come true.
I can do it now
If there's something you want to do
Wow, what's that?
I'd like to hear that too.
I see.
Really.
Can I tell you the truth?
By all means.
I want a lot of comedians to come to my funeral when I die.
That would be great.
You want a comedian?
Yes, sir.
Comedians, or celebrities, or entertainers.
I don't know, I think it's a little bit
I think it's nice.
right?
And something like that from the top.
and then you look at it from the top and you say, "Oh, he's here, he's here...
You know, that's what I'm thinking about.
Then let's do that while we're still alive.
You'd get a bunch of people who just want to flatter you then.
And by doing that, they can get a little bit more respect from their daughter or something.
I didn't know my dad was so great.
I think that's all I can think about.
I see... that's great.
I asked for it in one go, and they said no.
Matsumoto's subject is Kakizawa's love talk
Karen is...
Yes
what kind of person?
I'm already in elementary school, or I'm not going to change, no matter what you think.
I love people who are fast on their feet.
Ah, you said something.
I'm a really fast person, really fast, really fast, really fast.
I'm sorry, who is the fastest person in the world right now?
Usan Bolt
Bolt
So you must like Bolt then
Absolutely not.
I was talking about a little bit of tea.
It's easy to be realistic
You're going to get a bolt out of your eye when you hear that.
If you ask someone out and they say no
Tell me what kind of person you like to be in love with
Tell me I'm an interesting person, and if I ask you out and you say no
I'm going to lose my temper too.
I'm telling the truth.
Only women, really.
After this, there's a rush to meet up with the others.
What will be the outcome of the game?
Hamada's team has disbanded...
Kato, Kawaguchi, and Hamada joined at Komatsubara Park
Yay
Matsumoto team still has 2 pairs
Hamada team is left with Taki and Tanaka all alone
The possibility of all the members coming together has increased.
The next big one is an amusement park
Tokyo Dome City
Korakuen
Korakuen Amusement Park, please.
The three of Matsumoto's team and the three of Hamada's team, Taki...
Select Tokyo Dome City
So that means
If Hosei and Endo comes, Matsumoto team wins
If Tanaka comes, Hamada's team wins
Tensions are running high, and these three want win the game.
Okay, Shinichi Mori, sing it for me.
I've never sung before.
What kind of songs are his?
is his?
I only know Kitajima songs.
You know a Kitajima song?
It's a festival, it's a festival
I see.
Festival, festival, festival, festival
Good, good, good, good
something like that
Yes, he's going to be pissed.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Yes, I'm angry.
Then finally it's settled
Gaki News
Super Tide Stop Paradise Opens July 22
Don't Laugh This Year, Dr. Science
We are waiting for you all with a crack of happiness and laughter!
Three of Hamada's team and three of Matsumoto's team at the Oda amusement park
And Taki goes to Tokyo Dome City
Taki
If Hosei and Endo comes Matsumoto's team wins.
If Tanaka comes, Hamada's team wins.
Please come.
That's enough.
And
Someone's coming. Here they come.
I'm on it.
Oh!
Yay!
Matsumoto team wins!
Tanaka is the only one left
Where did he go?
Where are you?
I'm at Hanayashiki.
It's a Hanayashiki after all.
Joker Ebisu joins Tanaka.
So, Hamada's team is punished for losing.
Leader Hamada pays for everyone's cab and lunch
The showdown is over.
I guess it's over.
Check something.
It's already done.
The game is
The game is over.
Thank you.
I didn't know he was dressed like that.