Tonight's kid's episode is
Nishikawa-kun, look!
That's right!
Takanori Nishikawa and Hiros Alis were the guests.
Meet-up special without cell phone
This way!
Who? Who? Who?
I think we started with Arca, so to speak.
It's different.
You're doing me, and you're taking the young lady?
No, no, no, no.
The unseen parts of the program, which were cut due to airtime limitations, are now on display.
I've seen all of the ones with those two.
I'm like, I'm obligated to do this.
I knew it, too, but it's not coming out right.
I think that's what they mean when they say "classy.
We've shared.
So much so that I'm thinking about making a purchase.
gental man
I was getting ragged on until then, too.
Each of us goes to the place we imagine with the theme presented to us.
This project will not end until all the participants meet up.
Guests Takanori Nishikawa and Hiros Alis
7 players try to clear the game
If you meet more, break up immediately
Io Matsumoto also joins as a joker
The first subject is
this way
Beta
eh
Wow.
That's a lot.
Get in the cab, 12:10 game starts
I'll say from here, how about a forward roll
Yeah.
I mean, I used to go there a lot, or I caught a cold or something.
I used to go to Ebisu's Welfare Central.
I went to a hospital that's used to the sun, like that.
I think that comes to mind.
I think it would be Sanyo Hospital.
Driving to the destination to meet up with everyone
I mean, people watching TV.
I think there are a lot of people out there who understand that Matsumoto is right.
In the end
Majority rules, so this is a game.
So you want to get together with smart people.
It's very weak in terms of members.
And so on.
The deviation is really low.
I think that's five of our members.
But I said
because it's Amasaki Technical High School.
It's mechanized, so you can say the deviation.
There is no 32nd place
Always sick, always in the legal car
What about that one? What was the disease?
Peyronie's.
That's an egregious neny, but
This is still
There are three of these whole vertical lines.
In the implicit form
All 3 vertical lines
But they're hardening.
It's a doubled face.
This is a strange disease, really.
One in 500,000 or something.
How's your chin these days? How's your chin?
Jaw is a funny thing.
After the recording of "Don't Laugh
Get well soon
Is there anything wrong with that?
Nothing is wrong
But since I heard there's going to be a recording of Don't Laugh
I think I'm going to be sick again.
Matsumoto aiming for Juntendo again
Have you come to the hospital?
Actually, I'm almost done with hospitals.
I haven't been there much.
I like hospitals, Mr. Hamada.
You like hospitals, don't you?
But you're going to miss work very, very soon.
It's just a slight fever.
You're very aware of it, but you're very weak.
It's just a little bit hard for me because I'm mentally weak.
He says he takes a day off work right away.
Well, I've never missed a day of work.
I've been doing this for 35, 6 years.
I really don't have it.
He said he took a day off because he was sick.
I wonder if there are two or three times
I've had to take a little bit of time off because I was sleepy.
Everyone has arrived at their destination
Simultaneous calls confirm where they are
No matter what you think, it's Juntendo.
What?
Juntendo?
Hirose is located at Tokyo University Hospital?
Where is that?
I'm sorry, Endo...
I wonder if you guys have been watching the news lately.
I'm just wondering...
It's Nihon University, Nihon University Hospital
Nihon University Hospital
if there is such a place
Maybe former director Uchida will come out.
No one could join him at the hospital
And the second subject
The first place you go when you come to Tokyo
This subject brings back many memories for the members.
First, Hamada's story about his first time in Tokyo
Did you ever come to Tokyo before that, other than for work?
No.
There it is, but it's in Kitasenju.
Kita-senju?
Because that's where I was in high school.
I stayed at his house in Kitasenju.
We're going to have dinner here.
I was wondering what they're going to make me eat when I go to Ginza.
I said, "Let's go eat pizza.
With my companion who went with me
What's a pizza?
I said, "What's a pizza?" and I ate it for the first time.
Tanaka has a memory about Shibuya.
When he was in Hitachi, Tokyo
I was working part-time at a store in Shibuya.
I see.
Yes.
What was your part-time job?
I work at a coffee shop.
I'm in a waiter.
There were a lot of young women there.
I have a little bit of arm hair, don't I?
I'm in with a waiter.
I got a complaint from a customer.
They sent me to the kitchen.
He said it's disgusting.
Alta clerk, he said I'm sick.
I thought it was tough, Tokyo
The treasure star that aims for Alta...
Memories of good times
Iitomo means "good friend" in Japanese.
That's not a degural.
I mean, guests have been out there many times.
The first time the telecon came out
When is it ever good for that client?
and then suddenly you say
when it's going around.
When is there a good live broadcast, when is there a good live broadcast, suddenly
And then it's like, "Zawazawa
Suddenly, tantantantantan
Say it
I had a lot of stuff ready for you, too, but far away.
really
So I had him go right to commercial.
You're the weird jonder because you're coming in.
that's what I was told by Mr. Muri.
And the kid, you know, he was forced to leave, and he was told by the guard
During the commercials
Worst.
That's where the kid was sitting.
There's a stuffed bear with a paw paw on it.
He's making it a little more interesting.
That's Tamuri's ad-libbing.
It's from an old show called "Parlour".
It's a live children's show.
When Midori Utsumi was doing it.
One of the kids yells "tic-toc-toc-toc!
And then that kid disappears during the commercials.
The stuffed bear is in the child's seat
He's putting it on the table.
That's the way it used to be.
Meanwhile, in Alice Hirose's car
On the topic of her hobby, manga
Matsumoto-san and me there
When I was first introduced to you
When I told him about the comic book, he was very surprised.
It's like he has a different fetish than I do.
All the things you like.
It makes you look like a pervert.
So in a way, from Hirose's point of view
Mr. Matsumoto dares to put on muscle.
He is a pervert.
It's right at the end of the year or the beginning of the year or the beginning of the year.
On the day of the year when it's the most important day of the year
Lifting muscles and so on.
You're kind of tweeting up.
That's right.
I think that's what it means.
I chose it with each memory.
The first place to go in Shangjing City
Hirose arrives at Shinjuku Shintani one step ahead
My memories of this place...
When I think it's good
Also, I knew it was a meeting place.
Yo, I met up with a girl... here.
How many teeth did you have?
I did.
Matsumoto-san is in the car.
Oh, I'm going to go now.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to say, Matsumoto-san?
Of course.
Downtown
We're going downtown.
In the middle of a young man's pickup story.
Hirose has something on his mind
If I say this is Alice Hirose-chan now...
and you're like "wow"?
No, I don't know.
I don't get it at all.
I'm telling you, it's not going to happen at all.
I think you're holding back there.
Is he holding back?
Don't be shy.
That's great.
People are surprised at their own lack of popularity
Oh, oh, oh
Sanaga Matsumoto joins the group, but
From a distance
The topic is still
There are no people at all.
Hey...
No, no, no. You're a regular guy.
There's nothing like a caw at all.
Not at all, it's a big deal.
When Matsumoto-san goes, everybody stops for a minute.
I'm sure I'm a celebrity, I'm sure I'm a celebrity, I'm sure I'm a celebrity.
If there were, there wouldn't be this much space.
No, it's not even close.
I can do a teleclub rendezvous or something.
at a certain place
everyone notices me, whether they notice me or not
I'm going to go right now, and I said, isn't this awful?
Saku is like this, no, Tokyo is like this.
Tokyo is all like this
That's what we're getting together.
It's really a big deal.
I'm really from over there
I'm not sure I'm going to be able to stay with the talent much longer.
How many times do I have to say it?
Here's more
Let's definitely go.
Meet-up special without the phone
Two couples have already met at the first place they go after removal
The next subject is a university
Hamada and Hirose's company talked about Hirose's private life
Do you drive a car or something?
No, I don't.
Generally, if you come here, if you come there, if you come there, if you come there, if you come there, if you come there
You know the way.
But isn't there a limited number of places you can go?
Yes, it is limited.
I don't travel far anymore.
Heh.
It's a pain in the ass.
That's right.
I don't know if it's too much trouble for someone so young.
Let's get out more there.
Just because it's a pain in the ass to go out to eat.
And they start cooking.
I see.
There's a place called Meiji University right in front of you.
What are you inviting me to?
You think it's Meiji University?
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. 266
00:12:52,000 --> 00:12:56,000
And Matsumoto and Hirose...
I never thought about going to college.
268 00:13:00,000 --> 00:13:02,000
Why?
Did you get a job at Part Time News?
Yes, yes, yes.
in high school?
high school
deviation 69
Bullshit.
But he said that's about what the doctor said.
I don't know.
You're a messed up teacher.
Oh, yeah, Nishikawa-kun and I are the two of us.
I was a little nervous.
You were?
I had a feeling that he was going to be there at the hospital.
I don't know what I'm going to do, I'm going to become the second most popular.
What's going on?
Alice, you're not in trouble, are you?
But if you go that far, on the other hand
but if you go that far, it's the other way around
You might think, "What the heck...
And they're not even close to the same age.
I don't know who you're talking about.
Like Mr. Shino.
I don't feel like it.
Are you Shino Ikenami?
If you are Shino Ikenami, or if you become the second most popular...
I don't know why.
That's true.
With whom did you meet the most Natsume?
With whom did you meet Natsume most?
Yes, that's right.
With whom is Ichiban Natsume?
Even in reverse
Switch somewhere else
We're going to have to go for it.
I've already got a backup plan.
is the only thing I can think about.
I don't know how to make this more interesting from a TV point of view.
that's the only way to do it.
At that time, in Takanori Nishikawa's car
That's it.
It's definitely those two.
I know you're not going to like it.
overseas or in a rural area or something.
I wish I could do it, but I don't know.
You don't want to stop.
This is really...
That's the lottery tanny.
of something like that.
And it comes with a Barakel.
even that
The one outside
I'd like to go there, me
I'd love to go.
I see you've been watching a lot.
You know what?
when
I don't know what you're going to say.
The one with those two guys.
I'm looking at the whole thing.
You're looking all the way through.
You're looking at each station
I already have this
It's like an obligation.
It's like a sense of
about the same as the book of wells
He's a solid junior.
That's right, yes.
The same tension as the book of wells.
Whenever, when did you talk about that?
and you say, "Oh, that's it?
and then it's always
No, no, no, no
I know you're frustrated.
Oh, my God.
In this subject
Six people peeking down a long way at the University of Tokyo.
A joyous confluence
This system is over and done with.
And then there's the big one.
There's only one place to go.
It's only the long way.
but
You're lying.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I waited too long.
Joker Matsumoto Yushurai
1 2 3 4 5
6 disbanded
back to square one
I told you, I'm today
I have an appointment at 3:00.
Don't tell me.
You said it, but
What's the deal?
You don't notice it at all.
Meet up without your phone
Special
Starting from Zero
The fourth subject is
Departments
Because, you know, when you think about it
And there's all seven of them.
Iochan only
He's going to a totally different place.
I thought that was pretty hard to do.
So I'm thinking
I'm sorry to say this on such short notice, but
I hope you can make the joker go the long way.
And then it all comes full circle.
That's the end of it.
Then it ended at the previous one.
Opening
Today's joker is a long way off.
If you take back the
I can't finish now.
The rest is nothing more than an edit.
LOL
Matsumoto Katajyo Tanaka is
Nihonbashi Mitsukoshi
Hamada and Hirose are in Shinjuku
Select Isetan
First to arrive at Mitsukoshi
Matsumoto
Ah, this is the place.
398 00:17:38,000 --> 00:17:40,000
KOKOKEIEN guy is already done.
399 00:17:44,000 --> 00:17:46,000
Hello
Good luck
Thank you
Thank you.
good luck!
I'm trying to do my best.
I'm doing my best.
LOL
I didn't notice that at all.
LOL.
I didn't notice that at all, now.
I didn't notice that at all.
It's here, isn't it?
This is the only place I can think of.
When you think of department stores, this is the place to be.
Because this is the first one in Japan
Yes, if you're thinking about history, this is definitely the place to be.
There you go.
Right here.
That's right.
I think that's what I think.
I think it's coming out wrong.
That's not the same thing.
It's classy, even if you do it that way.
I don't think we're all going to be here.
But there are some really classy
Some of my buddies
I just thought it would be nice to know.
You got it, didn't you?
I'm even thinking about making a purchase of a product.
gental man
LOL
Adult town
Stunning in Nihonbashi
Tricycle confluence
Matsumoto is now in a better mood...
by all means
By all means
I need your support.
I think they're getting the message, after all.
I think it's beautiful.
LOL
I can't stop praising myself
I mean, it's not like I'm burnt out.
Well, to be honest, it's more like the height of virtue.
as a person
As a human being.
Not as a scholar or a merchant.
I'm not talking about money or anything like that.
I have something.
I've got some valuables
And then, of course
And the overall program balance.
I think about it.
When I go to different places
As one location in Nihonbashi
something
in the producer's sense
There's a place where you're looking at it.
I'm thinking there's so many of them.
The director says, "You want this, don't you?
The people who are looking at it are still like that
They want to see a lot of different places.
You're being kind when you say that there.
That's pretty kind, too.
It means the masses are not tight with the goods
I'm not saying that at all.
I just can't help it
around that time
I chose Shinjuku Isetan
Alice Hirose is
Alice is
Thank goodness.
Good
Successfully joined Hamada again
The result at the department store
As you can see
The endo in Zeph town is
I didn't see anyone on this day
No, entertainment
They say that's the last sexual harassment.
That's the guy.
If he dies, he's really a sexual harasser in the entertainment industry.
It's going to disappear.
If he dies
What is sexual harassment in the entertainment industry?
It's going away
without the phone
Meeting Special
The fifth subject is
Driving range
Hamada loves golf
Together with Hirose
Aiming at Jingu Gaien
time is lost
I'm thick
Is it not that much?
Except for the Jingu and the fire
And that Meguro string shop.
Gaien is the most famous.
I'll tell you what.
yes, that's right.
It's more of a service issue.
It's a service problem.
Really.
Endo should already know everything I just said.
I know where he's going to choose for me.
It's just the West River.
I have to see Mr. Endo soon.
Yes, that's right.
really
That's crazy.
All the way to your handiwork.
All day long
I'm on location alone.
On the other hand, Matsumoto Hoyo Tanaka's
The three men are
That one is really
I think he wants to be alone with me.
I can't do it.
It's
it's not going to happen.
There's always a guy named Hamada.
and he's always trying to get in the way.
This is also where I used to be
The old
In the past
from long time ago
for a long time
So there's a distraction coming in.
That love story
Yes, yes, yes.
Insufficient
Can I ask you to raise the cooler a little more?
If I talk about Hamada, he's hot.
But
I think Alice is even more sickened.
Alice, you must be in the middle.
In the middle
00:22:36,000 --> 00:22:36,000 --> 00:22:36,000
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
00:22:38,000 --> 00:22:40,000 because Scalera is getting a little touchy.
Nope.
You know, the last sexual harassment in show business.
That's what they say about that guy.
If he dies, there will really be sexual harassment in the entertainment industry.
will cease to exist.
They say it's gone.
LOL
And at the Jingu Golf Course
Matsumoto and Yamachan and Tanaka and
Matsumoto, Yamachan and Tanaka
who who who who
splendid
All seven successfully joined
Joter Matsumoto Iyo was headed for
Iyo is now
Where is she?
I'm in the swing
I'm at the Himon-ya
at the gatehouse
all right
OK
everyone
All seven
I put it in the Jingu golf course
Got it!
now
I met Mr. Sangma by chance
I just met with Mr. Sangma
eh?
at the Himon-ya
Sangma-san is going there too.
What a face!
Why don't you go out to the Himon-ya and you'll see
It's a big deal, isn't it?
Why do you say that?
Even in Yahara
It got pretty tough.
OK totally!!!