The first Gaki no Tsukai Arahende Chiki Chiki - My gun is my Finger and Mouth:
Space War Without Weapons
It has become a regular occurrence
This is only the second time
I still want to do space war once in a while
We did it last time, didn't we?
Finger guns
I wasn't funny at all.
papa-papa-pan
Not even close
Oh, I'll get it this time
papa papa
I can see it.
They used their finger's as a guns in battle, commonly known as "finger waving".
Right on the mark
Today is the evolutionary space war version of finger waving
Have you seen the filming schedule, the space war starts at 9:00
That's pretty epic.
These people are idiots.
They're in the early grades of elementary school.
I don't know how I felt when I was tuxedoing.
I've been thinking about it a lot.
I'll know when I back up.
And then we call in the guests, the same members as the finger-snatchers.
There it is.
You know the gist of it, and you don't need me to explain it to you.
So we'll just take it from here.
We're good to go with the board.
I think there's a lot of projects that I'm anxious to see when these three are called.
What is this?
We get depressed when things don't go well, too.
That's how old I am.
I'm not that old.
I'll be depressed if it doesn't work out
I don't think you're getting called back for another one with the results.
I didn't leave any results.
I'm sorry first of all
I'm getting a message that I need to separate the members.
So in terms of the story, yes.
Different planet.
You're starting to sound crazy.
Warriors on separate planets threatened with extinction by a major catastrophe
The teams are from different planets
Implanted in the princess's body to prevent her destruction
The power of the potential stone
It's a potential stone.
The power of the Potential Stone to prevent the destruction of the planet.
Two teams battle for the princess
Battle for the princess
The princess is over there
Over there with potential stones
She's got it around her neck.
It's true, the one on the chest.
Potential stone
That, that red one
What is the potential stone, Princess?
She's closed-minded.
She especially hates rakugo
Why is that?
She hates classical arts and stuff.
What kind of princess is that?
The result is the same team formation as the Finger Master Trick.
The space war for the princess begins
Space war
The battle is a space war
Survive the attacks of the opponent
Start from their respective positions
Victory if the princess is brought back
They prepare for the start of the space war
Each team holds a strategy meeting
Hamada's team is up first
Checking members' equipment
I have that one.
I have a hologram.
I'm gonna be out by early, so I'm going to go all out at once.
You're going out in a flash?
It's not me selling anymore
I don't have that much.
That's good, but I'm not sure about the weapons stuff.
That's fine.
As far as weapons are concerned
I'm the son of an arms dealer.
We're coming prepared today.
If you need help with weapons, just let me know and I'll help you.
Fujiwara used to use a rifle from a distance.
He was aiming at you.
Again, laser rifle.
And all the nails grow back, so...
Far away
Let it all stretch
Pretty much everyone has it, so it's okay.
I'll get the potential stone from the princess.
I'm going to give her a fake potential stone and take the potential stone without her noticing.
I'm going to replace it with a fake potential stone.
to Honma's potential stone.
I'll bring it over here.
The fake potential stones are
I'm bringing three or four, so
No, I'm not that big of a fighter.
No, I didn't think it was that big of a fight.
No, I think I'm going to go with goo now.
Space war.
It's a space war.
Please say space goo.
Like Honma's goo is no good today.
Cosmo par or something like that
Cosmo par.
Cosmopar of physical condition
It's very strong
Cosmo par of physical condition
It's a bit of a stretch, but I have a lightsaber.
Do you have a lightsaber?
I can do this even if it comes with a pew.
If you are in trouble, you can do this
Cosmo par
Cosmo par can be taken out
This is the greatest
On the other hand, Matsumoto's team...
Check the members' equipment
I have a shield.
That's good.
But it's definitely not good.
That's mine.
I had a backache just putting the shield on.
That's about it.
So they're going to be robbed.
Potential stones are absolutely necessary.
That's why
Potential Stone says it's good for back pain.
good for back pain?
Put it right here.
Anything works.
Potential stones are for sleeping.
Inobuta, how do you feel about this?
I'm a little far away.
I'm going to take the missile out of this area.
I think I'll go one by one.
Yudo's one.
Hosei
I have a throwing ring.
A throwing ring
You know this is a space war?
Nagi (throwing) sounds like negi (onion)
I'm not asking for a snack.
I have a sickle.
And that's the last of it.
You know this is a space war?
A sickle...
I think beam rifles are
What kind of beam rifle is that?
a beam rifle...
With a rifle that beams
It's like a beam, but it's not a beam.
I'm different, and have a light saber
I'm going to go with the close combat.
That's important.
That's strong.
Electronic beam whip
I like that.
And then there's
I'm going to put a shield on it and then I'm going to go...
I'm going to burn them with my eyes.
Beams from you eyes?
The only salvation for everyone is from the shield
I'll get behind it.
What happens when you get hit up close?
I'm going to move back.
It has a sliding door?
Shielded sliding door
I open it up, and then shoot from the eyes.
Top of a cupboard
Like a top of a cupboard
Both armies ready
Finally
The space war begins
Are you ready?
What's the fighting area size?
It's about 3.5m, but...
3.5m?
I was about a first grader then.
I became intelligent and died.
What the hell is this leader?
I'm telling you.
He's saying something.
Are you sure you don't want to do a lot of positioning and stuff like that?
Is this a strategy?
That's not an operation.
That's a risky move, but it could be an operation.
Maybe it's an operation.
It isn't an operation.
It hasn't started yet.
I don't understand these people.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't get your story at all.
Wait, wait, wait.
I didn't say start.
It's too late.
slow
Don't you have to get into position or something?
You're all lumped up together
Get ready and we can start.
That's what I've been saying all along.
Why are you replying?
Why can't anybody hear me?
That's all right, isn't it?
They get back to position and get ready to start again
The space war begins
All right.
Let's get started.
Let's end this early
Let's go.
Space war
Start
Not coming at all
I don't know which one is coming for me.
It's not me.
That didn't really hit me.
What are you doing?
what are you doing?
You're not dying at all.
That's not fair.
If you get hit, you're done.
You guys already got shot when you came here.
They all died there
He's already dead here.
I didn't hear that.
I've got a shield on it.
He's got his body all cut up.
No, that's not me.
I'm just doing holograms.
You could feel us hitting you
That's a high-performance hologram
I'm so disappointed.
He's putting up a barrier.
How can they come in with a barrier?
When I sit down, I'm the only one doing this.
That's for 1.5 squares.
That's not right at all.
It's like a hot carpet.
It's warm even if it's off a little bit.
If it's warm, it's dead.
The leader's face says about 4 squares.
If you get sick, you're conscious
he will not die
I'm telling you it's a space war.
so what's with the buddha beads
That's good.
We're relying on the God of the universe.
It cools down.
Please take it off, it's a space war.
All of them.
It gives me: Cosmo slap
Cosmo slap
Cosmo slap is weak.
It's not funny.
Once we get back to our respective positions
They go back to regroup
Koumoto's holograms are...
How do you do it?
Koumot itself.
Completely on its own
In front of
We've got to catch him.
I'll do it this way.
That could be a hologram.
Close it with a gulp.
I'm like, "Are you for real?
You better destroy it properly.
What does the Stone look like?
Let me check, shall I?
I'm just confirming, but you can take the stones.
You can't do this with every princess, can you?
The truth is, it's the whole princess.
The best way to do it is to bring her to you.
The princess
I'd like to fight around here if I could.
From over there
coming around the back
They're coming for the flag, and it's getting weird.
No, they're not fair.
If they say I'm not dead, I'm not dead.
Potential stones were originally called
because it belongs to the planet of Uchi
I see
It's running there.
I don't know if it's a fake.
the buddha beads
With fake potential stones
I'm making a cross.
It's not the six.
Pull the cross.
If you've done a baro-baro
Hey
I think I'm really going away.
It's really going to be the wood of the universe.
It really becomes a space mozuku
What's a mozuku?
Both armies
Start a space war
All right.
It's filthy in there.
there you go
Come on.
Here we go.
Space war
Start
That's not really me.
It's not really me.
Wait!
Stop!
What is it?
You've got a rag on you.
You meditate and open your eyes at the end
You put it out at the end?
Last one out
That was all done.
First of all, Koumot completely disappeared
He didn't participate.
Where did you go?
Where did he go?
He ran away.
What?
hologram
The real one is here.
What's wrong?
This is in shambles.
What?
You've been getting hit all along.
I've been working on the hologram all day.
Your boot is evidence.
What?
You know what I'm talking about.
He's really losing it.
You really need to stop using tires that look like Zakkies.
Tire tire like Zakk, stop it.
You'll do it.
But I think the princess already knows that.
It's called our value.
This way.
Princess, this way.
Look who's winning.
Can you look towards the winning team?
Everybody stop fighting.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're way too late
Oh, no.
We fought a lot.
Tell us that first.
This'll never be finished
I've got to get hit a little bit.
It's going to end up being our value.
Not at all.
I'll show you how many times
Come here, come here.
Insert block
what is that?
What the heck is that?
It's the same as the results.
What happened?
Result
He didn't say it like it was a special move.
Insert block
A long time ago
In a galaxy far, far away
Over and over a thousand years of war
For atmospheric qualifying
on the verge of extinction
There were two planets
One was
Kenne
Planet Machomkin's
Matsumoto's Army
The other is
Planet Mesgoly's
Hamada's army
The only way to prevent destruction
The princess has a neutral position
With the power of the potential stone
Purifying atmospheric qualifying
Right now
The fate of the planet is at stake
The final battle
is about to begin
Start!
There is nothing that can't be cut
by my beam saber
I'm gonna give it back to you just like that.
Now!
Go!
Take that!
Beam sword!
Stop motion!
Can't move
You're stuck for 10 seconds
What?
Go!
to the end!
Take this! Beam bazooka!
I've got you cornered!
Damn!
Okay! This is the only way!
The art of the alter ego!
Now there's four!
You don't know who's the real deal.
Die!
Beam!
Princess!
Come to our space side
That's it!
Beam saber!
Combustion power!
Stop!
Tough son of a bitch.
Lastly, Matsumoto and Hamada duke it out for the leader.
Who will get the Potential Stone?
This will decide the fate of each other's planet!
It's your planet that pollutes the water!
Damn! Here it comes.
This is just how it was meant to be!
Let's go, Princess!
Wait a minute! Before you go!
I hope you live long enough to see our planet perish.
What's wrong with you?
I can't do it anymore!
Hamada...
Let's go! We're going with you!
No, no, no! Ow, ow, ow, ow!
You can come with me!
Why don't you just go!
Come on, let's go!
Princess, let's go!
Great! Thank you!
Lend me your pajamas!
Pajamas!
hahahahaha
You don't know who's the real deal.
HOSEI!
And that's before we know who's the real one.
Surprise!
Think I'm pissed off.
Radiant!
You don't get mad at radiation.
I'm still surprised at the 50th place thing.
Hamada!
Stop!