Gaki no Tsukai Yarahende Special: Meet-up Special without Smartphones
You're such a nuisance to the neighbors.
I know you want to show off because you're so loud, but you've got such a voice.
You can't do that.
The rules are simple: You go to the place you imagine based on the theme presented to you.
If one person joins the others, they work together after that. If all the participants can gather at the same place, the game is completed.
I've got to end this day quickly, or else I'll be in the wrong place all the time.
I'm sure it happens, but if I end up alone, it's not a coincidence.
It's not our fault.
When people watch TV, they always say "everything Matsumoto says is always right."
No, he is terrible
If it was about this, I'd be here, because he's the biggest  idiot at Yoshimoto.
Biggest idiot in a hundred years of history.
Sei was lamenting
This time it's not a team game, but a special with 2 extra guests
Seven people will work together.
Special guests, come here.
hmm
Yes, first of all, Arisu Hirose.
I'm not sure where the resistance is centered, but I'm sure Bravo has a Board of Directors.
That can't be Maya Ш importance Chigar
You can't go up in the Natsuda Mountains ñ you have to pick a car, Min-kun.
I'm going to go up to Mt.
huh?
10 seconds.
Of course you know this project.
I can't tell you if it fits or not.
I mean, it's been 20 years since I moved to Tokyo.
20 years
Next year is already that R1 last year
R1?
But what about R2?
I don't know in what way.
I'm sending it to you?
And if this person meets them...
They have to split up
And start over
The joker of horrors.
Who is that person?
This is the person
Wow.
Oh, no, no, no, no
Suddenly he hit me.
She suddently hit me
She gets involved with me
Iyo Matsumoto
A little bit unpredictable, Iyo.
Even Iyo is long, of course, Tokyo
Yes, I've been watching a lot.
I always get it right.
What do you say?
That's great.
The first subject that determines your destiny
The first subject is here
Beta
eh
Wow.
That's basically big, right?
No, it's so-so, so-so.
Big or not good
Bigger is not better
Because you also have to think about Iyo.
Yeah, I think I've got the general idea.
The first subject is
Big hospital
Start at 12:10
Like a darts trip
You're lucky you're not on location.
If they send me over there
There's nothing rock 'n' roll about that.
Wow, that's a hard one.
A big hospital.
No, but if you think about it, there's a lot of them.
If you think about it too much
That's a lot of stuff.
I've been to a lot of big hospitals.
I went to the hospital right after Mori Mantaiket.
I've never been to the hospital right after a Gaki recording.
because there was quite a bit of it.
I don't go to the hospital at all.
Basically
It's like if you sleep, you'll get better.
I don't know at all.
Where are you going?
There are a lot of sticky places.
If you go there
Iyo is there?
between these two
Hosei sang a song about me, didn't he?
I'm a lip-synchronized player
Mouth-breather? What's that?
Mouth cracking?
No, it was scary.
Matsumoto shows a strange confidence.
But it's still like this
From here, let's say
Juntendo, right?
Yeah.
It's in Ochanomizu.
Go to Juntendoin
I'm going to Juntendo.
But I'm the last one, too.
I'm thinking of Juntendo.
I'm thinking of a kid who used to come here on location.
I think he's going to die.
Further legalization
Already me
I'm just going to float away.
That's what came to mind.
First of all, the hospitals I've ever been to.
Bonbon
But true
Bourne is coming...
I've never been there.
So it's not my feelings.
I can be objective about it.
where is it?
Keio University
Keio
There is no other choice but Keio
And Hamada
It's a pretty good old time
Catching a cold or something.
If you have a little trouble
Ebisu
We were going stellar central.
Drama image
You know, down there.
I don't know why they let me use it like that.
Hamada's turn for the drama location
To Hengxing Central Hospital
Guest Nishikawa is
Where to choose?
I mean, the entertainment industry.
I'd say you're in this kind of business.
It looks like security.
And that's the rest of it.
I'd like to know what kind of hospital you're used to for temperatures.
I think that's what comes to mind.
Then I think of Sanno Hospital.
Sanno Hospital?
Yes
Many famous people go there.
Akasaka Sanno Hospital
I don't think Tanaka can do it.
I don't think Tanaka is going to make it.
I'm always a little bit with you guys.
You're way off.
I've said it many times.
And the garbage man.
And that Tanaka
Toho
Toho Hospital, right?
Where is it?
Ikejiri
Ohashi Hospital
The Ki Nuta's
The growing hospital.
It's in Fukutoshi, Shinjuku.
It is outside Tokyo
The rendezvous on Shame Tanaka is
Chose these 3 hospitals
These three though
I think you all know that.
And the actress says that the disease can be cured by sleeping.
Alice Hirose is
University-affiliated
I think the hospital is bigger
something like that
It's called a hospital attached to a medical school.
Oh, that's it.
Is that it?
Is it safe to decide like that?
Yes, that's fine.
Let's go.
I'll apologize later and we'll figure something out.
As you can see, the destination is
The key to the confluence is
Endo Hirose's destination
as a matter of fact
The direction is one step ahead
Arrive at Shinano-machi Keio Hospital
There is this one.
I have this now
I don't have any, but
Well, well, well
Then there is
And there it is?
School is over
What?
Yay
What was the name?
You don't know your name?
Excuse me.
Reminder.
that's right
Name Name
name no more
Go check it out.
What's his name?
Stop it, you're embarrassing me.
At the same time, Nishikawa is
Yes.
I'm sorry, thank you very much.
celebrity at your service
Arrival at Akasaka Saburo Hospital
First of all, proximity.
Because it's already so close.
Because Hamahara-san wants to roll it up.
You don't think I'm going to roll it.
You definitely don't have enough.
Deluxe is already on the scale
It's just barely full.
Hamada is in Meguro
Arrive at Kosei Chuo Hospital
Here we are!
You'll see it in the drama.
I'm out of here already.
I don't know how many times I've said scene.
I'm here for the drama.
You use it.
Sekidai, right?
Kosei Chuo
And the other members
Arriving at destination one after another
First shot ever
I've never met anyone before.
I hope there's somebody there.
235 00:09:54,160 --> 00:09:56,160
And
Time is up!
Yea...
Time up here
Oh, Mr. Room, where did you go?
Simultaneous call to confirm whereabouts
you know what?
You guys think about it.
You started from Kojimachi, right?
That's a big hospital.
And the distance
Let's think about it.
It's Juntendo, no matter how you look at it.
What?
Juntendo
Juntendo Hospital?
Hirose is at Tokyo University
Hospital attached to the Faculty of Medicine
Where is that?
University of Tokyo
I'm at the hospital attached to the Faculty of Medicine
What's that?
What is that?
That's Endo.
Have you been listening to the news lately?
I wonder if you've been watching the news.
I'm a little bit curious.
It's Nihon University, Nihon University Hospital
Nihon University Hospital
If you're in a place like that
I don't know, maybe former director Uchida will come out.
Oh, where's Tanaka?
I am.
in Shinjuku subcenter
Tokyo Medical University.
Tokyo Med Univ.
Tokyo Medical University messed up
You should go home
Tokyo Medical University is a mess
Famous
That means Iyo-chan isn't here either.
Iyo-chan
Iyo-chan can do it too
Joker Matsumoto Iyo is on his way
The hospital is
Oh, what?
Ha-ha-ha
Ah-ha-ha
Sorry to keep you waiting
Iyo-chan is here.
This doesn't make any sense.
Ha-ha-ha
The first subject
No one could join us at the hospital
Nobody could meet up with us.
Ha-ha-ha
I'll see you soon.
Since all of you were not able to get together
I don't blame you.
I didn't get blamed for anything.
Yes, sir.
I was told, "Where is that?
I changed my mind.
Continuing the challenge
Subject
Coming to Tokyo
First time going to a place
What is this vague feeling of this
This is the stuff of a generation
isn't it?
This is a crazy lot.
The choices are
I think I fit.
I think it fits here.
I'm going to go to Tokyo, and I'm going to go to Besan, and I'm going to go there.
Tokyo Tower, for example.
Yes, sir.
It could be the Sky Tree now.
It could be Asakusa.
By the way, how about Mr. Hamao?
I'm going to go to
Well, I'm sorry
Alta Kanat
Ha-ha-ha
I'm not doing the good part anymore.
And Matsumoto?
Shinjuku, right?
It's still like this
orthodox
Furthermore, the
Where in Shinjuku, if you ask me...
We still say
I think it's Altamae.
It's a little bit old.
It's called Altamae.
But you know what?
I'm just saying, we
I don't think we have it.
on this subject.
If no one takes Shinjuku Altamae
That's the end of the Japanese entertainment industry.
Ha-ha-ha
This is hard to do.
It depends on who you are.
After all the trouble
Hamada chose
Then let's choose Tokyo Tower.
I want to get out of here.
Shinjuku?
Somebody's gonna come.
Tokyo Tower
Hamada is no way
Tokyo Tower is selected
Downtown at Altamae
Failed to meet up
The other members
Destination?
This is a real service problem.
in our generation.
People are only here now.
Tokyo Tower
What about Hamada?
I'm sure it's true.
I am now
If I had come to Tokyo
I thought it would be like Shibuya.
I thought
I thought, "I'm going to meet everybody.
Shibuya
Tokyo Tower
If you go to the natural flow
Shall we go
Shibuya?
Shibuya is
Is there a place you've always wanted to come to?
Tokyo Tower and
Shibuya Harajuku
I knew it... 109
I would have liked to have seen
But there
I don't think you all will ever come
By the way
Is the driver from Tokyo?
Tokyo, Japan
There is a City
But in the countryside
I don't mean in the countryside, but in Itabashi Ward.
I'm not in the country, I'm in Itabashi Ward.
Rural is dead, like a raccoon or something.
on the road
There's often a dead raccoon or something that's been pulled over by a car.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Where are you talking about?
I'm talking about my hometown.
Beware of bears...
There are often signs like that.
Bena
later.
Harajuku, Mt. Fuji Road
Takeshita Street
because our
I remember now
My little boy
Where do you want to go when you come to Tokyo?
He said Takeshita-dori.
Nishikawa is based on Oikko's opinion
Harajuku Takeshita-dori is selected
From memorable places to classic sightseeing spots
Each of us has his or her own thoughts and feelings
Will they join forces?
Matsumoto is Shinjuku
Shinjuku, moving to Shinden-mae
Generation
We laughed and we laughed
We're laughing at you.
at the time of
I've never been here before.
by that tree in Shinden.
I stayed at a place called Star Hotel.
I stayed there for a week.
I didn't even get a week's worth of sleep.
I'm staying over and trying to come up with a story.
I was out somewhere with Hamada's guy.
at the Star Hotel
Get something like a cup of fried noodles.
I forgot to bring my chopsticks.
You ate it on a skewer.
Nishikawa heading for Takeshita-dori, Harajuku
I remember when I was in a band
You don't have any money.
You don't have the money to pay for your own clothes?
You have to prepare it.
You're going to grab one piece at a time.
Head to toe
That's what it looks like, so go to Takeshita-dori.
And so on and so forth.
When you think about it
The first time you go to a new place, it's like...
I don't know, I just feel like I'm in the middle of nowhere.
Like a hands hat, too.
You bought it there?
I don't know why
That's a very fine stylist.
He's making it.
Well, well, well, design it well.
I did that.
We just edit our V and use it.
It's funny, but
I've heard of this happening.
I'm going to use seven V's.
You know how long I've got?
That's such a funny thing to say.
Nishikawa's car is
To Shibuya scramble crossing
Then there
Ha!
Where is it?
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here
Where beside the green train
See where you are
Hey, hey, hey.
What a sight of Tanaka!
ah, there he is, there he is
Aita ita ita
Tanaka Iru
I've got him.
at that time
Tanaka is
Gyp is here.
Oh, there it is.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
With Zip's location team
They had run into each other
what kind of location?
It's like the end of the world
Really?
something
TV is running
Tanaka bye-bye
me
I don't want to go there.
Nishikawa & Tanaka
Near miss at Dori-con
At that time in Alice Hirose's car
Downtown is the topic of conversation.
Who's Mr. Downtown?
Why are you two together?
Why do you wear your sunglasses backwards?
On the back of the head
Yes
Yes, indeed.
I laughed just now because I thought we were the same.
You looked for two people in a car?
You searched for a two-person car?
Yes, that's right.
I just thought it was kind of cute.
Hamada: Arriving at Tokyo Tower
Someone come
Please.
I need a shot here.
No, no, no, no.
with a wish for confluence
5 minutes of waiting
Come here, come here, come here
Come here, come here.
No, no, no.
Come on.
I'm sure you'll get at least a portrait.
Tokyo Tower, it's a solid portrait.
Mr. Hamada
ah
Good, good, good.
that's right.
Good.
Hamada and Hirose
at Tokyo Tower
at the confluence of the first
At that time, Matsumoto was
Arrive at Shinjuku Shinden
Something like a crowd at all
Since there is no
please.
If there's someone waiting for it.
That's a very popular one.
Yeah.
a father and a daughter
from Tokyo to Hirose
Going up from Hamada
in the press about those stories.
Yeah.
Ha-ha-ha
No, thank God.
if you look at it from a distance
I thought to myself, "There's no way anyone is a star here.
I thought
I didn't get a lot of people at all.
There he is, the talent.
This is how people get together
There is no such thing as a group of people
No, I'm surprised too.
I don't give a damn.
I'm really from over there
There he is, the talent.
How many times do you have to say it?
Do you remember?
I was saying, which one of you is Downtown?
They're definitely coming.
Downtown used this place for the kids.
Yes, yes, he used it.
After all, Alta is us
for comedians, for our generation.
It's a place of memories.
Aside from the unpopularity of thick
They meet up in front of Alta.
This is Tsukite Hosei
You don't know what to do when you say that.
Gakutei Hosei Kun
Hello
Time up here
Hirose.
Hirose, where are you?
I'm at Tokyo Tower with Hamada
Hamada
Tokyo Tower with Hamada
With name pattern
That's weird.
Where are you, Mr. Matsumoto?
I'm in
I'm going to say it as a matter of course.
In front of Shinjuku Alta
Alta-mae Alta-mae
Older
What's going on with Koboriko?
What about Endo?
You've come to Sky Tree, not Tokyo Tower.
Here we go.
That's too new for me.
Tanaka is
I, Tanaka, am at the scramble crossing in Shibuya.
What a fool!
I don't know, Tanaka.
I don't know, right?
Tanaka really should go home.
Where is the scramble intersection?
I'm not cut out for this, so go home.
Go home, please.
Please go home and stop.
No, Hamada, you're a lonely guy.
What's the matter with you?
We started at Alta, so to speak.
No, no, no, I thought that too.
And you're doing that to me, and you're taking the young lady.
No, no, no, no, no.
At the first place they go to after coming to Tokyo, two pairs successfully meet up with each other
And the joker
who who who
Ladies and gentlemen, this is Nishikawa.
Who's there, who's there, who's there
Go to Harajuku Takeshita-dori where Nishikawa is
Waiting
wait
Again, zero TV-like excitement.
Joker showing up in one place
Here is the current position 2 hours and 30 minutes after the start
The third challenge for the mass meeting is
Oh no, this is it.
There's a lot of it.
Yes, sir.
I've been through a lot, I've been through a lot today.
Rough again
This is already floating around a lot, of course.
It's just a matter of where to choose
blue amount
The university in Tokyo
From more than 150 universities, the members choose
Waseda Keio Rikkyo Nihon University Juntendo University
So only Tokyo Six Universities are showing up.
Yes, sir.
Say or blue amount
A year ago, I think it would have been blue amount Tokyo University Keio
Nichi-Dai is not included
Not included
But it's already still Nichidai
Now it's this
If TVK did it, it would be a five-hour special.
How about TVK
TVK 279 00:25:02,900 --> 00:25:05,900
While the names of famous universities that everyone knows are being raised
Hamada and Hirose pair is
Keio University of Tokyo, Waseda, Ao forehead
I have never been to any of them
I sometimes pass in front of the blue amount.
Same as above
Surprisingly, the blue amount is along 246
If you are traveling by car, you may have a strong impression of it.
You don't talk like that.
Yuta Todai was the first one.
Do it!
The younger person's opinion may be more likely to be that of Keio University of Tokyo
What do you do now? What if it doesn't work?
That's a round trip Ginta.
Young Hirose trusts his senses and aims for Tokyo University
The only thing that crosses Nouri's mind is
Land Yochanan is coming
He's definitely coming.
I'm not off by a long shot, Yochanan.
Musashi-dori is totally there too
You should go home
The rate of meeting up is 100%.
Joker Matsumoto's presence
Komatsubara University, Keio University of Tokyo
That's close to the blue amount.
University blue amount that I have been longing for
when you go home
I think he's got an ass. I don't know.
I heard it's OK all day today.
Damn.
Seven players go through the joker
Can they meet?
Waiting list special without a phone
Two groups have now joined
Aiming to get everyone together at the third subject university
The Taimado/Hirose pair arrives at their destination, the University of Tokyo
Sorry
I'm a little nervous.
This is the University of Tokyo where Alice went.
Please don't do this to me.
With a young sensation
Who?
I knew it.
I knew it
That's right.
That's good.
Good, good, good.
He might have found us, too.
You should come running when we're waiting for you over there.
Thank you very much.
Anyway, we meet up with the Nishikawa-Hamada-Hirose pair
If they go to Tokyo Tower
I think they will probably come here.
Did you get what you were aiming for?
Of course I did, sir.
The three of them head directly to the front of the University of Tokyo's Red Gate
Please don't let only Iyo-chan come now.
I really can't come any more
Oh!
OLA-OLA-OLA
See? See?
Oh!
Who's there?
Alice's?
Alice and ?
With Mr. Nishikawa's ?
Oh!
Right.
That's all I got.
That's all there is.
If you don't come here, it's over.
It's over.
Oh, thank goodness.
Oh, great.
That's good.
Oh!
Successfully joined with Matsumoto Hirose
Now 5 people gathered at Todai
That's good.
Good.
No, we'd be finished without it.
I'm already saying, "Japan is going to die.
Only two problem children left, Koboriko and
Will they all meet up at the University of Tokyo?
The above information is provided by the sponsors you see here.
That's right.
That's all I got.
That's all there is.
If we don't come here, we're done.
Meet-up special without a phone
The third subject is college
Five have already joined at Tokyo University
here's the key
That's it.
Only two small moat children are left.
as a result
Wait a minute... but you have to say it.
Two more.
That's the usual two.
What's going on with Koboriko?
No, really.
Why are these guys such foot ball chasers?
What kind of ideas do they have to live with?
What happened to the story?
Well, their stuff is not funny at all.
Don't do it.
That's it.
Jump!
go!
Yes, that's right.
University of Tokyo, right?
It's the only place, isn't it?
the only place to go is here
Endo only.
But it's coming from Sky Tree, so it takes a little bit longer.
It takes a little bit of time.
Well, if you think about it calmly, this is the only place.
It's the only place.
Here it is.
No, really.
I'm sorry, Tanaka.
I'm just in the car and I'm saying a lot of stuff about how I don't think of Koboriko's stuff at all.
I'm sorry.
I apologize for that.
Excuse me.
Time's up.
Time up
End
eh, right?
Time up
END
Yes
Where are you?
We are in front of Nihon University Nichi-Dai
Wow, it's Nihon University.
How much do you like Nihon University?
Everyone is here except you.
Oh, my God.
It's not "what".
Everybody but me.
What kind of person is that?
Oh, my God.
There's Tanaka, too.
Tanaka is here.
Tanaka.
Tanaka's way of saying
I don't like the way Tanaka says it.
There's even Tanaka who went to the Hanayashiki.
I'm here too.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you.
Yes, sir.
No, I'm not.
What?
No way.
Sorry again.
No, wait.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm waiting.
Sorry. 450
00:31:30,900 --> 00:31:31,900
You're lying.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
One, two, three, four, five.
Oh, there's one missing.
You're lying.
I
I'm really screaming.
I'm sorry I'm a little late.
Oh, no.
No, it's a scream, it's a scream, it's a scream.
Women, please.
It's like that one, the red crest.
Yes, yes, yes.
I've never seen that before.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
It's got to be a time like this.
Yes, it does.
Yeah.
Joker attack
Six disbanded
Back to the start of hell
It's falling apart again.
Ew.
This is the worst.
But still, Mr. Endo...
Only Endo
No, not anymore
I'm going to cry, I don't know what to do
I told you, didn't I?
I said today
It's going to fall apart.
He has an appointment at 3:00.
Don't let him in.
I've got 6:00.
Don't leave me in there.
I know I said that, but
Promise
Starting from zero
The fourth subject is
This way, please.
Departments
Difficult
Department store is
This is
If you go by inspiration, it's already
Mitsukoshi
Mitsukoshi in Ginza
Just today, this channel of mine...
I haven't met everybody.
I start moving, but
Can't shake the shock of the breakup
This breakup hurts.
Come here.
Just a little bit.
This breakup is hard.
Oh, no.
I didn't know this was possible.
This is way over here.
Let's end this while it's still light.
No, I can't finish this, I'll never finish this.
Iyo-chan can't get hit by a motorcycle.
It's not over until they all meet up.
This project
without being able to get back into it.
Decide your destination
Shinjuku
There is also Isetan
Shibuya
Seibu or
There's a lot of Ginza, too.
I have only one.
I can already think of one.
Just one more
please say it plainly
Isetan in Shinjuku
One or two maybe
I have a feeling we're going to meet up.
I know you're going to do it.
Mitsukoshi
Nihonbashi
I think it comes in old
Yeah.
Mitsukoshi
Many choices went up
This subject
The direction is Nihonbashi Mitsukoshi
Hirose chooses Shinjuku Isetan
Matsuda-san and his thoughts are always not that far away
It's not that far away.
That's true... every time.
It's a good fit, isn't it?
And I think they look alike.
Which do you think is similar to
My wife says he has the same eyes as Matsumoto-san.
His face...
The face ball
The face value is the same.
He said they're sharp.
At that time, Hirose was
Somebody go ahead of me, please.
I don't mind if you wait.
If you'd waited for me, I'd have already
Oh, my God.
I can't get enough of it!
Arrive at Isetan Shinjuku
Oh no!
Good.
Good
This is the place.
I guess it fits here.
It fits.
Good.
That's it.
That was fast!
Time up
Shozo Endo
Where is Endo?
I am
I'm in front of Mitsukoshi department store in Ginza
There it is, there it is
That's shallow.
Why not?
Tanaka is
I am
Nihonbashi Mitsukoshi
This is the main store
Tanaka and Matsumoto are with us
Motoi is with them
Yes, sir.
We, the distinguished guests, three human beings, are gathered here.
That's what I mean.
Nishikawa is
Nihonbashi Takashimaya
Even here it's just that, really...
Because the building is registered as a heritage site.
Well, that kind of information is
How about that kind of reason
It's getting kind of gritty.
Joker Matsumoto Iyo is
Shibuya Tokyu
4 hours and 20 minutes from start
The key to joining all the participants is
The lone Nishikawa and
I didn't see anyone on this day
Honkoku Endo
No, but the person who is in pin right now
You have to think about it.
I can't see anybody.
Ping Ping, think about it for a minute.
It's time to decide on the fifth
The subject is
Wow, that's weak.
I have no idea.
This sucks, all three of you.
You don't play golf, you don't play golf.
Hamada loves golf.
I thought of that right away.
It's an appearance.
Appearance.
Zing ballpark
Yes
With overwhelming confidence
Select Zing Golf Course
Where Mr. Hamada goes
You should think about it.
That's all there is to it.
Hamada is where I go in Hamada
I think I'll avoid it.
I think I'll avoid it in the future
And then we'll be done with it.
Tell him I'm going to be here a lot.
If they do it on TV, he's not going to be able to do it anymore.
He can't go to the driving range with his mistress.
That's right, I can't go to the driving range with my mistress.
You're going with your mistress?
He's with his mistress.
In the case of a mistress...
And that's what you're going to be able to do now, because you're going to be able to
I'm not going to go where he's going to Hamada.
Sonodo is often
The fire
I heard there's a place where they're going to hit the ground
I can't believe there's a fire.
If you go to a fire
It's the end of the world.
I'll just take a cab and go to Tereja.
LOL!
The name came up
Jingu Gaien
Only 2 places of fire
Big chance for all to meet up
Hamada-Hirose pair heading for Jingu
Me Iyochan is
I think I'm going to go to the string shop.
This time
Like I've been here before with my dad.
If you say that and you come to Gaien
That kinda sucks.
Then, Alice, you're going to have to send me a big boat.
LOL!
Mr. Matsumoto and
What do Mr. Fusei and Mr. Tanaka think?
I think it depends on you, Yamachan.
I've been there once.
At the outer garden
To the tennis court
Last February
The direction is
at the big table called tennis field.
Meet at Jingu Gaien
At that time
the adjacent golf course.
You should be seeing
It's right there.
I don't know if you're going to say that or not.
around that time
Matsumoto, Fusei, and Tanaka were
Matsumoto
With Alice
The fact that Hamada-san fits so well with
What kind of view did you take?
from the past
He's got it.
Scalpel.
It's more like attracting
The females don't like it.
We're not trying to attract them.
Then you're chasing your ass.
He's chasing the female's ass.
I've had it for a long time.
I guess it's a special skill.
Hmmm
like a superhuman cipher.
something like this
always like this
Not always the other chakra, but
young woman.
I mean, it's always illuminating.
with Hamada's bad words.
Enge Takenaga
Alice-chan is in danger
No, I'm a manager, I'm a manager, I'm a manager, I'm a manager.
I'm so sick of it.
what the hell is that?
He's doing something.
Behind the scenes
Like
because it doesn't
Why does Hamada keep coming back?
Hmm?
Me and Hamada
We have totally different hair styles.
Hamada and Hirose are
1 s ahead of the others to Jingu golf course
Are you okay?
Oh no, here it comes.
I may have to wait a little bit.
I think it's five minutes, ten minutes.
I see.
Ginza Nihonbashi to
If it comes
What the hell is that "if it comes"?
That's a lot of words.
That's right.
It's coming.
Already 4.5 hours since the start
Seven people gathered
Iyo-chan is not coming to the situation.
I just can't imagine it.
But it's not good.
It's not so good.
If this doesn't work
I'll stop being a kid and a comedian.
You're not...
you
I'm going to stop.
I'm not going to do it.
crafting
Each thought
Fulfillment
at Jingu golf course
Waiting for friends to arrive
Hamada and Hirose
Aita
there you go, there you go
Yay!
This is the only place I could figure it out.
around here.
I also do some running.
I knew there was a place for it here, so
That's good.
The end never came.
Now you're talking about a fire.
If you go
I don't think so.
No, he's a go-getter.
There you go.
Nishikawa is safe
They meet up with each other
Already from the first time zone
If we can't get together or something...
No, I don't want to do that anymore.
I can't take it anymore.
I wish a few more people would come.
I can't keep them coming.
Where are you?
Not at all
There is no sign of anything coming at all
I'm already starting to get crab bites.
No way.
You're gonna get bit by bugs.
I think they're already there.
And this season
5 o'clock.
I'm not going home
If it were YUJIRO, I'd be going home.
Oh...
No? Oh...
You didn't walk in?
Matsumoto, Yamachan and Tanaka and
Wow!
This way
who who who
Endo is
No endo
No, but it's okay.
Four minutes, you knew.
You know that the lawmakers are
Hosei was able to get it out here
When I came to some tennis court before
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
perfect
Only one endo left
Endo
Tanaka's partner for a moment
No, today's the day.
Endo is hard to see.
What clothes did you wear today, Endo?
I have shopping
You haven't bought anything.
I think I paid a penny or two for that guy.
I don't remember much
I don't remember much...
will he show up?
I've been waiting a long time.
Oh, you're the instructor.
Oh, you're an instructor.
A
Good
That's seven.
All of them are on the Jingu golf course
Success
The joker is
If he's somewhere else
It will be clear.
I can't do it.
Bottom
Hello?
It's Iyo, the joker, isn't it?
Yes, it's Iyo-chan, the Joker's Iyo-chan.
Iyo-chan is
Where are you now?
a shop that offers a wide range of products and services
I'm in the swing
I'm in a hikimon-ya
Good
Everybody, all seven of them.
I can put them in the Jingu golf course.
OK
good, good, good
Good, good, good
Mostly Hiromi
and
that's right.
Swing Himonya's
I have a card.
I just happened to meet Mr. Sangma.
Oh, you're at Sangma-san's right now?
I'm at Sangma's right now.
Oh, it's Mr. Sangma.
Ah
Welcome
That's great.
Miracle
Miracle, you.
What the hell is this?
I'm not supposed to be with everyone else.
You're not good enough.
Now you're out, Mr. Sangma.
Please go.
Please go
at a secret shop
Ah, Sangma-san is going there too
That's great.
What a face!
What the hell is wrong with his face?
If we all went to Himon-ya together
we'd be in big trouble.
Why do you say that?
New drama with Alice Hirose
Detective is too early
The fastest detective in history played by Kenichi Takito
solves the case before it happens.
Comedy Mystery
Starts July 19
Gaki no Tsukasa Special Edition
If you want to see it again, you can watch the full et
Regler broadcasts are also time-limited
Now streaming all at once!
Motion.
End
When he dies
He's going to die because of you.