So, Matsumoto...
Well, first of all, I'd like to take a look at something that's been done to my carry-on bag in the past.
You made it look like it was your own property.
Like "why is this in there like this?"
Today we're going to do the otaku visit part of it.
We're going to be doing a little bit of geek stuff in the house.
We're trying to see how many of the guests who are affected by this, who don't know anything about it, can see it for the first time and take advantage of the little blurbs in the room.
That's what I'm talking about.
If you make him say this, he's probably one of the top 1,000 people in Japan's comedy clubs.
He's in the top 1,000.
It may be higher, but roughly speaking, it's within a thousand.
So you're within the top 1,000.
That's within the hundreds, isn't it?
I don't know if it's within a hundred, but that's also within a thousand.
You have your good times and your bad times.
That's for sure.
You know, there are times when it's really bad.
And yet you have a level that's just barely within the top 1,000.
I'm not in good shape sometimes.
I can see it from here now, but it has an interesting appearance.
I'm going to shake the camera or I dare you to shake the camera.
I fantasize
No one is in
Good morning
here and here and here
Kyoyu-san's house
3 years
Quite a few districts don't show up.
last year's kotan
Last year?
Is that right?
Is that okay?
Cool nameplate
Special
I think this is a shoji?
Special Murakami
They'll know.
Because it's cold, for now.
long
Special Murakami
Sorry to disturb you
What is this?
Mori Castle
It's for neighborhood cats and so on.
I think it's a forest castle.
This is bait.
It's made to look like salt
Jet is milk powder.
I think it's salt.
If the customer sees it
That's a little bad.
Can't get in there
Cats don't think that way.
So this is what it's always been.
Vigilance.
Sorry to disturb you.
I'm sorry.
Come in.
Huh?
Mr. Shoji, I was just wondering...
I've got a lot of shoes here.
This is all of them
Left direction, or rather
I only had the left shoe.
I really don't know what to do
Why?
I have a pair of shoes that I walk on the left.
You've been walking on the left side of the road for a while now.
If it had been on your right
Walk to the right
It's more like being guided.
It's only left.
I'm going to turn left.
Right
What are you talking about?
Are you deaf?
I think you mean the right side is somewhere else.
There is no right
No right?
I didn't know you could buy like that.
It is possible to buy only the left side.
That's amazing.
I've got to come to this house.
I don't know.
The bills are great, but
Bills are great, but
Bills are like that, right?
In short
Four-letter word
Four-letter idiomatic compounds
By the way, what is it called?
What kind of guy?
This one?
Even if you buy dark, there is still night.
Mr. A
It's like you can throw a stone.
Watch out!
I'll tell you what to say.
if you could tell me.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Why are all the shoes on the left?
I'd like to hear a little more about that.
You mean left?
Actually, it's me.
I used to be a pitcher.
Baseball
Actually, I'm that one, aren't I?
All of them.
Do you know I walk like this?
No, I didn't know that at all.
Is this the way you walk?
I've never seen it before.
Walk a little bit, please.
Is that how you walk?
It takes a long time.
You're careful how you walk.
Yeah.
I'm walking through, but I'm forcing myself to walk like this.
You're forcing yourself
This way is faster
This is much faster
You are
You're in a mood
please.
I'm sorry, I'm at the entrance.
Excuse me for disturbing you.
What's this place?
What kind of room is this?
It's more like a guest room.
Oh, it's a guest room.
Who is this?
Is this Mr. Yoshida?
What? A little bit.
Which one?
Oh, this is Yoshida
Yoshida's
Who is it?
I don't know much about baseball.
Which Yoshida-san?
Um...
Ten years in grassroots baseball.
Repairs were taken out.
10 years of repair and delivery for grassroots baseball?
Yoshida
I think you're a pro, right?
No, it's not.
So many grassroots people.
Did you enshrine the ceremony?
No, I think it was on TV once.
It's just a coincidence.
You know, Yoshio Yoshida, the Hanshin's perpetual caretaker...
I thought it was
It's not a grassroots baseball game.
Raider
Ray
Yodogawa Raider
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
Yoshida's
What's behind Yamazaki?
What is this? What is this?
It goes outside.
Microphone...
It's not a microphone, it's a phone.
A string phone
Yes
Hello?
I'm just doing a program right now.
Yes, I understand.
Have a good time.
I mean, I used to do this.
Now when I've had too much to drink
If you feel sick, this is what you get
Can't buy it?
Could not buy?
I used to use this in the past.
Now I have a cell phone.
That's right.
I can't even hold it if I drink too much.
To the kitchen
So open this up.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but it's very detailed.
What is that? What is that?
That's, uh...
handcuffs.
Handcuffs?
I think he's in on it.
Electricity
So ours is pretty effective.
from the old days.
The one that takes it too and leaves.
There's a guy who's going to take it.
like a thief.
And you catch that at the front door, too.
Punishment here
Put this in and run the current
I'm so scared.
I wouldn't do that to a child, an adult.
But not that much current
because it's soft.
Only about 20 volts
That's a little bit
That's not good.
That's great.
Wow.
I've never seen anything like that before.
Rarely made only two
Until now
My senior, a comedian, with a guitar.
He's a guy who fills up his tank, and he's done it once.
What did that person do?
School money
My
I had it in my jacket.
It was
because it's a set
It doesn't matter if it's about 25 volts.
Yeah.
You're putting up a good one.
You like her, don't you?
Yes, I do.
even if you say that
Like I've grown up with this girl.
If you think about it
What to say
I don't remember her doing that.
I'll say it right away
comes out as
Hmm?
I'll get it.
That's the kind of crossing over.
With that kind of talk
Today
Guests
What do you say
Say it quickly
More of the old
I mean, there was a needle.
That's basically what I did the first time.
What do you say?
say quickly
I don't want to do this differently.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What do I say first
The prototype is
I know, I know.
And from my office.
Can I have a moment, please?
something like that
Say
And then I
You know, the president of the company, the managing director...
Said "Please buy it!"
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to say this, but
I'm a little bit nervous.
The most
A little
say what?
say quickly
soy sauce
Go to the next room.
As if urging
what is this?
I've seen it
The one you see at a family restaurant
Is this made by a commodity store?
That's amazing.
Because you can't do it with a machine.
Not by machine
I think I can do it.
I can't do it now
A place called Zambo in Chayamachi
From a coffee shop
Order
Not a great waste of money.
You cut it out of one piece.
It's like this, but
It's impossible without something of that size
You waste it.
I'm going to use this one more time.
One more time
How many of these can you get?
That's 8
that's about it
You can do 8?
I think it's been 3 years since I've received 8.
I finally got one now
Now the second one
in 3 years?
Yes.
It takes that long?
Try it.
This is...
Craftsman.
I've been doing it by imitation.
How do you do it?
If you could show me
I'll show you the same as this
I don't want to show you too much.
This is
I'm not in Miyadai Ward.
I can see these things.
What do you mean "technology theft"?
My lifeline.
my lifeline is going to be cut off.
Just a little bit
Just like that.
like this
This takes time
If you can't do one
I wonder what it would cost me too.
Here you go.
2 years
Is this 2 years?
This will take 2 years
This, by the way, also takes when
This one time, by the way.
It's done.
Send one back to China.
I'll have it varnished.
You don't do it yourself
Oh, no, no, no
Brusi here and that kind of thing.
There's a Chinese specialty resin like that.
And then you send it to them, and they varnish it.
and have it done
Have it sent
But.
Once you get the hang of it, it's easy.
Wow.
Wait
this
this is not good
This is not that one.
Somebody's going to hate me and do this.
isn't it?
is that right?
It's burning.
And that's it.
I'm going to do my tomorrow's
It's like a laughingstock.
Try it for a minute.
How about tomorrow
something
It's going to be good.
This way.
Perfectly already
That's not a hammer.
It's going to be good.
I'm serious.
I think I could sell it.
Thank you very much.
Which is tomorrow
What is it?
that way too
I want to go over there too
I want to go there too
I want to go that way too
Oh, I love this house.
That's great.
wow
Disgusting
You can see it when you look at it, can't you?
Alcoholic beverages?
Alcoholic beverages
This
This is a hose
Not a hub or anything like that.
I can't speak.
When I can't speak
This is always in the morning.
If you do this with a hub or something, you'll see what I mean.
Is it a hose?
Because that pee-pee is not coming out.
I don't know what that means.
How's your throat
And there's the throat
Various places
I'm just leaving it there.
I wish you'd make up your mind.
I've got to pee so bad, actually.
So you're going that way.
Which way should I go?
For users?
yes, yes, yes
I'm in the middle of something.
Behind you
what is that?
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared
Big
How about this switch
Don't push this one.
I'm scared, I'm scared
Just put the house down for a little bit
Don't put the house a little bit when you push it.
Don't push it.
That's why.
Why did you make that?
This is the one you just made
The Chinese
Contracting company
From the President
Why don't you put it on and see?
Why not?
Because I have a business partner, too.
This is not such a one-size-fits-all
I'm not going to be told to stop now.
I'm having a hard time
In so many ways.
In many ways
This is really bothering me.
What are you doing?
I think he's going for it.
of pickup
Apartment
No, no, no.
Tomorrow's weather
Weather
stargazing
I can't see the stars
It's a balcony
No, it's not.
I can hardly see anything.
I can't see a thing.
With this
I can see if it's raining.
Or if it's not raining.
Not so much.
And you can barely hear the sound.
Ehh...
That's how much they said.
You don't live in the world.
You're looking at rain.
You're looking at weather in short
Is this the kitchen?
Yes, that's right.
Here it is
That's a normal one.
Normal
What is that?
What is this?
Oh, this.
Yes.
It's for cockroaches
The ones that run around
How did you do that?
You'll get it when you cut it.
That's it.
It's not as primitive as it sounds.
Really?
No, it's not.
By centrifugal force
By one shot
Cockroaches out
Cockroaches
Poor guy in pain.
All at once
Breath of life.
What?
Mr. Camera
picture
There used to be
this
It's more like bait.
What is this?
What do you eat?
this, that, and that
Civet
That's a civet!
Ah!
A civet came here.
For years and years
He said crumbly.
How many times is that?
I only saw him once.
I wonder if he likes cabbage rolls.
They love cabbage rolls
I've tried so many things
I did cabbage, too
I can't see cabbage anymore
It's got to be cabbage rolls.
You'll never get caught.
I'd like to get caught a little bit.
Emo here
If you catch him
I'll tell you.
A civet.
Living room?
Is it a living room
Relaxed
I love Tomochika so much.
I know Tomochika.
I love it.
friend
All that's out there
I love it all
Cute Tomochika
Summary
I could use your help with this one.
I'm a junior member of the board.
Let's not do that.
The junior
Let's just stop with that one.
You like that.
When he's doing his sexy guy stuff.
When he sings
As a woman
I only see you as a woman.
That's right.
Isagui, or something like that.
There's a story tone, too.
Neta-tones
are you sure?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's got a gag on it.
It's a story tone, isn't it?
What is this?
Nyanyu ne
New No
Nyanyeewne
Just as I thought.
Thank you very much.
You're back.
I know you have other rooms.
I think you showed them everything.
There it is again.
Here it is again
You didn't go there.
So this is a room, too?
It's a bedroom
This is where you sleep
Japanese room
Because it has tatami mats
I'm sorry
We found something.
It's okay.
Is she hurt?
No, no, no.
She was on the ground
at the light pole just now.
Who is this?
Because she was on the ground
I'll call an ambulance, but she said "you can't!"
I found her lying on the ground
You don't know her at all.
I don't know her at all
Do you do this a lot?
People are often fallen down out there
What do you want me to do?
Until she gets well
Eh
Here
She says he doesn't have the money.
"I don't have an insurance card."
I don't know where she came from.
That's the police.
Okay.
That's good.
Sorry
grandmother
Excuse me
Is everything all right?
Are you all right?
You're going to be all right.
Let's take a look
Over here
All
All gone
Here
here
These people who was brought in and died
You're decorating it.
That's not good.
Oh my god...
That picture
The lady who is sleeping now
They're scared.
But here it is.
Gone two weeks ago.
Yes.
That's not good.
It's okay.
I have to tell the police.
It's not okay.
It's gone here.
So I'm going to tell the police.
if they lose it.
It's gone, sir.
I don't think he did anything wrong.
I don't think so
But...
what is this?
It's a pet.
Is he dead?
goat
Goat thus
People do this
I said it, but it's still a face
you know what I mean
You all right?
Are you all right?
Is she alright?
It's bad, isn't it?
Somebody call an ambulance.
No, now.
I told you to call one from the beginning.
Because I called an ambulance
It's too late now.
We're already that thing.
Thank you very much.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much for anything.
How was it, Matsumoto?
But
8 minutes is usable
8 minutes.
No, thank you.
That was quite a long time.
8 minutes
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Failure
But
Bad
that guy
since he was standing on the pole.
That's funny.
This is not good.
And the complexion
I thought something funny was going on.
I did a lot of spinning.
That's right.
And then we're going to go to the store...
Let's wander around
Shall we wander around town?
We have to do something.
1 minute
I'm calling an ambulance.
TV's Messenger DVD & Blue Bay Volume 25: Never Laugh at Treasure Hunters 24th Episode on Nov. 27