First time on Gaki no Tsukai Yarahende Chikichiki: Tanaka Naoki Wild Kingdom
Here we go
Our tension is about the same as that of the classroom in 1927
Say wild kingdom
You're right in the middle of the Jingqi.
Yes, but
That's kind of the point.
The point is right in the middle of this big city, Tokyo.
I thought there were a lot of these creatures.
And that's what we're trying to show you.
You're working very well today, aren't you?
How many times have you iterated this in your head and now you're in the show?
I've repeated it about 8 times.
Certainly no words well wasted.
This is a very useful project for all of you.
Is this for real?
You all have children, don't you?
Do you have a loud voice?
Really loud
Even more shrill than politicians
Election people
That's huge.
But if we can get the word out that there really are creatures like this in the big city of Tokyo...
I can be a hero as a father.
I'm not going to go to the country just because it's summer vacation.
There are others.
That's what I mean.
But the fact that there's so many cicadas singing...
It means there are insects.
I'm sorry about this, but what is it that's chirping now?
I can confirm about two types
Amazing.
Mimin mimin is mimin zemi.
So it's a jaegerjaeger
I think it's afrafimi that's squealing at a slightly faster pitch.
It's a collaboration.
I'm going to go back to that now.
We're going to go into the woods and the forest.
what's that?
It's grapefruit peel.
It's called limonene.
It has an insect repellent effect.
You should apply this before you go in.
We're not supposed to show our bugs.
This one works better.
Of course, there are a number of you.
More than ordinary insects
I'm this way
Absolutely no more
This is it.
Don't do it.
Wait a minute.
I've turned around.
It's a miracle.
The greatest creature lover in show business
Naoki Tanaka can be seen in the big city of Tokyo
Introducing various creatures
Not only to children
But to fathers who have children
At-home project
In an urban park with the Tokyo Metropolitan Government towering in front of you
What kind of creatures can we see?
Here we come.
Now poof, you've got it.
Catch it when you go.
That's a lot of crying.
But I'd like to see some cicadas, though.
If you guys are there
I can see the cicadas gunning for you.
There's something that looks like a shell.
Is it there?
Is there a brother to brother
Here it is.
It's right here.
It's an abrazemi.
This is a shell.
I know.
There is one.
Grab it by hand
There's so much
It's a cicada shell.
You can't eat them.
You don't eat this.
Eat it
Try it.
That's right.
If I ate here, wouldn't you pull it?
Maybe I'll be able to pull it off.
He's going to pull it.
I'll pull a little bit.
Then let's not do this.
If he pulls it, let's pull it.
How many days does that thing molt for?
Cicadas...
You have an image of Tangmei, don't you?
It's called custom or something like that.
You spend about six years in the ground
Actually, you live about a month.
It's widely known
A life span of one week is
Difficult to keep in captivity
A continuation of the theory that they die quickly
Early in the start of the game
Cicada shells are found
Continue further into the park
Something to eat
You can eat the rest.
I'm eating.
I've got some sea borers here.
You know, the teeth are eaten by bugs and stuff.
In this case, you have to go to the back of the teeth and see if you can find anything.
There's a worm in the back of your teeth.
Sometimes it's a sign.
What kind of bug is it really?
It's a sea hound nasca
Like ladybugs.
Like ladybugs hanging out on Nazca.
There are stinkbugs
Stinkbugs.
It stinks.
You're a stinky guy
Is it a stinker?
Of the stinkbugs.
This one smells pretty bad.
It smells like a stink bug.
When you stimulate it
A stink bug releasing a strong handshake
Repeatedly molts 5 times from larva
Becomes a larva
And it smells like that when it's in danger?
That's right, Endo.
They put out a smell so they wont be eaten.
Then try eating it from behind.
eh?
Stinkbug eating idiot
Where are they?
I've never called him before.
I don't know if it smells like that.
You can smell it, you can feel it.
It is
I know it stinks, of course, but
Smell experience?
Is that a good smell?
It smells a little bit like turtles.
It smells all the way up there.
You know what I mean.
But all I smell is your grapefruit.
It's supposed to smell so bad.
It's sealed up.
For example, I'm going to put this girl in there, right?
by your own smell.
There's an experiment that says he died.
It's true, it stinks.
Is it here?
That's a lot of money right there.
All I smell is grapefruit.
These things are still out there.
It's a little bit... it smells...
I don't even know if it didn't go bad.
Take a good look, folks, right here.
If you look closely, you should see him.
It's this eggplant plant.
So you found ladybugs.
Isn't that it?
Titmouse
There you go.
I saw ladybugs
I'll take some.
What ladybug?
Let's take a look at this
Oh, it's down.
I saw ladybugs.
What is this?
This is a double Yahoshitentou.
This is a double Yahoshi-Tentoo
Well
That's twenty-eight.
There are 28 stars
Double Yahoshi-Tentou
Born.
And Zaki's
Insect Fortune Telling is
Anyway, it's a knick-knack ladybug.
Is it good? No, it's not.
No, I don't think that's good.
Anyway, it's a knickknack.
Anyway, it's called "kotobu".
so-so so-so
Everyone's
They'll give you a funny sticker if you push them too hard.
That's for sure.
If you and I
Land of Dreams
A small forest
Wedding at the Church
The wedding ceremony was held at a church
to you, you're embarrassed.
The insects
They want you to kiss them.
to stand in a forest and kiss it softly
You gave me
Red
Blue-yellow
with caps on
The ladybugs
the ladybug goes out to the train
according to the sunfish
dance to the music of the sunfish
You got the cicada.
Cicada.
I'm sure he's there.
He's definitely here.
Oh, there you are.
There is a cicada.
suddenly
Why don't you just take it?
Just take it.
Take it.
There you go.
there.
what are you doing?
You're so clumsy.
You're not good at this.
Let's go, father.
Despite the crap
Insect collecting is
Tanaka
Restore the honor, new creature
We got him.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This way, please.
that's good
I mean, it's a mandarin tree.
There is a caterpillar somewhere
I haven't seen anything like that.
I'm looking at it from here.
you might be able to see it.
It's moving.
It's moving
It's a mess
All right.
Yes, sir.
Large
What is that?
That's a swallowtail butterfly
Eat it, Tanaka.
I don't eat caterpillars.
What do you eat?
That's not how it works.
Variant here and there.
It's a caterpillar, not an edible one.
You're not going to eat it today.
You can take it.
You can have them take it downstairs
You can have it down there.
Can I take it?
You're making me sick.
Everything's gung-ho
I wonder if this is going to work.
He's surprisingly sickened.
Oh, here they come.
Sorry.
I want to see it.
Is that creepy?
This is huge.
It tastes like green tea.
Definitely.
Color only
You're not an eye.
That's right.
That's not an eye.
It's not the eyes.
It's a black one.
You think it's the eyes.
I think it's a pattern.
This is made to look like an eye
To a bird that is external
I have such big eyes.
My eyes are just below that
that's right
I want to tell you this.
Insects are
They don't breathe through their nose.
You breathe through your body.
You have a hole in that body
And it takes in air through there.
So you turn it
In detail
Heavenly
You pooped.
You're not mad at me?
There's nothing to be angry about.
Not at all.
And that's what I'm breathing from here.
Insects
Because there are quite a few like that
I don't think so.
There are a lot of insects like that now.
I've got it right here.
There are quite a few insects like that now.
Don't you go toward the general
Such a caterpillar of a caterpillar
In search of living insect butterflies
Now a flower garden
Aimed at
Visiting for nectar
Yamato white-eye and Nagasakia swallowtail butterfly
Butterflies are a little bit small
It's the Yamato white-eye, right?
There are quite a few of them.
Yes, Mr. Zaki
Here comes Hon-san
It's a miracle
He's very angry.
There's a little butterfly.
It's a little bit small butterfly.
Yes, Mr. Zaki
Here comes Hon-san
Miracle
He's very angry.
I don't understand.
And they've got the Yamato white-eyes, too.
You went to get butterflies.
This one came right away, too.
what does that mean?
Isn't that amazing?
If you catch the Yamato white-eyes
It had a praying mantis on it.
It's a mantis.
You don't have this.
He was going for this butterfly.
There shouldn't be any child that doesn't eat it.
I don't know if they were going for it.
I've been hit
You idiot.
Why is it so
I don't know if I can go mantis
I'm scared
I'm going to go "kerr," that's normal.
It's stuck.
I wondered why it was so straight.
I thought, "Why is it so straight?
nothing to say at all
I'll leave it in then.
Captured praying mantis
Insect cage for the Japanese praying mantis
then
again
Missed again
I don't know.
Oh...
Oh!
Do you want to turn around?
right here, right now.
I'm in.
It's coming, it's coming.
It's not spiritual.
Matsumoto-san's back
Popped out
Miracle.
Oh my god, Matsumoto's back.
The miracle of cicadas stopping
What is this?
This is a nimin zemi.
This is Niminzemi, right?
Nimin zemi came to get insects
Do they perch on your back at the location
After all that insect repellent
We are all
We are alive
because they are alive
Singing.
We are all
We are alive
because they are alive
I'm sad.
Palm of the hand
To the sun
If you look through it
In bright red
Flowing
My blood
It's a worm.
Even okelas
even a water strider
It's a water strider
Everybody, everybody
They're alive.
He's my friend.
Come on, Shinjuku.
I've been allowed to go around.
Let's move on to the next park.
You're lying.
Beetles and stag beetles.
And that's a different type of park to target those kinds of things.
I'd like to move
Can I just take a shower at the Washington Hotel before I go?
I just want to sleep so bad.
I don't love you.
We've come about 15 minutes from Shinjuku.
Starting with the pond
Park surrounded by greenery and nature
Come on
Location moved
It's a park in the middle of a residential area.
There is a tree
A little bit of ecology again.
I thought it was interesting that it's different.
one by one
A calgum
If you look closely, you can see dragonflies and things like that.
There are dragonflies.
It's hard to set up.
One big quote.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Now
They call me Dr. Conchu.
As long as you ask the right questions
Nature will tell you what you want to know.
That everyone can tell me.
skillfully
I'd like to ask you a question.
I would like to ask you a question.
I said it first.
You were already here.
What the hell is this?
Cockatiels
This is
The difference between a bobwhite and a canary is
A leaf-eater is a leafminer
The sap sucker
Canavan
There are a lot of them
I can hold this.
I can hold that.
This is not at all
This is nothing.
There you go.
Just in time.
Is this just in time?
Is this just barely enough?
just barely
Ahh
I really don't want to do this anymore.
At least hold it.
Cockatiels are rich.
Cockatiels are rich
I went to the rain shop and bought some syrup.
I went to a rain shop and bought some taffy.
wow!
Guts mantis or
It's haraviro, haraviro
Harabiro mantis with a wide body
The praying mantis is the only insect
It has the property of turning around
Tragedy of the praying mantis
Hamada, do you understand?
Comiword destruction eats you up
Yes, it is.
For a moving object
because it will attack you.
So the males that you see after you're done
They think it's prey and they're going to attack.
It's true.
That's good, too.
Parble is
Parble gets attacked too.
Let's put this in.
And then after that, from under the fire
Dung beetles belong to the same offensive shell family as shrimp
and
From the crack of the fire
With canaries, which, like beetles, prefer sap
Members capturing insects in good condition
And more
What did you discover
Oh, what's this
It's moving.
What is this?
what is this?
what is that?
this
I'm going to float you now.
I can see it.
How seldom can you see it during the day
I found a cicada just before it floated away
It's moving.
I might be seeing this for the first time.
I think I've never seen that before.
Ah!
E
Probably
Ah
You'll hit the end a little more.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
He ran away.
Got away
Because the endo hit the bar against the tree now.
That's such a rare one.
That you let a precious cicada get away
The worst of all worlds
He was playing par on eda.
Is that true?
Oh, I don't know.
I've done so many things.
That's very rare.
We're at the stage now where we're going to stand up and climb the tree and float it.
By the way, this is
The staff took this picture by accident.
Cicada molting scene
Next the five head to
a grassy lawn.
Come on, folks.
Here they come to the plaza.
We are here in the square to catch insects
Insects are caught in this square
They walk around a lot
If you've been paying attention
Yes, Mr. Zak
Great, you're a good bug catcher.
What is this?
It's a white-fronted goose
Houzei captured.
You know, the white-fronted goose
The name comes from the pattern of their wings
White butterfly with mon
Ola ola monarch butterfly
Ola-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
Oh, it hurts already
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
It's funny.
Is he awake?
Let's finish on the run.
Let's get the pranks out of the way.
Insect collecting resumes
And now Hamada
what happened?
what's wrong with you
There are a lot of white butterflies.
Someone's gone somewhere.
Somebody just farted.
Who is it?
I heard it from over here.
Put the lid on it. Put the lid on it.
the lid
Oh.
Ummm
What are you laughing at?
I don't know, I'm holding it in my voice.
You'd better get it right.
I can't sing any songs.
There are a lot of white butterflies.
I've seen a lot of white butterflies and things like that.
Once the female cobbles with the male
If a different male comes in, it will not be accepted
Cobi with different males
Every minute, every minute, there's a white-fronted goose.
No, it's great.
If it still comes
If you're wondering what you're going to do about the site mitigation
Hamada, if you stay here
I'm still here
take
butterfly butterfly butterfly
on rape leaves
stop
to a leaf of rape
When it opens
stop at the warehouse
Cherry blossoms
From flowers
To flower
Stop
Play
Go ahead, play.
Stop.
It is in the main
Kabuto may be
there may be
That Kunugi, because there is a quercus
finally
In search of the king of insects, the beetle.
This is the tree where the beetles are.
Yes, sir.
This is more like it.
Kabuto is
Since they are nocturnal
Sometimes they're still in the dirt at this time or
I see.
I mean, it goes up at night.
It looks like a huge moon digging.
Inside, you know, sometimes they're there.
Right here.
At the base of a tree or something.
Sometimes they are there.
yay!
He's not here.
There's nothing here.
Hard, stone.
And after that
5 people desperately searching for beetles
But
Tanaka they're not here.
I don't see them.
They can't find
a single beetle.
Frogs?
No, a little bit, Kabuto, a little bit.
I was hoping to see that.
They almost gave up
Then
eh
eh eh eh
What?
salt white 2013
rave reviews
This year, a hot teacher not to laugh
From actual props used
Appears daily
Up to the qualification of laughter
We are waiting for Mr. Kanaga
eh?
Hamada
What?
No, this is a little bit...
I'm pretty sure he's already there.
It's a horseshoe, but it's a horseshoe.
It's a carcass.
The ants are so warm.
I wonder how they died.
I think it's a crow's nest.
I think it's possible that there's a horseshoe at the horseshoe.
It is quite possible
Wow.
I know you're looking at me from somewhere.
No, no, no, I'm pretty sure he's already there.
Since they started looking for the beetles..
30 minutes has elapsed
Still no sign of one
No sign of Kabuto? Yes, I think so.
No Kabuto?
I guess you can't be that naive after all.
Yes, it is.
Unfortunate giveup
No, just a little bit more, a little bit more here at the end.
I wanted you to be happy that I found the horseshoe.
Unfortunately
unfortunately
But according to Fabre, though
It's okay.
At least when you're in this huge universe of human beings.
Deeply
I've never been in a lonely hell
I'm going to tell Fabre for a minute.
I'm in deep.
Come in, come in, come in
We say goodbye to the insects we met this day
The wild kingdom comes to an end
Oh, here it comes, here it comes
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
oh!