Can one meet up only by intuition?
Gaki's popular project: Superb venues where you can meet up without a smart phone
Will the guests and Downtown succeed in meeting up?
Gaki no Tsukai Special Edition
Absolutely must meet up without a phone Special
It's been 12 years since I've been asked to laugh at the end of the year
We're going to have a guest without a phone
Hamada team and Matsumoto team are invited to a 5-on-5 team game
Let's have a guest on the stage.
Thank you very much.
Gorgeous members
The five guests are as you can see
10 regular members are divided into Hamada's team and Matsumoto's team for a showdown.
Okay, everybody, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Who, who, who
I'm going to give you all a little bit of a challenge.
And then I'm going to ask you all to go to the place that you associate with it, without any information on your phones or anything else.
If all five members of a team gather at the same place, that's the end of the game.
If we do this right, there's a chance that we'll end up with one more shot.
One shot, yes, it could be done, but I think it's a little bit too hard for us to do one shot.
I've been doing this for over 30 years.
And the losing team will be punished severely, severely, severely, so please help me out.
You're punished for losing the game.
We have a special rule this time
Actually, there will be one joker who will be moving around on the same subject as you all.
Yes, if you meet this joker, you will be dismissed and you will have to start all over again from the beginning
And the person who is the joker...
This time, the joker is Mr. Ebisu.
Here we go.
This is Dr. Yoshida
Okay, let's start the game, and I'm going to announce the first subject.
The first one is a big electronics store.
A big electronics store
This is surprisingly a little bit
I say what is that?
Excuse me, excuse me, just a second.
What is that? Wait a minute.
Just the appliances that aren't in both retail stores.
They're being electrified in the city.
Are they both retail stores
Looks more dangerous than a dangerous joker
There's a bad guy in there.
Let's start the game.
It's time to get into the 12 cabs
Who will be the first to assemble with one heart and soul?
Matsumoto team or Hamada team
There are more than 100 large electronics retail stores in Tokyo
Difficulty level is high
Can the five members of the Matsumoto team match?
There are several
There are several of them, of course, in Akihabara.
I mean, there's a couple of them
The closest we can get is
In front of Akasaka Tokyu
I don't know what to do
After much deliberation, I came up with this answer
Let's go there.
I'll do that... in front of the driver of Akasaka Tokyu.
And this is Yusuke Iseya.
Where do you usually go to the electronics store?
The one I mentioned the most for some reason is Big Camera in Shibuya.
The one store that has the biggest image is
I think it's Shinjuku
Yodobashi Camera
That's a culture.
I don't know about that.
Let's see
Is that right after all?
Iseya can't make up his mind
In such a situation, Hosei
Okay, Shibuya
Yamada Electric
And Endo
That's huge.
Big camera
That's the barn at the corner in front of the station.
Smoothly deciding where to go
What I'm interested in is
Isn't Kaelen Takizawa totally unreadable?
To the Japanese who don't know how to mass market
To a Japanese person who explains a mass merchandiser
I think I've never seen it before
Kaelen Takizawa, who seems to be a key person in Matsumoto team
I understand what you mean by "appliance store".
An electronics store is a store that sells
I think it is
Appliances and rice
The rice restaurant is that
Yes, that's right, a restaurant that sells rice
is that a rice
I wonder if I can play with electricity
If that's the case, then along Meiji-dori in Shibuya
Where do you usually play?
I was wondering if you are in Shibuya
It's almost Shibuya
Shibuya, yes
Since I was a child
What was your childhood like?
I was a girl who really liked people with big noses
She would find a guy, especially a guy with a big nose, and she would talk to him
I don't know, I don't know what it is.
I don't understand the childhood that I'm good at
The destination is concentrated in Shibuya
Names of famous restaurants in the press are lined up
By the way, for the general public living in Tokyo
Speaking of big electronics retailers
The survey asked
As you can see, the ranking is
Hamada's team of five, on the other hand, is headed for
I don't know where
I knew it
the town of Yurakucho
Big Camera
Big Camera in Yurakucho
I've seen it
Akko is the one I found in Akasaka
There it is.
Shibuya-Shinjuku, yeah.
I think I'll go to Akasaka or Yurakucho
So you chose Yurakucho.
Or Akasaka
I'm afraid
I think I can do one all the time
That's right.
You've been alone the whole time, that's a bad guy.
I mean, look at Tanaka and all the creepy stuff.
I'm like, "What the hell is that?
It's like, "You're just picking the creepiest places.
I'm the one who goes to rent a YOLO video
I go to my hometown, Tsudaya.
when the cameras are rolling on TV.
When I say Tsudaya, I mean, "Tsudaya,
It's like, "I'm going to choose mountain tea.
That's in the regular broadcast
The countryside is also my senior
Senpai!
Speaking of Tsudaya, let's take a look at the members who gather at Oto Oyasan
in a similar way
Good
That's right, of course.
and Tanaka?
Yes, he's not here yet.
It's very big, though.
Tanaka, who chose one mountain tea
At this time we encountered
Just a little bit in front of you
Pierre Taki just happened to show up.
Piel also appeared on this location.
Tanaka's Ponpots character arrives
What does that mean?
Can he make up for it this time?
I think I've seen this in Venus Fort.
I don't remember that.
Wait a minute, what else do we have?
I don't know if there's Ginza or something like that.
Oh, there's one in Shinjuku
It's in Shinjuku.
In front of Areta
Before Areta
So we rush to Shinjuku
You have to see the confidence in those eyes.
Aim for a little change of pace
I'm at the Big Lo in Shinjuku
I think it's nice there.
I'm going to see Tanaka early.
I see.
Big Ro
Big L
Big Lo, not far from Areta
If the store in front of Arita that Tanaka refers to is Big Lots, then
Kato's reading is correct
Hamada's team is expected to meet up with the others in Shinjuku
Meanwhile, this person also starts to move
Along the 246
I think there's something there.
Which one, which one along 246?
Where will the Joker Ebisu appear?
The first to arrive.
Matsumoto chose Big Camera in Akasaka find
Mr. Enough Camera, make sure you take a good picture.
That's big enough, isn't it?
At the same time, Shinjuku West Exit
Now
Ise is going to Yodobashi Camera Shinjuku Nishiguchi main store
Unfortunately, he has no teammates waiting for him at the moment
It's kind of sad when you feel like you're off the hook like this.
And in Shibuya
There's nobody there.
It's just the beginning, right?
Here we are at Big Camera
Here we are, Big Camera
Takizawa came to the Big Camera Shibuya east exit store in Miyamatsuzaka
Please, just one person, just one person
This is huge
And arrived at the same Shibuya
Alright.
Headed for Yamada Denki Labi
He didn't meet up with Takizawa
Ooran
I don't see anyone.
And the long way is Yurakucho Big Camera
No way.
Matsumoto's team is all broken up
Hamada's team captain, on the other hand, landed
Let's see who's there.
Waiting there at the Big Camera in Akasaka Find
No way... this is definitely the place.
Where is that red one?
There's a red one, but there's a red one
That's Matsumoto, and you're there, but you're not
I don't care if you're here or not.
Here comes the least painful one
What the hell is this? I've seen this guy many times.
There's ten of them.
Two of them are downtown, and the only thing that I can tell you is that there was only downtown here.
This is the end of the show.
I think we've had enough of this.
At that time in Shibuya
It's from Ebisu
Amazing.
Here comes Mr. Riel.
Enemy teams are joining each other
Right.
She's the only one
I'm just glad I'm not alone too
By the way, no matter how many times Mr. Sakizawa explains
he doesn't understand the reversal of both mask reversals.
They think both inversions are both.
Yes.
So I thought, "I'm here.
It's been around for a long time.
He-chan shock
45 minutes from the start
Tanaka is still with us
You see, he's always
I hate him so much
I don't know what's up with him, but he's been stretching it lately.
"I'm going to extend it, aren't I?"
"I don't want to go home."
Ryu Kato came to Shinjuku to meet up with Tanaka
It's not so easy
And then Tanaka goes to Shinjuku, just like he wanted
Is that what I'm saying?
Will we meet up with Kato on the street where BICQLO is?
I don't see anything like this
This is a big one.
That one
It's Ryo-kun
Ryo-kun was there
Tanaka-san, isn't it?
Tanaka-san is here
Ryokun Tanaka-san
Biclo
I think it's here
Tanaka, isn't it?
Over there
This is just a passing.
Tanaka, who was not Biclo
So which park is this?
See, it's huge, it's so huge
That's Big Camera in front of Shinjuku east exit station
Only 2 minutes away from Kato's BICQLO
And here the time is up
I knew it wasn't right.
Simultaneous call to see where their teammate are
Hello, it seems we're all seperate
Eh no way, we're all disjointed?
Where is Taki?
He is at the Big Camera on the corner of Meiji-dori in Shibuya
Where are you, Hamada?
I found it, Big Camera.
Hamada-san found it.
I'm in Akasaka
Tanaka, you're the slowest.
Shinjuku, Shinjuku
This is Big Camera diagonally across from Alta
Big Camera in front of Ulta
Not bigro
No one's chasing anyone, they're all in pieces.
Hello?
First of all, the original is waiting alone
With the enemy team, to be exact.
Enemy team
And it was Hamada-san
Hamada-san
And we were waiting for you and Mr. Hamada
Mr. Hamada
Where is Iseya-kun?
Where is Mr. Iseya
It's Yotobashi Camera at the west exit of Shinjuku
Here we go.
I'm not saying it doesn't have that, but
I don't know if you met anybody.
I met with Pierre.
Pierre, the enemy of Pierre.
He's at the Big Camera on the far corner.
I'm in the numbers, too.
I don't like this girl
Hello
It's big, but
You all didn't get together with your allies
And the joker, Mr. Ebisu...
We're moving together.
Mr. Ebisu
while everyone else is going to Shinjuku Shibuya or Akasaka
I went to Akihabara by myself
Akihabara
Where in Akihabara is Mr. Ebisu's electronics shop?
We have information that he is wandering around Akihabara, not really knowing what he's doing.
There's something a little bit wrong
Maybe they're going to spread the picture somewhere in India or something.
And now, ladies and gentlemen, let's move on to the next subject.
Yes, please.
The next subject is
art museum
I see what you did there
Who's there
Meeting up without a phone
The next subject is the art museum
In Tokyo alone, there are about 110 art museums of various sizes
Can you find them?
Matsumoto team's goal is
Let's see
The new national park over there
Midtown
And then
In terms of a museum
Nez Museum
Matsumoto, originally deeply shaped by art
Koho's museum is slurred
They say poof
I don't think there's a new National Art Museum or anything like that
I don't think the Nez Museum is coming.
I don't think he knows.
I don't think they even know it exists
Once you get in the cab
I said, please go to the Nez Museum.
I've had people say, "Oh, yeah.
Let's go to the new national monument.
No.
Ueno, Ueno
I'm going to Ueno
I don't care about the distance
If I'm doing the neighborhood, I'll see Hamada again
That's the only place I'm going to be at the museum.
I've been there a few times.
Go to Ueno
go to Manimatsu Ueno
Art Museum
I'm an art student, so it's natural for me to go around the university.
Or what I'm wondering is
Okay, hold on a second.
I should be thinking about everybody else.
Downtown...
Akazawa.
It's Akazawa kana, it's close
It's very close.
I'm a little too lazy to watch TV, so it would be nice if we could get together in the neighborhood...
I'll take it.
What is the museum that Iseya decided to go to?
Art museum
When I say art museum, I mean
If you think of it as a museum, you'll think of it as
because I go there a lot for work.
You're all going through there
And Matsumoto's keeper, Takizawa Takizawa...
like a museum to go to.
I'm not going to go to that.
I don't think "no way" is an overstatement.
Let's go for it.
The unthinkable choice of subject
I don't even know what a museum is
I only know what Makuhari Messe is
I'll put it up one more time
After much deliberation, she narrowed it down to
I wonder if that counts as art.
The first generation
That was amazing.
I think it's a work of art.
Although I have a bad feeling about Takizawa
Matsumoto and Baozei are going to meet up at Ueno
In the first place, art museum equals Ueno
the idea of "Ueno" is
I wonder if they have it without a forehead
No, hey, I
I really don't know.
Yeah, I don't know, it's like a museum or something.
I've never said
"That's a museum"
Now just a little bit of one
In the studio at Jingu
At the Jingu
It's the only place
I really can't think of anything else.
What's the museum about Matsumoto-san?
Does it mean that he's smart?
Only if you're interested in painting or something like that.
only people who are interested in paintings and things like that would go there.
It's like if I were looking at it, I'd be laughed at.
Oh, you're coming.
Having an unreliable leader
Hamada team members
It's a museum, right?
The first thing that popped into my head was
The New National Art Museum in Roppongi
Pierre trusts his instincts
to Roppongi
I thought I'd go to a place that popped into my head this time
That's Roppongi.
And I was there just last month
I go to this museum every year
So you don't go there to guess.
Yes, I'm going to guess, this time
As for Tanaka-san, I don't know anymore.
I don't know what to do anymore.
I have no idea, I can't even imagine.
Such a clueless man.
Tanaka is a man of his word
No, it's already floating.
No, it's right there.
Tanaka, you're very confident about this subject, aren't you?
How many times have we done this before?
Is this the fifth time we've done this?
I've seen a lot of them, and this is the easiest one I've ever done.
It's really, really easy.
Kawaguchi is the only one who hasn't decided where to go
Louvre Museum
Is there one in Tokyo?
I guess that's the level
I don't know what to do
It's going to be difficult, so I'm going to take a cab.
Roppongi
Near Midtown
Normal term street, right there
Museum of Fine Arts
The National Art Center, Tokyo
It's not the Mori Art Museum.
I don't know what to do
Let's go with the big one, the New National Art Museum.
Please, please, please
By the way, in the general survey
The National Art Center, Tokyo and Mori Art Museum are
Top 2 this is a difficult choice
Hamada's team of three heads to Roppongi
Chance to meet up
Joker Ebisu is on the move
Museum.
Art Museum
By the way
I think there's something there.
Don't you hear something about a museum?
Oh no, here
Even if you get to meet them
I don't even know what it's called, but I'm going to go to Jingu Gaien anyway
Here comes Hamada
I wonder what the official name is.
I don't think there's a museum.
I think you're saying something like Matsumoto-san
He said it on TV before.
What do you want to be?
I want to be a body macho
Look at a painting in a museum
Final decision on where to go
Matsumoto arriving at Ueno
Also headed for Ueno
Will it be a merge with Hosei?
You're doing an Arcimboldo show.
Arcimboldo show
Ah!
Matsumoto
Why all these different teams?
Why are we meeting?
Waiting for us was the enemy team, Tanaka.
I'm in the car, and I'm telling them about this art
I don't know if you know what I'm talking about, but Tanaka...
I went to design school.
Kawaguchi, on the other hand, is aiming for Roppongi
On the other hand, Kawaguchi aiming for Roppongi
I wish we could work together.
I'm a little nervous
We want to talk about it.
At the same time, Shibuya-ku departing Dai
Around the same time, the train departed from Shibuya-ku, Tokyo
Takizawa aimed at the museum and
This is it.
This is a work of art
The giant obj. on display
This facility is Tokyo Opera City
A complex facility of concert hall and art museum
This is the only one I can think of
Okay, I've got it.
And Kawaguchi of Hamada's team
Right in front of the National Art Center, Tokyo
Ahead of the National Art Center, Tokyo
Can you see it?
You see that?
Oh, Mr. Pierre
Oh, I got it, I got it
Oh, good.
Got it
I see.
Hamada's team, Pierre and Kawaguchi have successfully joined together
And then
Good.
Iseya joins up with the enemy team
That's it!
yes
here it comes
Right.
Except here, it's the other way around.
From my point of view, this is the best place.
Correctest of the correct answers
Tanaka-san is trying to get it.
Where are you
I'm at a ton every time.
Tanaka is just really weird.
That's not the answer.
It's really weird to watch
Time is up here
Time's up here
Eh, he's lying.
Time's up.
Simultaneous team calls to see where they are
I had a bad feeling about this.
Everybody's in that museum
You know it's a museum.
Of course I know what it is
The National Museum of Western Art in Ueno is one of the most famous museums in Japan.
Yes, I'm from Ueno.
Where in Ueno?
I'm at the Tokyo Metropolitan Art Museum
They went to another museum in the same Ueno Park
Iseya, you see, is...
The National Art Center, Tokyo
There you go.
I've been thinking a lot about the distance from you guys, and here we are.
Where are you, Endo?
It's a thermal art museum.
There it is, too.
I first generation
I have an exhibit of giants
I thought it might be there.
What's that?
I'm sorry I only found the artwork
It's a mess
I'm sorry
I really didn't realize
I don't know where everybody is.
Where are Pierre Taki and Haruna?
They are in front of the National Art Center, Roppongi
Wow!
Where is Tanaka?
I'm at the National Museum of Western Art in Ueno.
Tanaka
National Museum of Western Art
Ryo-kun
I'm at the Mori Art Museum in Roppongi Hills
Where are you, Hamada?
It's on the way out.
That big one there
I don't know what it's called.
It's the Seitoku Memorial Picture Gallery.
You didn't even know its name.
You're not supposed to go there.
Hi, I'm Ohki.
I'd like to talk about Mr. Ebisu, the joker.
You haven't forgotten about him, have you?
It's called Mori Art Museum in Roppongi Hills.
Short
What are you waiting for?
So now you see the positional relationship
The members gathered in Roppongi and Ueno
How to move on to the next subject
Let's go to the next subject
Tall building
Speaking of tall buildings
Building
I'm really confident about this one.
All right, I got it.
What is the building that Takechain visited after this?
The subject is a tall building
There are skyscrapers over 200 meters high in Tokyo
It is probably a skyscraper
There are skyscrapers over 200 meters in Tokyo
Approximately 25 buildings
Where do the Matsumoto team members go?
Where is the biggest buildings?
After the big one
The closest one goes to Roppongi Hills
and the closest one to Roppongi Hills is
The least hassle is over there, right?
I've got a date in mind, and it's the Shinjuku NS Building.
That's where we all went a long time ago.
Like when I was in college.
Sunshine in Shinjuku
Sunshine 60
This was an option a long time ago.
I still think it's that one
It's Sunshine, isn't it?
Sunshine in Ikebukuro
Yes Sunshine
Yes Downtown a long time ago
Shinjuku is the only place I can think of.
The expensive one in Roppongi is
The most expensive place in Roppongi is
Midnight Town near that museum.
Midnight town
It looks like he's going to Shinjuku.
He's in a building in Shinjuku
I've been watching him for a long time.
Okay, let's go to the Tokyo Metropolitan Government Building.
Let's go to the Tokyo Metropolitan Government.
This is easy to understand.
Hosei is going for Far East, and he's going for Tokyo Metropolitan Government.
Going for Tokyo Metropolitan Government
The tallest buildings are
The first thing that comes to mind is
Sunshine 60 is the first thing that comes to mind.
That's 240 meters.
Before Sunshine 60
So the Tokyo Metropolitan Government Building pulled it out at 243 meters
And you're in second place at that point.
But what do you guys think of the image
Sunshine 60 in Ikebukuro seems to be the most expensive.
how do you like it?
The height of Sunshine 60 and Tokyo Metropolitan Government Building is
Building Mania Far East Commentary Hall
After that, new buildings such as Midtown
The current height ranking is as follows
Knowing all about buildings, Far East is aiming for
The tallest building
Ah, but buildings
Counterpoints.
Where they're opposing each other.
Fuji TV
It has an elevator
It was pretty much 20 some floors up.
Matsumoto team far east Takizawa is going
holds the key
Meanwhile, the five members of Hamada's team are headed
The tallest building
Tall building
I think we're good here
Taller building
but it's like this
Yes, that's right.
And Haruna and Taki-san are in close proximity
Not here.
If they're not here, I wonder why they're not here.
Or they thought Kato was going to move on.
Will Kato's thoughts reach them?
The place I came up with
say it together
1,2...
Tokyo Mode Gakuen
Isn't that very high?
And one more thing for the two of you
Something to think about.
And here's where the risk of the joker comes into play.
Ebisu, I wonder if he's coming to Roppongi Hills.
Maybe he'll come.
I just don't think anyone from Tokyo Mode Gakuen will come.
I was imagining something like this
There's that one too
It's over there, isn't it?
The high one
I'll go here and there
Ryosan is going to come
From Roppongi Hills
I don't like to sit and wait
I'm thinking about the other thing
I think about the part where both of you are
Unfortunately, their feelings for each other are not mutual
Leader Hamada was still troubled
Are you all right?
It's called Midtown.
And then there's the Mori Building.
And then we go into the building
Hamada is unsure of his decision
What's a building?
I don't know much about it.
Sunshine or Tokyo Metropolitan Government or Roppongi
Midtown
Right.
What is the building that Tanaka is heading to?
If Hamada and Tanaka head to Roppongi
The chance to meet up with the others will increase at once
It's time to be on the lookout
Where is the Joker Ebisu?
Around Shinjuku
I think there is a tall building
I think there is a skyscraper in Shinjuku
I used to hang out in Shinjuku a lot.
We used to play mah-jong a lot in Shinjuku.
It was in Shinjuku that I got caught up in mah-jong.
Not good
Matsumoto arrived at Sunshine 60 in Ikebukuro
So he's the first one to arrive?
At the same time, Takezawa arrived
So this is it
If you look closer
Don't let me meet Ebisu
And then Ise
Oh no
To Roppongi Hills
I'm definitely there.
That's the enemy!
That's the enemy.
Joining up with Ryu Kato of the enemy team
Good, good, good
We could have met together
I couldn't see him at all
Actually, they were co-starring.
My first job was with Iseya
I played the role of a grandfather
You play the role of a child
In midtown
Pierre and Kawaguchi are
They were waiting for their friends to arrive
Leopard waiting
eh
The subject is a tall building
Kawaguchi and Pierre in midtown
Waiting for their friends
Waiting for leopard
eh
ah
Hamada
Yay!
Wow!
I'm so happy
I'm so glad you're here
I came in and you were there
no no no no
no no no no no
Here we go.
And then Hosei hoping to meet Endo
Somebody
Somebody, somebody, somebody
I knew it
Thank goodness I got it right.
But it's the highest.
The highest at 243 meters
Oh.
This is a different team.
Let's just do it with the regular members now.
Tanaka was talking about it
I knew that, too.
It's a place I remember.
So they're in a moving car
You went to the TMG with Tanaka on the second day when you got to know what was going on.
When do you remember that
I think Tanaka is going to come, too.
The two of us together in Tokyo.
The first place we went to was the Tokyo Metropolitan Government.
I have an emotional attachment to it.
Personally, as far as the Tokyo Metropolitan Government is concerned
This is the place of my memories
Although they are on the enemy team, they join forces
Just the three of you?
If it's a regular member
You found it, and Downtown would have been there.
I met him at the Museum of Western Art, Matsumoto.
Maybe we would have met up here.
Because they're going to the metropolitan government
If we lose the guest this time
There are no guests.
I don't want a guest.
I still think we should do it with us five.
That's a lot of people.
Time is up here.
No way
No way!
a little bit endo
Where are you?
I'm at the Tokyo Metropolitan Government Building
Me and Hosei are already there
I don't think so at all.
If you say it's a tall building
You know what I mean.
It's the Sunshine 60.
Ya, so old
Where is Karen?
I'm at NTV
Nippon Television Network Corporation
The mess and the idea
Don't leave Karen alone.
We should not leave her alone.
I don't think we're going to be able to meet up.
I'll match up with you
You should have from the beginning.
Tanaka, where are you?
I'm at the Tokyo Metropolitan Government Office.
Tokyo Metropolitan Government
There's all three of us.
With Hamada
Taki
Onnen in midtown
I got out of there
I think you're right.
Following the third subject
And the destination of the joker Ebisu
The point of interest
What a surprise for Ebisu!
K.O. Plaza Hotel, Shinjuku.
Not at all
K.O. Plaza Hotel.
Ebisu used to be
It was a skyscraper hotel in Nanha
K.O. Plaza Hotel Choice
I'm going to make it time for dinner today, so
You are free to go into the restaurant and eat
Yes, sir
Waiting
By one
Confrontation paused
between members at the same point, regardless of whether they are friend or foe
Lunch as you wish
So thin, yet so dense
And
The fourth subject that was settled on was
The next subject is
Famous bridges
Famous Bridge
That's not the answer.
Okay, I'm on my way.
bridge
No one is this white
There's the only one there
Don't listen in.
That's not fair, don't do that.
You're lingering
Excuse me, but I've got an idea floating around.
Nothing at all?
There's a bridge that's not floating at all
The bridge that the five Matsumoto team members are aiming for is
I mean, does Nihonbashi have a bridge?
That's a Nihonbashi bridge!
There's something you can't say anymore
Here we go, Nihonbashi
Now we come out
Nihonbashi and
The
It's the Rainbow Bridge.
I think I'll go to Nihonbashi.
Rainbow
No, but I'm going to be pissed off with you.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
Iseya can't decide where he's going
At any rate, he departs
Rainbow Bridge
I can't think of any underground
I've seen other bridges
But that one opened
Japan bridge
Nihonbashi, I often shoot there.
Nihonbashi is impossible
Matsumoto-san is definitely going to Nihonbashi.
what for?
I've been talking about Sunshine and the old days for quite a while now, so
Maybe the Rainbow Bridge came up recently
Maybe the Rainbow Bridge doesn't know
Nihonbashi, aiming only at Matsumoto-san
I think he's going to say it
Nihonbashi just because it's the beginning of Japan
Because it all starts from Nihonbashi
All roads in Japan start from Nihonbashi
So, for example, if you get on the highway from Osaka, it says 500 kilometers to Tokyo.
That 0 means Nihonbashi.
Nihonbashi
Iseya's prediction is apt
And as for Hosei and Endo
Rainbow Nihonbashika Chidugi
That's what I'm aiming for, Karen.
Rainbow bridge
I don't think Karen would say Kachidugibashi
And Matsumoto-san, right?
Matsumoto-san, you're a little old.
Matsumoto-san was talking about Nihonbashi
Matsumoto-san, you're a little bit old
That's why kachidugibashi
I told you I knew it was a drama or something.
And the drama also uses Matsumoto-san
Big chance to get everyone together in Nihonbashi
as it turns out
On the other hand, Hamada's team, which already has 3 members, has
Kachidugibasi
Kachidugi Nipponbashi Rainbow Bridge
And for the other three
And for the joker
That's right, isn't it?
So if you go to the same place as the joker
we have to break up immediately
because Nihonbashi is a bad place
I think Mr. Ebisu is going to come to Nihonbashi
That's right.
Mr. Ebisu doesn't come to the Rainbow Bridge
Shall we go to the Rainbow Bridge?
I'm going to go to the Rainbow Bridge to avoid the Joker.
Rainbow Bridge in the general survey
Nihonbashi Kachidougibashi three rulers
Where to choose
Kato, on the other hand, wants to meet Hamada and his friends
When they come to the bridge
Kato who wants to meet the bridge is
I'm not familiar with the bridge
Oh no.
The most I could think of was the Rainbow Bridge
It's a bridge called Nihonbashi
Bridge No.1 Bridge
Difficult bridgeDifficult bridge
what is it?
bridge
Yes
Okay, I'm off.
Kato's choice was
Tanaka, who has no idea what to do
How many, for example?
One is
Linked bridge
Now that's the only place that's really under control for now
Well, let's head over there.
Tanaka is still off
Nihonbashi
If you went to match
Nihonbashi, I personally would say Bay Bridge
Bay Bridge
But it's a little too big
A little bit too big for the Bay Bridge
Except for Tanaka, who is all over the place
Big chance for everyone to meet at the Rainbow Bridge
Joker Ebisu's move of interest
This time he seems to be lost in some sort of confusion
It's a big bridge
This is a famous bridge.
It is a famous big bridge.
Famous bridge
The bridge that Joker Ebisu chose is?
Matsumoto arrives at Nihonbashi
You're here
Nihonbashi bridge
Well, here we are!
Takizawa is in trouble
I don't think I'm going to see her.
I don't think we're going to see each other again, even if we're in Deluxe.
Takizawa is headed for...
Wait a minute
I think I might be kind of awesome.
Matsumoto-san is here
Matsumoto
Yes, that's right.
Yay!
It's the only place to be.
I didn't think I'd meet Takizawa.
I said to myself, "Matsumoto-san, this is the only place for me.
It's the only place for me.
Where else is there?
I knew I was saying this
But only Takizawa
Iseya-san
To be honest, I think he's already gone home.
The bridge that Iseya chose is
Oh, wow!
Oh, thank goodness
You're slow, you're slow
Good, good
Bravo bravo
I thought she was definitely not coming here
I'm not her, but I'm sure she's not there
I thought she was in Rainbow-Bridge
Oh, thank God.
Good
And they've got two of them on the other side.
I can't win.
Matsumoto-Takizawa-Iseya join together successfully
Hamada Team vs.
Hamada and his team of three arrive at Rainbow Bridge
Can you meet up with them?
Wow I don't know - I don't know
who is that?
That's Ryoke!
That's amazing!
as called
No, it's amazing
Yay!
Yay
Good job
There he is.
Why the Rainbow-Bridge?
Rainbow Bridge is the only one I could think of.
I thought, "This is definitely the place.
That's great.
Look, Tanaka's not here.
That's right.
After all, it's Tanaka, right?
Tanaka has not seen any of his friends so far
Chopsticks of your choice
And it's really starting to get late in the day already.
I think they're already here.
Until just now, Iseya was
I'm going to tell you that chopsticks are quite a problem.
I'm serious
Mr. Tanaka
Tanaka-san.
Nice to meet you
How do you do?
He's alone.
You're on your own again.
I'm sorry you're having a hard time.
We're a team now.
I'm surprised you made it down there.
This is the 5 o'clock team.
If you hold Karen
I've got her.
Even the blue team was worried
Karen's out of control, and this is going to hold her down.
Time is up here.
Time is up here
Wow, this is serious
Well, well, well, well, well, you've worked harder than most.
Good work
Where are Endo and Yamazaki?
Katsutoki-bashi.
Katsutoki Bridge.
No, no, no
Where do you think Tokyo started?
I knew it.
I knew it
Nihonbashi, right?
Yes.
That's the only way.
What?
Where is she?
It's in Nihonbashi
Yay, yay
Matsumoto-san and Karen-chan meet?
And now all three of them are here.
Yay!
you
I knew it was the Nihonbashi bridge!
That's a good boy-less
Tanaka-kun
Yes, this is Tanaka
Where are you?
Nihonbashi
Ah!
Where is everybody?
Everybody's here except you.
Uh...
There it is, there it is.
They're all here.
Except me.
You're lying, they're all here.
I knew it was you.
Rainbow Bridge
Yay, the Rainbow Bridge!
Yes!
Why did you do that?
Tanaka
There's a guy called Ebisu-san
He's going to come to Nihonbashi.
Oh, yes.
Indeed.
I've already seen a couple of people who look like Ebisu-san
In Nihonbashi
Now with both teams split into two groups
In other words, we are reaching to the all-against-all situation
What I want to know is
Where the joker Ebisu is going
In
All I care about is
It's a joker
Yes, you're all waiting for me
Ebisu-san's joker...
Somewhere where you all are
Somewhere
somewhere
no!
We are on our way
Stop, stop, stop
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
what
When you come to the same place, break up
Where the Joker of Fear Ebisu is headed
The Joker, though
Somewhere where you all are
We are on our way
What?
Stop, stop, stop.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
one or the other
no
What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Number 11
Eh?
Wait, wait, wait.
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
No kidding
It's here, it's here
You're lying.
No way.
The Joker is on the Rainbow Bridge
Yay!
Oh, my God.
Wow!
Sorry about that.
Yay!
Sleepy-feet
You were angry
That's scary.
They were broken up by the joker
Hamada team
Can they get together again on the next subject?
The next subject is
The big park
Large park
Yes
Yes?
Big park
Large park
Hamada team is again on their own
Aiming for the big park
Mr. Ito
We're back to square one
Actually, in Tokyo
There are a lot of big parks
Where are they going?
And then, poof!
I'm in Yoyogi
Yoyogi Park
But you can't shake Ebisu-san
Ebisu-san scares me.
I feel like Ebisu-san is not coming
I don't.
I will.
OK
Okay, Hamada-san
Big park
I'm so disappointed.
Well, I'll tell you what, though
The one that comes to mind is
Komatsuzawa or Yoyogi
It's not Komatsuzawa
Oh.
But this is a park
but this is a park
at Komatsuzawa Park
Komatsuzawa Park
Who's going to come?
Tanaka
Is this going to end?
Is it over?
Um...
It's a park where you're allowed to have fireworks
It's a park where you can set off fireworks
And there
We did fireworks last year
Yes, we did.
I just came up with
That's a park.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a big park.
Tanaka is
You've been to Ueno Park once today
Down at the museum
Tanaka is going through that process.
Once again
I have a feeling we're going to Ueno Park.
I think I'm going to Ueno Park.
I'd be glad if I managed to meet up with Tanaka first.
I think it's a good idea.
So
We're going to go to Ueno Park
Ueno Park.
And then
The #1 Problem: Tanaka
I'm on a pretty good line.
Mr. Tanaka himself
That opposing team and no luck.
I don't know.
That's why I'm
What I would have liked to have done if I had done the red team
yes, it would have been better if I had been on the red team
I'm right with Matsumoto-san on the second shot.
Hosei-san, you're in sync with Endo-san
With Iseya-san
I was also right with Karen.
I'm i sync with all of them
I'm going to make a pointless miracle
Tanaka keeps on connecting
All members of the red team
That's right.
Wait a minute, it's a park.
Odaiba Kaishin Park
Hibiya Park
Inokashira Park
Where are we headed next?
Hamada team key to the game
Tanaka's team
Meanwhile, they head for a certain park
The Matsumoto team
Well, but
No matter what you say to Karen, she's got it right.
that I was able to put my neck on.
I'm glad I was able to do that.
If I'd already been in the field, I'd have been
I don't know what it would have been like.
When you've already gone to the salt stop
I'm really
Where was I before the salt stop?
Opera City
Opera City I'm really
I was about to disappear.
I thought women liked museums.
You can't go to the museum, it's me.
Where are you going?
What are you interested in?
I'm pretty much interested in power pavilions and things like that.
For the first time in my life
I've heard of it.
Suryunyakt
Hey Iseya-kun something
I have no idea what he usually does
That's what I'm told.
I'll take Lendler.
I've never done it before.
Tigership
And then there's the movie.
I'm supposed to be doing a rendezvous.
Three or four months is
They're probably missing a bunch.
It's better if you think about it
And in the meantime, you can think of me and my company as
I heard it for the first time
I'm allowed to talk about that on TV.
Why is my business
Don't talk on TV
I'm in such bad business
It's a side business.
But what I'm thinking in my mind is
I'm thinking
Humanity's survival on earth
We're running a joint stock company
Did you notice that?
Only humans on the planet
think about what happens after you die
We can imagine it and act on it.
Which means that we are human beings
Proof is worrying about the future
And yet, after taking action
what is that?
I don't know, but I need to get out of this traffic jam.
Matsumoto's team is getting excited in the car
Meanwhile, Hamada's team
haaa
something about myself
Have you ever tried to figure out why you're still alive?
Yes, I have.
Yes, sir.
That's a lie.
It's more than that.
What do you think about a little bit of your future?
I'm always being asked to talk about it.
I'd like to hear what you have to say in between.
I'll be an interviewer
so on and so forth
Why don't you try it now?
You don't get many opportunities like this, Mr. Matsumoto.
NG = No Good
Almost no NG questions
You're almost never a person who doesn't have
Then.
My life is
How have you lived your life so far?
That's a NG
That's NG
the only one
You only get two, they say.
Then where did you get your clothes?
That's something different.
What I want when
Hey, it has been raining pretty hard.
I think we're getting there.
We're getting there now.
The park they came to in the rain
Uh huh.
Wait a minute.
How's that?
Yeah, that's right.
Mito Ward Shiba Park
Not there
I'm kind of in the rain with the wind like this
I can't believe I'm waiting for someone
I haven't done that in years.
I'm sure it's been years.
As night falls, the rain continues to fall
Come on Yamazaki, Endo for a minute.
Come on, Yamazaki, endo, come on.
Please, please, please.
about that time
please.
They're still on the move
Will the five of them make it?
Haruna Kawaguchi arrives at Komatsuba Park
around there
You're coming, Komatsuba Park.
There you go.
Ah!
Ita
long time no see
But...
There's no one here but me.
He's still not here.
More rapid development after this
that
Kawaguchi and Kato wait for their friends at Komatsuba Park
I think it's here
Is Ebisu still alive?
No, no, no, he's not dead.
Many, many times
It's effective, that power.
that
there
He's holding an umbrella
Yay!
Leader Hamada joins in beautifully
So the three of them are
Where's the manifold?
I doubt it.
At that time Pierre
Now
This is Ueno Park in Ichikabachika
National Museum of Western Art with writing
I think he'll come here, but it's not easy
Pierre's goal is to recover Tanaka, but
somewhere around here
Wait a minute.
There's no one around here at the moment.
Oh no.
Hey, can you do me a favor?
It's definitely Yoyogi Park.
They're already there.
Yes, this is Yoyogi Park
I can't think of anything else but Yoyogi
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on, somebody.
There you go.
There it is
Who is it, who is it, who is it
Ugh, joker
what the hell are you doing?
It's Mr. Joker Ebisu
It's you
Are you close?
I'm not saying we don't get along, not really.
They're just clinging to each other.
A little bit here.
Time is up
lie
Tanaka, where are you?
Where is the park?
I'm in Yoyogi Park
Yoyogi Park
I'm going to
I am in Ueno Park
Ueno park
Ueno Park
Yes
Here are the three of us.
Where are you three?
Komazawa Park
It's Komazawa Olympic Park
I miss you so much, I miss you so much.
I haven't missed you once.
That's right, I've never had sex with anyone.
you're not having sex with anyone
I'm not having sex with anybody.
I'm really lonely
Hello
We're at Island Park right now.
Yoyogi Park
Oh no, Yoyogi Park
Tanaka is also here
Tangawa is at Shinjuku Gyoen
Shinjuku Gyoen
You didn't go to that one?
I'm sorry.
Well, that's okay.
Okay, everybody.
please.
I just want to be done with this.
Please hang in there
Now for the next subject
I've got to stop for a second, end this, please.
Speaking of amusement parks
Uh huh.
amusement park
Speaking of amusement parks
No, this is already
I think it's the only way to go.
I'm sure it's a little tiny, but it's a little tiny
Akoyaro, we can play games, we can have a drink
I'm sure it's Akko
Okei-kata end of the line
I'm going to go
I think there's only one way to do it.
I think it's the only way
I'm confident
Please
No, I think that's the only way.
Yes!
Speaking of amusement parks
I see, shall we go?
Shall we go?
For the first time this day
Everyone immediately decides on a destination
Nope.
You definitely have to do it with the end or they'll come.
definitely coming
What will be the outcome of the game?
First to the destination
Hamada and three others arrive
Is that all you've got?
huh?
They chose
Tokyo Dome City Attractions
Kagurazono amusement park, a well-known and well-loved amusement park
The best theme park in Tokyo
No, they're coming.
They're coming.
They're gonna come
as one would expect
This is indeed coming
There you go
Oh, the red team
Oja oja oja
that
Three of them are here.
Good afternoon.
What's that? Oh, no, it's the enemy.
Oh, my God.
What?
It's just you guys
for now
Oh no, it's too tight now.
So that's the all that's left is Endo and Hosei, right
Yes, sir.
And we're waiting for Tanaka and Takiya
Hosei and Endo, the two of them are together
But I just checked in the cab.
and all the residents are there
Why don't you come over there, Mr. Ebisu?
We'll start from scratch again
No, I can't do it again.
Oh, give me a break on that one.
Give me a break on that one
I'll be the hero, I'll be the decider.
I'm really counting on you.
Oh, Taki
Ah, Taki
Taki
Good night
Now we just have to wait for Tanaka again.
We're just waiting for Tanaka
Tanaka, though
Yoyogi Park, you know.
If he doesn't come here, we're in trouble.
We're in trouble.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute
How many times am I
I mean, I'm the one who's worried now.
I mean, I'm worried that if everybody's already here
I think Mr. Ebisu is going to come too.
That's great.
No way this is going to end
Endo Hosei comes in
Matsumoto team wins or
Tanaka comes in
Hamada's team wins or
Ebisu comes in and no way
They all break up.
What's gonna happen?!
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute
Go ahead.
Come here.
Come on, please.
Okay, that's enough, that's enough.
And then
It's going, it's going, it's going, it's going
Yay!
Aaaaah!
After that
You were together the first time
Yes, I was.
At Yoyogi Park.
He's never been there before.
I've never been with any of them
What's with that guy this year?
What is he really doing this year?
He doesn't get along with everyone
Tanaka is
If it comes, where did it come from?
I'm Tanaka, I'm Tanaka
No, where are you?
I'm in Hanayashiki.
It's a hanayashiki, after all.
Correct correct correct correct
why?
Which is it, Hamada?
No, I mean, which is it?
All of them except you
There's the same place.
All of you
You're lying.
Where is it?
It's a public paradise.
It's Tokyo Dobe City
Korakuen
Korakuen, which means "public paradise" in Japanese
I had no idea.
Uh huh.
But
You're lying.
Oh, my God.
The joker, Mr. Ebisu...
I don't see him there
No, no, not again.
Mr. Ebisu, the joker...
I don't see him there
No, no, not again.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
There it is.
Mr. Ebisu was there
There he is!
Joker Ebisu went
to the flower house
Oh no
So
Congratulations to the Matsumoto team!
Yay!
And now, oh my goodness
The defeated Hamada team
I think that's a punishment for the leader
Why me?
Today
Cab fare for all
You must pay
approx.
200,000 yen
Exactly
You're paying half Tanaka, right?
No, I'm sorry about that.
Hamada
One
A fine purse
Hamada's
Ehh.
I'm absolutely disgusted.
I'm done with you, sir.
We're done for.
It's already raining
Thank you for your hard work
I'm sorry
Oh no
High paradise
independence
Guest Haruna Kawaguchi
Drama Aishitakatta Himitsu ha Aru
I can't believe I've been lied to my whole life
I want you to tell me the truth.
Airs every Sunday night at 10:30 p.m.
And
Yusuke Iseya is
The movie in which he appears
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamonds Are Unbreakable Chapter 1 is
Available from August 4
Great