A quadrennial celebration still fresh in our minds
It was also a battle to challenge one's own eyes
And here is another man who challenges the once-every-four-years battle
First time on Gaki no Tsukai Arahende Chiki Chiki Endo Takeshi no Limit Challenge
Non-Stop Water Slide
That's what this project is about, but before we do that, I'm going to let you all watch Mr. Irie for a moment.
He's been waiting a long time like this.
It's like male destiny.
like a man's destiny
Let's welcome today's star of the show, please.
I'm sorry about today, but thank you so much for doing this for me.
Endo, you had a fever last night
It was 38.4 degrees
A little bit, yesterday.
You had a fever that high, and you're going to do this record?
The last time I did this, four years ago, as Takeshi, I did it for an hour, and I was very happy to do it for you.
Four years ago in the same season
He challenged to imitate Takeshi for 1 hour continuously and achieved the world record!
This time, I'll imitate Takeshi and go on a water slide nonstop.
I wanted to challenge myself to see how many times I can do it in front of you all.
I'd like to try a little before someone else does it.
I hope to manage to set another great record.
Someone heard about this challenge and sent you a comment of support.
A message of support for Endo Takeshi from that person.
Congratulations from Osuki-san
The last time he cheered for Beatiku City, he said he achieved a world record
Endo also set a new world record this time.
I want to cheer him on when he slides down the waterslide while imitating Beat Takeshi.
I'm thinking like this, but speaking of Beat Takeshi, one week later...
This is it.
Outrageous days
In the last Outrage, there was a lot of talk about the dirtbags.
And this time, we're going to add to that.
It's a storm of the earth as an event because it's a Kansai dialect and a Kanto dialect.
He's some kind of a man who does something stupid, you son of a bitch.
Don't talk about this now, right, Beat Takeshi?
I'd love to do it.
I'd like to wait for the cinema
I'll do it really soon
Well, maybe President Mori understands the intent of this project.
Thank you very much.
Endo Takeshi's challenge takes place on a 146-meter-long waterslide
The rules are quite simple
All you can do is to keep on sliding while imitating Takeshi-san
The challenge ends when he reaches his limit and returns to Endo Shozo
Endo Takeshi, The curtain opens on an unknown challenge
This is the starting point
Once you get past that point, the clock starts turning.
I see.
That's quite a slide.
That's right.
It's not a small one.
It's the height, it's this one.
Now, if we can get past the start
He's twitching even before he crossed the start.
It's okay to still be Endo there.
He just noticed that and went back to normal.
It's so obvious.
That's right.
Once you go over, you start
Start
Can be done many times
Yes, you can.
Come on, Dankan.
Don't do Dankan.
Come on, man.
The slope
All right.
Slope
Yo-yo
You're doing something.
Tamaneshi
Pretty plinkly.
It's done right.
He's finally doing it.
he's finally doing it.
I think it's going to be a while
I'm working on it.
You're doing it.
This is
It's going to be harsh.
And love is bad, too.
Finally down to
Here we are.
With a temp of 38.4 degrees
That's right.
And last night it was mixed blood.
Are those underwear gonna be okay?
If you're close enough to support me
No good.
How old is Takeshi Endo now?
41.
We're the youngest.
He's the youngest.
We are the youngest
Youngest Takeshi
Skating through the first run without any problems
Takeshi Endo returns to the start
This is tough.
He has to climb back up.
This may be the toughest
I know what you mean.
An enemy that unnecessarily takes away your physical strength
Stairs
Stairs counting 82 steps are
Its height is
Equivalent to the fifth floor of a building
Of course
And during this time
You can also check the falling mirror later.
Takeshi's moniker.
He must continue
That's not so bad.
He's coming up.
I can still see one.
What are these stairs?
I'll have time to look up the falling mirror later.
Here he comes, here he comes.
You stepped on something.
From ahead
Takeshi, when it falls a little more
A little more
The monster staircase.
They come along
Yes, sir.
A little more
Are you all right, Takeshi?
You were fast this time.
As they say, "I knew it.
Right here.
The best place to show
he's going to stop.
Totally stopped
He stopped
I'm sure you don't use that much stamina, but...
But it's high stamina.
Something like a lump or something.
something like that
because there was
So there's 8.4 bars.
You don't know if there might be more.
I don't know what it is.
I think they put something like that.
I see.
There's all kinds of phrases and stuff.
That's not the point, generally.
It's just a normal face.
I wonder if he's dropping something.
That's the second time.
He's rushing out a little bit.
Yes, that's right.
Looks like we're still good to go.
Pace.
I can't pick up the pace.
I think he might have a little shoulder injury.
I see.
For this record.
They're not the same.
Picking up the pace
Tackle the third waterslide.
Same as the second run
Too much movement
Not fast enough
So from Hamada
of how to ski that leads to increased speed.
The suggestion is
Why don't you go straight down again, Mr. Takeshi?
If you don't move funny
That's what Taka told me earlier.
Yeah, that's right.
You're angry.
I'm not angry.
Are you angry?
I was told.
what is this?
Fourth run, with new advice
Gone.
He's going straight.
Straight ahead.
Smoother than before
Just so-so
It doesn't feel like Takeshi, though.
It's all gone at once.
That's about as much as I could do.
Good speed
Speed is good.
After 15 minutes
Just 4 runs
I'm not going to let you walk alone with you.
He's a little concerned about his shoulder.
Yes, yes, yes.
I think there is a possibility that there is something wrong.
This is just the beginning.
No, it's heavy.
Ah.
Oh, I'm right, I'm right, I'm right.
I didn't find a good one, you son of a bitch.
what the hell?
Originally this.
I heard you should do this, you son of a bitch.
What's wrong with your shoulder?
A little to the right.
I'm doing a light right.
I'm still doing it
I told you to use this, you son of a bitch.
Who told you that?
Nodarukanotaka's wife said.
And the salt water
deadweight
I don't think I'm going to say much about wife hun
1st class
Fifth challenge on a inner tube
Oh, this is fast, fast
Oh, that's great, that's great, that's great, that's great
Oh, wow, wow, wow
wow
This is good.
Oh, wow.
I like that.
Kind of.
a little bit
I'm having fun.
This is good.
You son of a bitch.
You're a Takeshi.
Nobody's here.
son of a bitch
You're the one with the righteous daisy
You've got to support me on the side.
Takeshi Endo goes to the tent at the bottom of the stairs.
Naturally, among them
I'm not kidding.
If you don't hurry up, I'll be waiting for you.
They never stop imitating you.
And after this
A new Endo Takeshi
that
It's taking a little bit of time.
There's something going on, isn't there?
a little bit like this
you know what?
oh
Matsuda-san...
Because you're late.
Sorry.
I'm not kidding.
I know you're coming back.
So you're going to keep going.
So you're going to go like this?
It's going to sell.
It's not easy to sell clothes.
Get a grip, you son of a bitch.
Get off my back, you son of a bitch.
Did you have any friends in the picture?
Oh, I like that.
Takeshi
Yes, yes, yes.
There's nothing to put in
what are you talking about?
When you fall
Zapper water blasted
That's good, you son of a bitch.
it's gone.
I don't like it.
Waterslide at Takeshi-san
I know I did something like this.
That's a lot of work, isn't it?
But he wants to do it.
That's heavy.
Even after this
Nice Christmas
Wearing a costume associated with a Takeshi
The challenge continued
Wearing an outfit associated with a Takeshi
Sorry.
what the hell is wrong with you guys?
Come on, Takeshi, this way.
Let's do it.
let's do it
Asbase.
Arr.
Ah!
Ah
And for the members who are watching the challenge
This is the kind of service
Here comes the pure white one.
How about some shaved ice?
How about shaved ice
The water is too noisy
I can't hear you.
shaved ice
how about this
wow!
All right.
Cold.
I know, I know, I know
I know.
You should be turning the car around by now.
Get ready to turn the car around.
Dankan and I are still turning cars.
I'm still the master
eh
I don't know.
Come on.
You.
I was mad at you.
That picture.
what's going on?
You're...
You
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Come on.
what do you think?
what about
ah ah ah ah ah
Let's go for the one that says so and so.
It's coming out pretty strong. 10 slips so far, 45 minutes have passed.
Because it's definitely debilitating, but it never stops going.
I wonder what he's going to write up so much - I'm starting to be impressed.
Kid kOffin so etted
Lesson: I'm sure they're going to say, dah
Oh, my God!
hmm
Ajisumi
I'm out.
If you put a noodle on top of a noodle and it comes out like that, it's important.
That's right.
Are you okay?
He drank some water.
You can't tell because you're wearing noodles.
What an idiot.
what is that?
I'm going to do 40 more.
Forty more.
Forty.
Target 50 slides
That's great.
That's an amazing record at this point.
That's it.
forgetting a little bit of footwear.
But you can see the shape of this
Why do you come here and forget your footwear?
Right.
No, it's not.
I'm doing many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many.
None of the corps are coming in.
Dankan
Taka
Kita-Yurakubashi Bridge
Edamame
I didn't come, mostly.
Pine tree at the shrine
I've never even heard from the pine tree at the shrine.
for three years
extra
It's a float, so you can keep it in.
Hey, hey, hey, it's a trip.
I don't think so.
You're fine.
still in good health
still going strong
I've got it
He won't stop
I think we're close to the limit
Still, two slips in a row in this outfit
In the first 1 hour and 20 minutes
15 water slides
Definitely close to Endo Takeshi's
physical strength limit
15 times
I don't know if the person who says that would say it's not enough.
I mean, you know, when you see it like this.
It's not so bad.
You can't casually say it's not much.
I was never very good at imitating the Takeshi.
He is
He's not good at it.
It's not that similar.
I guess it must be harsh.
It's harsh.
He got hit in the right shoulder and hit his head.
He has a fever.
Fever is out, too, and they don't look alike.
I think it's harsh.
Even as the sun sets
Endo Takeshi's challenge continued
What is this?
Yes, that's it.
Anyway, it's easy to understand
Not so bad
Thank you for waiting
Let's go for it
Anyone else with questions
Question Corner
I'm going to keep trying and trying and trying.
I'm going for it.
what the hell are you talking about?
He's not talking He's not talking
Cleaning is the best cleaning
cleanest cleaning
cleaning first
We're going forward.
He says who is the black devil
Who is the Black Devil?
Who's on a waterslide high
Despite Endo Takeshi's efforts
The number of members' mouths were extremely decreased
It's like she's becoming a child about twice a week.
To my daughter.
I wonder what she would say about today.
I guess I'll have to summarize a lot.
You're not well.
Hello
You like water slides?
Members who like water slides
I got Akats
I got akats
how about that?
Matsumoto, what are we going to do?
I think that's enough.
I want to repeat it.
Yes, it's a repetition.
I don't know who it is.
that's right.
Shall we go home now?
That's really
You and I need to talk to each other.
Yes, sir.
Tanaka talked to Endo today.
I called for something else
What the hell is this?
Even if you're alone
The challenge that never stops
What is this crap?
Oh, man.
I think they've gone home.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I'm not looking at you.
Takeshi's imitation.
I've been able to keep going this far because I've been able to
There was a reason.
The last word
Takeshi-san, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'm super mistyped.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
Thank you
Takeshi Endo's challenge has come to an end.
And then
thank you
That wasn't so bad.
I'll call Okamoto in a bit.
The president.
In everyone's view, your impressions aren't similar at all.
I'm sorry.
Sorry
I'm sorry, but I'm not sure which manager I'm talking about.
I think it's going to change
laughter