Tonight's Gaki no Tsukai will challenge you to see if you can do the exact same location three times!
The rule is that once you have done a completely free location, you have to do it three times.
You have to do a second and third location with the same content, relying only on your own memory.
The first location start where we have to remember what we did as soon as possible
Not great weather, but we'll do our best.
Oh, it's Cocorico.
Greetings
Excuse me.
With seat belts
Good morning
Greetings
please
That's great, but, you know, the weather.
Somehow.
Hosei, you're driving.
Isn't this car easy to drive?
Hosei
Matsumoto is next
Yay!
Is this for the passenger seat?
Yes.
Good morning
The smell of Osmanthus.
Seasonal
It's autumn
Maybe because I was born in September.
I think it's because I was born then.
You know, Osmanthus.
Why can't you say anything?
Hosei doesn't talk much.
That's what I've been saying.
He's not talking at all.
Even cab drivers talk a little more
If you're having this kind of Osmanthus conversation
Yes, this is Hamada
Like here
Good morning.
Good morning
What's your reaction now?
No, it's because the car in front of you just pulled up and tried to put you in front of it.
What the hell did you do that for?
It looks like there's some kind of complicated one on it.
No, no, no
You've got the other side.
No, no, no, no, no.
So there's a complicated one standing there.
We're all here.
Oh, Yamazaki is driving.
That's right this time.
Where are you going, Hosei, now?
No, you can already see it.
Here we are.
That one.
What is this?
Uh huh.
High paradise
Gorakuen Amusement Park
Amusement park
High Paradise Amusement Park
OH!
Here's that indoor facility for little kids to play.
Like  Mehtaka.
No, you know what?
It's really for kids up to about four or five years old, you know.
Mehtaka is would play upstairs.
You don't even play up there.
We're here.
Yes, we're here.
Arriving at Tokyo Dome City, our destination this time
It's still very open.
No, just the last one.
No, I thought I did it.
I thought I did it.
That's not good anymore.
What the hell is that?
No, no, no.
You're a grown up.
I thought I'd done it, but I've got this.
I thought I did this.
They bought a free pass to ride the attractions and
Go to the park as soon as possible
Too hungry?
A small stomach is
There is a crepe shop
Yes, there is.
I'll do it with Hamada's favorite banana-chocolate custard.
I love it!
you love it
You like bananas, you like chocolate, you like custard, you have it all.
But they don't have fresh cream.
If that's the case, this is better.
banana chocolate cake
Cake
Hosei and Endo also have the same banana chocolate cake special as Hamada's
Tanaka has almond chocolate
Matsumoto has a cheese crepe
Order the rope scattering pepper cheese
I guess the same one is faster?
I can't finish at all.
Oh, it's more like the same one.
Well, more and more kinds.
I love crepes!
You can add more whipped cream.
That's a waste of money when you can't eat that much.
I can't say I can't eat it, though.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Then I'll double it.
That's not good.
Crepes sukkah
You're a bad guy.
I don't know what's wrong with him.
yes thank you
Los Angeles
We'll eat sitting down
Receive the crepe you ordered
Like this so and so
Eating on the bench
Yes, I have.
I've never had crepes for everyone.
Crepes sukkah
Delicious
You know what?
I'll be honest with you, I probably would have preferred everyone's dessert sense.
I think we're getting a little bit of a meal now.
Shall we go home?
Come on.
Let's go home.
We've had enough fun.
Let's get on something and go home.
Let's ride something
Let's get one Viking ride.
One person rides?
Everyone rides together
That's impossible.
Where is the "impossible" part?
I want to wow and ride.
I really want to
Matsumoto can go away
I'll go that way.
If the loser rides
Matsumoto, the loser rides?
Because I am.
I can't get on it in the first place.
So you can't get on in the first place.
Not even close.
You can do me too.
I'll do it then.
I'll do it too.
Matsumoto, that way and hoi polloi
Practice
Matsumoto, that way and hoi
I'm sorry, I don't know who's watching.
I'm not the only one who sees it.
I'm not the judge.
I can't believe you're a delegate.
I'm deciding who out of the three of us is going to ride.
So you've already decided who the three of you are going to be.
is that right?
Matsumoto, that way and three people
Hamada then
Matsumoto Matsumoto
Face away, face away
face that way
Safe
Matsumoto Matsumoto
face that way
Oh, please.
Uh-huh.
out
Can I have one Tanaka?
No, I'm fine with just Tanaka.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
In the end, Tanaka is the only one.
to ride on the attraction
Hands in the air
Cocorico Tanaka go for it!
Aaaaah!
Uh-oh
I wonder what this is...
I think it's a sub-in.
That was a docudrama.
how did it go?
I was so scared.
And I never want to ride it again.
I'm too scared
So much for this.
No, you can't do this.
No, no, no, no
I can't, I can't, I can't
The details are really
Okay, that's enough.
Like a car door.
Ask for it and leave it open
That's the first time I've ever seen something like that
I mean the easy-to-understand ones.
And now
no matter how heavy the rain comes
I don't get crunched.
Is that bad, too?
To do a second location
To the starting point again
Wow, weird
Oh, I see.
It's like this.
Point to point
I'll have them look over here.
You right there.
I know I'm going to lose something.
There you go.
yes.
If Matsumoto doesn't remember, someone else is going to lose.
I think it was probably in that order.
I'm trying hard to remember now.
I love crepes
The challenge is to see if you can do the exact same location three times.
Start the second location
The weather is not so good
Let's go for it.
Cocorico
Good morning
please.
That was good today.
Good luck with the weather.
I see Hosei is driving this time.
This car is so easy to drive.
This car is so easy to drive
I love this car!
Matsumoto
Oh, there it is
ah, ita ita ita ita
this boarding house is fine
Is it okay if I sit in the boss's seat?
Thank you very much.
Thank you
I'm sorry
Oh, no.
That's a great scent of Osmanthus.
Osmanthus?
Mm-hmm.
Um...
It's my birth name.
Wow, that's something.
That's sensitive.
especially in the year that that Japan was born.
considerably
You don't talk at all.
What's wrong with you?
I'm not a driver.
You're a cab driver, not the other way around.
I'll get in on Osmanthus.
There's Hamada
It's really him.
main building
ita ita ita ita ita ita
ah
thanks for your time
thank you
What's going on?
You scared the hell out of me.
Oh, it's like it's suddenly on my side.
It's not like they're coming to me.
Yeah.
It's all black.
What kind of complicated thing are you riding?
Well, it's a complicated one over there, too.
I guess it's a bit of an oxymoron
What's going on?
They're all here.
Yeah.
yeah
Where are we going?
Yeah.
here we are
hmm?
Where?
What was that?
Coramin' Winds or
Ah, Coramin Winds
There's something for little kids to play with.
Like  Mehaka.
Yes.
Do you have a child of about four or five years old, budtaka, playing up there?
I guess they don't play.
We're here!
Oh!
We're here, we're here.
Arriving at Tokyo Dome City, our destination this time
Ah, go, go, go, go
You're the last one, Tanaka.
I thought I closed it.
Oh, no.
How much of a spoiled child are you?
I'm sorry, I thought I closed it.
I don't think so.
You can buy a free pass to ride the attractions and
Go to the park as soon as possible
Are you feeling hungry?
I'm a little hungry.
ah, something to eat
There's a crepe shop.
Crepe?
Mm-mm-mm
Let's eat crepes.
Crepes.
Hamada banana chocolate custard.
All banana, chocolate, custard, you like them all.
No, no, no, no
You can all eat now.
They don't have any whipped cream.
Then get a normal one.
Uh, standard.
Delicious, delicious
Delicious
Hosei and Endo also have the same banana chocolate cake as Hamada
Tanaka has almond chocolate
Matsumoto has a cheese crepe
Order sand scattered pepper cheese
Tanaka, what is this?
What's this?
Oh, you can increase the amount of whip cream.
And then you can increase it from 2x to 3x to 4x and so on.
No, no, no, no, no
But double it.
I love crepes
I did it right there.
That's right.
In the first accounting
Los Angeles
Embroidered on Tanaka's clothes that we all messed with.
Los Angeles letters
As a result, this time
I love crepes
In the end, they still can't remember Tanaka's Los Angeles
and pick up there crepes and go to the bench
delicious
In the first round
How is it?
Hamada hits Matsumoto who doesn't comment on the taste
And then
And here we go.
Let's go home.
Matsumoto suddenly says, "Let's go home"
Will he be able to reproduce it?
Maybe the first time we all ate crepes together.
Yes, that's right.
Itadakimasu
Delicious
not good
something like this dessert
Something like dessert would have been better.
I thought it was a little bit like a meal.
Crepes are a thing, aren't they?
Isn't that a ride?
What?
Let's get on the Viking
I can't. I can't.
Gradually, the Vikings are no longer
Wait a minute.
Let's do it with the photographer.
All right, let's do it with the photographer.
Matchan, let's turn around and eat.
I'll go that way and take care of you
I'll turn around and point to you.
That is, if Matsumoto loses
I won't do it.
I'm just going to do it.
I'll do it.
Practice on how many
Matchan, Matchan, Matchan, turn around.
Then I can't see it either.
I'm watching.
I'll keep an eye on it.
I'll take a look.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
We'll do it.
You guys see who gets on.
I mean, get out there and do it.
Are these three people decided?
I'll take a look.
Matchan, Matchan, Matchan, look away...
Oh, safe
Matchan, Matchan, Matchan, turn around
Matchan, Matchan, Matchan, turn that way
Oh, safe
Matchan, Matchan, turn around
Oh.
Tanaka!
oh!
me
1st time
Immediately after Tanaka loses
No, just one Tanaka, please.
No, I'm fine with just Tanaka.
Tanaka alone is fine.
Matsumoto says just one Tanaka
Can it be reproduced?
What do you want me to do?
No, I'm fine on my own.
That's all right, I'll take one.
One more person, please, at least one more person.
please.
No, no, no
That's right.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, Tanaka Ike
Tanaka is the only one who ends up riding the attraction
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
how did you do?
I was so scared.
I never wanted to ride it again.
Yes, sir.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
That was pretty good.
You all remember it so well.
You remember.
You forgot one thing on the crepe stand.
That one.
I remember one of mine.
I think it's Tanaka's Los Angeles.
And that's what Tanaka noticed at the bottom of the market.
Yeah.
I think I did almost perfect except for that one.
Yes, yes, yes.
You've finished eating your crepe and you're ready to go home.
That's a great readout.
You've been looking at it for a long time.
You've been watching Matsumoto the whole time.
So that's how it is.
Wasn't it a little bad there?
Matsumoto that way
I don't get it.
Wrong name.
hahahahahaha
The music and the front are out
I think I can do it perfectly next time
I think I can do that.
And the next one is perfect.
Start of the third last challenge
How about you, Matsumoto?
Isn't this car easy to drive?
Good morning
It smell's great, Osmanthus.
Osmanthus?
What's the smell of flowers on the month you were born?
It's kind of a bottle feeling.
You don't talk at all
This smell of Osmanthus is something an cab driver would talk about.
It's Hamada.
Good morning
how's it going?
Suddenly my car
Because I came to a black car.
It's dangerous.
You're driving a complicated car.
They're driving a forward-looking, complicated car over there.
No, it's not.
There's a place for little kids to play.
Indoor
like Mehtaka
A really small child like that who is four or five years old.
Mehtaka will be playing up there, but
I guess he won't play.
Our destination this time
Arrive at Tokyo Dome City
You left the door open for a bit
That's Tanaka, right?
I thought I closed that one right.
I thought I closed it correctly.
I'm sorry.
Five people who are reproducing perfectly so far.
Will they succeed?
Are you hungry?
There's that Tanaka's crepe, though.
Crepe.
Tapioca drink or something like that.
Hamada something like this is good.
Cinnamon apple cream
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
No, I'm really sorry.
I'm so sorry about that.
banana
Banana, it's darker than you think.
I'm getting a little senile.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Then this is really sorry
Really.
This lighting is
And after that
same amount
Wrong.
They forgot the words and deeds that they took
and make a series of mistakes
Early
No, no, no.
The managed to get to the end, but
There were three points
not reproduced
What the hell is that guy?
Oh, no, no, no
yes, do it!
This is what you get in a lotteries.
That's right.
Why don't we do it again in a year?
Let's see if you remember.
One year later.
Exactly the same thing.