You're making the staff pay attention to you, aren't you, Hamada?
You know, your last comment really made this whole place soft and fluffy.
It's about the same as before
Originally, these are also fluffy.
Fluffy shoulders, right?
It's too fluffy, isn't it?
It's not balanced
It's like a john bar.
It's so hard.
It's so painful.
It's not like that, you know, we're all still together.
I guess it's just Hamada-san.
Was it really hard?
what the hell?
This is already soft.
I don't think so, it's just thin here.
You've got thin skin, too.
It's there, but...
It's like an ostrich's neck, right?
It's disgusting.
Is it really that delicate?
You can't do that to your buttocks.
If we keep doing it for a while, we'll get it, too.
You don't get used to it.
It's like igodi.
I'm going to shift a little bit while I'm talking, just in case.
I'm still not feeling well this week, so I'm off.
You're you, you're you, you're you, you're something again.
That's right, Yamazaki.
I'm a little sorry about this one again.
It's a bunch of nose hairs.
Nose hairs in bunches
Left side great, left side
It's like a brush pen.
I was sick, so I can't help it.
Don't point your finger.
You can write "congratulations"
You can write that.
I'm going to get a bunch of people to come at me.
Please don't do that.
You should have left it in there.
I'm just trying to give you a little bit of an image.
I don't know, maybe it was in bed.
He said he fell asleep.
He was hospitalized.
I took four days off.
You weren't hospitalized?
He's not in the hospital, he's in the hospital, he's a natural enemy.
The previous one.
Previous
What happened with your intestines?
It's called colonic heartbreak.
Even though this one flows well too.
Only the name of the junior's disease and where he lives.
I can't remember at all.
Yes, indeed.
You're not interested in basic interest after all.
I've heard it a million times.
I don't even know where Tanaka lives.
I know, I've been asked that a lot.
I've answered it many times.
I know you don't have any real feelings today.
So is age.
Like saying keyed unexpectedly.
You know how old we are.
I mean, he's younger than Yamazaki.
Is he younger than Yamazaki?
Bingo!
I don't know how old you are...
You asked Mr. Zaki, didn't you?
I'm sorry, but the hair hasn't subsided at all.
Let's put it away
I'm back today, so I want to go with tone.
I don't want to be called a nage or something like that.
I'd do it in a chain.
Finally, stop it.
Don't do it, don't do it
Be gentle.
You're sick, you're sick
It's called colorectal system performance
What does that mean?
I know exactly what it means when I hear it over and over again
I don't know what's going to happen in the end.
It's a hole in your gut.
It doesn't matter.
You're smiling.
You're laughing so hard.
I don't know why it doesn't matter.
It's all right, it's all right
what's the worst that can happen?
what's the worst that can happen if a hole opens up
Honesty in the belly
The shit is going in.
It's really painful.
It must be painful.
Like, which one's going to ring.
I don't know.
There's a possibility that they're all going to ring.
It was a little bit like a he was crying wolf.
He gets hurt easily by the smallest things.
You know what I mean.
I'm not sure if it's true or not.
That's the kind of character that can help you.
Actually, I had a really bad stomach ache last week, too.
The reaction
That's the one to roast and pull.
I did it, but I had a really bad stomach ache that time, actually.
But today, when I said I had a stomach ache, I just said, "I have a stomach ache.
And everyone said, "Oh, no, not again...
I knew it.
I thought you were in bad shape.
But that's not what I meant.
I thought it was going bad over here.
You were in totally good shape.
You managed to hold it this way.
I wasn't feeling well, but...
You were in bad shape.
And then I went back to burdocking for a while.
I really need to show the filmmakers that I'm really a filmmaker, too.
I think it was on the day.
Yamaoka came in on the same day
Moriyama and Kobo are drunk
He looks bad.
Yes, they do.
Bad face
Said it, said it, said it
Oh no, tell me you didn't.
Well, well, well, until the day it happens.
Really?
I really don't know
I really don't know, let me discover a little bit.
You're not a performer.
You are not a performer.
No, no, of course not.
No, of course not.
What? What? You knew?
I don't know. I don't know.
I really don't know either
I don't know
Don't know, of course
That's because I'm already trying to find out who did it.
I'm going to be thorough.
This is so thorough
It's amazing how they start moving before you can say gobo.
It's like he knew.
Like they knew... momentary.
I already told you how I knew.
Hamada's then the last battle
That's it
in Piccolo
So you got that tone.
You got that tone
No, it's good.
That's great.
That's the real deal.
And that's it.
You're already coming back to life.
But there's a lot of things going on.
I don't think it's anything but burdock root.
I don't know, the tone, the way you say it...
It's all in the tone and the way it's said.
I can already tell.
This is a burdock
This is amazing
burdock root
But still... but still...
burdock root compatibility
This is already really
It's like caviar on the Ritz.
This bitter about as much as Ritz and caviar...
Here it comes.
That's the only one.
Because it's the only one that comes quick.
We want to see it.
We're probably partitioned by burro
I knew it was going to be like that.
It's not going to happen.
It will be.
No, it does not
The cat's with the burdock
what just happened?
I just heard a click.
And now
of the door for a moment.
I'd like to see this continue.
I really, really want you to keep doing that.
I'm even holding an elephant.
To the sapphire
elephant
Yes, yes, yes.
I ran away from Bwah.
I was running away, and when I turned the corner, poof!
I could see the ring.
There it is.
Yes, I have it
False.
I didn't know that was there.
I'm going to go for another round.
I've already done enough.
You've done the real target ring.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Surprise, surprise.
Is your voice okay, voice?
Are you going to be a little bit casseled?
voice
Voice time
Finger clattering
Okay...
You have to go that deep.
You've done a lot of skinny-dipping.
No, that's it.
That's great.
I've never had a voice time like that before.
No, but it was the first time in human history
With bare hands.
Even I'm more than the doer.
Of other people, of other people, of other people's throats.
You can't put a finger like that down someone's throat.
I hate it.
I'd rather they put me in there.
I don't like it, I can't get it down my throat.
I hate it.
That's fine.
really
I'm laughing so hard.
You're laughing so hard.
I knew it, he's that smug.
You know, this guy's an S.
He really wants to raid your mouth.
really, really
They want to put their money where their mouth is
I don't know what that means.
I really don't get it.
mouth
But if it weren't for burdock and moriman
a little bit like this
You know, you've been huffing and puffing.
That's it, isn't it?
But you know what?
If you can help it, sure, maybe.
I think there is.
I did my best.
Oh my god, Nakamura-san.
It was fun, Yamachan, it was fun.
He said it.
Even Nakamura can see the funny side now.
In the first place.
to begin with
Are you okay, Yamachan?
No, I mean, I'm fine.
But you're already healed.
I'm not cured, but...
Surgery or something on the back.
Surgery on the back
Five days.
But that's why I
I mean, I'm going to have a baby.
In September.
Oh, yeah.
Your 3rd kid
Yea, no kidding.
I said I said I said I said
Your 3rd?
Third kid.
Oh, yeah, you said it.
Come on.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
And I'm going to have a baby.
It's a boy.
Oh my goodness.
That's your first.
Yeah, my first son.
I mean, honestly, it's a lot of work for a boy.
I've never had one.
Then why are you telling me
Up to now
No, so I'm listening to you.
I've never had one.
I've had a little bit of that before.
Tell him it's a boy.
So wherever you go
I've been seeing a lot of boys lately.
I see.
Actually
see before
If you go to that platform
Master of the game
My daughter over there
If you're in line to do it already
boy
That's a boy about 4 years old.
He's already got this bee.
After all is said and done
Cross here.
Say "No, yeah, yeah, yeah" all the way down.
I think it's just that girl.
Boy
I thought boys were like that.
I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it
I was horrified when I saw that.
What does intestinal disease have to do with that boy?
What does intestinal disease have to do with that boy
I have a bowel disease.
I'm in a lot of trouble now.
I'm sure I'm going to go through a lot with a boy.
I was horrified.
And physical strength.
It takes a lot of strength.
I know you're in there.
But there's a boy in Tanana
I hear the Twasians are coming.
What?
you
Wow.
Is this for real?
Go ahead, doctor.
Where doctor?
Yes, sir.
Ekiming Hospital Municipal Cooperative Medical Department 1-chome
Naoyuki Uragami
Best regards
That's great doctor.
I'm sorry
I don't know, I'm not very good at explaining it.
We're going to need a real doctor.
Thank you very much.
Certainly.
How can the cause be that way?
Originally, the westernization of the diet
It is said to be one of the causes
It's the diet.
Dietary habits.
What you take too much of, and so on.
Meat products.
Basically, as a meal.
The more food products you eat, the more
It is said that consumption is less likely to produce
What was your diet before this?
Do you have any idea what you were doing?
Oil products
I see.
The oily meat
It's all meat, after all.
Symptoms of abdominal pain and fever
In so much pain that eating is impossible
The fact that you can come to the hospital
So it's going to be unbearable pain then?
Yes, it would.
I hear Yamazaki is lying.
Isn't that what you're saying?
I'm not lying.
We're ahead of you.
And here, you see, the sea has formed
And if that mass breaks up, it's called a prior
Originally, the colon is full of a bacterium called E. coli
And that's spread around in your stomach, so
And then peritonitis
It's called prior and it's a hole in the body
Peritonitis, severe infection, and that's how some people die.
So, is that pretty much what you're seeing now, Yamazaki?
Probably cured by antibiotics, so...
I think that's not such a bad figure.
I think it's a young person under 50 years of age
Those who still repeat like this
A person who has a social status is a person who is
I don't think so.
No, no, no.
No, they've told me.
Dr. Chabre told me.
The more minor the disease, the more likely you are to have surgery
If you are in a specialized hospital
If it is done in about a week in a surgery called abdominopelvic cavity
You can be discharged from the hospital in about a week
Should we do it in a week?
is it better to do it in a week?
Let's do it on Gaki.
Let's do it
Let's turn it around.
You're going to do the surgery.
I don't know why.
That's absolutely wrong.
We'll make it a documentary
Yes, that's right.
That's good.
Doctor, you can't just cut it off like that.
That's not the kind of surgery you want to do.
Yes, that's right.
If you do endoscopy, that's the kind of microscopic thing.
You put the camera inside the abdomen.
We're talking about cutting the choke off.
There are fewer layers of surgery and fewer complications in the actual field.
But, for example, if you have a severe case of trait
This is not easy to operate on endoscopically.
It's technically very difficult to do.
For example, adhesions to the bladder or something like that.
In the worst cases, the poop comes straight into the bladder.
Poop comes out in the bladder pee
Ew, scary!
Is there poo in your pee?
It's cold
Let's look at that, let's look at that first
You shouldn't.
All together, all together.
Yamazaki, poo comes out of your pee
That's where you wait.
You're going to blow it down, there.
It's time to home ring there and take that there.
Is that the worst that can happen?
It's going to be a very difficult surgery.
It's very hard to do a real match.
Yes, now.
Even that would be nice if you cut it with me.
You want me to cut it with you?
If I say I'll cut Tanaka too...
he'll cut you too.
Mr. Yamada, it's not becoming.
You have that look on your face.
No, no, no
I'm just now, Mr. Zaki, really.
If you really want me to do it, I'll do it.
you should cut it off, too.
You want me to cut it off?
Why am I cut apart?
Then get Matsumoto to do it with you.
Yes, yes, maybe.
Get Matsumoto to cut it with you.
I heard he's going to do some kind of surgery.
Matsumoto says he'll do it if he doesn't do it with me.
So I'm like, you know what?
Thank you. Thank you for that time.
You don't have all the formalities.
Wrong cover.
I'm doing my own internal formula.
You know, that
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here
It's really a wound like this.
See, it's not another centimeter.
I don't know how far she's going to go, but I'll tell you what.
Not so big anymore
Now, now
It's small now, the wound is
You should do it.
No, no, no, Mr. Zaki.
No, no, no, no
If you had done it then, you wouldn't have done it now, right?
That's right.
I've done a lot of Stark Live, too.
Just now, if I'm in trouble again, I'll tell you what...
You're thinking of taking a break for more reasons than that, you know.
That's right.
I'll give you a break next time, really.
If you don't do it, you'll shit out of your dick.
I'll give you a break on this one.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no.
No, you should do it, absolutely.
Get out of the bad food habit, that's what you've been doing for years.
That's right, that's right.
for the likes of you.
No, no, no.
Eh, wait a minute.
Really, um
You're not going to do it with me, dude?
what are you talking about?
Why would I do that?
Why do I have to do this?
I, I, I don't like it.
Not now, sir.
You're a hoaxer, hoaxer.
You're a hoake, hoake
Houke
Hokeya, just right
Bake, just like that.
Why, why, why?
Why do we have to make a profit?
I mean, you know, I'm just...
After 40
You're making the doctor laugh
Yes, sir.
He's laughing all the way, sir.
No, that's a little bit
Let's think about that for a second, let's think about that up front.
No, really.
Let's think about this when we're about to tell the doctor.
Are you thinking about it?
Thank you very much, Dr. Urakami.
Yes, thank you very much.
This is the one, this is the one
Really, really, really
from what I'm thinking
Hey, Yamamoto-san, let's think about it, really.
You should definitely do it.
I'll be surprised, if that happens.
It's absolutely fine, really.
how do you like that?
No, I'm definitely going to get everybody in trouble.
And now you're going to have a baby.
Yes, sir.
I knew it, that's why
I can't take a break every time.
No, really.
I'm sure it is, but
Because now the regular
And the only drive is GoGo.
We don't know how long we can keep that drive going.
I'm going to call myself that, see.
No, really.
No, that's it
You go to a hot spring with an idol girl.
When you come out of there's shit
Oh no.
No, no, no, no.
Because nothing can be different now.
before something like that.
That is, yes
I'm sorry, if that's the case, I'm not going
If you're really going to do it, even a little bit
Let me think about it for a minute
Scary? What do you want?
Scary? Yeah, that's it.
I mean, it's not scary, but it's...
They said it's still a little early.
What's early?
Um, I'm going to wear it.
to my doctor.
I promised him that I would make him wear it.
What the hell is that?
What is that promise?
to your doctor.
And he says, let's do it after I turn 50.
That's
Oh no.
but in the meantime, you know, it just keeps spreading out
But Tanaka's really doing it.
Why am I getting surgery?
I've been saying that for a while now.
myself, I've been saying this for a while now.
It's funny, this.
What I've been saying for a while now is
I'm sure it's there, and Tanaka
What are these three guys talking about?
There's no, there's no, there's no, there's no, these three of us.
really.
Really, it's not even usual, you know, with these three.
I, Tanaka, if you think about it, we live very close to each other.
I just moved in.
Yes, we are neighbors.
You haven't met him once.
Well, I've been in touch with him.
in the neighborhood
And, of course, you know, we've been introduced to this place and
And we go there and
I've told him it's good, but I've told him it's good.
I've never bumped into him.
I don't think so.
Do you actually live there?
I live there.
In that city
I'm here.
is that right?
I'm really rolling all the time.
I don't see you around.
If you're talking like that, have you seen Masakazu Tamura?
What?
I've been living behind my house for six months.
So it's like this?
is it like this?
There's a lot of them, but you can't see them.
I've never met any of them.
That guy, he'd walk in front of our house and dump it.
Tamura-san?
That's right.
Yes.
Damn, is that it?
Is that it then, or are you alone, or is there someone else?
I think it's just one person.
You're alone.
is that right?
Masakazu Tamura
Yes, I know, I haven't seen you.
It's been about a year now.
There are a lot of them, but I can't see them.
Yes, yes, yes.
There's Tokoro-san and others, but I can't see them.
That's right.
I know you're here.
Yes, that's right.
Please, I'm not going to meet you, so either way
I just, you know, I've been alone for a while now.
I'll call you sometimes.
No, no, no, no, but
I was eating at an Okinawan restaurant the other night.
The end.
No. No one else has
I'm about to cry.
"I'm having dinner alone at an Okinawan restaurant."
What?
I found an Okinawan restaurant by myself.
I'm alone at the far end of the restaurant
I was eating a set of Australian night jumpers.
I'm also drinking a little armoire and I'm on my own.
I'm starting to feel a little bit better.
I called Hamada, and I asked him if he'd like to come over.
But well, I got an answering machine.
He's living like that.
Yeah, one of them already.
You're not getting married?
You're not getting married.
Remarried?
I will not remarry.
Why not?
If you say it straight out and right away
It's hard to say it, you know, when you ask
They won't tell me.
I won't tell you who I'm dating now.
I can't get married, no.
I'm really sorry.
Why are you doing this?
Because my child is only 9 years old.
I'm not going to be able to do it until he's a little older.
Yes, that's right.
If you say that, it's impossible.
What if he says it?
Isn't it about time?
That's what I'm saying.
I'm saying no, like a marriage.
When are you going to let me see him?
How many people do you want?
how many people?
How many people are you talking to?
It's a time of year, so it's like a two-timing thing.
I'm not really doing it.
I'm really not doing it, and it would be a disaster if I went that far.
I don't even know what I'm talking about, Hamada.
I don't want to fly like that.
That's not how it works, there's only one of us.
I'm really that worried about it.
Tanaka is one of those people that you don't hear from the convivia in the face of trouble.
That's true.
But some times, I mean once or twice, Tanaka's family
together.
I'm not going out to dinner with you and the kids, either.
Really?
They bathe me, this kid here, my kid there.
That's great.
Are you really worried?
I like you very much, Endo.
I like it so much, endo
I love the ho ho ho ho
But I'm happy, this is
I come home from work and I really love my kids.
Mr. Endo, I love that you said you had a ho ho ho ho today.
Mr.Endo, I love that you did Hohohoi today.
I'm grateful for that.
Did you ever see anything like that? When your children were small, Matsumoto's children...
I met him when he was very small, at a school like NGK in Osaka.
And I'm probably the first person to say this.
I'm bringing him to a film festival here in Okinawa.
I was there for the first time, at Matsumoto-san's place.
with Matsumoto-san's child.
I'm being totally ignored.
What do you mean you've been ignored?
I was already standing there, so I said hello or something.
I guess I kind of bumped it a little bit, you know.
It was a little red.
I said, "What's wrong with that?
all the way to
You must have been nervous.
He's still tiny, and he's a little bit.
And then, to top it all off
Papa
And then he goes to daddy.
What the hell is he doing to his dad now?
So you've met him, you've seen him once.
No, no, no. I just thought it looked red.
I said, "What's wrong? I said, "What's wrong?
He looked at me for a second, and then he just said, "Dad...
You know what I'm talking about, don't you?
You know what I'm talking about.
I don't know, all the guys did it.
I don't know, it's just the way it's handled.
I don't know what it is, my daughter.
When she was little, when she was about Missy or something like that.
Hamada used to take me to dinner.
She's basically a very friendly girl.
When Hamada says come here...
She started crying.
I don't know what's going on
Don't you cry, I didn't cry at that part.
My boy, he said it with me, too.
So it's Machan, Yamachan, En-chan and Hamada-san.
That's a good boy.
He's a 3- or 4-year-old kid like Machan.
Don't you understand, that kind of thing
I mean, you know, Machan and I watch TV and say...
Machan, Yama-chan, En-san, Hamada-san
Hamada-san with three attachments
I'm not saying anything, of course, my mom
Please let him say Hama-chan already.
Please let him say "Hama-chan" right there.
He don't know if he's allowed to say that.
He thought you knew what you were doing, even as a child.
You shouldn't say Hama-chan.
That kid is not that cute.
Let me just say this.
Hama-san