Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende
tiny voice
Let's keep rallying until we meet a famous person
Komazawa version
please
You only heard the part about the braley.
I know what you're saying.
I can't speak that loud in that place.
No, where is this, what park is this?
Komazawa Park.
Komazawa.
1st Yamanaka Me Bro Jiyugaoka Come to Mihara Temple
This is the 5th time
Previous Yamanaka Me Bro Jiyugaoka Mihara Temple
This highly requested project.
There were many sightings
It looked like we might find a celebrity soon
It was unexpectedly difficult to find a celebrity
However
1 hour and 52 minutes from start
Finally
An encounter with Zabun Gurukato on his way home from shopping
Suddenly, we went to Kato's house.
to visit Kato's home.
The area where we're going to search for celebrities this time is Setagaya Ward
Komazawa
Komazawa University
Komazawa Olympic Park etc.
Lots of greenery
A popular bedroom community for celebrities
Many famous people have been spotted here in Komazawa
They can't leave until they run into one.
The harsh challenge begins
I think it's a tough challenge.
Komazawa
It's not in the city.
Residential area
And this is something else I'm going to say again.
Endo had a fever
Do you have a week system?
It's quite a lot.
No, you know, last time I was here, I was...
I haven't had a fever since the last time I was in Tohmichi Takiichi.
Pretty much 3 years
Tohdo Taki City has already been by the sea many times
I have to jump into the pool
I'm coming down with a cold in that situation.
It's going to take this today.
Because I was gawking.
To you, ladies and gentlemen, at Komazawa.
I've never met anyone in Komazawa.
I've never met anyone from Komazawa.
I hear rumors
Celebrities go out running.
I hear you're referring to it.
I've heard that people are
About Arthur Kuroda runs
That's good.
Just about right
just about right
This is human
This is a human being
Entertainment.
I didn't see it.
I don't know who was running.
Until you meet a famous person
Let's keep on hanging out
Komazawa version
The verification rule is for private celebrities
The location is not over until you encounter
However, the name of that celebrity
All the kid members have to be able to say it.
Otherwise NOT CLEAR
Of course, the celebrity
Needs permission to be filmed
What will happen here in Komazawa?
Is it possible to find a famous person
Can you do it?
Ah.
It's Yukio Nomura.
Yukio Nomura
No, sir.
She didn't look at me at all.
That's great.
Let's go around.
Shall we go inside?
People taking a walk or something.
Time for a walk, and so on
Endo
Ah!
The common cold.
You got a fever.
You've still got some sense.
You've got a weak body, Endo.
I was addicted to it.
I'm getting really sick.
He's not going to make it either.
Okay.
Surprisingly
Me and Tanaka
I'm not feeling well anymore, I'm almost gone.
But this
but it's just hidden.
I'm also a man of mind and body.
I'm always current.
Voices.
I can't hear you.
But we have one break in this series.
Matsumoto is resting.
That's a lot.
First for the five
They start searching in Komazawa Park
Why did you start walking in this park?
First of all
You know, that walk or something.
I'm just saying, you know, maybe there's a guy out there running.
I'm just saying that the store owner is...
I think it's good.
I think it's better to go far over there on this.
that way
No, I don't really care which one is better.
No one has the right answer.
Right.
The five,
Led by staff in the park
Head toward the stadium
We can't go this way.
And there it is, in the stadium...
many students who have just finished practicing.
and spot the gaki members.
Say what you're glad I said
Seriously
go for it!
Komaza Street
This is a pattern that will be raised in any way.
Recently
Not so much
how to raise
I've had it done to me before, but a long time ago.
Let's go to the bathroom in a karaoke box.
I was in a karaoke box, and I went to go to the bathroom, and then I see a student in the hallway.
and then you follow it step by step
in the hallway of a karaoke box
If that happens...
I can't help but laugh
I'm going to say it right there
Yes, that's right.
Have you seen any celebrities?
I don't know who it is.
I heard there was one running.
I don't like it when celebrities say that.
High school student
No more of these guys
Like in the morning.
Bing bing bing bing.
I guess so.
These guys are like in the morning
these guys are in the morning
Bing bing bing bing
What's a telemachine?
I'm still in my adolescence.
She had red ears.
Her ears were so red.
That was amazing.
Wow, that's great.
That's a dog.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're getting along.
You're taking some kind of a walk.
Have you seen a little famous person or something.
Looking for celebrities? I didn't see any today.
Who have you seen, by the way?
up to the Showa period
Because Showa
Kaela
For your child
There is also Shinji Yamashita
That's nice.
Just right.
Thank you
Shinji Yamashita
Shinji Yamashita.
Just right.
From the start of the light prize
20 minutes in
Facing Komatsubara Dori
Facing small staircase
There's nothing there.
Nothing.
From the station
It's a long way from the station, so it's already
I'm really going to lose people.
You see this staircase here?
Here we are...
We're at the park.
No - but how about
How about this
They're really not there!
There's no one here.
This is bad.
Oh, the look of that girl.
A little celebrity
Sounds like
I need to take a closer look.
You're not an actress, are you?
There's something in that bag... it's a script.
It's episode 4 or something.
Episode 4
I think it's about 4 episodes at the time.
No, no, no, no, no.
Even 4 episodes is a little bit slow.
That's a little slow.
Is it okay, that man 4 episodes
Not many people here.
Giving up the search in Komatsuzawa Park
Go to Komatsuzawa Dori
Once you get out of the park, there's nothing here.
This is a residential area.
There are no people walking around.
I don't think we're going to find them.
Just cross this way for a second.
There's a ramen shop, Lawson's, and...
Let's go to the store for a bit.
Let's go to all three stores for a minute
Across Komatsuzawa street.
There are many people
many people
Hoping for a restaurant across Komatsuzawa Dori
Go take a look.
Go take a look, Endo
At Hamada's direction
Endo and Tanaka go around the stores
Searching for celebrities
That's good.
Oh, and it was empty.
But not a single celebrity in sight.
All I saw were spinning cars and no one was there.
I thought there were about three groups of people a week.
Entertainers
Looks like it has a private room
Who is it? I said Komazawa Park.
Who is it?
Who is this?
It's really not there.
who is this?
really who is it?
It's not an individual.
We're all thinking about it.
I know you're thinking of that one, but
Five of them are on Komatsuzawa Street.
they decide to go forward aimlessly
We've got another barbecue place here.
This one's gone.
Xuanyuan and the bumblebee.
It's a little bit so-so here.
I hear it's a pretty reasonable place
It's a different concept from Xuanyuan
Wow, that's amazing.
cheap
Half price for elementary school students
Can't you go to Xunyuan?
A little high.
This one is better.
Cuyoda
Yakiniku King
Wow!
A girl like that is like Hama-san.
If you take them all to Xu Shuen, they'll be happy.
They'd love that.
All kinds of good rumors are going around.
You're talking to me.
No, my voice is a little...
Tell him.
If you sleep in line, you'll end up swimming in Xuanyuan.
and this will really go down in history.
No, no, no, no
They don't even have the inside track.
Did you say that?
I said it.
That's when they find out something promising
Mask up ahead
Oh!
oh
Good afternoon
This is
In front of them is a woman with a mask covering her face
Good afternoon
Did they finally find a celebrity?
Mask up ahead
Oh!
oh
Good afternoon
This is
This is a bit suspicious
this is a bit suspicious
Hello
Good afternoon
Excuse me
Are you in the entertainment industry?
No?
Are you a celebrity?
I don't want to get sunburned.
I don't want to get sunburned
I'm pretty sure that's what you're saying right now.
I'm sure that's true.
Atmosphere
Are you a celebrity?
No, sir.
I'm ashamed.
With no sign of encountering a celebrity
45 minutes have passed since the start
We've been stood on our own for a while...
What are we going to do?
What do we do?
I'm going over there first.
Why don't we go to the one where that guy is?
No, it's not.
I don't think there's any point in asking any of them.
You're a little purple.
Five of them are off the main street
They go off Komatsubara Dori to Komatsubara Park Dori
Proceed to an unpopular alley
What time do celebrities eat dinner?
ah, maybe 7 o'clock.
Well, maybe a little bit.
It's the same as the general point of view.
Roughly 7:00
Much, much more is much earlier, and
This guy is a genius.
This is amazing.
He's so good at parking.
I don't know how they did it.
I think every time
I didn't move it.
I think it's going to stay like that.
I'm still serious about this
Check it out.
He's moving it.
turning back and forth turning back and forth
Egregious
I've wondered about this a couple of times.
I was thinking, "This is great.
It's 5:00.
Now?
Just 5:00
They go to Komatsubara Park Avenue
No, there's no one there.
There's something at the dog boutique.
but
I think there are some people who don't have snow.
Sounds like a celebrity.
Something smells like a celebrity.
Yamazaki, you should go.
Yes, sir.
They smell a celebrity near by
So Hosei heads to the dog boutique
Are there any celebrities here?
I guess it depends on the time of the day.
If we had a little more time
I don't know if it would come up.
It's only 5 o'clock.
How's that?
I'm here at the point where I'm
I knew why I was going to do it.
If there is such a thing, it would be like this
In a restaurant where celebrities would come
I'm going to have to buy it now.
Hosei returns after the search
no good
No
It's a totally different person.
We need a celebrity to come.
I see.
What's a celebrity? he said.
I can't come.
I got barked at so much in there.
I knew it was an endo
more than a person
I'm naked a lot of the time.
He says he catches cold easily.
What?
That's it.
Let's keep it.
no big deal
Proof
What time?
15:05
15:05 done
He tried to cover it
He tried to pass it off.
The lamest.
The fact that you tried to take a walk it off
like it was nothing, is so lame
I can get tripped up sometimes.
Yes, it happens.
and so on
"I tripped."
That's one thing, but
Pretending not to trip.
That is so lame.
Now the time says that time
That's not the time you got stuck.
You're saying the time you pretended you weren't hooked.
It's 17:05.
17:05 minutes.
17:05 minutes
Time to pretend not to be trapped
I bring my dog in.
This is a little bit...
Do you want to have a cup of tea here for now?
I've had too many sleepless nights.
1 hour
Hamada is also in the 4cm tier
It's just enough to get caught.
Let's take a break.
Let's go in
They have a strategy meeting here.
Break time
I'm not going to go into appearance or anything like that.
Let's go into surveillance.
You're just a comedian.
I'm fine with the comedian.
It's the easiest thing to do.
I really do.
Anybody.
I'm going to go pee.
What the hell is that?
That's what I thought.
Just as I thought.
Komatsuzawa is
Who is Komatsuzawa
Who is Matsumoto?
And here we are back on topic
They chose Komatsuzawa as the stage.
To search for the culprit
We all decided together
I said, "Well, I've got to get you out of here. And it came out here.
What's up?
I'm just asking.
Stylish
Restroom in a cafe
There is a theory that there is no bidet.
There is a theory that it is not equipped with an oushlet.
I see.
Komatsuzawa is
I think we're having a hard time.
I wonder who decided that.
Yamachan said
Who decided this?
Wait a minute.
Matsumoto-san, right?
Gaki no Tsukai
I think it's better this way.
I've never said that before.
Don't lie to me.
You had a bad hand before you said it.
I know you know that.
You're the one making the decisions.
I really do.
Let's be honest, shall we?
We were going to go to Shimokita.
That's what it was supposed to be.
That's totally different.
You went downtown, you went to Shimokita.
Shimokita, on a different show.
in such a short time
Isn't it funny that we're going
I can see that.
Because that one did it a while ago.
I can't go back that way.
The other side has already done it
How many days later is the Shimokita location
Tell him it's going to be tough.
I said, "Why don't you go to a different place?
Then it's not.
I've been saying all along that
I'm saying that Ikebukuro is the place to be.
Ikebukuro is out.
I said Ikebukuro would be good.
All of them are staffed by
There are things like that.
These guys are really...
They're talking nonsense.
This guy
like touching a fine thing
If possible, with Mr. Yoshimoto
I don't want to work too much.
I guess that's it.
He's giving me air.
It's complicated.
That's for sure.
That's not good.
Is there anybody here who is a celebrity or something like that?
They come quite a bit.
Once a day, absolutely.
Once a day
She's something like
She's something
She looks like Keiko Fuji.
The old
Amazing.
Fujikeiko, you don't understand?
at the time of debut
You look like Keiko Fuji.
This is the same as Koko Ono
I don't need to move anymore
Yes, that's right.
what should we do?
Let's just listen to the sound of the street for now.
I don't think so.
Calm down normally.
The sun has completely set
In the dark in Komatsuzawa
Resuming the search
I can't even see people's faces.
When it's this dark
I'd rather have the lights on this way.
It's more conspicuous and you can get away with it.
at that time
A gauge
eh
Oops.
Surprise!
Finally
Famous person found!
I can't get out.
Are you free?
This may be
It's Gaki.
Kind of.
a little
Actually, this one
Because he is an announcer of another song
NG required to perform
Not clear
where is the best
I think we can meet somewhere around here.
I think we can meet here if we look
If you look at Brother Tom's
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
I was so happy.
He's not free.
Glad to hear it, though.
I don't remember if I'm already free.
but I thought
But Brother Tom
is there
Wow, that's amazing!
But now gah!
The four seasons are going up.
That was a long time ago.
Brother Tom's
There was a picture, that's for sure.
It's very much rooted in the community.
it was there.
It was nothing.
I'm home.
There's a drama going on.
Brother Tom.
And furthermore
Will they find a celebrity?
And then
The next time that
That man, Gadiro
Mr. Gajiro
Mr. Gajiro!
What a surprise to see Gajiro Sato!
Found
Yay, yay, yay!
That's great, great, great.
That's my dad's role.
Is it a store?
Just a little time
sorry
May I ask you to come out for a moment?
I'm sorry, sir.
Get your car in order.
It's been a while
Wow, that's great.
We found a celebrity.
Gajiro here
Good evening
We've been stumbling around like this, looking for celebrities.
there
Until you meet the celebrity
We didn't make it home.
I'll take that, please.
Thank you very much.
thank you very much
I'm going to say it right again.
Gajiro Sato
Pleased to meet you
Good.
Good
good
1 hour and 32 minutes from start
Clear without any complaints
where now
Store
Now?
From now on
I could go to the store now
No, no, no, I can't read it.
well
I found him coming out of the car.
What are you doing?
I'm stuck.
Thank you.
Thank you
Good, good, good.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
I'm going to go to the store.
business
Good luck with your business
That's perfect.
I have no idea what they're all screaming about.
Who noticed that?
Who noticed
A little more
If you have a long term in a cafe
It's not open anymore.
It's the timing.
Miracle
Sato Gajiro
Oh, good, good, good.
Com, you can't complain about this.
Yes, sir.
But it felt good.
The office said yes.
That's it.
Thank you
That felt good.
I was right next to him.
I almost kissed him.
I love you so much, I really do.
Bamu bamu news
Sebastian Masuda is
Yasutaka Nakata is
Hamada bamu bamu charmed
A completely produced work is
Finally completed
Its title is
I don't know why
December 16
Decided to accept and release Man
One moment, please.
kid's errand
DVD & Blu-ray Volume 21
Never receive
The Great Jailbreak 24
Released on December 2