This is Suiyobi no Downtown. Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu!
Now let us start, inviting our first presenter
Chidori
This time, we have brought an interesting theory
Everyone, do you smoke usually?
I have already quitted smoking
How many times did you smoke? Was it a lot?
Ah it was a lot, there was a period I smoked 5 packs too
One day 5 packs?
100 sticks of them
Hamada-san, you vape instead right?
Yep, not cigarettes
Comedians have quitted smoking, I have quitted as well
Daigo smokes a lot. Yeah I'm sorry
Daigo gives the image that he's a heavy smoker
With an exception to meeting everyone like now, he will keep smoking
During private times, I can't see him at all because the smoke covered him
He will keep smoking! It's true that not many can see me
During a race, you'll increase even more!
Well during M-1, I had to cut down on 2 cartons
It's around 20 packs
Today's theory will involve smoke addicts. Please look
Smoke addicts - no matter how difficult it is , they will go to the smoking area
Let's say it's me, no matter what I must get to the smoking area
Like sacrificing your life? Yeah like sacrificing my life
If the smoking area is at there
I will go there at all cost
Daigo will go for sure
To this point?
Sometimes during the 10 minutes break of a location shooting, you will go smoke too right?
Yeah of course
He will really go smoke , resulting in the cameramen and guests waiting for him
Even though he got reminded not to smoke during a location shooting
He will say 'If I can't smoke, I can't do my work at all'
When I go smoke, it is actually to help the staffs
This gives them a 10 minute break as well, I have thought this far
No no no, you are just twisting the truth
After this, heavy smokers will go undergo several kinds of challenges
I must climb up there
And also
Your partner is brainwashed by a fortune teller, suggesting to change name and you won't agree to it theory
I am Director Takuchi, nice to meet you
During an introduction, will artists remember other party's names?
We will do a live check
What is this person's name?
Theory test - Smoke addicts - no matter how difficult it is , they will go to the smoking area.
The targets selected are those who smoke more than 2 packs everyday - the heavy smokers in entertainment industry
We invited these 5 people under a fake program
To an abandoned school at Atami
Dragged them all the way to Atami...
Upon reaching the resting room, we will film them
No matter how difficult the situation is, they will sacrifice their life just for smoking theory
The first heavy smoker
I will be under your guidance
Ginshari's Unagi
He smokes a lot
Today, for 2 hours, these people came here with a No-Smoking car
Nowadays, you can't smoke on the bus anymore
When they arrived the destination, they're at peak condition of wanting to smoke
And then...
Just one stick, one stick is not possible?
Ah sure , it's fine
It was probably that he can't restraint his feelings anymore
Upon reaching outside, he begins to go to the smoking area with a cigarette in his mouth
However at that place...
Bet that he saw something bad
Eh?
What is this?
Obstacle 1: Smoking area is filled with smoke
Is this fine? It's filled with lots of smoke
Ehh?
Under this condition, will Unagi go in and smoke?
He probably thinks there's a fire accident
Who even dares to go in?
Excuse me
It's very smoky here
Tobacco stinks
After he confirmed it's not a fire accident
He'll go in for sure
Can't see anything
He really went in
Tobacco is a power that we don't understand after all
I have to smoke inside here
The door was opened but he only lighted up his cigarette after entering
His face can't be seen
What is he smoking, I can't even tell
Even in this state, he still wants to smoke huh
And so after smoking one stick
We reveal the program
Are we starting the location shooting now?
How do you feel?
Eh, it's not?
Eh what's this...
What is this prank?
Smoking... smoking area was it?
After we told Unagi about the theory
Is it so funny?
Ah yes I smoked
No matter how difficult it is, I will still go
Law is the only thing I'm afraid of
I will try not to step on the law's tail by a hair of string just to smoke
I must smoke at all cost
After we have come to a deeper understanding regarding heavy smokers
The next heavy smoker is
Saraba Seishun no Hikari's Morita
And after the briefing
Is there a place I can smoke here?
Yeah but you have to go to the campus to smoke, is that fine?
Okay
After being told by the staff that the smoking area is around here
With the help of the direction signs, Morita goes
This time, the smoking area is located at...
He has to go up the hill and down the hill, making a big round, for 1.5km
Obstacle 2: The path to the smoking area
Will heavy smokers go this far just to smoke, if he doesn't get to smoke he won't give up?
Well he's obeying the rules at least huh
After walking 1/3 of the distance
Something appeared, what is it?
Obstacle 3: The fierce dog stops infront of him
Eh?
It's a wild dog, it's a wild dog!
Nicotine vs Wild Dog
Uwaa scary!! This is scary
This is very scary
It's staring at him intensely
It's a skinny Doberman
After that, he walks up the hill
Too far too far too far too far
It's too far
After that, he walks downhill
It's too far!
He's complaining a lot
It's there
After 15 minutes of walking, he has finally reached the school's smoking area
15 minutes...
That's tiring
Isn't this one big round?!
Starting to get irritated huh
It's hot
It's hot!
Obstacle 4: 90°C Smoking Area
He's really going to smoke
It's too hot
This is scary
Is this real or what
Well, he will smoke for sure
Tobacco is amazing
Even in this condition, he didn't step out until he's done with his first stick
Indeed it was further than I thought
Yeah but... there's no smoking areas that's not far anyway
After seeing the Doberman
'Ah it's a scaring device or some sort' I thought
As long as you want to smoke, you won't go back until you get to smoke
In the end I must smoke, no matter what obstacles I will not retreat
This is a heavy smoker's depressing circumstances
Our next target is
Ah it's Manabu
Kaminari's Manabu
He doesn't seem like he smokes
It's 8pm
It's so dark - it feels a bit creepy
There's no electricity in this school so it's all dark
And so in this condition
Is there a smoking area? Smoking area is at...
Manabu got a lantern
Obstacle 5: The fear of darkness
As if on a spiritual location shooting, he will go to the smoking area in this abandoned school
Uwaa oh my god
Even though he's scared but he still didn't give up
What awaits him in the darkness is...
Uwaa x4
With the help of Sasuke, we got a warped wall
This show loves Sasuke a lot
The smoking area is at the top of the half pipe
Specially made - Warped Wall Smoking Area
Isn't this the smoking area
I can only try
What will the outcome be
Wants to smoke that badly...
Too difficult
With those boots, it's not possible
It's impossible to climb
Too difficult
Which is the goal
It feels like he's at the goal instead
Too difficult
Ah it's impossible
Uwaa he wants to smoke so much
Being pressured by this level of difficulty, he sinks into despair
At this moment, we reveal our program
Well with this, the program is already exposed
If he's shocked that would be a lie already
This is impossible
It's definitely impossible
The ones that can do it are those who have tried a million of countermeasures
The successful ones are those who gambled everything
So I can't do it
So how are you feeling right now?
I want to smoke still
I want to smoke even more now
And the theory begins on the 2nd day
There are 3 more difficult obstacles before the warped wall
It's becoming more like SASUKE's Obstacle Race
Tobacco Sasuke - First challenger is
Sumo&Tobacco Comedian - Akatsu
Really love him huh
The show loves Akatsu eh
I can't smoke here?
The show loves both Sasuke & Akatsu
Will he overcome the obstacles and complete the race?
The first obstacle
1.    Heavy door
What is this?
He spent some time but he cleared the first obstacle easily
Where is it?
And the 2nd obstacle
At here?
No no no how can this be
2.   Climbing the rope ladder
Even though he says that, he still goes...
He's really going to climb
I'm doing all this just to smoke seriously
Is this ladder fine?
Just for a cigarette stick
To this point...
He has cleared the rope ladder just to smoke
Tobacco is scary ah
This shows how scary Tobacco is
Next he enters the school compound again
Where is it?
Next, it's the 3rd obstacle
Mouu, what is going on here?
3. Ditch
I even brought my phone
Ditch...
You call this a ditch?
This is the worst
Ah he's wearing a snow white sneakers
And then Akatsu...
Oh he's using his brain
Using the trolley as a stepping foot
He cleared the obstacle by breaking the rules
And finally infront of him is...
I need to go so much trouble just to smoke?
Forget it, just let me smoke the normal way will you
No can do, go to the smoking area
What is this theory?
After seeing the warped wall, Akatsu already knows the situation he's in
He already put the pack of cigarettes on the ground
Yeah
What will the outcome be?
It hurts
Your body and this obstacle are not fated
I have never done this before it's so hard
Come on...
It's impossible
It's hot it's hot it's hot
He only wants to smoke
But then it seems like it's possible to do this
But...
Barefoot?
Ah barefoot might make it easier?
Iyaa Akatsu can't do this, the bounce back is too scary
Hot hot
Wanting to conquer the Warped Wall Smoking Area it's not that easy
The bounce back is too scary!
It hurts it hurts
Not long later, he was exhausted
And then...
Akatsu left after having an idea
Is he smoking? What happened?
Well he still has not smoked yet
Yep he has not smoked yet
He came back with a rake out of nowhere
And then...
He wants to use this as a hook and climb up?
With this position, he's really serious about it
What is this sports competition?
Is this guy an idiot?
Yes try harder!
It's dangerous!
It's slippery...
He can only try his best now!
It hurts!
Surrender
He really tried his best
What do you even mean by 'revealing the program'
It's not even a prank anymore
Yeah it's not considered a prank seriously...
It's really a pity isn't it?
This is cheating
No there's no rules or anything for this
I just want to smoke
Well true
And next the final challenger
Panther's Ogata
Yeah Ogata also smokes a lot
Then I'll go smoke
Okay
1. Heavy Door
First obstacle - the heavy door
Easily cleared
2. Climbing the rope ladder
Next it's climbing the rope ladder
Everyone will climb because they want to smoke
Without any questions, he continues to climb
Until now, there's zero questions?
Zero questions
With zero questions, he already reached here?
3. Ditch
What is this...
Because he doesnt want to dirty his AIR MAX, he took them off at the ditch
He loves sneakers a lot
Ah it's AIR MAX
Completing with barefoot
And then...
Despair...
This is a good expression
After seeing Warped Wall Smoking Area, Ogata figured something
I can only try
He climbs up to the starting point
What will it be Ogata-san
The outcome will be...
Who knows he can get to the top
Well he's also pretty athletic
So close!
Just a bit more
It seems possible
Wow it's a waist pants
Don't care about waist pants...
Just a bit more!
He can do it for the next one
I'm cheering so hard for him
This is the worst
From Sendai's high school prestigious football club - No 10. Ogata
His athlete skills are above average
He has already touched the top of Warped Room Smoking Area
I'm already here so I have to reach the top
I already figured it out more or less it's probably that show
He found out
Damn it
I must reach the top
He only just wants to smoke, it's amazing
Can he do it?
It feels like he's able to do it this time
He can reach the top can he
He can take part in Sasuke's obstacle race now
I did it, I did it!!!
Warped Wall Smoking Area completed
Where's your cigarette?
Oh he brought it
Smoking here...
He looks so cool
In conclusion, climbing a warped wall means nothing if you want to smoke
They really want to smoke
I understand their feelings of wanting to smoke
Nowadays the places you can smoke are decreasing so their desires are stronger
I don't really understand but I guess it's like their effort came to fruition so it feels better to smoke
That seems reasonable
Smoking in a clean environment feels very good too
For example, stations at the countryside are very clean
And places with fresh air too
But Hamada doesn't care about rules when it comes to smoking
Hamada smokes whenever he wants
That's not good
So Hamada smokes in areas that everyone is not allowed to smoke?
He smokes like it's normal
In this case the rules are changed
So the juniors that want to smoke will gather around Hamada
Moving Smoking Area
And the next presenter please
Oh he's here he's here!
Koyabu Kazutoya
It's a bit sudden but do you guys believe in fortune telling?
Athletes will believe in fortune telling, yes?
If given a choice, I think I'll believe in fortune telling
I lean towards the believing side as well            -You as well?
Well there are genuine ones and there are suspicious ones
There are those without power and cheat others too
Well there are good and bad
And with this, I'll be presenting this theory
Your partner is brainwashed by a fortune teller, suggesting to change name and you won't agree to it theory
So how's this?
Your partner is suddenly obsessed with fortune telling , talks about this shady fortune teller
Wearing suspicious beads, carrying a suspicious crystal ball
Drinking some weird water
It's easy to tell
At one glance you can tell it's fake
That's torturing
In the atmosphere of getting cheated your partner suddenly suggests to change stage name
'No no what are you even talking about?'
We will check if the partner will say such words, that's the kind of theory
So that's the case
Let's say if Downtown-san Hamada-san...
Hamada-san also has some suspicious beads
It's not some suspicious beads
Now there's fewer of them but there was a period you wore them until this place
Until there?
Sometimes the elbow will appear like this
When he raises his arm then you can see
Sometimes it clamps on his meat when he raises his arm
Theory test - Your partner is brainwashed by a fortune teller, suggesting to change name and you won't agree to it theory
The first group is Kaminari
Takumi will pretend to be brainwashed and suggest to change the group's name
The prank will start in 1 week
What's that?
Suspicious beads
Someone recommended me a Sensei from Saitama
He said if I wear this it'll bring me good luck so I wore it
Good acting skills
He also said If I wear the beads only , the power is not that strong
Suspicious water
Wait suddenly?
Suspicious crystal ball
This crystal ball too, it's better if I carry it around with me instead of putting it at home
Isn't carrying around too weird?
What happened?
Takumi's acting of being brainwashed by a fortune teller continued for a week
You will kind of be worried
Looking at Robocop
Idiot
You will wear this during our performance?
It's not necessary , I can take it off during our performance
How does it feel like now?
He believes I'm brainwashed
Ah really?    -Yeah he believed
And finally he's going to suggest to Manabu about name changing but...
But before that...
Did you hear from Yama-san?
About what?
It's only me but...
I'm going to host a program in Osama's Brunch
That's amazing
Brunch is very influencing, this will help our business a lot
It's good for our business
Our unit price will rise, character appearance fee will rise too
We will rise by a grade that's for sure
Because it's Ousama after all
It'll start in April
I'll support you a lot
Ah he's so kind
Just like this, Takumi made this fake news to convince Manabu that all this was thanked to the Fortuner teller
Finally, Changing Name Prank starts
Can I discuss something with you?
Yeah
I decided to do this from April onward
Right now my real name is Ishida Takumi
I write Takumi in Hiragana               -Yeah yeah
Using a Hiragana name for my work isn't that good
What isn't good?
You researched on it already?
No Sensei said that
What is this Sensei?
Saitama's Sensei
That Sensei said that?
Yes yes yes I was told by that Sensei
You were told by that Sensei and you decided to change your name?
Yeah I'm thinking should I change my name
Is your head spoiled or something seriously
What happened?
Takumi's... eh What is going on?
It's Hiragana
Yes the Sensei said I should change the Hiragana part of my name
Suddenly Manabu is in serious mode but...
What will Takumi change his name to?
Ishida will remain then add Yume and Mon. Then call it Takumi
Is your head spoiled? That's unreadable
Then it can be a loan word
It can't be a loan word
Manabu is criticizing him instead now
If I change the whole Takumi name
I feel like I let those people who kept calling me Takumi down
With stroke counts, Yume Mon is better
Yume no Mon? Is called Takumi?
Isn't that Mumon then
No it's read as Takumi
It's called Mumon but you can read it as Takumi
No it's Ishida Mumon then
What's that
To be honest, I'm also scared
Of what?
I got this from Sensei for only 1 week
And in 1 week, I got contacted for a big work
You're wrong about that
It's because of your hard work
But I didn't do anything , it's not hard work
No there's hard work
It's just a normal life...
There's hard work
It's hard to notice a celebrity's hard work
Is that right?             -Yes yes yes
Getting this big work isn't because of the beads
No matter how many times, I'll still say it's because of your hard work
This guy is like the Sensei now
Is Manabu going to brainwash Takumi?
When you use Hiragana Takumi to appear on M-1 Grand Prix
During that time will you be called as Mumon?
But the reason for not getting first place could be because of my name not being Mumon
His tone is like a fortune teller now
Manabu don't you like fortune telling?
I do like fortune telling
You... you spent your money on these things didn't you
You got conned into buying
No I wasn't conned I bought them because I wanted to
You got conned into buying then
You're not this kind of person Takumi
But... my popularity has been stagnant for these 2 years
It'll change for the better
It's fine it's fine
But it's because these 2 years didn't have much changes so...
It's only 2 years you don't have to rush
I bought all these things with the thoughts of 'trying it out for one time'
In the end, I got a contact from Brunch after 1 week
So I thought changing the group's name could help us as well
But everyone can still call me Takumi, the subtitle display will be different that's all
During our Manzai introductions
'Hey hey Takumi-kun'
'What's wrong Manabu-kun' we start it off like that
'Hey hey Takumi-kun' the moment I say that
The kanji Mumon will appear in my mind
It creeps me out
But this is nothing big...
I'll think that 'This guy is Mumon' instead
But it's not Mumon, it's Takumi
There's actually someone this gullible
Please consider my feelings when my head is smacked by that person
I'm being serious
I wasn't conned...
Seriously there is no persuasive power at all
It's not like from today onwards I'll keep buying things from the Sensei
Quickly dispose it, it makes me so mad
What's this? Aren't you the one that hates this kind of thing most?
He's really mad
I don't want to go out with this kind of person
I really can't trust someone that buys this kind of things
No no it's not like I'm asking you to buy as well
No... wait wait wait
It's my own business after all
Your life is my life and my life is your life
Uwaa so cool!
We should walk this together
He got touched, the one doing the prank got touched
The guy who carries craps around and believes in changing name
'Stop screwing around' is what I'll think of
Your life is my life
They were childhood friends since nursery
Not sure when but they were each other's partners for the group they made
They were partners in life who always held hand together
Now one of them is being conned by a suspicious fortune teller...
He wants to be Mumon
The other partner's heart is upset and unsatisfied
I really can't change my name to Yume no Mon Takumi from April onward?
No you can't
I can't?                             -No
Really can't?            -We'll disband if you want to change name then
Eh we'll disband if I change name?
Yes we'll disband
I can't believe it, it's illogical
The guy who worked hard with me until now
He's being conned by a bastard into buying things, changing name
Impossible, impossible
If you really want to change your name we might as well disband
Give me that guy's contact number
Why?
I want to call him
So manly
You don't have to
I want to call him seriously
I want to ask him to stop screwing around
You don't have to
I think there are lots of victims so we have to tell the police about this
But in the end I'm not a victim, I got a work from Brunch
No no Brunch has nothing to do with this
Because we have reached the 'Disband' part
We will now reveal the program
What is this...
Seriously...
Where and what was the prank?
What do you think this is?
Suiyobi no Downtown
Correct
Seriously
Don't do this
You really can't do this
Were you scared?
I was scared
Did you notice the suspicious water?
Yeah I noticed it
Ah you noticed it
Oh you noticed that I kept drinking this
I thought it was suspicious
Ah stop drinking it             -It costs 5000 yen
Are you an idiot seriously
It's unbelievable