★Subbed by fmck fansubs★
reddit.com/u/fmckfansubs
patreon.com/fmck
This is Suiyoubi no Downtown
Hello everyone!
MC: Hamada Masatoshi
(Downtown)
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Natsuna
Gekidan Hitori
Truaden Naomi
Our presenter will come out now
It's Audrey's Kasuga!
Presenter:
Kasuga Toshiaki
(Audrey)
- Toose!
(Natsuna) So loud
Yes, today
I shouted it louder than usual
- Because I'm fired up
- Why?
What I want to
say first to everyone today
Is that this segment
is this show's only segment.
- Oh wow
- It's a great work
Obon Kobon
I bet Obon Kobon have split up
So soon?
That would be a special, wouldn't it?
No, it's not that but
another variety favorite
You know the pitfall trap?
- I've fallen into them many times
- Many times
But generally when we do it,
the person falling
is what we like to see. But,
This time,
We're going to enjoy the part after the fall
Here it is!
If you fall into a hole but the sun sets
without anyone coming to reveal the prank to you,
you won't be able to stay sane
- No no no...
(Natsuna) Huh?
That's too much
The ones who aren't sane are the staff here
It's a theory thought up by the insane staff, yes
This is really--
It's after the hole
That's right, yes. So,
A normal hole trap
is around 2 meters deep
But this time we don't want
them climbing out
So the depth is more than 3 meters
That deep?
It's a specially made hole
- So you'll leave them inside…
- Correct
- Like that?!
- No no no no no
If they can just climb out,
it's pointless
So today it's just people in a hole...?
- Will that be okay?!
- Yes
- Can I ask you something?
Why are you doing something like this?
It's to see what happens
I'm really excited
Chiba-ken Kashiwa Shonan Yume Farm
And so today,
we've borrowed this camp ground
In the deepest depths of the forest,
which is also private property,
somewhere people definitely won't pass
a hole trap is set up.
And the depth of that hole
is an inescapable 3.3 meters.
It's close to twice the depth of a regular hole trap.
Falling into what could be the deepest hole
trap on a variety show,
are our targets:
This is Nadal from
COLOCOLO CHITTYCHITTY PEPPERS!
COLOCOLO CHITTYCHITTY PEPPERS
Nadal
Nippon no Shachō
Ketsu
All the way from Osaka,
this is Nippon no Shachō's Ketsu!
Hello, this is Kaerutei's Nakano!
Kaerutei
Nakano Shūhei
I'm going to win and buy a house!
Hello, this is Chance Ōshiro!
Chance Ōshiro
Panther
Ogata Takahiro
Let's go! Yeah!
Panther - Ogata
COLOCOLO CHITTYCHITTY PEPPERS -
Nadal
Chance Ōshiro
Kaerutei - Nakano
Nippon no Shachou -
Ketsu
First
hole
trap
First
hole
trap
First
hole
trap
Ranging from hole trap veterans to virgins,
we invited these five over
on different days.
And the fake show is...
a treasure-hunting battle show called
"Comedian Treasure Hunting King's Championship".
And to make them really think
they've been forgotten,
Joyman, Yutti,
(Omiotsuke) Kuroda Wakame, Oda Ueda, Koneo International, Santa Monica, Sekenshirazu
Nightingale Dance, Nature Burger, Mampuku United, (Bragoli) Daichan
Dummy comedians:
a total of 30 people will start from different places
and then disperse,
making a mistake by the staff
seem more likely to occur.
They'll be like "They've forgotten me"
Yes. And there are lots of people too.
- Even though they fell
- Yes
Start Point
Hole
And the targets
will be traveling alone to the Start Point
when they fall into the hole.
Alright!
I'm off!
This is so rural
What does "Gunfire warning" mean?
Look at this? Who's shooting?
Gunfire warning!
Please be aware
there are houses
in this area.
This is scary
Beware of wild dogs!
Wild dogs have been
spotted in this area.
Please do not approach
or feed them.
What is this scary stuff?
Wild dogs...
Beware of wild dogs!
Wild dogs have been
spotted in this area.
Please do not approach
or feed them.
Gunfire warning!
Please be aware
there are houses
in this area.
Regarding these two signs,
Fake
the wild dog sign is fake
but the gunfire one is real. However, this was not
filmed during the hunting season.
Real
Wow!
Isn't the fake one weaker though?
Is this the right way?
Hole
Start Point
Relying on a rough treasure map,
each of them enters the forest alone and walks for 10 minutes.
If I fall in there, it's over..
I'm so scared
That voice
And Nadal too
Agh, ouch
Wait a minute
What's this?
And then the remaining three
Woah, what's this?!
Hey, you did it!
Hey!
I hate you guys
Investigation started
At 2pm the five targets
take up residence in the 3-meter deep hole
and our investigation begins.
Remote 1
Remote 2
Fixed 1
Fixed 2
Pinhole 1
Pinhole 2
By the way,
apart from the cameras on their person
we've hidden some on branches
and in the hole:
Remote cameras, fixed cameras,
and pinhole cameras too.
This is kind of deep
Did I need to fall so far?
I spent so long falling
Hey!
There's so many frogs here
Poisonous frogs!
*tut*
5 frogs
Here's a frog
How cute
There's frogs! Wait a minute!
There's frogs! Hey!
So many mosquitos
There's wasps! Wasps!
Crickets too
A cockroach's appeared!
Well I guess I've got them in my apartment too
Busy marvelling at the hole's depth
and its rich ecosystem,
they all still think this is a
regular hole trap.
But...
This is taking a while. Hey!
Hey!
Why are the staff being so lazy?
Why dig it if you're going to forget about it?
Hey!
Don't caw-caw-caw at me
If this were a normal hole,
they'd never take so long
Wait...
the staff and cameras.
I've already been here 10 minutes
It's been 10 minutes since they fell
and their anger towards the staff
is starting to intensify.
And so from here,
so that they believe this is not
a regular hole prank
but some kind of mistake,
we've prepared more trickery.
First...
(Speaker) Everyone, there are 10 treasure boxes hidden
in this camp ground.
The treasure hunt starts normally
Please try your best to find them!
First stage - start!
It's weird the staff haven't come yet
This must be an accident
Wait, why is no one here?
What show is this...?
Doing this is so incompetent
I don't even know what show it is
Gradually they start to fear something has happened
Then, 30 minutes later,
The treasure hunt ends normally
The first stage is over!
It's time for those who didn't find a treasure box
to leave the grounds.
Good work!
Huh? She said they're leaving
Wait a minute
Am I just going to be left here?
Staff!
I'm here! It's Panther's Ogata!
I've fallen into a hole!
The possibility that they may be left behind
is starting to feel more and more real.
Then after another 15 minutes,
They hear the sound of the crew leaving
Cars!
I hear cars!
Hey!
Wait!
Wait wait wait wait
I'll do it now. One moment
Hey, wait a second
I hate you guys! Damn
You've really done it now
Hey!
What's going on ...
At this point they've
spent at least an hour in the hole
The staff have gone home for sure
This place is huge
Why would you film here?
The wild dogs are going to come out
Have you forgotten this?
If you have, this show's going to be awful
The suspicion that they've been forgotten
turns into certainty for some
And then...
Oh
Wait a moment
Something's been left here. Look
It's something about hole traps
"King of Chair"?
(Nakano) 2010?
What is this?
He thinks it's been there since then
- Wow
- This is elaborate
Could this be a hole from a TV show from 11 years ago?
Did I fall into a hole they abandoned 10 years ago?
Yes, we want them to think that this hole was created for an old TV show full of such traps called "King of Chair"...
"King of Chair"
and then forgotten about.
This is scary
It's becoming real now
To achieve this,
we created the hole a month ago
and aged it artificially
Furthermore, inside it
we buried things that appear to have
fallen in 11 years ago
Huh, so this isn't a prank? This kind of thing...
Did I just happen to fall in?
This is really something made for TV, isn't it?
Oh man, I started paying into my pension recently. Is this divine punishment?
Hey! Help!
Help!
The details of today's prank
Fake show from another TV network
Cars departed from production company's building
A shoot that the staff might forget easily
18 dummy comedians
Materials from 11 years ago in the hole
At the start they were free to choose a start point from numbers 1 to 30 but
whichever number they chose they were given one of 30 maps
that directed them to the hole
With this intricate deception,
almost all members think they've
had an extremely rare accident with an old hole trap.
Except for this man
I've had enough
This is messed up
I give up
Stupid mosquitos
Insect spray
Give me some
Lady AD
Get me some tea
He still has no doubt that this is a prank
At this point 1 hours and 30 minutes
have elapsed since they fell
The members,
sensing that no help is coming
attempt to somehow escape by themselves.
Damn...
This is slippery
Ahh, frogs! There are frogs, look
But the weak foothold,
3.3 meter wall,
and just in case,
oiled wall,
leave them at their wits' end.
This is disgusting
And so it began.
The prank on the other side of the fall
What will be the fate of the five of them?!
I see. That's the start
Wait, "the fate of the five of them"?
Aren't we going to help them?
This is amazing
- Amazing
- It is
There's so many fine details.
They really believe it
From the old show,
showing them that
It's elaborate
It's like Squid Game
What did the staff oil the walls for?
Also
Out of the dummy
comedians you used
Poor Yutti
Yutti
- He was there?
- He wasn't on screen long
Well-known comedians like
Yutti and Joyman
Joyman
Ah, so you used proper
comedians
To make it real
They'll believe this
If a skull comes out now, that's it
- Yeah…
- That'd be so scary
Like a number of people
had met a similar fate there
Today's investigation
is planned to last 6 hours until 8pm
But after only 2 hours...
I've fallen down a hole. It seems like a long time ago
Damn it
I'm tired
and hungry
Calm down. Just calm down
My mind's all over the place
Just calm down
Enya-san, Enya...
I'll sing Enya
Calm. I have to be calm
Frog!
Oh no, the GoPro's gone
I stepped on the GoPro
The GoPro's broken!
Wow
I said enough
Nadal uses his trademark lying
to try to lure out the staff to no avail
Three hours have now passed since they fell
The time is 5pm
The GoPro's died
Whatever
Nadal's lies turn into reality
I don't know anymore. The lens is brown
Sorry
I don't know anymore. Sorry, camera people
Hey, the camera died
This is it
This is my last chance
In the name of the father, son, and holy spirit
Our father who art in heaven. Hallowed be thy name
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done, as in heaven and on earth
Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners,
now, and at the hour of our death. Amen.
Chance's prayers go unanswered
I'm numb
It's no good. I'm going to die of dehydration
Then, Nadal's lying spreads to another man
3 hours ago
I finished all my tea. So dumb
I'm thirsty
Then...
I'll show you the spirit of an Amagasaki brown rat
It's full of moisture
Amazingly the wet fallen leaves supply moisture
There's moisture!
The time is 5:30pm
Sunset at last
Seriously?
Which show is this?
My leg's broken
He knows these tactics are pointless
It got caught on something weird and broke
Excuse my. My leg... ouch
The degree to which they think it's an accident
Nadal
Nakano
Shūhei
Ketsu
Ogata
Chance
At this point, one person
thinks it's a TV show prank:
Nadal.
Two are unsure if it's real or fake:
Nakano and Ketsu
And two are completely convinced
it's an accident:
Ogata and Chance.
Of the two sure
it's an accident,
Chance is trying to
stay alive in the hole
Whereas Ogata...
I'm going to climb it
Let's go
He resolves to climb out by himself
And so he ties his jersey
together into a rope
Rope 5m from
the bottom of the hole
trying to hook it on a
rope passing over the hole
so he can climb out.
Then...
Agh, this is the worst
(Ogata) Agh, the worst
This is horrible
He threw it without
holding onto one side
and loses it.
(Ogata) The worst
Whereas Kaerutei's Nakano...
No longer hoping for salvation
or escape, he's sleeping
What am I meant to do here?
It's just me in a hole
How is that funny?
With no jersey, Ogata
ties together all his clothes and helmet
to make an even longer rope
Naked and determined to try again
But it seems unlikely it can
reach the rope 5 meters away
4 hours since they fell
As this is happening,
the area turns pitch black.
So this is my life now
I'm not sure what's happening
I'm losing strength for some reason
So many mosquitoes
After being woken up by bugs, Nakano→
devises anti-insect countermeasures
and then goes back to sleep
Audio person, sorry. I'm borrowing this
Waist pouch for
pin microphone
Using the waist pouch for his
pin microphone,
Ogata improves his homemade rope
by making it even longer
Close
He continues trying,
with 27 attempts
It's hooked
Making a hook with the helmet,
At last he's connected
with the overhead rope
Ah, what to do...
Aaahhhh!
Defeat
Shit!
What's happening here?
What a boring project
It's the most boring project I've ever seen
Let me out
The time is 6.30pm
At this point we induce even
more fear with new tactics
Beware of wild dogs!
Wild dogs have been
spotted in this area.
Please do not approach
or feed them.
A dog barking
Isn't that a wild dog?
He puts his helmet on,
just in case
Woof
Woof woof
Woof woof woof
He intimidates the dog
Then...
Gunfire warning!
Please be aware
there are houses
in this area.
Gunshots
Gunshots?
Five hours have passed since they fell
It's 7pm
Ogata the primitive man's
rope has another success
Ah, looks good
- Can he？
- He can
Agh, so close!
Defeat
Damn it!
After that, even though he's able to get his rope
to hook onto the other one
the hook is unable to
support Ogata's body weight.
But, after 2 hours
the man who continued
trying non-stop
receives a huge win.
Come down
Good
He got the rope
Yes. Yes yes yes yes
I got it
OK OK OK OK
Tree
Post
The rope came off the post on one side
and now hangs like a
spider's thread from heaven
I got it. Yes!
What do I do with it?
It's a bit thin
I've got it
That's it. I've got it. Alright
Making a loop with the rope
he creates a foothold
exhibiting an uncharacteristic level of wisdom.
I had an epiphany
And then
Ah, I can't. It hurts
The top's slippery
After five and a half hours his hand finally reaches the ground 3 meters above him
Ouch
Huh? Huh?
Come on...
No, stop
Stop, stop
Really?!
He's literally lost his lifeline
No way...
As for the other survivor, Chance Ōshiro
I'm thirsty
And then he does something unbelievable
which we cannot broadcast
Wow
- Incredible
- (Naomi) Wow
(Naomi) It's really amazing
5 hours and 45 minutes since they fell
What time is it?
Anyone, even someone like an old guy I don't know is fine
Help me
It won't be long before something like that
So, in response to the request
Aaaahh!
Please help me
Do you have a rope ("himo")?
Sweet potato ("imo")?
Himo. "Hi-"
Imo?
Himo
Not imo
We send in an
old man with conversational difficulties
Imo
Himo
"Hi-"
OK fine. Imo please. Imo
Imo please
Imo is fine too. I'm hungry. Roasted imo
I don't get it
Why don't you understand it anymore?
Hey you old fart
Mind your words
As the last trick, each will get a different kind of character throw in
And following from there we will reveal the prank
Next, for Chance...
Aaaahh! Aah ah ah. Huh?
Foreigner who can't speak Japanese
(Chance) Who are you?
A ghost?
Aaaah! Wait a moment. Wait a moment
As usual, Chance exceeds
our expectations
Glory to the Sutra, Glory to the Sutra, Glory to...
Let me into Nirvana quickly please. Let me in...
Are you a ghost?
Huh?
Are you human?
Are you currently alive?
Are you foreign?
Ah, then, you're an actively serving person?
You're actively serving as a human, right?
A currently serving human?
Could you pull me out?
Huh?
You only have to help me once
We can talk after
Oh oh aahhh wait
(Misspoken) No way! Hey!
Next is Nakano
Help me
Speechless child
And then for Ketsu
Oh my god
Ah, could you tell me who you are?
Huh?
Good evening
Speechless old man
Are you from around here?
Who are you?
I don't know what you're going to do so I'm a bit scared...
This is so scary
It's so bad
And last is Ogata
But because he's still struggling
with his escape attempt,
we decide not
to interfere,
Planned character
Director with communication difficulties
and to see what
happens for a bit longer.
And so, 6 hours since they fell,
for the remaining four...
we reveal the prank now
We done?
So smooth
What is this?
(Staff) It's Suiyoubi no Downtown
Thought so
It was so long
Wh- what is this?
The one where you send in the angry old fart?
What was that? Seriously
We explain the project to Nadal
Staff) Nadal-san, today's project was to spend 6 hours in a hole
6 hours
I came here intending to win prize money, you know
It's just going to be the normal appearance fee with this
Downtown-san, we'll only get 10000 yen for all the work we do
Staff) I suppose you want to use the toilet now?
Please don't ask me that question so calmly. "Want to"?
I've been stuck here for 6 hours, haven't I?
It's not "want to use the toilet?"
Staff) At the end there...
Enough of this. Are you going to let me out?
Next is Nakano
Prank Reveal
Ah, oh my god
It's...
Is it over? Can I finish this now?
(Staff) How do you feel now?
How I feel? Horrible!
Above ground for the first time in 6 hours
I'm happy
So deep!
Prank Reveal
Next is Ketsu
Oh my god
(Staff) Good evening
Good evening
His eyes
Ketsu shows Kingdom-level shock
Um, earlier, an old man I don't know came here
Staff) What?
An old man I don't know
Staff) Who was it?
I don't know
Next is Chance
Prank Reveal
Huh?
What?
Huh? What?
What is this?
Someone's here. I'm happy. Someone's here
I've been buried in a mountain before. 27 years ago
Staff) Is that so?
Yes
But this was probably harder than back then
Ah, I'm happy. Yay!
Woah, there's so many people
Thank you so much everyone
Everyone, thank you very much. Thank you
After all he's been through, he unexpectedly kneels down on the ground in gratitude
And so, what is the fate of the
one person remaining, Ogata?
- Wow amazing
- Yes
- Wow
- So then...
Matsumoto-san, what did you think?
They didn't really say "help me!",
even when they saw people
That's right, yes
- They thought it was a ghost
- Yes
Either that or the person
who made the hole
They thought for a moment
"is this something he does to people?"
- Would they think that?
- Isn't it scary?
Like "I've been caught in this person's trap"
- Yes
- That's also possible
Like he's done it to them. Definitely
Oh and also,
Ogata-kun's rope
- It came off the tree, right?
- Yes
I have a hunch the staff did it
Yeah! It was tightly
bound to it at the start
Right? They were like 'Ah, he's
going to escape! Someone untie it'
The staff here seem
like they'd do that
I'm sure that's not true
- Is that so?
It feels like they just cut the end of the rope
- Suspicious, isn't it?
- It is
They wouldn't go so far
Ah, but I wanted him to escape
Yeah. Just a bit more and he could've done it
So we've made an exception for Ogata
- That's right. For Ogata-kun,
it's become something to escape
Just to see what happens
6 hours since falling
After the rope, which had been his
only hope up to this point,
came loose from the tree
it had been attached to,
Ogata was in despair.
However...
I won't give up!
I've got this rope now so
I'm going to be positive
Not discouraged from this harsh situation,
he ties together his helmet and the rope
and creates a new item.
He aims for above ground once more
And then...
Wow, the distance
is totally different
He makes his biggest throw of the day
Rope
Wire
He succeeds in getting it
caught on a strong wire
over twice as far as
the original rope
However...
Damn it
The connection is too weak
and it comes off straightaway.
It's fine. It's not electric
It'll do
After confirming there's no risk of electric shock,
Ogata starts trying again
And so here we have
his 113th throw of the day
By skilfully
rotating the rope
he manages to get it caught
and attached to wire
Alright!
Then by passing the other end→
through a metal fixture
he discovered inside the hole,
he makes the rope taut
and completes a suspension
bridge to the surface.
However...
Ouch, my foot hurts
It hurts and I've got no strength
Because he's putting his
whole body weight on the thin rope
his aching hands and feet mean
he's unable to climb and he gives up
Ouch, my leg's got a cramp
Ouch
And then Ogata devises his next plan
Screwdriver substitute
Using the end of a zipper
as a screwdriver,
he takes a screw out of the wall
Seriously?
Amazing
By cutting through the
thick protective sheet
and digging out the
styrofoam inside
he creates footholds
to climb with
Foothold
Planning to use both
of these to make his jailbreak,
Taut rope
it's Ogata, the wrongly convicted lifer
And then...
Distributing his body weight
between the rope and foothold,
and steadier than ever
he reaches the top of the hole
I'm not going to give up
Wow, so cool
Attempt number
And then,
after that
Aaaahhh
Ogata just keeps attacking
Damn it!
Damn it! Ugh
And then...
He finally holds the edge
with both hands
Like that?
It can't be possible
Aaagh
My hands can't hold it anymore
While climbing the wall,
he makes more footholds
in ever higher places.
No matter how many times
he fails, ittle by little→
Ogata's getting closer to the surface.
However...
Huh?
The rope he worked so hard to
get caught on the wire comes off
It's the worst thing
that could've happen
No way, it's breaking
Then, holding the screw in his mouth,
Ogata resumes his attack using the remaining climbing-only route
Attempt number
- He's crying
- It's disappointing
Because he
got so close
It's already been 7 hours since he fell
Ogata's mind and body
are reaching breaking point.
While the staff are preparing→
to rescue him and reveal the prank→
if the need rises
Ogata stands up once more.
He won't give up.
He's really something
- He's a tough guy
- Can he do it?
And then...!
- Come on, come on!
- Go!
Ogata's magnificent escape!
What is this?
What are you doing?
I'm so annoyed
What's funny about this?
It has to be Suiyoubi no Downtown, right?
(Staff) Yes
Of course it is
Were you planning to leave me in there for a week?
(Staff) We weren't really expecting you to climb out...
Isn't it...
You wanted me to climb out, didn't you?
(Staff) This wasn't about climbing out
But I did it before. At the smoking area
Smoking area
(Ogata)
Wasn't this like that?
(Staff) What was the hardest part?
All of it
My hands hurt, it was slippery
I reached my limit
I can't feel my hands anymore
It was really tough. The toughest thing I've ever done
I'm completely out of strength
(Staff) Good work
(Staff) Thank you. Well done
Thank you...
(Staff) How about some water and a shower?
What's this going to look like? I'm naked
(Staff) We'll put a mosaic on for that
Was it funny?
(Staff) Yes, it's fine
(Staff) It was funny
And so Ogata, after 7 hours and 12 minutes,
makes a safe journey home
He was angry
Yes he was
Of course he was angry
He looked like a hero
I couldn't hold back my tears
- He was so cool
- So cool
I came here expecting
something light
- Right?
- I never thought I'd be moved this much
- You're right
- But it really was amazing
I was just thinking but→
Do we really need the mosaic there?
No, sorry.
It is TV after all
- But because it's so moving
- Exactly
It felt like we were watching The Shawshank Redemption
- The jailbreak one?
- You're right
We were all rooting
for him at the end
We really were
Ogata's inspired the whole country
You're right. He didn't give up
- Amazing
- I really admire him
Next time will we make the hole 8 meters?
- Would we do this again?
- So good
★Subbed by fmck fansubs★
reddit.com/u/fmckfansubs
patreon.com/fmck
Next week, it's an
Everyone's Theories Special
Can a pro wrestler hold his fountain opponent down until the count of three?
- Hold on Nadal, hold on
- OK
Will they stay on hold
for their senpai for 10 minutes?
And...
Is harvesting the
bontan fruit
TL note: I'll explain next time
also called bontan hunting?
And the ineffective megaphone theory
All the detailed theories we've
accumulated will be released at once!
Shut up!