Today's Wednesday Downtown is...
When promised an appeareance on "Championship Special", you'll gladly accepted the offer, but when it turns out you're actually a guest on the "Introducing the Crown of the World" special, it's difficult to refuse说
The name of this theory is so long
-Yes
In light of the fact that the number of super-long theories increase every year
We will rank theories by the number of words they are comprised of
Long Theory Name Ranking Special
So, first of all, at 10th place
4 theories with the same amount of words
The specific word count is
An FBI inspector who is capable of seeing the answer on an foam board, they won't jump into a hole even if they don't know the answer 说
56 characters
In addition to these,
These two theories have the same number of words
As does this...
Even if you are told by your manager that "a weekly magazine will publish your scandal tomorrow", if you are a professional artist, you will still finish the day's work without any problems
The method to test the theory is
Three people who are in high spirits are targeted with a fake location shoot
During a break,
The scandal is revealed separately
First of all, Nadal
I have something to tell you
-Can't we talk about it here?
It's a little scary
Being brought to another room
They are informed of content of the report
Excuse me, I'd like to ask
Did you go to a party with some women at the end of last year?
The end of last year?
Around December time
Scary
This must feel pretty bad
Honestly, I didn't drink with any women
How can I say... there are photos in this report
A press release was also made
So, he is given it to look at
※Japanese law prohibits drinking alcohol under the age of 20
"Suspected of drinking with an 18-year-old high school girl"
A very serious scandal
What's this? Tsk!
You'd certainly be depressed
What's all this writing?
Tsk!
He's got a bad feeling
Minors?
Yes, 2 months before this location shooting
The theory began...
Good work, everyone!
We've certainly worked hard
A memorable party with close comedian friends
Sorry
Good evening
These ones are the type that we like
Pretending to be a girl and her friend whom the latter comedian knows
Very beautiful girl
The girls begin to set the trap
You can't do this!
Nadal must've thought he wont the lottery with these girls
This is bad!
It's true that they were indeed drinking together
So, at this time, the preparation for the theory was completed
Indeed
By the way,
The girl purposely placed next to Nadal is not actually underaged, it's just a setup
Just a setup
One of the others brought them
I can confirm that
Hey? Tsk
How old are you guys?
I am 22 years old
I'm 20 years old - 20 years old?
Wait a minute, you sure you're not 19 years old?
20 years old
-Please be serious
We are really skirting the line of the law
So true
Yes, and underage drinking can be a problem, especially in this period
-It is true
※20 year-old Tomohisa Yamashita was exposed for drinking with underage
I seriously confirmed that she was over 20 years old
It's the other guy that's the bad one
This is a
Tsk
This guy's a nutcase
There's really something wrong with his brain
You'd definitely be angry
These guys in Shibuya are all the same
These Tokyo people are all out of their minds
Crazy people all together, crammed into a crazy place
This is probably why weed is so big in Tokyo
I hate Tokyo because of this
This place has too many nutcases
I've never met even a single decent person here
Tsk
Angrily turning his anger toward the entire area of Tokyo
Hahaha why?
Apart than that,
I can't believe they wrote this
This "abysmal" tag
"Going with a minor" this sort of statement
They'd definitely say it
Can't believe they'd write "Abysmal, going with a minor"
It's over, he's going crazy
Writing this, it's really made me angry, tsk
I only have this bad sort of press, tsk
Always tutting
My press is all this type of gossip
Who even cares about this stuff anymore, tsk
He's saying a lot to his manager
He repeatedly says "Who cares?"
The report also mentions matters related to "sexual harassment"
I don't remember...
I really don't remember
It says in the middle of the article
Is there any possibility you said something like that?
I didn't, no way
"Have you had any action recently?"
To be honest Marin is in a very dangerous situation
It's definitely likely that you'd be targeted by men
Have any men been after you recently?
Have you had any action recently?
No comment
Marin you can hide behind this and whisper it to me
So many questions
But, how can I say...
"Have you had any action recently?" isn't really a sexual harassment kind of tone
"Have you had any action lately" is
When I said it I was like "Have you had any action"
Good thing the manager held back his laughter
Just now, it went up!
Can I talk to Yasumura later?
-I don't think so...
This is information we are getting in advance
So the two people there, and your wife, can't be told yet
Ah, so painful...
Please do not disclose it to anyone else
Such a liar
Still need to do the location shoot, what else needs to be recorded...
Don't pretend, don't pretend
And so, the result of this report
Nadal's main concern is...
This is so tragic
I still have an ad. What about that?
How can I put it? Probably also...
Wait, slow down a sec, this is too painful
That's too bad!
So painful, so painful
So painful, so painful, so painful
Yes
By this time, Nadal's commercial had already been shot
No Soup Guy Curry Rice
Curry that is fun to stir up
Thick and hard to spill
If it's noodles it will overflow with soup
It's curry rice without soup
There is really none?
It is without
No soup convenient curry rice
So the ad will just disappear?
According to the current situation, the probability is that it will be scrapped...
If something happens, it'll definitely be canned
Headache, headache
My stomach hurts too
Why does your stomach hurt?
There is also the matter of today's location shoot
It'll probably also be scrapped
But please don't tell the others
Please continue filming as if nothing has happened
Advertisement...
What's going on?
Money money money
Tsk
This sucks
What is there to say...
Can't we do something? We have to get it withdrawn
Withdrawal is really...
I can't not have it withdrawn, these guys are writing nonsense!
That alcohol... it was mine
Yeah...
No shit!
Hikaku paid...
You didn't pay!?
I really dont want to lose the advert
And so, he submits a request for withdrawal
This guy!
Get them to withdraw the article
This guy is really something
Seriously, how can we give in to this type of people
They're looking down on Yoshimoto
They do this kind of thing to blackmail people
This can't be done. This is a mess
Tsk, ahh...
So much to say!
If it does get published
Little mouth blazing
Tsk! Ah!
Withdraw the article
Just do it!
I really hope they will!
Ha...
This article is to be released
Shh!
Or... in all seriousness...
Shh, shh, shh, shh!
I know
He's getting louder
It sucks. It's so painful
What is this cough?
Damn, I don't feel well
This cough is definitely fake
Shriveling up straight away
He begins to feel unwell
Suddenly feeling unwell
Sorry to interrupt
The magazine's press release
So many lies
Must be painful
Recording continues
What will happen?
What will become of it?
Thank you
-Hello everyone
Great!
Yes!
Something's off
Just a little
What is this?
The energy is all off!
Contrasting the two who are still in high spirits
No sound at all
Nadal is moody in comparison to before
So, the next step is to tell Yasumura
That…
I've received some... bad reports
Eh？
The most uncomfortable point in time
18 year-old female high school student
It's over
"Decided to report Yasumura"
I asked her age, she said "20 years old"
So I'm not a criminal, right?
This is the end!
Do I need a lawsuit?
There was sexual harassment, right?
Sexual harassment?
Yasumura's already drunk, right?
Not drunk yet
Already drunk
Ah, I'm drunk
"I didn't want to look, but he made me look at his nipples"
"and forced me to toast by touching a glass to his nipples"
I guess it's true
You did it?
You really did it!
I did show her my nipples
What the hell?
Pull down from the top!
The worst thing to do
So awful!
Nipple Toast
What the hell? Nipple toast?
So cold!
Seems to be enjoying himself
So yes, the party was full of sexual harassment, so to speak
So rotten
If this is true, then I'm afraid...
I'll definitely be fired, especially in this day and age...
In the case of dismissal...
-Worst case scenario is dismissal, but thats the worst case scenario
Well... actually 99% of people would be fired, right?
It's still inside information
Fact checking of those involved is still in progress
Anyway, today we have to work as usual
The manager is really convincing
That's what needs to happen?
It is because fact checking is needed as soon as possible
This Yoshimoto agent is probably used to this kind of situation
So I have to inform you of this situation
Is this how it's going to be? Continue with this location shoot
So, Yasumura returns to the scene with a sense of retirement
Recording continues
How did it turn out?
Thank you
OK
Next up
Only Ogata is left to rush forward
Popularity among women matchup
Wow!
Yasumura now doesn't know where or how to direct his energy
30 minutes ago, the Yasumura was very cheerful
Became the Yasumura that is unable to play dumb
Even
0 points
I'm overwhelmingly superior!
From time to time, sad memories suddenly come rushing to Yasumura
So pitiful looking
Onto the final target, Ogata
This will be the end if it comes out
Drinking with underage people
Yes, minors
"Drinking, but no thank you"
Using my line in such a way...
This terminology is completely finished
It's done with
This girl is only 18?
-18
Doesn't she not look that young?
No, how can I put it...
She didn't look that young... she even had grey hair
Absolutely not
Would you drink with people like that?
Not only did she have gray hair...
But her skin didn't look very smooth either, skin really wasn't that good
That doesn't matter
In addition to this, there is a problem
Ah, what's wrong?
-It's written here
Behavior related to sexual harassment
Did this actually happen?
There was no sexual harassment
-Really?
Really, I swear I didn't
I have a wife and children
I still have to pay the loan on my house off for 33 years
Why would I do something like that?
I'm not doubting you
What can I say? For the modern day Yoshimoto...
Lying is really unforgivable
I know
Too convincing
No, if it's a lie...
Yes...
Does what's written here match the facts?
What the hell, is it or not
The phrase "want to get it on" was said
Did you say it?
Just as a joke
It's really more fun to drink with girls like this
Want to get it on ah, want to get it on ah
What about the hair?
Did you smell it?
Yeah, I think I smelled it...
But there was no actual contact with the hair
It is unclear why Ogata confessed to a crime he didn't commit
Perhaps if pressed hard enough, they'll confess regardless
No... is smelling someone's hair something that is forbidden to do?
You didn't smell it!
What is this, which law says you can't do such a thing?
Sexual harassment is defined as
The moment the other person feels uncomfortable, it constitutes sexual harassment
Wait a minute, I'm begging you...
It's unclear how this will be handled
But the publication is certain
No... what can I do after?
The thought that this won't blow over comes into play
At this point
Will everyone there be involved?
Can the others be blocked out?
It's going to be published either way, so maybe then can avoid taking heat for it
He's taking responsibility
This way, the others involved...
There's no need to involve all of them, right?
The manliness of Ogata,
Brings an end to this section
And the location shoot continues
By this point all three must be emotionally drained
And so,
Ah…
What a gloomy scene this is
The room resembles a funeral scene
And so, the location recording, which everyone was sure would be scrapped, resumes
5 seconds till start
4 3 2
What will happen?
Ok...
It's completely different
2 hours ago, the recording began with incredibly high energy
That's so funny
Can only clap their hands
A calm atmosphere makes one wonder if its a different program
At least they all turned up
Perform properly!
One of the most obvious is Ogata
He's just been told after all
Lets complete to find the best place to go in Venus Fort!
Nadal is still working hard
Please feel free to walk around the building
Raise your hand when you find it
Ok
It seems that tears are falling
Nothing can be done, you've still got family at least
It's really bad...
After that, a fortune teller is visited
And all recording for the day is finished
Afterwards, for the three people who left the scene
Fake weekly reporters arrive for surprise interviews
How will they react?
Really a full set of drama, eh?
Three people? Three people together?
Thank you for your hard work. Sorry to interrupt
About the report of drinking with minors
Is there any discrepancy with the truth?
-I'm very sorry. I'm very sorry.
You're admitting it? Admitting it happened? That's the truth, right?
-I'm sorry
No... I didn't ask her age, I'm sorry
Is this your confession?
No... I...
Yes, this...
Yes
Because the age wasn't confirmed
Eh?
-Sorry
Ogata? Who are you referring to?
Ogata?
-It's me
Uh, me too...
-I don't think so
"Me too"
I've also been told...
Hey, why... Yasumura too?
I was also told before that I was drinking with an underage girl
My manager said during the break
Sexual Harassment
-Yeah sexual harassment!
Ah, then it's the same
Well, you can also apologize, together we can...
Me too
Eh, what's going on here?
Hold on a second
-Wait a minute!
Hey, what's going on?
-No, I was...
Eh, wait a minute, eh?
So interesting
And so, the situation was revealed
Wow, so it was the same person?
-Really?
That's great. That's really great
That's great. Such a terrible thing...
-So close
It won't be published, right?
Wow, that's great
-I'm so happy!
I thought I was going to die this time, really
-So dangerous
You don't know how terrible I felt...
Next is the 9th super long theory
With a total of 57 characters
When encountering a middle-aged man wearing a bowler hat and holding a cane in an unusually long alleyway, you'll be extremely cautious
That's for sure!
Ungirls' Tanaka is called to a fake meeting
Tanaka
How will Tanaka react?
The meeting room is inside
-Good, good
Too weird
So that's the setup
Tanaka is lured through this area with various outrageous reasons
It's like that
Yeah
From directly ahead, the strangely-dressed middle-aged man is released
What is the result?
That's definitely the guy
Looks like it
He'll certainly shout
How can there be such a person
Absolutely shout
Waiting for him to say hello?
Ah…
A little bit too cautious, right?
Sure enough, he's wary
A bit wary
The theory is thus proved correct
As this has proved to be a good opportunity, we continue experimenting
Can't you just shout?
It's very simple, anyone can do it
Tanaka is then forced to watch as the AD asks the extra why he didn't shout in the distance
Is it alright if we walk back again... from there?
Can we go back?
-Ok...
Too tiring
The staff requests a second take
He already knows
Still wont shout, right?
Still, the shout doesn't materialize
So...
What's going on?
-I'm sorry
Why didn't you shout?
You're supposed to yell when you get right next to him, right?
-Yes, sorry
Can you do it? Do you need to practice?
Looking straight at them
Please do it
OI!!!!
Louder
OI!!!
Louder!
Still not loud enough
OI!!!
Shout it out, shout it out!
With the unexpected occurrence of seeing someone practice how to shout from a distance
Shouted out so loudly already
Tanaka couldn't help but laugh
How can it be so obviously visible
And so, the third take begins
Third already
The others were all the same
How will it turn out I wonder
OI!!!
Wrong, wrong
You did it wrong...
Yeah, seriously
Too exhausting
Did it wrong...
And so the truth is revealed
What? What? What is this?
I don't get you guys
"Being suspiciously lead into a long alley way backstage"
"When a middle-aged man with weird style walks past"
"You'd be wary"
Yes, it's a time to be vigilant
At first...at first I
The fact that I knew what was going on was obvious from my face
It was obvious
Yeah
-Right!?
This disqualifies me as an entertainer
Next at 8th place with 59 characters are these 2 theories from last year
The third was...
When arguing endlessly on the phone, to show they are right, the first thing the person will say after hanging up is "See?"
So, the verification begins
Komen...
By the way, he's a junior high school graduate, right?
They say he's a junior high school graduate
He actually graduated from high school
No... junior high school graduation, right?
He's not a junior high school graduate
Eh, really?
-Yeah
Really?
Eh? No way!
A debate begins
What a tiresome argument
I want to make sure, seriously
Hello?
Sorry to trouble you, Komen
Tsuneida is wondering...
We're both drinking
And he's talking nonsense
He says you're a junior high school graduate, but you're a high school graduate, right?
Right?
Komen is actually a high school graduate
So, will he say "See!"?
It depends on when you hang up
Okay, sorry
Here we go, will he say it?
You were saying?
Didn't say it
The next item on the list in 7th place is 3 60-character theories
First of all
For smoker comedians, if their cigarette is lit, even if the staff looks pale and says, "Your partner has fainted," he will not throw away the cigarette but will take a puff first
In any case, you must immediately put out the cigarette
Itakura has fainted
He suddenly fell down clutching his chest
What do we do?
Can you come?
Let's go
Took a few puffs
This one took two puffs
Such a big puff, such a big puff
Hesitantly hesitated
What a big mouthful!
Inhaled
Look! Look at the lag time!
This scumbag adult, such a big puff
Before rushing to his partner's side, he quickly puffs away
It lasted for a while
Two strong puffs
He was really smoking!
So, the truth is revealed
Eh?
No, no, no, no. What?
Didn't you faint?
Fainted...
No, then you're not... eh?
I fainted and yet i'm the last consideration
What's wrong with you?
What the hell is this?
Seriously, you're a terrible person
-What? Did I smoke?
Hopeless
Someone says to you "Your partner fainted"
You "Hey? Really? I see."
Is it reasonable?
What, what is this?
What the hell?
The embers were blazing!
Orange fire glowing brightly
What are you doing to me?
Why am I being mentally disturbed by this damn show
It's too much
The remaining 2 in 7th place are the chick theory and...
Baseball teams with kids who can just about step up to the batting cage have too small a strike zone and can thus win due to foul balls
The No.1 batter is the shortest child on the team, Takeouchi Hayate, who is 2 years and 1 month old.
Just 2 years and 1 month
Height 83cm
You can do it!
Aim over there
Let's get started. One, two,
Here comes the ball!
Looking at mom
Look at the pitcher!
Depends on the pitcher
Foul
It's high. It's a little high
Generally speaking this ball is on the low side
But this time it was on the high side
Good foul ball
So small
Look over there
Over there
Look at the big brother over there
Mamma
The next 2nd ball
Strike
Good shot
With strong adaptability, the second pitch was a strike
However, afterwards
High, too high!
Too high!
Frequent foul balls
Just OK
Later, two good and three foul balls
Not even watching
It's over
The No. 1 hitter cries
It's fine, it's fine
So the game was suspended
Afterwards, after 10 minutes of mom's reassurance
So long
Stay here. Don't move
Look at the toy, look
Smile
Guaranteed success
No more crying
Throwing while his attention is elsehwere
It is really too difficult
The height is too small resulting in great difficulty
Smaller than I expected
The same goes for the second person
The ball height is not low enough to guarantee delivery
And so, in line with the theory, runners are located on first and second base
The third batter steps up
Swing
Strike
It's still possible
Swinging the bat
Suddenly, having a vague understanding of baseball becomes an achilles' heel
Swing
Strike three
Due to swinging at every ball, the batter strikes out
Swinging the bat helped give me points
No. 4 is also struck out
Number 5 is also guaranteed
Bases are loaded
The bases are now loaded and the pitcher is in crisis
Is this how you play baseball?
Not only that
2 outs with bases loaded and balls in play
Come on!
Great fighting spirit!
This is the moment when a man must draw out his power
Don't swing it, don't swing it
Strike three!
Awesome!
Safe!
Super Long Theory Ranking
Next is this theory for 6th place
and another
When an angry person on the phone says "Wait there, i'm coming", no matter how the person looks you won't question their appearance
Tsuda is talking to his junior, Rice Sekimachi on the phone
The content is that he's suspicious of Sekimachi as people have been saying bad things about him
What the fuck did you say?
So much anger
Sorry
Other juniors told me you bad-mouthed me. You're disgusting
Is this something that people do?
Sorry, I...
Hey, don't try and apologize your way out of it
Good acting
What happened?
Still with the fucking "what?"
I was so angry when I heard yesterday so I wanted to call you
And then
I'm going over there now, you wait for me there, i'm really fucking angry!
And so,
Tsuda's change in appearance is...
Barefoot
OK
I go barefoot
-Barefoot
Would you realize?
OK
I'll freak out and make him focus on my face
Can he make the other side not ask himself about his current state?
What is the result?
Scary!
Hey, Sekimachi!
Oh, scared the hell out of me
Oi!
Good morning
What's wrong with you?
What did you do?
Realized?
What do you do? I'm asking you a question!
He's looking at the feet
I have been told by my juniors
Who the fuck are you to say that about me?
What are you doing?
You're barefoot?
Being barefoot has nothing to do with it!
So quick!
Instant kill
What are you doing?, you're barefoot?
Being barefoot has nothing to do with it!
He's concerned
So Tsuda was defeated swiftly in just 13 seconds
So quick
The truth is revealed
Kept looking at the feet
Whoa, what?
Really..what the heck!?
Thank you for your hard work
Don't "thank you for your hard work"
He's angry
After all, being scolded...
The project is explained to Sekimachi, who was a bit angry
No... I immediately noticed your bare feet
Too fast
Walking with this "slapslapslap" sound
You didn't think he was too angry to point it out?
I honestly just thought he'd gone insane
What is this?
So dirty
-So dirty
Next the top 5 super long theories are revealed
Alone at 5th place is
When asking the age of an old man who is obviously over 80, and you get an impossible answer like "60 years old", you'll still end up saying "you don't look that old"
So, the 89-year-old grandfather, who is surely not 60 years old, appears
How did it turn out?
How old are you?
6...60 years old?
-Yes
Ah, but ah...
You look very youthful
In response to the unexpected answer, Ogata replied, "you look very youthful"
Does this mean he looks like more than 50 years old
60 years old?
-Yes
Really?
Does anyone ever say "looks like more than that"?
It has been said
Yeah thought so
Is this deliberate...
This is a sweater for people over 60 years old, right?
-Is it?
Is it not?
-No
Already too much
Eh?
60 years old, that's not...
Still talking
Ishibashi Taka and others...
Born in Showa 36
That is, more than...
16 years older than me
Can 16 years older... oh I see...
You're the same age as Tunnels?
-Yes
So persistant!
It can't be...
No other questions at all
-Yeah
Perhaps comedians just look young...
Next at fourth place is
If an old man who suddenly instructed a segment on TV appeared a few days later as a director, his advice would be hastily taken to heart
Next in third place is
This theory introduced at the beginning of the program, with 66 character
Eh? The title is...
Crown program... ah
Next, the second highest number of words theory is
Even if a skit is initially not very funny, if good comedians take over and write a part each, it will eventually become more interesting
It's long
-Really long
By the way, this long theory originates with one of the member's of Knights
So,
Hello
-How are you?
It begins with determining the content and writing the first section
The skit is for a duo
It's about a taxi
After the performance, there's a questionnaire
It says "It's boring" or "same old stuff" or something like that
It's good to get perspective
As the skit that was initially performed live is not all that funny
This time, the setup is changed
The content is...
This is a person who has always had a hard time getting a taxi
The story of trying to stop a car
An idiot is driving a cab, and while driving a cab he's dozing off
The person trying to stop the car says "That's dangerous, is this driver ok?"
Then the cab slams into a wall
Boom, an accident
Then the man comes to the rescue
Saying "Is everything okay?"
"Where are you going?"
"I'm not getting in"
The person selected to take over the next part of the skit is...
Wow...okay
Am I pioneer in segment optimization?
-Yes
Sounds like a nice title...
What's worse is that after reading the beginning of the skit...
It's a bit difficult...
How to deal with the exchange...
And so, with much trouble, he finally manages to complete the second section
Afterwards, a collection of strong members continue the skit
Well, in order to put the whole context together
I did the best I could under the circumstances
The performers of the skit are...
Hello
Kamaitachi
After all, it's been written by famous people
If we can''t make it as funny as they want it to be
We'll get criticized afterwards
It's true, there's a lot of details, the tone and so on
I'm full of anxiety...
And so, two days later
In front of an audience that doesn't know anything, it's finally time to perform the skit
How will the finished product turn out?
Something has to happen
There's a worry that maybe the next person won't be able to continue it on
Super hard
It has to become more interesting
It becomes the thing that each person themselves likes
It's so hard to get a cab
Ah finally a taxi came, Taxi ~
What's wrong with that car?
The driver is asleep, right?
Ah, it's dangerous
Watch out!
Watch out, it's going to hit the wall!
Ah, an accident!
It completely became an accident
Is he okay?
Where are you going?
I'm not getting in!
I can't be a passenger, right?
The airbag is so slow...
You scared me
-You're similarly slow to react
Wow, this is bad. It's peak traffic time!
Can this go back in?
Eh?
The airbag, can it be stuffed back in?
Uh, I think they're mostly single-use
Ah, damn it, I wanted to drive a little longer
But the car is finished...
The front is flattened
Eh?
You're not injured or anything?
No i'm fine
Eh?
What's wrong?
I can't get out
Eh?
I'm stuck
Are you okay?
Eh?
Ah, i'm out
What's up with you?
Wow, seriously!? It's flattened
Why are you laughing?
Wow, this...
That stinks!
Did you shit yourself?
Ah, I have the vague memory of needing to go to the toilet before the accident happened
The impact of the accident forced it out?
Ha ha ha ha
That's it coming out, right?
I got out, this got out too
It's no laughing matter
Huh?
Ah, cat!
Ah, there's a cat!
What's up? Lonely?
No, it's stuck
It's completely stuck inside
What is it?
There are so many problems that I don't know where to start
Okay, let's start with the cat
It's poop, isn't it?
First
Calling the police is the right thing to do
Suddenly normal words came out
That's true
I'm in Akasaka 5-chome, I shit my pants
What's the use of this report?
Seems like they won't come
Of course
Eh... can you put this back?
What?
This!
How can you put that back
It's not good to improperly report the accident!
But how should I say it?
Just report the facts, right?
This statement is a bit difficult to make for the person involved in the accident itself
There's a cat.. can it be called a meow body accident
It'll be seen as bullshit
Combine that with the fact that I pooped in my pants
Could it be called a human fecal accident?
-Don't call it that
Don't get hung up on what to say exactly, just call them back
Eh?
People are starting to gather
What?
Someone wants to be picked up
Sorry, I can't take passengers now
A strange guy!
A strange guy on the same wavelength as this guy
Meow body accident? That's right
Human fecal accident? Yes certainly
Is this a pre-existing term? Am I the only one who doesn't know of it?
So it's impossible to carry passengers
No passengers after an accident
Eh? You're saying the car is empty?
As I said, an accident has happened
Eh? You're saying the anus is also empty?
No, it's something I can decide, maybe I can put it back
Weirdoes and weirdoes have become tangled
Weirdoes and weirdoes are fightings over a weird thing
What the hell is this situation?
Ah, are the police here?
Wait a minute. Here it comes. It's great
Huh? Words?
Weirdoes and weirdoes have become tangled
Weirdoes and weirdoes are fightings over a weird thing
Akiyama wrote this, right?
Strange people and strange...
Akiyama's part
Wait a minute. Hey, what's going on?
My name is Riverbank Ghost Light
Riverbank Ghost Light？
It's definitely Akiyama's work
Not in this form, but i've worked as a singer previously
What happened all of a sudden?
But Riverbank Ghost Light has not yet debuted
So i'm working hard as a driver to support my dream
You are developing too fast
Let me tell you what you said before
Weirdoes and weirdoes have become tangled
Weirdoes and weirdoes are fightings over a weird thing
This is the first time I have encountered such a resonant words
These are not lyrics
This encounter with you must also be fate
No, it's not
Let's sing together
Sing what?
Sing this situation out
No, it's too embarrassing
Weirdoes and weirdoes have become tangled
Weirdoes and weirdoes are fightings over a weird thing
Whose fault is it that it turned out this way?
The fault of the cat? Shit's fault?
It's your fault for driving tired
Yes, it's my fault for driving tired
Meow body or human feces or
This idiot or that idiot or
All are ~ because of ~ driving ~ tired ~
Please do not drive tired
No one's laughing
I guess it's better to broadcast an educational video as usual
No, live performances like this makes people happy the most
But they're not here to have fun, they're just here to renew their driver's licenses
Fine, let's start from the beginning again before the afternoon traffic rules study
Let's go
-What a pain
Wrapped up with foolishness
Thank you for your hard work
I'm a little confused...
Wasn't that really unfunny?
When reading the script, because we know the people that wrote it
In our minds, we could see the person talking, the person making jokes
It gave the feeling of "so interesting" and "so funny", but the result...
It's amazing how it all came together...
Well...I don't know if it's right to say so
From the beginning of Akiyama's section, it became really unfunny, right?
If Akiyama had performed it, it would have been funnier...
We practiced many times
More rehearsals than for the M-1 competition
It's impossible
-Impossible
Lastly, the number one ranking for the longest theory name is
Using a street-based sticker form of voting of who you'd rather sleep with, if singer Tortai Bukuro has 99 votes and Masaharu Fukuyama has 0 votes, the state of the possibility of going with Bukuro will increase
The winner clocks in at 75 characters
The above is the final ranking of the longest theory names
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03