Next, defendant, Onuma Akihiro, please come to the court.
Defendant, Onuma Akihiro.
He is the famous director of the Gaki no Tsukai.
He is a character that people should love.
However, the reality is very complicated.
It is clear that the people around him are causing a lot of trouble.
He was found guilty of murdering his wife.
He was sentenced to death and charged with the crime.
All the evidence and testimony are true.
We will now begin the trial of Akihiro Onuma.
Prosecutor Hamada, please present the evidence and testimony.
Yes.
Everyone, before that,
Yes?
Onuma-san is...
He is wearing a uniform.
That's right.
Please refer to that. That is the Kyo-Bi fishing board.
It's thick.
By the way, that jeans was also given to me by the TV program.
Coincidentally, that jeans was not given to the band.
Don't get a jean like that, Kyo-Bi.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
This time, I wanted everyone to understand the Onuma's location better.
We made a proof video.
That was a surprise.
I think Onuma-san had a lot of income back then.
But it was a surprise.
That was when Onuma invited me to a dinner with the three of us.
I'll pay for the rest, so eat whatever you like.
Thank you.
And the meal is over.
Onuma-san, I think 1000 yen each is enough for two people.
Oh, really? Then pay for it.
Thanks for the meal.
Yeah, sure.
Now, let's go.
How much was it?
1900 yen
What? Then give me 50 yen
It's 50 yen, it's my money, give it back
I invited him myself
It's 50 yen
I didn't believe that he would get so angry at 5 o'clock.
I was surprised at that time.
That was when I was in the A.D.
One day, it was time for dinner and we decided to order delivery food.
Onuma-san, I'm going to take out the food, what should I do?
Food? What should you do? The food is expensive
But this dough bento is 1000 yen, everyone will take this
Ah, really? Well, 1000 yen is fine
30 minutes later, the food arrives
Hello! Thank you for waiting
And the bunch started collecting money from everyone and went to Onuma
Onuma-san, it's 1030 yen
What's 1030 yen?
It says 1000 yen here
Why is there 30 yen?
It's just a small amount
I didn't hear that!
You said 1000 yen
I won't pay you any more than that!
I was really angry.
I paid 30 yen and solved the problem, but I don't want to be involved with him again.
I'm sorry.
I was doing a program called Hatsumei Shogun Downtown.
I felt like I saw something I shouldn't have seen.
This program was held like every week after the recording of Hatsumei Shogun Downtown.
This program was used as a tool for many everyday items because there were many invented products attached to life.
After recording, there was a man who was making an uneasy movement while the staff was cleaning up.
Well, mayonnaise, tissues, vegetables...
There are so many things left over today.
Onuma, who eats up the children he's going to use from now on.
And a lot of people.
You had all the necessary necessities.
I think you had a good life.
There is a 5 yen incident in the past, but you have a picture of it in the morning!
What do you think?
It was a promise to split the money.
You said you would split the money!
Everyone is scared!
I think that's just my opinion.
Well, you're right.
You said you would split the money, so it's 5 yen.
It's not about money or money.
That's right.
Even if you pay 30 yen for the consumption tax, it's still 30 yen.
I get 1000 yen for lunch every day.
Oh, I see.
And I didn't ask about the consumption tax.
You didn't ask?
How much did you pay?
I'm 35 years old.
35 years old?
Yes.
What? Are you kidding me?
Yes, I am.
Oh, really?
You look very stylish.
I think you're stylish.
35 years old?
Yes.
Are you married?
Did your wife decide that?
Well, I'm an independent renter, so...
What?
I'm an independent renter, so...
I spend a month on my own, and...
You decide on your own?
Yes.
Okay, sit down.
Next, please watch this VTR.
It was at a drinking party.
I met a person I broke up with.
I met her at the broken newspaper store.
I'm going to sing.
Hey Otomo, hurry up and put the song in!
The time is set, so if you don't play it, I'll be in trouble!
And two hours have passed
Excuse me, it's time, so please go to the police station
Ah, yes, understood
Mr. Ono, please pay the bill
Although he obviously noticed, the Ono who ignored Otomo
What's wrong? We'll pay for it too, how much?
It's okay, don't worry
I'll pay for this with my card, so please pay later
Everyone, I'll pay for this, so you don't need to pay
Really? I did it!
Leave it to me, DENGA!
I'm calling the witness.
Then, I'll call the witness.
Then, witness, please come in.
Please.
Please come in.
He's the director of Otomo.
AKIRA HARUIN!
You're Otomo's mother!
Well, regarding this...
I think you're going a bit too far.
I think he's lying.
No, I'm serious. Is this completely true?
Yes.
This is true.
I just put my hand on it.
You took it away.
Wait a minute.
What do you mean?
I put my hand on the card.
Why did you do that?
Why did you put your hand on it?
It's your card, right?
Yes.
Why did you put your hand on it?
No, I'll split it up with everyone later.
In a male team.
So, the card...
I have the power to grab the cards.
What do you do?
Well, I do this...
You should have told us that!
That's not right!
It has nothing to do with your power!
Do you have a card?
Yes.
Then you should have done that!
I leave it when I go out for drinks.
That's not right!
You're hiding it!
You invited him, didn't you?
Why did you leave your card?
But...
I thought someone had a card in the locker.
But you are the senior, aren't you?
Yes.
If you invited him, you shouldn't have paid for the card.
I see.
I hate you.
I hate you. I hate you.
I understand.
That was terrible.
Thank you very much, Otomo.
Next time...
There's more?
Yes, we have another case of VTR. Please watch it.
The staff room for the kids.
As usual, they are working.
Oh, you guys are hungry, aren't you?
I'll feed you, so follow me.
Really?
The staff are surprised to hear that the famous Onuma is going to treat them to a meal
Onuma-san, where are you going?
Just follow me
Eh? Where are we going?
I thought there was another program recording here
Oh, here it is
What?
This bento is delicious.
You guys should take one too.
I won't hold back.
Shogun-san, you're here again.
Yes.
Please, Shogun-san.
I'm Tsutsumimoto, the director.
Shogun-san, what program is this?
This is a Japanese TV program called Koi no Karasawagi.
Ha ha ha.
Yes.
So, you're not involved in the show?
No, not at all.
I see.
That's how it is.
I just thought, there's a good place nearby.
You said, there's a good place nearby.
That's close.
It's a different school of rock stars.
It's close, but...
The bento here is good.
But that bento was good, right?
It was good, but...
I ate it in the lobby.
You ate it there?
You didn't take it home?
No.
Why?
I don't know but...
You mean you're going to treat us?
I'm going to eat it as usual.
I think he understood the meaning of saying that he's going to treat us.
Stand up!
What do you mean?
Is this true?
I've been thinking about this for a while now.
When we were recording, we would bring a lot of bento to the show.
Quite a lot.
If there was any left over, we would throw it away.
You thought about that all the time?
Yes, I did.
To be honest, that's what happens on our show.
This is raw, so rather than throwing it away, it's better to eat it.
But I've been thinking about that for a while now.
Why did you eat it on the spot?
Well, if you're not careful, it's like a crime.
A crime?
I have something else that is a bit easier.
Do you have a recipe?
It was when we were recording for the show,
I was with Oonuma-san and we were thirsty,
so we decided to go buy some juice.
It wasn't near here.
Next to Meiji Co. was the Japanese Youth Center.
We were trying to buy some at the store.
You found it there?
It was 110 yen, but when I tried to put it in, it was 150 yen.
Oh, I see.
You read it.
Yes. When I saw that, I couldn't drink it.
I couldn't drink it.
What is that?
You're being serious.
I can't drink it!
But you were scolded by him.
What?
You?
Yes.
You licked it?
No, I didn't.
Really?
When I climb mountains, I think I can't help it because I brought it here.
But in Tokyo, the tourist fees are not paid.
Now, let's continue.
Still more?
That was when he went to Isawa Onsen in Yamanashi prefecture as a child's servant.
Hey, Onuma! Hurry up and change and let's go to the party!
Sakamoto-san, I'm a little worried, but I wonder if I'll be robbed of money or something?
Then, why don't you put it in that safe?
Oh, that? If it's that safe, is it okay? I'll do that!
I'm going ahead!
The party has started and the staff is getting excited.
Hey, Okonuma. How's the money? Did you put it in the safe?
Yes, I did put it in the safe but I was a little worried so I put half of it in the safe and brought the other half.
Really?
You are really cautious
So, how much did you bring?
2000 yen
2000 yen?
Then, you only put 1000 yen in the bank?
I was worried if something happened, so I split it into two
Chief, please tell us about the second case
Well, you know the story now, so you are the one who is right.
Yes.
Is there anything else that has been put in the safe?
When I came back and opened it, there was a letter of intent.
Did you pull it out?
I'm not joking.
It's not a joke.
Is this the truth?
When I travel, I have a habit of going to the safe and my wallet separately.
I think it's a good habit.
So, I'm not saying it's a habit, but I'm saying that I put in 1000 yen.
It's not something I did without knowing.
Thank you, Mr. Sano.
Thank you.
Now, finally, the VTR of the incident where the big-nose dog was seen in full force.
Was there in Yoshinoya?
That was when we were filming in Yoshinoya.
I remember this.
After the filming, the producer received beef bowl from the shopkeeper.
Hey, you guys! I received beef bowl.
Share it with everyone.
Yay! I did it!
Looking at the scene, Onuma grabbed the AB.
Hey, what did you get earlier?
It's Yoshinoya's Tadaken.
Give it to me. Give it to me.
It turns out that Eddie took the Tadaken.
That night...
Give it to me.
Today is a dinner. Hurry up and prepare it.
Really? I did it!
It's been a while since they went out, so they are busy.
The destination they arrived at is Yoshinoya.
And of course, the payment is...
Please pay with this Tadake.
Chief Asai, I have a witness for this case.
Please come forward.
I'm Takahashi, the AD.
I'm the director of Shogen.
You all know this already, but Onoma is the director.
Takahashi is the assistant director.
We're all different ages.
How many tickets did you get?
I got all the tickets.
All of them?
Shut up!
Hey!
That's right.
I thought at least one or two.
It's a bit embarrassing.
Actually, there's more to this story.
Onuma-san also received it.
What? Wait a minute.
That's not fair.
What's going on?
So rude.
What? What do you mean?
How much money did you get from the AD?
50,000 yen.
How many times did you take your wife with you?
5 or 6 times.
I think she got angry at the AD.
Angry?
What do you mean by angry?
You've been angry for a while.
Let's read the Gokko dictionary.
Do you understand?
Sorry everyone, but we have a scene in the waiting room.
This is amazing.
This is more than I expected.
It's more than I expected.
I didn't think it would be this good.
It's all over the place.
The eyes are dead.
To be honest.
The eyes are rotten.
I didn't see it like that, but I saw it today.
It was rotten.
I think this is a complete crime.
A crime is...
It's a crime.
Please announce the verdict.
The defendant, Onuma, has caused many incidents with his extraordinary sense of money, and has caused trouble to people.
Therefore, the defense has no choice but to give you a fine of 1 million yen or a dance on the street.
But if we tell you the truth, we want to hit you.
But if that doesn't work, we'll have to do something else.
Dance.
There is no need to worry about weak.
Happy Birthday to you, Yamazaki-chan!
Happy Birthday to you!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Before the party, please say something to Yamazaki-san.
I'm happy enough just with this.
Well, well...
Being born in the precisely Year of the Corn.
There have been...
Chair Khas Marcel's
There have been hard times for me, but...
I have put in effort to make it bigger and...
and...
It's going to make a 처음 in long journey
You're terrible.
That's terrible.
I can't even make a toast.
Thank you for watching!