Next up is the Suwa presents stress relief show, the Nico Nico Auto Bus Tour!
Today, we have Suwa-chan's...
Yes, yes, yes.
Please take us somewhere.
Yes, yes.
Let's go somewhere.
Well, to be honest, I'm not that good at this.
Why?
No, Suwa-chan, you should go first.
Thank you very much.
Your gyalas won't be up for sale from April.
They won't be up for sale?
That's a very clear mistake.
That's why you're so gorgeous today.
Oh, today?
Oh, I see.
But there's something I'm a little worried about.
I want to avoid trouble.
You know, we're all talented.
If you go to various places, you'll meet various people.
It's going to be fun.
I wonder where they'll take us.
That's something to look forward to.
I'm looking forward to it.
This program is brought to you by the sponsors.
So, let's talk about the theme.
First, the theme.
The theme, huh?
I haven't been there much.
I've only been to Kiboto.
You've been there, haven't you?
Why have you been there?
Why are you here?
I'm here to perform a song from Odaiba.
What song?
I'm here to perform Miracle Type.
I heard you're doing a comedy show.
It's like a reenactment drama.
You can't say it's a comedy show.
I've been here before.
You've been here before?
I do listen to it a lot.
Why?
At work.
Really?
You haven't been to the TV station recently?
No, no.
Just today?
No, no. I don't really go to work.
I don't really look at the scenery.
I do look at the camera like this, but I've never seen a bigger one.
After the school trip, they headed to the popular tourist spot, Odaiba, in a fun atmosphere.
The restaurant is a bit small, but it's better than the real thing.
One tenth smaller.
This is what couples come to see, right?
That's right.
They come to see and ask how it is.
They're running a restaurant.
It looks good.
Let's eat.
I'll eat while I'm eating.
I'm hungry.
Looks delicious.
Let's eat.
Hello.
What do you want to eat?
I don't know.
I want to eat yakisoba.
Yakisoba?
Yes.
But we only have one.
We have to buy one.
That's right.
What should I do?
You can get a hot dog.
I don't know the character of Enzo.
I'll get a hot dog.
What about you, Zaki?
What do you want to eat?
Zaki, do you want yakisoba?
I'll get a hot dog.
I'll get a yakisoba.
Yakisoba?
Zaki.
Hey, Mr. Yamazaki.
Yamazaki.
What are you doing?
Don't come close.
I'm sorry.
I noticed you and you started to look at me.
I didn't do anything.
You did it.
I looked at you and you started to look at me.
Stop asking about the noodle place.
Stop it.
I don't want to.
That's not the case.
The business over there...
That's right.
They won't come to the noodle place.
But...
You've seen it all, haven't you?
I've seen it all.
You're mistaken.
That's right.
Yamaguchi-san, Yamaguchi-san.
What are you doing?
I'm done.
I see.
Let's have fun.
No more.
Please, Yogiya Yama!
I was scared.
Please.
Don't cut it.
Wow!
It's good.
The usual song is good.
Is there such a rock?
I wonder if it was already there.
How is it?
There's a place where I did rock music.
Ah, that's the place.
I did it! I did a battle with Kuma.
Ah, I see.
That's around here.
It's calm.
It's good that you have a good choice, Tsukawa-san.
Thank you.
Then, let's drink some tea.
Let's go.
This is my first time.
Wow, it's cute.
It's cute.
Mameshiba!
So cute!
Mameshiba is so cute!
It's not bad.
It's not bad for the eyes.
Hey, Mr. Tsushima.
I'm leaving.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Didn't you die?
Hey, you too.
You too, wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I'll be waiting.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I hate that kind of girl.
Why are you so old?
Are you taking a walk?
Why are you so angry?
I'm surprised.
Please.
It's like a talent show.
Yeah, yeah.
I didn't realize it was going on for so long.
Is it because I'm talking?
Although he had some small troubles, he decided to get back on his feet and enjoy shopping.
It's true, it's true.
It's good that it's on sale.
I've never been with you before.
Me neither.
Let's go shopping!
Can I buy something?
Sure.
What a young lady.
Yeah.
What?
Who are you?
Let's go shopping.
What?
Let's go.
Why?
What's that face?
Hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
What's wrong?
Hey, hey.
You're a young lady.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
You're going to cut your nails?
No, no.
I don't think I would cut my nails.
I wanted to do something.
You're going to look at me with a dirty look.
That's right.
I'm going to look at you with a dirty look.
I know that kind of thing.
I've been doing it for a long time.
If you were a professional, you would have been able to do it.
That's right.
Right?
Why do you have to compete with an amateur?
That's right.
Osamu-san, you said you were going to do it.
We are also amateurs.
Amateurs?
You just said that.
What's wrong with you?
I'm over 40.
You're working in the industry.
You're a fool.
But what about this hat?
It's popular now.
It's a good thing.
Stop it.
I'll buy you a new one.
I'll wear this all the time.
Really?
I can wear it for many years.
Oh, I see.
What?
You want to wear it?
No, I'm fine.
I'm glad you're the only one who bought it.
Thank you.
Oh, it's a face mask.
It's a face mask.
Do you want to try it?
Oh, my God.
Oh, this is ours.
Oh, really?
Don't you have a ticket?
I'm not laughing.
I'm laughing at my own game.
What?
Let's go over there.
I told you to stop looking around.
I'm not looking.
Look around.
Everyone is looking around.
Stop it.
I told you to stop looking around.
I'm sorry.
Everyone is looking around.
Stop it.
Stop it!
Sorry, Nishan.
Sorry.
You can't do a location.
I can't.
You can't use it.
What is it?
Why are you angry?
What did you do?
I don't know.
I was just looking at the face.
But you did something.
I'm not that angry.
What is it?
Let's stop here.
Let's go to the bus.
I'm sorry.
It's a very good item.
The next destination is the ship's science museum.
I want to display it sometimes.
Thank you very much.
You display amazing things.
Yes, it's pretty good.
It's good.
I want to see it.
I don't have time to study this.
This way.
Can I go in now?
Yes, please prepare it properly.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Let's go in.
It's an exhibition hall.
Yes.
Let's go.
It's cold.
My feet are frozen.
This is...
I don't know why.
This is bad.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Masa, what are you doing?
Come here.
He's being stepped on.
His feet.
He's even being stepped on.
You too.
What is this?
No, no, no.
I was just about to enter.
What is this?
He clearly came after me.
Kevin-san stood up.
Sorry.
You're the one who stepped on my foot.
Me?
No, I've been stepped on since the second half.
Let's have fun.
Have fun.
This is not good.
Let's change it from here.
Let's have fun.
I think it's okay to look at the order.
Can I look at it?
Yes, you can.
Yamato is cool.
He's cool.
What are you doing?
I'm stretching my hand.
You're stretching your hand.
I'm stretching my back.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What the hell?
What are you doing?
Hey, Mr. Nekko.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
Ah, wait, wait.
You, you, too, too.
You're a child, aren't you?
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
You're a child, aren't you?
I'm small, but I'm a little big.
Stop it.
I am a man.
At that time...
I said something like a mature man.
I am 47 years old.
47 years old, right?
Please forgive me.
I am over 40 years old.
I thought so.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, sorry.
If it was that girl, the other guys would have been in trouble.
The broken surface area finally reacts, and the trouble that they should have avoided continues for some reason.
While trying to calm down, they head to Pallet Town.
Wow, it's beautiful!
Isn't it?
It's amazing.
It's beautiful when the lights are on.
What is this? It's like a car exhibition.
It's a Toyota.
Toyota.
Toyota is good.
Let's see the car.
Is it OK?
I want to see it.
It's like a statue.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You can't do that to an old lady.
That's right.
I'm gonna cry.
I was so surprised.
Let's have fun.
It was a good choice for you.
Let's go to the Ferris wheel.
Driver, please.
I'm scared.
Let's go.
Your face is big.
Big face.
You look scary.
Of course it is.
Well, well, well, well.
In the end, we've been talking about it for so long, but now it's finally time for you to go.
Oh, that's right.
Well, I don't think I've had much reaction from the audience.
That's right.
We're looking forward to it.
Well, we're looking forward to it.
I'd like you to die this time, Yamazaki.
What about it?
Come on, Yamazaki.
Well, well, well, won't it grow more?
Won't it be around April?
I don't really like it.
Why?
I wonder why?
It's even more tiring.
It's not tiring or long and hectic.
It's scary.
Really, Morimang is scary.
Seiji, did you watch the match?
I haven't watched it yet.
What did you do?
Oh, the New Year's party?
I'm really angry at Yamashita.
That's not true.
He really died.
I can't die from being shot at close range.
Because it's a taxi.
But you didn't even ask for it on that day, but you came to Takishido and did it.
That was the Takishido I still drink.
I don't spend any money on it.
I drink recently.
I thought I shouldn't drink and drive.
I asked Yamashita to drive.
I sometimes ask for it.
When I got home, I thought it was bad.
I don't need a taxi.
I was eating a lot of food.
I had no choice but to drive because I had no money.
I had no money.
I had 850 yen in my pocket.
I asked him if I needed this.
He said, I don't need it because I can cut the steering wheel.
Is that true?
It's true.
I only have this.
I don't care if it's an old man or something.
I don't care if it's a classroom.
I'm going to eat it.
That's the worst!
There was a point card incident.
Junior's younger brother moved.
He said, I'll move.
I went to the TV station.
It was about 100,000 yen.
That's all.
I was moved by the point card incident.
Where's the point card?
You're talking about something weird.
I don't have anything.
You should just go.
What is this?
You should have told me about the point card.
I was just spending money and looking at other places.
I was with Yamashita.
And then, you know, the point card...
What do you want to do?
What do you want to do with the point card?
He was so angry.
Please do something about it.
I said, that's your point card!
He said, your point card is a
stupid car!
I have his point card!
That's also a point card I made when I was in high school!
It's not his!
He pushed it away!
He's good enough to be a judge of the school's case.
It's terrible.
When I was in Guam, it was raining.
To be honest, I was playing cards.
I was playing blackjack.
I was playing 5 times and 21 points.
I was playing 5 times.
I was like,
Come on!
My parents came to me.
Yes!
I was in the middle of the game.
The whole theater was in a mess.
That's like a mood food!
You shouldn't have killed him!
That's a Tsuba!
Tsuba-chan's jacket is deep green!
You're wearing a pizza!
That's so stupid!
Hey!
After eating at a restaurant, I feel a little bit of superiority in putting out the Platinum card of American Express.
What is the superiority of being a successful Matsumoto-san class?
Certainly, well, well, well, I don't care anymore.
What are you talking about?
In the past, I was worried about more things.
I forget all the economic things and all the things that I can do to save money.
I'm quite a big fan of yours.
Big fan of yours?
Because you open the fridge like BAM!
Everyone does that.
No, no, no.
I want to see the energy of the people who earn money.
I will cool it down anytime.
Everyone will give you money.
I can't do it without money.
It's a game.
It used to be a game.
It's like a game of getting caught in the middle.
I will definitely do that.
I'm not doing that.
You must have used tissue a lot.
In the past, you didn't use it that much.
That's not true.
I hate it.
When a woman comes and spills something,
I go like Bap Bap Bap Bap Bap Bap Bap Bap Bap.
Oh, oh, oh, long, long, long, long.
No, no, no, no.
I use it all the time.
I don't need such an uneducated woman now.
That's a long time ago.
I'm all about Bap Bap Bap Bap now.
Really?
No, no, really, really, now I'm able to earn money by myself.
I've changed a lot.
In the past, when I used to do this,
I used to do it with a good feeling of cutting the hair.
I used to do it the other way around, but recently I've been doing it like this.
You used to do it the other way around and still be able to use it here.
I thought I was going to get it again.
But now, the environment is already...
You don't have to worry about it.
I don't have to worry about it anymore.
It's a big deal.
It's a little detailed.
It's fine, but it's important.
There's a net.
A net for pouring water.
That... is only a little bit of it, but you throw it away...
Just a little more...
Until it comes, just leave it there.
You...
You!
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.