I want to go to my wife.
You should go.
It's in English.
If you don't change your pants, you should change your clothes.
I thought you were going to change your clothes.
What time is it now?
It's 3 o'clock.
That's terrible.
In terms of time, it's about 2 hours.
It's about 2 and a half hours.
It's better than just saying that.
Good morning.
Your wife is changing.
What's wrong with you today?
What's wrong with me?
The hot and spicy Ankake match!
This is the Morimon match
Let's go!
It's a tie!
It's not easy.
What is this?
Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's dangerous!
That was really strong.
It's hot! It's hot! It's hot!
It's really hot in Japan.
It's really hot.
The stage is too small.
No, it's not the stage.
It's the ring.
You're making a big deal out of this.
Wait a minute!
I'm serious.
That's not true.
How many times have you done this?
I think I've done this about 5 or 6 times.
But it's like, I wonder if it's okay.
But this is a popular corner.
It's a famous corner for the famous writer.
It's definitely like this.
My wife and I will definitely get excited.
What?
It's definitely more exciting than my wife.
There's no doubt about that.
Do you think it will be a good story?
Of course.
To be honest, Yamazaki VS Moriman is about to be...
It's like a comedy.
It's not a comedy.
But it's a bit sad.
It's not something a wife would do with her child involved.
I think you can get more numbers from that.
If you can get numbers, it's good.
Well, I can't.
Hey, Mr. Tsubasa.
What is it?
I don't have any special memories of you.
Mr. Tsubasa.
I'm just kidding.
Well, this video was made with the support from the sponsored at Collector promisingacked masks ordinary, white Muslim mosque in the city of Hikacchula
This show is presented by the sponsor you are looking for
Nothing can be forced to happen?
From now on, it's time for the official death match between Itao vs Yome.
The tension is low.
From the bottom of hell, you can hear his footsteps.
Who are you talking about?
The blue Grim Reaper of the Naniwa.
ITAO!
Ah, the red hair.
It's not red hair.
Let's stop with the red hair.
It's my own hair.
Red hair.
A wife who is a comedian.
A wife of hell.
A woman who is a reverse-savage in South America.
What's a reverse-savage?
The bride is here!
No, no, this feeling...
It's all on me.
Shut up!
What is it?
Why is Yamada here?
There are so many girls here.
It's Judge Yamada.
You're a judge.
What kind of connection is there between us?
I forgot to say this, but I have someone I want to introduce.
What is it?
Thank you.
I think I've been on American TV before this program.
That was a great, a great popular kid.
And I heard that the president of the goods is selling well.
No, no, no. You're making it up.
I want to say something.
No, no, no. You're just saying it.
I'm grateful to meet Takenotsukai. Africa will make big money.
It's an honor to meet Takenotsukai members. Today, I brought the goods of my company which is a big hit in Africa.
Oh.
Look at this.
Wow.
It's just a sticker.
I'm not going to do it anymore.
Why? I don't care.
Can I say something?
I'm sorry. I made a mistake.
Where is it?
It's here.
It's not here.
I'm making money.
No, no.
It's not like that.
It's a little different here.
It's different.
I'm really old.
It's like, you're rich!
Africa will make big money.
They're making a lot of money in Africa.
You're good at manzai.
What?
Let's start with the first match.
The first match is this.
The winner is...
The one who can't give up on the internet.
I've done this before.
It's 100 degrees.
It's hot.
I'll show you.
This is really hot.
It's really hot.
It's too hot.
It's fast.
You just put it in.
The steam is not coming out at all.
Oh, it's a shrimp.
What are you saying?
Yamamoto, what are you saying?
You're making a mistake.
The first one.
What the hell is this?
Everyone has a fear of getting heatstroke, so I'll give you a poncho.
Does it fly that much?
It's dangerous if you put it in a box.
There are different kinds.
It's been denied.
But I can't wear this when I'm in Yamasaki.
One, two, three, four, five, six, five, six, it's 3,000 yen, Mr. Suga.
What?
3,000 yen.
But, it's Evo-chan.
But, I've already passed it through three times.
Yes, it's already a wrinkle, right?
Ah, if my neck is torn.
It's torn.
It's already torn.
It's still there, right?
Excuse me.
It's no good.
No, is it?
No, it's already, look, it's already early.
It's still hot.
The temperature of the hot water will drop.
I see.
Excuse me.
It's too early.
It's too early to take money.
Thank you for your patience.
Now, let's start the game.
The hot water match.
It's hot!
It's hot.
Drink water.
It's not stuck.
It's a good thing.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ouch, ouch.
It hurts.
What is this?
The next match is this.
Is it over?
It's OK.
If you don't get the water on your face, it's not good.
Drink this.
Poisoning blowfish match.
This is dangerous.
I quit.
I use real poison.
If you get poisoned, it will be a disaster.
If you drink this, you will be fine.
You will be fine?
Yes.
Please drink it.
The hot water didn't come at all.
That's good.
Take and Sen.
But insurance is like that.
Ah.
If there is an accident, insurance will be included.
Well, well.
I don't like lemon.
Lemon is a little...
It's my own water.
Well, well.
It's a good thing to drink it.
Excuse me, it's 6,000 yen.
It's 6,000 yen.
Then, this is...
You should have said this before you drank.
If I had said this before I drank, it would have been something like,
something that's a waste.
Something that would have been something that the Kansai people would have hated.
You should have said this before you drank.
I don't need vitamin C.
I don't think vitamin C is that expensive.
Now, let's begin.
Poisonous
It's always stuck.
It's so long.
Eh?
It's a
If you wipe it once, it won't stick.
It's a continuous one.
It's a
What is this?
I don't know.
The board is broken.
You got stabbed, right?
Sorry.
The next battle is this.
Are you okay?
Poison, poison.
Poisonous snake battle.
The battle of the six soldiers, start!
That was dangerous.
Is there a trap?
When we finish getting ready...
the
I'm coming.
From Hama-san.
Itama-kachi.
And the next is this.
I don't know what this is.
K-1 match.
This is...
This is the real deal.
For this,
you're trying to...
You're trying to...
Then, K-1 match, start!
You're wearing a ring suit.
What's going on?
Hey! What's wrong? Hey!
Sorry!
What's your name?
I'm dead.
Why?
Wait a minute.
No, no.
What?
That's the problem, right?
The TV is so extreme that it's like this.
What's wrong with that?
I was made a gear for the entertainment world.
What?
I said I wasn't dead.
Anyway, this is the one I was preparing.
What did you prepare?
It's over until the end of the month.
Wow, that's a lot of money.
280,000 yen.
1.0 million yen for the lion.
And another 1.5 million yen.
And another 1.3 million yen for the fox.
That's all the money we have.
Yatta-kun, you can go.
Yes.
We've also sent out the money.
Please do this for us.
You can marry her.
What is this?
It's a song, so it's a good idea to consider it.
Yes, it's a good idea to consider it.
But the wife is the one who should consider it.
You can consider it.
Yes.
Then, please do the rest.
Halloween.
Your mother is dead.
I'm sorry, but I'm waiting for a good reply.
A good reply?
Please.
What are you going to do, madam?
You're not dead, are you?
Why would I die?
I wouldn't die.
I'm not dead.
What is this?
I moved.
You moved.
I laughed.
Hey Yamada, you're not dead, right?
Good evening, Yamada
Good evening, Hamada's medicine box
Weihai
I'm sorry!
What did you say?
I don't think you're a lively audience.
Well, it's not bad.
I don't like you guys at all.
But you shouldn't say that every day.
But that's right.
I'm sure you're lying that you'll be able to meet everyone again.
Because you don't remember.
I don't want to hear such lies.
I'm sorry.
Well, I know you're alive and well.
I'm not alive and well.
I'm alive and well.
I know you're in a good mood because you're alive and well.
But if you pretend to be alive, I'll beat you up.
This guy is an idiot.
Right? I am...
You are an idiot!
You don't get carried away by a three-shot.
But when you came out, you had a smug face.
Smug face.
No, it's normal.
Look at my three shots.
I feel like that.
Ah, but think about it.
Think about it.
It's been 20 years.
What?
Combination.
Ah, yes, yes.
Right?
It's been 20 years!
This book is in the 18th issue.
If you think about it,
the people of downtown Matsumoto have already passed the age of one year.
Ah, that's right.
Eh!?
Why do you have such a strong impression?
Is there anyone in their 20s?
Anyone in their 20s, please raise your hand quickly.
The year these people were born, we were already in a combination.
20 years!
If you take 3 years, it's 17 years!
That's a lot!
It's a huge thing!
I know that!
What?
Just by looking at your face today...
Ah, the look of a dork?
The look of a dork...
Ah, today...
I want to brag about my hair...
Well, I'll brag about it a little bit...
After a shocking encounter, I have a question for Matsumoto-san who has built up his image of a human being called Matsumoto Hitoshi.
What kind of appearance does a little devil, who you have only met twice in your life, have?
When did you meet him?
You surprised me.
You've said it twice.
Even though I said a little devil, it's not that he looks small.
He's about the same as usual.
Actually, the clothes are a bit small.
Why do you not understand that?
It's pretty tight.
The chucks also open quickly.
What is a chuck?
The chuck is usually up to here.
The sleeves?
The sleeves.
It goes up to here.
When I was talking, it came up quickly.
It's like a dumpling here.
I saw a guy who made a hole here and passed his fingers through.
He was like a
In the back, his back was visible.
What does he do?
He is a little devil.
Originally, he started from a little devil.
Before becoming a devil?
Yes, yes.
And then you want to become a demon as soon as possible.
So it's not a big deal to be strong.
That's right.
So you have to work hard from now on.
But I'm still in training.
So I'm wearing a bathrobe.
A bathrobe?
It's a bathrobe.
It says, Takeuchi.
You're wearing your own, right?
I can't get my own used.
When I become a person, I'll measure it and wear it.
It's like a uniform.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's called a ax.
Where did you see it?
Behind the fridge.
You didn't get hurt, did you?
Behind the fridge?
There must be a reason why you were behind the fridge.
If you were a demon a year ago, you would have done something crazy.
When you find it?
When a car comes, a huge rock...
...and it goes BAM!
And the rock goes BAM!
And then he goes,
Laughing like this.
This is the devil in front of you.
You found him in the refrigerator, right?
Did he do something to you?
I know him.
He's a little devil.
I haven't got a license yet.
What did he do to you?
You see,
He goes,
I heard a sound like this.
I thought it was the sound of changing the refrigerator.
It's noisy.
I looked at it and it was doing it.
I heard it with my mouth.
I thought it was strange.
I said, come here! Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
What? You caught me?
Yes, yes, yes.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
I said, help me!
No, I'm not scared.
You said, boom, boom, boom.
I said, I can't sleep!
Yes.
And then...
What's funny, you guys!
But I can't sleep. It's strange that I can't sleep.
I see.
Because I'm a demon.
Yes.
Where did you stop?
Around the temple.
You should have stopped there.
Right?
I was about to find it in the back of the refrigerator.
I thought it was a little dangerous.
You thought so?
I thought so.
Ah, I see.
Then, next week, stop me.
Certainly, when I was around the refrigerator, I felt that it was becoming a little bit of a joke.
Ah, is that so?
Yes.
Why didn't you stop there?
You couldn't stop it.
I wanted to do the boom behind the fridge.
To be honest, I thought I could take it a little more.
But I didn't think I could.
The return was a little weak.
I thought it was weak.
I thought I was going to get a pimple on my face.
I was thinking, I can't say it, I can't say it!
But then, something was wrong.
I was thinking, what should I say?
I can't think of anything!
I can't even open my eyes!
I'm thinking now!
I can't think of anything!
I'm thinking of something else!
Let me go!
Nothing!
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.