The recording of the boy's use.
I can't see that man.
It's like a white horse.
White horse?
It's like a slipper.
It's not like that.
It's no use to beat you anymore.
Today is a special training.
What are you talking about?
What is it?
What's that?
What?
Is that a compliment?
On the contrary
That's not fair
Are you from the St. Force?
I'm so angry!
Stay home!
The comedy is not fair!
That's terrible!
Really?
You were staying home, right?
That's why your Ma is like a house Ma
Now, now!
That Ma?
What? You're late!
What are you doing?
Today, from Osaka...
I called people from Yoshimoto Shinki Station.
You started from Koke?
Ah, Shinki Station.
Koke is the theme.
Koke!
Don't do it! Don't do it!
Yoshimoto Shinki Station is a place where Koke and Tsukkomi are played to the max.
This is the Koke of the Shinki Station that Matsumoto mentioned.
Hello.
What?
I'll cut you down.
The iron plate pattern of the famous joke and the one who gets a cramp and cramps all at once.
Matsumoto wants to force the cramp that has completely shifted after making the four of them experience a cramp.
I'm sorry!
You're wearing a costume!
That's right!
You're going to be on stage!
Of course! Go!
Ah, I'm sorry! I'll open the door!
You're heavy!
Get ready!
Yes!
The four men in their costumes, without knowing the story, go to the stage of the new play.
Matsumoto checks the four men's
The four of them are going to be the ones to make a fool of the new drama.
Will they be able to make it?
Ah, there are so many customers today, I'm so busy!
I have to work hard!
I'm so happy! I have to do my best!
What's wrong? What's wrong?
What are you doing? You're going to say something weird, right?
What do you mean by that?
I came to return the bowl I brought from the delivery
Thank you for your help! I'll make some tea, so take a break.
Thank you! Thank you!
It's a call.
I'm busy!
I'm not going to cut it!
Are you taking it?
I made a mistake!
You made a mistake! You're a customer in Toronto!
It's true!
It's ringing.
Hello! Thank you! It's a delivery.
One tempura udon and one stamina udon.
It's a seaweed udon, meat udon, and fox udon.
Understood. I'll deliver it right away.
Please give me 5 curry rice.
What are you doing?
It's not the same. You asked for more, didn't you?
I wrote it down, so it's okay.
Really?
I'm sorry I'm late.
Hanako-chan, you shouldn't be late from the first day.
There is a deep reason for this.
My mother...
Mother, she passed away?
She didn't wake me up.
What is that?
Listen to yourself!
Do your best!
Yes.
Please go to the car park across the street.
Please work hard.
I'll get in your way.
I'll get in your way, so go home.
Yes, I'm coming.
Are you really going home?
Why did you let him go home?
He went home on his own.
What's up, you two?
I'm Matsuzora from Yoshimoto Kinjo.
Yoshimoto Kinjo?
Who's the owner of this place?
It's me.
You?
You know a guy called Yoshizawa Yutaka, right?
He's my brother.
I see. He's been living somewhere since he borrowed money from me.
It's me, Dazai.
My brother left here 5 years ago and hasn't come back yet.
Liar! I know you!
I'm not here.
What will happen if Yutaka becomes Dazai?
I taught you how to use this guitar that you borrowed earlier.
I'm scared.
All of you!
Take him to the ocean.
No, no, I'm scared.
I'll push him down from the ship!
I'm scared.
A shark will attack you soon.
Here it comes.
I'm scared.
You're going too far!
Are you okay?
If she said that, I wonder how much trouble she would cause by making a debt.
Lady, did you see your brother?
Well...
Did he cause any trouble?
I'm sorry.
It's a complicated story.
I want to know.
If you work here, can I ask you a favor?
Sorry.
It's okay.
It's okay?
Why are you hitting me?
I'll hit you.
It's okay.
Actually, I have a brother named Yutaka.
We're running a store together.
Five years ago, Yutaka jumped out of the store and made a sound.
I still can't forgive you.
I see.
That's what happened.
I'm back.
Yutaka!
Sister, I'm sorry for being so hard on you.
Why did you come back?
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't have to say that.
I came back because I had to.
You get angry after listening to me.
Sit down.
Yutaka, what happened?
Actually...
Actually
You are a fool!
You haven't said anything!
You just doubled your answer.
Ask the question after they ask it too!
Ex poster
Meeting
I bet it didn't come true.
It wasn't our Drawh!
Qualify too
They should have answered after they have asked.
Which one?
It was just...
You have to answer too!
What a waste!
What's wrong with you?
You're not even telling me properly.
What happened this year?
Five years ago, I became a guarantor for my friend's debt.
That friend ran away.
And when I was at this shop, the debtors came and came to disturb me.
So I thought I shouldn't cause trouble, so I left this town.
But if you're going to go back, at least pay off your debt.
You should have come back.
Wait a minute. I paid it off properly.
Why? You said you paid off your debt first.
What's wrong with that? I paid it all back.
I'm back to normal.
You're a movie star, Yasue-chan.
You should go back to this store with Yudaka-kun.
There's no reason to say that.
I don't want to see your face anymore.
Go out!
Onee-chan!
Why are you the one who says that?
While laughing.
Why did Yasue-chan say that?
Hey, Yudaka.
You're not going to pay me back?
You're not going to let me pay you back?
Wait a minute.
I paid you back all the money.
You've been a pervert all day.
Give me the 1 million yen!
I can't do that!
I have no choice but to do this!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Wait!
What are you doing with a stick?
I didn't do anything
You didn't do anything?
Why did you take the stick?
Today, the lady with the glasses is not here.
Who is that?
What are you doing?
I'll take your sister to the shakky.
No, no, no!
Please, please, please!
Please let me take my sister!
Let me go!
Then pay me!
Ah, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
I don't care what happens!
Please let me take my sister!
You're acting like a hero.
Hey, Shaku-yo.
No, I haven't returned the rizoku.
Forget about the rizoku.
Tell your sister about this!
I'll get a divorce.
O-Nano!
Sister!
I'm going to the bathroom.
You're so mean!
What?
I want to clean it up a little.
Look, I'm going.
Wait a minute, Yutaka-kun.
Yasue-chan, can I really let you go?
You have nothing to do with this!
You're a jerk!
Hey!
Wait a minute!
If you're going to leave, take all your belongings and leave!
Wait, Yasue-chan.
Your clothes are in the absence factors catchingstein.
Yes, I will take them with me.
And also tell him to bring your shoes.
Okay. I'll take his shoes, too.
And also your blanket. Get everything you can bring anywhere else.
Wait a second.
Why would you please bring me everything?
If I can't go out with you,
If I can't go out,
I'd rather stay here.
Se-chan.
Instead,
I'll let you work hard until you get a break.
Sister.
You're back.
I'm so glad.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. I should have understood you more.
No, I should have understood you more about my sister.
You weren't nice to her.
No, I wasn't nice to her.
I'm not nice to her.
I told you.
You're my brother but you're noisy.
You are noisy and you are sulking.
You're a fool!
You're a piece of shit!
What the hell!
What did you think of them?
It was a good fit, it was familiar.
It was a good time.
First, Tanaka.
Yes.
You're just bad at this.
And Hamada, you didn't have a good reaction for a few episodes.
I'm sorry.
The last one, the one that you stayed in the open for a long time.
I hate that one.
I thought that was the end, so I was waiting for him to get off the horse.
That's the bad part of being a veteran.
That's enough.
Overall, he's 0.42 faster than me.
0.42 faster.
Yamazaki is 1.65 slower.
1.65?
Endo is 8 seconds faster.
8 seconds?
Of course, it's not that fast.
But that's how fast I felt.
I see.
It's not done at all.
In the first place, it's too broken.
It shouldn't be broken no matter what.
I'll show you a example.
Really?
I'm sorry to the people of the new drama, but I had the same thing done in the previous one.
It's not broken at once.
In that one?
When you absorb all the moss from the plants and when you are done, you will be able to collect all the moss in one go.
Then everyone will be happy.
That was a lot of moss.
This is the real moss.
I will show you.
You will learn.
You're not allowed to do that!
The four of them are too drunk and they're in a serious situation.
They're about to fall in love.
Matsumoto is determined to do it at the right time.
The four of them are watching from the other room.
When will Matsumoto show his true self?
He's not here
I have to work hard today too
What are you doing?
He had that kind of face?
He didn't look like that
He was like that
I'm Matsuura Yumoe from Yoshimoto Biyuu
You know a guy called Yoshizawa Yutaka right?
I'm Yuttaka's little brother
He borrowed money from us and took a loan
Borrowed money?
That's right
I'm sorry but my brother left 5 years ago and hasn't returned since then
You know a guy called Yoshizawa Yutaka right?
I'm Yuttaka's little brother
He borrowed money from us and tried to steal it
Borrowed money?
That's right
I'm sorry but my brother left 5 years ago and hasn't come back since
If you know it, it's no good
He's really getting in the way
He's getting in the way
He's already got a lot of money
He's not getting anywhere
A shark will attack you soon
What does that mean?
Here it comes
Scary scary scary
Here it comes!
The makeup is so weak.
You're only doing it once?
You're so good!
Please go home!
My debt recovery rate is...
The next day
Zero!
Zero?
What the hell?
What the hell is this?
This is in the way.
Okami-san, did your brother do it?
I don't know.
What about the trouble?
It's a complicated story, so it's okay.
I want to know.
Well, that's true. When it comes to work, Yasui-chan, can I ask Hana-chan to teach me?
Ah, sorry.
It's fine.
It's fine? Why did you hit me?
What?
He's the best note.
It's true, right?
It's true.
Ryuu-kun, Ryuu-kun.
I'm back.
That's strange.
Yutaka!
I'm sorry for being a fool
Why don't you say something?
Why did you come back?
Yasue-chan, don't say that
You'll get angry when you hear the truth
What happened? Sit down
Sit down
Don't listen to the story
You'll get angry
Reitaka-kun, what happened?
Actually...
Don't say that
I didn't say anything yet
You'll get angry when you hear the truth
Yutaka-kun, what happened?
Actually...
You're lying!
Yasue-chan too!
Yasue-chan too?
What's with the
Yutaka-kun, what happened?
Actually...
That's what happened.
What's that?
You too?
You're the one who's not saying it properly!
What happened?
Five years ago, my friend's loan was in debt,
My friend ran away.
And I had to pay back the debt.
When I was at the store, the debt collector came and tried to get in my way.
He said I shouldn't have been in trouble, so I left the town.
I see.
So you didn't have to be in trouble, so you left the town.
But if that's the case, you should have paid back the debt before coming back.
I paid back the debt properly.
What are you talking about? The debt collector came earlier.
I paid back all the mistakes.
There's no mistake.
That's fine. But Yase-chan, can you go to this shop with me again?
I can't.
This girl left this shop just for me.
I can't do that.
I don't want to see her face.
Get out!
Onee-chan!
You're the one who should say it!
No, Kanji is in the right place.
This is a troublesome topic.
Hey, Yutaka!
You're back!
Matsuura-san, I've paid you back for the money.
Hey, you're the one who gave me the most change in the world.
The world's fastest one million yen!
Pay me properly.
I can't pay that much!
Then, I guess I'll have to do this!
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait, wait, wait!
What are you doing, doko?
Hey, hey, hey!
What are you going to do with a naked woman?
I didn't do anything, though.
What did you do, doko?
You didn't do anything?
What are you doing?
What are you looking at?
Hey, get out of here.
What are you doing?
Hey, this is bad. This is about the debt.
Your sister is in debt.
Wait a minute.
Please don't take my sister.
You have to pay for it.
Hey, wait a minute.
I don't care what you do.
Please don't take my sister's debt.
You're so stubborn.
What kind of face is that?
Hey, come on.
Shakuya-san, I'm sorry to say this but...
No more reasoning! This time, I'll get back at your sister for having a reason.
What kind of face is that?
You're so full of yourself.
It's already the end.
Right? It's already over.
Yes, it's over.
It's already around here.
That's right.
There's still a chance.
It's over.
Are you kidding me?
What's wrong with you?
This isn't the place.
This is a good place.
I'll wear it.
You only have one last word.
Wait a minute.
I was scared.
You have to go out.
Take all your luggage and get out.
Yasue-chan.
There's a lot of clothes in it.
No, you're getting in the way.
You're getting in the way.
I'll take your clothes with me.
And...
Take your shoes with you to the store.
Okay.
I'll take my shoes with me.
And...
There's a futon, so take it with you.
Wait a minute.
I'll take my clothes, shoes, and futon.
You can't just take everything and leave!
If I can't take everything and leave...
If I can't leave...
I should just stay here forever, right?
Here?
No way!
What are you doing here?
That's strange.
It's so moving.
It's not a joke.
Everyone was really surprised.
It's like I was defeated.
Good work.
The 4th place is the new member.
We were watching it from the room because it was so good.
That's where the brothers' music flows and it's a show place.
I said, DOOON!
I was surprised.
I thought, what is this?
You don't usually do that kind of voice, do you?
That's right.
There is also a story that I was told to do it for the sake of the show.
I wanted to ask you.
Why is it that way?
I've been nodding my head while listening to the lines.
Yes, yes.
He was biting the screen.
Yes, he was biting.
It's a ghost.
What?
It hurts.
What hurts?
Apologize.
We?
We apologize.
It's because you made trouble.
she said she can't do with it
and what is this?
Mashimura ate it
Yes, this is not ok
wow
The number of broadcasts is distributed exclusively by Hulu.
Kyuryu Kensaku!