Next time on the first episode of the Gaki no Tsukai Arai, we will be giving away the 1 million yen prize money for the manly badminton tournament!
Let's do it!
Let's get a million yen prize money.
A million yen! That's a lot.
I've been practicing.
Badminton?
Seriously?
I really thought I'd do it today.
The team division is...
Who?
Don't die like that.
What are you doing?
Sit down.
Don't come out.
Hello?
What are you doing?
I'm practicing for the musical instrument.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I don't think you can do it.
Why can't you connect?
What do you mean?
Wait a minute.
I'll call you later.
No, I can't.
I can't talk right now?
Excuse me.
May I speak to you?
What?
My wife, Chiaki...
I called my manager and he said he couldn't get in touch with me for 5 hours.
No, no, no. It's not like you're working.
No, no, no.
There's no way that's true.
I don't usually do that. I usually try to get in touch with her.
I've been married for 5 years, but I've never been in touch with her for 5 hours.
What do you mean?
You mean you want to go look for her?
I want to return it.
Of course, as a professional, I want to do my job properly.
But I can't get into the mood.
But you have to do it so that you can concentrate.
Excuse me, can you stop it?
Why?
I'm really sorry.
Can you let me return it?
What is he doing?
Did you go somewhere?
I went with him this morning, but he said he was going to a picnic land in Sagami.
I didn't hear that.
At work?
I don't know if it's private or not.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry. I know.
I know he's saying really bad things.
I really know, but can you find him?
What should we do?
And would they still be able to find Chiaki?
Let's find Chiaki...
We're going to find him?
What the...
Then who in the world says we go?
And who are you?
I don't know, but you probably go, right?
Let's seach for him, but any repeat night, we'd be able to find him.
Chiyaki's wife is gone. A big search special.
We've arrived at Sagami-ko Picnic Land.
It's long.
This is...
I'm sure there's someone in this neighborhood.
Chiyaki!
It's not early.
Chiaki!
Chi-chan!
Chi!
Can you call Chiaki?
I think she's responding
Chiaki! Chiaki!
Everyone's here! Chiaki!
Chiaki!
I'm sorry, but can I get off the car?
You're looking for a walk?
Yes, please.
Chiaki!
But you can tell that he's not here just by looking at him.
He's so annoying.
He's looking for me.
Chiaki!
Chi! Chi-chan! Chi-chan!
Chi!
What?
Everyone, what are you doing here?
We're looking for you.
Chi!
What?
Everyone, what are you doing here?
Good morning.
What are you doing?
I'm here for a drama shoot. I'm going home.
What's up?
Endo.
You look serious. What's wrong?
I'm Endo Kokoro.
Nice to meet you.
My wife's name is Chiaki.
Chiaki?
What happened to her?
I haven't been able to contact them for about 5 hours.
I've been looking for them for a while.
What?
That's terrible.
We have to find them together.
But...
It's a good thing.
No, no, no.
Let's find them together.
I'll look for them too.
Right?
But that's a little...
When you're in trouble,
you say,
let's help each other.
I think it's better to have more people than one.
Then, let's look for him.
SHIRAKUN!
SHIRAKUN, where did you go?
Sorry, thank you.
SHIRAKUN!
Chiaki!
Why are you here?
Sorry.
It's okay.
We're all in this together.
Thank you.
Chiaki!
Oh, shut up.
Huh?
What's this?
Excuse me.
Oh, this is...
Strawberry...
It's just strawberry.
What?
Chiaki, you collect strawberry goods, right?
That's right.
This must be Chiaki's.
He's definitely near.
Really?
There's too many, I don't know.
This must be Chiaki's.
Hey, Chiaki! Chiaki!
He's near.
Chiaki! Chiaki!
When I found the strawberry goods, I thought, this is it.
I knew that Chiaki-kun liked strawberry goods.
I thought it would be cute if Chiaki-kun had that strawberry bag.
This is getting worse and worse.
It's getting worse.
The fire is getting worse.
There's a little bit more up here, so let's take the bus and look for it.
Really?
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Where did Chiaki go?
He goes back to the bus to find him.
Chiaki! Chiaki! Everyone's here!
Chiaki! Chiaki!
Is this him?
Chiaki!
Hey, Chiaki!
There!
Chiaki!
Stop!
Don't worry about me.
Chiaki!
Hey!
Good morning.
What are you doing?
Picnic! Picnic!
What's going on?
Chiaki is not here.
Is it Chiaki?
I'm looking for her.
Really?
Shinya Ohada.
Nice to meet you.
It's not about Tanemama.
We'll look for her together.
You came here to play.
It's a picnic.
Tanemama is teaching us.
So let's go together.
Let's go!
Chiaki!
Are you coming?
What a fool.
Chiaki!
Something is falling.
What is this?
There must be something nearby.
There's no mistake.
Is this a body part?
Chiaki is a fan of Henshin, right?
Yes.
There's no mistake.
There's no mistake, right?
You're not going to say anything, right?
Endo-san, there's a observation deck.
Really?
Let's go.
They'll definitely be here.
Let's shout from the top of the observation deck.
Jyakyuuun!
Endo-san, I'll go look down.
You're really something.
She's really going.
Sister!
Man-chan, you're amazing.
She's so kind, isn't she?
She's really kind.
She's working hard.
I'm going to watch her again.
She's really kind.
I always thought that Endo-nii-san had a good wife.
But now that it's come to this,
I'm going to have a heart attack.
Endo-san isn't here.
She's not here?
Yes.
Okay, thank you.
Endo's gone.
How was it?
Nothing
Why? What did you see?
What's wrong?
Let's look for her
It's getting dark
It's a problem. She's lonely
Oh?
Nana-chan in the summer
Good morning!
Oh, good morning!
What are you doing?
Eh?
No, I'm...
I'm in the toilet
Yes
In the toilet
I was filming there, the AV
Ah, in a place like this?
Yes
No, I'm in the recording room
There are many things to do
There's no one here
Yes
What are you doing?
My wife is called Chiaki
Yes
She's missing and she's missing now
Everyone is looking for her
Eh?
Mr. Shiaki, you don't know?
Then I'll look for it with you.
No, no, no, that's really...
But I'm worried.
No, no, Nare-chan is so enthusiastic.
She's helping me.
I'd rather be alone.
Please.
Please help me.
Are you done?
It's over.
Well, there's no end.
It's getting dark.
The more people there are, the more likely they are to be found.
Is it okay?
Chiaki!
What is it?
This is that.
It's Nontan.
Nontan.
Ah, Nontan.
Chiyaki-chan, you're doing it wrong.
Why do you know?
You're doing it wrong.
So, I'm sure it's this.
That's right.
I think it's been about ten years.
I was doing Nontan's voice.
That's right.
Did you know?
It's around here.
Let's look for it.
No!
There's nothing to look for.
This is no good. There's nothing left.
This is impossible.
I couldn't find anything in the mountains, so I'll go to the back of the mountain.
I'll go too.
I'll wait here.
Okay.
Wait a moment. I'll go with three people.
Three people?
Three people.
Chiaki!
Wow, look at them. Gays, actors, and AV actresses.
What?
What are these three?
Shiraki!
They're all handsome guys.
Right?
Shiraki!
Hey!
Mr. Shiyaki!
I tend to misunderstand as an AV actress, but I'm the type of person who doesn't leave people in trouble.
So I thought I could help Mr. Endo at this time.
You should have come back.
Endo!
It really looks like Houston.
What the hell?
No way.
There's no one here.
No response?
No response.
Mr. Ogata, you said you were a cop.
No, you can't give up.
That's right.
You can't give up.
If you give up, everything in your life will be ruined.
That's right.
So you can't give up.
Yes, I understand.
Okay, let's go.
Chiaki!
Endo!
Oh, that's the place where the
Hiyake!
He's the one who's next to Osaka Dome.
He's not here.
He's next to Osaka Dome.
Good morning!
What are you doing?
What are you doing here?
What are you guys doing?
We're here to talk about something.
Why?
Here?
It's been half a year since M1.
It's been a while.
Why are you talking about something here?
We're here because we're bored.
Oh, really?
Well, well.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
My wife is wearing a tiara.
I can't get it. I'm not good at it.
I'm looking for it.
But it's okay. I'll tell you the story.
That's a big deal.
We'll look for it together.
They said they'd help us.
We'll accept their kindness.
Together.
Let's look for it together.
I'll go to the back.
Chia-kun!
Hey, you're getting better.
You're right.
Chiaki!
What's that?
This is the guy who does commercials.
There's definitely someone.
The one who does the car wipers.
Chiaki,
this is the guy who does commercials.
I'm telling you.
You're doing well.
So, there's definitely someone around here.
Chiaki!
What is it?
There's a book here.
I see.
What is it?
It's in the book.
Let's look for it.
Oh, I see.
No way!
Shiro!
Mr. Rei!
It's over if you stay here.
Shiro!
Mr. Rei!
Kiyoki-kun!
Sister!
Wife!
Wife?
I don't think you understand if it's a wife.
Can you do it in Chiaki?
Whose wife?
There are many.
Ujiin!
Yes, I never said it, but I didn't expect the worst to happen.
I thought only that I could save Inoue.
If you're alive, you can see that smile again.
I'm always talking about how ideal couple is.
I couldn't believe that his wife would end up like this.
That's weird.
Yeah.
It wasn't a good match.
Let's go to the police.
Let's go!
That's weird.
You're kidding me.
Mr. Shiyaki!
There's someone here!
Really?
Mr. Shiyaki's hair.
It's over.
Oh, Chiaki!
Chiaki won!
I'm so glad.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Chiaki, what's going on?
Chiaki.
What?
Good morning.
You can't be in the middle of the sea.
What's going on?
Good morning.
What are you doing here?
This is a very famous place called Nakanawari no Kana.
I had a fight with a man yesterday.
I was asking him if he was coming back.
Oh, really?
You had a fight with a man?
Yes.
Why do you all look so serious?
My wife Chiyaki is missing.
I'm looking for her.
Chiyaki?
Yes.
That's terrible.
But I'll talk to Mr. Karasawa.
I don't have anything here, so I'm dressed like this.
Can I help you?
If you want to help, you have to tell me in advance.
I'll help you.
I'm a little bit scared.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I saw something shining.
It's a big one.
What is this?
There's definitely something.
It's Chiaki.
I've seen this before.
I wonder why a young girl like Chiaki-chan ended up like this.
I want to change too.
God, please do something.
I prayed with my heart.
Chiaki-chan!
Where are you?
He's an old man.
He said he was an old man.
After this, Ichido kept shouting Chiaki's name until his voice was hoarse.
But, unfortunately, he couldn't find her.
The search took a long time.
Yay!
Chiaki!
Is Chiaki really safe?
Yay!
Okita!
I'm safe!
You've already decided.
I've already told you a lot.
Let's all work together and shout.
Ready, set...
SHIRAKU!
It's over.
It's impossible.
I don't have any confidence.
It's time to call.
It's really hard.
I'm going to call the police.
You can't say yes to everything.
It's really hard.
Hello?
Oh, really? I got it.
What?
I love you.
Wait a minute. What time do you finish today?
I can't do it if it's late.
It's too early.
I love you.
Sorry.
What's wrong?
I found it.
It was in my cell phone for about 5 hours.
It was in your cell phone?
Yes. I was told to come home early.
I see.
That's great.
Thank you.
You saved my life.
Thank you everyone!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
I'm sorry everyone.
Everyone, please take care of your juniors.
That's right.
I'm really sorry.
What?
I can't do it anymore.
Oh!
I got it.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, I understand.
My Yoyan is mine.
Natsumi, is that you?
Yes.
Okay.
Let's look for him together.
Really?
I'll look for him. I've already done it.
Can we look for him together?
Yes.
Natsumi!
Hey, Natsumi-chan!