Yōkan no Kanna
Yōkan, Tsutai wa Nakayoshi-san
Itsumo Futari de Mitsuyo-kan
Yōkan no Kanna
Yōkan no Yome
The night is coming
It's already time
Everyone is here
It's not that I'm bad or anything.
If I had to say, I'm a politician.
What does that have to do with anything?
The Takeshita cabinet.
That's old!
Well, there are a lot of things.
What else is there?
Let's go on.
But what about the punishment game?
Oh, the punishment game! That's right!
If you don't tell me that, how will I do it?
It's already decided in my head.
Can I say it?
For now, just say it.
This is going to be a really interesting punishment game.
There was this guy, the magician.
Copperfield.
Go see Copperfield.
America or something.
Why?
With four people.
They made you teleport.
If you go boom, you won't be able to get rid of the four of them.
And when the other four came out, for some reason, he became a skinhead.
This is...
Do-wan! Do-wan! Do-wan!
Endo! Do-wan! Yane! Tanaka! Do-wan! Yamazaki! Do-wan!
You're not even talking.
After Endo, why did you say Yane?
You should have said Tanaka right away.
I think this will be a great thing.
Think a little more.
Think a little more?
Yeah, a little more.
But, you know, you thought you were doing it, right?
I don't think you had any problem with me.
Neither Tanaka, nor Endo.
After all, that shit...
That shit is terrible, right?
Who would be in it if that happened?
I was totally late.
I was nervous.
If Yamazaki suddenly did it, it would be the worst.
I was the first one to think about it.
And then, I heard the sound of the sun and I thought,
It's too late!
You know,
I don't think you can see it on TV,
But if you look at the camera from the side, you can see it.
At Tanaka's place, the difference is about 3 meters.
If it wasn't for that, I would have lost more.
What is that guy?
I see.
I really didn't want him to be born.
That's not what you're saying.
It's because of the show.
That's true.
When he came to me from the end, he was like this.
It was a loss.
But before that, he was that slow?
He was really slow.
He's a neck.
He has a little bit of a ego, so it's fine.
Really, it's fine?
You might think I don't say this on TV, but I think Fujii is cuter.
I feel like I'm in the same boat as Fujii.
I see.
I think Fujii is cuter.
That's why I said, if it's a neck, then let's just say it clearly.
Understood.
Neck!
That's for the person himself.
That's right.
Even if you say it in a fake way, it's not a problem.
It's not a problem, if you say it's a neck.
It's a fake!
I was angry at first, but after you said you were going to quit, you said,
Say it!
This face!
What's good about it?
You're taking a life!
That's right!
Say it!
Hey!
You're talking like that?
What are you talking about?
But you're a kid, you have nothing to do with it!
I have nothing to do with it!
You do!
What do you mean you don't?
Say it!
Yes, I have.
Oh!
Simula X.
Tensai TV.
Oh!
Osaka Nagoya.
I have.
You have.
And you said that you don't want to do it!
Hey!
Don't say it!
I said it.
It's over.
It's over?
You should be the one to say it.
Oh.
Oh, it's over?
It's like going back to the bath.
Well, it's fine.
Well, let's think about it again.
Oh, really?
What's going to happen to you?
The story changes completely.
The car...
It's starting next month.
What?
I can't use my cell phone.
Oh, you said something.
You were driving.
There are so many idiots who talk on their phones and cause accidents.
They are even allowed to drive this car.
I can do it all by myself.
You can do it.
Right?
That's why it's so...
That's why it's gone.
That earphone.
Ah, yes, yes.
I can't drive like this.
But I think it's strange.
What do you mean?
What's the standard for the police?
What?
If you do this, do you know what will happen?
Even if you don't have a cell phone.
That's what I'm saying.
But, what will you do if you smoke like this?
You can't do the same thing.
But that's because it's impossible.
For example, what is it?
If you drive with your shoes like this, is this a violation?
I drive with one hand.
No way!
You can't do this with your shoes?
I drive with one hand.
You can't do this with a cigarette?
No, no.
Why?
You haven't been told that before?
Then, you should have put your phone in your shoe.
So, you shouldn't be stiff.
You shouldn't be stiff, but you put your phone in here.
If you're asked what you're doing, you should say,
in your shoe.
I'm going to talk with my shoe.
That's what you should have said.
What's wrong with you? You're taking me to a different place.
The place you're going to is not a hospital.
It's a hospital.
But I'm always like this.
That's right. There's no one who drives normally like this.
There's no one.
When you get to a certain point, it's like this.
What's this?
Well, in my case, I'm left-handed.
That's not good.
You're a fool!
Well, I'm right-handed, but...
Are you going to brag about your left-handedness?
Toll On
About the nuanced
Don't you think this is a fray?
What's the big deal?
Before your debut as a downtown, you had a baby with a thousand children as a step-mother.
Yes, yes.
You were born in the Rammer's method, but you were born too many times and were sealed away.
I heard that there is a method called the human method.
Yes, yes.
What is it?
Actually, it's the human method.
Whichever is fine.
It doesn't matter. You have to be clear about that.
It doesn't matter.
What is your wife's birth date?
What?
What did she give birth to?
What do you mean?
What did she do?
What kind of body did she have?
I want to know that.
I don't know what kind of body she had.
What kind of body she had?
What room is it?
Where is your room?
Sofa?
You don't have to make me do that!
What about the country?
I think I know
There is a place called Hitoho
Please teach me that
It's also called Nishinho
Is that okay?
If you are going to do this, please watch carefully
Please leave your hand here.
It's not breathing.
There is something like hi-fu.
It's not hi-fu.
Lamaze's method is...
That's what I'm teaching you.
Please do your best until you get your head out.
Do you mean that I should do my best?
You should do your best to live until you get your head out.
And when your head comes out,
Don!
But you can't make a mistake.
If you do this first,
the child will be like this.
The back will be like this.
I can't do it fast.
It's better to do it fast.
I take the train everyday to go to work.
Wait a minute. Are you editing something?
It's like the first time.
What are you talking about?
Why are you sweating all of a sudden?
I don't know.
What are you talking about?
What is it?
I take the train everyday to the company.
What was that?
What are you talking about?
I'll go back and press it again.
You're going to the company by the train, but you don't like the crowd.
That's right. There's a thing called people-intention.
Mr. Matsumoto of the train research group.
Yes.
Please tell us how to spend the train comfortably and freshly.
Of course there's that.
Please tell us how to spend it comfortably.
It's like this every morning.
It's like this.
You have to use this.
Because you have the rhythm.
Yes.
Right?
You have to dance.
It's a train.
Train.
Yes.
You have to dance.
You dance so cool.
No.
You can't do that.
It's just a piece of cloth.
Even so, I'm saying it's OK.
It's OK.
Try it.
Please, continue.
It's embarrassing.
OK, please show it.
Ah, it was embarrassing.
It was a good idea.
It's like an eraser.
Before her debut as downtown, she was the first woman to have a baby.
Her birth was born in the Ramaz method.
But she was born too many times and was sealed away.
I heard there is a method called the Hitoshi method.
What kind of method is it?
Actually, this is called the Hito-shi method.
I don't know that.
It's called the Hito-shi method.
You can say either.
What should I do?
Please teach me.
Hito-shi method.
Please do your best until you get a head.
What do you mean by do my best?
I mean, I'll do it with all my strength.
And then, don!
Don!
If you don't pay attention, if this leg goes don, your back will go round and round.
You're a little...
Please say it differently.
Terrible!
I'll kill you as a partner of the comedian Tsubushi!
How many are they dori?