The first time, the Badminton tournament where the winner gets 1 million yen!
There's no one here today, right?
That's right.
Your opponent is Endo-san.
Endo-san's temperature was a little higher than the normal one.
It's a little higher, but I'll take care of it.
I'll do my best today.
That's what you're supposed to do.
Actually, I was thinking of Hamada-san's power-hara.
What? Really?
My mental state...
I didn't know that.
It may take longer than I thought.
Endo-kun's vacation.
The four of us should play badminton and wait for Ku-chan.
That's enough.
That's not enough.
You can't eat a million yen.
In this day and age.
That's right.
I understand.
Rock, paper, scissors?
Rock, paper, scissors.
And then, with a rock, paper, scissors, you do that.
That's right.
Hello Japanese comedian people.
Hello to all Japanese comedians.
I am Benjamin Bonas.
I am very very big money owner
I am the world's richest man
When we were talking to the four of you here, you were already looking at us
We were waiting for you
You should have waited for Kuro-chan first
I don't know that!
He was eating a lot of characters.
A man who suddenly appeared, called Benjamin Bonas.
What is his purpose?
What's wrong?
You are Benjamin Bonas too?
I am Benjamin Bonas.
Don't imitate me.
World famous.
I heard that there are many famous musicians.
For example?
Michael Jackson
That's amazing.
Madonna
Eihara Masahiro
Why are you suddenly saying that?
That's a lot of names.
Now?
Now
Audition
Now, I will hold an audition to decide the next Hollywood star.
Audition?
Yes, me is America.
I will take you to America.
I know.
Iwagawa said it, but it seems to be going up a lot.
It's going up a lot.
I smoked on the smokehouse, but I'm as strong as a log.
I'm as strong as a log engine.
It's going up a lot.
Are you okay?
Adachi of the book.
Cal
What's your name?
I love you Benjamin Bonas
Oh
Thank you
Social distance now
What is this?
If you do it, you'll be in trouble.
Social distance is a good way to keep your distance.
That's a great way.
You guys, do you know anything about Hollywood?
Of course we do.
There's a Hollywood version of the Gakitsuka.
I know that.
I'll teach you.
This is the Gakitsuka member, right?
Yes.
Gakitsuka member, okay?
For example, this.
Yes, that's me.
If it's Hollywood, this person is doing it.
It's Sam Schultz.
Hollywood Sam Schultz.
It's a white peach fruit.
And this is the end of today's break.
The end.
I'm telling you, I'm telling you.
It's a famous saying.
Who?
Rampage Jackson is doing it.
Oh, that kind of person.
I'm doing it with a chain.
I don't know who it is.
It's Kevin.
It's a little similar.
The flow is completely different.
Oh, this is the problem.
You're the only one who's not happy.
I'm going to take you to Hollywood, but you don't know anything about Hollywood, do you?
No, I don't know anything about it.
Okay, so I'm going to test you on Hollywood.
What about Hollywood?
Hurry up and tell me.
You're the important one.
You're the important one?
I don't need to be told.
Wait a minute.
Do you know anything about Hollywood?
No.
What do you mean?
I've been there.
You've been there?
Yes.
When did you go?
Wait a minute. When did you go?
About 20 years ago.
You went about 20 years ago?
Yes.
How many days did you go?
I went for about a week.
You're quite a long-term goer. You know a lot about Hollywood.
Well, I went to play and stuff.
Where did you play with Hollywood?
What are you talking about? Stop it!
What are you doing?
I deleted it because you started talking
Oh, sorry
I didn't want you to talk
It's rude, right?
No, it's fine
I'll do it
Who else played with Hollywood?
I've been there
How was the American era?
The American era?
No, it's fine
How was the American era?
I'm fine with just closing my eyes.
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine with just doing it while I'm on the phone.
Oh, you went to New York?
New York is great.
It's my job though.
I like New York a lot.
I'm not laughing because I'm not that far from Hollywood and New York.
If I went to Japan, I could go to other cities.
But in America, I'd have to use a plane.
I'm not kidding.
I'd have to use a plane to get there.
It's fine.
Please tell us more about it.
There's something about it, right?
Sorry, sorry.
I don't think you know anything about Hollywood.
So, get into me.
Tell me about my cool points one by one.
Adachi and Carlton will give you a demonstration.
Everyone, please watch.
Let's go.
Hey, Ryo-san!
Can you sing a cool song for the bonus?
1, 2, 3, 4!
First, Adachi-kun, go for it!
You're very rich
Next is Karukin-chan, go for it!
You're tall
Yeah!
OK, OK
Now I'll have you guys die together
I can't do that!
I really don't want to do it
I'll do it in order
So you can say my cool part
And at the end, there's a key
This is a game called Kill or Kiss
If you get a kiss, you're okay
If you get a kill, you're out
Please
Okay, let's go
Let's go!
It's long
Hey you guys!
Please say something cool about me, Benjamin Bonus!
First, Hosei-chan
Please say something!
The watch is very cool
Next is the horse, please say it
The white hair suits you
Next is the hippo, please say it
The cut-out is cool
Next is the raccoon, please say it
The sunglasses are very gorgeous
You're a real shiba inu.
Seriously.
Hey, you're a real shiba inu.
Hey, bring me some
No, no. I got a cold.
I'm begging you, Tanaka.
You're the only one who's slipping right now.
Seriously.
How many percent of myself did I get?
In my mind...
Hey!
Calm down, I'm calm
I can't stop the others
I'll show you a demonstration
Hey Hosei-chan, let's do all of it
Yes
Say all of my lines
1, 2, 3, 4
Look at Hosei-chan
Look at me
Arland Chirp Chirp Arman
That's the best
The needlework is close
The belt is cool
One more time, Hose-chan, say it
If the stick is easy to use
One more time, Hose-chan, give it to me
The jacket suits you
Houdara Tanaka-kun, say it
The socks are very charming
What are you doing?
You're really a shiba inu.
Someone bring me some角材.
Kill.
No, it's not a kill.
Hosei-chan did so many things.
Let's do it again. Can you do it again?
Yes, I can.
Can you do it?
No, I can't.
I can't do it alone.
I think everyone should do it.
I can't do that. I'll leave it to you.
If you want to quit, I'll quit.
Can I quit?
You can quit.
Then I'll quit.
You're quitting?
Yes.
Then, Hosei-chan, get out!
Please leave.
You've done your job for today.
I'll quit.
Sorry, I...
You can do it again.
That's right. Sorry.
I didn't think you'd ask me to leave.
There's no way I have a chance.
Please leave.
Really?
Thank you.
No, no, no.
How was it?
Can you give me a chance at the end?
Do you want to do it all?
I'll do it all.
And then, if you get a kiss, I'll accept it.
I see.
Okay.
I'll give you four kisses.
Four kisses for one person?
Yes, yes.
Okay, I understand.
No way. I'm doing something impossible right now.
Yes, I'll give you the last chance.
Can you do the opposite?
I got it
Let's get on the stage
Let's start with the feeling
Let's go
Let's do it with the feeling
Hose-chan
You'll get a good result
I'm sure you'll get something
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14
First, Hose-chan, give me a shot
There are two rings
Next, Hose-chan, give me a shot
The glass in the sunglasses is piling up
Your white hair is shining
Never were you given us Californians ka!.
Stuck to your wszyscy herr hair.
form MErando
It had its whereabouts.
Why, well
You got any answers to this here?!
Yeah loud af.
Hey, I guess
WE'LL should try
Diet
Durin
Excuse me.
What the hell is this?
Shouji-san, you can go.
Are you sure?
Do your best.
Hosei.
Yes.
Come here.
Are you sure you are okay with that?
Are you sure you are okay with leaving the room?
No!
I told you so!
You will get angry.
Excuse me!
Come on! Come on!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Get out!
Please forgive him.
That's enough.
Are you regretting?
Yes, please forgive me.
Then, I can't go back.
Next, to go to Hollywood, speed and reflexes are important.
I'll give you a test now.
Everyone, please put this on your right hand.
Put your right hand on your right hand and try the Haryutou Star's secret skill, the reflex test.
From now on, we will play a reflex game.
The title is, Guntei Up Down!
Please raise and lower your right hand with the capacity of a hataage game.
I'll raise and lower my hand in an English way.
I think it's difficult because it's English.
Oh my god!
What?
In the end, it's better to translate it.
Your fast is the key.
The speed is...
Max speed.
It's max speed.
Let's go with space speed.
Ultimate space speed.
Okay.
Can you do it?
Raise your arms.
No.
Lower your arms.
No, no.
Don't raise your arms. Lower your arms.
Oh my god!
And the pattern is the same all the time!
All of them are the same!
What?!
Help!
The next game, Hollywood Star is...
What is Hollywood Star?
Crocodile Dandy
It's Crocodile Dandy
Open
I'll give you a chance to fight.
I'll start with Kanji.
Put this on.
The items for Crocodile Dandy are knife and cowboy hat.
First, Tanaka, who is familiar with animals.
Yes, yes.
Three, two, one.
I'll give you a chance to fight.
Tanaka san
Yes
3, 2, 1, Fight!
I think he's done
He's been bitten
Good, good, good
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Yes, yes, yes
You did it
Raise your hand if you've defeated him
Yes!
Nice fight
Okay, good.
Thank you.
Okay, then, Machan, can you do it?
Yes.
Let's go, 3, 2, 1, fight!
Help me!
I'm dying!
Don't make a comedy.
No, you have to do it properly.
I didn't laugh much.
You didn't come to make a joke like that.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I see. I'm sorry.
The staff told me that I came here to die.
I was told that I came here to die.
I'll do my best.
Hosei, can you do it?
You're the one who's going to die.
I'll give you a little more difficult challenge.
Cut this crocodile.
Let's go to the real crocodile.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I really came here to die.
Open your eyes!
Eye spray!
The dog is changing...
He really is going to die...
Open your eyes!
I'm counting on you!
Now, Hosei.
Very strong.
I will kill you.
I have never seen you like this.
That was good.
Then, Hamada, you try.
I'm scared. I'm going to do it.
Then, Mr. Hamada, fight!
You defeated him.
No, no, no.
You completely defeated him.
Did he eat it?
What's wrong?
I was hit like this and I slipped like this.
But when I came back, I went back a little.
You went too far.
I went too far.
With this, all the tests are over.
Who passed the audition?
Finally, I will officially announce who passed.
Hama-chan.
It was amazing.
I'm sorry.
What?
Yun-bo was like this, and I was like this.
It was a huge shock.
I'm sorry.
Pass.
It was amazing.
Hama-chan, congratulations on passing!
Congratulations.
It's a pass, but...
Hama-chan, congratulations.
But, I'm really laughing, but...
The screen is too Asian.
So, let's change our faces.
What?
We can't catch up with that face.
Can't catch up?
It's impossible, honestly.
Tama-chan, let's go fix your face.
What?
Takasu is waiting for you.
What are you talking about?
Let's go.
Yes.
You're really going to take me?
Well, I'm a little scared of being taken by Kuu-chan.
Come, cutie
Wow, you're doing well. You're not tired, right?
I think Benjamin will be back soon
Sorry to keep you waiting
He's here
Come
Come, cutie
You're doing well. You're not tired, right?
It's good that you're beautiful
I'll give you a needle
What?
Anyone is fine.
I don't think anyone is fine.
It's not about the face.
No.
Didn't you say you don't need a face?
No, I don't need it.
I don't have a face.
So, I think anyone is fine.
No, it's because you have a spirit.
Mr. Benjamin.
What?
I'm sorry to interrupt you.
What's wrong?
There is a phone call from the American Space Agency.
A giant meteorite will soon crash into Japan!
What?
You're kidding, right?
We're the only ones who can do that, right?
Yes!
Let's go!
...
I don't wanna close my eyes
I don't wanna force me
Cause I miss you, baby
And I don't wanna miss a thing
Cause even when I dream of you
You see the light
You don't miss me
And I don't wanna miss a thing
Don't wanna close my eyes
I don't wanna fall asleep, cause I miss you baby
Don't wanna sleep
I'm sorry, Hamada-san
When the curtain was closed, Kuu-chan said,
Did he say that?
He did
Oh, really?
I wish the curtain was closed a little more and I could have waited a little more
I'm sorry, Hamada-san, it was pretty early
But, the meteorite fell and...
And the only one who saved them was...
Those four people.
I was watching something like that.
I wonder what it was.
Jackson 5?
That's right.
Jackson 5.
The end
It's Snoopy
What? What? What?
What? Really?
It's over
It's over?
You're kidding me, right?
What was that?
Is that all?
Earth was saved?
Saved?
Yes, the meteorite hit us.
We were saved?
I don't know.
Earth was saved, but we weren't.
Endo and Rossi were the best.
The two of them were resting.
Good work.
I don't understand.
I'm going to show you a little more.
I'll show you a little more.
New Dog
Mokumoku
Thank you very much.
The past broadcast was broadcast exclusively on Hulu.
Furu Kensaku