The Beijing Olympics in August
Kitajima Kosuke, start!
The gold medal in the world record of the swimming athlete, Kitajima, is new to everyone's memory
And here is another man, challenging the world record
I was told to do the high jump
I wonder how it would be if I could record it for an hour.
The pride of the Endo-chozo, Endo Takeshi.
He has been active in various scenes, but it took him 30 minutes to record all of them.
I've never seen anyone record an hour.
So I want to be the first to beat Takeshi in the world record.
Will Takeshi be able to beat Takeshi in one hour?
The 3600 second miracle, Takeshi Endo challenges the world record.
But Matsumoto-san, this is a reckless challenge.
Yes, there are many challenges in the world, but I think this challenge is very reckless.
What do you think, Ayakata?
When I first said this, I thought, can I really do it?
How about you, Yama-chan?
I think it's hard to talk for 60 minutes.
I see.
I wonder if it's okay.
He is a very calm person.
Really?
He was calling Tokyo Walker in the dressing room.
I think that's why he's so calm.
I think he's going to do it.
Can I call Endo?
He's already in a different place.
Endo!
Good evening.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Thank you to the people who gave us this opportunity.
Downtown, Hajime, Yamaguchi, Tanaka, and the staff. Thank you very much.
I'm worried if it's really okay.
Even B-boy Takeshi hasn't done this before.
That's right.
There is only one rule for this challenge.
More than 10 seconds of silence is forbidden.
At that point, the challenge will fail.
But it was a failure.
And then, in the last 5 minutes, he went to the studio and made a world record in front of the members.
I think Takeshi-san will be silent for more than 10 seconds.
Please give me a cheer!
It's the season when we can't do anything.
That's right.
It's always this season.
It's this time of the year. I guess you're curious about the change of seasons.
Endo, who has been given a means to communicate, cannot know the situation of the studio.
Endo Takeshi's lonely battle will open the curtain.
Ready!
It's starting!
What's going on?
Duncan!
You know what?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Duncan, you bastard!
Huh?
You don't have to say it over and over again, Duncan!
What the hell are you?
If this happens, we can't do anything.
We can't help you.
Do you know who you are?
You are a
Is it okay?
You talk too much, can you sleep at this pace?
Turn the car!
I'm waiting for you!
You have time to end the video.
I have time to finish the video.
Why are you saying that?
What are you saying?
I've been eating since I was a kid.
Are you still a kid?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Why are you so angry?
Why are you angry?
Don't take it off.
You don't listen to Shio.
I'm eating.
My car is there, isn't it?
What kind of image do you have?
You know my car, don't you?
Let's go, Mahoto.
What? What? What?
I don't have such a car.
What are you doing now?
Turn it quickly.
I've done a lot of things.
What's your car?
Mentally, mentally, it shouldn't be abnormal.
Turn it quickly.
But my family is watching.
You're still talking.
They're watching and they're watching with faith.
I told you to turn the car around.
You're still talking.
It's a car.
Your voice is a little...
You heard me?
You're in trouble.
I told you to turn the car around.
Turn it around quickly.
This is really tough.
You have some time.
I'll order you ice coffee at Konjakuwan.
Taka.
Call TMC.
I'm telling you to order me ice coffee at Konjakuwan.
Taka-san, you still haven't ordered me ice coffee.
Even if you want me to turn the car around, you should order me ice coffee, you bastard.
Hurry up and turn the car around.
Say it from the forest.
The president.
There's no need to turn it around.
Why is that?
I can't go home.
Why are you sitting here, Duncan?
Hurry up.
If you have time to smoke, turn the car.
Turn the car.
I told you to turn the car.
Well, it's been 10 minutes.
I gave him a little.
I'm a fool.
I'm probably hungry.
I heard that the person who was the one who made this challenge was the one who was in the support VTR of the actor Yukari Endo.
That's great.
Let's take a look.
A message of soul sent to Endo.
Hello, I'm Kuriru Matsumura.
The first person to imitate Takeshi, Kunishiro Matsumura.
He has the skill to make Takeshi-san's heart beat fast, but he sends Eiru to Endo who is aiming for the world's best.
I also heard the voice of Takeshi-san who has been doing this for 20 minutes.
I'm getting tired.
I don't think the lord can imitate me this much.
He imitates me so much.
Endo, I'm happy too!
If I can do this for an hour, I'll be a real comedian!
The next message is...
Hello, I'm Nishioka.
The former housekeeper, Nishioka, has a big deal with a famous actor who used to live in the same apartment.
He sends Eil to Endo.
I moved last year.
Chiaki and Endo said they would buy the room.
Chiaki was very motivated.
But, it's been less than a month since we last saw each other.
I hope you'll aim for the world record and show us your best.
I hope you'll let us see you play in the Chia Cup again.
Tokuma-san also did a VTR.
He's still doing it in the middle of the VTR.
It's getting dark.
It's a story that you and Kiraiyu are also like that.
It's a story that Kiraiyu will be able to live with the money he makes.
The car hasn't started yet.
It's not going to start yet.
It's going to start soon.
The wax of the park is coming out.
It's from Mr. Yumeida of Piccadilly.
It's true.
I'll tell you that I love you.
I'm grateful.
Stop playing the guitar!
I wonder if this is reaching Endo.
Endo can't see this.
That's right.
Hurry up and turn it, Daka!
What are you doing?
Turn it!
You're so angry!
Turn the car!
I'm waiting.
Daka!
There's nothing here.
What?
The car is already running.
Hurry up and do it.
I see.
Hurry up.
What happened to the coffee?
Idiot.
What are you drinking?
I can't drink it.
Hurry up and do it.
Turn right.
It's already running.
I'm sleeping.
Why don't you sleep?
Go to sleep, you bastard!
Go to sleep!
Hurry up and go to the pub!
You always sleep in pubs.
Shut up and go to sleep!
Don't get up, I'm sleeping!
Stop!
Hey, you bastard!
You should have stopped the car here.
Open it.
Open it, Duncan.
Open it first.
Stop it.
I'm filming.
You bastard.
Shut up.
Duncan, stop the car.
Why can't you stop the car?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You bastard.
Go to sleep.
What are you doing?
Okay.
Now, we have a letter from Endo's mother.
Kiyo-san.
Let's read it.
To Sho-chan.
How are you?
It seems that you can't come back to Osaka recently.
I'm looking forward to seeing you on TV every day.
Sho-chan has grown up to be a great adult.
When he was a child, he was a child who drank his father.
Once he sucked out his father, he was not far from his father.
Sho-chan grew up by drinking his father.
His mother was healed by raising his father.
And this time, he challenged Takeshi's impersonation.
Congratulations.
I never thought I would be able to be with you for this long.
Don't give up until the end. Keep it up, Kiyomi.
My father was a very good student.
He still likes to be with me.
You know that?
Yeah right now.
I've told you before.
Why did you bring it?
What is this?
Bring the menu!
Oh really?
That's the menu of Duncan.
It's in the restaurant.
It's written there.
You should bring the menu!
I can't bring the menu.
You're just drinking alcohol!
Don't you have anything else to drink?
Come here you bastard.
Come on, Mimata.
Mimata, you're always like this.
Hurry up and bring the menu!
You bring the menu, I don't know what to do!
The restaurant staff will bring the menu!
You're kidding me, right?
Now, let's sing a song for Yama-chan.
I can become stronger only by the number of tears.
The flower that blooms on the asphalt.
I'm not afraid of anything.
Tomorrow I'll come for you
Hurry up!
That's enough!
Turn the car!
We're going home.
This shop is enough!
Turn the car!
We're going home.
His voice is like that of a normal Edo.
Totally.
Now, Tanaka is writing a letter to Edo.
I'm also writing a letter to my partner for the first time.
I'm worried about writing a letter.
Excuse me.
To Endo.
I think that Endo will be able to do something as a partner for this challenge.
I will read a letter of encouragement.
You have been surprised since childhood.
When I was in middle school, my parents found out about the ero books that I had hidden in my house.
Most of them were about Go-Rou, Skorra, and so on.
But the book you used was called Jiko.
In high school, you were good at baseball, and you were called from 7 high schools in Japan.
All high schools except the one you chose were selected to be the head of the school board.
You have achieved this unrivaled achievement, and I am surprised again.
From Naoki Tanaka.
I see.
There are many different feelings.
I can't think of the ending.
I thought I would sing while thinking of what I was doing to Shiranosu-san.
I thought it was very sacred.
The level is high.
That's why it's a challenge that can be done.
Put the song in.
Why are you singing Medley?
Where is it?
Come on.
You should sing with Duncan.
You're a piece of shit, you bastard.
What the hell is this?
I'm going to kill you.
It's a sport.
We're going to do sports together.
That's it.
10 seconds left.
Hang in there.
It hurts.
It's okay.
You're doing great.
I'm still working on it.
I see.
You're doing well in the first few episodes.
I'm still working on it.
You're saying something.
We have more people who are still dreaming.
Please support us.
A message of soul to ENDO.
Hello.
The CEO of Office Kitano, Mori Masayuki.
He is the representative of the company and also the producer of the movie, Ratsuan.
What is the message he wants to send to Endo?
This time, Endo Kokoriko will be doing a long time recording of Takesu's impersonations.
I hope you can challenge this.
And, by the way, the movie that is currently being shown is...
It's a pre-release!
Akiresu Tokamen.
This is a high-quality film. It's well-received and highly-appreciated by critics.
I hope you won't miss it.
Please watch Akiris and Kame.
I hope you will watch it.
I will be happy if you will promote the film.
We are still working on it.
I see.
It's a great film.
That's amazing.
What the hell are you?
Who are you?
This is bad.
Standing is boring.
Let's read more books.
It's almost 5 o'clock.
We'll be heading to the spa.
There's a lot of stuff coming in, you idiot.
Do you understand, you idiot?
It's about time for the third one.
That's right.
The last 5 minutes!
Here it comes!
Go for it!
Go, go!
The last 5 minutes!
Will he be able to do it?
Let's go, Minato!
Go for it!
You're saying you're going to the spa.
You should start the car.
You should start the car first.
It is the last 5 minutes
Why is Mushiwa here already
There are some audience groups who support kind foods
How complicated
I've never heard of it.
It's being supported.
Now, just a little bit more.
Now, to sell the last strength and do our best, let's sing another song!
I'm a little confused
I can say it, please say it
Don't lose, just a little more
Run through to the end
No matter how far apart we are
Our hearts are always by each other's side
I'm going to chase a distant dream
I won't lose, look over there
The town I can go back to is nearby
No matter how far apart we are
My heart is by your side
I'm still looking at the same person
Ah! I'm already dead!
Hang on! Hang on!
Time's up!
Hang on!
Hang on! Hang on!
I'm almost done!
I wonder if I'll make it...
What are you even looking at?
I'm done!
Just a little more!
Ah, I'm going to die!
I'm going to die!
Endo! Endo!
That's enough!
It's about time!
I'm not talking anymore!
Endo! Endo!
What is this?
Why are you trying to get into trouble?
Let's get out of here!
Endo! Endo!
Wait! Wait!
I'm going to get in trouble!
What the hell is this, you bastard!
Why do you work out so hard, you bastard!
Duncan, you! Look at this, study!
Why do you say you love Chiaki, you bastard!
It's not related, you bastard!
Who are you?
Don't look at me!
Let's count down from 10 seconds ago.
What the hell is this!
15 seconds.
If you can't do it well, then eat it!
3, 2, 1, go!
Oh, he did it!
He did it!
Endo Mageshi, the world's greatest!
Endo, endo!
He did it!
He finally did it!
Thank you.
This is amazing.
He did it, he did it! He did it for an hour!
Thank you.
What?
Thank you, you bastard.
I really did it in one hour.
You really did it in one hour.
I did it. I did it.
I didn't cheat at all.
I did it.
I thought I might quit halfway through, but I did it several times.
Duncan never turns the car around.
That's what it is.
He doesn't even bring the menu.
I thought that the shop staff should bring it.
It was a complicated private room.
I'll put the one that is not edited in the DVD.
And I'll give it to Endo.
I'll leave it on the road for the viewers who want it.
That's right.
Thank you for your cooperation with the people involved in the Otsutsuta incident.
Gakugou Sky News
The final game of the punishment game that was discussed by all 5 people.
Including the unreleased broadcast, it is recorded for about 4 hours and a half.
On November 26th, it will be released.
Yamasaki, who has been defeated in the previous battle, challenges the enemy Moriman.
We are now seeing something really strong!
Will Nishinomiya be able to gain glory by
Thank you for watching!