The next day
I saw the sports news the other day
Apparently you can catch 8kg of anago
Where is it?
Tokyo Bay
That's not it
What kind of Tohoku region is it?
8kg is like this
It's anago
It's just one, right?
It's not?
It's definitely not
It's like this
It's called anaconda
You're such a big hole.
You're a snake.
I'm not a snake.
I'm a person.
I'm really curious about the news.
Why did you dig a hole?
I think there were many other things.
I saw it and I wanted to dig it.
Is what Hamada said last week true?
To find out, we will challenge the monster-sized hole digging in the Tokyo Bay.
In the first episode, Hamada's words are true or false?
Monster-class giant Anago Tsurou!
From the beginning of the end, the octave was higher.
I didn't want to go that high.
That's why I have an image of Hamada.
This is good.
It's here.
That's right.
It's not that heavy.
This is good.
8kg.
But, you know, it's on the news.
If you catch a lot, it won't be on the news.
That's right.
You're good.
You're good at sports.
You were on it yesterday.
That's not easy to catch.
Why do you have to spend 30 minutes to catch this?
Get a normal one.
A normal one.
This is it.
How many kilograms is this?
This is...
It's less than 1 kilogram.
It's 150 grams.
Really? That's a lot.
What do you mean by that?
It's like sushi.
That's right.
Itamae-san is strong today.
He'll grill it.
If you can make something over 8 kilograms,
you can grill it here.
That's right!
Grilled with a gang-ran.
Yes, yes.
However, if you can't catch a fish over 8kg,
you will be given a very expensive 8kg steak.
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
It's a very expensive steak.
No, no, this is definitely...
Why do you have to give me a steak when I can't catch a fish?
No, I will definitely make you do that.
It's not like the nori in the show, but I will really make you do that.
I will definitely make you do that with your money.
The funny thing is that we caught 7kg of fish, and it was pretty fun to watch.
And we also want to see the 8kg of steak.
We want to see the 8kg of beef.
We want to see that.
How many grams is this?
150g.
What are you talking about?
We were all like, wow.
Isn't that where the fish are?
Why did you say that?
Why did you say that again?
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors
The five people on the boat are going at a high speed to reach the point where the giant conch will be caught
The tension is rising
You're the one who's going to fish?
You're the one who said it first
That's why I'm here
That's not right
There's no sign of fish
It's not even out yet
What do you mean there's no sign of fish at this point?
30 minutes have passed
Finally, they have reached their destination.
That red and white tower, right?
That's the point.
It's not a building.
It's just a little bit in front of it.
It seems that the girl is already up there.
This is the point, right?
No, it's Hamada-san.
I'm going home.
Hamada-san!
I'm sorry. I'm the one who said that.
It's too cold.
I've reduced the speed. It's about time.
Really?
Yes.
It's about time.
Where are you going to take me?
I'm going to make you laugh.
I'll be the first to get out of the stage.
You're crazy.
They finally arrive at their destination.
The five of them learn the tips of how to fish giant conch.
When you fish a conch, you have to look at it like this.
You have to look at it like this.
If you think it's heavy, you can just grab it like this.
It's difficult.
It's quite difficult.
Can you film it?
I can.
8kg.
I can't believe you can't even lift 8kg.
Really?
8kg?
As the expectations increase, the giant conch starts.
It's not like this.
Is it coming?
What? Is it coming?
I don't know.
Don't be so negative.
It's funny.
I'm pulling it, but it's not working.
He's a bad guy.
He's like a CM Matagi.
Don't think so much.
It's scary.
I want to see it.
I want to catch it.
I'm scared.
That's not true.
It's not a good story.
Without any sign of success, 15 minutes have passed since the start.
His expression has gradually become more fierce.
I can't draw that kind of thing.
I'll go to the front.
I'm not sure.
Ah, this is not it.
He doesn't seem to be motivated.
I can't believe it.
He said it himself.
He's trying to blame it on Endo.
He's trying to make me angry.
I was wondering what he would do, but it was faster than I thought.
He was on the way.
This is a bit...
I'm not sure.
Which one will it be?
I don't know.
I can't catch anything.
The anxiety between the five began to grow.
At that time...
Ah!
Eh?
It may have come!
Not yet, not yet.
It's coming, it's coming.
Eh, really?
It's coming.
Here?
I'm not wearing it.
Oh, you're wearing it.
You're wearing it, right?
You're wearing it.
It moved!
It's coming!
Go! Go!
Hurry up and wear it!
My head hurts!
Wait a minute.
Really?
It's you, right?
Right?
You're fishing for a boat, right?
Wow, it's huge!
Wow, amazing!
This is still a baby.
What?
This is still a baby?
The chin is like a cat's.
Like a cat's chin.
He caught the first big fish, but it was still far from 8 km.
And the time of silence begins again.
Hamada-san!
What?
Why?
It's not going at all.
I caught it.
8 km.
I said it was about 1 km.
It's 8 times of this.
It's not a big deal.
You did it like this, right?
Like this.
Like this, right?
I'll tell you.
It's a hole.
It's a hole, right?
It's not over yet.
Time passes without a sign of the second one.
The giant hole that causes 8kg still doesn't exist?
At that time, a hit came after a long time
It's coming! It's coming!
Put your weight on it! Put your weight on it!
Stand up! Stand up!
Oh, it's coming!
Is it big?
Wow, it's big!
It's bigger than the one before.
Wow!
Look, it's 8kg!
8kg is...
It's pretty heavy, isn't it?
It's heavy.
It's bigger than the one before, right?
It's bigger.
The sun is setting, and it's time to catch a huge fish.
It's already rising.
It's a solo fish.
Will it be 8kg?
From now on?
Once he regained his motivation, this man...
The man is...
What the hell are you doing?
Wow, it's huge!
It's huge!
It's 8kg!
8kg! It's 8kg!
It's heavy!
It's 8kg!
This is amazing.
It's heavy!
Wow!
It's a red cone!
That's why I said it!
What is this?
It's like a little lover's village.
It's like this village.
I have a lot of fish.
You should practice.
It's May soon.
May is the birth month.
It's not a birth month.
Wait a minute.
This is amazing.
Look at this.
I told you.
I caught three fish, but the scale is getting bigger.
I've seen bigger ones than the one before.
What?
That size?
I want to see it.
I want to see it too.
That size is amazing.
Oh, it's coming again.
The order is amazing.
It's coming to me.
I'm down?
I'm coming.
It's coming!
Wow, that's frustrating!
That was amazing!
What?
It's not a ton, it's a ton!
It's not 8kg, it's a ton!
It's 1 ton!
It's 1 ton?
It's like a ton!
The huge hole is starting to appear one after another as they approach the time limit of the plaster.
Hurry! Hurry!
I want to do this too.
The rain is coming!
It's coming! It's coming!
It's coming!
Roll it! Roll it!
It's huge!
Takadan-sama!
Don't look at me!
Wait, wait!
It's too big!
It's coming!
It's big, but it's smaller than the one before.
It's big!
Is it a sea bass?
It's a sea bass.
Wow, it's huge!
It's huge!
It's long.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's really amazing.
Wait, it's just me.
I want you to experience this.
Thank you.
Only Matsumoto hasn't caught anything yet.
Will Matsumoto be able to get the answer?
This is all I have.
I thought I had it, but I was wrong.
He is trying to find out where Matsumoto is.
Is there another one?
Yes, there is.
Matsumoto-san, you are...
I got it! I got it!
You are not aware of it.
You are being told.
No one can tell me.
Go to the endo.
Wow.
The flowers of life are blooming in the valley of the waves.
Wow, another big one!
Wow, it's big!
It's big!
Wow!
This is amazing!
Hold him! Hold him!
Hold him!
Look at his face!
Why are you holding him?
He is fond of the fish.
It is heavy.
Hama-san, please do your best.
Hama-san, please do your best!
This is so heavy.
Oh, it's big!
It's big!
It's really big.
Wow.
It's strange.
It's amazing.
I caught this one.
I got it.
It's big.
This is big.
Wrap it more.
More.
Let's put it in the net.
You look like you're doing something.
What are you doing on a boat?
It's huge!
Really?
Wow!
It's huge!
Get in! Hurry up and get in!
This is no good!
It's huge!
It's thick!
This is huge.
All of them are like this.
Huge.
And the squid is...
It's like this.
I haven't eaten all of them.
Thick.
This is amazing.
This is huge.
This must be 8 kg.
Huge.
This is definitely something.
This is amazing.
It's so big!
It's big, isn't it?
While the fish are being caught one by one, Matsumoto still can't catch any.
There is only a little time left.
At that time...
Ah! Matsumoto! Matsumoto!
What are you doing?
Ah!
It's coming! It's coming! It's coming!
It's coming, isn't it?
You're really...
It's a new one!
It's coming, right?
It's coming!
It's the last one.
Is it coming this time?
It's big!
It's a normal anago.
It's about 150cm.
Huh?
It's coming!
It's small!
What is this?
I'm embarrassed.
It's the first time that everyone is happy with this.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Are you ready, Hama-san?
I said, are you ready? You understand what I said, right?
But this...
We haven't measured it yet.
The two fish you caught were quite big.
It was indeed thick.
It was indeed a bit surprising.
It was amazing.
But it's said that there are still twice as many fish as that.
That's not true.
No, no, no, this is true.
Let's measure it again.
If it's over 8kg, we'll eat the anago.
If it's not, we'll go to the steak restaurant.
You guys are a little scared.
We'll see if we can measure it.
The result is out!
Thank you!
We should do it.
I'm not sure about the popularity of this place.
I'm a big guy.
No, you're not.
You're so small.
Yamazaki-san is one.
Kurosu-san is one.
Tama-san is two.
I'm six.
Tanaka is two.
There are 12 of them in total.
If there are more than 8kg, we can eat them.
If not, I'll go with 8kg steak.
I want to fill my stomach with anything.
Look at this.
If you look at it like this, it's a shark.
It's a shark.
It's as big as a water tank.
Well, we can't help it if we measure it.
The biggest one is already...
The biggest one?
This one.
This is 11.12.
If you weigh it, it's amazing.
Let's measure it right away.
How many kilograms is this bucket?
This is 1 kilogram.
It's already been pulled out.
The numbers that came out here are the same.
Really?
This one looks smaller, but it's not.
This one is bigger.
I'm begging you, the steak is huge.
Now, that's...
I can't eat this.
The steak is good.
How about this?
It's over 8 kilograms.
It's really bad.
I'll eat it.
Is it over 8 kilograms?
The result is...
this!
Wow!
That 4 times!
8.3kg!
We did it!
Wow, it was all real!
This is amazing!
Well, no matter how much you pull, it's still over 8kg.
That's right.
Immediately, they will cut the 8kg giant conger eel and make a conger eel bowl.
Ah, it smells good.
It smells good.
It's a little different from this.
Yes.
It smells good.
That's the end.
Ah, this is the end.
Is this me?
Amazing.
What is this?
This is Tanaka.
Wow, it's huge.
Mr. Hamada, this is for you.
The one on the left is for you.
Thank you.
That's mine?
That's right.
That's yours.
That's mine.
What is this?
Thank you.
Why didn't you give me a high-five?
Let's eat.
Wow, it's a little hard.
Wow, it's hard.
Don't complain all the time.
Wow, it's true.
Wow, it's really good.
It's hard.
It's dry.
The rice doesn't come out.
How did you eat this?
Well, it's okay.
Hey, I'm scared.
It's not good.