Tonight, finally, it will be revealed
An artist who makes such a ridiculous sound appears in the studio
I said it once again!
Ladies and gentlemen
It's hot
It's hot and you must be frustrated
Recently you must be very angry
It's not because it's hot
Did you go there?
Where?
I heard that you were there
The golf bar
I've been there.
You've been there again?
I play golf.
Miyasako said that golf bars are fun but she doesn't go.
So I went.
It's a bar but it's golf.
There's a screen and it's like a ball is being hit.
It's like a girl is playing golf.
There are some rooms like that.
I was left behind.
And then he said,
Here you go!
That's too high!
And then the caddy came
And he said,
How many shots do you want to shoot?
Yes, yes
And he shot
Well, 250 feet
Yard
He's pretty good, isn't he?
I said,
I can do it
And then he said,
Are you ready for the real show?
And I said,
Yes, let's go
And he shot
Then, he goes down again.
He's like, do your best!
The caddy is also cheering for him.
He's like, one more time?
Then, he goes down again.
Nine shots!
You're not good!
You'll never come back like this!
I can't even go through this whole thing!
I went home in 10 minutes.
You know, I'm so sweaty...
I couldn't hit it, so I got angry.
What are you saying? I hit it!
Even if I hit it once, it didn't react.
The machine didn't react.
It shouldn't react!
I mean, obviously, the object is flying.
It's flying so fast.
I'm sorry, I wanted to react.
Please say it again.
If I say, BANG, it will roll.
Will it react?
I don't know.
It's like, BANG!
I don't know why you're so excited about the golf cart.
It's not a shop that can be so excited.
I was thinking about going to bed.
I opened the fridge and saw a lot of bottles.
I was curious about what was inside.
Then, I heard a sound!
It was a sound of a no-shiku type somen noodle.
In the middle of the night, in the kitchen,
I can't find a single piece of somen that's a type of a farm.
I can't move.
I'm not saying that, but I can't eat somen at home.
That's right, I can't eat it at home.
What will everyone do?
What?
I can't even clean the house.
I see.
There are many parts of the body that are flying around.
If you move, it will stick to your legs.
Anyway, I don't know what to do.
I see.
I want to sleep. I really want to sleep.
But I'm a type of brain-dead person.
Oh, okay.
I'm going to go back slowly.
I'm going to do this with a
really sticky shadow.
Why is that?
I can't stand it.
And it takes about 2 hours to clean it.
Even though I clean it, it's completely finished.
When I look at it like this, it's completely shiny.
And it smells like soy sauce.
And I wonder how I should eat this somen.
That's...
I have a sweat.
I don't know why.
I don't know why, but I guess it can't be helped.
I also made a trickle-wiper.
Yes, yes.
Something like this.
Like this.
I feel like I can't pull my fingers out at once.
I see.
It hurts.
I made that and made a trickle.
It's over in one go.
It's sticky.
It hurts.
You should study more.
No matter how many times I do it, it's not enough.
It's so sticky.
It's sticky.
Why is that?
It's because of the brain.
Today, we have a special project.
That's right.
For now, Saki, please.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm shooting a summer video.
I'm in Okinawa.
I don't think you know, but my junior is a rice ball.
Hatsumi.
I don't think you know.
This time, Yamagaki, Miyasako and my junior who is in love with Miyasako are rice balls.
It's about 2 meters long.
Seriously.
I said, you're sweating a lot!
He said, this is not sweat. It's rice's Tokijiru.
No one will laugh.
I took this to the bodyguard.
He was originally a volleyball player.
He wore glasses and brought a suit.
I brought it here, or rather I brought it here on my own.
And then, all the way through Okinawa, I was doing radio like this.
Why?
I was doing earphones like this, saying, no, no, no, no, no, no.
If someone came, I'd say, I'll drink it!
This guy, his spitting sound is amazing.
Spitting isn't like that.
It's not like that?
You can't say spitting.
I see.
He's screaming!
It's so funny!
Well, that's how it is.
Yes, yes, yes.
Last time, right?
You don't know, do you?
No, I don't know at all.
We don't know either.
We've never seen it either.
I also came to Okinawa for the first time.
You don't know, do you?
I came to Okinawa for the first time.
Then I'm fine with it.
What kind of answer is that?
Wait a minute. It's like I'm introducing the rice balls.
It's like a rice ball.
This is the secret of the boss.
I'm not going to let you go!
I'm going to hit you on the knee!
I'm going to show you my secret.
Here's the rice ball.
Oh, amazing!
It's stretched!
I can't handle it anymore.
Sorry.
What is this?
Stop it!
I'm the one who will be in charge of Yoshimoto Kouki's special effects.
Why?
What are you talking about?
Mantaikonbi New Romance Onigiri
Honestly, in the 5th year, the stage was quite big.
It was a bit scary.
You're sweating a lot.
This is not sweat.
It's the bone broth.
You're sweating so much.
It's slowly soaking in.
I see, I see.
You ask the body?
I ask the body.
I see.
He can weigh everything with rice.
Oh, really?
That's right.
Ask about his height.
How tall is he?
193 cms.
That's not it.
No, no, no.
I don't need to say it.
Well, well, well.
I can weigh rice with rice only.
That's all.
I understand.
Then, how big is his foot?
...27.5 hectares!
That's slowly changing.
The number is gradually opening up out of the vat.
Even theasserts increase.
It's beginning topast!
The number of products are growing so rapidly.
This guy...
into the goes!!!
Isn't that enough?
This guy had an intense dizziness.
The five of us went to the same room,
He slept outside for the first first two days.
It's too noisy.
The sound is really amazing.
We'll show you all that today.
How much...
You too...
You too, you can't do that.
I want to hug you.
After this, we'll show you a shocking sound effect.
The world's biggest comedian, Onigiri
Is there such a thing as a breath of air in the world?
To find out the truth, let's get closer to the comedian Onigiri
He's really big
Onigiri
Onigiri was born in 1977 in Hokkaido.
He was born in 1977, and he was raised by his father who was 185 cm tall and his mother who was 175 cm tall.
Onigiri grew up and became taller and taller since he was a child.
When he graduated from middle school, he was 188 cm tall.
And he made use of his height to work hard.
I wanted to be a player like Nakagawajitsu.
Yes, volleyball.
He dreamed of becoming a pro player and dedicated his youth to playing onigiri.
After graduating high school, he joined Meimon Shin-Ittetsu Kimitsu.
He started to spend his days doing volleyball.
The sun was setting and his dream came true.
He was able to stand side by side with Nakagaiichi.
But why did he stop playing volleyball and start to be a comedian?
There was a time when Mr. Nakaguchi's salary was dropped.
He was dropped at the gym.
That's what I thought.
That's not good.
It wasn't that good.
You're not good at all.
I'm sorry.
The rumour that the onigiri that became a comedian is amazing has emerged.
So this time, to observe the sleeping state of Onigiri,
we installed a camera at home and waited for Onigiri to come back.
Amazing.
Why is there such a big city?
Oh, I'm in the back room. I'm sorry, but I'm going to sleep now. Good night.
Good night.
It's past 1 o'clock in the evening.
Onigiri who ends the day as usual and goes to sleep quietly.
What kind of change will happen from here?
That's right.
I've seen it in my sleep.
Yes, it's a long listen.
Hmm.
Well, I guess all of the back自己
when you feed your след also have this kind
Hmm...
I'll show you a video.
Oh...
What is this?
It's not a sound.
This is good.
It's a barotel.
It's so scary.
What is this?
It's so annoying!
As he continued to scream, he found out that there was a law in the sound of the rice ball.
You're screaming!
It's not breathing.
It's so annoying.
I don't know why my earplugs are all wood.
The earplugs are making me angry.
It's breathing here.
I see.
It's breathing again.
What kind of comment is that?
I want to go
What?
I'm sorry
You can tell by this?
What is this?
When you measure the volume
It's huge
The sound of a
The maximum sound is 94 decibels
This is equivalent to the sound of an iron bar under the guard.
It's so weak.
How many hours have you been doing this?
Grandpa, grandpa, good morning.
Good morning.
I'll take this off.
Yes.
Can I sleep on the floor?
What?
Wow, amazing!
This is amazing!
This is really amazing!
Amazing!
I don't have any more water.
I'm screaming.
I've never seen this before.
This is a secret.
Ahhhh!
I can't believe it.
And my body was like this.
Ah, that was gross.
What was that?
I was like, wow!
It's not fun to travel with this guy.
I had fun.
At that time, did you dream?
No, I didn't feel refreshed.
You didn't feel sleepy?
No, not really.
You're the type that sleeps without being tired.
Yes, yes.
You're tired when you wake up, right?
No, I feel refreshed.
Ah, you feel refreshed.
If you're with your girlfriend, you won't be scared.
I agree.
What's with that experience?
I'm looking for a girlfriend!
You're not going to say it?
I'll say it, but I'm really weak at pretending.
I want to ask the expert about the sound.
You should ask him.
The sound of a rice ball like a scream of a beast.
Will the expert answer?
The expert is always the worst.
I've never seen a video that looks like this.
It's scary.
As long as you watch the video, you can recognize the time.
THexac rating書証
We need to win more decision
Ext jam 5
It's ordinary for this to be magic
It is also a risk factor for the brain, nervous system, nervous system, and brain function.
Therefore, it is necessary to get the medical equipment as soon as possible to clarify the cause and to take measures.
This is scary.
What are you doing?
I'm not lying!
But what you said was true, right?
It was true!
This is the end.
Let's watch it again.
This is a valuable VTR.
It's more precious than the eel's roe.
It's still barely here.
It's already started.
Oh, it's like a dog fart.
I can't remember the last one.
This is a good one.
This is disgusting. I hate this.
I don't know this one.
Wow!
What?
Did you turn on the engine?
21 in the
yeah yeah yeah
om Get
that
What the hell?
He's definitely saying it right.
He's saying something.
He's going like this.
Uuuuuuugh!
What's wrong with you?
To be honest, I'm sorry for bothering you with rice.
It's normal!
Don't cry!
I'm not crying!
What is it?
I just saw rice in your eye!
You're the one who's crying!
I don't know why, but I got hurt too.
I don't know why, but...
After this, we'll have grilled rice balls.
Can I ask you about the technique of making rice balls?
Technique?
Since it was volleyball, the speed of the back burn was half.
That's right.
The attack.
Can I ask you about it?
Ah, sorry, then I'll...
...
Sorry.
You're crazy. You're absolutely crazy.
I'll never do that!
Yamashita-san, please wait a moment.
Sorry.
Angel Akira, go!
Angel... who's Angel Akira?
Who's Angel Akira?
Angel Akira.
Hey, you can't do that!
I'm not going to do it again.
Wait, wait.
Just say it out loud.
You're the one who's going to get in trouble.
No, I'm not.
Do it with a chair.
With a chair.
How far?
Here.
This is bad.
You're going to get kicked off the high place.
Are you going to sit?
What?
Let's start
You're so annoying
You're touching the dust
It's cute.