Tonight, that popular show is back for the first time in 6 months!
The gorgeous guests keep appearing! The mouth-bucket festival, begins!
Night's mouth-bucket hit studio!
Good evening everyone!
We have returned to our fans' love calls.
We will be the MCs this time as well.
Thank you!
This time too, we have invited a special guest from actors to comedians.
A famous rehearsal was conducted before the recording.
Among them, the most serious man is...
Let me see it.
When is it coming?
Check it thoroughly until the end of the cut.
This is important.
I'm wearing it here.
Mouth-to-mouth battle.
Who will win the crown?
Let's start with the first mouth-to-mouth singer.
The queen of the Enka Kayo Kai is here like a lion.
Misora Hibari's love 33
문득子 열면
Ah...
Love
With lots of руки,
And skinmans,
Come together without desire.
Some people are cute.
Thank you very much.
I'm already feeling the urge to sing.
It was a very emotional song.
It's the same as always.
Hibari-san, you received the National Nutrition Award in 1989.
What kind of products did you receive from the government?
Ask Kazuya.
Oh, thank you.
Kazuya-san, you raised Hibari-san as a woman.
What was the hardest thing about raising her?
Ask Kazuya.
Ask Kazuya-chan.
Kaguya!
He's not at the studio right now
Thank you very much
Let's move on to the next mouth-to-mouth singer
With a bright smile like the sun, the Harajuku gyaru is also here
Everyone, let's dance together
Mr. Yosuke Tagawa's Rui Rui
Rui Rui
Why are you saying Rui Rui now?
He dances a lot
I'm hungry.
He's dancing a lot.
I'm getting angry.
I don't know if I'm in love or not
I'm really scared
I'm going to get lost
How long will I see this lonely dream?
I'll rub your cheeks
I want you to understand that this is the end
Come on, let's dance under the sun
Come on, let's do the Lui Lui dance
Take seven steps
This is his song
It's a song
Today is bye bye
Look, I met you who is so cute
I'm in a good mood, Louis Louis
Louis Louis
Wonderful
Thank you very much
Mr.Tada, please
This time, you sang Louis Louis
What is the meaning of this word?
Rui Rui means...
Thank you
It's a word from the other side of Japan
Brazil?
It's not from Brazil, it's a word from the neighboring country
It means thank you
Is it a slang?
It's a scary word
It's not a slang, it's a slum
Slum is scary
Slum is not scary
Thank you very much
Thank you very much. Please take a seat.
Thank you very much.
Now, let's move on to the next singer.
A Yankee from Fujisawa who doesn't even cry,
takes a metal bat and hits the rock world with it.
Mr. Shima Daisuke, the man's award.
and I could not deliver the song.
Seriously, what is a boring song,
a boring song he?
and I born as a rich boy
How I have USching and-
I was living believing that
I heard somehehe
Forget the tears of the past.
Very
life
Even when I felt like I was being carried away by the weight of time
I held on to my blue fist
When I was a child, I was a five-year-old
I was shining in the night sky
Don't forget the feelings you felt when you saw the shooting stars
Even if pulling is the only thing a man can do,
I believe in this heart and keep on living
The Ventriloquism of every word
Even the bloody and
Thank you.
Here you are.
Thank you very much
Since I was young, since I was in my teens
What's up, you idiot?
It was pretty bad, I was really angry
It's fine to say it with your tongue, but what kind of bad things did you do?
That's right, I was really angry at the make-up room
What?
I was angry at the mirror
The Rikishi's...
Of course, there's that anger
There's anger in your heart
This girl is bad
What the hell are you doing?
I'm Hikari Osaru.
I'm not doing anything. I'm just standing still.
Hikari is just standing still.
Let's finish this quickly.
You want to finish this?
I want to finish everyone.
Thank you very much, Mr. Shimada.
It's a little scary.
Let's move on to the next mouth-to-mouth news.
In 1973, a student band formed in Asahikawa, Hokkaido, became big and sang a suspiciously fleeting adult love song.
In a safe place, the heart of Wine Red.
It's like a movie.
Ah, is that so?
Really?
What is this?
That's good.
What are you doing?
If you gently hold on to the memories that seem to be forgotten
Rather than forgetting them
It's good
I want to love you more than I do now
It's good, it's good, it's good
How dare you find out his face niin
The scene of the
I'm afraid I'll be out of the picture.
Thank you very much.
You look like Shinji Hanimura.
I don't know who you are.
I'm doing it in the Tamaki.
Was your body so wide?
No, it's with curry.
I'm going up and up.
It was a bad mass.
Is he a magician?
He's not a magician.
What kind of care do you give to keep your voice?
I give a massage with cola.
Massage with cola?
That's pretty stimulating.
He's a bit of a
Of course, we didn't accept it at all.
We confirmed it, so we know.
We confirmed it, so we saw it.
After this, more and more expensive guests appeared.
Now, let's move on to the next mouth-to-mouth singer.
The appearance of the king of rock, who became the stronghold of rock believers all over the country.
R.C. Succession's Night in the Afternoon
Who is this?
The one who is in charge of the current situation
Tsuda-san
The rain of blood has done it
The engine has gone crazy
The fuel tank has been crushed
What's wrong? Hey hey baby
The battery is running out
It's not good to be too clean.
It's better to be more clean.
He's not moving at all.
I can't get on you on a night like this
I can't let you go on a night like this
There's no one to call, right?
The best!
I'm doing it at a store.
Thank you very much!
It was very impressive.
Thank you very much.
I was able to see a wonderful performance.
I heard that Tomokazu Miura was a high school classmate.
Yes, yes, yes.
I heard that.
That's right.
Since then, I've been...
I'm not sure if I should say this.
I used to go home with him on my bike.
It was 100 points.
The song is still that, but the deep part of the talk is...
You can still go on.
Really?
There is a favorite food.
What do you usually eat?
It's Koya tofu.
Koya tofu?
No.
A little...
You think too much.
Suddenly Koya tofu.
Do you often watch TV?
I watch it a lot!
Is there a show you like?
From the world's president!
Ah, no.
There's no such thing as wrong.
What's wrong?
Thank you very much!
Congratulations on your new seat!
Why are you crying?
Next, let's hear the next one.
The main character of the national film has appeared.
He sings along with the famous lines that everyone knows.
Kiyoshi Atsumi's, The Man is Sorrowful.
I was born and raised in Shibamata, Katsushika.
My dear brother, I want to be a great brother who will make you happy someday
Without the meaning of struggle and effort
Today, the day of tears
The sun of the sun is falling
I want to ask you about director Yohji Yamada. What kind of person is he usually?
I like occult, so I told him about aliens.
Oh, really?
I always say that I made the mystery circle.
I blew it up.
You blew up Yamada Yoshi?
You guys are all rough.
Oh, I see.
Do you two from downtown and Matsumoto-san have a co-star?
Do we?
Long time ago, we only met once.
What program did you appear on?
In a local program in Kanagawa,
I was riding a bike
and I was on a show called Tofu shop
I got lost in the middle of the show
Then, the staff didn't come at all
So I went home
I didn't want them to apologize
But I thought I would have to do something called a ritual
A ritual?
Not a ritual
It's a ritual, you idiot!
It's a ritual, right?
Am I allowed to do it?
Ah, it's gone.
No, that one was...
What is this?
Is this the end?
After this, that hit song will be a hit!
Now, let's move on to the next song.
A miracle middle-aged man who became the Japanese singer with millions of hits in a row.
Utada Hikaru's Traveling.
Oh, was it hit in?
Oh, doggo dog.
He must becemos to the point of Danny's
Oh doggy...
I'm getting a voice in my head
I'm going to accept you
I'm going to stop
I don't want to be true
I'm trapped in the wind
I'm climbing up the moon
My moon is next to you
Suddenly, I'm back to myself
The star of my dreams
Traveling, I'll take you
Traveling, to the place where the whole world gathers
Traveling, from here to there
I'll take you
Tatara Tatara Tatara Tatara Tatara Tatara Tatara
Uo-oh
Thank you very much
Please come this way
It's very big
It's this big?
It's big, it's big
It's big
There was a story about a man in Italy who got divorced
Can I ask the truth about this?
He lost his kiss.
Really?
Is it important?
I used to have a kiss.
I don't know what to say.
I lost my kiss.
He can't hear.
Where do you meet an Italian man?
There is a drinking party in Italy.
In Italy?
Yes, there is.
Those who are really experts are gathered.
I don't like these experts.
It happens regularly.
It's a happening party.
It's not a happening party.
It's a drinking party.
I don't know.
Zen is not in it.
It's a little embarrassing.
Stop it!
It's a story from before!
I don't want to say it anymore.
I want to say it.
I'm really going to get the car ready.
The amount of sweat is really...
Is that so?
It's like a trap inside.
Really!
After that, that popular comedian will be
I don't want to say it anymore. I want to go home.
I'm already in the car.
The amount of sweat is really...
Is that so?
It's like a trap inside.
After that, that popular comedian will be forever silent.
Let's move on to the next silent scene.
Sometimes actress, sometimes singer.
The miracle of Taiwan given by heaven is coming tonight.
It's being shown by Judy Long.
It's ugly!
MUT mobile isn't the main end is it?
A TV program, you started as a TV director now?
Still don't understand Japanese?
It's an old lady!
There's an old lady like this!
An old lady doing a speech!
It's an old lady!
There's an old lady like this!
She's a woman who lived in a park.
I'll be waiting for you
Please come back to me
The wind is blowing from the sky
We are here
Oh, it's a smile
Smile
Smile, smile
The last part of the song is the most important part.
It's very elegant.
It's cool.
The last part.
It's ugly.
It's dirty.
Thank you very much.
It's wonderful.
I heard that you had a good relationship with Yujiro Ichihara.
What kind of person is Yujiro?
Yujiro is fast to move.
Fast to move?
Yes.
He is impatient.
He is like, let's go to the next one.
Yes, yes.
Why is it one-sided?
Recently, he hasn't been talking, so I forgot a little.
Ah!
He hasn't been talking much recently.
Yes, yes.
This is strange.
What do you think?
He is a bit ugly.
Isn't it ugly?
Shimo-san and the others are saying that he is ugly.
Isn't it normal?
I don't know.
I think it's normal.
It's like a normal meal.
The second half of the G-Series mouth-to-mouth battle!
Really?
Mouth-to-mouth monsters are appearing one after another!
The winner is...
Dragon...
So amazing, Romultan!