That man comes to the studio before the recording.
Good morning.
Hello.
What's up?
Well...
I bought the format of the program the other day.
Thank you.
This?
It's popular abroad too.
But I heard that you don't really understand it.
No, it's not like that.
Really?
The number of African TV stations is huge.
There are about 12.
Then...
If it's 12, it's not that big.
Last year in July,
When the ratings are high, they will be challenged to a quiz that Itao has proposed.
But the content of the quiz is something that the common people cannot understand.
And this time, what is the purpose of Itao's visit?
It's like a business trip.
I don't think so.
It's a little before the actual performance.
I know. I thought of a new format this time as well.
If you'd like, you can buy it.
Then, please leave it to someone.
No, no.
Please look at it.
There are songs, but I think it'll be more real if we actually play them.
I was wondering about other songs, but I thought it'd be nice to have Nittere-san grow up and Nittere-san grow up to this point.
I thought I could do it, so I came here in the rain.
What should I do?
What are you talking about?
Let's go.
Really?
Yes.
It's a waste of time to talk about this.
Let's go.
I'll be waiting downstairs.
Please.
What are you talking about?
I can't say anything.
He's talking nonsense.
Tonight, gather in the holy hall and get the title of the true hero, using your own intelligence, strength and courage.
Come on, heroes!
The first battle of the first series
Heroes, are you ready?
From now on, you will face many difficulties
But, after you overcome them, you will get Heaven
When you get 1000 Heavens
1000 Heavens?
The title of the true hero
You will get a pendant and a prize of 1 million yen.
Do your best.
What should I do?
I do it every time.
Just listen to me.
Let's go to the first stage.
Heaven's Road.
The Heavens Road is prepared here.
This road is very narrow and unstable.
You have to cross this road within a minute.
Please get the Itzy Stone in the treasure chest.
It's a good thing to see.
On the way, the violent gladiator will cover your path.
If you succeed, you will get 200 Heavens.
Now, the hero, Hamada!
Let's start the game!
You have one minute to limit your time.
Within that time, you can try again and again.
Ah, I see.
Heaven's Road, 3 o'clock!
Start!
I think I can get 200 points.
Scary!
Scary, scary.
This is impossible!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Time is running out.
Be brave.
You are not doing it.
It's too fast.
It's too much.
Go, go, go.
Wow!
Mr. Endo, you have obtained 200 Heavens by hunting for treasure.
What is this?
It looks cooler when you take it out.
Right?
Mr. Endo, you have obtained 200 Heavens.
Wow!
You are so surprised.
You are falling.
Heaven is so surprised.
200 is a bit too much.
Everyone's.
Everyone's Heaven?
Yes, everyone's Heaven.
Please do your best to reach 1000 Heavens.
There's 200.
There's no more 200.
There's a key, but it's open.
Now, let's move on to the next stage.
This is Heaven's Balloon.
As you can see, the Yomegraduator is now fully charged and is sleeping.
If you can break these three balloons without causing the Yomegraduator to wake up, you will get two Heavens.
Now, who will be the hero?
I don't want to do this.
Hero, Ideo Yamazaki!
He's sleeping.
He ate a lot of ramen.
He ate 3 times.
Now, Heaven's Balloon, It's the start!
Start!
While he's sleeping.
While he's sleeping?
Don't wake him up.
It's a dead end.
Oh no!
His wife...
He's sleeping again.
Oh no, he's sleeping again.
He looks really tired.
It's okay.
If he says he won't wake up now...
This is okay.
He's done with the second one.
Oh, is this one awake?
Oh, it's gone to sleep again.
This is the first time I've seen this.
It's the first time.
It's okay, it's okay.
There's only one balloon left.
If the wife doesn't wake up after this, it's clear.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Oh, no.
Oh, did you wake up?
Oh, what a shame!
YomeGraduator, wake up!
Heavens Over!
What a shame!
What's wrong with you?
That was a close call, but unfortunately,
he woke up with the second balloon.
Yamazaki-san, Heavens over!
Oops!
YomeGrad's battery is dead.
Everyone, do you want to charge your batteries?
Or not?
Are you asking us?
Can we decide?
But we're enemies, so it's better not to die.
Then you can't get the 1000 Heavens either.
Do you want to charge?
Then I'll charge it!
Okay, please take a look at the time limit while the wife is charging.
Start charging!
Tomato?
Tomato, right?
That's the amount of charge.
Oh, I see.
The charging has started.
What the hell is this?
It's almost full.
Why didn't it come out at first?
I didn't get any.
You got a similar one yesterday.
I'm not satisfied yet.
Oh, you're satisfied?
Now, the charging is complete.
Then, I'll take 20 Heben for charging.
Are you going to take it?
It has nothing to do with charging.
Yes.
Why are we charging for a seat?
Hey.
Did you take too much?
I took too much.
There are more than 20.
What are you doing?
You are overdoing it.
The charging is completed.
The next stage, the third stage is Heaven's Pant.
What is it?
You are taking it off.
Now, this stage is...
You will be wearing the panties of the hero of the YomeGraduator.
You will pull the panties from yourself.
If the panties come off at the same time as the YomeGraduator,
you will get 200 Heaven.
The panties you will get are here.
Now, then...
This raw panties,
for the rental fee, you will get 50 Heaven.
I'm going to get it?
You're going to get that too?
50?
Count properly, 50.
You don't look nervous.
Shut up!
You took too much.
I did.
There's nothing left.
You're too much.
50, go.
The game is over.
Now it's the wife's choice.
If this sound is played, it will be the wife's choice.
The challenger will be the wife's gladiator.
Now, the wife, go to selection.
I haven't done it yet.
Who will be chosen?
It's a selection.
Sees!
No!
Why?
The final decision is made.
No way!
It's a perfect match.
It's a perfect match for Yome.
I don't like it.
I don't like it!
What?
With Yome?
You both wear the pants.
If you can take it off at the same time as your wife, you'll get Heaven.
What do you mean, same time?
I don't know when my wife takes it off.
Oh, I see.
You've been waiting for this, haven't you?
Of course.
Please set up your underwear.
Set up your underwear.
What's that?
This is scary.
Hama-san didn't lose.
It's tight.
It's torn.
It's no good.
I can't show it.
Let me show it.
It's a mess.
This is no good.
No matter what, I can't do this.
Let's go!
The last one!
One more!
Please look at this carefully!
Yome!
If Yome can do the Panto at the same time as me...
This is a joke!
Heaven is over!
No, no, no!
The one in the middle is out!
It's out!
I don't know when I'll do this!
Even if I get hit suddenly!
No pants matching! Heaven is over!
What is this?
It's a shame.
Heaven!
Thank you very much.
This is a bit of a shame.
This is a big deal.
Please return to your seat.
Oh, this sound is...
The previous winner of the ITSUJI KOROSIYAM, Yamazaki-san,
defeated the previous graduate,
and he has come to the stadium to revenge Yamazaki-san.
What?
Yamazaki-san, it's dangerous.
It's scary.
Yamazaki-san.
if you cover this sheepskin you will not be able to see your face from the Gladiator
that's not good
you should be covered
it's dangerous
he's getting closer
cover him
quickly
if you cover him you won't be able to see your face from the Gladiator
Yamazaki
he's looking for him
I can't see it now.
You're so scary.
Is he writing?
No, no.
I can't see it but I can smell it.
You're so scary.
I can't see it.
I didn't notice it.
That's amazing.
He left without noticing Yamazaki-san.
Yamazaki-san, I'm glad you didn't die.
Now, I'll take the rent of the Itzy Mantle.
I'll take it for 10 times.
What is this? It's really a lot.
Count it.
10 times.
It's 10 times.
It's like this.
It's a lot.
That's all you got?
Now that the training is over, let's move on to the next stage.
The final stage.
Yome-san has crossed the line!
Now, in this stage, Yome-Gladiator will dance to the music.
While the music is playing, you will dance along with it.
And, in order to not be noticed by Yome-Gladiator,
you will have to take the Itzy Stone next to you.
Currently, everyone is just about 10 Heavens.
However, I am not a demon.
If you challenge the 10 Heavens all together,
if you succeed, you will be recognized as a true hero.
Will you challenge the Heavens all together and overcome the Heavens?
I don't understand the meaning.
I want to do it.
I will challenge it.
Will you be okay with the Heavens?
Yes, I can.
We've got a head-on.
Now, everyone,
Yome-san's It's G Start!
Now, everyone, please dance.
Please stand up while you're standing.
Please refer to Yome's dance.
Please take a look at the dance of the bride.
Now, the song has stopped.
Did you see it?
Everyone is watching.
Yes.
Tanaka san, go to hell!
Out!
Out?
I don't understand.
I don't understand at all.
I think Tanaka san wasn't moving at all.
Let's play the second song.
We have to dance the same song.
Start!
But I don't understand.
I can't do it with my hands.
Please dance as much as you can.
When you turn around, it means that you are going to hell.
The song has stopped.
Oh, he's faking it!
That's not fair!
Oh, there's a whistle here. What could it be?
Oh, it looks like Yamazaki-san got a red card.
It seems that the aggressive side was not enough.
He is out.
He lacked the positivity.
He was drunk.
Moreover, when will he get his will back?
He will not move forward.
When will he get his will back?
He has been with his wife all the time.
He is always moving sideways.
Yamazaki-san, you can't participate in the next game.
The next song, start!
I can do it.
You can do it.
I can do it!
You can do it!
This is...
Oh, too hell no!
What the hell is this?
I didn't move!
Which one of you moved?
I'm out!
If you had taken the stone just now, would it have been okay?
That's right!
I don't know!
If you had taken it...
The stone slipped!
What's wrong?
Hey, shut up!
How many times have I told you to do it before?
Let's go. Let's start the next song.
I'm not going to do it.
If you don't do it, you'll get fired.
Oh no!
Yes.
Mr.Takoyama, 5th place.
Thank you.
It was close.
The hero, Mr.Matsumoto, is left alone.
I'm left alone.
It's hard.
No, no, no, let's do our best.
Let's take it.
Let's go.
The next song, start.
It's good.
If you look at it from here, it's stupid.
It's good. It's good.
It's really cold.
It's cold. It's cold.
What is this?
I don't care! I lost!
It's long!
The song has stopped.
It's...
...Dest.
Everyone has become go-to-hells.
What?
And so, the winner is...
The end of its G!
What's going on?
It's already been decided!
The winning number is...
Zero Heaven!
Unfortunately, it didn't reach 1000 Heaven.
And so, the winner is...
Yome Graduator!
Congratulations!
Yomegura Theater
The award goes to the Yomegura Theater for the award of 1 million yen and the Itsuji pendant.
Congratulations.
You threw it away.
So, Yome and Hitamu's Nekomaru Itsuji Colosseum.
See you next week.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's a mess.
Thank you very much.
Is that the end of the game?
What did you think about this game?
It's a game that you can get numbers.
I didn't understand the reason until the end.
I didn't understand until the end.
But it was very exciting.
I don't think I can win.
I think that if you watch it and think about the strategy, you will be able to win.
Is that so?
Of course it is.
But the TV show people don't know about it.
They don't know how to watch it.
I didn't have that idea.
That's the most important thing.
Yamasaki vs. Moriman is finally decided!
The man who was stood on the cliff is the eternal rival, Shukuseki Moriman!
Don't miss the shocking battle!
I brought the next man to the other side.