The Grand Prix for the Claw Swing!
This is a Grand Prix to see how the challenger can do the Claw Swing of a man who knows nothing about it!
But if you think that the video of a man doing the Claw Swing of a man is not worth watching,
If the judge, Downtown, presses the button on his hand, the video will disappear and only the sound will be played.
The person who can do the Chikubi-sui that can be seen on TV without the video being deleted will be the winner
The first challenger is Kokoriko Endo
The target is the senpai that Endo is afraid of, Kimura Yuichi
I was always busy when I was a kid
I was busy with my work and my career
I was doing it to make my child cry
Endo is starting from the story of Kimura raising his breasts to make his child cry
You have to go like this
Everyone please look here
You are amazing
You are the best
Why?
You are amazing
You have already crossed the pass
You make a sweet noise
Next is Kokoriko Tanaka
The target is a fighter, Bobby Oragon
Bobby, you want to fight?
Yes
Do you still want to fight?
You're strong
No, you're amazing
Tanaka wants Bobby to show his muscles
He challenges him to a neck-water
I'll do it with my neck
You're not going to do it?
You can do anything
Bobby, you can do it
You can do it
If you don't talk, I'll lick you.
I don't want to.
Bony.
Bony, Chikuya.
If you don't talk, I'll lick you.
What are you talking about?
I don't know if you can see it, but there are people who can lick you.
But I don't think you can see it.
I can't see anything!
You can't see anything!
Bobby is scared of it
After this, Tanaka tries to suck his nipples
The most important part is the speed
Bobby is so annoyed that he failed to do the neck-swing
The third one is the first one to use the hug, Miki Kosei
The target is the senior who is scared of Kosei, Shidori Daigo
I live in Tokyo, in a hotel for 3 days.
Living in a hotel is really hard.
He is stressed out by his work in Tokyo.
He wants Daigo to suck his nipples.
I can rely on you.
Why do you want me to be your nipple brother?
I'm not sure if you understand.
He says it's painful, but it's really hard to come to Tokyo.
You understand, right?
I've never heard of the walls of Tokyo.
For now, he wants to show his nipples.
Next to the 5th.
Don't touch it.
I'll never touch it.
So don't touch it.
Just don't look.
I know.
Wow!
Stop it!
Sorry, I said it out of the blue.
I'll do it in one go.
One go.
His cheeks are going to pop.
I won't forget.
I'm sorry.
One night.
I'm sorry, I'll do it.
What is this?
1 is long.
Can I challenge once?
Can I?
I count.
Thank you.
1,2,3,4,5
It's like this.
Please look at this.
I want you to see this.
I worked hard here.
I want you to see it
He's really good
He really did his best
He showed his long neck
And tonight, Hosei will challenge that veteran entertainer
The next challenger is Ho-Sei.
Ho-Sei's target is this person.
This is Wakamishouji.
What do you think?
It's a little difficult.
It's difficult. He's 10 years older than me.
He's a veteran.
I think it's difficult to suck the nipples of a veteran.
That's the difficulty.
Let's start the Nipple Sucking Show.
Hosei Hisei, let's go.
Hello.
Good morning.
What?
He's here.
What's wrong with you?
I can't stand this kind of talk.
No, no, no.
Talking is...
It's not normal.
I'm...
What's with your face?
I'm gonna end this!
Please watch!
It's okay already!
Let's watch!
Watch?
Let's watch! Please watch!
Please watch!
It's already over?
It's pretty fast.
I'm a bit nervous.
Me too.
Me too?
I'm sorry.
You're so annoying.
Can I sit with you?
Please.
I'm sorry.
You're not my mother!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Actually, I have to sit a lot this time.
What?
On the show.
Sit on what?
I'll sit on various things.
I think it's better to sit on this.
Well, can I sit down for a moment?
Now?
Yes.
May I?
No, I'm really sorry.
Wait a minute, Mr. Shun.
What is it?
Please sit down.
Let's take off your clothes.
It's starting now.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
Please take off your mask.
You are an idiot.
What is this?
You are a fool.
Wait a minute, Mr. Choy.
Wait a minute.
Why are you asking me?
So, how many seconds do you want me to ask?
How many seconds?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Please explain it to me.
I'll ask you.
What the hell is that?
He's sitting down.
You two are...
...the same age?
Please do it properly with my 926.
I got it.
It's so hard.
It's not a joke.
It's so fun.
It's so fun!
It looks so fun!
It's like they're playing together!
I don't know anymore!
Wait a minute.
Please give me a moment.
Don't hit me!
He's a real man!
Hey, don't do that!
Stop it!
Okay.
It looked like he was having a lot of fun.
It was fun in the end, though.
How long did it take you to suck it?
It took about two seconds.
He didn't let me suck it that much.
But Shoji-san did.
I think Endo is the one who breathes the most.
Well, it's a high-level breath.
I breathed for about 30 seconds.
There were various forms of chikubisui.
The four teams are over.
How about the judges, Dan-dan?
That's right.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Please announce the winner of the water king of the nipples!
No one else!
Wait a minute!
I can't say that he's the king of the nipples.
Really?
I don't want to call him the king of the nipples.
I'm just doing it for fun.
I need to change my target.
Like a more actor.
Like Umezawa-san.
No way!
I came to Tokyo just to get my nipples done.
Just to get your nipples done?
I went back to Osaka just like that.
Wait, wait.
I think there's still the second episode.
At that time,
I'll be wearing this mask.
I'll be wearing a mask that only the people who can sit on.
Like, Sina Kippei.
That's a bit scary.
It's really scary.
It's okay to go to the other side, right?
If you don't go to the other side, it's a bit...
When you do the second time, think about the target a little more.
Raise the hurdle a little more.
I think you should raise the target.
I want you to do your best in the second time.
This was the Chikubi Watery Grand Prix. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry to say this, but I'm going to challenge you to see if you can do the Chikubi.
I'm really bad at Chikubi, so I'm waiting for you in the forest.
I'm so nervous!
Excuse me, Mr. Kibura.
Mr. Kibura said,
I'm not like that.
I thought,
how can you say that?
I'm really...
I don't think so.
Excuse me.
No, no, no.
I don't want you to do that.
I thought you would reject me.
But surprisingly, you were so easy.
Don't say that.
You were really not rejecting me.
You were so easy.
I thought you'd be proud if I sucked your nipples once.
Please read it.
I didn't expect you to suck my nipples.
I was planning to do it.
Thank you.
How was my nipple?
Your nipple?
Yes, it was cute.
Thank you very much.
Please leave a bad impression.
It was disgusting.
Why did you have to be so mean to me?
I'm back!
Yes, this atmosphere is coming out!
I'm not mistaken!
The next day
I'll do something about Aoyakia.
What?
Why do you hate it? I really don't want to do it.
You don't want to do it?
I really don't want to do it. But it can't be helped.
I have a question for you, Mr. Downtown.
The other day, Tomoyo Harada released his 35th anniversary album.
Don't you do anything about it?
I don't have anything to do with 35th anniversary.
Oh, it's his first anniversary.
Do you want to hold a dinner show?
What are you talking about?
Dinner show?
Do you want to do a dinner show?
I want to do the dinner show that I used to do in the old days.
I did it in a project.
What was that?
When we were singing, the staff were all dressed up and the rain was blowing.
We put on a hot thing.
It's violence.
The moon was funny.
That's why I said it's scary.
No, no.
The staff is sitting down.
It's a plan.
Why is it so hot?
You were doing it too.
Well, in the past, I was just doing it.
I dropped things.
This is the Downtown Dinner Show that was held 24 years ago.
The staff is enjoying the dinner show as the audience.
They are going to sing a variety of songs.
It's so fun.
I'm going to get a lot of complaints.
I don't think it's going to work now.
It's not going to work now. It's going to come soon.
Oh, really?
No, no.
There are a lot of people watching TV who are going to complain now.
The other day, I was on a different TV.
There was a story that made my wife angry.
Well, for example, when I get home,
Isn't there a time when your wife is on the phone?
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
There is, right?
And at that very moment...
...he said something.
Wait, wait......
You said, that's what I think.
What??
Did we call you passes easily?
Wait, wait...
My husband is on his way home.
He is already here.
Absolutely my first date with him.
My husband came from work,
I don't want to get close to him.
But I don' think you had a phone call.
No, no, no. What about you? What about you?
What?
You came back from work and your wife called you.
You have that kind of situation, right?
Well, yes.
My answer is,
I just came back from work,
so I'll ask her once and call her again later.
That's my answer.
I'll ask her,
and say,
Welcome back.
That's my answer.
You're so stubborn.
Don't you think so?
I'm so angry about that.
I can't think of anything.
It's like an old-fashioned way of thinking.
I'm sure it's true.
I'm calling because I have something to do.
You must be lying. You're amazing.
You're amazing at lying.
This is the house.
What?
No, it's a lie.
Let's talk about the town.
What?
I don't know what's so funny.
It's 4 o'clock.
But you're home.
Your husband is home.
But I told you after I came home.
This phone call is a long time.
Yes, it's a long time.
Then,
I'll tell you.
You look like you're angry.
I can't stand it if you make that face.
When I saw the picture, I was wondering what was going on.
But you said it was still being broadcasted.
It's so high.
When I said that it was still being broadcasted,
I was told that I was a very low-key person.
And this atmosphere.
Something like a bad guy.
And if this is broadcasted, I will be a bad guy again.
I don't think I can be a bad guy.
I think it's fine because there are many different ways of thinking.
You tell me too, the one who gets angry at his wife.
I'm the only one who does it.
You tell me too.
Sometimes when I go somewhere with my family,
like a car ride,
there are cars at home and mine,
but I don't use my car for that kind of thing.
I can't ride a car that well.
But there are cars for my family.
And then, well,
my family's car is usually my wife's car.
But when I go somewhere with my family, I get in this car.
Well, it's a good chance.
I'm driving at high speed, and gasoline isn't going in at all.
No, I'm going to get out of here.
Yes, you're angry, right?
I think you should get mad on the way.
No, no.
I know that I'm going somewhere with my family tomorrow.
But there are some cases where you can't get your wife in on that day.
You...
You have a bad taste in women.
No, no, no!
That's not true!
If you do that, I'll break your wife's jaw!
I'm sorry!
You're still in the drive recorder.
If you drink now, I'll have to buy it.
What an adult.
Say it.
There's nothing.
Don't lie.
Say something that makes your wife angry.
I'm the only one who's being told to say something.
You're being told to say something?
I'm the one who said it.
If it was that kind of theme, I would say, for example, there is such a thing.
Don't be fooled.
I didn't say it on my own.
Say something.
Say that I'm very hungry.
What are you talking about?
Do you have that?
I can't change the water of the water server at all.
When it's reduced, it becomes like this.
When it's more, it becomes like this.
I'm told to change it.
I don't have it anymore, so I change it.
So you're like, what is it?
Not for this!
Hold on, actually I'm somewhere in the editing studio
I'm cutting all of your parts
No way, I'm done
Only because of this that you get angry, right?
I'm not angry, but I'm waiting for him to completely change.
You'll change when you realize it?
I'll change, but...
Eh? You'll change?
I'll change, but no matter how I think, he's trying to completely stick to me.
When there's about one last cup left, it's like a chicken race.
It's spicy, but...
I can't drink until this guy drinks.
If I drink now, I have to go home.
What an adult.
You should go home quickly.
Don't say that.
No, I can go home.
If you say so.
There is such a thing.
Like a
It used to be.
Say that like you used to do.
Say the old days like you do now.
Say it like that.
Why are you talking so seriously?
Are you crazy?
You should talk like you do now.
You can say it like you did 10 years ago, but you should say it like you did last week.
That's what talking is all about.
What are you going to do if you get 35,000 points?