The 100m freestyle softball competition
No rest at all
The hidden opponent will be given a softball competition
The competition will be so intense that the opponent will be knocked out
The opponents are Takashi Sasano, Mr.Malik, and Riki Takatou
Fee-Fee All-Stars
Are you serious about this?
Of course!
I'm hungry
The youngster is attacking from the beginning of the game
I thought I would be heavier
He's aiming for 100 points and shooting and shooting
But, because of the veterans, unexpected happenings also happened.
You look tired.
Ko-san, what happened?
When I heard the steps, I was like, gukiii.
You're not burning up.
Currently, they have 12 points with 1 out of 2.
Will they be able to win with a score of 100?
What you say to a diving Titanic?
residue
but
Fifi All Star's every time touc outer space
the one on spot last clips
DJ Ko
Pe melon
It's been a long time since I've seen this.
That was good.
That was a great shot.
The pitcher's hand is getting better.
The pitcher wants to change the flow.
Inomoto is in the first and second place in the runner-up.
The next is Komomo.
What is that?
That was dangerous
Where is it?
It's a two outs
It's a three outs
He's trying to get the bat out with a three outs chance
I'm going to do it
Ready
Go
Okay
Nice
Sasano's error and the 14th point
Are you okay?
14 points!
86 points left!
The movement I imagined didn't follow my body
I was old and I was like a father in the sports world
I fell down
I couldn't dodge it. I might have tried to take it.
It was too early.
Oh, I see. I should have dodged it.
I couldn't dodge it. I couldn't dodge it.
It was a bit frustrating.
And Hamada's first hit of the ball...
I'll hit it.
And Hamada's ball is in front of him
Nice!
Let's go!
You can do it!
Nice!
Why did you sing?
Let's go!
Matsumoto
Matsumoto, please!
There's only one left!
Let's go!
Matsumoto continues
Thank you!
Hamada wins with the original timing
19 points are in
As expected, he can go up to 100 points with just one attack
That was a bang
OK, Komu-san
This is bad, really bad
It's out
It's out, yay
Change
What's this?
Matsumoto is out on the form and it's a 3 out change
The first attack is 19 points off
He's out of his mind and is on defense
But it's enough.
Yes, but we have to finish with the three of them.
Finish it.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Nice shot.
The back of the first floor.
The Gaki no Tsukai team is being protected.
The picture is being taken.
The ball is being thrown.
Fifi All Stars, the battle batter is Takashi Sasano.
It's okay, it's not Sasano.
Zero-one!
Hyakki-chan, do your best!
Good, B-chan, good!
I see, he can't wait.
I'll give you a warning!
1 point for Sasano!
Sasano's shot fly is a one-out.
The next batter is an Egyptian talent, Fifi.
People say I can do anything with my face.
I'm fast, right?
Egyptian people wearing baseball uniforms are very rare internationally.
I think Egyptians will be surprised.
It's the first time in thousands of years that Egyptians have worn baseball uniforms.
So when I wore it, I thought it would look good on me.
I've been thinking about how to show it.
Batta's way of holding the ball is different!
Batta's grip is off
It's a tie!
Nice serve!
The batter is Mr. Marik, the super magician.
I don't know this.
It's scary.
Let's see the ball.
Marik seems to be good at it.
I don't know this.
Look at the ball carefully!
Good!
Don't throw it away!
Good, good!
It's coming, it's coming.
When I was about to shoot, there was still a ball around here.
Huh?
On the contrary, it's hard to shoot a slow ball.
Look carefully!
He's so fast!
I experienced it for the first time that I couldn't shoot because I was too slow.
I could see it.
I was definitely here.
I was just hitting the target.
I was supposed to hit it, but the ball was still here.
I can't shoot such a big ball.
This is a bit frustrating
After the first round, the score is now 81
Something strange has happened to the guest team's bench
I can't get out at all
Let's go over there and ask
Maybe the fiber is...
The fiber is gone, Hamada is checking the opponent's bench
Sasano-san, are you okay? Do you still have any
Are you trying to send death to your enemy?
You don't need to be so cruel.
Are you really okay with this?
You're going to be like this forever.
You're going to be spinning around in the shopping mall.
I'm training my body so hard.
I'm not going to ride an escalator.
20 times each.
20 times here, too.
20 times.
And then I did it 20 times.
So I did it 100 times in total.
I'm really good at things like this.
I can do it forever.
She's still in good health, so she's going to try again.
Good!
Wow!
That's great!
You can run!
She's trying her best.
It's spring.
What was that?
I can't get over it.
It's like he's taking it easy.
Right after this, the danger approaches the pitcher, DJ Ko.
The batter is the former high school baseball player, Enzo.
It's a high ball!
Show it high.
It's high!
Nice!
That was close!
This is good!
It's okay!
That was dangerous, Endo!
You can't hit the pitcher's chest!
That was dangerous!
Why did I have to win that game?
Endo was on the screen.
If it was a dodgeball, it would have been a big deal.
It was a big deal in baseball too.
I do exercise. I do walking.
I also play with professional table tennis team.
I also play with professional bowling player.
Mr. Endo.
And Mr. Tanaka.
After Endo, Tanaka also...
The ball is in the net.
Oh no!
Wait!
I told you not to hit the pitcher!
You shouldn't hit the pitcher!
Is that how Kokoriko is?
The two of them are together.
Right?
And he says, sorry.
But he's not sorry.
There's one more!
It's scary when the ball comes.
So even if it's a little bit,
I think that if I keep raising the tension of my feelings, I can reduce the fear.
I'm a DJ, so I'm always doing that.
I'm always doing it like this.
When you enter the second floor, you will be affected by the fatigue of the defense of FIFI All Stars.
Oh!
So close!
Stop!
Naemachi!
You almost got it!
That was close!
It's been 35 years since I played softball.
My head is...
I'm full of energy, but my body can't keep up.
Inomo-chan!
Oh no!
It's a serve!
That was close!
It was so close!
When the fly came for the first time, I couldn't see it because of the sun.
I lost my confidence and the rest was completely broken.
It's coming!
I was surprised that the shot was shot from many places.
My knees and my hips are hurt. My fingers are all over the place.
I'm so sick of it.
The same goes for the Gakitsuka team.
Yoshinobu, who are you?
Why are you so slow?
You're going to be exposed!
Both the defense and the offense are exhausted
The Gakitsuka team has already finished 5 rounds of the game
The enemy is getting tired
Are you okay?
I'm really tired
Tanaka is the batter
Look!
Go, go, go!
Don't push yourself too hard!
The second goal is a normal one.
But it's a running home run.
Let's go!
Even though they lost 13 points in this game, they still have 68 points to go
FIFI All Stars, who were being pushed, finally counterattacks
The batter is Daniel Carl, who has a strong sense of skill
Look at the mirror
Carl, fight!
Fight!
Ahhhh!
Error! Error! Error!
Tanaka's error!
Tanaka's error caused the runner to lose his balance for the first time on this day.
Akira, catch it!
The next player is the former idol, Mizusawa Aki.
The strong player is here!
Fight!
With the feeling of being in front of the ball, he desperately tries to catch it.
Nice!
OK, OK!
Next, we have 73-year-old actor, Nobuto Okamoto.
Here he comes!
Oh, scary!
Dangerous!
It's raining!
His eyes were so blurry and the wind was so cold.
His eyes were so blurry and I thought the ball was coming.
I thought, is he going to be okay?
I thought, can he see clearly?
He caught the ball firmly and got a clean hit.
Okamoto is in the first place, Daniel is in the third place, and the two runners are in the same place
It's here!
This is bad!
This is scary!
So I'll go this way
This is a little scary
Let's go see the ball!
Right after this...
It's fallen! It's fallen!
Why did you fall here?
I want to throw up
The former Osomori Rikishi, Taka Toriki, did not expect to be hit with a softball
Taka Toriki
Scary
Taka Toriki is also a
He fell down!
What are you doing?
Why did you fall down here?
What happened?
His chin is black
I couldn't see it
I couldn't see it either
What happened?
My leg hurts!
My chin hurts.
After the shot, your chin...
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
What happened?
My leg... I tried to move forward, but I couldn't, and it fell off.
I thought I should have practiced a little bit more, but my legs didn't move forward.
I couldn't run, so I just held it.
It fell from my chin.
Was your chin in the frame?
Yes, it was.
It fell from my chin.
I'm glad I didn't hurt it.
The result is a draw.
It's a draw.
It's a change.
I was surprised.
He didn't come at all.
He's a coach.
He doesn't come at all.
Looking at the three-time All-Star defense, which is not easy to catch,
Hamada has a suggestion.
Let's go!
Do you want to call it 50 points instead of 100 points?
How many points do you have now?
32 points
It's getting better
Please tell us how it is
You can't say that
It's getting better
The team is getting better
It's not a high score, it's okay if you lose once
Is that so?
Yes
You're strong
I only got one
After the game, the strongest batter in Gakitsuka, Endo, shows his skills.
Here I go.
It went in!
As expected!
It's the first home run of the day where the left fencer is changed to a bigger one.
It's a new experience.
Nice!
You just hit one ball!
That was a good one!
Fifi All Stars' biggest problem is...
It's a miss!
It's impossible.
Nice cover!
The ball comes.
Why does the ball come?
Because the person in front of you doesn't stop it.
When I was practicing, I was able to get a few shots with Fifi-san, so I thought it was easy.
But it's different.
When the ball comes to the batter, it's scary.
I'm really scared of the ball.
But today, Yasutaka-shi...
You should have moved a little.
Yes.
Because I'm at home all the time, I'm 100 steps away from walking on my smartphone.
The attack of the third round is also very tiring.
The game is getting more and more difficult.
The third round is over and the score is 44 points difference.
Is it okay to end with 50 points difference?
What are you going to do, Justin?
I can't give a conclusion yet.
You can!
And you can't say a word to Marikku.
Are you having fun?
I'm not tired.
I knew it!
So, if they get 50 points, they win.
The remaining 6 points are the real goal.
He is very motivated.
I'm scared.
The 50 points are for the kids.
The continuous explosion.
Come back.
The three of you come back.
You can do it.
Stop.
Return the shot.
Finally, there is only one point left.
Here!
OK, it's the last one.
Last!
Yes!
The last one is a home run?
It's close!
But it's over.
50 points!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
The pitcher was good.
It was good.
I just threw it to the last.
I can't hit it.
I don't have experience in pitching.
Let's do it again soon.
Next time, let's do it with a thick candy.
bin Mostly
resignation
Even if the world is full of conflict
I won't give up with a bright smile
The power of the Han, and the power of the Pharaoh
Today as well, my spirit won't stop
Even though you lost, you still sang high notes
I don't know
I don't have time for this
I want you to teach me how to do it
I can't eat anymore
The past episode of the show is being broadcast exclusively on Hulu
《Kyuryu Kensaku》