About a year ago, the two men of the Heipo Island were doing a punishment game of 24 hours of interview
But what they saw was...
If you're going, then don't ring the alarm!
It's just a director, not a good one!
A director is not like that
It's not like he's a human being who's being punished, he's just a trash
Mirba has become a VTR that gives a deep impression
So...
Let's meet in the second part!
So, the second part
This time, to increase their mutual affection, they will challenge a heart-warming journey of a man.
The two men journey of Nadal and Heipo.
A journey of heart-warming and high-spirited travel.
So, Matsumoto-san, this is the second part.
Well, these two are actually quite compatible.
In Shimata, it's called the downtown of the Dine.
I've never been told that.
Really? I thought it was written on the internet.
When I went with Heibo, it was really scary.
Heibo is really good when he has the time to express himself.
But when he's gone, he's like...
Wait, is this the one?
This is the one.
There are so many.
It's the normal person.
It's definitely not the normal person.
Why? They are just ordinary staffs
That's not true
During the winter season, the day of the filming was blessed by the clear sky
From the Japanese TV channel, the location of the filming was Chiba prefecture
He always complains about this kind of stuff
I don't want to cry anymore.
You're suddenly cold.
I don't want to see it anymore.
From the beginning...
The director, Heipo Sekai, is 64 years old.
He has been in the show business for 30 years.
He has shown extreme fear,
scorn,
lying, and problematic personality.
He has done it.
And so, he is going on a journey with Nagaru this time as well
The journey's stage is at the clock station in Midoriku, Shibashi
The journey's start is about to begin
Good morning
So you didn't ask what we are doing?
No, we didn't
The journey that you two are going on is here
What? What is this?
What is this?
The person in the photo is from a house far from the people
A house?
The owner of the house and the owner of the house are having a heart-to-heart conversation
There are people?
Yes
It's not normal
The first mission is to ask the locals to find the one-off inn in the mountains and have a heart-warming conversation with the owner there
To find the way to the destination, they ask the locals
We're going to ask them too, right?
Yes
It's been a while
Excuse me
Are you asking the local?
Yes
Excuse me
Excuse me, hello
I want to ask you about this mountain, how to go there?
This way is the way to go
Which way?
Straight over there
Wow, this is...
If you go straight, you will reach here
Thank you
The mountain is this way
They are trying to get a good relationship, but they don't say anything
They are asking questions
They are not
They are not coming to us
And then
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Ah, let's go.
Is it okay to talk?
Ah, beautiful girl.
Beautiful girl.
Excuse me, Miss.
Miss.
Excuse me.
I'm a woman, so I want to talk.
I want to talk to you.
Is it okay?
Stop asking questions and get off.
I thought it was a beautiful place
This is Luan's healthy massage and relaxation salon
where he has several stores in the prefecture
Don't say it's healthy
What is the course chosen by the store?
It feels good to be in the middle of the store
But I'll wear my wall pants
It's amazing
It's a little clean
Excuse me.
Is Mr. Seiya okay?
Yes, he's okay.
He's really okay, but he's asking.
Nanahara-kun, what's wrong?
This is a massage, right?
Yes, it is.
You're really good.
I'm sorry.
I can only hear the sound.
It feels good.
Wait a minute, this is a mistake.
This is...
Hartford's reaction is so normal.
Aoki-san is also smiling.
Thank you very much. It was very pleasant.
After this, they continue to ask questions.
Somehow I understand.
They know the way to the destination
It's a sushi restaurant
After lunch, they go to the sushi restaurant
How is the sushi?
Thank you
It looks good
Is it really okay?
You can't eat it in one bite
Eat it in one bite
It's delicious!
Ah, I forgot to put it in my mouth
It's delicious
Eat it in one bite!
You're a cockroach!
Nadar, you're dirty!
The two who finished their lunch at 2pm
They head to their destination by car with no car navigation
Actually, from the current location to the destination, they leave the parking lot on the left
They take a left turn and a right turn to reach the destination
Don't you look at the map?
I don't like it
Will they be able to reach the destination?
I'm back
It's left now
It's not right?
It's right
Let's go right
Right is... which way is it?
Right is right?
Right is right
Is it here?
It's left
Is this okay?
Look at the map.
I can't see anything because of this map.
To the right.
There's a big water stream.
Straight ahead.
Is this right?
I'll take a picture of the Hama-zushi.
You took a picture of the Hama-zushi?
I should have taken a picture of the Hama-zushi.
Straight ahead.
Was it this muddy?
I don't know.
This is the forest right? Which way is the forest?
I don't know
Wait, I'm scared I can't stop
After asking around, he decided to confirm the location
What? What happened?
Mr. Kondo
Open it like this
Ok, I'll open it like this
What?
I don't know where it is
Excuse me.
I'd like to show you something.
We're at Tokino Station.
I'm not sure how to get there.
Do you know where we are?
We're not on the train.
You're not on the train?
What should we do?
We're not on the train.
So, what should we do to get here?
Oh, sorry.
We're stuck.
I don't know what to do.
He decided to go back to the station.
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
Where are we?
I don't know.
Oh, come on.
I'm sorry.
I told you that the train is running around here.
It's my fault.
Please go back.
I don't know.
Where are we going?
Let's check it out.
Let's stop pretending to know.
I got it.
It's close
He asked again
I want to go here
Yes, yes, yes
At the south exit, there is a place called Atemido-oka
The person who knows the way told him carefully
Go straight here
I understood perfectly
This time he seems to have understood it properly
It was a good explanation
It was easy to understand
This is left
This is here, Hamazushi
Yes, this is Hamazushi
This is completely normal
It was right after I said it
It was straight
Yes
The road is very clean
Finally, he is on the right way
This is it
Let's go
He asks again near the destination
Excuse me, can I ask you something?
Can I ask you something?
I want to ask you about the way, sorry for the inconvenience
Ah, I see
I understand
Can you guide me? I have a car
You can guide me
Oh, really? Thank you
You can go home
Thank you
He is so kind that he will guide him to the destination
Thank you very much.
That's great.
You're going to follow that?
I'm really grateful.
I don't think there's anyone so kind.
It's hard to find.
What do I do?
Did you get this?
Let's go.
You're going to follow it?
Yes.
There's a field over the mountain.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Thanks to the kind person, we can see the goal
It's narrow
This is not a road for cars
This is a bit...
It's a mountain road
After driving for 4km, we finally reach the destination
It's quite a long way
It's a bit rough
This is really...
I can't believe it.
It's coming out.
It looks like a forest.
Yes, it's a forest.
I'm scared.
It's scary.
Is it scary?
Yes, it's here.
I felt a strange feeling, so I was surprised.
There is a goat.
I'm scared. I can't do this anymore.
Finally, we arrived at a house in the mountains.
What kind of person lives here?
Is this really the house?
Yes, it is.
Let's ask the people who live here.
Yes, let's ask.
Are you the residents of this house?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm NADARU from Chikishiki Peppers.
I'm the director of the program. My name is Heipo.
I'm Murakami Mikiwo.
Murakami-san.
Murakami Mikiwo-san is 69 years old.
He is the owner of the house he is going to take care of.
What is the building there?
This was originally built when I moved in.
I used to be a housewife, but I like DIY, so I made it myself.
Now I only use it as a warehouse.
When you work, do you go home?
Yes
I see
Actually, Mr. Murakami, who has been living in the countryside for many years,
He moved here from the city to take care of the environment.
I'm grateful to you.
I helped you.
They are helping Mr. Murakami with his farm work
Is it okay to be so close?
It's okay
Is this garlic?
Can I smell it?
Wow, amazing
Wow, garlic!
Wait, wait, wait
Come here for a moment
This is amazing
This is amazing. This is garlic.
The sin of harvesting is to harvest grass.
The country boy Nadal is good at harvesting grass.
It's good.
You have to do it properly.
Oh no!
What the hell!
Hey! Hey!
Watch out!
Wait a minute!
Just let go!
Straighten your back.
And then you'll hit it.
I'm scared!
Is this okay?
Oh no!
What the hell!
What is this?
It's no good
Please do it
Are you looking at it?
What is this?
It's a field work
They have harvested a lot of vegetables
To cook these vegetables, they go to Murakami's house
Do you think there is a prison here?
I definitely think so
I don't think so. I'm not good at the countryside.
I see.
I was born and raised in Japan. I'm a real Japanese.
I'm a great father.
I'll call my wife.
Your wife is here.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I can't hold her.
Why?
I don't bite.
That's good.
Don't look at my face.
I'm so angry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Is that possible?
No, please stop it.
What are you doing?
Ah, it's cold.
You're noisy.
I'm sorry.
No, it's not a problem.
You're a fool.
What's wrong?
It's amazing.
Did you get a hit?
It's good.
He is making dinner with vegetables that he got from Murakami's field
Heipo seems to be making a stew with radish
Can you do it?
Yes, I can
Soy sauce
How long does it take?
10 to 20 minutes?
I wonder why.
It's almost done.
It's hot.
I wonder why.
You should wipe it.
If you do it like this, it will be white.
On the other hand, Nadaru is trying to fry onions and garlic.
It looks delicious.
I think this is delicious.
It's done.
Onion and garlic.
It's really delicious.
Can I add more salt?
It's delicious.
I really did it with my own ability.
It's not bad, is it?
It's delicious.
What?
It's a secret
Next is the stewed radish that Heipo made with only soy sauce and salt
It doesn't look bad, right?
It looks delicious
It's a little hot
It's not too strong
Wait a minute
The soy sauce is too strong
You should hold the soy sauce
It's okay
I'm going to eat it all
He's going to eat it all
He's going to show it to us
The Japanese style food seems to be a failure
Next, Murakami-san will make pizza with his own hands
It looks delicious
Let's eat together
What is this?
It's so dirty, even if it's a woman and a pizza.
It's so delicious.
Pizza is delicious.
Do you eat pizza like this sometimes?
Yes, I do.
It's so dirty.
I want to eat pizza sometimes.
Please come here.
After the meal, Mr. Murakami's reflection is a hot topic.
What was the reason for you to live here?
I was born in the countryside, so Iwate.
Iwate?
I wanted to live here after I retired.
Your mother is from Iwate?
Yes, she is 93 years old now.
She came here every year to play with us.
She is so nice.
I received a letter from her
From your mother?
Wow, that's amazing
I'll go and find it
This letter...
It seems to be touching
It's not sad at all
Iwate's mother will read the letter written to Murakami
I'm sorry for the long time I've been away
How are you all doing?
Iwate is doing well.
It's cold every day, so I can't leave the hut.
It's especially cold this year.
I went to the hot spring with John and Sina.
I remember that I went across the river with a big bag.
Please go to Iwate. I'll be waiting.
Be careful not to catch a cold.
From Grandma.
I can't believe you wrote such a great letter.
It's amazing.
My mother is 93 years old.
Really?
She is fine.
It's wonderful.
I can't write such a great letter.
I'm sorry I'm 93 years old.
What's wrong?
Thank you.
It's wonderful.
What?
Did you get a call from your mother?
That's great.
He's a double.
He's talking about his parents.
He's a good boy.
I don't know why, but my father and mother are from the same hometown.
They're called Miyagi and Iwate.
My family is small, so they go to the hot spring.
But they overlap.
I know them well.
You don't have to cry.
It's okay.
It's not embarrassing.
It's not a big deal.
I'm not like that.
It's okay.
It's a treasure.
Let's see your face.
I've never seen you being so serious.
I'm serious.
I've never been like this.
I'm happy.
He showed his true feelings.
His tears of joy.
What is he thinking now?
I'm sure that the girl in the massage shop is a real girl.
Stop it!
It's a family matter.
He kept saying that.
After this...
No!
It's out! It's out!
The man's journey continues on the forest
I was worried if it would work
I was worried if the tractor would work
Did you return the license?
Yes, I did
How much? 60?
I returned it at 55
That's fast!
How confident are you?
Did you really write that letter?
I really wanted to live long
The staff didn't expect it at all, so it was a really bad atmosphere
Why did you expect it?
It was a good atmosphere
Oh, it's good!
Shiopara 2019
Shiopara's popular show, the bus tour that you must not laugh, will be held this year too!
The strongest comedy guests are waiting for you!
Next week, the two men's tour will be completed
I can't do it anymore. I can't do it anymore.
Director, come here!
Can they face the heartful ending?
They are really excited.
Where is the guy who can't finish this?