This week's night's lip-syncing hit studio, the second half!
Last time, the luxury lip-syncing artists performed their dreams!
A hot stage was opened up!
And this week, the guests are coming in one after another!
Who will win the award?
Last time, the artists who were so good at talking were eliminated.
Next, the 10th person.
Now, the idol who debuted with a star's birth will go up to the next stage as a first-class singer representing Japan.
Nakamori Akira's Sasu!
I won't need a man that can deal with those entonces
Okay?
The flames that sleep in the chest that disappeared
Wake them up and chase after the dream that now flies away
Show me your real love
The flame that can't disappear from your chest
Souan Brother
Thank you very much!
How was it? Sing it.
Yes, yes, yes.
I can't hear you because you put your hand on top of it.
I don't think it's possible, but it says in the document that Akina-san doesn't have a single joke.
No, it's not Akina-san.
That's not true.
No, no, no.
A single joke?
Please, please.
I'll tell you.
No, it's not.
You can show it to us.
Is it okay?
Akina-san?
Yes.
Te-te! Te-te-te-te-te!
Te-te-te-te-te!
Ha!
That was quite loud.
That was Akina-san. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
He even showed the gag.
It's so precious.
Next is the mouth-to-mouth singer.
As the final weapon of the Komuro family,
he is a charismatic singer who has created many things in the 90s.
Amuro Namiede, Toraemi!
This is the one that makes you angry.
It's the one that makes you angry.
I practiced a lot.
He practiced a lot too.
The sound was good.
I don't know this one.
I wrote it on the back of my head.
I want to deliver my feelings to you
More than anyone else
Try me, I love you
My love is blooming
Now try me, even if my sad feelings disappear
Yes, try me, I'm looking at you
Believe in me
Try me, tomorrow is different
It's all about deciding.
Thank you very much!
What a wonderful dance!
Please come over here!
Thank you for coming.
There was also the Amurabu-m.
Yes.
What do you think about it?
At the Amurabu-m, I really don't know.
You say that to yourself?
Yes, sometimes. I say that to myself when I'm talking to Monkeys.
Super Monkeys?
You have to put Super.
If you don't put Super, it changes the meaning.
Today, we have a friend from the Komuro family.
Where were you? What are you doing?
This is fun!
I haven't said anything yet.
Where were you?
What were you doing? This is fun!
Come here.
Then, you should go.
This is fun.
Thank you very much.
Next is the first one.
A beautiful fairy who came to Japan.
Agnes-chan's Hina-geshi no Hana.
It's great. It's in the 70's.
Is this okay?
It's not okay.
I'm sorry.
No, no, this is no good.
This is just the three of us. Let's go.
This is just a little short-circuited.
Let's go with the
This is already a little crying...
Shake shake
Love's feelings overflowed in my chest
Love's tears spilled out today too
I remember it. I remember it.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
How was it? Please sing.
I have learned a lot of Japanese.
She has learned a lot.
Just a little.
Where are you from?
Hong Kong.
She has a great sense of Egypt.
I haven't been to Egypt yet.
You are from Hong Kong, right?
Yes.
Ah... Don't turn around.
I never turn around.
You never turn around.
It's because of Serah.
You turn around immediately.
You're a genius.
That was Serah. Thank you very much.
Next is the mouth-to-mouth singer.
That Koizumi Junichiro is also a big fan of the Japanese monster visual K-band, Mano Jishite.
X-Japan's Kurenai.
What's going on?
I'm a little shocked.
This is amazing.
It's really shocking.
I thought I was going to faint.
I'm a little shocked.
It's a story. It's a story.
Really.
It's good.
I'll meet you again
Chocolates, chocolate, more chocolate
I'll be with you
We'll find the way
E
E E E E E E
It's good, it's good.
It's just a croquette.
It's good.
It's not better than the end of action.
It's great.
The end
Thank you very much
It was wonderful
Suddenly, it became intense
The way he shook his head suddenly became intense
I did it as usual
Is that so?
Today, you are alone
Yes, I have a neck injury
I see
Is your neck okay, Yoshiki-san?
It's okay
I think it's okay to use it.
What?
It slipped perfectly.
It slipped from the top.
It slipped.
Toshihisa, there is no such thing as slipping.
There is no such thing as slipping in a regional K-band.
How was it, Monza-san? X Japan.
Why was it called?
At one time, I didn't like it.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, Kousaka!
No, no, no, it's different.
I'm not sure if I can say this.
This is the first time I'm singing this song.
That's not true.
It's Toshi's song.
It's not the first time.
I don't know Toshi.
I've been looking up a lot of things, but I haven't found it.
I don't know at all.
hahahahahahaha
It's dispatching singer
certain charisma of the young manенко
Causing young fall into the destruction RJ
that which leads the youth from the performance
OZAKI UTAKA's Night of the didgeridoo
Next is
came out of an amateur
I'm looking at the textbook and the outside world
I'm looking at the door of my heart without a door
I don't want to.
I know.
There is no escape if you are found.
Crouch and lean back.
I can't laugh.
If you understand the secret of the heart,
Adults will look at you.
And tonight, your friends will make plans at home.
I don't want to go home at school
I don't even know what my existence is
I'm trembling
I'm going to move
I'm going to start running with a stolen microphone
I'm sorry, everyone.
No, no, no.
To the back of the cage of the dark night.
That's good. That's good.
I don't want to be tied up by anyone.
On this night when I ran away,
I felt free.
On the night of the 15th.
The winner is...
Congratulations!
Ozaki-san, congratulations!
Congratulations, Ozaki-san!
We have a question.
Ozaki-san, what is your current role?
My role?
Yes.
I'm a woman.
A woman?
Yes.
You're a woman, but you're not a woman.
When I'm with her, I can write a lot of things.
Ah, I see.
You can write new things by being with a woman.
That's right.
That's important.
Mr. Ozaki, where were you when you were 15?
I was in Naples, Italy.
Who are you talking about?
You were in Naples?
Yes.
In Japan?
You were in Naples when you were 15 and broke the window of the school building.
Did you write that in Naples?
Yes, I know it well.
Did you write it in Naples?
Actually, I did it to steal a motorcycle or a car.
He stole a bike in Napoli.
Napoli?
He's a thief!
He's talking about something really weird.
What?
It was a joke.
It was a joke!
That was a joke!
It was a joke that made Ozaki-san cry.
That was Ozaki Yutaka-san. Thank you very much.
This is a famous mouth-to-mouth singer.
He's the king of comedians in Japan.
With this song, he makes people smile and happy all over Japan.
Ueki Hitoshi's Suudarabushi
Eh?
I can't believe it
That's amazing
This is not good
It's not good
Even if you're going to get drunk
You can't make it in time
earthworm
Sui sui sui dararatta sui sui
and that's it.
That was great!
Thank you!
That was great.
That was the second round.
The second round?
He was singing, right?
It felt like he was singing.
It was a pretty good synchronization.
Zabuki-san, who was the member that you got along with the best among the Crazy Cats?
No, no, no.
Mike.
Suddenly, I started sweating.
It was a pretty good expression.
Donato.
An unexpected person appeared.
Now, finally, the last scene.
The treasure of Japanese music, who is always challenging the field of new music without being trapped in the circle of enka.
Mori Shinichi's mother.
She has a good face.
Good face, good face.
No, no, keep it that way.
Keep it, keep it.
I'm asking you, it's the last one.
Seriously.
Mother, mother,
I look up at the sky.
When it rains, I become an umbrella.
Someday you will become the umbrella of the world
Please tell me
The truth that I will never know
I don't know.
Good, good.
Wonderful.
Thank you very much.
Where do you usually hang out?
I hang out?
I hang out with golf, and watch movies.
I think I have many hobbies.
What are you into the most now?
Well, I guess...
I guess it's a gym.
A gym?
You can't fool me.
What?
You can't fool me?
No, no, no.
Let's talk about hobbies.
Who do you go golfing with?
I have many old friends.
I go to sushi restaurants.
You go to sushi restaurants?
No, I don't have any celebrities.
Oh, really?
I'm just a fool.
Where do you live?
Can I ask? Where do you live?
On TV.
I live in Setagaya.
You're a fool.
I'm not a fool.
You don't have to be a fool.
What's your motto?
My motto is,
I'll do my best.
Are you a fool?
I'm not praising him.
He's a hard-working man.
He's a great man.
He's the best.
The song of all the mouth-to-mouth artists is over.
Who will win the crown?
Now, the winner will be announced.
The winner?
The winner is Yutaka Ozaki.
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Ozaki-san, you won the award, but how do you feel now?
I'm quite moved.
He's moved.
It's not like he won the award.
I want to hear it again.
This time, the winner, Ozaki Itaka-san, will sing a live song.
Please give him a round of applause.
Thank you.
Now, it's 15th night with Ozaki Yutaka.
J church
What a stupidity
I'm watching a dream that can't be reached in the sky far away
I want to be a hero who has no place to go
I'm burning up a ball, and if I find it, there's nowhere to run
I'm stuck in a car, and my back is stiff
I don't know what to do anymore
I'm a village of grown-ups
I'm a schoolboy who's been living in a dream
Anyway, I don't want to go to school or the movies anymore
You're fast!
I'm going to take a bath.
Thank you very much!
The next episode will be on November 29th!
The Science Doctor 24 hours that you must not laugh!
DVD and Blu-ray will be on sale November 29th!
From now on, I will be the one to jack this bus!
For good luck to all thewell-known sound track HEONれたンチャット
dat ai indopunes
and bus-jacks
Song Old Science which seems to have no problem
Thank you for watching!