April 5th, this day, Yamasaki Kokoriko from Downtown became the judge and the new regular member audition was held.
Who will be the participants of this audition?
Please come in.
Thank you.
Now, everyone.
The new regular of the Gaki no Tsukai.
Ode-san.
From now on,
whether you are suitable for the Gaki no Tsukai.
We will carefully decide.
This is what it is.
Everyone, thank you.
Thank you.
Hey, first of all, let's introduce ourselves.
Yes.
From the left.
Which one is left?
I'm fine with it.
From the left.
Excuse me.
I'm Tokuyoshi Mi, 31 years old, from Kyoto.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Fuzesu, nice to meet you.
What?
I'm not sure.
What did you say?
I'm Fukuda from Tutorial.
Fukuda-kun?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Tamura from Yoshimoto Koukyou. Nice to meet you.
I'm Kirin. Nice to meet you.
I'm Kosugi from Black Mayonnaise.
I'm the champion.
Nice to meet you.
What do you mean by champion?
The champion of M1.
It's 2005, right?
Yes.
Well, from here on, everyone, you have your own good things.
There are various things.
Then, I wonder if you can bring it.
Well, we've done it after all.
It's not difficult at all.
Well, everyone, do you know what this is in front of you?
Karashi-renkon?
Yes, Karashi-renkon.
It's a simple story.
Try to suck up the Karashi.
Let's try to suck up the Karashi of Karashi-renkon.
Tamura, you try.
Yes.
I'll suck it up.
The other members, please sit down.
Yes, yes.
It's thick.
Please.
It's my first time seeing a sad lotus root.
What should I do? I'll suck it up.
Try it.
I'll do my best.
I'm sorry.
Like this.
Yes, yes.
That's good.
You can just suck it up.
You can hold it up to here.
That's the image.
Okay, okay.
I'm going to suck it up.
Okay.
I'm sorry for the failure.
I'll go.
I don't know if it's done.
It's done.
I don't know.
It's spicy.
The spiciness is coming.
I thought I could go with more youthful image.
I wonder if it won't come suddenly.
It won't come suddenly.
Don't pull it!
I'll do it.
I'm facing you.
Please.
You can do it like this.
Especially.
I'll do it.
It's working.
What's this?
It's pulling.
Is it that low?
No, it wasn't like that.
Oh, it's gone.
It's a bit low.
It looks like it.
Why?
It doesn't look like it.
It wasn't like that at all.
It's the third one.
Yossha!
Yes?
It's because it's hot.
Hurry up.
Excuse me.
I'll have it.
It's hard to swallow.
Can you do it?
I can do it.
Why are you not breathing?
I'm just breathing.
You're not breathing at all.
Why?
Breathe in.
I'm sorry.
That's enough.
Masugi!
Is this okay?
I don't think it's too much of a blow.
You don't have to avoid it.
You can talk here.
But look at it. How is it? Can you do it?
Yes.
I've been holding back for a long time.
You mean the stimulus?
Yes.
I see.
You've been holding back for a long time.
Yes.
I'll hit the head.
Choose a good one.
It's already started.
It's not just about choosing one.
It's your choice.
Like this.
I sucked it up.
It's really beautiful.
It's beautiful.
It's beautiful to open the hole.
From here?
Kiri Kiri Koukou!
Congratulations!
It's Kiri Kiri!
If you say it without a key, it's the most...
Kiri Kiri Koukou!
Take?
Do it.
I'll do it.
Oh, that's so bold.
I didn't think of this idea.
This is good.
It's stuck.
That's good.
You're almost there.
Oh, it hurts.
It's impossible to close it.
It's different.
The hole is different.
Check it.
Check it and try it.
That's right.
They are saying it too.
I'm not sure.
Just barely passed!
It was a short one.
Next, we have a newbie.
Please give him a nickname.
Yes.
I'll start.
First, this person.
The person who's done.
YOSHIDA.
What do you mean by a waste?
A waste.
A scheme.
A scheme?
Yes.
Tatarin of the lower town.
Minoru Shiraki.
That's all?
Iida.
Iida Shoko.
It's not Ada.
Ah, sorry.
Is it like that?
Yes.
Next person, please.
Here you go.
You idiot.
Free.
Here you go.
You're taking a break again?
I see.
Michelangelo.
Sky Blue.
That's the point.
It's looking good.
Next person, please.
This is difficult.
I see.
It's difficult.
You're going to see the orchestra right away.
It's a bit long.
The adagio.
Ah, the adagio.
Teresa.
Yes.
Spanko.
Ouch.
Yes.
Hogarakka.
Don't take notes so often.
It's my nickname.
Tamura-san.
Oh, sorry.
Let's move on.
It's a nickname.
Tight.
What kind of girl is she?
Are you going to jog again?
In Adana.
Are you kidding me?
It's possible that you'll be fired.
This is the third time.
In Adana.
Please do it in Adana.
Jackson.
Yes.
A lot.
Restaurant.
It's difficult.
Let's go to the next one.
Thank you.
I see.
This is a method.
One-Action. This is good.
This is good, isn't it?
Mrs. Time Machine.
You can go to the worst.
It's your feelings.
It's your name.
Next.
Telekura.
Are you going to look at my hand again?
Um...
Tamura-kun.
Please give me a nickname.
I'm going to quit.
Is this on purpose?
No, I'm just doing it for fun.
Please give me a nickname.
There are more categories than people.
I'm going to reflect on my actions.
I'll do it like this.
Then I'll try to make it short.
Yes.
But if you're going to be called a restaurant, that's better.
Thank you very much.
Somehow luxurious!
Kotsugi!
Kotsugi and Fukuda!
You've chosen two amazing people.
Let's do a game of Godzilla vs. King Ghidorah.
Godzilla vs. King Ghidorah?
I'll tell you what you'll do.
I'm sorry.
This is a big one.
Try it quickly.
Yes, yes. Sorry.
This is Godzilla, right?
The neck is white.
Pass! Pass!
No, it's fine.
Can you do it around here?
Yes, yes.
Come a little closer.
It's fine if you use this part.
I wanted to see it closer.
This part is not good.
There is a field, so it's OK.
You can use it here.
You can touch it.
Can I do it here?
OK.
OK, start.
Pass!
Oh that's good.
I passed.
I just passed.
The power of that sword is different.
The raw power of that sword is different.
The one that can be cut can take it.
Go ahead.
Just cut it!
So who wants to play Godzilla?
What?
Who wants to play Godzilla?
Godzilla vs. King Ghidorah?
I'll do it.
Go ahead.
No, a little more forward.
If possible, come to the place where you can touch.
It's close.
Well then, I'll do it.
Oh, it's 5 o'clock.
Pass!
This is a pass.
You're amazing.
Amazing.
He's got a lot of power.
He's totally different.
Alright!
Hurry up.
Try it.
Run.
Please.
Run as if you're hitting the shoulder.
It's okay.
This was better than I thought.
I think it's better to show it like this.
It's better to show it like this.
Well, then...
Kasugi!
Did you get sick again?
Yes.
No, I didn't.
It's okay.
Now, please stand up.
Well, this is a bit of a sudden request, but...
I'd like to sing a song by a tuna fisherman.
I'd like to sing a song by a tuna fisherman from Oma.
I think it's too easy.
The sea, in the sea there is a man's mirror.
In one mirror, a tuna is reflected.
Gouka!
That was wonderful.
It was wonderful.
Well, what he said was a mess.
Yes.
Parula!
Tuna fish dish.
No, that's not it.
It's not?
The bride's song waiting for the fisherman to return.
The bride's position is...
The bride's...
Sorry, it's about the bride.
Please.
Okay.
Not yet, not yet, my darling, not yet, darling, darling.
Tiritiritokyo!
That's a waste!
You're really...
You're really a pain in the neck!
Thank you.
That's a close call.
Hmm...
Kosugi!
I just got a new name.
Mr. Katsumi.
Yes.
Please sing a song to celebrate the big success.
Oh, that's good.
I see.
Please.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
For such a simple thing.
For Kosugi, it's nothing.
Come here, come here.
Come to me!
Go, go, go, go!
That was wonderful!
Suddenly, it's a good song.
It's a good song.
Then,
I wonder if Kosugi-kun can sing this song.
Kosugi!
I'll sing a song about a bride waiting for her husband's return.
You saw it, didn't you? The one that I failed earlier.
It was a bad one.
It was.
I won't do such a simple thing again.
There are many types of Garuna, so I'm just choosing.
That's right.
I'm just doing it with my body.
The laces you gave me are wet today too.
The laces you gave me are not dry today too.
Go-Ka!
That was wonderful!
Kozue-kun was wonderful.
I see.
Kozue-kun is tough.
Okay, please.
That was perfect.
That was good.
Next week, we'll be looking at the children's show, the new regular member audition.
Black Mayonnaise Tutorial
Kirin is facing a new challenge
Can the 3rd round overcome the pressure they've never experienced before?
It's perfect
It's good
Among the 3 teams that have shown countless miracles and unexpected performances, who will be the ones to pass?
And after the audition, the 6 members will be faced with a new trap by Dues Hamada.
Don't miss the shocking ending!
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.