Let's do it!
I've never done badminton before.
That's right.
I'll do it too.
There's a net.
Really?
Someone go there.
I'll judge.
What?
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
What's going on?
What do you think?
The funny mess that appeared in the recording of the movie,
The first time, he died in a play,
And the second time, he died in a doll play.
The red chicken that ran to him later, was eaten by a ferret.
This time, what is their purpose?
We are doing a hero show right now.
Please watch it.
It's starting soon.
No, no, no.
Anyway, this is a show.
Yes.
It's a revolutionary show.
But before that, if you could watch it a little bit.
It's a follow-up.
I watched it before, but it was a little different.
There's a difference in time.
The previous Kami-shibai and Ninkyougeki was a bit unpopular, so I stopped it.
It's over soon.
It's over soon?
Yes, I can't take that long.
Hero show?
Yes, it is.
We have already done all the half-finished parts.
Hi everyone! Thank you for waiting.
Today, we have invited you to the Hero Show Super Victory.
Now, let the hero show begin!
Please say something.
I said something, but I didn't understand.
I see.
My name is Black Zorg.
Our goal is to take over the world.
I will destroy the Super Victory that always gets in the way for me.
What's with you guys?
Since I came out, you don't look happy at all.
Those of you who love Black Zorg, raise your hands.
You guys! You should have been ashamed of yourselves!
You bastards! You bastards!
Come here!
Everyone! This is terrible!
We have to shout out loud, Super Victory!
Ready, set...
Shagoo!
No, no! Call your big friends too!
Ready, set...
Shagoo!
Wait!
Who's there?
It's my friend!
It's not heavy at all.
It's different.
You've been caught by the super-duper-human.
I'll be your opponent!
This is different!
It's a real fight!
It's amazing.
You're fast.
You're spinning around.
What the hell?
Ah, I took off your scarf.
Hurry up!
If you keep doing that, it's over.
You're so weird.
You can't even see me!
If you're like this, I'll turn into a monster!
Mic, mic.
Ah, mic, mic.
Super Victory, I forgot the mic.
What the hell is this?
I want to play badminton.
You're good.
What is this?
What?
What the hell is this?
He's like a tree.
I don't understand what he's saying.
I can't understand him.
I don't understand.
I don't remember well.
I don't remember well either.
Joking, kidding, kidding.
Joking, kidding.
Hey!
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm just moving my body.
I don't understand what you're saying.
You're a fool.
The meaning is...
Long!
It's long.
It's a long song.
Oh, he's gone.
It would be nice if he could always be bald.
It's not like he's gone missing.
It's like he's transformed in an instant.
Oh!
Lord Wada!
How long does it take to change that?
The power of surprise that can't be put into words, the right hand!
The infinite power that is in your body, the left hand!
He's looking at the pen with his bare hands.
The unbelievable power of mystery, the right leg!
You're slow!
The power of the king of the Great East Asia, the left leg!
This is a different style.
Power Head, the power that destroys anything!
Unforgettable power, Light Year!
Unforgettable power, Light Leg!
The first law of the universe, the infinite power, Left Leg!
The proof of justice, Super Victory!
You're wearing a big hat.
You bastard!
What's with you?
You're not allowed to wear a hat.
I will never forgive evil, Super Victory!
What?!
Super Victory!
You guys are going to lose the tanker!
Today, I will defeat you!
Super Victory!
I knew that the movie was good.
You bastard!
You're not going to drink, are you?
Shut up!
Get out of the way!
Today, I will avenge my uncle!
Your uncle?
What?
What? That's the end?
No way!
Let me explain.
The Master of Super Victory is a well-known martial artist.
He is one of the world's top three masters of martial arts.
He defeated Mugyu with his Seiken.
He broke the neck of the beer bottle with his sword.
He fought against the enemy with his pinky.
There are many legends about him.
They are called by their names, such as Ushigoroshi, Beer Bin, and Yubi no Koyubi.
Also, there are 3 million disciples all over the world.
They are called by their names, such as God Hand, with the thought of respect.
After the war, after the war, there were many fights in the dark.
They fought one after another, and were called the Fighting Brigade.
However, after that, they returned to the mountains for three years.
When you want to drink, want to hug a woman,
and your heart is so empty,
you can shave off one eyebrow with a razor,
and you can't appear in front of people.
You can't get out of the evil spirit,
so you can be called a one-eye for a while.
I'm not sick.
I'm fine.
I'm a super-victory.
Doctor!
Please help me!
Unzuru Denai...
Master! Master!
There are so many of them!
Master's breath has stopped!
Unzuru Denai Super Victory...
Master! Master!
Master's breath has stopped!
Unzuru Denai Super Victory...
Super Victory, take my revenge!
Old man!
It's long.
It's really long.
You're sweating like a Super Victory.
Your sweat is coming out from your pants.
The color has changed.
No way.
Wow, here it comes again!
It's coming out again.
I don't know what it means.
I've never heard it.
It's not a song of Shizuoka, is it?
Ah, I don't know.
I don't know anything.
How much of this skill does he have?
How much of the singing ability does he have?
I don't know.
Heart us open new
Listen
author?
that's his original song
I sometimes saw my eyes in a lie
Always match
Happy, happy, happy!
It's a perfect match, isn't it?
It's before the battle, right?
Yes, before the battle.
The explanation of the master is...
It's back to normal.
I will definitely avenge you!
What?
I am the devil's grudge!
I've never seen a devil like that.
Definitely!
This is the Devil's Sword.
What is this Devil's Sword?
Let me explain.
The Devil's Sword is the Don of the Kaijin Clan.
It is a three-dimensional martial arts master of the Kaijin Clan.
He killed Buffalo with one punch.
He cut the neck of the plastic bottle with a chopper.
He fought with his index finger.
There are many legends.
He killed Buffalo.
and the finger of the hand.
Also, there are 2.7 million kaijin who were raised by one person.
They are called Godfather,
with respect.
After that, they go into the mountain for three years.
When they want to drink, want to hug a kaijin,
and when they are so excited,
they cut off one of their tentacles with scissors.
He became a monster that cannot be seen in public, and after he chased away the evil spirits, he was called a shoulder-choking for a while.
He's an idiot.
He's an idiot for saying such things.
He can't study.
Don't worry.
Black Zorg, I'm fine.
Are you okay, Devil 4?
I can't believe my love for Super Victory is being destroyed.
Are you okay?
Devil Sword! Devil Sword!
Don't worry.
Black Zorg.
But I can't let Super Victory be destroyed like this.
Are you okay?
Devil Sword! Devil Sword!
You bastard! Show me your face!
Take my revenge!
Devil Sato! Devil Sato!
What a stupid show!
No way!
I don't think so.
The song has changed a bit.
It has.
I've never heard it before.
This is it.
Ballad version.
That's what it is.
What the hell?
I'm looking at you.
I don't know which way I came to see.
I came to see this person's face.
Hey!
What's up, Eden?
He's here.
You're the reason why the terrorist is dead!
I'll never forgive you for this!
I won't lose to a villain like you!
Hey, don't be so mean!
Please, don't be so mean!
Hey, hey, come on!
Yes?
Come on, come on!
You can do it, Kamiya.
If you're a hero, you should do action.
Action, action, let's go!
You can't kick or punch like you explained.
I won't forgive you!
I'll kill you!
I'm going to use my power!
This technique is to pull your body!
What? Damn!
Then, take this!
Wow!
Ah!
Ah, my body is pulling my power!
This technique is to pull your body!
You're a fool!
Now, let's go!
Now, you!
You will return the power that I have absorbed to you!
I will not give up!
This is a battle of the century.
This is the technique of returning the power that you absorbed to you!
Take on my power and suck it back from inside myself!
what happened?
I was sucked back into myself...
I was sucked into the energy being sucked back and sucked many time...
This and that couldn't suck me back and sucked me back up!
This and that can't suck up!
Here, you can take on the kasuma
I'll return if you'm buying or giving back what you
were unp None to the
I'm done with you!
Get lost!
I have a secret weapon that can defeat you in one blow!
What?
Take this! Super Thunder!
My penis is being torn apart!
Your penis is being torn apart.
You should go to hell!
You're so stupid.
What?
The chinchin is not torn apart.
The power increased by coming back from the edge of hell.
What?
Take this!
Devil Echustream!
I know!
The chinchin is torn apart!
Why are you laughing?
What are you talking about?
I feel like my penis is going to break!
You're so clingy!
I'm not in the serious mode!
What?
I'm going to be serious from now on!
Galaxy Mosquito!
My penis is itchy!
I want my penis to be covered in meat!
Give it back!
You're so weak!
What?
Take this!
Let's go!
What?
How's this?
Not yet!
I'll do this again.
What?
What is this?
It's over.
Okay, everyone.
How was the story so far?
Do you understand?
What will happen to these two?
I'm curious.
I would like to take a break here.
It's over.
Are you enjoying it?
It's long.
It's long?
There are many places I don't want to go.
I'm a child.
I think I'm saying too much about the new girl.
Is it okay to say that?
I think it's better to say that.
Anyway, I don't think it's good to say that to a hero.
That's right.
It's a hero award.
I realized that there is a limit to the number of hero books if there are two people.
I have a request.
I can't ask you to help me with the hero book.
That's...
I don't know. We came here to play badminton.
But it's a really simple role.
I'd like to ask Hamada and Tanaka to play the role.
I have the image of a role.
Why?
Really?
Yama-chan?
I have the image of a role.
I see.
But I understand badminton.
Then I'll go.
Thank you.
Please do it.
Please be happy.
Thank you.
Is it a good time?
We will show you the power of Black Sphere!
Hey, don't be so stingy!
Hey, you have to cheer for us!
Victory Lady! Victory Lady!
You came, Victory Lady!
I can't see it.
I can't see it either.
You can't see it.
Don't shoot the strawberry flash!
I can't see it.
I did it.
Give it back to me!
No!
I'm losing energy from my penis.
What are you doing?
I can't do it like this.
Everyone, give me power!
Everyone, if you don't do anything, Super Victory will be destroyed!
Everyone, please give a shout out to Super Victory!
Ready, set...
Ganba!
Even bigger friends, more, more!
Then, Super Victory will lose!
Ready, set...
Ganba!
No! I can't reach it!
Look! Evil always wins!
Super Victory lost?
Why did Super Victory lose to Black Zoology?
Because everyone's support wasn't enough.
Let's practice to make a louder voice than usual.
I'm angry.
Well then, everyone, goodbye!
It's over?
Huh?
The lady's left behind?
Don't look at the lady over here.
I can't look at the lady.
It's over.
The show's over.
It looks like it's over.
No, no, it's weird.
Wait a minute.
Victory.
It's strange that you are pulling me so much.
Thank you.
Let's do it again.
You are going to miss it.
Sorry, I'm in the room since 7.
This room?
Yes.
Thank you.
What? Is that a team?
I think so.
What is this?
I feel like I was told to do this.
I can't watch it.
I can't watch the ladies.
What are we going to do?
I don't know. Let's do the badminton.
Let's do it.
We'll do it.
Can you do it?
Go! Go! Shiodome Jamboree!
It's fun! Come here everyone!
The kids' booth is being held on Japanese TV.
We have prepared various devices for you to see.
What is this?