Every time we have a new member of the school, we will have a special 10th anniversary party!
We have a new member of the school!
Say something!
I'm being rude!
You're just a bad guy.
Say something!
What are you doing?!
Is this okay?
That's right.
I've been a Yakuza for 10 years.
I see.
So, as a Yakuza,
I'd like to have a skit with everyone today.
What?
Do it.
I'll take a picture of you.
I see.
I've never been a skit.
I'll do it because I'm bad at it.
You're a skit.
You are a bad singer. You have never done live show, right?
So take off your hat!
That's why I'm doing it. Do you understand?
Yes, yes!
Yes!
I want you to receive my painting lesson.
This is a big deal. Why do you do it?
This is my second time.
I've done it twice.
Do you have a license?
I don't need a license for scuba diving.
You do!
I don't need it.
How about Tanaka?
I've done it three times.
You're a real man.
Really?
Where did you do it?
I did it in Ishigaki Island.
No, I did it in Austria.
Austria!
You're kidding me.
Austria is a mountain.
It's Australia.
What are you doing?
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
This time, the place where the scuba will be held is the 5m deep pool at the Ok Marin Pro in Nerimaku.
As you can see, even in the teacher's Yamagaki, he has only dived twice.
This is Hamada Endo's first time.
Can they all take a photo of the sea?
Yamachan's Tsukiyama Koshu!
Yes, please.
I'll teach you properly.
It's my first time, so if you teach me with money, I'll die.
That's right.
If you do it with half the fun.
I'll never do it with half the fun.
First of all,
It's normal.
It's not really half the fun.
First of all,
Don't lick the sea!
I'm writing it in Akaji.
You must not lick it.
Yes.
Normally...
What did you say?
You must not lick it.
That's all I said.
Hey!
You can give it to him.
Don't laugh!
I'm just saying the same thing over and over again.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Please put it in the corner of your head.
In the corner?
I don't want to put it in the corner.
Akaji is the most important thing.
It's okay. Just put it in the corner.
Don't lick your eyes. Next!
First, the mask.
The mask in the water.
I'll definitely wear the mask in the water.
And the regulator.
The mouth of the regulator is a tail.
A tail? What is a tail?
It's where you breathe.
And the auxiliary air source.
This is written as the source of air, and it's called the air source.
No, it's not like that.
It's not like that at all.
Tell me what it is.
It's a special case.
Yes, I'll explain.
What is this?
This is the pressure gauge of the air pressure gauge.
This is how much air is left.
Next is basic knowledge of diving.
First, knowledge to balance the pressure.
If you remember the unpleasant feeling when you first learned it...
What is unpleasant feeling?
Matsumoto-san, you have it, right?
Right now, it's a little unpleasant.
Ear-pulling.
Please do ear-pulling.
If you can't properly pull out your ear,
the eardrum in your back...
BANG! BANG! BANG! BANG!
You'll break it!
I won't explain about the technique anymore.
I'll teach you how to remove the ear.
Please pinch the nose.
It's the first time.
I'll never tell you.
It's easy to break it.
Yes, I do.
And then, I'll put it on my mouth.
Do you put it in when you put it in?
Yes, I do.
You put it in, but you put your nose in?
Yes, I always put my nose in.
But your nose is like this.
Yes, it's like a mask.
But the mask has a hole so that the nose can be pinched.
Oh, really?
Did it have a hole?
It's not a hole.
Everyone is trying to figure it out.
It's from the top, right?
If there's a hole, it's going to be a hole.
No, it's a hole.
The mask has a hole to make it easier to pinch the nose.
How do you do it?
Like this, and then, when you exhale,
you face this way.
It's hard to understand.
You face this way.
The earpick is used to push air out of the nose by pinching the nose and pinching the nose.
You can also use it when you're on a plane and your ears are tingling.
If you don't do this, the air will come out from your ears.
I can't do this.
You can't do this.
If you can't do this, you can't go down.
I can't go down.
Please do it, Mr. Amada.
This is also a challenge.
Next is the lungs.
You go down like this.
And the bubbles that come up, if you go further than that, the lungs will burst.
And you will get sick.
Really?
If that's the case, I'll quit.
You'll get sick.
If you go further than that, you'll get sick.
You're saying it like you're sick.
It's called a water-sickness.
Really?
It's a serious disease.
This is very...
It's like this.
What? It's like this from here on?
If you suddenly rise, your lungs won't be able to withstand the change in pressure.
Don't panic, slowly continue to rise while breathing.
Next is a hand signal that's important to protect yourself underwater.
It's a trouble.
This is this.
Matsumoto-san was like this.
He was like this in the drama.
Lastly, the question for Yamazaki-sensei.
Okay, then.
End.
Today is a poll, so it's like this.
If a shark comes out, what should we do?
When a shark comes out, you should definitely meet it.
That's true.
If it comes out, you should meet it.
If you encounter a shark, don't panic and wait for it to pass by the nearby rock.
What if you get your feet caught?
When you get your feet caught, don't do it.
What?
What if you get caught?
Take off your regulator, take off your fins, take off everything.
You're naked!
Right?
Diving maturi!
You're the one who's scared.
We're going to practice in the pool.
You're the opposite.
Daki-san.
Are you okay?
Ah, yes.
First, we'll get used to the water.
It's something that can be taken very cleanly.
It's amazing.
Amazing!
Okay.
Let's go!
Why are you looking at me?
You're always there.
What's with you? You're not even looking at me.
Amazing!
You're always there.
Thank you very much.
I'll show you the secret of the secret.
Okay.
The next day
Oh!
You did it!
Contact!
This is so much fun!
It's floating so much!
I thought I could do it with this.
What is this?
It feels good!
This is so fun!
This is fun too!
This is fun!
Now, the important part, the ear-picking practice.
Let's go!
Please play the song!
Please!
Hurry up!
I don't know what you're doing.
It doesn't hurt yet, right?
It's not good to do it like this.
I can't do it.
I want to wear it more.
It's too deep.
I'm scared.
I want to do it here.
You lied.
My legs!
And he wears the earthenware.
I'll put the legs in.
Wow!
I'm so tired.
You've been doing this for a long time.
What should we do? Let's go.
Hamada, if you're free, let's go diving.
I'm going to get stuck.
I'm not going to let you go.
Hamada shows his high tension.
Will he be able to finish the photo shoot smoothly?
Alright!
Why are you laughing?
You're not a pro! What are you doing?
I'm doing a butterfly knot.
No way!
I'm sorry.
A shoulder knot.
Next, breathing training underwater.
From the top.
Where?
From the bottom.
This is the first time for Hamada, a beginner.
I can't do it!
I can't do it here!
After a few practice sessions, Hamada is gradually getting used to the water.
The other members are breathing through their noses.
Up until now, it seems like everyone has been doing well in scuba diving.
I feel like I'm the only one who's breathing heavily.
It's because you're too much of a swimmer.
Too much of a swimmer?
I think I'll be fine today.
I'll change my swimming style here.
Yes, yes.
Is this okay?
It's okay.
Yes, it's okay.
Mr. Kawabata, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Okay.
Yes!
Okay, then.
Yes.
This is, um,
Mr. Totsumon wants to learn how to do this.
Yes.
How to deal with the water when the mask is soaked.
I see.
Yes, please.
May I?
Yes.
Listen to me. Are you listening?
Yes, I am.
You are not listening.
I am listening.
Are you okay?
I feel like a city person.
I don't know.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Sometimes water comes into the mask.
So, when you push here and look up and when water comes in, you say,
Ha!
Yes.
Do it.
Ha!
I can't hear you.
You can't just say,
Huuuwaaa!
You have to stick it on.
Let's try it.
Put it in.
It's in.
It's scary, isn't it?
Wait, wait, wait.
Ouch!
It's a pervert!
And the way to deal with troubles underwater.
Next, remove the regulator.
What do you mean?
Maybe you can remove the regulator.
No, it's not like that. Do it properly.
Why can't I do it?
Remove it.
If you bump into it.
And then, the other regulator.
There's another one.
There is, right?
Please give it to the person next to you.
Eh, you remove it from the inside and it comes in with water.
There's this button, right?
Yeah.
Push it hard.
Then the air won't go in.
What?
What are you talking about?
I'll kill you!
I'm going to kill you!
I'll kill you.
The water won't go in.
Ah, I see.
I can't believe you can do such a good thing!
Let's try it.
I'll do it.
I'll push it.
Really?
Everyone is passing the regulator to the person next to them.
Will he succeed?
Don't make me laugh!
Please forgive me!
That's right!
Listen to me! You don't talk to me at all!
You don't talk to me at all!
I'm doing this, but you don't talk to me at all!
Hamada is not doing well at all.
He is being taught by everyone and he is challenging himself.
You are breathing in slowly.
You are breathing in?
Yes.
And then you add this and then you do this.
Ready?
You are weak.
You are kind.
Are you okay?
Okay, I'm ready!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I did it, right?
I did it, I did it.
Okay, good.
A commemorative photo of waiting.
Let's go to the last gate.
As a commemoration of today, let's take a picture at the pool.
It's not there.
No, no, no, let's take it there.
This is my ideal.
Oh, that's right.
Well, I know it's bright, but the ideal is.
This is impossible.
Because I have a bench ready for you.
Well, maybe, but I can't go that far.
Dan-dan-san, please put it in the middle.
Is this a goggles?
Do I take it off?
Yes, you do.
Oh, it's red!
This is the real one, but it's still red!
It's a good thing that you're with Mr. Warakawa.
If you're the one who's going to be the one who's going to be finished,
it's going to be a mess.
That's dangerous.
So, shall we start now?
First, for example, if something happens,
like if you get sick or get injured,
the person on your side will be responsible for it,
I'll make it my own fault.
Please sign this.
You're crazy.
I'm the one who's to blame.
This has nothing to do with me.
You signed it, right?
Okay, I signed it.
Okay.
So, 5 meters...
If you're 5 meters away, I'm telling you to blow your head off.
Let's have two people take this.
Just the two of us?
When?
I'll take this off and leave it on after everyone takes it off.
Just for you, Bantam?
No, for you, Bantam.
This is the pose.
Ehh?
Is it a pose for a comedy?
A pose for a comedy.
This is the 5-meter long drinking set.
Each person will go down to this place.
First, Yamazaki.
Good luck!
Wow, he did it!
He's going for the omega!
Wow, I'm impressed.
He's a fool, he's not going to be hurt.
I'm going to go.
How can you stand on the ground?
If you go down, you'll break.
Oh, really?
Hurry up.
Because he's a gay.
I don't understand what you're saying.
I'm getting more and more confident.
I'm going to go down.
I'm sure I'll explode again.
It's a shocking video.
I don't know. I'm so used to this TV program.
You can be careful.
Well, that's it.
Yes.
I'm doing it for 10 years.
I'll do my best.
It was fun today.
I'm doing it for 10 years on TV.
Yes, it was really fun today.
Thank you very much.
I'll prepare a meal for you later.
I'll be a pervert.
Can they take a commemorative photo at 5 meters?
The two people left in the downtown.
If you say you can't go to Hamada, I won't be there.
Let's go!
I'm sorry.
Kamata failed.
You should have put the end down.
It's hard.
This is nothing.
Let's go.
It's a running town.
There he is.
He's going.
I can't do it.
My ears hurt.
My head is getting swollen.
Failed again.
I'll try it.
My head and ears hurt.
I'm tired.
Please take a deep breath.
I'm going to be here all the time.
I want to hear it loud and clear.
Matsumoto fails too.
He can't go down to the bottom.
Here, Matsumoto will do a side challenge!
Matsumoto has shown his hard work.
There's only one Hamada left.
And the final challenge.
Hamada is desperately trying to take a photo.
The photo that will be a big hit will be announced later.
Are you taking a photo?
I didn't see it.
The group has a pose, so it's hard to move.
Oh, I see.
It's like a finished product.
It's the 10th anniversary.
It's a beautiful photo.
It's a good one.
I'll keep it safe.
I saw everyone from above.
I'm counting on you.
It's a photo that's a gift for the viewer.
Of course.
It's a good one.
I've been holding my nose all the time.
The challenge that the always cowardly Downtown has done, which seems reckless
Their courage has given us a sense of emotion
Thank you, Downtown
This is a memorable scene
And a splendid 2 shot of downtown!