Next time, we'll be visiting the idols of the next episode of Gaki no Tsukai!
Tama-chan, are you coming?
How do you feel about the time difference?
What do you mean by the time difference?
If you go to see Tama-chan, you'll see the time difference.
It's the time difference.
It's the time difference?
We haven't seen it yet.
That's right.
You want to see it?
You want to see it, right?
Of course!
If it's Tama-chan, it's fine if she loses the popularity
I'll accept the loss
Tama-chan!
Suddenly appeared, Tama-chan who has become popular all over Japan
Recently she has been in Yokohama and the world has become Tama-chan fever
Tama-chan is going to meet a child's servant
If we go anyway, it's not just us, it's a child too
Oh, that's great!
It's a good thing.
We'll do something good, right?
Let's have them come up.
Please come up!
Yay!
Thank you!
If this was a normal version,
there would be a little kid and a little old man.
A little kid.
A real little kid.
It's rare for kids to do this.
It's rare.
How old are you?
How many years are you in elementary school?
Three years.
3 years, 4 years.
You can do it in 3 years too.
4 years, 4 years.
It's 4 years.
It's okay.
This program was brought to you by the sponsors.
We're here!
This is the first time we're here, right Tama?
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
I wonder if Tama-chan is here.
There are normal people but isn't it cool?
What's cool?
Don't be silly.
It's not cool.
I don't think there is.
I don't know if there is.
I want to see Tama-chan.
I don't think there is.
But there are 100 of them.
You have to see them.
I don't think there is.
There is.
Let's call them together.
Really?
Ready, set, go!
Tama-chan!
Stop it!
That's not cool.
It's not cool.
Hey, you're weird.
Everyone's acting like idols.
I'm still laughing, but if you read it, it might come out.
Ready, set, go!
Stop it!
Tama-chan!
No, that's not Tama-chan.
That's not Tama-chan.
That's...
Hey.
Ah!
He's famous! He's famous!
I'm not famous!
Ice cream is so strange at this time!
It's not strange!
Tama-chan, isn't he here today?
Tama-chan?
He's not here!
Look! He's not here!
Is that so?
He's not here? Where did he go?
I'm sorry.
I heard that he's seen a lot in the nearby center.
Center?
He's seen a lot!
I can see Tama-chan!
You can see her?
Yes, I can see her.
Let's go then.
Thank you very much.
This is good information.
Please do your best.
Where is she?
In the bathhouse.
I don't understand. Why is Tama-chan in the bathhouse?
I don't know.
It's strange that a new girl is in the bathhouse.
Don't say new girl. It's Tama-chan.
That's why.
Here, here.
Oh, it's you.
Alright, see you guys!
I'll go take a look.
I want to see you.
I'll be right there.
Call me when you're there.
What?
What's wrong?
He's not here.
Look at him.
I'm sorry.
Why are you so angry?
Then, let's start from Tamagawa again.
No, no.
But it's frustrating.
Hey!
What?
Which one?
Hey!
Look! Look!
It's Tamagawa!
It's true!
It's not!
It's Tamagawa!
Shut up!
One, two!
Tamagawa!
It's embarrassing, so stop it.
I did it!
I did it! Look at that!
Say it!
I did it!
It's embarrassing!
It's embarrassing, so stop it.
Wow, amazing!
It's different.
Why?
Oh, it disappeared.
It's amazing.
It's good that you could see it.
What are you going to do?
Tama-chan
Tama-chan?
If you find her, go to the Yabuya store
That's dangerous
Really?
Who asked you to do that?
Yabuya-san
Let's go
Where is Yabuya?
What's with that attitude?
Where?
Yabuya-san
Thank you
Tama-chan, Tama-chan.
I don't have it.
You were completely fooled.
Hey, hey.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Well, Yagura-san...
Let's go.
What?
What's wrong?
Tama-chan is...
Tama-chan.
One, two, three!
Tama-chan!
Don't say that!
Listen to me, Tama-chan!
You're looking at me with those eyes!
No, I'm not!
You're not!
I'm not looking at you!
You are!
No, I'm not!
Huh?
It's gone.
Excuse me, where did Tama-chan go?
Tama-chan went to the bowling alley up ahead.
Please, old man!
Bowling hall!
There's no way I can get better than this!
You can watch it over and over again!
Right?
The one watching that is cuter.
That one is cute.
Hey!
Isn't that Tama-chan?
Bowling hall?
Tama-chan!
Okay, one, two!
That's not fair!
Ready, set...
Tama-chan!
Wow, amazing!
I'm also a Tama-chan!
Amazing! I'm so happy!
This is really Tama-chan!
Really!
Really...
Is that Tama-chan?
Which one is it?
It's Tama-chan!
It's not!
Ready, set...
Tama-chan!
It's not!
It's not, it's not
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
It's completely different
It's totally different
There's no way there's a girl here
It's so cold
It's so cold!
You're so noisy
Tama-chan!
There are people here, and it's so noisy.
I can't imagine going out.
It's impossible.
There's no one over there.
There's no one.
Let's go.
You don't know?
What happened?
Hey!
I got it!
What?
What happened?
I got it!
It was at number 66.
Number 66?
He threw it.
What?
Sad
Ok booming new boy
Tom&
Mahno
What?
Ok booming new boy
Tama-chan!
Wow, amazing!
Amazing!
They moved, they moved!
They moved!
Wow!
Ready, set...
Tama-chan!
Shut up, you guys!
It's been a while since we've seen this.
They're moving so fast!
Yeah!
Is that really just one?
It's a family!
Wow!
Tama-chan, you are great!
We saw it!
It's great!
Tama-chan!
What?
It's great!
Tama-chan!
Let's go!
The end
But when we started filming,
I didn't think we would see so much of Tama-chan.
I didn't think so.
It's the first time we've seen her.
Let's go home.
It's great.
What?
What is this?
It's Tama-chan!
It's the pride of the group!
I'll do it with the people of the Eagle Bomb!
Ready, set...
Tama-chan!
It's funny!
It's full of Tama-chan!
Tama-chan!
Amazing!
That's great!
Hey!
What?
The next day
The boy who is close to the baby
Baby baby
Gari Gari
The next day
Good evening
Hello, good evening
The other day, I was having dinner with Kim and his junior, Chihara.
He asked me to go to a tea shop.
I asked him where he could find tea in this neighborhood.
He said, let's go to the place that is a little far from Harajuku.
I asked him where it is.
He said, I don't know.
I was wondering if I had been to Harajuku.
I was a little far from Omotesando.
I don't know where I was.
I said, I had been there three times.
I don't know.
It's hard to understand.
I don't know if I've been to Harajuku.
I said, let's go.
I remember the car.
I was close to the car.
I stopped the car.
I said, I remember it!
I don't remember stopping my car here.
Everyone thought I was stupid.
But I was like, it's just a car.
Because, you know, with me...
You have memories with me.
I have memories with you.
I said, what is this?
I came here three times, I clearly remember that!
I said, this way!
And I walked like this.
I've never seen anything like this.
I thought.
I said, well, well, well, look at it later, look at it later.
Ah, excuse me, here it is.
I said, I'll definitely say it.
It doesn't turn here.
I turned around and looked at it, and it was gone.
It was gone, but it was in Okonomiyachi.
I said, huh? It's gone.
I said, really?
Was there?
I was like, was there a satin?
He treated me like a fool.
I was so annoyed.
I told him that there was a satin.
I told him to come.
I went in and said,
excuse me, this was a satin shop about 8 months ago, right?
He said, yes.
Look!
I said, look, there's a counter in the movie theater, and I remembered that it was here.
He said, I don't remember at all.
I said, why?
He said, excuse me, I don't know the contact information of the master of the pizza shop.
He said, I don't remember.
I said, I don't remember.
He said, if you look for it, you might know.
He said, look for it. I want to contact you.
These three are here.
I said, wait a minute, I want to find a lot of small ones.
I remembered!
I said, I've been here three times!
I said, I'll come to Yamashita now.
Oh!
Well, that's the way it is.
I said, I'll come to Yamashita now!
I said, I'll contact the old man in the main building.
I was like, wow, that's a lot of calls!
That's enough.
That's enough, but I wasn't ready for that.
I was already drawn to it.
I was like, I'll call them later and tell them to clean up properly.
I was like, let's go to a different place.
I was like, you guys are hopeless!
You weren't wearing any of those?
I didn't say a word.
It's cold.
I'm getting a bit of a blur.
But there are things like that, right?
There are things like that, right?
Everyone's talking and...
When did you hear that?
You're saying it like it's new information.
It's like, do you know?
That's a lot of Yamazaki.
You're the one who asked.
You said something like a comedy to me!
I told you twice!
I'm sorry.
You didn't say it until the end.
I'm sorry, I made a mistake.
I didn't say it.
It's embarrassing.
I think the people in Okonomiyaki were surprised.
You said it that much?
I suddenly came in and I was very angry.
I thought I'd do something really stupid.
Well, well, you have to be careful. You're already 40.
You should be careful.
I said it earlier, but when you get to this age, you'll be left with the same tiredness as the day before.
That's a big deal.
No, no, no. I'm not tired. I'm still tired. I did something yesterday and I'm still tired.
You're still tired.
Oh, really?
Yes.
And that's why you're tired.
I'm tired!
What did you do yesterday that made you feel sick?
What?
What did I do?
Don't be so sick!
Masumoto-san, please tell us how to get into the gray zone.
How to get into the gray zone?
Ah, there are many ways.
There are no ways.
You can't get in.
I can get in.
How did you get in?
Well, I'm in various studios, you know.
I'm in various studios, you know.
I can go to those places, you know.
No.
No, I don't know what you're talking about.
I can't get in, can I?
I can take a bar-like thing and...
No.
I want to say that.
I'm not.
You've been doing it with 4 people, but you've done it with 5 people.
No, that's not true.
So you're good at it.
If you say that, we call it downtown.
What's downtown?
Two old men are doing it.
If you say that you want to go downtown, I don't want to stop you.
With 3 people or 4 people.
It's hard to do.
Three people?
I can do it all by myself.
I don't need two people for that.
I know that.
But this is not good.
I don't know about the gray.
Why? Because there is a part of the instrument.
Yes, there is.
What do you want to add and what do you want to remove?
Why do you think that the gray should be four people?
No, I don't feel uncomfortable if one person enters.
If you say that, it's a f***ing f***er.
One person left and another one joined.
I don't care about that.
Your way of saying it is f***ing f***er.
If you say that, there is no one in the CC Girls anymore.
You are the first one.
You are completely changed.
Well, that's like the read-and-sell giant army.
What?
There are no former Titans.
There are Titans and Shishi.
And there is also a pirate.
I don't know.
I have been doing this for a long time.
If a person enters the game,
I think the person watching TV will be surprised.
I think so.
I think I can't enter the game.
I think I'm fine.
Really?
I'm asking you.
I'm not asking you to borrow money, I'm asking you to teach me properly.
How to get in.
I'm asking you now, how to get in.
I'm asking you to borrow money.
The best way to get in is to have a disciple.
The question is who to ask.
Who should I ask?
A disciple of Grey.
Someone like Amagappa.
I think it's the worst.
Why?
Why? The leader is a genius.
You're not a genius. You're not a genius.
You wrote the poem yourself, right?
There's a harsh part.
It's a sweet cup.
If you put out a cucumber...
I'm sorry.
Your hair is like that, so it's not like you're a cucumber.
It's not a cucumber.
It's okay.
You don't have to be so excited.
You have to be a takuro to express yourself.
In Amagappa.
But if Amagappa says it, it's no use being a takuro.
What's with takuro? Don't just come in.
It's like that.
I said, I'm sorry.
He only read the sweet words.
No, you're getting angry. Go home.
He said, Porin Porin from Ki.
Why did you hide it?
Why did I hide it?
There are hundreds of wounds on Matsumoto's whole body.
He remembers everything, who was which and who was which.
Ah, yes, yes.
What is the third scar between the split of the butt?
That is...
The queen of Gotanda.
Pah!
It's recent.
The queen of Eri.
This guy is so stupid.
This is the Queen of the Uguizudani.
Hey, stop it!
You only talk about the Queen.
You don't even talk about the one who fought with someone.
You only talk about the Queen of Gisa.
I can't accept all of that.
Are you saying that you are fighting?
I'll tell you, but there is no such thing.
What?
I'll tell you the truth.
Wait, wait, wait!
I'm really not!
I'm not a bug!
I know that!
What do you mean you're not a bug?
Sometimes there are people who really think so.
I'm not a bug or a candle, I don't use words.
What do you mean?
Everyone is mistaken.
If I say something like this, you will take it seriously.
I have a chikubi and a kanji as much as you think.
Don't you know what a chikubi and a kanji are?
I don't think so.
I have a kanji as much as you think.
But even if you don't have a position, everyone thinks so.
I think so.
That's a really big mistake.
But I think M is M.
M is M, M is M, but even if you go to the sex life, you do it with your nipples.
It's not like that.
I don't know what you think.
I say something like, it's not like that.
Please make it a conversation.
It fits like anything.
And I can't even speak.
I'm serious!
I hate you!
I can't even laugh!
Ah, I see.
I understand that.
I'll do a little skit.
You can't get into it, can you?
Yes, yes, yes.
I'll do it however I want.
But surprisingly, I can read the paper.
Ah, the words?
I can't even think!
I don't know what will happen next.
If that happens, I can't do it at all.
I can't do it.
I'll destroy it.
The 80 minute course.
It's long.
Can't you just let me see it?