The next day
Hmm...
It's cramped.
It's cramped, right?
You're sitting down.
But, Mr. Kokiuchi's lyrics are...
Mr. Kokiuchi's lyrics are impossible.
That's fine, though.
It's cramped.
Good morning!
Oh, you're here!
Long time no see.
Good morning!
I was doing a recording in the neighborhood, so I came to say hello.
All of them?
I was busy earlier
You won the R1
The flower of light
The R1 Grand Prix that will decide the best in Japan for the ping-pong player
Out of the 1239 people that entered this year, the old man won
Look at that, he's got something on his nose
I've seen it
I want to see it
You can't do that now, can you?
No, I can.
Really?
No, it's a sign.
Sign?
It's not how you use it.
It's in there.
That's a lot.
It's always there.
It's a sign.
Do you want to see it?
I'm going to do this.
He's an interesting guy.
I'll do it for you.
I see.
I like it.
You can clean it.
You can clean it?
It's like a paper.
It's a mental thing.
I can't see it.
Wow.
It's amazing!
It's the same as before!
You can do it like this.
Wow, this is amazing!
This is a wonderful technique!
This is the Noodle Rope.
Noodle Rope!
Wow, amazing!
It's moving!
I can't get it.
Is it the basic Udon?
The basic is Udon.
But can you get the general ones?
I think I can get the general ones.
But I can't get the ones sold in the supermarket.
I think I can.
I want to see it.
Can I go to the supermarket?
Can you buy it for me?
I want to try many things.
I have time.
You have time?
Yes.
I've been told to go around this area.
You can go around as much as you want.
You have no time at all.
Really?
It's okay.
That's right.
Let's go.
Let's hurry.
Yes.
Super.
Super is here.
That's right.
This program is brought to you by the sponsors of the following episodes.
Ah, but this is not bad.
It's good.
It's not bad.
I want you to try the sashimi.
This is not bad.
It's not bad.
This is a bit of a surprise.
Kimchi.
This is a surprise.
This is a big surprise.
We can't think of something like this is impossible.
Let's try it.
There's this much. You can put this much in.
Oh, you can do it?
This is a nice toy.
I can do this.
The staff members are doing it well.
This is easy.
Oh, you can do this?
Really?
Well, I can do it.
You can do it.
It's not a fake.
I can do it.
The result is...
Yay!
Thank you for waiting!
It was pretty tough.
We won a lot.
We didn't even have to change the color.
Should we just take it out?
Well, yeah.
I don't really care about the packaging.
Ah, this should be fine.
This is also a safe bet.
Safe bet.
You can take the root.
Eh?
It's bitter.
It's bitter?
It's bitter!
Ah, I see.
Leave it to the old man.
It's so annoying.
Can I use the Kiyomend?
Ah, Kiyomend.
Eh?
I'll do it.
I want to do it.
I want to do it even more.
How can I do it?
I want to cut it.
But it's a knife.
Ah, I can't cut it straight away.
I see.
How was it?
It's so good!
It was so good!
Let's do it from here.
Even though it's not like you can't eat it.
I'm so hungry.
It was so good.
You can eat it smoothly.
I can do it easily.
What is this?
This is too thin.
It's too thin.
This is impossible.
This?
There are many kinds of
things.
Ah, here?
Ah, that's good.
It's not a slug.
It's a raccoon.
I want to do it too.
You have to do it with the energy.
Oh, you're going to use a ball?
If it's too thin, it will be...
It will be a shabby ball.
Water?
Why are you doing that?
It's like a spear.
Oh, it's going.
Oh.
Oh!
You look a little scared.
Yes, yes.
What's wrong?
Where did you go?
There's a letter of return on your face.
It's you!
What's a return?
It's this.
This?
Oh, this is it.
This is a return.
Is this a return?
It's a return.
Really.
If it's the other way around...
Oh, it's the other way around.
Yes.
I'll try to turn it over.
Oh, this is good.
Ah!
That's the scary face.
It's scary.
Wow, wow, wow.
Oh, it's good.
It's not reaching.
The length is...
This is bad.
It's just right.
Get out, get out.
Ah, this...
That's right!
You're too close!
I can't do this!
You can do this!
Ah, Zenmai!
That's not right.
You have to look at it from the nose.
Ah, that's right!
Ah, this is also bamboo.
Bamboo is also...
Ah, it's coming!
It's coming!
I can see it from here.
I can see it.
It's in my throat.
Did you fall down?
Don't bite me!
It hurts!
It hurts so much!
Every time...
Don't fail in many ways!
I'm eating it!
I don't want to eat it!
That was great!
It was really good.
It's good.
This is the technique.
The angle is really...
That's a great technique.
He's moving in such detail.
He's actually working.
What are you doing?
This is bad.
Are you going to eat this?
It's so good!
Amazing!
I'm going to eat it all!
It's so easy!
This is a squid!
It looks like a squid!
I'll succeed!
I'll eat it all!
This is good!
Please!
Oh!
The finish is...
It's been 90 years!
You can do it for 90 years!
It's too smooth!
It's not going to stop!
The finish is all smooth!
Smooth!
Slowly!
You're doing it too fast!
It won't stop!
It's too smooth!
This is good!
That's a BGM!
This is the success pattern
In Japan, we call it the Dabaku Daisetsu
What's this?
It's a toy that you put on your head
This is completely...
It's easy to do
If you cut here, you cut here
It's very fast
Isn't this easy too?
This is udon, right?
Yes, it is.
Wow, it smells so strong.
It's coming out.
Is it a bitan?
Eh? You're lying, right?
Amazing!
This is too easy.
Did you sell it at the supermarket?
I sold it at the supermarket.
I think it's possible.
Really?
It's possible.
It's not too thin.
I didn't know that.
You connect the one that came out.
I see.
If I'm not good at this, I'll be free-passed for the rest of my life.
Free-passed anywhere.
This is dangerous.
Oh, I see.
This is easy.
Easy?
How can I say this?
This is great!
This is really...
This is a free pass!
This is great!
Ladies and gentlemen
Good evening!
I'll do it.
There are many people.
Yes.
There are many.
But, you know, you lost 2 games of soccer, but you're still in good shape, right?
I didn't lose.
Oh, really?
I'm still playing.
If you say so, it's a little funny.
Are you a little worried?
I'm not worried. I'm not interested.
I wonder.
I'm not interested at all.
I'm not interested either.
But aren't you worried?
What do you mean?
It's like, I'm going to talk to Matsumoto Eide soon.
That's what I think.
Why do people get so enthusiastic?
It's only at times like that.
I don't usually say that.
You don't see it, do you?
It's funny because there are no people.
It's like high school soccer.
In the daytime,
It's a little creepy.
It's creepy.
If I say too much, it's like, no, I can't.
Why? Don't you want to say it?
You want me to say it?
Which one?
I don't understand Japanese
Well, I'm sure you all don't know
I was looking at the dressing room
There were three balls this time
Why did you put three balls?
I was just looking at the dressing room
I heard that you always say,
Aue Aue, when it comes to soccer.
Aue Aue.
You always say that.
Aue!
Why?
You don't say that in other sports.
Why do you always say that in soccer?
Like, the iron country.
Why?
The iron country?
It's not like that.
Whether it's baseball or volleyball,
you do it in other countries.
You don't say that often.
You say that a lot in soccer.
Yes, yes.
Why is your mental state so weak?
You want to go home immediately.
I don't know that.
Everyone says that.
Everyone is like a worm.
I still don't know the answer.
Why is that?
It's just a way of saying it.
I say it so often. The soccer players say it a lot.
No, no, no.
Only me?
I'm the...
Aoi?
I don't want to say that.
I heard about how you change your mood.
What do you mean?
I thought I'd tell you.
I change my mood?
Well, it's a bit expensive.
Yes, yes.
You know, there's that thing, right?
You do it with people who think, right?
Yes, yes.
There is an object there.
The one between me and you.
Ah, there is, there is.
That object is...
How much does it cost?
That object.
Mine is...
585,000 yen.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's quite expensive, though it's a styrofoam.
That's right.
And Hamada's is 485,000 yen.
When I asked where this difference of 100,000 yen came from,
it was a bit hard to say.
No, no, it's because he's famous.
If he's famous, Hamada-san's face will be more prominent.
Ah, so it's a work of making it.
It's okay if you don't dig so deep.
It will take 10 years.
Ah, that's interesting.
It will take a lot of time.
It's like that.
It's like a good thing.
I see.
I don't have any feelings for you.
That's why.
Ah, I see. That's why it changed.
I see.
I thought I'd tell you that.
Thank you very much.
Now!
Shall we announce the correct answer?
What?
The correct answer...
This is a question for Matsumoto, the hero of the entertainment world.
I heard that you have seen the Ultraman from the rebellious period.
What kind of behavior did you do?
It was really amazing.
What?
First, I broke the door.
I didn't go home for three minutes.
Oh, I see.
It was like it had nothing to do with me.
I said,
Alright!
Scary!
It was scary.
That's not what you want from me, is it?
No, no, it's not that...
I was wondering what kind of way you were acting in the rebellious period.
Ah, I was acting really bad.
For example, how?
Eh?
What kind of way?
What kind of way do you mean?
No, no, that's not it.
You've seen the rebellious period drama, haven't you?
Of course.
You haven't? Which one?
I haven't.
You didn't say that before!
I'm asking because I have it!
You haven't, have you?
I haven't, I haven't.
I'm just imagining it.
Apologize.
I should apologize?
Sorry.
Matsumoto-san, when you went to play with your brother in the forest, you found a candy store. Is that true?
Don't lie, Matsumoto.
Hurry up and show me the soccer.
I have that kind of feeling.
This is true.
But!
If you imagine a house of sweets that often appears in movies or movies, that's a big mistake.
In reality, it's not that gorgeous.
It's a little lower budget.
It costs that much?
Yes.
How is it?
Basically, it's all covered with miso.
It's all over the place.
When it's over, it's like a house of sweets.
It's like a house of miso.
It's like the miso of the Miso Dengaku.
It's like,
What is this, Nii-chan?
This is a bit too much!
This is not the way it should be!
It's like Japanese style.
The window is also...
What is it made of?
It's like a niko-gori.
It's soft and fluffy.
It's quite thick.
There are many small shrimps in it.
Oh, big brother!
What are you looking at?
I can't see anything because it's so thick.
Most of the shrimps are moving.
It's not shrimp, big brother.
It's sweet.
Well, it's sweet.
The door knob is like a poop of a turban shell.
Oh, I see.
It's deep green and it's like a burr.
Oh, it's disgusting, big brother.
It's sweet.
It's not sweet.
Well, well, well, we stayed for one night.
You can't stay?
Well, it's my house, so I can't stay.
Really? So you had a bed?
I had a bed.
What did you make of the bed?
What?
That was made of wood.
You can't eat all the curtains!
It's a pain in the ass.
The curtain was Yuba.
I can understand that.
I told him not to say that.
Who said that?
You.
You said that?
Because it's my house.
So there are people living there.
Who?
People with a lot of guts.
They always stay there.
Nii-chan, you're so sweet.
That sweetness is different!
If Hamada-san died first, what would you put in the coffin?
What would you put in the coffin?
I would put in things I like.
I want to do many things for you.
You like yakisoba, right?
I like yakisoba. Don't say that.
I'm not a person who likes it.
I'm dirty.
You're dirty.
Why do you care about it?
And then you put the fried noodles in.
And then you put ginger in here.
You put in the ginger.
That's good.
It's normal.
And then you put in a lot of erotic DVDs.
There's no place for you to put them in.
There's a lot of them!
If you move them, there's still more down there.
Don't blow it!
Half of the ball is out!
Do it after I put it in!
What are you doing?
I put it in earlier so I can't catch it.
You can't do that with one or two.
But I don't know which is my favorite.
That's fine.
Well, that's that.
I think about that.
And that hamburger.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
If there's a fried egg on a hamburger steak, it'll be a great show.
If there's a fried egg on a hamburger steak...
You can't get excited!
You're saying too much.
I'll put it on the steak.
What?
I'll put the fried egg on the steak.
On the triangle piece.
I'll make a triangle with white meat.
And the middle one is yellow, boom!
I'll do that for you.
And when you close the last one,
If it's stuck,
You'll be like, ahhh!
Don't get it dirty!
At the very end!
I think that's good.
Everyone will cry and say,
Please watch it.
You can't see it from here!
It's covered in yolk!
When you bake it, the yolk will look good!
We'll do it again this year!
In the last sushi battle, these three people were punished.
And this time...
The battle with the Bilibili outlet!
From the 100 outlets, the one who was affected by the power of fear is...
Hanashite!
DVD, 3 consecutive releases!
That hot spring that you must not laugh at, and the trip of a night trip,
The movie, Yuugawara, will be released on DVD soon!
The second half of the movie will be completely recorded!
The fifth volume will be released on June 29th!
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.