This studio is cold.
Yes, it is.
I'm used to it, so I'm trying to wear long sleeves.
He's trying to wear it.
This room was really cold.
I was surprised.
Good morning.
You look good.
I look good.
You look really good.
I can tell from this past.
What day is it today?
It's September 12th.
What's the occasion?
It's my son's birthday.
You know it, right?
September 8th is Matsumoto's birthday.
Today is the 12th.
It's a little past, but...
The Tokyo Olympics...
There are many competitions.
It's really cool.
It would be great if it could be done.
He said to give it to me as a birthday present.
He has been racing in the past 8 races and has made his dream come true
Starting with the world record of high speed racing
He challenges the fastest in the world of racing, the 3 laps
A miracle play in the air
He hits back the 150km high speed ball
A new world record in weightlifting
A 50cm fire limbo dance
He swam 25 meters in 10 seconds
He also challenged the swimming skills of the team
The 58 year old Matsumoto will challenge this time
Let's see what he's got
Let's see this
Basketball
It's here
What is this?
Did you see that?
This! This! This!
This!
Here! Here!
This is really cool!
You wanted to do this?
I wanted to do a Hollywood dunk.
No, no, no, no.
Dunk?
But if you guys do it, you'll let me do it, right?
I have a lot of confidence.
Do it quickly.
Quickly?
It's your birthday, but do it quickly.
If you can, then do it properly
Everyone, let's change into black clothes
Let's change
For Matsumoto's dream, the Black Clothes Week has come after 2 years
Matsumoto Hitoshi decides on the ARIUFU
The big guy is the most...
Yes.
...thick.
But he's quite tall.
He's quite tall.
He's tall.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Did you hear anything?
I did.
He's 58, but he's like a Japanese chord.
He has a sense of
Yes.
Did you explain it properly?
Yes, I did.
What kind of way did you say it?
What kind of way?
Somehow, that technique...
Sorry, I didn't see the part of the dance.
Somehow, I heard rumors that it was done quickly and it was over quickly.
And, to say the truth, Mr. Hosei said it.
I admitted it.
Then, let's do it.
Don't push me.
I'm sorry.
Lift it up and go down.
Excuse me.
Legs.
I can't put any strength.
You can't put any strength.
It's easier to do if you put strength.
I can't do it.
I'll do it.
OK.
Ready, set, go!
Ouch!
What is this?
Put it down slowly.
This is too heavy.
Bring a mat.
I'm sorry.
I'll use the mat.
You can use that.
You can use this to get a hit.
I can use this to get a hit.
I'm not that happy.
When I'm waiting for you to get ready,
you should stand up properly.
I don't have to say anything.
Okay, then.
If you jump and come to the right position,
I'll do this.
Please do it at the right timing.
I'll do it.
Excuse me.
Ready, set, go!
Here we go.
It's going well.
Bounce here.
Put your feet on it.
You can't stand up.
Ready, set, go!
This is good, isn't it?
Here, here.
That's right, that's right!
More, more, more!
Keep going, keep going, keep going!
Raise it, raise it, raise it!
1, 2, 3!
Alright!
Okay!
Ouch!
Here!
Yes!
I heard something.
Masumasa?
When I went to the other side, I heard a small voice.
My armpit hurts.
You're a fool.
Seriously.
Who was it?
The one who was doing this.
Was it you?
Are you angry?
I don't think I'm angry.
I just said I wanted to sing.
It hurts a little.
If I'm not angry, I can't say, wow.
I said, let's do it.
I said, I can't do it anymore.
I said, it's okay.
So you wrote it because you thought it was good.
Yes.
Excuse me.
You don't have to do it anymore?
I have a sideburn.
I have to have all the Japanese energy.
You know what?
I know that they are not going to succeed.
No, no, no.
I know that, you guys.
That's not going to happen.
They are not motivated from the beginning.
They are serious.
I'm telling you to lend me your strength!
Why are you crying?
You're the one who's telling me to do this.
You're the one who's telling me to lend me my strength.
On the contrary.
I've lost all my strength.
You don't want to be a glutton?
That's what I'm saying.
You can't do that yourself.
Why are you asking me if I have a military service when I'm over 8 years old?
The second challenge, receiving a complaint from Matsumoto
Is this okay?
I think it's okay
But it's not as much of a burden as it was before
But either way...
Ah, please.
Ah, somehow...
He's in a good mood.
Maybe I said too much.
Sorry, I think I said too much.
But I think that if you don't have one feeling, you won't succeed.
We're definitely friends that can be understood.
Except for Inamoto.
Eh?
He's not hooked on it.
Let's do it.
Masumoto-san, please come here.
Please.
Let's go.
There is something to be attached.
Should I turn it over?
Yes, please.
Please turn it over.
Please attach it.
Let's go.
I'm going to fill the meat. I can do it.
I can do it.
This is bad.
It's hard.
Don't shake it.
Did you do the simulation?
It's okay. I did it.
Do it slowly.
Do it like the simulation.
If you can put it on, you can get the license.
Okay.
What kind of simulation did you do?
The age of simulation.
Tell me the age of the person who did the simulation.
Okay, let's start.
Please.
Don't put the ball in.
The start is okay.
The ball.
Ready, go.
It's heavy.
Goal!
Turn the ball towards you.
OK, OK, OK.
Why is your hand on Inoue's shoulder?
You have to put it in with this.
It's important to catch the ball with your hand.
That's right.
Ready, go!
I'll do it.
Goal!
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Wait, wait, wait.
Mr. Matsumoto!
That can't be on the screen.
That was probably...
When he jumped,
his face was already on the screen.
Really?
I can't reach them.
But he said,
Thank you very much.
I think he said,
It's OK.
If you don't want to quit, then quit.
Let's go home.
We've done what we had to do.
We can't do anything more than that.
The next day
Excuse me.
I thought of giving up the trombone and lifting it up with the power of the balloon.
If there was something unfortunate, I would have given up.
But I think it can't be helped.
They were shouting, ''We're going to cut your flesh!''
It was really scary.
They were actually cutting my flesh.
When they were cutting my flesh,
I don't know who it was,
but there was a guy who was laughing like, ''Keta, Keta, Keta, Keta, Keta, Keta!''
It's not a place to laugh.
Everyone wants to believe,
but they're all idiots.
They can't get anything good out of this.
That's not good.
I'm saying this because I trust you!
Except for Inamoto.
Why?
Right?
So, really,
I can't trust you?
Then, I'll do my best.
Please.
He regains his composure and takes on the third challenge.
Alright, let's go!
I think we can do the next one.
Let's go.
I'm always curious about this mat.
You can ride on the chair like the one before.
You can sleep facing the front.
I think I'll do a simulation.
Yes, you did.
Please sleep facing the front.
I'll set it up.
Which way is my head facing?
Head facing that way.
I'll do a simulation.
What are you eating?
You're so considerate.
Please do it.
A smart kid did a simulation.
I think this is okay.
This is okay.
You should go to a proper university.
This car is really scary.
This car is a simulation car.
What kind of simulation car is this?
I don't know.
Is it a young car?
Yes.
It's too different from the young cars.
There are no simulators for 58 years old.
I want to get poisoned.
Please do it.
It's dangerous.
Help me.
More.
Lower your body.
Let's put it down
If it's this far, it's fine
Is it fine?
Then please try lifting it
I'm going to lift it
It's going to work
It's going
It's coming
It depends on how you pass
What should I do?
This much?
It's close
Next!
Let's go!
Put your hands out!
If you hit here, it will turn
Close!
You can do it!
The direction is...
Close!
It's OK now.
What should I do?
So close!
Matsumoto-san, you can go in a little more.
I want to go in a little more.
It's good, isn't it?
I'll go in a little more.
Matsumoto-san?
Matsumoto-san, you were so worried.
You can go in a little more.
He changed again.
If it was impossible, it would have been better to bend the handle.
I see.
You should have bent it.
Yes, bent it and put it here.
Let's go to say that.
I should have tied it up and done this.
Yes.
Let's go.
Let's go to say that.
Excuse me.
Hello.
I felt like he was being bullied.
He was aiming for the face.
He was saying that he was sorry that he didn't hit the face.
Masao-san, that's a misunderstanding. He was the one who hit the face.
I think it's really important.
It's really bad.
Whether you have the will to do it or not, really.
I can't understand what Mr. Matsumoto is saying.
I know.
I was so surprised.
I can't see what he's saying.
His eyes are all red.
No, he's angry.
Anyone would be angry if he did that.
Think about it.
It's better not to say it.
Of course.
That's the way it is.
Yes.
Please.
Say goodbye.
Yes.
Let's think about it.
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry.
The fourth challenge based on the reflection of the previous one.
You can definitely do it.
Yes, I can do it.
This is the main character.
This is.
It looks like it's in.
Yes, it does.
But Fujiwara, please do this.
The idea is perfect.
If I do my best.
It doesn't hurt.
It's not dangerous.
Thank you.
You want to show your youthful side?
If it's good, everything is good.
Yes.
Let's go.
Why is it dangerous?
Is there a mat in the bedroom?
Well, let's get on it.
Hold it.
Oh, this is dangerous.
Put it on.
Fujiwara, get ready.
Well...
First, put on the helmet.
Put it on.
Put on the helmet properly.
Here we go.
Good, good, good.
Good, good.
Then, pass it.
Hey!
Here it comes!
This is so cool.
So cool.
The ball... the ball...
The ball is out.
Again.
Put the ball back.
There.
Yes.
Be careful.
It's amazing.
Good, good, good!
It's coming, it's coming!
Slowly, slowly!
PON!
It's in!
Congratulations!
It's so messy.
You went in so cleanly.
What's going on?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Did you lose the timing to be happy?
You're being shy.
We were happy at first.
That may have happened.
I'm sorry. I was the first one to say,
I did it.
I was happy.
Let's go apologize.
I'll be done here.
The picture was beautiful.
Excuse me.
If you had to choose, would you say that you were happy that we won first place?
No, I wouldn't say that.
I'd say that it was too cold.
It was cold in many ways.
And I'd say, why did you guys get in the frame?
I want to do it all by myself.
I've been doing it a lot.
Should I do a little of Harapan?
No, that's fine.
No, no.
It's fine.
I don't have to do it.
Excuse me, but...
What is it?
What?
This one.
It's a vegan roller.
Why is the vegan roller here?
I don't know.
You're too much. Your face is red.
It's not red at all.
Will they succeed this time?
The fifth challenge.
This is the last one. Let's decide the best one.
We can do this.
It's okay.
That was the first shot.
That was the first.
It was already over.
He's in a good mood.
I'm sorry.
I'm not angry at all.
I see.
There are many things that happen at the end.
You get hit, you get hit and you turn around.
Life is like a dark night.
I'm not going to be the last one to get hit!
Let's do it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't have the ability to do it.
I'm waiting for you again.
Yes, yes.
Please turn your face this way.
Please lie down.
I'm really not injured.
Let's go.
Please hold on to both sides.
Hold on tight.
Be careful.
Please come in.
Let's start.
Hello.
Okay.
Okay, I got it.
Please.
Perfect.
There is nothing.
Okay.
Hello.
Please.
Is it okay to start here?
OK, let's start!
Yeah!
That was good, wasn't it?
It's over.
He's sleeping.
Is he crying?
He's crying.
He's happy.
There was a guy who covered his face with a cloth.
Hey, I can't breathe for a moment.
You?
Yes.