High Tension The Best Game
At home, High Tension The Best Game!
With what you have at home, you can play the ultimate high tension game. High Tension The Best Game!
There's no pattern at all!
The selection from 297 candidates!
The super exciting game of young comedians!
Let's move on to the 5th place this week!
411 points! My handmade mask, Miki Kosei!
Congratulations!
Is this your first time?
Yes, it is. I got 5th place for the first time.
The room is white, so it looks a little dull.
My wife told me not to show anything other than this room.
I'm really sorry.
What was your job during your self-restraint period?
I'm doing a new comedy show with my brother Asei on Instagram every day.
Is that a PR for Kyoto?
Please stop, Matsumoto-san.
Please stop.
The world has forgotten about it.
What is a PR for Kyoto?
I didn't get it.
I didn't get it. Please stop.
I'm sorry.
He got something, didn't he?
I didn't get it
I will play a part that I have summarized
Please stop it
You got it from Yoshimoto
This week's 5th place
Miki Kosei's My Handmade Mask
My handmade mask is here
Here it is!
Isn't it cute?
I'm wearing my wife's underwear!
My wife's underwear!
There's a ribbon here!
Isn't it cute?
It's a match!
Thank you!
It's here!
Thank you, wife!
I'm not laughing!
I'm not laughing at all!
I'm earning money with this!
Look at me!
Thank you for your wife, Yome.
Thanks to Yome's panty mask.
Thank you very much.
I will do it with gratitude.
Thank you.
Yome.
You finally laughed.
My family is safe and peaceful.
Thank you very much.
Thanks to downtown.
It was Yome's panty mask.
Thank you very much.
Is it a love story?
I told you not to show your room.
I was wearing a pair of pants, but I said ok.
What is this?
Is it just me? I don't like this.
You were sleeping in that.
Let's go back to the announcement of the best 10.
The 4th place is...
554 points.
Tashi-san's favorite, Tom Brown.
First place.
Congratulations!
Hello!
I hate this kid!
Kanoa-san clearly said he hates you.
Well, everyone has their own likes and dislikes, so it can't be helped.
It's not a big deal, is it?
It's an apartment.
It's an apartment?
Do you have a bath?
For the past 50 years, I have a bath.
How many rooms?
It's 4.5 million yen.
What?
If you earn 3 million yen, you can get a bigger place.
No, I didn't get any.
It's like a non-fiction.
It's not enough.
It's not a non-fiction.
I've seen the movie.
According to the staff's information, this person has a woman who calls him on a lonely night.
It's not a good thing.
I love the Philippines pub.
The Philippines pub?
There is a 32-year-old woman named Erica.
Do you go out with her?
No, I don't go out with her.
I went to the pub and got along with her.
I called her a few times during the quarantine.
He laughs at my jokes.
When I call him and say that my face looks like Tamaki, he laughs.
I don't have anything yet, but I hope I can do something good.
What are you talking about?
I'm the one who's talking to you.
It's been so long.
Let's go.
This week's 4th place.
Tom Brown's favorite song.
※opposite song
Hahahaha exceeding...
Hahahahaha
oush!!
THoss ituo
It's to beat
What? What? What!?
Hahahaha
You sang well.
Wakamatsu is singing.
What is this?
It's a soap.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
It was a lot of fun though.
Now, before announcing the 3rd place, let's have a spotlight for this week!
Spotlight
If you have the energy, you can do anything.
The 27th place is Nelson's Wada Manju.
Congratulations!
Yes
I thought you were Kinoshita from TKO
No, I'm not
Manju-san, I heard you have a special skill, please show us
Oh, is that okay?
Yes
Manju-san
You said you have a special skill
It's a down jacket
Down jacket, I see
From the top, white, red, purple, green, and blue
If you choose one color, you can remove it without using your hands
I see
Then, the most difficult one is purple
Purple seems to be difficult
I'll go with the purple one.
No, it's the bottom one.
It's the bottom one.
What the hell?
Except for the blue one.
Except for that one.
Anything else is fine.
I don't know why I can't accept it. It's the most difficult one.
This week's 27th, Nelson's Wada Manju.
If you have the spirit, you can do anything.
I'll put glasses in the boiling water!
I'll do it!
I'll take it!
It's hot!
I can do it!
Damn it!
It's hot!
I took it!
Thank you very much!
Manju-san, you don't look that funny even if you do it on your own.
What are you talking about?
Let's have the next spot light artist come on stage.
Please come on out!
This week, we have the person who was ranked 19th in the list of the most scary person in the world, Mr. Ijiri Okada!
Please welcome him!
Today, we have a person who has a long career.
Ijiri, where are you coming from?
Ijiri, how long have you been doing this?
It's been 33 years.
It's not that different from us.
What about you, Izumi? Is your work hard?
Since the end of March, I've lost all my events.
I see.
I had a lot of work in the
I want to do it.
So, can I do it?
No, no, no. But this is not a council.
No, no, no.
Don't do it.
No.
I don't want to do that.
I don't really want to do that.
I really don't want to do that.
Let's go to the 19th place this week.
Ijiri Okada was too scared to say a word.
Hey! Hey! Look at that face! Hey! Look at that face!
I'm scared! Answer me!
I'm scared!
должны
icte
Dangerous, you'll cut your tongue.
Hey!
Hey, which one?
Which one? Which one?
But it's fine!
Hey!
Bama-ko!
Thank you very much!
Lastly, can you imitate the court?
Sure, I'll do it.
Can I do it?
Yes, you can.
Okay, I got it.
Let's stop it!
What are you doing?
You can touch your wife's nipples from the side.
It's hell.
I'm sorry, I'll call you back.
Out of 297 applicants, the one who unfortunately missed the best score is...
The comedian who was ranked in the last few places.
The combination of Jyaraihoga, Tom Brown and Nunokawa Hiroki.
The winner is...
It's a great balance.
I was a fool!
I was a fool even if I was hit once!
I girl uzog spel on the scale of aof
No no no
He这个 in hycheering
I girl y ci
pharmacy
Submitted
Kitty
じゃない
I want to eat more delicious food!
Delicious food! Eat!
My body is so tired.
Amazing.
My body is so tired. Good job.
So, let's announce the top 3.
This week's third place is...
712 points
2020 Hamada Masato Shoujo, Kogoriko Endo Shoujo
Congratulations
It's a new house, a new house
It's cool
It's a nice house
It came down from the stairs
This is your new home, right? It's close to Shinjuku, right?
Yes, it's been a little over a year.
I haven't been there, but you haven't been to Hama-san?
I've only been to the living room once.
That's right. It was really fun back then. Thank you.
What are you doing now?
Oh, yes. She's next to me right now.
Yes.
The wife behind me.
Chiyaki.
What?
No, no. I'm Masami.
She's looking at her wife, and while looking at her eyes, she's looking at the wife behind her.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
I'm doing this.
Oh, I see.
Today, you are still wearing that kind of clothes!
Stop it!
You are showing too much!
Stop it! Stop it!
Is it really Mr. Inigiri?
Mr. Inigiri?
I heard that you have something you want to do remotely.
It's remote, so when I appear on TV,
I do an interview with Hamada-san,
where he is scratching his neck.
Ah!
It's a customary pattern.
I think you can do it remotely.
You can't touch your wife's nipples from the side.
To my wife?
Yes, just put your hand out and let her touch your nipples.
Masami-chan!
It's a little bit of a sudden thing.
It's okay.
Just put your hand out.
Excuse me, madam.
And then, like I'm doing it, stop it!
I don't want to say stop!
I got it.
Just the hands.
Mr. Endo, how do you feel today?
You are the third place.
Stay home.
Stop!
I can't stand it.
It's a little confusing.
I'm sorry.
The mother touched the father's nipple, but the son came to see it.
It's a hellish sight.
This week's 3rd place,
In the 2020 Hamada Masato Award for the Kojiko Endo Syozo.
It has nothing to do with it.
The bicycle that Mr. Hamada gave me.
The bicycle I got at the New Year's party
I've gone through the security check, but I didn't get caught once yet
So, from now on, I'm going to ride this bicycle, ride it, ride it
I'm going to run, after all, I'm going to run
I'm running
You're not getting on
I can walk on my knees
Alright!
I like that movement
I can read it from your legs
Run
I'm running
Thank you very much
Touch your neck again
I wonder if there was a space.
I think it's a little too much.
How much space is there?
How is it?
Hell.
Hey, hey.
There's a lot of them.
Hell, hell.
The children are fighting.
Next, the second place is...
896 points
He is doing it at home, plus minus, Iwashi Yoshimasa
Congratulations on the second place
Iwashi is the second place
Iwashi-san is the second place after 9 years
I really didn't think I'd rank second.
What did you think?
I thought I'd be 6th.
6th?
Thank you for your surprise.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
Did you get it?
You got it.
It's out.
It's out!
This week's second episode,
Plus or minus Yoshiyoshi Masa is doing
Homemade Good Husband!
Ah, there's a lot of washing stuff.
If you wash it with the oil,
it won't fall off.
It's covered.
You're wearing a bow too?
Look, he's wearing a bow.
You're wearing something.
I got it.
I have to have sc inmates
Oxfam you Giu Mai Pita
The people who just started a party
, a飯!
The flour, don't you.
refuel
Oxfam No Wait
it's different
I'm sorry.
I was surprised.
Social distance!
Thank you.
Who is the winner of the 1st place?
Let's find out!
The winner of this week is...
1st place is...
971 points
God's, Kaminari-sama's, God's request
Tsukitei Hosei
Good evening! Congratulations!
Hello?
It's Osaka, isn't it?
Is it muted?
Isn't it muted?
It's the worst.
Yes.
No, no.
Wait a minute.
Are you alone at home?
Well, I have a daughter, but I also have a son who is 7 years old.
You are very good at armpit sweat.
I'm worried because you touch your armpit again.
I can't help it. It comes out.
It comes out.
The armpit sweat.
It's not a smell.
Let's go.
I'll do it.
This week's first, the moon-shaped law, the god's, the god's, the god's, the god's message.
For the purpose of studying fortune-telling, I've been staying in Kisosan for 52 years.
Today, I'm going to specially study Hamada Masato of Downtown and Matsumoto Itoshi.
obtainortunes.
Theש undesirable events,
and their Physicians,
who,
through the disease of this ей,
follow drugs for an downloads purposeers saying
they will create destroyed realization on this world
that let an efficient trust
to implement the
Aki- أGRkra
Kamen Rider Sumo!!
Ura nauna yo! Ura nauna yo!
Oshiri o, oshiri puri puri ni shite ura nauna yo!
Ura nauna yo!
Hey, something is coming!
Kame kame kame kame!
GOOOOOO!
BAAAAA!
Boku ni ochita! Boku ni ochita!
I lost!
I became a giant fish!
That's the one that's a little bit like Unako!
I did it!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
You had a great voice!
Teacher, you're not good at all!
Everyone, we'll take a commemorative photo at the end
Face the camera and...
High pose!
The past broadcast was broadcast exclusively on Hulu.
Blue Kensa-kun