In the first episode, we will have a remote fanfare with 9 people in a row!
Masuo-san, what is this about?
I'm sure you're familiar with this, but the number of people using the remote is increasing.
It's almost like that.
I thought it would be nice to use the remote to do a fanfare.
What kind of person is this Mentsu?
Yes, I've been told that it's interesting in the interview.
I don't think there's an answer to the question about the lunch.
There are countless kinds of jokes for one topic.
I'm looking forward to the interview.
Then, shall we introduce who the nine people are?
Yes, let's do it.
Everyone!
Who are these nine people?
The hand-shape is also the best.
I think it's better to introduce yourself.
Can you introduce yourself?
It's Yama-chan.
I'm Hosei Nitei, 32 years of my acting career.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Shodo Endo, 29 years of my acting career.
Thank you for coming.
I'm also Koko Riko Tanaka.
I'm honored to be chosen for the interview.
The salaryman who was drunk said that.
Is it okay?
Next is the winner of the 25th year of his career, Shogun Shiragawa.
Please.
Next is...
Good morning.
I'm the 20th year of his career, Daihatsu.
Please take care of me.
I'm sorry!
You're also wearing a big cut.
That's amazing.
I don't have much.
You can wear a big cut if you tuck it in.
That's the difference.
Thank you.
And now, the 14th member of the GYAKUEN GENKURI POCKET, Otake!
Otake-san!
Otake wasn't chosen!
I wasn't chosen.
But, do you need these three?
First, this one.
Hello, I'm Masaharu Fukuyama.
I'm Masaharu Fukuyama.
I'm sleepy. I'm sleepy.
I like you.
But Zaku-shi is also a good singer, he has a good performance in the Japan Grand Prix
I'm a fan of big shows, please look forward to it
Biii! I'm Kojima Yoshio!
Oh! Girigiri!
What is this?
Yoshio has the image of a big show
No no no, I came to Tokyo to do a big show
That's right!
Just as I thought!
No, no, no, no.
Then it's not a naked person.
Last one!
Thank you!
I'm Pantone Wato.
Thank you very much.
Today, too,
I had 10 chocolates
for the big day.
That's right, that's right.
Wait a minute.
That's right, that's right. Please wait a moment.
The above voice acting challenge will be given to the remote O-Giri.
Introducing the rules.
Each person will announce the answer to the O-Giri given.
Matsumoto will judge whether it's interesting or not.
If you fail the challenge when you get an interesting internal judgement, you will have to clear the 9 members in a row
In that case, we will give each of you 10,000 yen
That's amazing
If you don't have work, let's all work hard
I also want to say something
If the answer is the same among the 9 members, I will simply hate you guys.
There is no such thing as the same answer.
Let's do our best, everyone.
Let's do our best.
Now, the time limit is 1 hour. Let's go!
This is the first question. Matsumoto-san, please.
It's easy to think at first. How about this?
How much does the first line change?
What is it?
Can I go smoothly?
I think it's a good idea.
It's the first line.
I can hear the chorus.
The pen is not moving at all.
I'm worried that the pen is not moving.
Ah, I see.
There are too many choices in my head, and it takes too much time to organize them.
Please think about it.
Is it because Otake is organizing his face?
No way.
Everyone is writing.
Hurry up and write.
It's time to...
No, I can't do this.
I'm going.
It's over.
So, Matsumoto-san, who will go first?
Then shall we start with the first introduction?
Okay, let's start with Yama-chan.
Yes.
What is the most important line that Nishikko-san has thought of?
Hatssaku!
What?
Wait a minute!
I'll give you a raise!
What?
When are you going to use it?
If you use it, you'll be able to use it when you get a good one.
When I get a good one?
That's strange.
Is there anyone who thinks that I can use it?
Who?
That's good.
I was the one who said it!
Tanaka! Tanaka!
Now, Hikoto-san, what do you think the Gimei ZuriF will be?
That's the question!
Either way, it's impossible.
Isn't it too soon?
Just one person!
I'm really confident.
Someone, someone, go!
Ah, Zagoshi?
Can I go?
Let's go. What is the line that you think is the most important?
I'm going to go!
The image is a little messed up now.
I see.
Let's move on to the next topic.
What is the first place of Kappa aru aru?
Please show us.
This is a good question.
There are many people who don't know Kappa.
There are many features of Kappa.
I use that.
Mame-san, you really don't write this comment right away?
No, because my IQ is high
You can do it, you can do it
It's over!
So, Mr. Matsumoto, where do you want to start?
Where do you want to start?
Please decide, Mr. Hamada
But, Tanaka has already finished writing the first episode
Okay, then let's start with Tanaka
What is the first episode of Kappa Aru Aru?
The magazine cover says,
Hey!
Is it bad?
It's harsh.
You should listen to this.
Please write it.
Here comes the letter.
Here it comes.
What is the first letter of HAPPARUARU?
In winter, hair grows fast.
Girl, you may not be funny.
Wait a minute.
It's fast.
I can't say it clearly, but you may not be funny.
It's not Kappa Aru Aru, right?
It's not Kappa Aru Aru.
It's not, right?
Otake, let's go.
What is the first place of Kappa aru aru?
Don't soak cucumbers in water
It's funny
I like cucumbers
It's quite funny
Let's go Yoshio
What is the first place of Kappa aru aru?
What is it?
The river is pretty bad.
It's not bad.
Okada, you go first.
You can go first.
What is the first place of Kappa aru aru?
The sneakers don't fit.
That was a little funny.
Wait a minute!
The flow will stop next time.
Tsuda!
You did it!
Yes, I did it!
What is the first place of the Cup RR?
Mezakusa Genki!
You were running away!
Alright, if it's like this, it's Yama-chan.
Do you want to see it?
It's no good to watch it.
Next, Kappa RR. What is the first place?
The plate on his head is thin.
It's thin.
He was talking.
I don't understand.
He was saying BOO at the plate.
I couldn't hear it.
Can we go with a good tempo?
Can we go with pan pan pan pan?
Yes.
I see.
The next question is this!
What is the reason why the pink screamer is screaming?
Please show us the picture and scream!
Wait a minute, so it's in front of everyone?
Yes, so you can just show it and scream.
So it's like he was doing it beforehand?
He didn't have time to think?
He just died!
He was taken from the back!
I don't know. It's fine if you know it in advance.
I know it. I know it.
Please don't say that you know it.
The argument is not there.
Let's go.
First, Otake.
Kaze Kimi
Correct!
Okay!
Let's go!
How much?
No, no, no!
Shouji!
Eight pieces!
Wait, wait!
Mom!
I want to eat seafood!
Correct!
Wait a minute!
What is that?
What? What? What? What?
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat seafood.
It's the sea, so I think you remembered seafood.
Is it okay to say that it was released once?
Because there was a flow.
To some extent, it will also be a flow.
Because there was a lot of it.
Even if it wasn't Augusta, I'm sorry, next.
Tanaka!
Osaka!
That's not good!
Tanaka, you're always red!
I don't understand what you're saying.
Tanaka-san, you're not good at acting.
Alright, let's wipe out the pride!
Pride!
We'll change the scene.
Tanaka, you're like a convenience store.
This is the most embarrassing one.
The most, the most?
It wasn't in the video.
I really thought it was GIN.
It's so funny.
I was swallowing, swallowing, and then spit.
I wanted to hold my laugh.
Akko-san, you can't say goodbye.
You can't say goodbye.
I don't want to hear that.
You haven't got the first one yet.
I want to get it.
I'll take this one.
Masuo-san, you should be a little more relaxed.
I understand.
Lower the bar.
Please.
And it's a very good topic.
This is it.
This is the question.
What is the next year's popular dessert?
Please think about it.
There are many.
It's often seen in the big screen.
There are some that are popular every year.
But I think it's harder to slip.
What did you say? You can't even open your mouth.
If you just put ink in it, it'll be fine.
Is that okay, everyone?
If we look at the screen, let's start with the middle one, Tsuda.
What is the next trend in sweets?
Pink Ohagi
Okay okay okay
It's pink
Pink Ohagi
Now, Yama-chan
What is the next popular dessert?
Gorilla potato
You did it
You are being very kind to me.
How is it?
All of you are booing.
I'm serious.
If it's Akko, I don't know what to say.
How many times do I have to say I don't know what to say?
I don't want to hear that.
You are being kind this time.
Wait a minute.
This is a booing.
But I did a booing.
If this is a pinpon, I'll be in trouble.
Yoshio!
By the way, let's see.
Yoshio, what's the next popular dessert?
Anago-ppi.
What's the difference between this and Gorilla Live?
What's the difference between pinpon and bun?
Zagoshi, let's see.
What's the next popular dessert?
3. Fried rice without a plate.
Oh, that's a good one.
It's a sweet.
I see.
There's no plate.
Let's hear only Choji.
Let's see only Choji.
What is the next popular sweet?
Tapioca.
What?
Ewa.
That's a bad one.
Ewa?
Alright, this is it! Shodo, go!
What's the next popular sweets?
Poop parfait
I won't say it. You didn't hear it, did you?
You didn't see it, did you?
No, no, no. You didn't see it, did you?
Just the sound.
Wait a minute. I want to go with this.
Not at all.
This is bad.
I'll give you a very easy one.
A very easy one.
If I were to say it on this scoreboard, the regular people are completely destroyed.
It's a bit too early.
It's a bit strict.
The regular people are strict.
I'll give you a light one.
The lightest one today.
Here's the question.
The North Prince, Kinya, wants to see me too.
I want to see a bit of snow.
Now, what is the name of the person who gave the name?
Please show us!
This is definitely good.
The amazing actor, Mr. Kitagawa
Because he is a big shot
The tension
And the feeling from there
It's very funny
Isn't it good?
It's basic
Okay, Shoji!
What is the name of the person who gave the name?
Let's go!
Yakin
Correct!
Okay
Zaboshi!
What is the name of the food that Mr.Hikawa ate?
Kinpoko
Correct!
Okay, okay, okay
Otake! What is the name of the food that Mr.Hikawa ate?
Kinchaku Bukuron
Correct!
Good, good, good
What is the name of the prince?
Kitaboshi Pin-chan
What is this?
Okay, let's go
What is the name of the prince?
O-chan
Okay, Yama-chan, let's go
What is the name of the prince?
Basha Basha!
Wait a minute!
What is this?
It's like Michopa, like Yuki Poyo.
I don't understand.
Akko-san, please stop.
By the way, Tanaka!
Yes.
What is the name of the person who explained it?
Kitao Kimi Kimi
Ah!
That's tough
It's a bit of a fan
The ABC is...
It's tough for the younger members
Yoshio, Yoshio, by the way, what's your name?
Prince Kimi Kimi
You're wearing it!
I hate you
No, I'm not
You're the last one to wear it in the garden
Say it already
What's your name?
Ok, tea time?
I don't want it.
You don't want it?
You want to be called a boon?
Finally, the 9th place is cleared.
Big chance!
Yay!
Yes!
Ah, there's 30 minutes left.
What?
Already 30 minutes?
This is bad.
Let's go on and on.
Let's go with 5 people
This is good
Next question
Question
In 2020, Shin Momotaro
Dog
Monkey
What is the 4th friend that comes to mind?
Please write your answer
The newest Momotaro
This is like a question from the New Mon edition of Oogiri
I see
Let's go
We have to go
That's right.
Ok, let's go.
What is the fourth otomo?
Yosuke!
That's good.
That's interesting.
Ok, let's go.
Zagoshi!
Zagoshi, what is the fourth otomo?
Sakai Masaaki.
I feel like he's a bit of a child.
Let's go with Kusuzawa!
What is the 4th otomo?
Pepper-kun
I see
It's good, it's a good idea
It's a good idea
Shouji!
What is the 4th otomo?
Kaeya
It's good
Let's go with Sake
Sake!
What is the 4th sound?
Medaka
Yoshio, go!
What is the 4th sound?
100 days after death
It's a trend, isn't it?
It's better to have a trend like this
Alright!
Tanaka, let's go!
What is the fourth sound?
It's the grass.
That's enough!
What's with this regular scene?
Isn't it a bit harsh?
It's not harsh.
If it's not Tanaka, then it's Shouzo.
Well, that's right.
What is the fourth man?
Yes, Son Masayoshi.
I don't know if I said it in the flow.
What is the fourth man?
Shoei.
I was saying it.
It's time to say it.
No.
There is no Shoei.
Yama-chan and Tanaka are not here
No, no
Even if they come as a person, it's not like a movie
It's a movie where they're taken away
That's everyone
What is the 13th OO?
Microphone exercise
The second half of the sister's cooking
What is the thank you in OO?
It's a rain-candy!
And finally, a big chance!
If he succeeds, he'll get a prize!
He's attacking from a distance.
And...
If it's Makko, then we're done.
We're done.
Don't say that!
The last episode will be broadcast exclusively on Hulu.