I want to know more about Inagaki Gorou
Quiz, Inagaki Gorou's 100 things
National star, Inagaki Gorou
With Satoru Shindo and Kishinagi Tsuyoshi, he has created new characters and has been very active in dramas and variety shows
Big news!
Last year, they had to show off their music and read the big news
Tonight, we will reveal the true face of the mysterious national star
First question
What is it?
What is Goro's hobby?
I have no idea.
I have no choice but to guess.
The answer is open.
Ah, I see.
So I'm the only one who's doing outdoor sports?
I don't think so.
I don't have the image of tennis.
Is there anyone who drinks wine?
If you collect wine, it's boo.
That's right.
If there's wine on it, it's the right answer.
There are people who put it on the wine server.
Isn't it good to drink wine, including that?
No, it's a bit...
I'll give you a bonus.
Really?
No, no, it's fine.
Now, the correct answer.
It's cute.
It's not bare skin.
What is Gorou's hobby?
Oh, it's Gorou.
Hobby.
I have many hobbies.
Really?
But, as I thought, I haven't been able to do it recently.
Golf.
No image.
The only thing that is different from golf is the outdoor.
I have no idea.
It was outdoor.
Can't you take some of the forbidden area?
That's not good.
Golf and tennis are completely different.
Outdoor is the only thing that is different from this.
Golf and tennis are a little different.
Really?
Golf is different from this question.
Golf...
What is his special skill?
I don't know
It's not golf
Open the answer
Oh, mouth-to-mouth
Something
This is amazing
Goro-chan is blowing like this
He's been blowing for a long time except for recording
Now, the correct answer is
Goro's specialty is
He sees through the true nature of people at first sight
Don't you want to hear more details?
What do you mean?
I want to hear a little
When I first met her, I knew she was a good person and that she would suit me.
Excuse me, I met her for the first time.
How did you feel when you first met her?
Well, Ho-Sein is...
He doesn't really have much contact with me.
But he's very...
He's very confident.
He has a glass heart.
I think that's what he's like.
I'm sorry, I've never been interested in him.
I'm really sorry.
I was thinking about it
I was in a lot of trouble
Do you think that much?
What is Gorou's charm point?
Let's go to guess
I will definitely guess
If I say it very simply
That's right
I don't know
Well, whatever
Answer open
Is it Matsumoto?
Matsumoto-san, it's Urunda.
Yes, I added a little bit.
Yes.
So here, the difference between Endo and Urunda appears.
This is the eyes.
It's more clear for me.
If it's Urunda and eyes, it's my point.
It's not Endo anymore.
If it's Urunda, it's not Endo anymore.
That's right.
If it's eyes, it's Endo's point.
No, I'll add a little more.
What kind of eyes?
I'll add more.
If you get the word, you lose.
Now, the correct answer.
He always has a straight face.
The gap between his straight face and his smile?
His eyes are quite narrow.
I don't like his smile.
This gap?
AL llam it the eyes
They call it that
can't really search for it
you can kinda panic
What rendering of the movie does he fiancied?
Let's go
I think this is how they look at it
Apply direction
This is a lucky question.
I'll take this.
Is this a lucky question?
Goro-chan has this image.
This is amazing.
The answer is...
This is really...
I have an image.
Everyone knows this.
It's famous.
Yes, it is.
I can't wait for this.
Yes.
Now, the correct answer.
What is Goro's favorite alcohol?
Well...
Wine.
Yes!
Okay!
Okay, okay, okay.
This is also a feeling that you knew without saying anything.
It's like, what are you listening to?
That's right.
Beer?
Is there anyone who removes it?
If you wear beer there...
It's a full-blown feeling of going to the bird.
It's not a bird.
Remove it with beer?
Please don't do that. I didn't go to get it.
Alright, I've caught up with you.
What was Gorou's childhood dream?
Eh?
Wah, what is it?
Please!
The answer is open!
Matsumoto-san, you are an idol?
I think I have decided.
Let's announce the correct answer.
Keiji-san.
He is not an idol.
Keiji-san?
Why did you want to be Keiji?
I wanted to be Clint Eastwood.
Dirty Harry.
It's difficult.
I'm a good person to Yamanaki-san.
No, no, no.
A little more.
Beer for baseball is like the body of the Summers.
Are you an old man?
I'm like a representative of the old man.
What is the most important thing for Goroh?
What is the answer?
It's difficult
It's difficult, isn't it?
The answer is open
I was able to say this because I liked it
But people who like golf might not like it
Well, you're right, you took care of it
You said it
And Hosei-san can't even laugh
If you don't become a comedian, you can't find the word, Kyo.
I found the word, Kyo, but I didn't find it.
You don't say it.
Now, the correct answer.
This is a personal space around me.
I thought it was Tanaka for a moment.
I thought it was Tanaka.
It's a staff around me.
It's like a feeling towards your friends.
It's difficult.
It's a distance.
If Goroh were to go out with a member of the group, who would it be?
This is something that Hamada-san, who is not here right now, would say.
He's alive.
He's really energetic.
Hamada-san is not a suspect.
He's just a suspect.
Ah, but...
Let's see...
You said yourself that you like golf.
Yes.
I think you know that I like golf.
Really? How do you know?
I've told you that I like golf.
I don't have any.
I've never thought about you.
I remember that.
I think so too.
I've never thought about it in my life.
Now, the correct answer.
Who is the member who goes to drink with the members?
Endo?
Really?
Thank you.
Why?
I feel good. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Why?
I think it's because of golf.
Honestly, everyone wasn't that different.
It's like, who cares?
But Endo-san is the only one who can play golf.
That's true.
I thought he would have it.
I thought Matsumoto-san would be in pain.
I'm worried about that
I see
It was surprising that he put it on everything
What kind of underwear does Gorou wear?
What kind of underwear?
What's a betta?
Answer open
It's like this, right?
But the three of you are boxers, right?
Yes, that's right.
I got that.
Kage-chan?
No, no.
This is no good.
It's not like that.
I thought so.
You've wrapped too much in it.
Now, the correct answer is...
Boxer brief.
Alright!
Thank you.
Okay, okay.
What are you talking about?
Please join us soon.
We've been doing this for a long time.
Why?
What is the most expensive gift that Goroh has ever received?
He must have received many things.
Ah, that one...
Wow, what is it?
That one is not here.
Open the answer!
But it's like this.
That's right.
Vintage wine.
How much is it?
About 3 million yen.
I'll be in the trial for that.
That's tough.
Cars...
How much is a car?
That's a lot of money.
No, no, no.
That's how it is with wine.
If you become an accident, you'll still be in trouble.
You won't give me an accident.
I don't need an accident.
That's 20 million yen.
That's a lot of money.
That's a lot of money for a golf club.
Gold Club is 1 million yen.
Full set is 1 million yen.
The winner is...
This is...
1 million yen.
Now, the correct answer.
I think I know this.
When I was in my teens...
Rolex watch?
Yes!
It's about 500,000 yen.
Probably.
I can't agree with that.
I was selling it.
It was half a million yen.
No, no, no.
I think it's worth it.
The most stressful moment is...
...a crowd.
The correct answer is at the end.
That's right.
Taking a picture of a flower.
The unexpected answers are repeated.
I see a video of that.
That is...
Ikezawa.
Goro-chan doesn't even know that.
After talking,
after saying this and that,
he says,
do you understand?
That's difficult.
It's not difficult.
What is the name of the lullaby?
I don't expect anything from people.
That was a great answer.
Endo has been leading the 3-question-correct answer.
Will he be able to get the correct answer back?
Who do you think is the most useless member of the 5th generation?
This is a service question.
This is...
Wait a minute.
But...
That's right.
That's it.
That person is not that person.
No, I guess you got it.
I didn't feel that much hatred for Tanaka.
I know it's not Endo.
Well, that's right.
But I'm not interested in it either.
But you're not interested in it, so it's not a failure.
I'm not interested in it. I don't think it's a failure.
I think, Hamada is not a failure, but a disorder in his life.
Ah, I see.
That's what I mean.
He doesn't change his underwear.
That's what I think.
I have all the answers, but I can't put them all.
Now, the correct answer.
Stop it, Goro-chan
It's Hosei-san
What?
Eh? Goro-chan?
Even when he's sweating
What? You were going to say the reason
You said the reason yourself
I have the image of him sweating on TV
Goro-chan's way of looking at things has changed
That's right
How many seconds can Goro do 10 push-ups?
I think he can do 10
How many are you able to do?
I think I can do a few
I think this is enough
This will hit, right?
It's a matter of who can do it
So fast
So you do it with the intention of doing it quickly, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
You have to hit it completely.
Yes.
Then, the announcement of the correct answer.
You have a lot of eye power.
Please prepare for the announcement.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I'll sing 10 times, right?
Is it okay like this?
Yes.
Is it okay?
Ready, start!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
Correct!
Seriously?
Even though it's a failure
It's not a failure
It's not a failure at all
What is Goro's favorite song from SMAP?
There are so many songs
This is a chance question
It's close to the previous one
The answer is
The answer is...
That's right.
That's right, but...
I think Lion Heart is also there.
I think it's really there.
Dynamite.
Even if it's a dynamite...
Stop it!
Now, the correct answer.
Well, this is too difficult.
Of course, there's only one flower in the world.
And then, there's orange.
There are many songs that I like, but the most is called Summer Day Yuka.
No, Goroh, that's not true.
No, it's not true.
We don't say that.
Summer Day Yuka.
Goroh, that's...
No, we don't know that.
That's...
The result is...
What is Gorou's weakness?
The answer is...
Amazing!
I've never seen anything like this before.
If you get this right, it's probably the first time in the past.
That's right.
Now, the correct answer.
Let's go with this.
The weak point is...
I think it's dance.
But he was dancing
Why is it like this?
What is Goro's favorite alcohol snack?
Normally it's that
I see
It's a bit like this
What is it?
I'll show you one
It's done.
Although the cheese is not so good, it's a cheese tart.
It's limited edition.
I don't think it's good to say cheese is bad.
I guess it's better to take a step further and go to cheese tart.
The liver patty is amazing.
It's amazing, he made it with a lever putty.
It's amazing.
I don't think anyone who makes lever putty would say that.
First place is...
Now, it's time for the correct answer.
Well, it changes a lot, but recently...
Oil Sardines.
It changes a lot.
Let's listen to the one before.
The one before.
I think it's raw ham.
There's a good raw ham shop in the neighborhood.
That was close.
It changed.
It was close.
Raw ham is frustrating.
Who is the person that Goroh respects?
This is hard.
Wait a minute, I haven't seen it yet.
Well, I'm going to run away a little more.
Oh, I have a hint.
You have?
Is that so?
Answer open!
It's Quint Eastwood.
I told you.
Dirty Harry.
You like movies, right?
Yes.
The director is also a movie director.
Yes, he said that.
So I thought about it a lot.
It's completely this.
Now, the correct answer.
Do you know this?
What?
You know it, right?
Everyone said it on TV.
Hiro-kun, who is a non-local.
Ah!
Have you heard of it?
Yes, yes, yes.
I respect you.
Who is it?
I have an uncle who lives with me.
What?
Yes, yes.
Do you still live with him?
I've decreased the number of times, but I come here twice a week.
You've decreased the number of times?
With your uncle?
I'm sorry, but what do you respect about him?
I'm sure there are many things.
He's a great scholar and he has a lot of knowledge.
He taught me golf, wine and many other things.
He's like a father, a best friend and sometimes a lover.
He's saying complicated things.
He said complicated things at the end.
He threw it in.
Don't come closer.
Inagaki's answer is a complete mess!
No, no, no.
The members are shocked by Inagaki's answer.
If you're going to be fair, where are you?
That's where you're going to be serious.
Who will win?
That person, right?
I was really happy. It seems like he was interested in me.
It seems that he has taken a picture of us.
That is our true power.
The previous broadcast was broadcast exclusively on Hulu.