Let's play basketball
This program is provided by the following sponsors
so swojąjkuk Use Defense
...you know what? We are playing football
Yes
so let's think as siaraoh Jukou
Will that be fine?
I would be very happy if you really did.
I Yangji was trying to show the energetic talent of peette
But I want you to understand the feeling of a taxi driver.
Yes.
Let's do it together until the end.
Happy Birthday
Oh! Coolly.
Hey brat!
He is a black 我是I am a cone-eater dry.
But WHAT?
What's going on?
In a little while, the tickets will be sold out.
What?
Think about the fans' feelings at the concert.
Yes, I understand.
Who are you?
I'm the producer of Okama.
Recording is going smoothly.
The guys have also started to get on the boat.
The water is shaking, the boat is shaking.
He is a taxi driver.
There is no one waiting.
I can't wait
It's cool
No.2, No.3, No.1
No.2 is cool
Close the door, close the door
OK, let's go to the next one
Shall we go to the next one?
Takeo
Yes
Can you make the part between No.1 and No.2 cool?
Cool?
Yes
You use the word, right?
What will you do?
No, it's OK
You don't have to use it!
The recording is in the middle of the song, and the members are arranging the song one by one
You're going to sing right away?
I'm going to close my eyes and go to sleep.
You're going to close your eyes and go to sleep?
That's good.
Let's try it again from the beginning.
I'm going to be a good singer
This is impossible
Hatake, you can say that your guitar is pretty good
Like this?
Let's do it again.
The next word is,
Super tire.
The car never stops.
The taxi drivers are slowly turning their colors
Back alright
What is this?
I'll hold your hand
I'm the driver
It's alright, it's alright
Cool!
It took a long time to finish
That's the good part
It was good
Between the 2nd and 3rd, each person has a different level of motivation.
There's the drum solo, and the group dance, and the formation.
I want you to make this song 15 minutes long.
That was one chorus, not one minute.
The recording is finally coming to an end.
Taxi Driver, Salam Q Version, complete!
Yuichi Shisou's
Tachibana Hayashino's
It will appear right now.
OK!
Good!
The next is Taxi Driver's final version.
Go Kai!
I'm a taxi driver
I don't have a car
I don't have a bus
I'm a taxi driver
I don't have a car
I put my ear, I put my heart, I'm a mysterious driver
Ah, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Masha orai, mak preparation orai
It's a long one, Deba.
Well, um...
Wait a minute.
I don't know what this is supposed to be about.
Well, you see...
I've seen it on the players' airwaves.
It's the first time for everyone to see it live.
Ah, is that true?
It's like, wow, a live pose!
That's how it is.
And, the song was long!
That's also true.
Thank you very much.
Do they not listen to you every time?
They listen to me every 10 seconds.
They listen to you the most.
I don't know, but they listen to me all the time.
I sing at concerts.
And you sing Heihei.
The guitar is interesting.
Sweetie,土産!
At last!
======
I felt really sad after I think about the series.