Karashi, try sucking it up.
Last week, the final audition for the new regular member of Gaki no Tsukai was held.
It's the worst.
The participants of this audition, who will be playing the role of the main character in the final showdown, are...
Black Mayonnaise
Tutorial
And Kirin
A mirror, a mirror
Finally, the new regular member of the Gaki no Tsukai will be announced
The results of the evaluation will be announced
Who will be the one to hold this crown?
Furthermore, after the audition, the unbelievable nightmare that attacked the young comedians
This is the first round.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
So, the one who is good at Kotsugi and is good at Okama, do the mouth-to-mouth fight.
Yes.
Here you go.
What is your store?
What?
What is it?
It has nothing to do with you.
What are you talking about?
It's a customer's question.
Ah, I see.
He's really angry.
I don't think it's a matter of time.
Isn't there a problem with your store?
The story is pretty...
I'm not joking!
It's not funny to see Okamoto's face!
I have it!
Shiro has it too!
What?
It's not Okamoto's style to show his face in a comedy movie!
Don't show your nose!
Okamoto, you can't do that!
That's not good!
That's not good.
He said that's not good.
You want to do it, right?
Wait for the tenant!
From this building!
If you say tenant's condition, the condition is the same for Tanaka!
I'll do the long lines.
I'll do the long lines like he always does.
That's good.
So, Sobu-kun, please do the funny sound effects when you take the tissue.
Let's do it quickly.
Say the sound effects with your mouth.
Yes.
Pa! Pa!
Let's go on.
Let's go on with the Pa.
Shubi! Shubi!
Ten-taka-ten-tun!
Tontoko-tontun!
I see.
Sasuke!
I'm ready.
What do you think?
You changed it!
I did.
You changed it, didn't you?
You changed it completely.
I did.
Why did you do it three times?
Which one?
There were many choices, but you changed it.
Live!
L-L-L-Live!
Yes, you can say live.
Which one?
That's it, right?
Yes.
So, in the end?
Live!
Which one?
Live.
Live, right?
Live is fine.
Well, well, it's fine.
Pass!
Amazing.
Can you sing a song by Tissue?
I think I can sing.
Why do you look so annoyed?
I don't like it.
You don't raise your back.
I'll pass. Please do your best.
I want you to sing while dancing.
That's right.
You can hold it, Tissue.
I see, I see.
I see.
Nice, Kosugi.
I see it while looking at the box.
Tissue, Tissue, Tissue.
Except for us,
if you put two together,
and put one together,
Naruto,
your power is completely weak.
Go, Kakyoin!
That was wonderful.
I was just thinking about this, but Endo-san, can you do that?
Me?
That thing.
That's right.
Kozue-kun, you can do that.
You can do that.
That's cool.
It's cool.
I think it's good.
I think we can see something good.
You can decide who will do it.
I see.
I want to see Koshii-kun.
He has a good potential.
Yes.
It's good.
It's a mess.
It's ok.
It's ok to say that it's a hug.
The way you do it is different.
It's very luxurious.
It's like a celestial body.
It's amazing.
It's like a real thing.
3, 2, 1, go!
Do you know?
Hey!
Ah!
Wonderful!
As expected, it's a regular.
Wonderful.
Now, the way...
Someone should do it.
Then, Mr. Yamaguchi.
Is it okay to do it alone?
It's too small!
Hey! Hey!
It's perfect.
It's good, right?
It's amazing.
It's like a lecture.
The
...
school
remember
this
3, 2, 1, go!
You're doing it!
Hohohoi! Hohohoi! Hohohoi! Hohohoi!
Wonderful.
Gouka!
You're really good at this.
I'm good at it too.
You two are like, what? You don't want to do it?
What about you, Tokui?
Oh, I'll stop.
Do you want Tokui to do it?
Yes.
You want him to do it?
Yes, I want him to do it.
Then why do you want him to do it?
It's like it's just me...
You mean it?
Only me?
Only you?
It's just me...
It's a mess.
A mess?
What do you mean?
You hate the way you do it?
Let's just say it.
Kousugi, look behind you and say,
I'm sorry.
Then, let's sit down.
I'm your partner, so I don't know why you're saying that.
But there's that kind of thing.
There's that kind of thing.
It's not on TV.
There's that kind of thing about partners.
I'm sorry.
Kosugi!
Yes
What is this?
Thank you, Mr.Kosugi
Good luck
Now, the face tube
I want to see how funny your face can be
Does anyone know?
I don't know
I'll stand there.
Then, can you do it, Mr. Hamada?
Please.
What is this?
Well, I think it's difficult to do this.
That's right.
Mr. Hamada, please.
If this is the basics, then...
Well, it's okay to laugh at anything, but the most interesting thing is...
Even at this point, it's interesting.
Oh, that's fine.
Okay, I'm in.
I'm in.
I'm sorry.
Pass!
Thank you.
I'm sure you'll get a medal someday.
I'm not sure.
Tabura!
It doesn't matter where you hit.
Are you okay?
I see.
Here you go.
The first hit.
You surprised me.
Are you a high-performance machine?
Kuma!
You look really annoyed right now.
You're right.
You're a big fan of Okama.
Look, Hana has a lot of stuff.
That's good!
That's good, Futakura!
It's good, right?
This is good, right?
It's like it's there.
Yes, yes, yes.
Ah, that was good.
It was really good.
Now, who's next?
Kotsugi!
Let's go.
Oh my.
Wow, this is great.
This is great.
This is amazing.
It's like Minami Shinsuke.
This is great.
Let's shake your head a little more.
Wow!
Wow, amazing!
Ah, that's good!
That's good!
He's laughing!
After this, the shocking announcement of the pass!
Well then, everyone.
That's all for the audition.
Now, it's time to decide whether you can become regular users of the game.
The team that has scored more than 2000 points so far has passed.
It's a good result.
Let's start.
Let's have a show of the judgment!
The national
commissioning
comments
Poison
cake
Hello I thank you very much
What do you say?
Yes
What's this?
No, no, no.
Please, leave.
No, no. I've done a lot of things.
Please stand up.
You've been saying you passed all this time.
What was the score?
Who got the most points?
The tutorial was the most important.
60 points.
That's low.
It's 2000.
You can't pass unless it's over 2000.
Not at all.
Kirin is...
40, I think.
40.
41.
4 o'clock?
How about you?
How many drinks do you have?
I haven't seen much.
Thank you very much.
Please, go back.
From there.
Please drink cold drinks.
I don't think it's a good idea.
It's not a good idea.
Maybe it's not a young artist.
Oh, really?
Oh, a regular artist.
A regular artist.
So, I'll give a chance to the young artist.
That's right.
Unfortunately, the audition for the young artist ended without a winner.
But, their trials were not only this.
Well, it's not a surprise.
I invited three people to drink with me.
I was talking to them.
I thought I would say something bad about Hamada.
You are his junior.
I was leading them.
But Hamada was avoiding it.
I thought I would ask him to act.
It's interesting.
I don't know who will be the next one, but I'll say it's 6 people.
After the recording, there are many things that we think about.
I want to hear it.
Kotsugi was really rejected by Hamada.
I don't know if he has a crush on Ichimosu.
He has a crush on him.
I don't know what that is.
I don't want to be a partner with him.
He's my partner and my junior.
That's right.
That's tough.
Then, take him.
I'll go with Tanaka, and Matsumoto will come later.
There's a reality show.
Then, I'll go.
Please take care of him.
We'll go home.
I'll go home.
I'll go for a little bit and come back later.
This time, the flow of the Puchi-Dokkiri is
Yamasaki and Tanaka, who are inviting the young man to the bar
Matsumoto, who is late for the meeting, and Endo, who is late for the meeting, are waiting in the next room
The moment the bad mouth comes out, Hamada enters and says it's a dead end
This is the scene
Hamada checks the young man's words in detail in this room
The rest is just waiting for the moment when the young man says bad mouth
This time, the prank is to set up 6 cameras and do it in a year.
Who will be Hamada's target?
Hamada and Endo arrive at the store.
After 10 minutes, Yamasaki and Tanaka take the 6 young men to the store.
The cold is coming.
It's coming.
It's cold.
What is this coldness?
What did you do?
What is this?
It's a hair clip.
I'm sorry.
Well then, good work.
Good work.
Oh, is that so?
This is the room for women.
Oh, here?
This is the room for men.
So, men don't usually enter.
There are a lot of girls here.
Here, Matsumoto arrives late as planned.
For now, he goes to the room where Hamada is getting ready.
This is amazing.
I want a cake.
This is delicious.
This is not delicious.
I want a cake.
Really?
Why?
You're popular.
You can't be popular.
I'm a painter.
I can't be popular.
Finally, the prank begins.
Who is going to be the one to be Amata's model?
Hello, Mr. Amata.
But, well, I'm a little bit of a loner.
Do you want something?
Yes.
I'll just take a little bit.
If I don't come, you'll laugh at me, right?
No, no.
Of course.
I'm talking about the story of KOSUGI.
KOSUGI is a bad guy.
He's a bad guy?
He's a bad guy.
That KOSUGI's activity is...
That KOSUGI is terrible.
He's a terrible guy.
I don't like him.
He's my junior.
You're his junior?
I was the one who was the most upset when I said that.
Because I was quite confused.
I have a time when I don't understand.
Why did you say that?
Why?
But that's a bad guy.
That's...
No, wait a minute.
That's bad.
No, that's...
That's a surprise.
It's a surprise.
There are times when I'm surprised.
Someone's been on the plane for 11 days.
I'm addicted to it.
Well, you told me today.
I'm addicted to it again.
I've been doing this for 25 years.
And then, he started to throw the bucket.
It was the opposite.
There was a place like a natural place.
That rubber was amazing.
It was a face-kissing rubber.
The rubber of Hamasawa.
It was good.
The face.
Damn it.
What the...
That was the picture with Con-s Sierra.
That was really close.
I wondered if he had grown aшая.
It's a genuine photo.
Listen, don't...
Do you remember the gingerbread lovely day?
I said no.
That's also very good.
What?
That's annoying, isn't it?
Kosugi-san.
How is it?
The rubber face.
It's pretty bad.
It's a little different.
What?
It's a little different from usual.
It's not normal.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for the last one.
That's right.
What do you think?
It's bad, isn't it?
Well, how many times, how many times...
Oooooooohhhhh...
The crow's there...
Pay attention...
Beg, beg give it up, give up?
Naake, naake, naake!!!
dolphin, dolphin, whale!
talked to too many people
Pity Ushiromori
It was a ray of italics
What the hell man falling again
That's Ohyama回
Ohk...
苗木によくだっていい?
Who the hesitant, what's theур?
HUH?
**
No, I can't.
Why?
How about Yamada?
I'm not going to do it.
Yamada, this is...
What?
Well, you know...
It's a little bit like curry.
The smell is a little bit...
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.