Next time on the Gaki no Tsukai, Chikichiki! No, no, no! Kiss no Uchi! Madonna and the Scented Bus Tour!
What's going on?
To be honest, I'm not in the mood for this.
Why?
Because if you think about the past, everyone wears a tuxedo.
What kind of tux did you wear in the past?
You got it right.
If you wear a tuxedo in front of this boy, you'll be made to do a stupid thing.
There's nothing to be happy about.
I'll explain the rules.
Just like last time, we'll play a game in the bus.
The loser will get off the bus.
This is the same as before.
As the title says, Madonna will be waiting for you.
Madonna?
Yes.
So you want to kiss that person?
Kiss?
Yes.
Well, you know, it's like a kiss with Madonna.
What are you doing?
His face is huge!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
First, we'll go to Tokyo Tower.
Tokyo Tower is good, right?
There are a lot of tourists.
But today is a sunny day, so maybe there are no people.
I'm sorry, but I'm really worried about Madonna.
I can't do it.
The first Madonna is here!
The first Madonna is Kocho Ran Abeko.
The charm point is that all three sizes are 130 cm.
Super body.
This is the first time I've ever seen a man with a big mouth.
I'm serious.
Really?
You're just being a wimp.
I'm not a wimp.
I don't do that on TV.
You're so full of yourself.
I'm tired again.
The first game is...
I want you to hit me.
I'll do it.
Pin, Pon, Pan
Wow, that's it!
Only when you say Pan
And then, turn this way
When you say three times out, it's Madonna and Kiss
Wow!
I can't win this!
Let's go! Pin-Pon-Pan Game, start!
Okay, inside of thecks it is К и tud colour
You just said it
know something
what lol
He speaks試 interview
You should taste
You can't lose!
Hamada-san did it safe but it was a terrible mistake
It was dangerous
Ping!
Pong!
Pang!
Ping!
Pong!
Pyo!
I'm glad I got over that
You made a mistake in the second and third rounds
Let's start with Yamamoto-san
Wait a second
I'll wait for you
Ping!
Pong!
Pang!
Ping!
Pong!
Pang!
Ping!
PON! PON! PON! PING! PON!
Ah, that's wrong!
It's wrong!
Matsumoto-san is doing it right.
Why?
Why was it at that timing?
It's wrong!
It sounded like Takeshi-san.
PON! PON!
After this, Tanaka made a mistake and Matsumoto, Endo and Tanaka lined up in the first floor
No, no, no
You have to sing the BING!
Too weak!
This is scary!
Let's go!
Bim, bom, bam, bim, bom, bom, bim, bom, bim, bom, bim, bom
Ahhhh!
What the hell!
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow!
I'm sorry!
I found you!
Why?
In the rain that is falling, the bus is going to Tokyo Tower
Everyone, please check this out.
Wow!
He's wearing a dress!
That's gross!
Wow!
He's wearing a dress.
That's gross!
I don't like this!
Now, Mazumoto will kiss you.
There's a situation.
Oh, there is?
Please protect it.
Yes, sir.
He screams out loud, and runs towards Abeko.
And then...
Wow, that's a safe kiss.
They hug each other and kiss so sweetly.
Wow, that feels good.
But I'm not sure if he'll do it or not, but he'll probably do it from the other side.
Yes.
No, I'm really waiting for it.
I'm waiting for it.
Mr. Mazono.
Please.
No, I'm not doing it.
I'll be watching from here.
There he is.
What is that?
I don't like this.
It's raining!
There he is.
Wow!
The size of his face!
He's sitting!
It's long!
He's so tall!
Abeko is really tall!
Isn't it long?
I can't speak.
Abeko!
You are overreacting.
Wait, wait.
Round 2.
He is like a chameleon.
It's hard.
Abeko!
It's too long!
Too long!
You're so tired!
Yes, it's too hard to do it.
It's too hard to do it.
Ouch!
It's too hard!
It's swollen.
I was surprised.
What's wrong with your face?
He's wearing a mask.
He's full of shit.
You're doing something bad.
I can't leave him. I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do.
I'm afraid I'm going to collapse.
The second point.
It's a good atmosphere.
It's good.
I go to the holiday and buy things.
Young people are also...
Even if you say that you are a person.
I'm more than that now.
What is the name of the woman in the picture?
It's a big picture.
Here!
Tsubaki Funako, the main character of the Japanese-style painting.
Her charm point when she was 40 years old was a glossy, fine teeth.
This is the one that is attached to the back of the leaf.
Basically, it's a stick that goes like this behind the leaves.
This person is a person with a bad stomach.
I have a bad stomach.
What's this?
The next game is the Magi Shinji Game!
I have nothing else to do.
This is bad.
The three lines of the line drawing,
Naha Naha,
Maggie, Shinji, and the person in the middle,
became big.
Where should I start?
Miyasako?
You start with Maggie.
Yes.
Maggie, Shinji,
became big.
Maggie, Shinji, you've grown up!
This is the one!
I'm getting goosebumps!
This is bad!
I'm going to lose!
Everyone, I'm fine!
No, no!
My eyes are swimming!
Let's put this up!
Tan tan tan tan!
This is so bad!
The members who want to avoid kissing Madonna. The game is heating up.
Yamasaki who is good at this game, and even Hotohara made a mistake. Everyone except Endo is standing side by side.
After that, Yamasaki and Miyasako made a mistake and finally the two of them reached.
Who is kissing Madonna at the spring break?
Oh no, oh no, oh no
Miyasako-san first
Ok, let's start.
Magi! Shinji! You've grown up!
Ah!
No!
Even if you get the answer right
Hamanaka, no
Magi! Shinji!
Nice!
I can see it now
Hamanaka...
Let's go
Magi! Shinji!
It's gotten bigger!
The winner is...
Amuro-san!
Yay!
Amuro-san won!
Downtown!
The bus is going to Odai Bay, where Madonna is waiting for her.
Oh, she's here.
Where?
Where is she?
She's here.
She's here in real life.
She's here as if she's watching us.
What's going on?
According to the staff, the public is...
I'll explain the situation.
Hanako-san, please get off the car.
When you turn around,
Who is it?
When you do this,
I'll give you a bouquet of flowers.
From here on, you can't do anything.
You're talking a lot.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Thank you.
Chief.
I'm sorry.
It's just this.
It can't be helped.
Then, excuse me.
I'm going to the big one.
The big one.
Let's go.
Who's wearing glasses?
Wow, that's...
It's a question mark.
Who is it?
I don't know.
I wonder why you don't know.
Who is it?
I don't know.
Then, I'll give this to you.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You look like a honeycomb.
Honeycomb? No.
Thank you.
Wow, this is amazing.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to do that.
I can't believe it!
It's a big deal!
Wow!
What a big deal!
I can't believe it!
Wow!
This is intense!
This is perfect!
This is it.
This is the same as the one in the movie.
The one in the Russian movie.
Wow, Nagairo.
This is really good.
The other one is broken.
This is broken.
Oh no.
That one is falling down.
Are you serious?
It's intense!
It's over! It's over!
I'm red!
Bye!
He's running away!
This is hell!
Look!
His mouth is all red!
Scary!
Wow!
It's a real one!
You're good!
Wow!
Amazing!
The photo is totally different.
Right?
His face is so pale.
He's pale.
Wow!
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
No, I think I did well.
Absolutely, Matsumoto-san did well.
No, no, no, no, no.
It was a pretty good one.
I'm still watching this.
It's not a step ahead.
Now, there's more than that.
This is the final point.
I can't think of it.
Okay, I'll do my best.
So, we are going to the Palette Town.
That's good.
The last Madonna is waiting for us.
There is a guide car.
That's good.
We will go to the next Madonna's scene and have everyone check it out.
We will announce it here.
Check it out at the scene?
Yes.
No matter how many times we took pictures, it didn't show.
It's finally the last Madonna.
But the third Madonna is in a mysterious veil.
The next game is...
The carbonated game!
Yeah!
It's a clock game.
It's a simple clock game.
Somehow...
You have to say the Japanese words that don't have the word, ta and da.
You are Japanese, right?
Ta and da.
You can't say ta and da.
Let's start the game.
Let's go.
Start!
Kotohara.
Miyasako.
Ito
Yamasaki
Endo
Ihara
Miyamoto
Yamakawa
Michii
Inoue
Hurry up!
Kudo
Chihara
Yamano
Miyao
Michi
Wrong!
Wrong
What are you saying?
I said Michi
After this, the game became more and more intense.
The names of women who don't have children, the names of men with four characters, and the game with three characters.
The five of them made two mistakes.
Finally, everyone was the least.
Everyone was the least.
Really?
Yes.
It's really decided.
Ah, I'm the worst. I'm the worst.
I can't do it.
Alright!
What kind of kiss will Ai do?
Ready, set...
Domino
Knock
Walnut
Mouse
What?
This is...
What are you talking about?
If I say A, you say mouse!
You should have seen it clearly
Yes! Madonna's
Finally, the bus is waiting for the mysterious Madonna
To the final point
Everyone, please look
This is a place I hate
It's so cold
Oh, that's the one!
The girl's clothes!
Oh, it's big.
It's beautiful, though.
Who?
So, here's Madonna.
It's big.
There are so many people.
So, everyone, look at this crowd of people.
This is the model.
First, look at this.
She's beautiful.
Then, look back.
She's wearing a wedding dress.
Then, she says,
I love you.
Then,
she says,
She's not wearing a wedding dress.
She's wearing a wedding dress.
Who is that?
She's a bit of a heroine.
A heroine at the end?
It's embarrassing.
It's like a punishment for being shy.
That's not good.
It's hard to do.
That's good.
There are many jellies.
I don't like this.
Madonna is...
This person.
Madonna.
I don't like this.
Madonna is...
This person.
Madonna.
Wow!
It's Mimata!
It's a man!
It's a woman!
It's a woman's feelings.
Isn't it bad?
It's like love.
If you wait too long, it will go higher.
Yes, yes.
Do your best.
It's breaking.
It's a big one.
It's slow.
Sorry, sorry.
But it's just right.
Why is it right? It's left.
It's nervous.
I love you.
10 people
There he is!
Wow!
He's coming!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
Hey.
What's going on these days?
There's something strange.
Something strange?
I don't know if you're angry or not.
I see.
I opened the parking lot.
I was about to go.
A taxi came.
I was waiting for a light.
The taxi stops in front of you and takes you off the bus.
What?
It's totally fine whether you're in front or behind.
It's completely self-evident.
What would you do if you were a normal person?
I would wait.
I mean, I can wait, but I don't know what's going on.
I'm getting angry.
I guess so.
Why am I here? I'm not supposed to be here.
I'm just a little behind.
The taxi driver apologizes.
I'm sorry.
The old lady who came down said,
That's fine.
But,
If you apologize like that,
What is this feeling?
It's fine.
I'm sorry.
Why?
But it's strange, isn't it?
What is this feeling?
The other day, I went to Kiyoshi-cho.
Yes.
I happened to go there to eat.
That's right.
I heard that you were going there occasionally.
I didn't know that you were going there.
But when I came, you came.
I think you were a little drunk.
I said, I'm going home soon.
He said, this is your treat.
He said a light joke.
I couldn't accept it.
You don't have to say that.
I was wondering what was going on.
I think he was saying,
I'm looking forward to the matcha.
That's a good thing.
I wrote it and said to Yamazaki,
I'm looking forward to the matcha.
I said that.
And then he looked at you and said,
Why are you laughing?
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.