Next time, at the Gaki no Tsukai Ara, the Spring Rambunctious Badminton Competition will be held!
This is good!
Badminton!
The staff will be 19.
With badminton?
That's stupid.
Is it okay?
What is it?
It's Rossi.
When Rossi came, I didn't know who else would come.
I'm not playing badminton.
I'm aiming for 19 points.
I'm not aiming for 19 points, but I'll go further.
I'll go further.
I'll do it.
What is it with Rossi?
What are you talking about?
Please calm down.
You!
We're calm.
Suddenly, Rossi appeared at the recording studio. What is his purpose?
I'm doing research on the future.
I succeeded in calling the future people.
Why are you doing research on the future?
I'm doing research on the future.
It's not working.
I have a feeling that it's about the future.
I came here on a future day because I'm doing this.
If I were Rossi, I would like to do it again from the beginning.
But I'm not Rossi.
Rossi succeeded in calling people from the future.
Now he will let me meet that person.
I'm going to get a ride.
Here he comes!
What?
What's he doing?
What's that?
He said, good morning.
It's a normal bike.
Is it a future scooter?
It's pure white.
It's a future scooter!
It says Suzuki.
What's inside?
That's so Ami Suzuki.
Ami Suzuki does Ech Mog
Ami Suzuki has a lot of
不管 16 of the world
from no I forever
of the future
or SUBSCRIBE
is decided
The 6th time?
It's always floating, so it becomes a wet suit.
The Earth is changing so much.
It changes so much.
It becomes a strange phenomenon.
A meteorite falls on the Earth.
A thin one.
It's thin and small, but it's about this big.
It doesn't affect anything.
I don't know about that, but I'm a thin guy.
I'm thin, but I'm going to be a magma.
Everyone says I'm a magma.
That's a magma.
I'm a magma.
Don't talk too much.
I'm close.
You're a Miyajin.
You're not a Miyajin.
I didn't mean that.
I doubt about the future.
I'm sure of that.
Then, let me give you some information about the future.
I'll ask you a question that is not important.
This is a big deal.
The result is a big deal.
This is the most important.
I have three grapes and three of them.
I'm curious about the first one.
Is it C?
Yes, yes.
This is C. It was the point where a thin meteor fell here.
That part is popular.
C is...
Chan Kawaii.
I haven't heard much about Budo.
No, no.
I've never heard of it.
Is it like that with Mr. Fukura?
That's right. There are tons of magazines about each famous person.
GirlsGetA chance?
Any current magazine that gets a chance like this can MGH2.
What does that mean?
It's a new story.
What do you mean?
That's why the world is like this.
It's a new story like this.
The future is like this.
This is amazing.
Do you care about the future of TV?
I do.
You do, right?
There's a TV stick.
Don't you care about this?
I don't know anything about it.
This is the son of Kawasaki Mayo.
What kind of person is he?
Kawasaki Jam.
Mayonnaise and jam.
Do you have anything you want to ask?
What's going on with this program?
It's the first time I've seen it.
This is slippery. Turn it over.
Sorry.
You have great acupuncture power.
Acupuncture power?
You can use acupuncture to stick it on.
I don't have any acupuncture ideas.
It's slippery.
I can touch it with my finger.
Where are you turning it over?
What?
I'm turning it over.
What was that?
The point of contact.
Show, you're still doing it.
I'm doing it.
It's a very important thing.
Are you okay with the magazine?
What?
Magazine.
What is a magazine?
No, I'm saying.
It's a magazine, isn't it?
I'm saying.
You're saying.
The face is red.
The future people are not excited.
The blood will rise immediately.
Is there anything else?
After all, the use of the instrument is rough.
That's right.
I'll tell you a little bit. Actually, I'm still doing this.
What?
I'm still doing it.
You did it?
I'll tell you a little bit.
Are you okay?
What's the matter, Mr. Koki?
Is it a virtual currency or electronic money?
That's a borrowed bike.
I borrowed the bike of Mr. Dodo of Route 33.
I don't know.
The Dodo of Route 33 is going to the customs to save money and go to the customs.
I didn't know that.
I don't know that.
The money hasn't changed, has it?
It's the same country.
This is the current one.
The bike is the current one.
Yes.
The Dodo of Route 33 will not be broken in the future.
That's right.
We don't have any of them now.
He's crying.
He even took the manager of the yakitori shop.
I don't know.
Look at this.
This is the current Gaki-tsuka.
Yes, it's been a year.
Yes, the members have changed.
What?
16 years.
But the tradition of Gakitsuka has been inherited for 16 years.
I'm sorry, but something has changed.
It's a pity.
This is a bit political.
It has changed to a New Romance rice ball.
This is Matsumoto's Son-taku.
I'm not interested in it.
You're not interested in it?
I'm interested in it.
I don't do it on TV.
End.
Sorry, End.
Let's see.
This is a bag.
Dorian's bag.
This is a complete Hamada's
respect.
I know Nakai-in, but...
I'm not interested in him.
Let's see Hosei.
Yamajima has changed.
Hosei has changed too.
Let's see Hosei.
He's dead.
Doria is dead.
Hamada's choice is terrible.
He's totally changed.
Now, it's time for the big announcement.
It's over.
It's not a joke.
I'm sorry.
It's from Antalya.
It's a bit tired.
Matsumoto has changed.
Then, only Hamada is left.
Yes, so it's like Hamada Dorian's God's Day.
What's the name?
It's not a guy.
Then, it's not a guy.
It's not God's Day.
It's a red face.
It's not a gift.
I'm going to put a gift on it.
Let's see.
Who is it?
This is Takahashi Meiji.
Takahashi Meiji?
No, no.
He's almost 80 years old.
What? 16 years old?
I don't think so.
I'm doing it with these members.
Don't be ridiculous.
Don't get off!
You can be close to me
From here, he will change into the clothes of the future
From the future cookie, he will learn about the future
I changed into the clothes of the future
What is the meaning of this?
What are you using this for?
This is a Tama-bikku.
This is when you do that.
It's like imitating a fire extinguisher.
It's like a fire extinguisher.
I don't do that.
Have you ever done that?
We can't do that.
As a future person, I want to be in the same rank as Geno.
I want to be in the same rank as Geno.
The color is different.
If you look at Mariko Kagama, her blue cape is all the way over there.
It's so high.
She's wearing a cape that's all the way to her chin, and she's wearing a cape with her eyes open.
She's still wearing it.
It's amazing.
Now, let's go to the grave of the future.
It's completely different from the present.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Let's go.
First, we'll learn how to go to the grave of the future.
What kind of evolution is the grave 16 years later?
The shape of the grave itself has changed.
It's almost like a grave.
Tanaka, what kind of grave do you think it will be?
A grave of the future.
It's very compact.
It's small.
It's really not a big thing.
It's a very good place.
Actually, it's almost the same as a real life.
The land is gradually disappearing.
The population is increasing, the land is getting smaller and smaller, and the grave is getting bigger and bigger.
That's the future that's coming.
But, this small grave...
You're just going to come out like this, aren't you?
That's what they say.
It's not like that.
Anyone who wants to see the grave?
Everyone?
This is the shape of the grave.
It's like a TV video.
A TV video?
There are so many TV programs, right?
And the TV programs are lying around like garbage.
So what should we do?
Let's use them as graves.
They are dead and burnt to the bone.
The bones themselves are garbage.
Let's put them together with garbage.
Now the graves are garbage.
By the way, look at this.
This is Hamada.
It's a gold fish.
It's Hamada's stomach.
Oh, it's Hamada's stomach.
My name?
16 years later, Hamada is gone.
I'm sorry.
I'm the only one left.
That's a photo of two months of 16 years.
This is a photo of two months of 16 years.
Like SIrongrrr
We call him SIrong!
....しまして
I called my name Siiroro
◆SHIRorono
I went to the live broadcast
inventing new characters
Get out
You worthless
You read it, you know it.
This is the item of the name.
It's a lie. Be careful.
It's a lie.
You try it.
Me?
Yes.
Hama-chan likes this.
How about this?
I want this.
This...
This is...
I see.
Ah, you only noticed it!
Oh, I see.
Shall I do it this way?
Stand it up, stand it up.
Stand it up, and then this way,
Ah, I'm starting to feel it.
It's really starting to look like a grave, it's disgusting.
It's a little...
Then, go back, go back, that's not it!
Ah, it's wet!
It's all wet!
It's okay!
We can use it later!
Don't talk about your concept!
Sorry!
Don't get angry!
You guys are always getting angry!
Just by looking at it...
But I want to see the right answer.
I'll show you my drawing.
Huh? It's the same.
It's the same!
They're all the same.
What's the problem?
This one!
I got it right!
Amazing!
I'm going to the toilet.
You can't go in the toilet.
That's not good.
That's why I was so angry.
Why were you so angry?
I was very angry.
I'm going to watch TV.
I miss watching TV.
Are you happy?
I want to be by your side
I'm doing this for you
I wonder if it's possible
I did it, but...
I see
I see, so you can see the individual like this
I can see the nostalgic video in the grave
It's not like this
I see
It's a memorial
What?
From the top of the cliff?
That's not good.
You should have put it on the top of the cliff.
Let's go to the top of the cliff.
Let's go.
I think it's a little overlaid on the video of the private.
The
The mistake of the shaft is that...
Then let's go next.
What?
I'm being guided.
Are you sleeping?
The magazine is strong, isn't it?
Can you tell me what to do next?
Why don't you turn on the engine?
Is it a TV video?
Every time I turn on the engine and press it.
I feel like you're sending me to the station.
You can go home with a beautiful face.
It doesn't make sense.
Next, we will learn about the future history of the world.
What will the 16 years of Mamemaki be like?
Well, then, I'll have Hamada do the demon.
I'll have Hamada do the demon, so come with me.
They will be dressed as the 16 years old demon.
Demon, come out! Demon, come out!
Demon?
A
Hamada-san
It's a lie
The future Oni is like this
Hamada! Hamada!
No
No no
It's meaningless
It's the real Oni
The real Oni
It's meaningless
Even if you imitate Hamada, you are still similar to him.
Hamada is already Hamada.
That's right.
It's meaningless.
What do you want to do?
You look alike.
What do you mean?
You look like him.
I will now ask you to do a
You guys are trying to get us out of here, but we are trying to stay at home.
We are like Hamada Deva, we are sleeping.
Is that a weapon?
It's wet.
No, no, no.
We are going to sleep and kill you guys.
No, I don't want to!
You guys are too strong!
We're just a group!
You guys have a weapon too.
We use our arms.
You guys are just a tool.
A tooth.
A tooth?
Instead of beans, you can use a
This is a gimba.
A human tooth.
A gimba?
While the music is playing, we'll attack you guys.
You guys don't have the right to dig it up.
The moment the music starts.
What?
And there are times when the music stops.
It's time for the on to stop.
Bang!
Yeah.
That's a chance.
It won't move.
Come on, bang bang.
Then, the future of the story.
Start!
Is this song?
Ah!
Hey!
Hey, Kota!
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm sure you don't like it.
Scary scary scary.
It hurts.
Music stop.
Ouch!
It stopped!
Ah!
Ah, it hurts!
It hurts!
Eh? What is it?
What is it?
What is this?
Tachō Eva
Stop it, stop it, stop it
Stop it, stop it
What are you doing?
It's Osaka!
Osaka!
Osaka...
I've never heard of Osaka like this.
The show is over!
It's over.
It's crazy.
Good luck!
Jinba, Jinshi.
Hitoshi, Hitoshi, Hitoshi.
Hitoshi.
Wow!
The best of the best
Now, I'd like to announce the best of the best
The person who will announce it is this person
Why?
Mr.Moto?
He's the future
Then I'll take this
Thank you
Why?
Mr.Moto is not the future
Tsuyuki-san from Fuji TV
Tsuyuki-san from Fuji TV?
Yes, Tsuyuki-san from Fuji TV
The one who did the Fuji TV announcement
It's complicated
The winner is...
Tanaka! Congratulations!
You're not supposed to be doing that
Why?
The last time I was forced to do it, I was so scared
My chest became so heavy
Congratulations.
I will give you a reward.
Then, Tsuyuki-san.
What is this?
It is a tunnel to the future.
What?
You are interested in the reward, right?
I will show you the future for 5 seconds.
That's great!
In other words, Danaka-san,
please put your face in the flapping for 5 seconds.
You can see the future.
Please tell us what kind of future you had.
Wow, really?
It's 5 seconds, right?
Please put your head in.
Put your head in?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
The end!
Did you see it?
How was it?
After he said, yes, okay, the cookie was apologizing to us.
That's true.
I'm sorry.
You made a mistake. It's 30 seconds later.
Let's go home, Suiki.
Suiki, this is not for you.
Oh, it's not for you.
Adios Japanese people.
Gakizuka members, thank you.
Let's go!
This is the worst.
I hate this.
I want to do this.
Don't walk!