I'm not a fan of the character, I'm a fan of the character.
I'm a fan of the character.
But I played here before.
You did, right?
I did.
Ah, you did.
You did.
You did?
Monkey Magic
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors
Starting October, I'll be doing the show, Saiyuki
It's a Japanese TV series, it's a new series
Yes, I'm a drama actor.
I'll be the main actor.
That's strange.
So, the company said that it's a bit too much.
So, if Downtown and Kokoriko can help me, the project will be approved.
I...
The whole company hates it.
I'm going to go to the location, so let's go to the place where the dance is.
I don't know.
And you are the main character.
That's the same in the world.
I understand your feelings.
What should we do?
Kintoun!
Hey Yamada!
No, Kintoun
Kintoun
Tonight Yamada
Yamada-san
Teacher!
I'm the one who's in the drama!
I'm the one who's in the drama tonight!
You can't get on.
This is dangerous.
I'm going to do it.
Let's go.
This is dangerous.
It's not so well decided.
It's a waste.
Let's do it.
We'll play a trick and get 2 out of it.
And then, we'll get out of the one we got.
The 8 of them will play a trick and get 2 out of it.
The one who can't do it till the end will be the first member to be eliminated.
You can't do it anymore.
Ready, start!
Go, go!
Go!
No!
That's difficult.
You can do it with a swing.
Start!
With a swing.
No!
Just like that.
Please watch carefully.
Start!
Yes.
Out.
Please do it again.
Everyone will be out.
But you have to do it several times.
Out.
No, no, no.
Out, out, out!
I think I can do it.
Out, out.
I'll do it.
Oh!
Amazing!
You're out!
Okay, okay, okay.
Endo is really good at this.
He uses it for cooking.
I love this.
What's with you?
That was so uncool.
I'm sorry.
No, no.
What's with you?
I was like, I'm going to do it!
You did something bad!
This is fine, right?
That's true.
You really didn't do it?
I wanted to do it too.
Because if you do this, you'll get two.
That's not good.
That's not good?
It's so bad!
I bought a reason.
The first one is out.
Let's put it there.
I bought a reason.
Don't come out!
Only at times like this.
Don't come out.
There's a lot.
It's coming out.
It's better to die.
It's in a different room.
It's coming out.
If it hadn't come out, it would have been a mess.
I did it!
This is not Dengo.
I did it twice.
You did it so easily.
This is not Dengo.
I hate it!
I really hate it!
I also hate it.
I thought it was a guy who was out.
I'll take the punishment, so cut it out.
What are you going to do? Yama-chan out.
Zaki-san out.
What are you going to do?
Then what is it?
Well, I can't say that it's a method of thinking that I did such a cowardly thing.
I don't think it's a method of thinking.
I think so.
It's called Chouhakuai.
That's a bit unfair.
That's unfair.
Tell him.
He's wearing a sticky jacket.
Did you decide?
Oh, you decided on one person?
Yes, this time.
I'm not sure if he's here, but he's serious.
He's serious?
Well, but...
I really hate the sales director, Kosugi-san.
I don't know who he is.
Stop using your personal name.
It's been a while since I heard that name.
It's been a while, right?
Kosugi-san.
But I think I understand why he's hated for his frisky style.
Oh, really?
But, you see, there are still two more.
What?
Are you talking about someone else?
Or someone from a different place?
Nagoki, you...
You should have cut off the fight and not done that.
What are you talking about?
You should have done the PPP.
Is that so?
I thought you were going to say something, so I did something.
What is that?
This is...
It's a hula hoop.
This is tough.
And then?
The next one?
I'll think about it.
Then you decide.
Yes, I'll decide.
Please.
Oh, right.
Kinton!
Stop it!
It's Kinton!
It's coming!
What should I do?
You can't choose.
I think that's a bit dangerous.
This is a game of Fluff.
There are two of them.
It's not that easy. It's a game of rotation.
Let's have a match and the winner will be eliminated.
A match?
Yes, a match.
The two of us will play.
There are two of them?
Yes.
The loser will be the next opponent.
The two players will spin the Fluff and the one who falls first loses.
The last person to be eliminated is the strongest member.
Naoki, you decide.
Then...
I'll do it with Oruma-san.
Naoki will do it.
Then, right away?
Yes.
If you practice, you'll be able to do it.
Here we go.
Ready...
Start!
Okay, finished!
Delicious!
I didn't think so!
It was delicious!
It's more like bamboo shoot.
It's like that?
It's a little more of a back.
Bamboo shoot?
I'm already out.
It's okay because it's bamboo shoot.
Next, I'm out.
I'm out.
Me?
Ready, go!
Stop!
It's a dead end!
This is impossible!
This is worse than I thought!
My body is gone!
I don't understand the meaning of this!
It's the same as the one that Kotonji dropped!
What should I do?
At first, you should have done this.
You should have done this.
Endo, who do you want to go first?
Endo, you should go first.
Then, Hespo.
Ready, go!
It's narrow.
It's definitely good.
If you don't do it before you get better, you'll never know.
I don't know the meaning.
Let's do it, Matsumoto.
I don't think I'll lose this.
Ready, go!
You're done.
Yes!
I will win for sure!
Who is it?
Hamada-san and...
Nakamura-san
Yoshinobu-san
Yoshinobu
Please look at this
Yoshinobu-san looks like a turtle
He looks like a turtle
I want to beat a turtle
Let's go
Ready...
Start!
Yoshiro, you were good.
It was close.
Endo was a little behind.
But Endo was a little better than before.
Yes, a little better.
Arudan.
Don't say that.
You didn't know this was coming?
No.
This will decide everything.
Yes.
I will win.
The one who loses.
Ready, start!
Wait a minute!
One more time!
Let's do it one more time!
We still have one more time, right?
You're really like a douji.
Really?
Let's do it one more time!
This is the world of Japanese.
No, no, no.
Ready?
Ready...
Go!
Which one?
That was a little bit wrong, wasn't it?
Really?!
It's the same.
You hit the shoulder.
Isn't that you?
If you did that, it would have been a
It's the same.
Let's do it again.
Don't you do something bad?
You open your legs when you fall.
No, I don't do that.
Both of you do.
What?
You're lying.
You're really a doji.
No
Ready, start!
Which one?
I really don't know.
It's so weird.
This is the last one.
How bad are they at hula hoop?
I don't know what you mean.
I'll start. Ready, start!
Which one is it?
I'll start. The person who says Hamada wins...
Aso! Aso!
Then Enzo wins!
No way!
Amada-san wins!
Amada-san, you win!
No way!
I was just waiting!
I was waiting for you!
Amada-san,
Saggo Castle and Sanzo Hoshi.
I should have won Sanzo Hoshi at the end.
I see.
Then, let's go with Sagojo.
What?
You should do Sagojo!
No, no, no.
Sagojo is a bit strong.
What is that?
Wait a minute, this is also...
Ah, I've decided!
So, Yamachan and Hamachan.
Yes.
That's good.
There's no third person, but I think that's good too.
If it's something, I'd like to be the horse for Yamachan and the other person the chowhacker.
That's a good idea.
Even if it's just a trend...
Hey!
No, this is a proper drama.
What do you do when you are an amateur?
It's okay now.
Then, let's decide on the third one.
Let's decide on the third one.
How do we do this?
That's the point.
There are ideas for comedians.
There are.
Oh, this.
That's right.
Let's do the third one.
The third one.
I think Matsunaga is better if possible.
Well, that's true.
Well, anyway...
I understand.
See you.
I'm counting on you.
What are you doing?
I'm having a bit of a cramp, but it's a bit wet.
Yes.
So...
When you squeeze the water out, you can't squeeze it out completely.
I see. Let's do that.
One by one, they squeeze out the water.
The person who can't squeeze out the water will be punished.
No, just once.
No more holding.
Just once.
If you do this, it will be over after the Kabutogani.
It's possible.
I can drop it, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, well, it's still easy.
It's still easy.
Which one? Which one is easy?
Which one is better?
Oh, it's not that easy.
This is okay. This is okay.
Oh, it's okay.
This is probably going to be 4 or 5 laps.
It's okay.
I'm going.
It's getting better.
OK!
It's getting worse.
Just one drop.
Ok, I'll start.
What?
You're too fast.
I'm sorry.
What did you do wrong?
I made a mistake in the hand.
You're not doing anything wrong.
I'm doing it.
You're doing it with both hands.
It's coming!
Here I go!
Just one more round.
I have to squeeze it in from this much.
Let's change it.
It's starting to look pretty empty.
It's coming.
I'm going to go now.
You don't have to go that far.
I know.
But I know. I'm starting to get impatient.
The first two.
Wow! It's a squeeze!
This is bad.
Yes.
If it comes this far...
This is bad.
I think this new hair style is better.
Yes, let's make it new.
This is like a grip.
Next time, it's not good.
It's okay.
Next time, I'll do it properly.
Why is Mr.Sanji's hair like this?
That's right.
It's okay.
I feel like I'm losing.
The grip is...
Is that so?
I wonder how it is.
I'll leave it to you.
I'll do this.
Everyone is having some fun
Monkey magic
Born from an egg on a mountain top
The monkeys, yes monkeys that ever hulk
He knew their magic tricks from day one
He'd keep the guards and everyone would have some fun
The monkey magic, monkey magic
In陳光之家 of Shinjuku, 5 years ago L кол s view
How are you?
No problem
Perfect
A
virtCry
of
arbitrator
I
Y
Gandhara, Gandhara
They say it was in India
Let's go to the land of love