The next day
You're late
You're slacking off
Good morning
You're late
Sorry
Sorry, the other person was late
What?
I thought you were late
I thought it was about time
That's strange
We should have come earlier
Sorry
You didn't tell them about today's call?
I'm not sure if I can say this.
I'm in my teens, and I just graduated from high school.
That's young.
You just graduated?
Yes, I just graduated.
And I'm told that I like young men.
You're young?
You're not that young.
If I were, I would have quit.
I don't think I need to stop.
How long will it take?
About an hour.
What?
That's a bit too long.
I'm sorry.
An hour?
I think I'll just stay here for an hour.
I think I'll head home.
I'll go home for an hour.
My house is close.
I think so.
Then, at 5 o'clock...
5 o'clock.
I want to be back at 5 o'clock.
If you can come back at 5 o'clock.
18 o'clock...
I don't know what to do.
If you have time, you can call me.
I don't mind.
Even if you suddenly quit, I'll be back.
Then, at 5 o'clock.
At 5 o'clock.
Do you have a meeting?
No, we have 5 people.
So you have 5 people.
I'm sorry, but I might not be able to make it.
I might not be able to spend much time.
I'll call you again.
Excuse me.
It's 5 o'clock.
Yes, it's 5 o'clock.
Then, let's go have some tea.
You can drink here.
I want to drink delicious coffee.
Do you have time?
I have time.
I'm going to the pizza shop.
Okay, I'll be there.
Then, I'll go out.
You're going out?
Yes.
I'm going to go to the temple.
Oh, it's still just me.
It's so cold.
It's been an hour.
I know.
You're not here?
No.
It was hard to keep track of time.
It's cold.
What? It's cold.
I thought I'd get wet in the car passing by.
I thought I'd never see her again.
I need a break.
You're so slow.
I don't think so.
What?
I think it's too young.
I thought I'd quit.
But I can't destroy my license.
Your juniors are doing it on purpose.
Thank you.
I wonder if he'll like it.
I don't think so.
I was in my teens.
That's right.
You were in your teens.
Why would you come to my place?
I don't think so.
You were in your teens.
I'm not.
Do you have a forestry shop?
We have a forestry shop.
Please go there.
Thank you.
What do you mean by a forestry shop?
Where are you going?
You're late.
I know.
You're faster than us.
Zaki-san too?
I haven't seen him yet.
Only Yama-chan?
Yes, only Zaki-san.
He's the same.
What's the age difference?
9...8 or 19.
Well, he's the only one who talks and moves.
What's up with you?
You're still not here?
No, I'm not.
Well, that's good.
You're late again.
I'm not here anymore.
It's okay.
I was thinking of going home.
But you're not here at all.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I thought I'd go to the hospital.
But it's bad.
It's bad for your license.
That's the only thing I'm sorry about.
And I'm a teenager.
Ah, it's so cold.
I'll wait for another minute and then I'll go home.
You're going home?
Ah, you're here.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Sorry.
You're so annoying.
I just got a call from a girl.
Yes.
She said she was going to cancel today.
What?
Sorry.
Why?
There's this girl called Miki-chan.
But that girl couldn't come because she had some business.
What do you mean?
There's no other girl, then?
So, there was something like that, so I had it prepared.
What do you mean?
You had it prepared?
I had it prepared, but...
I have someone I'm going to see.
That's fine.
5 people?
Yes, 5 people.
But you can't just go like that.
But you're going to see her, right?
She's a bad person.
You're the one who's bad.
Call her.
I'm not going to call her.
If you're going to call her, that's your fault.
You're the ones who are bad.
I really only did what I could to break the face of RIZENS.
You should read it.
It's a beautiful girl.
She likes an artistic man.
What do you think?
It's a bit complicated.
It is, isn't it?
It's not a big deal.
It's complicated, but the face is really cute.
Here.
Ah, I see.
Yes.
That's not what I meant.
What was it again?
I'll say it as soon as possible.
I think...
The contact is off.
It's off.
Somewhere.
Did you get in contact?
I'm going somewhere. I'll go home for now.
In about an hour?
Yes, in about an hour.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm sorry.
I'm not allowed to come in.
I'm sorry. I don't have a license.
You're in the 8th floor, right?
Yes.
I wonder if it's the 8th floor.
It's exactly 8 o'clock.
It's about 6 o'clock.
Yes.
Sorry.
Sorry for the trouble.
I'm going to go.
Really?
Yes.
I'm going home.
The client is coming.
I'll be in trouble if I make a mistake.
I'm going.
Sorry.
It's OK.
I'll be back at 6.
OK.
If he comes, I won't be able to come.
I won't be able to wait.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I think there are 5 people.
I think there are 4 people.
Sorry.
I'm not going to be here.
I've always wanted to eat at this restaurant.
Let's ask them if they want to eat.
It's not that much less now.
I'll spend some time here.
I'll just eat a little.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I'm sleepy.
Shin Data
Unaware of what's going on, S Ren comes to work in>-
Family
I'm sleepy.
You made nightshade?
... those are the times when I got those.
— Look at this, man... — This is a closer look.
I hate this the most.
I was sleeping.
I want to go home.
You're right.
I thought I was going to get angry.
The literally last grandma
I can't do this.
I'm not good at this kind of stuff.
I don't like you.
I don't know.
What's up?
Come in.
I was thinking of going home.
Yeah.
Hamada-san said he might not come.
I understand.
He might be back at 5.4.
Hamada-san is coming?
Wait a minute.
It's nothing.
It doesn't matter if it's Gordon or not.
It's just the face of the normal license.
Huh?
Is it here?
Who is it?
No, I don't think so.
I think he might not come today.
Oh, really?
Hamada!
Oh, Mr. Hamada?
Oh, here.
You came.
What?
You said you might not come.
Oh.
Well,
There was nothing there.
Where was the toilet?
I think it was in the back.
What is this?
I'm making a song right now.
This?
Sex music?
Someone is coming in.
What are you doing?
It's a Japanese-style scene.
Well, it's fine.
I don't want to do this anymore.
If I get invited to this kind of thing again, I'll refuse.
Is it not time yet?
It's not time yet.
Huh?
Sanlona?
I don't think the number of people is right.
Are you a university student?
I'm a university student.
Here he comes.
He's here.
Your license!
I don't have it.
You can't just come here.
What should I do?
Oh we see!
I'm going to the end.
You're going to the end?
Can you go and tell them?
I'll go and tell them.
Let's just go and check.
There's no mistake.
That's right.
You can take that.
What?
I see.
How is it?
Can I just check?
It's definitely a witness.
Well, it's like a witness.
Yes.
License?
No, no.
No, I mean...
A license to eat with a big mouth.
Then that's why you are weird.
You are really weird.
You are the worst.
The worst.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
What? What? What?
Tell him that he's not related to this.
This has nothing to do with this.
It has nothing to do with this.
What? What?
Are you the main protagonist?
What?
That's the worst!
I'm not doing it.
That's the worst.
You're really cool.
You're slow!
What are you doing?
What happened?
He refused again.
What?
I'm sorry.
He said he found a scene he wanted to draw on the way here.
That's not true.
He said that.
No, no, no.
He didn't say anything.
No, I didn't say anything.
Did he say he was coming?
Yes.
Yes, he did.
Did he really say that?
Yes.
He said he would come even if it was a lie.
He did?
Yes, he did.
And the four of us.
He said he would come when we were playing.
Oh, really?
What?
What is this?
Oh, I see.
Oh, it's like this.
What should I do?
Everyone is so sweet.
The beautiful voice.
It's a bit empty.
I've seen the Jura. I'm aware of it.
Well, I'll let you do that.
Then, I'll go ask.
Go ahead.
Excuse me.
Well...
Ah, I don't know.
Look.
What?
Ah, yes.
Look closely.
Look.
It's not weird.
I don't know.
No, no, no.
Excuse me.
What's your name?
You're not supposed to say that.
It's not gross.
Gross?
Yes.
Who is gross?
Who are you talking to?
I'm talking to the whole team.
I heard what you said about Rises, but it's not gross.
I can prepare another one, but...
I'm an OL.
I'm an OL for a first-class company.
You're a person who knows the upper class.
Yes.
But I don't know if it's because I work in a hard place, but...
I like men with wild tastes.
That's right. I'm sorry.
I'll stop.
It's not like that.
It's just that this time is hard.
What do you mean?
It's confusing, right?
It's hard, right?
What about their faces?
They're so cute.
It's strange to say that they're cute, but they're not.
They're not.
I don't understand the meaning.
That's right.
Then what is it?
Then we're not gonna have to match like that.
That's not what I mean.
What are you doing?
You're making fun of me.
You're so stupid.
I'm busy.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
Good.
Is he still here?
Not yet.
Was it too early?
I think he'll be here soon.
I don't know.
I'm hungry.
Oh....
How long has it been?
Not yet.
Oh, really?
Not yet?
Not yet.
I'm sorry.
Too slow.
It's slow.
Not yet.
It's hot.
I'm not done yet.
You're not done yet?
I'm sorry.
I have to steal the boy instead.