Next match is En-do vs Guts.
Let's go.
Kogon Tozai.
The store name of the convenience store.
Ready.
Lawson.
Yes.
Seven... Seven Eleven.
AMPM.
Yes.
Jona-san.
Yes!
Yes, start.
This is...
It's like something that happens in a general house.
After this, Guts is still not correct.
In a flash, he reaches the fourth question.
This is amazing.
It's amazing.
It's a title match.
The Japanese Prime Minister of the past.
Ready!
Kishi Nobusuke.
Yes.
Nakasone.
Satoeisaku.
Kaifu.
Hara Kei.
Ito Hirofumi.
Kaifu.
I'm going!
Mom, please stand over here.
Why?
Wasewasa, go over there.
Seiki, Seiki.
Yes, do your best.
Yes.
Then why did you stop twice?
That's right, I can't do it.
I'm the one who should stop.
That's right.
Thank you.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Please, J.K.
Yes, J.K.
No, me.
Yes.
Please, J.K.
What?
Rock, paper, scissors!
I'll go first.
I'll go first!
Hamada-san, you go first!
The first one is...
The name of the state in America.
That's good.
It's easier!
It's easier, isn't it?
That's Hamada!
Say more!
I don't know that!
It's easier!
It's actually easier.
You guys are so dumb!
Speaking of summer's seasonings...
Mr. Hamada, please.
Watermelon.
Windmill.
What about us?
Ice strawberry.
Wait a minute.
You don't say that?
No, no, the ice is my...
My
I'll be in the Kourin series from now on.
I have a lot of friends.
I wish I could find a series.
That's right, Katsuo-san.
I see.
I always talk about it.
Yoyo Tsuri.
Ok, it's a book store.
There is a book store.
I said OK.
You are so mean to the talent.
OK.
OK, Mr. Matsumoto.
Super Bowl Tsuri.
Hey!
OK.
Safe.
The shaved ice is just the smell of strawberry and lemon.
There is a reading rule.
Yes.
Mr. Matsumoto.
Tube.
Oh!
It's coming!
Okay!
Eh...
Sadan!
Wait a minute!
You said Sadan!
That's not right!
Ah, Sadan is not good!
The tube is a bit...
What?
Please, please, please, please, please, please!
Out!
You guys are really annoying!
Hey, come on, come on, come on!
Yeah, come on!
Here we go!
The second question is...
Guts-san will be the one to answer.
The world champion of boxing history.
Start!
Guts Ishimatsu.
That's right.
I'm laughing, so I'll just say it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Pim-pom!
Toka-chan.
What is the correct way to say Toka-chan?
Tokashiki Katsuo!
Fighting Harada!
Pim-pom!
Piston Horiguchi!
Boo!
And...
It's over!
Thank you.
Why do you look so sad?
The third question.
The name of the talent who has been in the east, west, south and north for a long time.
Kitajima Saburo.
Minami Kousetsu.
Minami Haruo.
Minami is in it.
Minami is different from Minami.
Oh!
OK, OK.
It was a good show.
Thank you.
Let's go to the next one.
Tokyo, 23 districts.
Meguro district.
Kenpon.
Nakano district.
Pimpo.
Edogawa-kun.
What?
What is this?
Hey! Hey!
Here it comes.
Let's go.
Should we say four letters?
Then, from Matsuboshi-san, go ahead.
Eh, Sessa Takuma.
Oh.
Ichigoichi.
Eh, Baji Tofu.
Eh,
What was it?
Shochiku Bai.
Yeah!
Thank you!
I'm not going to do it!
Please go to the first round!
It's D1!
Hamada-san, D1!
Can you move a little bit to the side?
A little bit more.
Face the front.
Scary!
You won't be able to break the sunken glass.
Let's go with the names of the couple.
Well, that is...
Sonomama-san and Kato Kazuko-san.
Yes.
Well...
Ikue-chan and...
No, not Kato.
Watanabe Toru-san and...
Yes.
Nagato Hiroyuki and Minamida Yoko.
Oh!
He knows a lot about that!
Who would do that?
There are still a lot of people.
Well, well, well, OK.
Why did you get caught by that?
You're not allowed to get caught!
You're done!
Out!
That was a good one.
You're still here.
Okay, last one.
Not yet.
You're still not ready.
I'm trying to do it.
Masato-san, Kounin!
The name of the person who was on the Choja Banzuke in 1999!
Best 10!
How is it?
Ah, then...
Hamada Masatoshi
Yes, that's right
The one next to me
The one next to you, that was included too
What kind of way is that?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Um, Ishibashi Takahaki.
Yes.
I don't know from there.
But I don't know from there.
Well, it's a lie.
There are seven more.
Well, that's not an example.
An example?
Let's go.
What do you do with an example?
Please stand up.
Um, Akashiya-san.
Eh?
It's not in!
Ahhhh!
No!
Thank you!
It's not in!
It's in!
No, it's not in!
It's just a little bit in!
Now!
Mr. Tanaka!
I strong
веро Nee
Takahashi
Make come
The There
Sak revealed
Kirby
Yamaguchi
видео
I'm so tired!
Hamada, did you gain more weight?
Yo, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
The innkeeper is a good friend.
We always drink together.
The innkeeper's wife.
The night is a dark inn.
Ha ha!
The next day
Let me introduce you to Seiro-kun
He's not that popular but you're also black
I'm not that popular, you shouldn't think about me
I'm a summer holiday
I'm not working at all!
You're not thinking!
You're a fool! You've been on a trip twice!
No, I was in Okinawa for a while.
So you were in Okinawa before that?
No, I was working in Okinawa.
I had no choice but to go to work.
I didn't do it because I wanted to.
That's fine.
You were in Guam?
I was in Guam.
People who have been on this channel will be surprised!
What are you talking about?
Probably the darkest combination in Japan.
Well, well...
Well, for now.
With the collar too.
It's funny.
But in Okinawa, you wore a typhoon, didn't you?
I wore a typhoon. You wore a typhoon.
And then, what was it...
For about two days, something terrible happened.
What?
It was like a festival.
Rain and wind.
It was like a whirlwind.
I was wondering how strong the wind was.
I thought I would slip and fall down.
I have a weird back.
I can't help it.
I was like,
You can't do that.
You know, you didn't do the earth's work.
You're so bad at this.
You're not even good at it.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
You're so noisy. You're scary.
You can't do that.
No, I can't do it if my blood pressure changes.
What's that?
If I get on the plane, I'll get a fever.
Oh, really?
No, no.
You're saying that.
You're scared, right?
I was in Okinawa and I was taken to a place called Hakunijima.
I was put on a plane and it was really small.
I got on it suddenly.
What does it mean to get on it suddenly?
It was like this.
I have been on a plane with 6 people.
You are a woman who has been on a plane with 6 people.
It's like you said.
You're kidding me!
When I got on the plane, you said you were scared.
I thought you would definitely be scared.
Because the captain would hand me a towel.
Behind me.
I was like, what the hell?
The passengers would hand me a towel.
That's right.
I don't have a towel.
I'm a person who treats people with kindness.
I was so scared of that thing!
But it's fine, you've experienced it, right?
I'm laughing, but usually, when there's a big plane, they say,
Turn the door mode on.
That's just a voice, but there's no way the door mode would go off.
I thought I had to say something, but I thought,
What should I say?
I turned from the right propeller.
I told the audience about it.
Oh, really? I turned.
I was looking right.
I looked left. I turned left.
I went back and forth.
I was burned like a local old man.
I felt like a man who was wrapped in a towel.
I was wearing this and that when I was in Nankai.
I explained the situation to the stewardess and the old man went back.
I said, I'll go around from the right propeller.
I'll go around from the right propeller because I'm in a good mood today.
I can't say anything.
Why did you put it on?
I didn't say anything at first because I was in a good mood.
What is this?
I thought I could do it, so I took it off.
I thought I should say left, but I think it's better to say right.
How many days did you go?
About 4 days.
Ah, 4 days.
Well, 4 days is the best.
Yes.
It's not like it's cut off.
I'm taking videos from far away.
Yes, yes, yes.
How many times did it cut off?
But I'm more angry at the fact that she's so far away from me.
That's the thing I want you to stop the most.
That's a first-class thing in Tokyo.
It's a first-class thing.
If you go to a place like that, I don't think you should stay still.
No matter how many times I go, the old lady in Osaka is the most powerful.
In Osaka, in the whole world, all over the world.
That old lady in Osaka is...
She's powerful.
Did you go there?
Yes, I did.
I slipped on the mat.
You were wearing a swimsuit.
I slipped on the long mat.
I don't understand.
There was a swimming pool.
There was a Tartar.
It wasn't Tartar.
I don't think so.
There was another one.
I was like, whoaaaa!
And then, I took a picture of the old lady.
I was doing the video.
At that time, you were so excited?
I was like, this is so funny!
I thought I should run and run again and take a picture of her.
I was doing it all the time.
She was obviously taking a picture of me.
I was like, excuse me.
But the worst thing is that I have no children.
When I look at my bag, I have no one!
What the hell is this?
This is what I look like.
Right?
Really.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What is that?
I was taken this kind of face.
I remembered that, but it was still funny.
There's a guy like that, a slider. He's always so excited.
He's like, Mr. Matsumoto, you go this way, I'll go this way.
Let's see who's faster!
And then he goes,
When he goes,
His head goes like this.
When I came out, I was like this.
I was very excited.
This is a Soba-don, so I bought it!
I'm angry.
What are you angry about?
I'm sorry.
It's your fault.
It's my fault.
This pool is so hot.
What kind of way do you use to hit here?
I don't know.
Marimo was playing and he said,
That was painful.
It was scary.
And he was really scared.
Was it this kind of face?
What?
You're making it sound like a movie.
As the winner, I have a question for you, Mr. Matsumoto.
In pro baseball, the coach often goes to the referee's decision and leaves.
How do you decide whether the referee will let you leave or not?
I see.
There are people who often get hit in the shoulder.
What about that?
If the judge thinks it hurts, he will be released.
If the judge thinks it hurts when he hits you with his shoulder, will you be released?
You will be released.
What if he hits you with his shoulder?
Can you hit him with your shoulder?
You tell me.
Please try to hit my face.
I'll show you just for your own good.
What the hell is that?
What is that?
For example, if you say, I'm the one who did it!
I'm the one who did it!
You're saying that, right?
If you say that, you can't be released.
If you touch it like this...
This is...
This is not for you...
Stop it!
But you're the one who did it!
What are you doing?
I'm doing it!
So, if you feel pain...
Pain is absolutely no good.
So, you're going to be discharged from the hospital if you make fun of me?
Making fun of you?
Judgment.
Judgment?
Isn't that a possibility?
For example, if you approach me like this...
What's that black thing?
That's not something you can laugh about and keep laughing about.
What is it?
Something like this.
That's not something you can do and keep laughing about.
But I've been doing it all this time.
From the front of the second floor to the back of the eighth floor.
I can't fight anymore.
I'm told to go back to the bench.
I'm doing it even if I go back to the toilet.
I don't care about that.
This is a question for Matsumoto-san who is going to be 500 years old soon.
Please tell us your impressions of the battle at Sekigahara.
I was nervous.
Hey, hey!
Before it started.
That's funny.
I was nervous before it started.
I was so excited.
When it started,
It's not like that.
I was already excited.
I was like,
Waaaaaaah!
But before it started,
Before it started,
I knew it was going to be like that.
What kind of story?
I was told to wait a little bit more for the setting.
Which one is it?
No, I was waiting.
But it's like this.
It's like the story of the Seki girl.
I don't know.
We are in trouble.
No, no, no.
What is it?
How was it?
In the end, there were so many people that we had to fight.
The battle at Sekigahara was amazing.
I thought, this will be remembered in history.
Really?
When I heard the sound of the gun, I thought, this will be remembered in history.
Who did you tell that to?
I told him I knew him.
You were friends?
Yes, we were friends.
We were in the same school.
Oh, I see.
I asked him how he was doing.
He said he was nervous.
I told him I was nervous.
We became friends.
He said, wow.
He was also pushing me.
I'm done.
This is a historical document.