The next day
Excuse me
Yamasaki san said, if you can come, then come
No, I can't come
No
What do you mean?
I don't understand
If you can come, then come
No, no, no
I was there earlier
I'm not sure.
If you can come here, then come.
You want to see it?
Yes.
Outside?
Yes, outside.
What is it?
Excuse me, please come this way.
This is a domino.
Yes.
No, no, no.
I knew it.
Excuse me, please come this way.
What?
Please.
What's this?
Still holding a acorn...
Ш Sheikh!
Well…"
Here's the key to your luck
writer
In this MYSTERY WORLD
There's a lot of
equipment
A ring that imitates acorns
once I am here
MANIFFICIENT
like because I'm the king of the azure eye
You punk
Bring this four weeks toes
If you find it, I will give you a wonderful treasure.
However, in order to know if this gold gold coin exists, I have to solve the mystery I thought of.
Can you solve my mystery with your wisdom?
Then I will give you the first hint.
Now, please bring out the goddesses of fortune.
You idiot.
Ah, I missed. Ah, it's a coin.
It's not on the coin.
So what should I do?
I should find the goddess of fortune.
I wonder if it's gold or four pieces.
It's a children's show.
This is a big place.
I was told to look for it here.
Something like that.
Clearly.
What's that?
Is that a goddess?
Yes, it is.
What's that?
That's a first class machine.
It's a first class machine.
It's a first class machine for kids.
Is this a goddess?
It's a goddess.
Is it a goddess?
It's a special thing that you can see from a vehicle.
The puzzle that can be seen from the vehicle is called Tokubesshi.
Tokubesshi, I see.
Toku is Tokubesshi.
Is it over there?
Over here?
Why is it a B-bock?
This is also a smoke.
Then, Endo, go!
Everyone?
I don't like it!
This is pretty scary.
Wait a minute!
No, no, no, no, no.
So what kind of movement is it?
There's something!
It's pretty scary!
There it is!
Good luck!
It's a red one!
What is this?
It's coming forward!
Come on, come on!
I don't know.
Please be careful with your hands.
Thank you very much.
The last one is the last one, right?
I don't know anything.
The first one is probably like a karaoke.
Karaoke?
Honestly, the two in the middle didn't see it.
I haven't seen it either.
I'm sorry, Mr. Hamada.
I can't see it.
You didn't see it at all.
I saw it.
Why should I go?
I asked.
To be honest, this is the second time.
It's a very cut candidate.
I saw the same picture twice.
I got it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay if you do it.
You're a weird kid.
No, no, no.
I can't use this.
Look at this.
Did you see?
I didn't see anything.
A toothbrush and a pencil.
A fire bug?
No, it's a tower!
A beetle!
A tower?
A chimney!
It's a chimney!
A beetle?
It's a beetle, right?
The word that came out is...
If you think of a beetle, there's the next command, right?
It's a beetle, right?
What the hell is this?
A beetle? I think there's a beetle in the ride.
That's definitely not it.
A flying beetle.
There's no doubt about it.
There might be a gold coin.
There's nothing here.
Hey! What's this?
What's this white thing?
I think it's a part of the gold coin.
This is the worst child's story.
I see.
It's a gold coin.
Really?
I think it's a gold coin.
It's a coin.
Here it comes.
Gentlemen, you understand very well.
I have been working for Mr. Dilber for 25 years.
I am not a brah.
But the second gold coin is not that easy to get.
Then, I will give you the next scene.
I have a big hero who was buried in the ground in his villa.
Please eat the western food.
It's about time for your soup, so I'll be around here.
Good, good, good, good, good.
What is this?
I don't feel like talking about this.
Eat the sacred food that the great hero who will rule the earth has.
Eat?
What is this?
Is it sold somewhere?
I'm not sure.
I'm sorry.
What?
Do you eat this?
Is there anything to put on it?
You can eat it.
There's nothing.
You can put ketchup on it.
You can put it on it.
You can eat it.
There's a lot of them.
What should I do with this?
You should eat it.
Say it.
Say it when you're not supposed to.
There's definitely nothing in this.
You ate it all.
Ah!
Ahhhh!
I'm gonna eat this.
What's the meaning of this?
When you show your courage, you'll know what's gold or not.
What's this?
This is for Hamada-san.
Hamada-san's courage is being tested.
Can I leave this?
Eat it all.
Why are you so fair?
This is dangerous.
This is not good.
This is bad.
Wait a minute. This is bad.
Why are we standing still?
It's time to show your courage.
It's really me.
It's Hamada-san.
It's big.
This is...
This is the senior and junior.
This is the senior.
Hamada-san.
Help me!
This is Hamada-san!
Hamada-san, you're the best!
Wow, it's so high!
I want to kill Hamada right now.
What are you talking about?
The next day
How was it?
He's crying
Unfortunately, I've never been in trouble
I hope you eat it
There's something
It's like going to the men's toilet
I see
There it is
I think it's the same
Oh, it's true!
Ouch!
It's done!
Oh my god!
Why is this one sticking out?
This is a very dangerous thing to do.
Why is it in the toilet?
It's good.
Let's open the box and the one with the most.
Ready, set...
This one!
This one, right?
Let's open it!
What is this?
You're so scary.
It's still the same.
What is this?
You opened the box, didn't you?
You got caught.
Then, open this one.
But, it's open.
Oh, oh, oh!
It's a second one.
It's easy.
I just left it there.
I'm so heavy!
Then just leave it here.
Let's find something.
Shoo! Shoo!
Oh, another one.
Here it comes.
Hi!
Are you surprised?
You can't open the surprise box.
My name is Audrey.
I'm working for Mr. Gilbert.
Because Mr. Gilbert is a cutie.
Well, your adventure continues.
When you go down the slope of hope, an angel will appear.
Oh no, it's already this late. I have to hurry.
Alright, see you later.
The angel of hope?
It's a good thing that the weather is nice today, but it's not good to be shaken even by a child.
Please read this.
What?
I kicked it.
I'll tell you a great secret, so wait in front of the nearby public telephone.
I wrote something.
Call me?
It says, call me.
Hello?
It's the GAL from before. Did you call me?
Yes, I did.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha. You're lying.
What a shame.
I'm the phantom thief, Jiruba.
I'll teach you the secret of the gold gold coin.
Yes.
Go in the direction of the arrow.
Hello?
Yamazaki?
It's a phantom thief.
He's a phantom thief.
Why does he want to write down the arrow and give us the gold coin?
This is the one, right?
Ah, this is it!
It's a go-kart!
It's a go-kart that's divided into two people in a van.
We don't know what a van is.
That's true.
It's a ride-or-die thing.
Let's go!
What are you doing?
What's the point of riding that?
This is it! It's Jiruba!
You've been caught again, guys.
I am Jiruba's eternal rival, the 100-point clock!
I have many traps, so be careful!
I also 20 years ago, in West River,
I was bitten by a white crocodile and died!
Please be careful!
Then, tell me where the next gold gold coin is!
Why are you laughing?
You dirty Ero brothers!
You two will explore the mansion where the monster's hair grows
and take the gold gold from the king of terror.
I pray for your safety.
Who is the dirty Ero brothers?
Ah, me and...
Eh?
Oh, you two are going to join us?
Again?
Ah, this combination?
Yes, yes.
I'm sure you'll be surprised.
Then, Chibiero Brothers.
Do your best, Chibiero Brothers.
I'll get the gold.
I'm counting on you.
I'll get it.
I'm gonna die if you don't move.
Nothing came out.
I can't see anything in the circle.
Nothing came out yet.
It's a goldfish.
Scary, scary, scary, scary.
Something's coming.
Ahhhh!
It's a big surprise.
Don't do that.
Scary!
You're not breaking the screen at all.
I'm with Hamasato!
I'm scared!
Ahhhh!
I'm a cameraman!
It's not funny.
Why?
I'm done!
What?
I'm scared by myself.
I'm scared.
Please help me.
Heibo, shut up.
Shut up, Heibo.
Heibo is the scariest.
Heibo, go forward.
What is this?
No.
Heibo, shut up.
It's not funny.
Hey, it's so small.
What are you doing?
Wait, wait.
You were on it?
In that place.
Oh, there's a monitor.
Yes.
I didn't notice at all.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
How was it?
It was a refreshing experience, wasn't it?
What is this?
Even so, you have already obtained three gold coins, haven't you?
Who is this?
Well, what is this?
Lastly, please find Tama-chan's friend and obtain the gold coins there.
You, the Chakre Brothers...
Chakre Brothers?
You should go there!
I've already been asked to do this!
This will be your last adventure.
What?
Tama-chan's...
Hey, come out!
I'm done with this!
I saw something.
Tama-chan's...
What's with Tama-chan's?
My friend was looking at me.
It's your last adventure, right?
I think something's burning.
I don't know if I can do it.
The size is different, so it's not that hard.
It's stuck.
These guys are from the road.
Look at this.
It's a hamster.
You're hiding it all the time.
Hamster.
Ah, Tama-chan.
I'm looking for Tama-chan's friend.
That's why I'm looking for a new type.
Ah, a new type.
Ah, this is Ashika.
Ah, there's something.
I'm going to put it on the bottom.
It's a medal.
Ah, a medal!
Did you get it? That one!
It's a medal.
The last one.
If you get close, you can get it.
But if you get close, you'll be like, pshhh.
That's amazing.
I'll start.
Ah, it's already hot.
I can't catch it.
Tanaka, catch it.
I'm going to push.
I knew it.
It's so easy.
I caught it.
Kaito, Zilber, Foo...
I got it.
It's not as easy as I thought.
Is it Zilber?
Zilber.
Congratulations.
You've finally found the 4 gold coins.
Now, with the 4 gold coins, we'll go down the hill of fate.
We are also humans.
Behind the door, there are treasures waiting for us.
Waiting for us?
We'll be happier than you guys.
I'm waiting for you to read the
The treasure is waiting.
There is something to be angry.
Oh, that's it.
There is such a place.
Oh, look.
It fits here.
It fits.
The last one.
The last fight.
Do you know what it is?
It came.
I don't know who's crying when I say it's in.
It's in!
Look, it's out!
It's a key.
The key came out.
Ah, that key!
You said it's in, so you took it out.
That's right.
Thank you.
It's in.
Here we go.
Yes.
End.
Here we go.
Yes.
End.
Ah, I see.
So you want me to sit down?
Yes, you can sit down.
Let's see.
Let's go.
The opening.
Everyone, let's go!
1,2,3!
I'm in love with your throat-colored cheeks
I'm staring at your machined line
If we look at each other with a sparkling look
My heart will go crazy
I'm in love with your throat-colored cheeks
It's too fast!
It's a little too fast, isn't it?
Aga-sen is here.
Yeah!
I want to start with a one-sided love.
I want to love you so much that I don't know what I don't know.
I don't remember.
Ah, I can't go back to that person
I can't go back to my lover
I can't go back to my dreams
I don't know.
I don't know the lyrics.
This is almost a full chorus.
I thought it was a foreign singer, but it's been a while.
Ah, it's over.
I'm hungry.
Hello.
What?
What is this?
Yama-chan wanted to do this.
I wanted to show this to you.
I'll leave it to you.