In the past 3 episodes, the famous people of the entertainment world competed in the black bass fishing tournament.
This time, the fishermen gathered with the pride of men.
In the first and second episodes, Matsumoto won the championship in a row.
Last year, Itoi Shigesato won the first prize.
Who will be the winner this year?
In the fourth episode, the entertainment world fishers will compete in the black bass fishing tournament.
Yeah!
So!
We're here!
Yes!
It's the first time for me
This is the first time for me
First of all, this person
Who is it?
Recently, on the weekend, he played a game with his child in the park
Hamada Matsumoto!
Oh, he's here
You called me here
I'm the host
Nice to meet you
I'm an amateur
No!
We're the 6th year
Are you okay?
Yes
I've never won a championship.
That's right.
I'll do my best today.
Please win a big one.
Thank you.
Next,
He is a man who has recently improved his resistance to fat.
He is Mr. Matsumoto.
Dangerous.
I know this.
It's dangerous!
I'll do my best today.
I'm aiming for the victory and going home.
Yes!
What?
Why are you doing that?
It's not like that.
Thank you.
Let's go.
It's more popular than your CD.
Okada Tamio!
Nice to meet you!
How do you feel about us?
I don't know yet.
Nice to meet you!
Every time the long-legger is on the air, the shampoo smells good.
Yosuke Inochi!
Thank you for coming!
Nice to meet you!
What are you doing?
I'm just doing what I'm supposed to do.
Did you wait for something?
No, no, no. I didn't ask anything.
Thank you for coming!
Now, the next guest is amazing.
It's his first appearance.
Let's introduce the super big guest.
Mr. Yabunagi Yone!
Thank you for your hard work!
I'm so happy today.
I've been in the entertainment industry for 11 years and I've been ranked the same as everyone else.
I heard that you're the same age as Eguchi.
That's right. I'm Eguchi.
Eguchi?
I'm a new member of the team.
Do you know Voice?
What is Voice?
I'm going to sing and drink it.
You're a good singer.
I'll sing next to you.
And then, I'll do the fishing.
This is the last one.
Yes.
Itoi Shiritoshi!
I want to hear your name.
Who is it?
Oh, I see. Itoi-san won the last time.
I did.
Oh, I see.
While being banned from puns.
Now, let's start the meeting.
Tanaka-san, please say hello.
Yes.
A greeting of the meeting.
Please.
I want to see you guys, B-class talent and C-class copywriters, gather together and do something.
I don't think I can do it, but I don't know what's fun about fishing when you can't even fish.
It's tough.
Anyway, everyone, do your best!
Amazing!
Start!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
It's been a while since I've been to Kawasaki.
It seems that the situation isn't very good.
I just don't want to be around them.
Please take care of me.
I'm going to step up to the top 5, so I'm going to aim for 4th place.
I'm going to enjoy it.
It's been a while since I've been fishing.
I'd like to be in 2nd place, but I'm not sure if I can do it.
I'd like to enjoy it.
Hey! Why are you so far away?
Hey!
I'm here!
For the sake of the rainy season, there are many people here and Kawaguchiko is in an unstable condition.
Of course, the points to be caught are limited, and the three seats are gathered at one point to start casting.
This is the musician duo of Hamada and Okuda.
What about a day with a wind like this?
The wind is strong and his condition is terrible. He is a very angry person.
Itoi's father seems to be able to catch fish.
This is a new father-gag duo, Matsumoto and Itoi.
I have a bad feeling about today.
What is it?
Will you fall off the boat?
No, no, no. I think it's okay.
I think so, too.
Yes!
The first hit is Shigesato Itoi.
Thank you.
What?
Is it big?
No, it's small.
Itoi-san, I gave it to you.
Really?
Yes.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's just as I said.
Hamada and Okuda are in a hurry
And here is Eguchi and Yamazaki's duo
Yamazaki, you're ready to go online?
Thank you
I'm ready to go online
I'll save you anytime
No matter how much
For some reason, Yamazaki is being polite
What is the first prey?
It's a big one
A big one?
A big one
What is it?
Huh?
Oh, it's coming
Eguchi, did it hit?
It's a hit!
The two feel the impact
Idiot
On the other hand, Hamada and Okuda have no chance of winning
Come on, Okuda
I'm going
Hamada is in a good mood. He looks serious.
If you come here, I will throw you.
Go away!
I will hit you.
30 minutes have passed since the start. Matsumoto has no fish.
He has not caught anything since the beginning.
If I catch one more fish, I will be relieved.
Matsumoto is also anxious.
I got a hit!
This is the first hit for Yamazaki.
Wait a minute.
You did it.
You were ahead of me.
He said that he was tired and had a cold.
His body is weak.
His body is very weak.
He got caught by the camera.
Matsumoto also got a hit.
He got a hit.
It's not bad.
Slowly.
I'm sorry.
OK.
It was good.
I'm so relieved!
You're good.
I can't believe I caught such a big one.
Hamada and Okuda move to the next spot.
Okuda caught something for the first time.
This is so small.
I got something.
I caught a big one.
This is so great.
This is great.
Only Eguchi and Hamada are not caught.
It's time to put the fish in the net.
I brought the fish in the net.
Thank you.
Eguchi's fish was broken.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a whole fish.
Is this a calcium fish?
Yes.
There are still fish.
This is a Japanese fish called calcium.
I'm sorry.
I thought you would be able to do it.
What's going on between you two?
It's a love-dutch pair.
A love-dutch pair?
Please talk to me.
Please talk to me properly.
I can't talk when I'm drunk.
I don't have a hangover.
No?
That's good.
What a child.
Oh no!
Hamada is frustrated. At that moment, the rod is bent.
What is this? What is this?
What is this?
Look at this! This is bent!
It's bent like this.
Damn!
Seriously?
What is this?
Why am I like this?
On the other hand, Eguchi is also impatient.
I don't want to be a stickman after this.
I know.
This is bad.
At that time, Hamada is the first to be hit.
This looks big.
I was caught.
Really?
It's okay.
It's big.
Should I wind it?
Yes.
It's big.
Yes!
This is bad.
This is bad!
Eguchi is panicking.
Alright!
What is that thing you're holding in your hand?
This is...
This is the V.O. of the brand that Hana-san is promoting.
I'm going to drink this V.O.
We have a telegram for you, Sabino-san.
Telegram?
Okuda-san, nice to meet you. I'm Koko Riko.
Nice to meet you.
You guys?
We're about to debut as a group on Okuda-san's show.
Thank you.
Please support us.
Meanwhile, Itoi hits the second one.
But it's around there, right?
It's coming!
It's really coming.
Really?
I'm starting to feel the pressure
On the other hand, after catching the first fish, Masumoto has no luck
And Kokoriko appears with a sash
Hey! Big talent!
What do you think?
You caught one, right?
Really?
Mr. Idori is the second place
What do you think, Mr. CQ Rider?
CQ?
Sougo-san is CQ?
I have a photo.
First, I have a photo of Toji-san.
Please ask.
Since I don't have a sense of humor, I often get to see humor and jokes.
I think that's important.
Toji-san's remodeling course.
That's good.
That's the same as before.
I read the book, but it doesn't get fixed.
You read it well.
Thank you very much.
I have a photo of Mademou.
What is it?
It's the same book.
It's not a copy.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
You are a pervert.
You are thinking about weird things.
I'm a pervert, too.
But I can't win against you.
I lost.
Did you see Hamada's video?
I didn't see it.
But I heard it was big.
You said it with your mouth.
I was very happy.
It's pretty big.
It's as big as the Macadamia nuts.
If you say it's a nut, it's as big as the Macadamia nuts.
Really?
It looks big!
I'll stand it up.
Alright!
Thank you.
I'm not in the way.
You're in the way.
Everyone, it's Downtown Lure Time!
Downtown Lure Time was introduced last year.
This time, it was newly developed as a lure that can be caught in earnest.
Who will be the winner?
Let's choose the winner.
First, the musician team.
I'll take it.
Do you want to do it?
I'll do it.
Then, you do it yourself.
I'll do it with Matsumoto Rua.
Oh, no!
Ouch!
I got it!
I got it at first!
I got it at the Matsumoto Tour in Hamada!
Then, Matsumoto-san.
Yes.
I'll do it with Hamada.
Matsumoto-san, Hamada Rua.
Hitoh-san, please do it with Matsumoto Rua.
Eguchi-san, do it with Matsumoto Rua.
Yes, Matsumoto Rua.
Nohoshi-san, do it with Hamada Rua.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Ready, start!
Start!
How good is Downtown Lure?
Oh, it's swimming properly
It's swimming!
It's really not impossible to catch it
It's not zero
It might be better than the last time
The color is pretty plain, Masamodo Lure
At times like this, the fish are going to be caught
Oh, it's clear
It's a waste of time.
Time is useless.
You can't catch it.
Good luck. It's 100,000 yen.
You know you can't catch it, so you're saying 100,000 yen.
There is no hit or shit.
The downtown lower time is over!
Yay!
That was great!
One person, Eguchi, who can't catch anything.
I can't catch anything.
Why?
This is not the end.
Eguchi, who keeps asking himself the same question, is screaming in his heart.
Ah!
Hmm?
Are you coming?
Did he run away?
He ran away.
What?
I'm sorry.
That was a big one.
Did you get hurt?
Well...
I didn't think I would get hurt this much.
Ah...
Yeah.
How is it?
Eh?
Are you fishing?
Why are you eating the bait?
Fish, fish.
Eh?
I know it's hard to get into that kind of character.
It's not like that.
How is it, Tamiyo?
I'll do my best!
I'm coming!
You said it too much!
I'm sorry, Tano-san!
The exit where he moved repeatedly and looked for the right point,
changed the lures and went out to the last corner.
There was a man's will.
I'll definitely do it.
The first one to arrive is...
Is this how you do it?
It's coming!
It's coming! It's coming! It's coming!
Wait a minute, the drag...
The drag is hard.
It's huge!
What are you doing?
Reel! Reel!
Wait!
Oh, it's coming!
It's coming!
It's big!
The prey has finally arrived. Will Eguchi's determination be enough to tie itself up?
Stop for a moment.
It's big!
No, not like that.
The Elster has been caught!
Amazing!
So no one caught anything with this.
That's good.
It's dramatic.
Taigu is in a good mood and continues to hit.
The loser and the other members also hit repeatedly until the end.
And finally, the time is up.
I'll tell you a story.
I'm going to eat.
I don't know if I can win.
I don't know what to say. I think it's like, whatever you do, you win.
Thank you for your time.
The winner is...
The result is...
How about you, old man?
I don't think I can win.
Oh, really?
Is this enough?
Here it is.
This is amazing.
I'm not going to do that.
That's not good.
Yamanashi-san is...
21.
22.
22 points!
Eguchi-kun.
Eguchi-san.
Eguchi-kun, you should try it.
Okay.
This is...
8?
8.
It's about 8.5.
8.5.
8.5?
This is going to be 5.
Yes.
This is a little small.
From there?
That or this?
It's 8, right?
It's 8.
What is it?
It's huge!
This is huge.
It's 30!
30?
30!
Oh!
Hey!
You're so weak!
I'm not weak!
I'll try to see through the water.
Hurry up!
I'm begging you!
2, 2, 25!
Oh!
25cm!
I can't do it!
If you look at the
big
Thank you!
I got the first prize!
I thought you were lying!
Young lady, you are the 4th Chikichiki Entertainment Contest winner.
And...
So cute!
It's the 4th year!
After the election, without reading the surrounding atmosphere,
without making a big laugh,
What are you saying?
I hereby declare that the first-year students have achieved excellent results.
On July 1st, the Japanese National Team's producer, Sugai Kenichi.
Thank you!
This is the number one T-shirt!
This is a collaboration with everyone.
This is a trophy.
Thank you!
The prize is a prize for the winner, Hama-chan.
Okudai-san, please take the second T-shirt.
Thank you.
Here you are.
Number 2 T-shirt.
Thank you.
Number 3 T-shirt.
Number 3.
Eguchi-san, 25.5 cm.
Number 3 T-shirt.
Thank you.
Number 4 T-shirt.
I got 4.5 cm before.
Thank you.
And the winner is No.5.
No.5.
And the last one is 22cm.
It's a human t-shirt.
Why are you wearing this?
Please watch the video.
It's a high-class video.
Thank you.
I think the real hammer is better.
I'll send you this.
I'll be doing this for a couple of days in the fall, so please look forward to it.
I was 2nd place, so I'll start again from 4th place.
4th, 4th, 3rd place.
I'm a little bit higher than them.
Next time, I'll be in 2nd place and then 1st place.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please continue to support me.
I'm really frustrated.
I feel like I don't want to be in the top 3.
That's all I want to think about.
Thank you very much.
So, today's victory was a natural victory.
I can't beat him.
I'm a TV show host, Tsurijiman.
I'll come anytime.