The history of club activities with the kids
The life-threatening
High speed spinning
And tonight
Club activity part 3
The Kuchobashi Club starts
So Matsumoto-san
Yes
The new club has been launched
That's right
It's the Kuchobashi Club
Kuchobashi Club
This is what we call it, the Kuchobashi Club
For example
So, we're done with the end of the story.
What's going to happen next?
How long can we endure?
That's what I want to do.
I thought about it last week, but I've been depressed since last night.
I really hate this.
What is our name club?
This is the Baccarat.
You look strong.
Thank you.
The opponent today is…
Kusugurizurizu.
What?
This team is the leader of the Aroha.
Go ahead!
Oh, you're not telling us to laugh, but you're not making us laugh, right?
That's right, no matter what I do, the audience won't laugh.
Hey!
It's a trap.
It's a trick.
Hey, it's Matsumoto Hama.
Hello.
Why don't you call me high tension anymore?
Oh, you're right.
You're right, now that you mention it.
Oh, I know why you don't call me high tension anymore.
What is it? What's wrong?
What?
A hot spring trip.
Oh, that.
Well, if you say it like that, it's...
I can't do it, but I know you're a loser in the hot spring trip!
I betray women, but I don't betray men.
If I win today, I'll let each of you stay at my house.
No way!
Please.
Hey!
Hey, what's going on?
What?
You know, I can't take this kind of reaction anymore!
I want to laugh at it with my words!
His face is shining.
What?!
This kind of reaction...
Let's do it again.
Let's have the chairperson do it.
Thank you.
is that you notice that knock in the corner is old Japanese profiteering equipment?
banging in front of your boyfriend is not the ultimate.
The more you push your boyfriend the stronger the nail taking in the works.
My industry in This district shows a lot of performance when you 당신er in the 36th, separ Soviet world cup games.
I see.
What do you call the person?
I call him Double.
Wait a minute, the season is off.
Is there a season off for comedians?
Yes, there is.
Do your best!
Congratulations!
Let me explain the rules.
The challenge is to have both teams compete with each other.
The team mates will be given a time limit until the time is up.
The team's total time will determine the winner.
The time limit will be announced after the challenge is over.
First up is Kusugurizuri's player, Fukawa Ryo.
What will be his reaction?
Ah, I'm tired.
I'm tired.
The parents of the mountains
Oh no!
It's not good!
No, no, no!
It's too much!
No!
Wait, Fuka, can't you do a stone-pushing move?
You keep saying no, but you can't do it.
The no and the happiness,
the happiness...
The happiness is the most important thing.
It's a bit of a burden.
But the voice is not coming out properly.
It's fine.
Then, for now, we'll talk about the usual things.
Yes.
Shouldn't we start with Endo?
That's right.
Are you okay?
Really, to a person called Eri-san,
Endo-kun really is a whole body life form.
A whole body life form.
Eri-san is a fool.
Like a romance novelist.
The battle with Kojoba Pharo is over.
How long will the body of the
Sensen Seikan team last?
I'll do my best.
I really can't move at all.
Please.
Ready!
Wait a minute.
Yes, yes.
Start!
It's no good.
I can do it.
Hamada is a very Wizard.
Track him down.
It is not allowed if you show your venirison, and you guys want me to do that side...
I'm scared of your acting!
I can't stand it!
You'll never be able to do it when I'm around!
Please stop it!
I'm scared of your acting!
Really?
Hey, this is not good!
You can still do it!
I can do it!
What's wrong with you?
But I'm practicing now.
Oh, really?
It's a bit of a burden.
I'm sorry, but that's really...
What's wrong?
I want to go over there and smile.
You're like that.
That's right.
What?
That's true.
The law of the Kusugurizuri is the law of the house.
Can you show us the
That's right.
What?
That's not true.
The law of the game is to be self-sufficient.
Can he show his true self in a poor life?
Ready...
Start!
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
I'm scared!
Oh my god!
He's shaking!
I'm scared!
A 5-year-old?
Oh my god!
I'm scared!
Help me!
Say it properly!
What's wrong?
Is this Yamaguchi?
Who is it?
Wow!
I didn't want to see you!
I see!
I saw you quite a lot!
I was born in the year of the rat.
You have a very good sense of smell.
The one who is not a child is Yamasaki.
Can he withstand the mental strength of a middle-aged man and a child who is as good as a child?
Mr. Yamada, you look fine.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Alright, let's go!
Yes!
Good luck.
Ready...
Go!
Okay.
Nice touch.
He's trying his best.
This mountain, this mountain, this mountain, come here!
Good luck!
I'm sorry.
It's dangerous.
Open it.
I'm sorry.
It's dangerous.
It looks like a
there should be a lane for it
B, re, d
There should be a lane for it
There should be a lane
I'm sorry!
This is bad.
I can't take this anymore.
I thought I was going to die.
You're surprisingly sticky.
No one is going to draw that.
I don't want to do this anymore!
That's why I told Takasu!
I'm a strong man, so I'll definitely do it!
You're really strong!
Really!
The second round of the Kusuguri series is the self-proclaimed chief, Inoue.
After being cornered to the extreme, he's the one to pay attention to.
Inoue.
Before you go, tell me what you call a tea bowl.
A tea bowl.
Yo!
Alright, start!
The answer is...
Oh, that's strong.
But it's different from usual.
I can't get it.
What do you call this thing?
Fu...Fu...Fuutarou.
It's strong.
That's a big idiot.
I'm listening to Beethoven.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
This is bad.
Wow, amazing.
This is strong.
I don't think I have that much weight.
Tanaka is probably S.
I'm counting on you, Mr. Tanaka.
Please give me a good place.
Of course.
I think you have the ability.
Otherwise, I will go beyond the limits of my seniors and juniors.
The middle fielder is Tanaka.
He is short but has a S heart.
The Saya baby noises challenge the sky.
Do your best.
Ready...
Go!
You can not win!
That's enough
I
are are are are are Chef Taro Hamada!?
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
I get it!
It would be more fun if you do it like that!
He's saying that.
Really?
Well, well, well.
You were just rolling it out.
As expected?
It's okay.
Because,
He laughed more than Tanaka.
Stop it!
Really, stop it!
How pitiful.
I'm going to become a professor of psychology or something.
I'll be told like this.
Captain Kimura Yuichi is the vice-champion of the Kusugurizuri.
It looks strong to the eye, but...
This...this...this...
This magic tape is a little...
Let's go!
Ready...
Go!
Ouch! Ouch!
What?
What's wrong?
Stop it!
I'm sorry!
Which one is it?
You can do it!
Shima-san!
Shima-san, answer!
Answer!
You can do it!
Say something!
Eh?
You can do it!
Which one is it?
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no!
I'm done! I'm done! I'm done!
Wow, I've never seen this before.
You were talking in your voice.
I was acting like a girl.
Kojima Faro's nickname is the dress comedian Hamada.
What will happen if the person on the other side is defeated?
This is pretty scary.
What do you think?
It's not scary at all.
Eh, this is exciting.
It's exciting even for you.
It's a S.
That's the way M thinks.
Hama-san, ready, start!
I'm ready!
Oh, it's coming!
How is it?
It's good.
Good.
Your face is still good.
Is it okay?
No!
No, this is not good.
This is not good.
You'll be kicked out.
aur to talk!
Let's go!
Take it easy!
I'm about to die!
Let's get him out of here!
I will do my best!
Omiya-san, do your best!
Do your best!
I will do my best!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Omiya-san, you did your best!
Nice fight!
Amazing, isn't it?
You were a great teacher.
There was a time when I had a cramp.
You had a cramp in the spring and summer.
It ended in the summer.
It was like that at first.
What did you say at first?
When I cut a part, a switch comes in.
I think that switch is different for each person.
I knew it when I did it myself.
I don't think I can do it.
No, no, no.
The winner of the Kusugurizuri is Jodan's Mimata.
Let's see how he does after he's recovered.
What do you think of Mimata?
I think he's a bad guy.
I wish he was a cuter guy.
Mimata is a cutie!
He's a cutie!
I don't think he's a cutie.
It's not there.
Start!
This one.
It's like, go straight.
Hey, can you change it with the camera?
It's not there.
What is this?
There's no pot yet.
Oh, I see.
What is this?
If I get a present, I'll be happy.
This is good.
This is...
Ah, here it comes.
This is a Nampo course!
Ah, Mr. Akiyama, this is no good.
What's not good?
This is no good.
You already knew?
No, it's...
We can still do it, right?
No, we can't do it.
We can do it, we can do it.
Right?
No, no, no.
No, this is...
I'm done.
That's the same thing!
That's so dangerous!
I'm raising the bar!
I don't want to see it!
The feel is too different!
The feel is different!
I'm self-sufficient!
But Matsumoto-san, you have to do your best too!
That's right!
It was long!
Kojoba Parod's leader is Matsumoto!
Will he show the true power of the Do-Em-Gainer?
He challenges the last battle
I'm going to win!
I'm begging you, really
It's okay, it's okay!
I'm begging you
Yabai!
Nice shot!
Straight Cut Maximum Strength
a sorry
Co- mammal!
Are you OK?
Ok, I can't still do.
More, more!
Get a motorbike!
Does anybody know?
Does anybody wanna try?
It's Shurg can!
It's the welder!
пон jeux
Oh!
milk
gaming
Alright!
It's eroded it's eroded!
Says
Scan Tayo
Test
That seems to be Shin Kayo
Was there someone?
Was there anyone?
Was there anyone was there
Finally
There was
It was rather tough
IT
Oh!
My!
Gou Priest!
I'm done!
Let's see the times of both teams!
First, the time of the first team.
The time of the second team is...
26 seconds!
That's pretty good.
Then, the first team.
What about Endo?
Endo.
30 seconds!
Okay!
That's pretty good.
Okay, okay, okay.
I really felt it.
I feel it.
F einge's record covers the entire event, the GC part between Uncle Yama, With müze ahead of Tsubohashi and Numbern-san
and the versuchen race, KOTSUBA HOR örrhomoz took advantage of fame.
strong fighting spirit, from number of girls to 함 be a fierce opponent.
This is it!
His которой was a nice time
wait. How many minutes?
about twenty-one minutes
4 seconds or more.
Wow, that's not good.
I'll go for 1 point.
Close it.
Wow, wow, wow.
Wow, okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
Let's see the butt.
I see, that's the butt.
The butt, the butt, the butt.
4 seconds, 4 seconds.
Wow.
That means...
3 seconds.
20 seconds is not enough.
You have to win with 3 seconds or more.
I won by 1 point.
I was almost beaten.
I'll make it vertical.
1 point or 4 points?
1 point or 4 points.
If you win by 1 point, you win.
He won by 20 seconds.
I'm happy.
Well, I guess they didn't raise the flag for 1 minute and 43 seconds.
The 4th DVD is about to be released.
The last one to be released for 4 months is the cut-and-paste talk with the un-released scenes that couldn't be broadcast on TV.
And the 15-year long battle, the punishment game, will be released in full swing.
Look forward to it!
Please, please!
Thank you very much!