Kazushige Nagashima's honest rumour, Soda Kareta-san
For example, who is the old idol?
Kawai Naoko-san
That's true
And also, Ikue Sakagibara-chan
Even though I'm angry at my son for saying that
You're looking at him with that kind of eyes?
I remember that.
There was a TV show where Mr. Ega threw a batting ball at Matsui and Ega explained the rules.
After Matsui finished batting, he jumped in to get in.
I thought I'd get out of the game and get in, but Ega didn't even look at me.
That was really a trick.
I want to do a voice acting.
I have to match the voice with the picture on the rock.
But it doesn't fit no matter how many times I try.
It does fit.
I changed the picture later.
You changed it?
I'll call you after that.
I'm the champion!
Hamada is the first to win the first half.
Who will win?
The rules are simple.
The person with the most points will receive a present from Kazushige.
Here we go.
I'm so excited!
Please bite my earlobes!
Da!
It's Da!
Da?
Not Da, it's Da!
Ah, sorry, it's Da?
It's Da, right?
Yes, it's Da!
Ah, I see.
What's going on?
This is also a bit erotic.
It's like that.
It's about what I like and what I don't like.
I like my right side.
Do you bite?
I can bite.
I think there are parts that you want to bite.
Do you have any parts you want to bite?
I don't have any parts I want to bite.
Are you a god?
Of course I'm a god.
But I don't think you're a god.
How many?
About the nipples.
Ah, the nipples
No, it's the one that's biting
If it's a mosquito, it's either painful or not painful
It's not like that
It's being abused
It's not about being bitten
There's something
No, no
I really don't think it's good
You guys should relax and do a free talk
Of course you want to be bitten
No, not at all.
Who's scary?
Where do you want to be bitten?
I'm all for the ultimate law.
You want to be bitten?
I don't want to be bitten.
I don't know what it is.
There must be.
Endo is a bad guy.
He's not an adult at all.
No, it's not.
He's worried about his wife.
He's close to the interview at the children's school.
I see.
He's in the middle.
I think that's a negative.
When I went to the interview, I said I wanted to be bitten.
I think the child will be affected.
What kind of school is that?
Let's go.
Present
Give or receive, red rose.
Is it a negative?
It's a negative.
I'm getting a lot of flowers.
I'm in front of you.
I really like to get flowers.
Is that so?
My mother loves red roses.
I always give flowers to my mother in Hawaii.
I want to get red roses too.
Men don't like flowers.
N-no, I never bought you anything.
You never bought her a flower?
Even a present?
What?!
Well, you never gave any gifts to her.
But!
I don't know if you never ordered a group of flowers.
Oh, OK, but on the stage?
Or the там?
A partyING for you?
You got it, too?
A wedding anniversary?
I'll send it to you after I've ordered it.
Wow, that's amazing.
That's a lie.
I got an image.
What are you guys aiming for?
It's not a lie.
I don't want to give it to you guys.
I'll send it to you.
A stupid one?
There's a company.
I'll do it.
That's nice.
I'll do it for the stage.
I'll do it.
Do you give your wife a kiss?
No, I don't.
I give her a gift.
If it's a gift, it's a flower.
Do you kiss your wife?
Yes, I do.
I see.
But you are a couple.
I also...
kiss?
I do.
Why are you saying such a thing?
I'm already 50.
You kiss your wife.
Why do you kiss your wife?
You kiss your wife, right?
I don't have a wife.
You're speaking in a weird way.
Let's start.
I've never heard of Matsumoto-san's high school days.
It's a C.
I've never heard of it.
I won the championship when I was 20 years old in a TV show.
Oh, the one about the comic book.
The one about the adult.
But I've heard a lot about my high school days.
Oh, high school days.
But you were more into my high school days than yourself.
Well, I was in the first year of high school, so I don't know much about my school days.
It's a school that makes you feel like you're going to a junkyard.
We don't take any classes.
It's a school that smokes cigarettes during class.
No, no, no.
Even if I say it, there were about 32 percents.
That's the last one.
At least 25.
7 is also over.
And that's the one from Amagasaki Industrial High School.
I was in that machine car.
There were many bad things.
And domestic violence.
Yes, really.
The Bebop High School was destroyed.
It was that time.
Everyone was really bad.
In the past, everyone was riding a motorcycle in the high school.
It was normal.
It really happened.
It happened when I was in middle school.
The other gangsters were all like this in middle school.
They stopped their classes.
There were times like that.
There was a school called Odako next to it.
It's a school for male and female.
There was a lot of jealousy about it.
This is a boys' school.
But when Odako passed by, everyone choked.
Choke?
The national road is so stupid.
That's a little cute.
I was in the school where the match was held.
All-girls.
There were only girls who were discriminating in the class.
I was surprised.
So that's the rest of the voice room.
No.
Yes, yes, yes.
It was like,
I'm going to announce the results!
Really,
During a normal class,
I'm going to announce the results!
It was like this.
In the high school dormitory,
The results were announced, right?
The news reported it, this guy.
During the class, he suddenly had a parasite.
Eh? Matsumoto-san?
Is that so?
During the class,
During the class, suddenly,
Ahhhhh!
No, no, no!
You're so mean!
Let's start!
Okay!
The truth is...
I don't know...
I never gave up on the path of a leader.
Really?
I want to hear this.
Come on!
I did it there.
Leader...
I can do this.
This is a baseball story.
That's right.
Yes.
Oh, I see.
I realized it at the end of last year.
Giants changed to Hana-Kantoku.
At that time, Coach Miyamoto Kazutomo, Motoki Daisuke, Mizuno.
They were friends who played together a lot in the game.
Why am I not in?
That's all.
It's not like he's busy or anything.
That's right.
That's the difference.
Does that have anything to do with your past achievements?
To be honest, it does.
Well, anyone can say that.
Considering that, there's no room for Kazushige to enter.
You're still saying too much.
It's not just anywhere.
I think there's somewhere.
What do you want to do?
You want to be a director, right?
Anyone can be a director, if they play baseball.
Director Ichi.
Of course.
If you have to say more, a director of the Titans.
If it's not the Titans, but a director...
But if you're told you can be any director...
Yes, I'll say Titans.
Right.
That's impossible.
Hamada-san?
I don't know.
Impossible?
I don't know anything about baseball.
Well, I don't think Kazushige has any record.
He has a record of memorial.
I don't know if that's different from being a director.
That's right.
He's a famous actor.
Matsumoto-san, you know a lot.
No, no.
If he doesn't have a record, I don't want to be taught by you.
Hamada-san, can you say something?
For example, he became a batting coach.
This time, Nagashima Kazushige is a batting coach.
I'm not sure if I can beat you.
I'm sure you can beat me.
I'll beat you all.
No, you can't.
I can't beat you.
I'm sure you can beat me.
But I'm interested in you.
Do you have a dream of leaving it behind?
What do you mean?
I wanted to be a member of the different world if I didn't join the entertainment world.
I wanted to be a member of the committee.
Committee?
Yes, and before that, I wanted to be a police officer.
There is a place where the people here are one-sided.
The world over there.
One-sided?
Like a back and forth.
Not a police officer, but a police officer.
He came to the government office and put a gun on his head.
And he put a police cap on his head.
When he was riding a two-seater, he said,
Hey, come here!
That's what he wanted to do.
He kicked the front tire.
He's got a license.
That's scary.
What about you, Matsumoto?
If it wasn't for this world.
If it wasn't for this world...
It's not like that at all.
I don't have any experience like that.
I think it's cool for a shogi player.
It's cool.
Like Fujii-kun.
It's cool to see Fujii.
I think it's cool to do it without any tools.
Certainly, there is a shogi.
There is a hammer and a sword in the Hamazoo Seiran-tai.
I came with a bag in my hand and went home with a lot of money
Finally, the fight for the title was over
That fight was faster
From here, the fight for the title that no one knows yet was revealed
This is amazing
In the past, when we were doing Japanese TV, we had a corner where we had to fight against various fighters.
At that time, Ogawa-san and Inoue Kosei-kun were doing Judo.
I thought Judo was amazing.
I thought Judo was strong.
The result is?
It was fast
The ball looked big
It was a huge advantage
It was scary
It looked big
It looked like a dodgeball
It would have been easier if you said it bigger
The results so far are as you can see.
Will Hamada win? Or will Matsumoto win?
Which one will it be?
Let's move on to the next one.
6 is not correct.
2 is found out and you apologize on the floor.
What are you saying?
It's the same thing.
I'll start.
This is quite...
What is this?
This is...
I want to talk about my situation at that time.
In the era of Yakuza, there were two people who were dating.
Coincidentally, two people.
Did you really like the same person?
Yes.
What I made a mistake was that there was a girl named A and a girl named B.
I called A on this day.
I thought B was the next one.
But for some reason, it was the next one.
A was the next one, B was the next day.
We fought in our apartment.
It was a fight.
At that time, I was asked,
Which one do you choose?
I was told by A.
But I couldn't say anything.
When I was lying down all the time,
A stood up and went to the kitchen and brought a knife.
Oh, this is the one.
I have a save game the next day.
In spring.
I have to go to the save station.
It's okay.
It starts at 8 o'clock.
This guy is a blue bastard.
It's about 2 o'clock in the morning.
At that time, we had a floor.
There was a floor, and I was sitting down and saying,
I'm really sorry.
I apologized.
I thought the movie was good.
He stepped on my head from Kotobu.
I hit him.
I saw about 20 stars.
From above.
The floor is hard.
Stars really appear.
This is what I want to send out to the whole country.
Stars appear.
I'll show you my teeth!
Before this, when A woman asked which one to choose,
flooring has this kind of connection, right?
Like a groove.
She stabbed the knife right here.
That's amazing.
So, normally, if you're a man, you might think that your teeth might fly off.
You can't imagine that a knife would stick to the floor.
It happened to be stuck here.
But it happened to stand up.
The knife stands up.
The knife also stands up.
This is what I said in the national broadcast.
The knife stands up.
The knife stands up and the star stands up.
What happened to you, teacher?
I was late because I was sleepy
Next, the last one
Really?
Please take care of me
This is the last one
Super
Unfortunately
Onee-chan's Mune-Momezu
You only have 4 minutes
The last one
What is this?
This is last year's story
I don't go to Ginza very often.
I'm influenced by Sanma-san, so I really like Sanma-san going to a club in Ginza and drinking my sister's boobs.
You're saying amazing things.
Sanma-san says that himself.
I'm sorry to say this, but on the day of the Setsubun, we went to the Mamenakishi temple.
Before the Setsubun, we did a ritual.
It was a proper shrine ritual, so we all wished each other good health.
I heard a request from Sanma-san that he wished that good breasts would come closer.
I thought, as expected, it was a breast.
I'm not kidding.
Did you really say that?
I really said it.
You didn't say it so that everyone could hear it?
I said it out loud.
Out loud.
But I heard it.
Really?
Really.
It wasn't because you were fooling around and the camera was rolling.
It was because it was something you were good at.
I chased after my boobs from there.
I chased after them from before.
Last year, I couldn't chase after them.
I don't go to clubs very often.
Is it okay to drink boobs at a club?
It's not good
It's okay
I'll drink it
With this, all the Karta is over
Who will win?
What will happen?
It was tough
Matsumoto-san was going to win
It was a close game
Congratulations to Hamada-san
Congratulations
I was looking for it
I was waiting for this.
What is the reward from Kazushige?
What is it?
I brought wine.
It's a high-class wine.
It's expensive.
It's about 50,000 yen.
It's more than 100,000 yen at a shop.
Thank you very much.
Do you like red wine?
Yes, red wine.
Have you ever been drunk?
I've been drinking.
I've never seen it.
I want to drink it.
I'm going to come with a Santa Crab.
You're going to come with a Santa Crab?
No matter what happens,
I'm going to be the best Sake-nochi!
I really don't want to get angry at people over the age of 8.
If I talk too much, I'll get angry.
I'll get angry at the world.
I don't want to get angry. I will never get angry.
I will never get angry.
But I have a suggestion.
Yes, yes.
Really...
You know, when you get in a car, you park it at the parking lot of Aodora.
Yes, yes.
That is...
First of all, it's expensive in Tokyo.
Oh, in terms of price.
It's really expensive.
You can only stay for 2 hours.
If you don't, you'll get 4000 yen.
It depends on the place.
Sometimes you get 4000 or 5000 yen.
I see.
It can't be helped.
But you can't use 10,000 yen bills.
That's true.
Right?
It's okay to ask for the price.
But is there anyone in the world who has a thousand yen bill?
That's true.
If you think about it, you have to use 10,000 yen bills as a corporate effort.
There are two kinds of 1000 yen bills.
It's a plastic one.
It's a patterned one.
It can't be done on top.
It's patterned.
I understand that.
If you get into the rain or wind, it will cause a breakdown.
So you have to do it like this.
Yes, and then I have to do it like a plastic bottle.
This is going to be like this, but while I'm doing this, it's going to be like this.
You can just do it like this.
But I don't think it's going to be like this.
Ah, well, well.
It's impossible.
I want you to think about it.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
No, you're not angry, are you?
No, I'm not angry at all.
And recently, there was a guerrilla war.
It rained a lot.
So I did it there.
You see?
I couldn't use an umbrella like before.
I had to use both hands.
I had to use 4 life jackets.
And there was a little sun.
Was it for the machine?
Maybe it was for the machine.
There was a little sun.
It's short.
That's the center of the waterfall.
It's the most wet.
It's the most.
I'm excited.
Can't you do something about that?
Just a little bit more.
I thought I'd try not to get wet.
It's like this.
I can't do this anymore.
You're getting close.
What's that? What's that length?
You're not thinking about other people.
I'm not thinking about anyone.
You can't get the machine wet.
Then I don't need that.
I'd rather not have it.
If I had that, I'd be dead by the time I was done with it.
I'd be the first to run away.
I'd be the one to get all the
I'm a man of my word!
I'm the best!
I've been through all the bad luck in the world!
I really want you to stop!
It's short.
The people watching this...
I think they'll understand if you drive a car.
I can only think of it as a habit.
You won't get angry, will you?
I've been saying something like this for a while now.
I'm just crying.
You should have talked more quietly.
You definitely want to sing, right?
I want to sing here!