7th Gaki no Tsukaiya Arahen's Tsuke Tsuke Gainojin Tsurisu Tenshuken!
We're here, Mr. Tadana.
We're here.
It's a big event once a year.
Yes.
We're going to start right away, so I'd like to introduce you to our guest.
First, this person.
He's already 38 years old.
He's the fashion leader, but he doesn't even have a face.
He doesn't.
Hamada Masato-san!
Nice to meet you!
Thank you!
I don't really talk much, so I won't use it.
I'm the main fishman.
Please take care of me.
I'll do it this year.
Next, the man who has the strongest wallet in the entertainment world,
the comedian Matsumoto Hitoshi!
Nice to meet you.
I'll do it today.
I'll do it.
I'll catch the one I caught on the first day.
Thank you very much!
Next, for the sense of gag, the best in the entertainment world,
the father gag copywriter, Itoi Shigesato!
I had the impression that you came in early today.
No, it's not past 8.
8?
It's early.
It's actually 1.30 today.
Thank you!
Next, we have a winner who hasn't been here yet.
He is the one who came here without a break.
It's Yosuke Eguchi!
Thank you!
You still have a chance to win. You will be the 7th winner.
Is that so?
Yes, it is.
If you don't win today, you won't be able to go to the next round.
I'll do my best.
I'm a little bit tired.
Thank you for your time.
Next, Asakusa is known for Kaminari-mon.
And this person is Iemon.
The Yellow Monkey is Yoshii Kazuyama.
Is this year's schedule tight?
The atmosphere is very good.
It's been a while since I've been on TV, so I'm really nervous.
Well, do your best.
Thank you.
Next, we have Kato Haruhiko-san, who has been wearing black sesame
and senzu since this morning.
Kato-san, you're not very excited, but do your best.
I'm always nervous.
Why are you nervous?
It feels like I'm in a big entertainment world.
Hey, just say it!
I'm getting scolded.
Do your best today.
Thank you!
The peak of being a comedian was 10 years ago.
Now, it's the grumpy, Yamazaki Hosei!
I'm a fashion leader.
Where are you from?
Thank you very much.
And finally, the winner of the previous year, the Grand Champion, Mr. Okuda!
Thank you for waiting.
I'm the winner of the first round. I want you to do your best for the second round.
I don't want to lose.
You don't want to lose?
I'm a little bit nervous.
I'm nervous.
This time, we have a close contact with foreign TV stations.
Really?
What do you mean?
Oh, you're here.
You were filming Mr. Mitao's dance.
Where is that crew from?
It's the Central Government of Africa.
You're totally out of it.
You're too close.
There's a camera here too.
Think about it.
It's definitely not the way to hold the camera.
You're laughing.
You're always in the scene.
What scene?
You're like Pan Sen from the sky.
It's old.
The type is old.
Now, the tournament will start soon.
From the chairman of the tournament, Naoki Tanaka,
I would like to announce the tournament.
From now on,
Please repeat after me.
Something like us.
Please.
People like us...
Have no sense at all!
Especially me...
Can't even get a laugh...
But I'll do my best!
I'm sorry I was born.
Anyway, the competition is about to begin!
Go for the championship!
Thank you very much!
Jack's father is a bit upset.
Why?
The 7th GENERATION FISHING CHAMPIONSHIP
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors
In the midst of the great weather, the 7th GENERATION FISHING CHAMPIONSHIP has finally begun
The spirit is enough, the battle to become the champion is being held
At the start, this man's rod has been lost
It's coming!
Look!
Yamasaki's sudden hit!
Hey, look!
Look!
This year's not going to be easy!
On the other hand, the Hamada, Okuda, and Yoshi team
This team also hit Okuda early on
Oh, the cod is coming
The cod is coming
The cod is big
It's big
Hey hey hey!
Seriously?
And the loser, Hamada.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's big.
It's coming.
It's coming?
Hello.
Another one.
Yoshi is not here yet.
It's the same as usual.
Hello!
Wow!
It's huge!
No, it's small.
It's small!
And this is the team of Matsumoto, Itoi and Eguchi.
Matsumoto is the first to be surprised.
It's a little cute.
I just cried.
It's a big one.
It's coming.
It's small though.
This year's fishing competition is going on at a high pace.
After this, Itoi Kato will fish the first fish.
Only two of the eight members, Eguchi and Yoshi, have not yet caught anything in the first 20 minutes.
I will fish this parent fish next time.
Yoshi, turn off the camera.
Is it not good?
I heard you say, you came.
In a visual way.
Why are you guys shooting the camera?
Turn off the camera.
You just ate.
I just ate.
Are you talking to me?
Is it my fault?
Hamada is complaining about the fish, but Yoshi is getting more motivated.
And finally, the rod is dead.
Finally!
It's a big one!
This is bad!
This is a big one!
I got it!
Yoshi is happy to have caught the first fish.
And next to it, Hamada also caught a fish.
What's this?
It's not that big.
It's big.
It's exploding.
Hawaii, are you watching?
Sorry.
It's so small.
It's big.
Yoshino's is big.
And it's a replacement.
What's mine?
You said something big.
What's that?
The only one who hasn't caught anything yet is Eguchi.
Eguchi, if you catch anything, you'll be in trouble!
What are you saying?
Wait a minute.
Eguchi is left alone and is in a hurry, but the lure is caught and he's in a state of shock.
This isn't the time to fish.
In the end, he is caught by Hamada again.
Ah, you are in the middle of the road.
What?
You are close to downtown.
Downtown?
I don't know, you are an amateur.
I thought it was a black bass, but it seems that he has caught a lure of Matsumoto.
Mr. Hamagawa, I would like to ask you a question.
Excuse me.
I caught two fish, but the size is not good.
I think I caught a roll.
Please roll it up.
I caught two fish, but the size is not good.
I think Yoshi's fish is the biggest.
I can't look at the camera.
It's okay, it's the African style.
Oh, really?
I'll do my best.
Okay!
Where did the sabiris come from?
And here again, Matsumoto gets hit.
It's here.
Oh, it's big, it's big.
Ready, set, go!
Okay!
Actually, he gets the 4th one.
Isn't that amazing?
It's amazing.
Something happened.
Matsumoto-san, you have a lot of them.
I'm the one for today!
The TV station staff wants to say something
Please, right now!
Are you going to laugh at this?
Go home!
Is that okay?
The three of them are already an hour into the race.
Downtown Lure Time!
You have won the prize!
This is the second time in a row!
Do your best!
The person who uses the special Downtown Lure and gets the prize quickly gets 100,000 yen.
Last year Eguchi won 100,000 yen.
This is a one-shot match where anyone can win.
Who will win 100,000 yen this year?
Here we go.
Bouncing Ray time start!
Eguchi hasn't won a single one yet.
He wants to take a look at his honor.
But...
Here it comes!
Kato suddenly hits the target.
If he can get it, he will get 100,000 yen.
It's coming!
No way!
I grabbed the root of the plant.
Sorry, sorry. It was exciting, right?
It was exciting, right?
Yes, it was exciting.
You're watching it now, right?
It was exciting, it was exciting.
Oh, it's coming!
This time, it's Yamasaki's turn.
It's coming, it's coming!
This time, it's going to be hot.
It's coming!
It's a big one!
Amazing!
It's a victory at once!
Hello!
What's going on?
You know what's going on, right?
That's not right.
You can't do that while fishing.
First of all, the fish will eat you and you can't do that.
Definitely.
Look!
Hey!
That's enough.
Look ahead!
And right after that, Matsumoto's rod is in trouble.
It's coming!
Downtown Lure Time, Matsumoto's Saw
It's here!
What is it?
Matsumoto-san, you've won 100,000 yen!
I did it!
That's amazing!
It's different from last time
It's here!
I was so embarrassed
The prize money of 100,000 yen was obtained by Matsumoto
The next round is the second half
The one who got the most points is Okuda
That's right
That was fast
You acted well
Good, good
Yoshin-san, you took it off, right?
I didn't take it off yet
Good
You took it off
It's long
I'm taking it off
And Hamada continues
This boat is coming.
The bus is coming.
It's small.
I want a bigger one.
It's not bad.
It's good.
Hamada is fishing smoothly, but there is no luck with the big fish.
The last 30 minutes.
Tokunin Eguchi-san, do your best!
Hey!
He's a no-show.
I heard he's a zero.
You're only taking me?
Yes.
I see.
In 30 minutes.
Do your best!
This is bad.
So noisy.
Wow, so big!
Here again, the difference between Matsumoto and Zettou is huge.
It's huge.
This is huge.
Huge.
Huge!
It's a giant bus.
I'm nervous.
This is the perfect three.
Wow! It's huge!
What's with you today?
This is huge!
What is this?
It's huge!
Ego-chan, you're not supposed to be clapping!
I'm so happy.
The time is running out, but Kato is caught.
It's heavy.
This pace.
Got it.
Kato is happy as he caught a fish.
I did it.
Look! Look!
Look! What are you doing?
This is a bit...
See? I told you!
The participants who have won the big hit of Matsumoto and Kato...
...are looking for the next big hit and are putting on the last spurt.
This time, it's a win that hasn't happened in a year.
Who will win the trophy and be drunk by the taste of victory?
You're completely drunk!
This is a joke!
You're full of energy!
You're so cool!
I'm going to win the Eguchi!
Nothing!
I got it!
Carrot!
Carrot 4.5 points!
I got one!
Next is Hamada!
I know you want to eat the second one.
This is a little big.
It's 31cm.
Look at me.
You don't know, right?
It's about 8cm.
This is the biggest, right?
28cm.
I don't know.
Itoi-san, you're here.
Itoi-san, it's okay.
Oh, it's 30.
30.5...
No, it's 31.
It's 31.
31.
I see.
The winner is...
Yes, Hamada Sankei.
Yes.
I have a good feeling about this.
First, Yoshii.
Yes, Yoshii.
30.
It's 31.
31.
Yes.
Next, Matsumoto.
Mine is...
First, look at the numbers.
Wow!
It's huge!
This is huge!
Look! This is the first time I caught a big one!
Isn't it amazing?
This is huge!
This is amazing!
I did it! I really did it!
37!
7!
Awesome!
This is...
Next, Haru!
Yes!
But this is big!
This is big!
This is long too!
Big!
This is big too!
Oh!
This is big!
My heart is pounding!
Go!
Go! Go! Go!
What's 37?
Ah, it's not!
It's not!
It's 35!
35!
35! Kato-kun, 35!
Why did you come to see this with such interest?
Finally, the remaining one is the champion of last year!
But this is different.
Mine is long.
This is Matsumoto-chan!
30 points!
That means the winner is Matsumoto-chan!
I did it! I did it!
This year's results are as follows.
It's been 5 years since Matsumoto won the championship.
Eguchi's results are the worst.
This time, Matsumoto's 3-in-1 fish restaurant is the champion.
Furthermore, we will present 10 people with the speciality of Kaltura, downtown luer.
Please apply!
Today...
I was a carrot.
I really don't know what's going to happen next year.
I'll say it again, but I want to aim for the championship.
It doesn't matter if I'm third.
The one who was pitiful in the world was Yoshiko Ebuchi.
I wonder why I can't catch any fish with that image.
If I were him, I would cry.
I don't think I've ever been in the top 10.
I don't think I've ever lost.
I want to do my best next year.
Today, I've been working in the clinic since 5am and I've been working for 12 hours.
I have to start work soon, but please call me again next year.
I was so excited until my throat was hoarse, but today, I was able to enjoy and relax in this nature.
I hope you can come to the event next year.
Thank you.
I think I'm a person who can be expected from now on.
Good luck!
Matsumoto from our team did well in today's boat competition.
I was able to win.
I want to be better than him next year.
I'll do my best next year.
I have something I've been hiding.
I've said a lot today, but I didn't wear a lure.
But it still comes.
But it's black.