Next time on Gaki no Tsukai Arahen, the 28th year's new regular show, Nishikawa Kiyoshi Audition!
He really wants to be the regular of this show.
I'm sure he will.
He will?
Why would he?
He said he would never lower his gyala.
He's very strong.
That's amazing.
He said he would never lower his gyala from 250.
I thought that was amazing.
The host of the comedy show, Nishikawa Kiyoshi.
He led the Mantaifumu with Yoko Emeyashi and became the leader of Yoshimoto.
He wanted to become a regular of Gaki no Sky.
So, Nishikawa Kiyoshi held an audition for Gaki no Sky.
If these 5 people can join, wouldn't it be a bit awkward?
It's not awkward at all.
Well, it's better if they don't join.
But...
But what?
No way!
I don't know!
I'm doing it!
Well, I'm not sure.
Tanaka is still not well.
He's not well.
How many times do you say that?
He's really not well.
I'm getting thinner.
You're right.
I wonder if he was doing RIZER, but he's getting thinner at the same pace.
This is a lie.
He's doing RIZER.
I see.
Mental RIZER.
I'm fine.
Let's call him. Please come in.
Please come in.
Please come to your seat.
Can I sit down?
Yes.
You don't seem to be in a good mood.
I met you guys about 4 years ago
I felt like I was at the edge of death
So I'm a little nervous today
One more time!
I'm scared of this
One more time
Please do it regularly
How about it? Could you tell us the good points of each member?
The first thing I want to say is how serious Tanaka san is.
He is the person I can trust the most in the entertainment world.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
Hose san, you have moved to Rakuoka.
I think that is great.
Thank you.
It is difficult to go to Osaka after realizing that place.
It is great.
Matsumoto-san, you've become rounder since you had a child.
You're really great, but you're really polite.
You've done a good job with the morning greetings and the afternoon greetings.
You've become able to do it properly.
I was really surprised.
After all, you have to have children.
I see.
I shot the full-body shot of you, but at that time, thank you for the first email.
What kind of email was it?
I was told to do my best in Medama.
I was told to come back soon. I'll be waiting at the scene.
Is that true?
Yes, it is.
I was called Medama right away.
Were you called Medama?
Well...
Since I was little.
No, you were called Kanade-san.
I don't usually call him that.
That's right.
So, if you get this regular, would you be okay with a medallion?
If I could, I would have stopped him at Nishikawa-kun's place.
I have a lot of juniors, so I have a lot of juniors.
I also got it back right away.
I'll do my best to fix it quickly and get back to the scene.
I changed the mat to a lip.
I'm sorry for that.
What did you say?
Lips.
I'm sure you'll forgive me for the ad-libs I do on TV.
Is that okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry about that.
Endo-san.
Endo-san?
I'm sorry, but I can't think of any comments.
What do you mean?
I'm not sure where to praise you.
So you don't have any good points to praise me?
No, that's not what I mean.
It seems like you have something you're good at.
Good? Good?
I haven't watched TV much, but I can imitate.
We are the most unprofessional in the field of impersonation.
In that field...
Here is the information.
Bobby Orokon is in the film.
What are you doing?
It's not me.
I didn't do it.
Who said it was me?
I came from far away.
Not me.
The end.
Thank you very much.
Does that mean it's not similar?
No, no.
It means that you have been shown various things.
Can I ask one more thing?
Yes, yes.
What is it?
Mr. Morishige rides a motorcycle and starts the engine.
That's great.
Excuse me.
The end!
It's not that similar.
I usually do this in front of the mirror.
I laugh at myself.
Oh, really?
It's good, isn't it?
It is.
I think it's good.
Yes.
Do you have any ideas for a one-shot gag?
A one-shot gag?
Do you want to think of something right now and do it?
Well, if I had any, it would be very beneficial.
It would be very beneficial for the regular audience.
Well, you're suddenly going to say a lot of things today.
So, in that case, I won't forgive you!
Everyone laughed.
I won't forgive you.
Can I do it again?
One more time?
Yes.
I won't forgive you!
It's cute.
It's really cute.
I might change it.
Really?
Yes, I won't forgive you.
I'm doing well now.
I'll do my best.
What do you think?
Is there anything else you want me to do?
I want to see your reaction.
I want to see it.
I want you to prepare it.
It's like this.
Ah, I see.
I wonder if Nishikawa-kun can do it.
What's in the box?
Ah, yes.
It's the way to do it, right?
Rather than doing it.
Start!
Please be careful.
You have to be careful.
If you go too far, it's dangerous.
It's going to cut through the rubber.
That's right.
I saw it.
What? You saw it?
Wait a minute.
You shouldn't do that.
It's going to get caught and fall.
I was surprised.
He's so mean.
He's a scoundrel.
Scoundrel?
He has a scary reaction.
That's true.
He's very brave.
He'll be fine as long as he's not hurt.
Let's see the reverse.
I won't forgive you!
This is good.
I think we should stop the scene.
It's too short.
It hurts.
I've been watching Matsumoto-san for a while.
His facial expression has a lot of different patterns.
He's like that.
I want to see his facial expression.
I want to see it.
I see.
The one shot gag was amazing.
It expanded the range of the video.
What is this?
If you look at the front,
If you look at the back of the curtain, the face is hidden behind it
The curtain will open at the end of the scene
So you can show various expressions
Interesting
Do it again
One more time
It's the same.
It's not different.
It was the same.
It was the same as before.
You don't need to do the ka-ka-ka sound.
Ka-ka-ka.
That's right.
3, 2, 1
I can't shake it
That's not necessary
End
3, 2, 1
It's impossible
It's impossible?
It's not that bad
I'm doing a comedy, but I can't shake it with that face expression
I think I can do it.
Please forgive me.
I can't do it.
Nijigaya, you can't say, please forgive me.
It's not good.
I'm sorry.
I'll do my best.
Next, I want to see number 3.
This is a number.
Number?
So it's a level.
There are numbers from 1 to 5.
You can choose one of them.
I want you to shout out various things with the voice that matches the level.
Shout?
Shout.
What was your wife's name at first?
Nishikawa.
Her name is Helen.
If you call her name, she will scold you when you go home.
But this is just a part of the audition.
Yes, it's just an audition.
It's fine if you're just saying that you did it.
You're really good looking.
What happened?
It's been over 50 years since we got married.
We've never called each other by our names.
Really?
But today is just an audition.
You did well.
You did your best.
If you pull, you will get the same level.
Level?
Yes, can I?
Four.
Furen!
Four is good.
That's great.
That's really good.
That's good.
Okay, let's go.
Furen!
Are you watching?
No, you don't need to.
You don't need to?
You don't need to.
Please put your knees back.
I'll do it.
But if you suddenly choose 4 and 5, what will happen?
As for the luck...
Okay, let's take it.
Okay.
That's different from before.
It's different from before.
I'm sorry, but I think all of them are 4 and 5.
That's not true.
How lucky are you?
Tanaka-kun, do you have anything to say?
I've experienced it myself as a kid.
I was shot with a gun every season.
It was a prank.
I'm ready.
Hey, Nishiki!
wet because I hear you
let's take it
and
If it's not the beat, it's not the heart.
How was it?
It was good with the right.
If I had hit the heart with the left, I wouldn't be able to perform this much.
I would have died instantly.
But in the end, it was the heart, right?
Yes.
He's been singing for a while now, so I want to see some good parts of him.
He's been releasing a lot of records.
Can you sing a little bit?
That's a good idea.
Can you sing the song called Road?
The song called Road.
That's the name of the song.
Can I sing a little bit?
Yes, please.
I think it was happiness when it was nothing.
The night that is nothing, the night that will never return
Excuse me
Your voice is very good
Thank you
If I had listened to it a little more, I might have cried
That's right
You sang it so well
Maybe you would have cried while singing
I can't sing Kanda-wa
If you sing, you'll cry.
Let's go.
I want to see it closer.
No, not at all.
Please, Kanna.
Have you already forgotten?
We went to the Yokocho's place together in a red hand-picked muffler.
We said, let's go together.
I was always wait for you.
I didn't afraid of anything,
when I was young.
But your kindness scared me.
That's all.
You really feel like crying.
I'm sure I'll cry.
But there are five teachers here.
I'm not going to be embarrassed or feel inferior.
I'll remember my initial intention and not forget the past.
You can't cry when you're done.
I don't think I can cry when I'm done.
I don't like it. I'll end up lying to myself.
You'll end up lying to yourself?
I don't sleep at all.
You too?
On Monday, the 17th, at 10pm, the 90th episode of Gakunosukai Special Broadcast!
We'll be welcoming guests and we'll be doing a waiting game without smartphones!
Please, if there's alcohol, this is the ending!
Don't miss it!
Can you do a
I've never done that.
I'm not good at it.
The general gag is the word.
Kanaga-kun, can you two fight with each other?
With Kanaka-san?
Yes.
It's the first time.
I'm sorry.
I can't talk to you.
Start!
What are you looking at?
I'm not looking.
You've been looking at it for a while, haven't you?
No, that's...
You're mistaken, aren't you?
Why are you staring at me?
It's disgusting!
I'm telling you I'm not looking!
What's with your attitude?
Ask the people in this shop!
I don't have to ask!
Why?
You're staring at me all the time!
It's not just because I have big eyes that I feel that way!
Don't use it! It stinks!
You're saying it too much!
Where did you sleep?
I slept right next to you.
What's wrong with you guys?
Shut up!
Chaos will occur.
I don't like it!
He said it because he doesn't like it.
Shut up!
What are you looking at?
I said I didn't see it.
Don't look at me.
I don't like it.
I don't like it at all.
Hey hey hey hey! Wait a minute!
What is it?
What are you doing?
You're not sleeping at all.
Are you the same?
Are there only people who can't sleep?
I'm looking at Jiro Jiro, he said it was creepy, so stop it.
I'm not looking!
I said you were looking!
Why are you looking at Jiro Jiro?
Let's go to a prison.
Apologize.
It's your fault.
It's not my fault!
I'm asking you to apologize.
Hey, stop it already!
What is this?
I haven't slept at all for 3 days!
Shut up!
What's with your hair?
I haven't slept at all because of you guys!
We don't apologize.
It's our fault.
I haven't slept since 8 on Tuesday.
What day is it now?
I still have a heart attack and it's been 3 hours!
Where are you from?
I told you before.
You're the one who's causing trouble for everyone.
That's enough!
The end!
This is the worst.
Thank you very much.
I want to see this.
I want to see Jose-san's.
It's a live-action play.
Yes.
What?
I think it would be a great point if you could do this.
I have a paper play here.
I'm doing it while looking at the picture.
Helen's return.
It's starting!
It's not a return of the crane.
I have to say this myself.
One day, the boy climbed a mountain.
Then, he met a girl with a long hair.
I thought it was a girl with long hair.
It's too early.
She was a beautiful blonde girl.
I was surprised.
What did you do?
I met you by chance while I was lost. Thank you for your help.
What's your name?
No, no, no.
You can't say it in English.
Open the door and tell me your name.
Next one.
When I woke up in the morning and opened the door, I saw that Helen was folding a flag.
She was also folding your cardigan.
This is a cat.
The one who was chased wasn't a cat.
That's all.
The end.
How was it?
It didn't really become a reward for the family.
I don't understand the meaning.
But the picture doesn't look like a reward.
Is it a problem with this?
I think so.
No, no, no, it was an audition.
If I didn't make it, I wouldn't have made it.
I think so.
But it's really beyond my expectations.
It's amazing.
But I'd like to tell you about the failure later.
What? Later?
Yes.
By the way, what was the most difficult thing today?
It's all because it's my first experience.
The most difficult was the play.
Good morning.
It was fun.
Thank you.
Good morning.
It was fun.
Thank you.
The result is here.
I don't know if I can smile or get angry.
Failed!
Can't you hear the reason?
I couldn't hear the reason.
I see.
I'll go to the office and check everyone's schedule.
Can we talk a little more?
It's okay.
Excuse me.
Please enjoy pregnancy reality of Magma w friction