We're told Mr Matsumoto is a fearless person, but can you narrate
to us the most life-threatening situation you've been in so far?
did the guy actually call you "fearless"?
let's see now, the most dangerous experience I've had till now would be....
...I guess it'd have to be the time I was whacked by a gorilla!
where was this?
around here.....it went BAM!!
I meant where were you when this happened!
well let's see...I was playing baseball...
WHERE!?
in the field, in the field!
which field?!
let's see now - it was the Amagasaki baseball
field (Matsumoto and Hamada's hometown in Hyogo prefecture)
huh! You've never told me this story before!
Really?...(politely)..well, can you please listen anyway.....?
Wham! You remember, I used to hit homeruns all the time back then, right?
OK, if you say so...(stiffening up out of respect) - aye,aye cap'n!
my adolescence was all about homeruns, man!
what're you, an idiot?....enough already!
Wham!!!   Man, did I strike the ball hard back in the day!...SMASHED it
clear out of the field, and it broke the glass in someone's house!
Oh, really?
Well, so I make my way over there to apologize....
but when I got there, there he was....the Gorilla!
really? a Gorilla? you don't say!
Well...actually, there was an old man too....AND a gorilla!
Oh, I get it, the gorilla was with the old
man at his place! I get it now!
He said, 'What do you plan to do about this window kid? I
just replaced the glass after it was broken a while back!'
And through it all the gorilla was like this...(sways and swaggers about menacingly)
Sounds like a yankee punk gorilla staring at you up and down!
Go on....
well, I was like all...bowing down low...being humble, you know?...
....just genuflecting and flopping before the guy, you know?....
I was also just a kid back then, remember?....
And just then, the gorilla pushes the old man aside....and....
wow! he stepped out in front of him, did he?......and?....
'Why the hell don't you just apologize punk?!'
wait...hold on a second here....
(gestures: 'aren't you getting ahead of the story here?')
The gorilla spoke?
No, that's what the old man said!
Aaaaaah, I get you now -  had me going there for a while!
...no, it was the old man, of course....(chuckles to
himself at the idea of a gorilla talking)
thanks, ok i get it now... startled me there for a minute....
And so the old man asked me why I wouldn't apologize....
....and then it was like,'Oi, oi, oi, oi!'
wait, wait, wait, hold on a minute again!..the
gorilla threatened you with,'Oi, oi, oi, oi?'
no, no, that was the old man again!
aaah, i got you -  so it was the old man talking again
.....wow...the old guy sure has a lot to say, didn't he?...and then?
well, so the old man was like,'Oi, oi, oi, oi!'...right?
And I was humbly like,'Well, I don't see why I should apologize,
since I will definitely compensate you for the damage done.'
....and when I said that, it just stepped out menacingly and was like,'YOU
THINK COMPENSATING FOR THE DAMAGE IS GOING TO MAKE EVERYTHING OK?!?!'
wait, wait, wait, hold on just a minute again!...this was the goril.....?
no, no, it was still the old man, the old man!
Ok, i get it - so it was the old man again...........the old
guy sure keeps stepping out into the front a lot, doesn't he?
With the old guy stepping out so many times, you'd think the poor gorilla would start to feel cramped and crowded out - he'd think
'Should I just squeeze myself to the front from the side somehow? Why doesn't the old geezer just get out of the way?'
And then it was like......BAMMM!!!......I don't know if it was a big rock or a
desk lying around or something that was dashed to the ground...and it said....
Oh wow!...and then?....
'DO YOU THINK YOU CAN FUCK WITH A GORILLA AND GET AWAY WITH IT?!?!'
eh?..stop!...wait, wait a minute....was this the gorilla?
no, no, the old man, the old man again!
and then ......(in a soft voice) 'just compensate us for the damage'
THAT was the gorilla speaking!
Eh?!
OK, so THAT was the gorilla speaking!
For the first time, the gorilla spoke
Pretty chilled out gorilla! - not in the habit of getting angry is he?
He just says softly,'Compensate us for the damage'!....oooooh, wow!
Weren't you in the least bit startled when the gorilla started speaking?
No, that part didn't startle me, not really!...I was
a wild and reckless guy back then.
But really....isn't it odd and funny?....I mean why should anyone have to apologize...if you
compensate for the damage, that should be the end of story, right?.......
He was like, 'You bruised me right here in my arm!'
Wow, you injured the guy?
That was once again the gorilla I'm talking about....
Eh?!
You mean the gorilla addressed you formally and said, 'You have injured me!'.....?
And then he walks up all of a sudden, and....
Wow, that must have been scary!
He must have been around this tall, right?
Sure, he was a big, tall gorilla!
BAM!!!!
Wow, did it break your jaw?
No, it was the OLD MAN who got whacked!
Eh?!
Weren't they living together happily all this time?
'That's how much destructiveness I have pent up!'............
All right, that's enough!
..........was what the old man finally said!
Eh?!
Man, what a strange, scary day it was!
But no one whacked or even touched you!