(Hamada reading aloud viewermail)
"We're told Michael Jackson is due to visit Japan soon...."
"....given that Matsumoto-san and Michael Jackson are such good friends..."
"....is it true that MJ hangs out with Matsumoto-san at his house whenever he visits Japan?"
I guess you could say Michael and I go back a long way...
....back to the time he made his earlier trip to Japan!
Wow! Was it a chance first encounter?
Not really, I went to see him in concert.
What's so special about that?!
No, no, that was just how it all began!
Ok.
I was in the front row!
No kidding?
I guess Michael sensed something special in me then!
Of the several ten-thousands in the audience, I guess he was struck by how I was looking at him!
I guess I really stood out!
You can really tell, 'This guy's a hard-core fan!'
The intensity with which I was watching his act must have carried through to him!
I guess it was from the second half of the show that Michael would just stand right in front of me....
...and do THIS!!
And that's when he started visiting me, and hanging out with me at my place!
Many times, huh?
I guess so!!
Right, but the guy wants to know what the two of you would be upto!
Well, he would help out around the house in many ways!
With what?!
Well, for example - when I would be doing the dishes, he would be waiting next to me patiently with a towel to dry them off!
What a nice guy!
Oh yeah, for sure! - and then when I'd have to lift something heavy like a table....
...Michael would stand at the other end, and give me a hand picking it up!
He's such great guy, and pretty handy that way!
And then, when you had to make those tricky maneuvers with long items of furniture....
...Michael would know exactly how far to back up before swerving!
This one time, Michael backed so far up, it was just amazing!
You just can't make sudden, sharp turns with those long tables, otherwise - BANG! - you'll end up banging your elbow against the wall, you know?
Michael wouldn't do that - he'd go back all the way, and THEN make the turn!
He really got it!
That's when I realized just how supremely awesome the guy really was!!
That IS pretty awesome!
You wanna know something else? - we both have the same tastes, Michael and I!
Absolutely, SPOT ON!
You're a jackass!
We even laugh at the same things!
How come he laughs at everything you find funny?!
Like, say for example, when you serve a bowl of hot miso soup, and then set it on the table....?
....and the bowl starts to slide, and it makes that funny slipping sound sometimes?
We just like totally crack up at that, Michael and I!
And then he does that famous 'hoo-hoo-hooooo' yell!
Oh yeah, it's a riot!