THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
When a comedian gets married,
the reception gets really lively.
Everyone tries their best
to make the guests laugh.
Say cheese!
Okay!
Can I have one more?
But for some reason,
I don't do well in situations like that.
This show is like a wedding reception,
but the people who usually laugh,
the bride and her family, aren't there.
Nori-ka?
-"Norika"?
-No, no.
That's his ex!
You definitely said it.
I've seen every season of this show.
I love ego searching.
People always write about who they want
to see in the next season of Documental.
My name always pops up.
Apple pen!
I couldn't understand why
I wasn't called up earlier.
Well, here I am.
Here I am!
I usually play off other people
to create my humor.
So I imagine that's how
it will work here, too.
Whenever somebody does something,
or whenever somebody does something wrong,
I'll be there to join in.
Since you like fishing,
do you prefer fish sausages?
-I guess so.
-Yes, I do.
-You do?
-Rather than German ones.
You prefer fish?
All I want
is for people to think I'm funny.
That's the tough thing
about this competition.
You pay a million yen to be in a room
where nobody ever says you're funny.
CONTESTANTS ELIMINATED SO FAR:
JIMMY ONISHI, KENJI TAMURA
He got me.
Orange card!
"Don't put your arms...
around my waist."
That's a double penalty.
-You put that much on?
-What is this?
What a well-behaved penis.
It's a clever penis.
Red!
Are we on?
Don't you need more?
-Do I?
-The leftover wax is enough?
The leftover wax should be enough.
-It works better with more wax.
-You're kidding.
But it's too hard now.
Really?
The paper won't stick to it.
I see.
That hurts!
Ow, ow, ow.
No way. That must be painful.
May I cover this?
Like a Chinese zombie.
It's starting to look better now.
It hurts?
How could Tamura leave it so unfinished?
What a parting gift.
Next you stick the sheets on,
then rip them off.
Hold his hand.
Does it hurt?
Will that work?
-It doesn't feel like it'll work.
-I think it will.
-We have to try.
-Do it in one swift pull.
Here I go.
Ready...
Look at that!
So much hair came off!
"The Harmonica of Joy."
Hurry up and pull the other sheet.
-So much came off.
-It sure did.
That harmonica makes a beautiful sound.
But they did remove a lot.
That'll turn into a rash.
Does it hurt? Or not?
It hurts?
You said, "It hurts"?
It doesn't hurt?
"It hurts."
Should we stop?
"Don't stop"?
-That's "Don't stop."
-Keep an eye on Takahashi.
You want us to do it?
"Do it"?
"Do it."
-Should we add more?
-You think so?
"Add more."
This is going to hurt, Koba.
What idiots.
You're putting it on his penis.
Is that okay?
-It's all over his penis.
-Don't wait too long.
Ready to try again?
Here goes. Ready...
Wait. You're grabbing his hair.
Is that okay?
He said "No!"
But it won't just go away.
Can he grab it?
"Just one pull."
"Just one pull, okay?"
-Let's finish this.
-Go for it.
Ready...
His voice skipped the harmonica
and came out as a groan.
Why don't we put the vibrator here?
If we turn it on, he'll focus on that.
-Wouldn't that be less painful?
-It can distract him.
Zakoshi is up to something.
Here it comes.
It's working.
-It's working.
-Yeah.
Are you ready?
-Ready?
-Wait. Zakoshi's here.
Havin' fun?
With this?
He freezes.
He suddenly freezes.
Hey, touch here.
Touch it.
-Touch it?
-Yeah.
-Why?
-Just touch it.
I'm about to come.
Touch it.
I came.
He came?
I'm about to come.
-Is he laughing?
-I'm about to come.
I'm about to come.
This is good.
Keep going.
I'm about to come.
That was intense.
Why didn't he let me come?
Junior never actually came.
May I make a phone call?
Ordering food?
Actually, I was supposed to call somebody
before the show started.
In this season, we'll try a new rule
that I've been contemplating for a while.
They can use a Helper.
Did something happen?
They can bring in one person.
We'll see a complete outsider
come into that space.
The Helpers will be like
Windom in Ultraseven.
"Capsule monsters."
They get to use one "capsule" each.
He's been asking me for advice.
Hello?
-Hello?
-Thanks for calling.
As I texted you before,
I don't think you should do it.
But I want one more try.
Who is it?
I don't think you can do it.
I think I still can. I want one more try.
It's too much.
-I can do it. I'm sure of it.
-You're the only one who thinks that.
I can do it. Please hear me out.
Can you come now?
Yes, I'm nearby.
My seniors are here.
You'll have to make it quick, okay?
-Okay.
-But I doubt I'll change my mind.
-I'm on my way.
-Okay. Bye.
-Sorry about this.
-Who is it?
-This guy wants my advice.
-You want him to quit?
I told him to give up.
-But he wants to do it?
-Yes.
Can he come in for a moment?
-Somebody's here.
-Who is it?
He really should give up.
FORMER WORLD CHAMPION BOXER IN
THREE WEIGHT CLASSES - HOZUMI HASEGAWA
Let me fight, just once more.
-You can't do it.
-I'm sure I can.
Listen to me.
We're the same age, so I know.
Our bodies have a limit.
But I still think I can do it.
Just once more.
Then show me how well you can move.
Why is he asking Yamauchi?
I'll check your reflexes to see
how they're holding up.
If they seem okay, I'll think about it.
-Ready?
-You'll use that?
That's how that other boxer trains.
This does nothing.
There's no point training like this.
That's enough.
There's no point at all.
It doesn't train anything?
-It's pointless.
-Pointless?
-Kameda always did it.
-You can still move.
Next, show me your punches. Come here.
One-two combo.
-Was Yamauchi a boxer?
-I don't think so.
One-two, okay?
That's it.
Okay.
Next, do a one-two, then a body blow.
Let's see if you still have it.
Don't hold back.
-One-two, body blow.
-That must hurt.
He's hurting.
One-two, body blow.
I think that's enough.
-Stop it, Yamauchi.
-Yamauchi, I think--
I think you should let him
make a comeback.
Yamauchi?
Yamauchi, that's...
You've taken quite a beating.
You've made some ground.
-Do I still have it?
-I think you do.
I'll give you a call.
Let's talk more about making a comeback.
I'll be waiting.
Sorry for the interruption.
Goodbye.
That was Hozumi.
Did you do boxing?
No, I didn't.
-Never?
-No.
He's nearly back in form.
You don't know what he was like
in his prime.
He wants to make a comeback.
This isn't a studio?
Sorry?
-A studio?
-I may have made a mistake.
Well, this is a studio.
Sorry. Who are you?
But this isn't a recording studio, is it?
-No, it's not.
-Is that so?
You see, I'm a musician.
Okay.
But you aren't musicians?
-No.
-We're not.
Is that so?
You see, I'm a freelance artist,
all the way.
-Okay.
-I'm not with any agency.
I sing whatever comes to mind.
You're a singer-songwriter?
Have you released any songs?
I have a song about order.
Order?
"The Song of Order."
-"The Song of Order"?
-It questions the proper order of things.
-That sounds unique.
-Maybe I know it.
"Do you date before having intercourse?
Or have intercourse, then date?"
It's about that.
Could you sing it for us?
Do you date before having intercourse?
Or do you have intercourse, then date?
It's about order. And the tempo.
Do you date before having intercourse?
Or do you have intercourse, then date?
"The Song of Order." The order of things.
-Is there more to it?
-There's more.
I tell a number of people's stories.
-You sing about order?
-I do.
Do you date before having intercourse?
Or do you have intercourse, then date?
-Is that the chorus?
-Exactly.
-Are there verses before and after?
-Of course.
What did you do after you started to date?
After we started dating,
we went to a hot spring
What did you do after the hot spring?
After the hot spring, we went to an inn
What did you do at the inn?
We went to the inn and had a drink
What did you do after having a drink?
You guessed it, we had intercourse
Do you date before having intercourse?
Or do you have intercourse, then date?
It's "The Song of Order."
Is there a message to the song?
I was just wondering whether people
had intercourse before they dated or not.
I wondered what people do.
I think both cases happen, don't they?
I put all that in a song.
Like which do you put on first?
Jeans or a shirt?
Just like that.
-Do you have a clothes version?
-I have a clothing song.
A clothing song?
-It's all about clothing.
-Jeans and shirts?
Do you put on jeans, then a shirt?
Or a shirt, then jeans?
Is it jeans, then a shirt?
Do you put on a shirt, then put on jeans?
Or do you put on jeans
after you put on a shirt?
That was powerful.
I see.
So, what do you guys do?
Well...
We're comedians.
There was a time when
I wanted to be one, too.
-A comedian?
-You wanted to be one?
Did you go from comedy to singing?
Or did you sing before trying comedy?
I wanted to do comedy,
then I became a singer
After I became a singer, I had intercourse
Intercourse?
You see, I love it.
-Intercourse?
-Yes.
Do you write the melody, then the lyrics?
Or do you write the lyrics,
then write the melody?
What happens after I write the lyrics?
Of course, I make the melody
What happens after I write the melody?
Of course, I record the song
What happens after I record the song?
You guessed it,
I have intercourse!
You sure like intercourse.
Go away.
Go.
Hey, somebody!
Hey!
Somebody!
Hey, somebody!
"Hey, somebody"?
Would any of you happen to have
a charger cable for a PSP?
What do you want?
Would any of you happen to have
a charger cable for this PSP?
-No, we don't.
-Sorry.
Oh, my.
What game were you playing?
Me?
Well, I had the good fortune
of playing Tetris.
-Tetris?
-Yes.
Our musical theater troupe,
the Takarazuka Revue, are playing nearby.
In between shows,
I had been enjoying... a game.
You're with Takarazuka?
-So you're a woman?
-Yes, I am.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am a member of the Takarazuka Revue.
My name is Kaoru Osuda.
Kaoru Osuda?
Please call me "Oskar" for short.
-You're a woman?
-Which troupe are you in?
The North Troupe.
The North Troupe?
Don't the troupes have names like
"Moon," "Flower" and "Star"?
We have North, South, East and West.
-We are...
-You are?
-However, Takaraz... kazu...
-"However"?
We're the Takara-revue-zuka.
Does nobody have a charger?
-Not on me, sorry.
-We don't have one.
Devastating.
How shall I spend my break?
Well, I guess I have no choice.
All I can do now is dance with joy.
Would you please join me?
But I don't know a thing about Takarazuka.
-Don't worry. Just follow my lead.
-Let her lead you.
-Have you ever danced before?
-No, never.
Well, let my...
-Please stand.
-What?
-"Let my" what?
Let me lead you.
I'm worried.
Light and hope...
and dreams
We each have our
Dreams
But when you're feeling down,
what does your heart tell you?
-I...
-They will become
Our precious memories
In times of sorrow and pain
We must always look ahead
And walk on
Thank you for helping me pass the time.
I truly am grateful.
If anybody happens to have
a charger cable for a PSP,
please bring it to our gig.
Your gig?
We're doing a national tour.
It's called "Weekend Takarazuka."
Like "Weekend Yoshimoto"?
You do that? We do "Weekend Takarazuka."
Yoshimoto has a weekend show
called "Weekend Yoshimoto."
We do a similar thing at Takarazuka.
If we play near you, please do come.
I must leave now.
He made a big move there.
He sure did.
Akiyama, look at this.
Me?
-What is it?
-Tell me who it reminds you of.
-Should I turn it over?
-Yeah.
Who it reminds me of?
DRIVER'S LICENSE
ATSUSHI TSUTSUMISHITA
-He had a gold license.
-How is that possible?
He had a clean slate until then.
-He had a gold license?
-He had no driving offenses.
-You borrowed it from him?
-Yeah.
Do you know he changed
his social media icon?
-He did?
-Yeah.
-What is it now?
-Pipo-kun.
-The police mascot?
-Yeah.
-That's provocative of him.
-Wow.
Eikoh has never been
with Yoshimoto, right?
That's right.
Want to see what a Yoshimoto pay stub
looks like?
-Whose pay stub?
-Yoshimoto--
-It's a real pay stub.
-Is it?
It's real.
-Whose is it?
-I wonder.
-Is it okay to open?
-It's January's pay.
Whose is it?
It's not something you show people.
-This is scary.
-Hide the amount.
It's Tsutsumishita's!
What month is it for?
-January.
-January?
There are a lot of items.
Look at each amount.
"Minus 5,400 yen."
"Talent Expenses, November"?
What's that?
He earned 25 yen in royalties from
the DVD sales of Ametalk! Vol. 6.
How did he contribute so little?
-Since he's on leave now?
-Right.
-He only gets royalties from DVD sales?
-Exactly.
The Lincoln: Sports Day Special was...
"One yen."
One yen?!
-How do you even transfer that amount?
-It's too low to be taxed.
So what's the total amount?
Is that a "nine"?
"Nine thousand, five hundred
and thirteen yen."
Tsutsumishita hit the big time.
Really big time.
With zero hours of actual work.
How much did you earn
while on leave, Eikoh?
-Zero.
-Zero?
It was the same for me.
I was just getting DVD sales, and...
So,
shall we bring out a zombie?
-Zombies?
-Zombies.
Here they come.
It's time.
-We have to stay strong.
-Jimmy's coming, right? And Tamura.
-Jimmy and Tamura.
-This will be dangerous.
He looks exactly the same as when he left.
He had hours.
He hasn't changed one bit at all.
The World Cup.
Give me a minute.
Just a minute.
Singa-pole.
It's a pun about the center being a pole.
-"Shin-ga-pole" and "Singapore"?
-Singa-pole.
That hurts.
-Is he naked?
-He attached it directly.
That hurts!
That hurts.
-I said that hurts!
-You're neatly shaved.
Where did you find that?
Where did you find it?
An online shop.
For 1,980 yen.
1980.
Was it sold like that?
You didn't alter it?
-You didn't alter it?
-I didn't. It came like this.
-Does it come off?
-Huh?
He never understands the first time.
If you lift it up by the chin,
it slips right out.
Singa-pole.
You tied it on?
-Is that okay?
-I tied it on.
Singa-pole.
Today, I...
I was...
Ouch.
I was on the train... Ouch!
-How is this attached?
-Stop touching me.
It hurts.
It hurts my private parts.
On my way here today...
Ow.
Can I take this off?
No.
-It hurts.
-You can't.
But...
It... Ouch.
-It's killing the tip of my toes.
-Your toes?
I didn't mean my toes.
-The tip of your toes?
-Your toes?
-That's what he said.
-It's not my toes.
The tip of...
The tip of my...
-The tip bit.
-Tip bit?
The tip bit.
It hurts as if it's being pinched
by a zipper.
-That must hurt.
-It really does.
Is it erect?
It's not erect.
-It's pinched?
-It's pinched. That's why I'm in pain.
What can we do?
I have really tight foreskin.
That was a bold revelation.
We can't help you there.
That's not important now.
It's not?
It's not important now.
Anyway,
on my way here today,
I rode a bullet train.
And at Hamamatsu Station,
my hands got stuck in the door.
That's why there's blood under my nails.
-It wasn't just my hands.
-It wasn't?
My feet too.
-Your feet too?
-My feet too.
How were you stuck?
People can't get stuck like that.
I got stuck like this.
-That's impossible.
-I was like this.
Both feet.
I got stuck with both feet like this.
-That's why your nails are red?
-The pressure--
His testicles are so round.
-How round.
-Hey.
Watch out. I'm gonna fall!
I have blood under my nails.
His testicles are so round.
And you have terrible bunions.
You can laugh, Jimmy.
You're allowed now.
I am?
-You're already a zombie.
-Zombies can laugh?
Sorry about that.
Want to play Russian roulette?
-That's scary.
-We have no idea what's in that.
Should I go first?
I'll go first.
You guys pass it around. Russian roulette.
-That's too scary.
-What will happen?
It's the kind of thing that kills people.
I don't want to die.
It just goes bang?
-How many bullets are there?
-Huh?
-Why don't you ever get it the first time?
-12 bullets.
-It doesn't hold that many.
-It couldn't.
-Isn't it six?
-Six bullets.
One out of six.
-Is a real bullet?
-Yeah.
Does it go bang?
-Does it go bang?
-What other noise would it make?
-He's mad at you.
-Does it fire anything?
I'm sorry. Does it fire something?
Stop making them repeat themselves.
Will it go bang?
It will go bang.
Do you need that cap?
It doesn't do anything.
It's for fire safety.
You go first, Jimmy.
Okay. I'll go first.
Here I go.
I lost.
Get those bunions taken care of.
You can laugh, Jimmy.
That was close.
-That Singa-pole was dangerous.
-It sure was.
Jimmy's face is so funny
when he tries not to laugh.
The fact he hadn't changed was funny, too.
What are you doing, Zakoshi?
I'm gonna take a bath.
-What?
-A bath.
-Check the water temperature.
-You're all bathing?
-You're taking a bath?
-I am.
-We want to freshen up.
-Yeah.
-This is too hot.
-Where is the bath?
Now it's perfect.
-Will you fit?
-Yeah.
-You won't fit.
-I need a bath.
-Can it take his weight?
-It will break.
-Won't it break?
-It's okay.
-You won't fit.
-I can fit in this bath.
-It's totally the wrong size.
-Is the table okay?
-Think it will break?
-Definitely.
Do it on the floor.
What are you doing?
Akiyama's taking a bath too.
He's totally having a bath.
They both chose to have a bath?
Okay.
How is it?
It's just the right temperature.
Is that so?
Each has his own style.
-Actually, it's a little hot.
-It's too hot?
How about Akiyama?
-He's washing his whole body.
-Let him dip too.
-May I?
-Sure.
-It's a little hot.
-It is, right?
I thought so too.
-It's a little cold out here. May I?
-Sure.
It's a nice bath, isn't it?
It's quite warm!
-A little hot, actually.
-Right?
-Is that how you take a bath?
-Yeah.
You have a unique method.
I want to dip it all the way.
I like dipping it to the very base.
-You'll catch a cold.
-That's why I go deep.
Didn't Gauguin do a painting like that?
He has his own approach.
He sheathed the whole lot.
That's how you put the whole lot in?
Did he wash off the suds?
-Then you switch to the cold water?
-Yes.
This feels so good.
Thank you.
Shall we release Zombie Tamura?
Okay, let's go.
That always scares me.
Really? It looked like fun?
It looked like great fun.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-I was pretty confident about that.
-I can see why.
-It's hugely popular in Osaka now.
-I was wondering why.
The Fartmonica.
Everyone, Jimmy wants to try it.
-Could you line up on that side?
-Again?
And if you hear anything,
tell us.
If we hear what?
A sound from the harmonica.
With the Fartmonica,
you lose if you make a sound.
-Jimmy's going to play it?
-Right.
He's still wearing that thing.
-What?
-His Singa-pole.
He's still wearing it.
-Are you?
-No.
-Yes, he is.
-We can see it.
-Why is he laughing?
-What's so funny?
-Use your hands, Jimmy.
-Here we go.
If you make a sound, you lose.
Ready?
Here I go.
Where did it go?
-He broke it.
-It broke off!
My Singa-pole...
-What happened?
-It's coming out!
His Singa-pole is peeking out.
That was unexpected!
F.
F?
He has absolute pitch.
Was that an F?
F.
F?
That one sounded different
from the first one.
F.
-Play a C, please.
-C?
C, please.
What was that?
-C.
-Say, "F"!
You need to say, "F."
Play anything but a C,
and say "F," no matter what.
We're leaving.
I've been alone with him for too long.
Ouch.
That was close!
So close!
That was a dirty move!
That was close! I couldn't take any more.
That was like revisiting
the very origins of comedy.
-We stuck at it.
-You sure did.
I think two of you laughed.
Who?
I think it was Takahashi and Jinnai.
I think Takahashi laughed,
but I held it in.
Let's see.
I've been alone with him for too long.
Ouch.
That was only as much of a smile
as Junior made before!
-There's no difference!
-You sprayed a laugh.
He did.
You're both out!
All right!
-They're both out? This is big.
-It is big.
You're all on thin ice.
All except Zakoshi.
-Zakoshi.
-He has zero cards.
At this rate, he'll win.
I have zero cards.
But Zakoshi is making a lot of moves.
He's really going for it.
-So nobody can complain.
-Right?
If I was playing it safe,
they could complain.
So for now,
-we're going.
-Good job.
How can I put it?
It was bizarre in there. It really was.
What did you do after having a drink?
You guessed it, we had intercourse
Do you date before having intercourse?
Or do you have intercourse, then date?
It was even more bizarre in that room
than I could have imagined.
Well, what can I say?
It's frustrating.
It's like...
Yeah.
Jimmy was just too much.
Ouch.
You can't help but laugh.
Sooner or later, he gets you.
Well...
That was fierce.
So, how is this going to turn out?
Here we go.
Zakoshi, can you go over to that sofa
and do something for me?
Nobody's ever laughed at this.
Your impression of Masanobu Kurisu.
All right.
-Who?
-Masanobu Kurisu.
-But Junior doesn't know him.
-So what? Nobody laughs anyway.
-What's the name? Masa...
-Masanobu.
-Who is he?
-A pro-wrestler.
A bald one.
Not even pro-wrestling fans laugh at it.
Go do it in the corner.
What the hell were you doin'?
Why didn't you jump in
and stop the referee?
What were you doin'?
Get that camera outta here!
I told you to get out!
Get outta here!
What the hell are you doin'?
What's this?
-What?
What the hell are you doin'?
It's a tag match!
Why didn't you jump in and stop him?
Get outta here!
I said go!
-What are you doin'?
That was a tag match!
That's a funny sight.
-That was amazing!
-Yeah, that really hit the spot.
What is this toy?
That was too much.
Magnificent.
That was magnificent.
-That monkey is amazing.
-Whose point was it?
Kano, for bringing it.
Or Junior, for handing him the harmonica.
The point belongs to one of them.
Akiyama, you're out!
You fought a good fight, but...
Just over one hour to go.
We're down to the last hour.
Zakoshi is so tough.
He was closest to the monkey.
I saw it coming,
but I just couldn't dodge it.
I'd never laugh at a normal harmonica,
but that monkey came back
with exactly the same melody.
I laughed with a clear conscience.
My bag is still full of things
that I wanted to do today.
But I still have enough time
to create fun as a zombie.
So I'll switch modes and do my best.
Here we go.
Now then, Zakoshi.
Do that bit which bombs at every theater.
Your impression of Hiromichi Fuyuki.
Fuyuki gets laughs!
Hiromichi Fuyuki?
-When he's with Chono.
-Okay. Well...
Imagine Chono is standing here.
But Hiromichi Fuyuki is a wrestler
who doesn't speak very clearly.
He says to Chono,
"If we teamed up,
we'd be invincible. Right?"
But he's so unclear,
this is how it sounds.
Right?
When will he start the impression?
He's already doing it.
-I'm doing it.
-That was it?
I'm still doing it.
OK, here we go.
It scared me again.
Zombies, eh?
That was close.
He came straight back as a zombie.
Well, you know.
I guess it's age.
I'm getting way too flabby.
So I've started doing
"formation gymnastics."
Since it can't be done alone,
I've started doing it
with members of the public.
And going to the gym is a bit, you know...
Do you mind if I bring someone here?
Please come in!
-Hello. It's nice to meet you.
-Hello.
-Thanks for coming.
-Thanks for inviting me.
Do you know who I am?
Yes, I'm a big fan of yours.
Of course I do.
I selected you from
a number of applicants.
-Thank you.
-The pleasure's mine.
Did you hear we'll be doing
gymnastic formations?
That's all I've heard.
-We'll be exercising.
-I see.
This way, please.
Thank you.
We'll be choosing formations
at random from this box.
How should we do this?
-Thanks for coming.
-Not at all.
Right?
Okay, let's go with this one.
"The Kaminarimon in Asakusa"!
The famous gate outside that temple.
How shall we do it?
What shall we do?
We have to make a formation.
Okay.
Could you widen your stance a bit?
Please spread your legs more.
You'll be the gate.
I'll be a tourist at the gate.
Okay. Please spread them a little wider.
Perhaps this will do.
Oh, my. Is this Kaminarimon?
Oh, my.
Okay.
Today's my lucky day.
I'm going through the gate.
You're a very small Kaminarimon!
Yes!
-A narrow Kaminarimon!
-I'm teeny.
What?
I'm teeny!
This is a little different from
the Kaminarimon I know.
I'm teeny!
-But what a great view!
-Thanks!
What a fantastic view!
Great.
I think that went well, didn't it?
What's next?
Let's see.
I can't believe they aren't laughing.
"A piano performance"? What shall we do?
Since you're a lady,
you can be the pianist.
Okay, I'm the piano. Start.
Please play me!
More!
That's it! Plink, plank, plunk.
Classical music!
Play a bit more down there. A higher note.
That higher note.
Isn't the key a bit lower?
The key.
No...
Where is the key?
Play the key. Where's the key?
-Where's the human key?
-There's no key here.
Something's not right.
Are you ignoring one key?
-I am!
-I thought so!
You're ignoring one spot, right?
She's definitely ignoring one spot.
Okay, let's try another.
This one?
"Driving a bulldozer"!
How do we drive a bulldozer?
What shall we do?
Can you drive?
No, I can't.
Well then, let's do this.
It moves like this.
-Like this?
-Hop on here.
-Sit down or it'll never work.
Sit here.
I have to sit there? Why?
-You have to--
-That's too embarrassing.
-Come on. Sit here.
-You can't drive standing up.
-No.
-I chose you out of all the applicants.
-Okay.
-Not just anyone will do.
-Okay!
No, it isn't!
Sit here.
-It's embarrassing!
-Sit right here.
-Sit here. Like that.
-Okay.
Further up.
Sit further up.
You have to sit here, or there's no point.
-This is the seat.
-The seat? Okay.
Drive me.
-You have to come further up!
-But it's embarrassing!
-Why?
-It just is!
What's with that?
Man.
What's this?
It says "69."
Sixty-nine?
That's my age.
Your age?
That was close!
So close!
He got me again.
Again...
She had just the right level of shyness.
Thank you.
I think the fact she wasn't
completely into it was wonderful.
Yamauchi came very close.
But he scraped through.
Kobayashi!
You totally laughed, right?
-I did.
-You totally laughed.
Let's take a look.
What's this?
It says "69."
Sixty-nine?
That's my age.
Your age?
That's hard to describe.
It was a happy moment.
I laughed out of happiness.
-It was heartwarming.
-Yes.
So...
You're out.
Part of me wanted to see you do a 69.
You are the last four.
Well, you know,
this may sound like an excuse,
but personally, I think the casting
for this season was terrible.
How so?
I went in ready for war,
but the room was full of my friends.
The moment I saw the other members,
I thought, "What am I going to do?"
But in the end, I was simply wrapped up
in a blanket of warm laughter.
I laughed twice,
but the same thing happened both times.
The moment I felt my heart warming up,
a laugh slipped out.
You put that much on?
What is this?
What a well-behaved penis.
It's a clever penis.
I went in wanting to tear the place down,
but I just had a nice and enjoyable time.
Here we go.
That scares me.
May I take these out?
May I?
-You still have them?
-They look painful.
-They look scary.
-Really?
Could you do it?
No way!
You can't touch other people's eyes!
But...
To be honest, today is the first time
I've ever worn contact lenses.
-But you can't touch people's contacts.
-Really? Is it illegal?
I wouldn't say it's illegal.
Legally, there's no problem.
-It's about hygiene.
-It's unhygienic?
Fingers are dirty.
You won't?
With a tissue?!
But when I was rubbing them before--
You can't do that.
Pinch them with your fingers like this.
You're nearly there.
Nearly there.
I have to touch my eye?
Hey! Wait a minute!
Hold on!
What am I doing
laughing at somebody's balls?
-He laughed.
-Are you out?
Do you have one more chance?
That was nasty.
-They ganged up on me!
-They sure did.
But rules are rules.
You totally cracked up laughing.
Let's take a look.
I have to touch my eye?
Hey! Wait a minute!
-You laughed hard!
-Sorry.
You're out!
After making it this far.
-Zakoshi is too tough.
-He sure is.
No, I wouldn't say that.
He doesn't even seem to be
holding it back.
I'm so frustrated.
I'm sure you are.
I wish you all well.
There were only 40 minutes left.
Just 40 minutes.
I'd earned some points too.
It's so frustrating!
I've watched all four seasons so far,
but it's totally different
when you're actually there.
Everyone is so talented,
I started feeling embarrassed about
doing the bits I'd prepared.
It takes guts to perform in front of them.
Even when you're prepared.
Would any of you happen to have
a charger cable for this PSP?
-No, we don't.
-Sorry.
Oh, my.
But I'm amazed I held out until
there were only 40 minutes left.
I'd like to pat myself on the back
for that.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Do you mind if I call my Helper now?
-You have that left too?
-Yeah.
-Of course.
-Okay?
Come in!
Here comes Zakoshi's Helper.
He's my junior.
-He's with the same agency?
-Yeah, Sony.
It's Jiro, from the duo Charming.
He's here?
Come in!
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Jiro, do your thing.
-What thing?
Your onnagata.
Like in kabuki,
when a male actor plays a woman?
But that takes time to prepare.
Don't tell me you need time to prepare
at this stage!
Sorry, but it really takes time
to prepare for that.
There's no time to prepare!
Okay, there's space back there.
Go get ready.
-A kabuki actor playing a woman?
-Yeah.
-My onnagata?
-Do your onnagata.
And hurry up. Don't take too long.
A male kabuki actor playing a woman.
-Onnagata?
-Onnagata.
I'm a woman!
I'm a man!
Way to go, Jiro!
Well, he did laugh.
More than anything, I was surprised.
How fast did he undress?
-That was all about speed.
-He's super fast.
That speed... Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I've never seen you clothed,
but nice to meet you.
That speed was lethal, right?
Well, I was surprised.
He's fast.
That's what it was about.
-Let's take a look.
-Give me a break.
Do your onnagata.
-My onnagata?
-Do your onnagata.
-Hurry up. Don't take long.
-It was such a basic setup.
A male kabuki actor playing a woman.
After waiting to come out for so long,
he went backstage again...
I'm a woman!
I'm a man!
What's done is done.
-I'm going one-on-one with Zakoshi?
-Thanks.
-It's just the two of us? Me and Junior?
-Right.
Really? All right!
Yamauchi put up a great fight, but...
After coming this far, I wanted to win.
But the moment he appeared,
I thought,
"He doesn't look like a comedian at all."
That was funny for one thing.
I thought he looked like a writer,
or maybe a researcher.
Onnagata? But that takes time to prepare.
After leaving the room he got butt naked
with such incredible speed.
Then he came out,
and it had nothing to do with kabuki.
I'm a woman!
I'm a man!
I wanted to hold out a little longer.
I hate to admit it,
but Zakoshisyoh is such a strong opponent.
I can't believe they're not laughing!
NEXT EPISODE
Here come the zombies.
Give me your underwear!
The best feel-good massage.
Me too, please.
It was exhausting even just to watch.
I'm worried about
how sore I'll be tomorrow.
Really worried.