Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!
Look at his mouth.
What?
What's wrong, Jimmy-san?
Look at his teeth.
He laughed.
What's this?
Balls.
Can I touch them?
I wouldn't recommend it
but if you wanna.
I want to touch,
just a little.
There we go.
So fluffy!
It was pretty decent.
Compared to past versions.
It was
incredibly good.
It was a good Documental.
For real, yeah.
Okay,
so maybe what comes next.
I wonder...
Let's continue.
Alright, here we go!
Can I use this?
He can?
Can we use the tofu like that?
Yeah, for sure.
What's that?
It's a brush... a brush.
That's pretty overkill.
Is it for dogs?
No, no. It's a woman's
brush, I think.
About 2000 yen.
Okay, wanna play Karuta? (Editor's Note: 1)
I made an original Karuta.
Let's do that!
Me too!
Okay, we have to look first.
This is "A".
"Anal and shrimp?
Raw or cold?"
This is "I"
"I came, so I opened my eyes."
That's crazy.
"I came,
so I opened my eyes."
It's too much.
"I came, so I opened my eyes."
"I came,
so I opened my eyes."
Wouldn't you normally close them?
"I came, so I opened my eyes."
Just a face.
"If you squint a little,
the mosaic disappears."
Right, right.
"E"
"Eguchi Yosuke?
He'd look good with some lipstick on."
Next. "O"
"Oh, pussy."
"Ca" ("Ka")
"Can you get me some of that
sweet shit?"
Damn, who was it?
Wasn't it you?
Weren't you talking
while smiling?
This is pretty serious.
No, but I was just smiling
to make others smile.
Like inviting us?
Exactly, I'd say
that I'm in the clean— clear.
Clean?
Clean clear?
Okay, so!
Who was it?
Uh... Koba!
Huh?!
I wasn't smiling!
—For real?
—Yeah!
—You sure?
—Take a look!
—Totally sure?
—Yes.
You were already on a tight rope
with Cookie's Karuta game.
It was pretty serious.
I think I was holding it.
Really?
"Ka"
Can you get me some of that
sweet shit?
You were smiling!
He was smiling!
That counts as smiling?!
You were smiling!
—No way!
—Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Have mercy.
You should be out for lying.
He was totally smiling.
Jimmy was smiling as well
at a weird time.
All along, yeah.
I can't even count anymore.
That's just my face.
No, no, not at all.
Right, we're following the rules.
Okay, here we go.
Everyone left.
Feels lonely in here.
I want to look at this.
Let's wait until
everyone's back.
Let's just do it a little
"Anal and shrimp?
Raw or cold?"
That's good.
"I came, so I opened my eyes."
That's pretty good.
This is great.
"If you squint a little,
the mosaic disappears."
Great, great.
Are you imitating
Master Daisuke?
I am, Kansai style.
"Eguchi Yosuke?
He'd look good with some lipstick on."
"Oh, pussy."
Can you get me some of that
sweet shit?
Amazing.
"My balls are hot.
My balls are hot!"
Wa-wa-wait.
Just once.
Don't waste it now.
We should wait.
Let's look at them together.
Together, yeah.
Call them over.
Let's look at them together.
What?
Cookie's Karuta.
Can I show you
something in the meantime?
It's a prejudice book I made (Prejudice/Stereotype/Bias)
Prejudice?
What should we do?
Just ask for one
and I'll say it.
All my prejudices
are right here.
Give me a prejudice!
Alright, what number from the top?
The first one!
Alright...
People who look like Inagawa Junji
hit women.
"Cha!" (Kenji Tamura (Tamuken) - "Ciao")
The "cha" isn't necessary.
I was close.
I was about to laugh
but it brought me back.
I pressed the wrong button.
Give me another one.
What number from the top?
Number six, let's do that.
Grannies
Grannies that gossip
in spring
get cancer.
Don't joke about that, man.
It's a prejudice...
Prejudice?
It won't open!
It's already dented
just open a hole.
Koumoto-san look at this.
Damn it
Whoa, your back...
What happened to your back?
What's that, man?
I was playing with my hamster.
Those bangs are too short.
Who are you?
I'm Mito Natsume. (EN: 2)
Ah, Mito Natsume.
-Ouch!
Not Masami Hisamoto's sister?
-What was that?
There we go.
Mito Natsume-san?
Wait,
I'm a little thirsty.
No, no, no!
Watch out, watch out!
That's not for your eyes!
My eyes hurt.
Remember these.
Remember the Karuta.
What's this Karuta?
Master Daisuke sure has
a foul mouth, huh?
He doesn't say much, though.
Read them.
What?
Read.
I slipped up and told the story of how
I got beat up by Nakabo at a festival.
The manager... couldn't come out...?
You shouldn't be reading this!
Too fast!
-It was Koumoto!
-Definitely Koumoto!
-No way!
-This is serious.
Koumoto!
That was just hilarious
come on...!
This is how I managed to hold on.
With this.
That's how you do it?!
You can't be doing this!
It definitely wasn't me!
Is it so wrong
to use this?
Well, yeah,
this time it wasn't Koba.
I think he knows,
but it was Koumoto.
For real...?!
Read.
I slipped up and told the story of how
I got beat up by Nakabo at a festival.
The manager... couldn't come out...?
You shouldn't be reading this!
Here you go, Koumoto.
That's rough!
-Second one!
-Ah, right!
Was it this?
That was dirty, really.
You took that picture?!
Here we go!
Whoa!
What's wrong?
You're Mito Natsume, right?
What's going on?
What's that sticking out?
It's just in there, chill.
Is that the head?
Not the head. Just how it looks.
That's embarrassing.
That's Mito-chan's?
Definitely Mito-chan's.
You're too hard!
Mito-chan's is that big?
The head?
The head, yeah.
That's how it looks.
It's not even that hard.
It's hard.
Take it out, man.
There's something there.
What did you do to your dick?
His balls are red.
You pulled on your balls?
What's that?
Wa-wa-wait!
Kubota too!
I'm fine, I'm fine.
This is just-
That's not normal!
That's an STD!
It's far too red!
He has red-ball disease.
No, this is just tight
and kinda hot.
He laughed out loud, right?
This was pretty bad, yeah.
We didn't get that much
on camera, don't worry.
An STD?
Kinda
Not really, but it just
looks a bit like it.
This is pretty normal.
That's red!
No, no, no!
He has red-balls disease, ,man!
That's just what happens when it gets hot
so I use a towel and-
I pack one of these.
You were gonna use that later?
What's that?
It gives it shape.
What's going on?
Wa-wa-wait!
Yeah, right.
I couldn't hold it at all!
Well, this is a point for Nadal.
Yeah!
A point for his balls.
A ball point.
Ah damn!
We're in a rough spot.
And it's all at a bad time.
Alright!
Only two hours.
Still four left.
I thought it had been more time.
There you go again, man!
What?
What's wrong?
No, come on!
We can do this.
We can laugh right now.
No, man...
I have to do it again...
Can't be helped!
I haven't done anything!
Huh? What?
Don't know?
Show us.
What's wrong, senpai?
Is this it?
Why d'you take the matches?
-Those are matches!
-What's with you?
Are you mad?
No man! It's in my phone!
You guys are so unfair!
What? Huh?
Wanna look?
No, I won't loog.
"Loog"?
Wanna watch it all together?
Look at this.
Like this?
"My cock?
It has high level phimosis!" (EN: 3)
There's the "wa" karuta.
"My cock?
It has high level phimosis!"
There's the "wa" karuta.
Who put it there?
That's not good.
Jimmy-san?
No, not me.
-He really said that?
-He did.
What is it?
"Maybe I can chew the juice
out of a turd!"
Maybe? What?
He says this?
-What?
-Who says that?
He really said this.
"Wash me from top to bottom!"
"I haven't used soap
in about eight years!"
He said that too
"Sypu!"
Huh?
"Pussy sypu!
Pussy sypu!"
"Maybe I can chew the juice
out of a turd!"
"Wash me from top to bottom!
I haven't used soap in eight years!"
"Nishioka Sumiko?
Don't know her!"
"Can you give me that
sweet piece of shit?"
"First year of Reiwa!"
"A girl I want to fuck?
Zawachin!"
"Detective Night Scoop."
"I don't watch it since
Nagahara Seiki isn't around."
I like it.
Did he say this "ne" one
to Master Hanako?
-What?
-Ne.
"Never look at that hag while she sleeps!"
I'm sure that made
Master Hanako angry!
He didn't say that to Master Hanako
so it's fine. It was Miyako Chocho
This is pretty fun!
More than metal, huh?
You tryin' to pull out your head?
So I've been doing reporting
on adult toys for a while, right?
And lately there are many
with like a good rhythm.
Yeah, they've kept evolving lately.
The rhythm is pretty incredible.
The rhythm?
They don't go just "bzzz"
like the other ones.
It's more like this...
I thought it could match to music.
I feel like you could
put music on this.
With the rhythm?
No way!
Isn't it great?
Really amazing.
What's that?
What's that over there?
Jimmy-san, right?
That's Jimmy-san, right?
You saw that?
Wanna try
how this one vibrates?
Whoa!
That's good, pretty good!
Yay!
Tokyo!
Who are you?
I'm Ujita Minoru. (EN: 4)
What's he doing?
A pretty old-fashioned idiot.
What about the sound?
Want some ice cream?
Ice cream.
Ice cream? Really?
I made it myself.
It's homemade.
You sure?
It's all gooey.
What's this?
Ah, thank you so much.
Is that homemade?
Thank you.
Huh?
Hey! This is lube!
Are you trying to kill me?!
That must be bad for your body, man.
No, lube is fine.
Otherwise...
Workers would end up dying.
It's not something you eat, though.
-This is great!
-Let's do some sumo.
Why sumo right now?
Sumo with lube?
You still have some.
It's sticking all the way there!
Look at that thread!
Do something!
He's really eating it, huh?
I'm feeling sick.
That's gross!
That's too gross!
Stop it, man!
Too close, too close!
Gimme, gimme.
Just once, gimme.
Spit it out.
I want three bowls of rice with this.
Gimme, gimme.
This is awful.
I want four bowls. Five.
I'm gonna stir it all up.
All of it.
Sasaki-san!
Sasaki-san.
Welcome
You look scary!
Well, I'm... I'm Sasaki.
Welcome!
Sasaki-san! Sasaki!
Who the hell are you?
Welcome.
So you're worried
about your bad breath?
Well... yeah, kind of.
Okay, let's take a look then.
Yeah.
Ah, this is it.
Sasaki-san, your tongue
is all covered in moss.
Moss.
Moss on your tongue.
The green one?
Yeah, yeah. That's the smell
on your tongue.
Really?
So let's take it off.
-Right.
-It's for the best.
Thank you very much.
Look.
Don't you puke.
Don't start puking.
Don't do that!
No!
Hold it in,
like a big boy.
Okay?
Look
See? There's a lot of it.
This is what causes the smell. Okay?
Come on!
What did you eat?
No, just an onigiri.
An onigiri?
Definitely not an onigiri.
No, it's just-
This?
Not an onigiri.
It was an onigiri, man.
Is this an onigiri?
I also had some karaage. (EN: 5)
So you eat karaage too?
That's bad, man!
You're eating karaage?
Take that out, please.
Because the onigiri-
Doctor
Excuse me.
I farted earlier
and this came out
of my butt.
Could you take it out?
Please take it out, doctor.
Take a seat.
No, I just farted earlier.
Ouch ouch! What you doin'?!
Stop it, stop!
What're you doin'?!
Stop! Stop it!
What is it? What's wrong?
What happened?
Watch out!
He's for real, come on!
Some random guy.
I barely made it out, though.
He got you in the head?
That was pretty close!
He was pretty serious!
He got you right here.
I'm Super Sansuke! (EN: 6)
No way.
He's here?
Not many people
try a Sansuke impression.
I saw him a couple days ago.
It's sloppy
and the hair's too short.
Too white, too.
You two match.
Nah, I'm fine.
I'm seriously worried.
It's a tiger.
That stinks, man.
That stinks, shit! It stinks!
It's that good old
summer stench.
What kind of smell is that?
For real,
who thinks that?
It smells too bad.
Whoa! Gross!
That stinks!
I'm sure it's not that bad, right?
Damn, damn, it stinks!
Too soon.
Your reaction was too soon.
What?
It just
It was an impulse.
Of course not.
Alright, smell it then!
It stinks!
Too soon.
It was too late.
Too late.
So it's no good?
Not Sansuke?
Sansuke is in trouble.
-It stinks!
Too late!
Too late, huh?
So late I could die.
Doctor...
In your mouth.
I'm sure Yoshimoto will tell us
to stop after eating shit.
Inada is
about to puke.
What's that?
He's just about to puke.
Are you okay, Inada-san?
What's that sound?
I'm trying to fool myself.
To not puke?
Doing that helps?
Nadal, let's do that.
The Nadal reverse.
The Nadal reverse evolution.
It's been a long time, huh?
It can evolve in any way.
Revolution.
If you say "pencil" I can go
"sharpen!" like that.
I can make anything evolve
in Nadal reverse evolution.
Anything goes?
Tissue!
Flowing tissue.
Nadal reverse: Flowing Tissue
Evolution!
It normally doesn't flow,
but this one does down the toilet
That doesn't feel like an evolution.
Okay, the table!
A rotating table.
Nadal reverse evolution!
What's a rotating table?
A table is a table.
Twisted intestines.
Twisted intestines?
It's a disease in your intestines.
Okay... cancer.
Nadal reverse evolution!
So it gets worse?
I thought it would get better.
It's evolving.
So it gets worse.
Trophy!
Uh... gold medal.
What's over there?
What trophy?
No, I wasn't looking at anything.
Miyasako-san. (EN: 7)
Kiyohara.
Nadal reverse evolution.
He evolved?
Is that an evolution?
Criminally, yeah.
Criminally?
Not criminals!
Can you do me?
An evolution?
Something I'm aspiring to.
Let's do that, yeah.
Shimaki Joji. (EN: 8)
Huh? Why?
Evolution.
Gorgeous.
That's good.
Yeah.
Do Koba-san.
An evolution?
Sasaki Kensuke. (EN: 9)
Nadal reverse evolution!
I kinda get it, though.
Why, though?
Okay, Jimmy-san.
Sato Jiro. (EN: 10)
Nadal reverse evolution.
Is that good?
I think so, yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
It's not an evolution, just a lookalike.
Is there like a devolution?
I've never done that.
He might go off the deep end then.
Let's go with a devolution!
Pencil!
Uh... trash.
Trash?
That works with everything.
It's the same for everything.
It's kinda like philosophical.
Okay, Jimmy-san.
Uh...
Matsuo Bannai. (EN: 11)
Yeah, we don't look alike.
Isn't Bannai-san older?
We're contemporaries.
Then it's not a devolution.
It's not a devolution!
That's not a devolution.
Bannai-san is way better.
A sekitori? (EN: 12)
Where are you going?
You can't go that way.
No way.
What was that?
Huh?
What are you a grandpa?
Where are you going?
A grandpa?
Um... so...
The strobes?
Yeah, I want to project...
This way. This way.
Ah, that way?
And then turn left.
What's this all of a sudden?
I want you all
to see something.
Ah you wanna do something?
We'll watch
I'm gonna do something.
Show you something.
Of course,
just do it.
Okay, I'm gonna show you.
Maybe we'll learn something.
You can go this way?
That way.
This way.
Devolution? Devolution...
What is Nadal reverse evolution
devolved?
It'd be Nadal reverse.
-Do it with a better voice.
-What about Nadal reverse?
If it devolved?
"Nanno"
That's Nadal reverse devolved?
-What's that?
-Nanno
That's not funny.
Who does that?
Cashew nuts
No, pistachio.
"Nanno"?
What are we going to eat?
He's pretty serious, huh?!
You're impressive.
I'm hungry. Wanna order something?
Take that.
I'm starving.
Let's choose.
Look at that. Ina-chan.
Rock paper scissors
What can you make?
Right hand is a claw.
Left hand is a claw too.
We go shrimping.
We go shrimping. We go shrimping.
What's that?
Rock paper scissors
Rock paper scissors.
What can you make?
One on the right
One on the left
Eye crushing,
eye crushing, eye crushing.
Rock paper scissors
What can you make?
Right hand goes here
Left hand goes-
Feeling empty
He can keep a straight face?
Do that here!
What about the strobes?
I wanted to see the strobes.
Should've done that here.
Jimmy-san!
Use the strobes!
I think he's getting serious
so don't start nagging!
You didn't use the strobes.
Do it with the strobes
one more time.
Didn't you go to check
the strobes back there?
I'll do it again with the strobes.
He was looking for them.
That would be a dramatic change.
I'll do some ventriloquism.
Good day!
This would've been better
with no strobes, definitely.
The rhythm is all off, too.
It should be faster.
This is probably the worst thing
you could do with strobes.
Jimmy-san is all wrong about this.
It's impossible to tell the movements...
My right hand!
My eyes...
My eyes hurt.
A question.
Who built Osaka Castle?
That's the end?
Jimmy-san.
Wait, that was too hard to see.
My eyes hurt.
You see, ventriloquism...
I was doing ventriloquism.
It was great
But we couldn't see your awesomeness
because of the strobes.
Yeah, yeah!
It was all wrong.
You should do it here
We could see if you did it right here.
Alright, then let's do it here.
Alright, can I do it?
Yeah.
Okay, one question!
Sure!
I'll answer anything!
His mouth is moving.
It's moving?
Who built Osaka Castle?
Toyotomi Hideyoshi.
And who built Edo Castle?
Yeah.
Tokugawa Ieyasu.
It's 8:45 right now.
How should I attack?
What's the right attack?
Eight...
Beep
Beep...
Eight...
Forty five...
One minute
It's 8:46.
Huh?
What?
I should've attacked instead.
Well, it's just...
What's going on?
He'll answer correctly.
Ah, he hasn't answered yet?
No, not yet...
He's gonna answer correctly then?
He hasn't yet.
Ah, he's gonna?
I see!
Don't stop him halfway there.
Answer quickly.
How should I attack at 8:45?
I don't know
about that...
Not by the hourglass
I see, that's true.
Eight... wait...
What's this about?
The hourglass looked
just like 8:45
The hourglass looked like 8:45?
Because it's two circles?
Yeah yeah
The eight
The shape's like an eight? Then 45?
The 45 is on its side.
Where? What's that about?
I don't get it.
Did you smoke some pot back there?
Huh? Pot?
You're fucking crazy.
You've been weird since then.
Pretty insane.
That's some clean posture.
You did ballet or something?
Baseball.
Your leg posture is clean.
Hello
Ah damn it!
This is serious!
I'll answer anything about
the show business! (EN: 13)
Show business?
You curious?
Yeah!
You too?
That's not really great.
What's the future of
Johnny & Associates?
Who should answer?
Kubota-san's...
Why do I have to-
Makoto, Makoto.
What?
Makoto.
The name's Makoto.
What's gonna happen to
Johnny & Associates?
It's gonna collapse.
It collapsed yesterday.
Yesterday?
It didn't, though!
Is that true, Makoto-kun?
They replaced their windows.
What?
Windows?
Ask any question! Go on!
Okay, so about the entertainment industry...
what actor likes to pretend
they're an MC?
Pocaskajan.
Huh?
Pocaskajan!
Pocaskajan? The trio?
From Wahaha Hompo?
Pocaskajan will take over
the world of comedy.
You agree, Makoto-kun?
Makoto-kun does, yes.
Yes.
You think so?
Okay, go ahead!
What woman could I hit on
in the show business?
Kudo Shizuka.
Huh?!
Kudo Shizuka-san!
No way!
No way, man!
What big couple's
gonna get married soon?
Let's ask Makoto-kun.
Married soon?
A big couple...
Can I say?
Mihara Junko-san and...
Hashi Yukio-san.
That's unexpected.
Weird choice.
Who's the strongest
performer out there?
The strongest fighter.
The strongest fighting performer.
I'm curious.
They're asking you.
Makoto-kun.
The strongest performer.
Eh... the strongest performer is...
Um... Giant Baba
What should I say?
Makoto-kun, what do you mean?
He's dead,
Makoto-kun.
I'm sorry!
Nadal, can you
borrow Makoto-kun?
What?
What what?
Ventriloquism.
Hello. I'm Jimmy.
Jimmy-kun...
He's not talking at all.
Hello, I'm Jimmy.
Who's talking?
I'm sorry. This is my doll
Jimmy-kun.
I can do ventriloquism
without moving my mouth.
Ask anything
and he'll answer.
I'll answer anything!
Even anything about you?
Yeah, of course! Go on!
Jimmy-kun, what's the worst thing
you've done so far?
Okay. Pyromania.
That's cute.
Pyromania is cute.
You lit things on fire?
Yes!
Where?
All over the place.
You're evil!
He's pretty serious!
What's the most fun
you've had so far?
Okay
The first time I peeled my skin off.
Huh?
Skin
Your dick's?
Yes!
You like touching your dick?
I love it.
It didn't hurt
when you peeled it off?
It hurt
but it felt really good later.
So it feels great
after it hurts a little.
Did something come out?
Yes!
What came out?
Okay...
Tell us!
Yes!
Maracas.
What do you mean maracas?
It's over it's over.
We're done here.
It's over once
maracas show up.
This is for training.
Ina-chan, you have
any complexes?
He does?
Well you see... it's about my nipples.
Many people have complexes
about their nipples.
I can see something.
A complex?
Jimmy-san, Inada says
he has a complex.
They're too dark
and huge.
Dark and huge?
It's so ugly, I've turned down
all nude job offers so far.
Show us.
It's probably not so bad
if you can show other people.
Take a close look.
It's serious.
All of a sudden...
Here we go.
Here we go?
Huh? What?
They're pretty.
Huh?
How are they dark and big?
They're pale!
Pale!
I can't tell them apart!
Those would look good
on a girl!
They're good looking!
Your mom's tits
were pretty, right?
No, my mom's normal.
Normal?
I'm sure they're pretty.
Are they inverted?
Those are pretty tits.
They have no color.
Completely transparent.
That's unusual.
They're really light.
That one's getting hard.
Hard?
Well, I haven't done anything.
They're probably inverted nipples.
They're not.
It's hard with your hands.
Okay,
wanna use some lube?
Don't be so reckless
with Ina-san, okay?
Wait, wait. Stop.
It's fine.
Lube is a natural product.
Is your skin okay?
Can you get it even harder?
It's not getting harder.
Not like this?
Make it get harder!
Like a real man!
Koumoto-san...
Is this too weak?
I'm gonna do it harder.
Koumoto-san, make him a man.
It's getting harder.
For real, it is!
For real!
Hurry hurry!
Do it more!
How is it?
I'm close!
You came?
I'm feeling more sensitive.
Look! No way!
This one's different!
He came?
Not so slow?
Turn it
and open like a screwdriver.
Like a screwdriver...
Turn right.
Can I turn it around?
I'm closing it?
Ouch! Ouch!
I'll open up, sorry.
Open open open!
It's getting loose
It's getting loose!
There it is!
It's hard for sure!
Just twist it!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Sure!
Huh?
There we go!
That's it!
He smiled naturally.
There we go.
Don't fuck with me, Kubota.
Someone's finally out.
Took us long enough.
Took you long enough, huh?!
It was practically
a stalemate!
So Cookie smiled
naturally, right?
He smiled naturally.
Like it was obvious.
He smiled like it was obvious.
Of course I'd smile
with that face in front of me.
Open it.
I'll open it up. Sorry.
Open open open!
It's getting loose
It's getting loose!
There we go!
It's hard for sure!
Just twist it!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Sure.
Huh?!
It's pretty obvious!
Just like a regular helper!
So Cookie!
You're out!
Damn it!
But Cookie might still
come back as a zombie.
It could happen.
I'm gonna take you all down!
I was surprised by
Ina-chan's nipples.
It was impressive.
For sure, yeah.
They've been like that forever.
Like a nordic girl's.
For real!
An eastern block country.
Thank you all!
Nine left.
It's hard, for sure.
I tend to forget the feeling.
I also laughed a lot my first time
but when I won,
I somehow managed to hold it.
But I completely let go
of that holding back feeling.
Thank you very much.
Sure.
It's rough to have comedy be
like all or nothing.
Though I guess I got nothing this time.
I think it's perfectly fine!
It's fine, yeah!
No problems.
No problems, right?
And the nudity too
It was relatively tame
Compared to previous seasons?
For real, yeah!
There was almost no nudity.
We just battled with pure laughter
that's what it feels like.
Nudity like that
is tamer than idol pictures.
You could even sell it.
Who'd wanna look at that?!
Strip more!
That was the complaint?!
They wanted more skin?!
That was it?
Because Ina-chan's nipples
looked so good!
They didn't want something
so clean!
They wanted filth!
We didn't need this!
Amazon has their bar too high!
That's true, yeah.
There was nothing wrong.
Nothing, right?
I don't get it at all!
It was as fun as
a Jackie Chan movie.
The action of laughter.