Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!
"So Fujimon, yeah, yeah."
"He doesn't strike me as a winner."
"In my opinion."
"He's more of a supporting character."
And even then sometimes I wonder in what way.
— Come on, do it already!
— Why third place?
Do it in any case!
Don't look!
I'm not looking!
— Get it right!
— Start from the third place!
Just get it right!
A supporting actor someone you want to take out as soon as possible, right?
Even when you're feeling about to laugh
You can tell early on if someone is trying something funny
So targetting a single person,
and going one on one against them,
is pretty common from the more skilled people.
There are quite a number of strong people, I think...
I try to get as many different people involved, though.
It's going to hurt like hell, right?
He laughed, yeah!
He's laughing a little.
Just a little smile.
He's laughing, yeah.
Seiji, you're out!
The Chihara brothers are out!
That's right!
Rock, paper, scissors!
— Rock, paper—
—This is bad!
—Whoa!
There it is, there it is!
There's no way!
So Cookie has an orange?!
Cookie and Oshiro-san have...
some pretty good point leads.
He has something again!
Karuta?
Um, Cookie! Come here...
What is it?
Just come here...
Oh, Fujita!
—Kawahara-san!
—Hey! (Editor's Note: 1)
How you doing?
—I'm doing great!
—Why is he here?
—It's like foreshadowing.
—It's foreshadowing, yeah.
Hey, there!
How have you been doing lately?
I had a performance recently!
—Have you been performing?
—Yeah!
I used to visit a lot long time ago!
—Thank you so much!
—Back in Kanpachi!
I see, thank you so much!
You're so loud!
—Thank you!
—Back in Kanpachi, right?
—Thank you so much!
—And I think in Kannana too?
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
It's okay?
He was the boss with Mixi?
—Huh?
—That's right!
—Mixi?
—With Chance...
—It's hilarious!
—Mixi...
I'm Chance Oshiro.
Ah, ah! Oshiro!
—You remember?
—Yeah, yeah.
I used to be asked if I was Aoki Chance's disciple.
Yeah, I used to be W Kenji's disciple, actually.
Who's W Kenji?
You don't know W Kenji?
The guy with Moriwaki-san?
No, no, W Kenji is...
the guy that goes like "ain't it so?!" from Miyagi prefecture.
Huh?
You don't know W Kenji? He does Manzai.
—I don't know him, sorry.
—Who was that?
There was Miyagi Kenji, Azuma Kenji—
Why did you come here today?
I'm just here to...
—Help Fujita?
—Huh?
Fujita?
No, no, not at all.
You're in red today?
You didn't know I like red?
You saw him wearing red, though!
—I'm sorry.
—That's just half of it!
My glasses are red, my T-shirt is red,
and my shoes are red!
Because the company's numbers are in red, of course!
—For real
—You doing okay?
—What was that?
—The company is in the red
That aside, I'm going to make some ramen now.
Alright then!
—The boss himself?
—Can you even eat anymore?
—Um, boss?
—Yes?
How long are you going to take?
I'm just gonna do it in a flash!
It's just that we don't have any water boiling.
Can you stay around here in the meantime?
You're not boiling water yet?
We have to get it boiling soon.
I'll get that done, then.
We just have to get this here and boil it.
—Soup?
—With this.
—We don't have soup?
—This is the soup.
—That?
—Yeah.
Wait, can I ask—
—ask you to talk quietly?
—Yeah.
—Who's speaking loudly?
—Yeah, they're too loud.
Sorry, can we have you do that?
The ramen?
No, you're making ramen here?
Wasn't it Chance's turn?
Let's do the ramen there, then.
—I thought it was Chance's...
—Yeah...
Do you have a moment?
This looks like it's going to take quite a while.
Boss, are you taking long?
—No, no, I'm just—
—Wait, boss...
Can you give us a tuning note?
You think you can play a game with us, boss?
The boss is just...
The boss has to pour the water and—
I don't mind singing.
—No, that's just—
—Okay, just one song.
Ave Maria!
Jungfrau mild.
Amazing
Boss...
Um... that was good.
He wants to become an opera singer.
—Huh?
Once the ramen's done...
Please leave it until after it's done.
Can I ask you to sing one more?
Toreador, en garde
—Ah! I know this song!
—Toreador, en garde
toreador, toreador,
Et songe bien,
oui songe en combattant
Qu'un oeil noir te regarde
Torador, l'amour,
l'amour t'attend!
Okay, thank you very much!
That's enough, that's enough!
Okay, Karuta! (EN: 2)
"A red cock, huh?!"
Can you stop singing that already?
"U"!
"Your wife's nipples look like an eel"
"Ke"!
"Kept three markers inside my asshole!"
Come on, just...
Stay quiet... can you stay quiet? Hey!
"Ya"!
"I'm gonna gobble that soft cock right up!"
A red cock, huh?
"Tempting me to jerk off? Guess I'll oblige!"
"K.O for a smaller girl with just a right jab!"
"Mamo Meemo"
—Did he really say all that?
—He did.
Even that thing about the small girl and the jab.
Then this is what we have.
—You're still going on about that?
—We have a lot of them!
That's enough already, Coo...
This is a collection of all my past masterpieces.
—The best of the best.
—Right.
This is my masterpiece.
"The wife caught me spanking that ass and now I'm dead."
That's not even Karuta anymore.
What's this one?
"The wife caught me spanking that ass and now I'm dead."
—An old saying?
—An old saying.
"The wife caught me spanking that ass and now I'm dead."
"Is this child a creampie?"
—An old saying?
—An old saying.
"Is this child a creampie?"
Come and read this.
Okay, it's done!
—That was quick.
—Great!
—It's done!
—Thank you very much.
I'm going to dig in, then.
I don't think he said that.
Alright!
He definitely did say this one, though.
Liar.
—Where are the condiments?
—No way!
Um... It's only for Fujita?
Only for Fujita?
You all want some?
No, I'm fine, really.
Besides, we're having pizza.
You have to eat that before the pizza gets here.
—Right.
—It's just noodles?
These noodles are pretty stiff.
What about the condiments?
I don't really like them.
It's bad?
You shouldn't say anything, since he's a pro.
Right.
It's all chunky. Look.
Can you sing this in some pretty voice?
In that opera voice from earlier.
Pubes!
K.O for a smaller girl
with just a right jab!
A red cock!
Oh, yeah!
Soft cock!
I'm gonna gobble it right up!
Okay!
—Something came out of your mouth.
—Whoa!
That was pretty rough.
Fluffy pubes
look delicious!
You're getting a bit annoying, boss.
Your wife's nipples
look like
an eel!
Boss, wait, boss...
Can you stay quiet for a little while?
What was that?
—Sorry?
—Huh?
What's that?
Guess we don't need the harmonica, then.
Boss, please come here, boss.
You want more noodles?
—You don't want the harmonica?
—Do it one more time.
—You're so talented!
—Boss, please sit down!
What's going on?
Boss...
Leave it in there.
—Okay.
—Here we go.
You made a sound.
You want more noodles?
—I'm having some.
—More noodles, more noodles.
It's just that you had left...
More noodles.
Yeah.
Patience!
For anal, my anal will...
immediately stretch!
—My anal will...
—Just anal is fine.
Anal, anal.
Anal! Anal! Anal!
So uh, have you heard about the merger (EN: 3)
—between All Nippon Airways and Japan Airlines?
—I didn't know about that.
ANA and JAL will join to form ANAL.
—ANA, right?
—That's cruel!
—Boss...
—It just fits perfectly.
How long are you staying?
Until... you know, that.
Alright then, I'm leaving with a Pei-Pei!
Pei! Pei! Pei!
Daisuke...
The ass goes pei, pei!
—That's not funny at all.
—Thank you very much.
—Thank you for the attention.
Spontaneous gags like that aren't much fun at all.
Thank you, thank you!
—Thank you.
—Pei pei!
Why did he come here?
Why did you call him here anyways?
Everything's backfiring today.
Well... he's pretty popular, at least.
—That's true.
—No, no.
I guess it was fine, though.
So I had a kid,
you guys wanna look at her face?
We're good.
I don't think you should.
She's still only three, so I think it should be fine.
I took a lot of pictures.
She's super cute!
She's pretty cute.
—She looks like you.
—She's a girl, but yeah.
She really looks like you, and she's super cute.
Kids are usually really ugly at this age.
They look like gorillas and stuff.
—Or like sumo wrestlers.
—Right?
—Super cute.
—This is from when she was born.
That's enough, right?
—She's cute.
—We already know she's cute.
I'm so jealous!
What's this?
What's going on here?
—It's fine, right?
—I guess, I don't care, yeah.
That looks good! Who took that picture?
—That was me.
—It's a selfie?
Show us the kiss one more time.
He has plenty of kissing pictures.
Why do you want to see that?
You can see the kiss full on.
Okay, sorry.
That's pretty cute.
—Your wife is pretty cute.
—Being married sounds good.
What's this?
Show them to us one by one!
That's good, I'm so jealous!
Whoa! Full on kiss!
That's a nice background.
Yeah, it sure is.
That's Paris?
—You want this?
—Thank you.
—It's Thai viagra.
—Whoa!
—This is pretty bad.
—Thai viagra?
—It's fine.
—You don't want it?
Doesn't viagra make it super hard?
You've had viagra before, right?
—Look.
—Huh?
I'm getting kinda horny.
—Painting your face again?
—There he goes again.
You're doing the same thing from earlier?
I made it a little thicker now.
It's even harder to tell now.
This guy's a complete idiot, for real.
Why are you turning it off?
—Huh?!
—The kiss thing.
—Come on, that's enough.
—Do it again!
You should leave it on all the time.
Hey, can someone help me out practicing?
—No, I'm fine.
—I'm fine, yeah.
I'm really sorry.
—It's okay, it's okay.
—Leave it.
—When it hurt earlier—
—Look at—
Look at the time already.
Right? So I just wanted you to help me out.
I don't want to help you out.
I'm good with electricity, so...
—Can I do that?
—Yeah.
But it's just that doing it like that is boring.
Bring some hot tea over.
And so it's going to spill if it doesn't work.
What do you think?
I'm pretty sure I've seen this before already, though.
I think this is a pretty new gag.
Tea... where do we have tea?
Are we gonna do this?
What do you think?
We also might have zombies showing up.
Right?
—What's going on?
—What's going on, yeah.
Wait, what's going on? What's that?
What's that?
What are you putting in there?
Can I take a look?
The viagra from earlier?
No, actually, isn't that...
a remote control vibrator?
—It's my first time using one.
—Where's the control?
It's right here, isn't it?
Was that Shouji's reaction?
Okay, so are we going to use the hot tea?
With this on...
Does that hurt? Can he stand it?
We could add this on as well.
It's no good, huh?
—Bring some hot tea.
—What are you doing Shouji?
—Are we doing this?
—Huh...
What's wrong, Shouji?
—Bro.
—Who you calling bro?
What are you doing, Shouji?
Come on, this is taking too long.
What are we going to do?
Isn't he going to drink it?
We just need something hot.
What about the ramen?
Wouldn't that work?
It should work, yeah.
Stop that already!
—Bro!
—I'm not your "bro".
—What about this?
—Whoa!
We don't have any soup? Or water?
Would hot water work?
Sure, that should work.
Really? So water or soup would work?
—Yeah.
—Shouji...
I'm giving you the water.
That burns!
Where? Why? It wasn't me, right?
It hurts all over!
That burns!!
Hurry, "bro"!
Cassius, does this work? (EN: 4)
—Cassius?
—Isn't that Shinsuke-san?
—No one remembers that anyways!
—Wasn't that the name Shinsuke-san used...
when he produced music?
—Shouji.
—Stop it, bro, for real!
Shouji...
Bro!
"Bro"?
Hurry up already!
Cassius, can I give this to you?
Come on man...
Can you drop it with the "Cassius" thing?
Isn't that in Hexagon's style, though?
Since we're doing the whole "bro" gag,
we could go with "Cassius" as well.
But I'm not even Cassius.
That was just a name that Shinsuke-san used
when he did music production.
Like with Sata Andagi?
Well, I guess so, yeah.
Was he in Sata Andagi?
He wasn't.
—The Okinawa rail
—flew off!
That's a Sata Andagi song, right?
And he took to the gap between the clouds!
You sure know that song, huh?
Sengoku-san flew off!
Right.
Isn't he almost laughing by himself?
Who the hell's Sengoku-san?
A racer from the 8 hours endurance race.
You remember Club Shinsuke?
—Team Shinsuke!
—Damn it, there he goes!
This is "high school girl"!
Chan! Bara! Sho!
My father's rival!
—What the hell's going on?
—I don't get it.
He's an entertainer...
My mother's teachings!
Great song, huh?
— My mother's teachings!
— I think the song's great, actually.
There's basically no filler.
This is where it gets good.
Isn't he doing it twice?
These are the village's rules.
He's been doing it for a while, huh?
Is there even a punchline?
Where, though?
In a remote region!
That's pretty bad.
—A remote region?
—A remote region, really?
Thank you very much.
Huh?
A solo act?
—What's going on?
—That was a great song.
— Huh?
— A high school girl?
No, I'm just here as a demonstration.
—A demonstration?
—You mean an audition?
The audition's not today?
—It's not.
—Really?
We're not doing any auditions here.
—You're wrong.
This isn't "Close Up Gendai" from the NHK? (EN: 5)
—There was no punchline after all.
—"Close Up Gendai"?
They don't even do gags there.
—None at all.
—That's not a comedy show.
They told me to prepare a revenge gag.
—What are you talking about?
—You're wrong, though.
But "Close Up Gendai" isn't really...
they're more social focused so...
Right.
Wait— wait...
He's gonna cut him! Watch out!
Watch out with the neck!
—What are you doing?!
—Watch out with the neck!
—Ah!
—That burns!
Stop it with the neck.
—Where?
—The neck?
My neck...
And he goes and asks anyway.
Ouch! That burns! My neck!
She's not stopping so...
Tell her to stop!
—Then you have to—
—That hurts!!
The sword hurts?
The sword, yeah.
I'll do it with the back, then.
The back!
The back's hot!
That burns? Right?
The back of her sword's incredible.
The back of her sword's incredible!
The back...
Ouch!
I can't take it.
What's going on?
Want us to call Matsumoto-san?
You wanna get a red?
No, no, not a red.
—Want to retire on your own?
—I'm not doing that.
Wait a second. The pizza will be here soon.
—At least until the pizza's here.
—Until it's here, yeah.
You think I could do a little something?
—Huh?
—Okay, Oshiro-san.
This one got me banned from eldercare.
—Whoa!
—It got you banned?
Yeah. Here I go.
Here I go.
I love grandpa's smile!
I love grandma's smile!
What's Earth, aliens or God?
Burns!
Are you okay? Watch out!
— I love grandpa's smile!
— No, no...
— Are you okay, Oshiro?
— I love grandpa's smile!
— Watch out, watch out!
— Grandma's smile...
Grandma's smile...
Wait, wait!
— God, aliens and Earth...
— No, no, wait Oshiro!
God, aliens and Earth...
Are you alright?
—No, no, no
—Ah!
No...
What happened? Are you okay?
— I love grandpa's smile!
— Come on...
—That's enough!
—Is this the last one?
— I love grandpa's smile!
I love grandma's smile!
Grandma's smile...
What are you...?
—Are you okay?
—No, no, no.
Earth!
No, for real. This is too much!
Scary! Scary! Scary!
What is God? Grandpa? Grandma?
Come on, man, no way!
That burns! Too hot!
—This guy's a complete idiot!
—I brought some medicine.
Can I drink it?
You're drinking it?
That was a tough act.
—A tough act.
—What's he doing?
You did this in eldercare?
—I think that's too...
—Of course you'd get banned.
He's looking all pale.
This is quite the picture.
What's going on?
It didn't work out.
It didn't?
It had to come out more like...
Like expanding?
Like bursting out of your mouth?
Like pouring?
I guess the powder was too old.
—Sorry for the wait!
—The pizza's here!
—Fujita!
—Excuse me!
—Thank you very much!
This way.
Would this way be okay?
This way, yeah.
Can you leave it here?
I'm leaving it here, then.
First the Yuzuinari Orizome, right?
—The inari.
—This isn't an ashtray okay?
Oh, the sushi!
This is the nagoya dish for three.
That's what Cookie requested.
—Right.
—Thank you very much.
Well then, I'll take my leave.
That looks good!
Right now?
Now?
—Was that it?
—That's it, but...
It's not that amazing even when it works.
Ah, I see.
Wanna play a game again?
—I do.
—A game, right?
Okay, Koumoto and Shouji, sit down.
—Sitting down?
—Yeah.
Fujimoto, I'm done with the painful games!
No, no, no!
You two guys do it!
You put this in your mouth,
and one of you goes like this.
So with this in your mouth, you have to strike like...
And if you do it right,
you have to truly slam his head.
Making a sound?
More than a sound, it has to look painful.
If you wanna do it right, you really have to...
get the proper timing.
I see. Can I take a swing?
—You can, yeah.
—So I have to go like this?
Right! You can't use your hands.
Okay, first attack, Koumoto.
Let's go, Koumoto! Go ahead!
That's no good, yeah.
You have to go more like...
Yeah, more energy.
—Okay, change, change.
—Oh, this is bad.
—Okay, move your head.
—I don't really understand...
I don't really understand what I have to do.
Okay, let's go. One, two...
—Ouch!
—Whoa!
—He's really strong!
—He's good!
—Shouji-san is pretty strong!
—He is.
What's wrong? You okay?
It's just that...
I think I have to pay a visit to my dentist...
All of my teeth feel like they're gonna fall off.
I thought they had fallen off.
—Huh?
—They're there, they're there.
You still have all of them.
Okay, ready?
So come on...
You really have to let it down with force, okay?
Here I go. Let's go.
On the count of three.
One, two...!
—A little more!
—What was that?
You go easy on him when you hit him!
You have to give it a little more!
It's like you stop, like...
This isn't working,
it's not working.
So like...
you have to raise it and lower it swiftly!
Okay, switch!
Fine, but are you really doing it Shouji?
He is.
—Ready?
—Yeah.
One, two...!
How do you do it?
Take a strike right now!
—Ready?
—Yeah.
You have to go like this and lower it.
So when you go,
when you go like this...
Man, this part of your neck
just screws up all over.
Right here.
It goes like this...
around your neck, around here.
So I don't do...
You're really getting hurt today, huh?
Okay, wanna do it one more time?
Are you doing it?
—Right!
—That's how you do it!
Right, Fujimoto-san?
Yeah. Let's go on the count of three.
Here.
Here we go.
One, two...
What happened?
Are you hurt?
It hurts? You okay?
It's because this is a stick,
I'm sure he's not going like this,
but like this for sure!
—That hurts!
—Ready?
Ready? You sure?
Let's go!
—Ouch!
—Here we go! One, two...
Ouch!
Ouch...
Come on, drop it already...
Please.
Sorry.
—Let's stop that.
—Sorry.
I'm feeling dizzy.
I always thought that...
that you were hiding things from me.
You're always making a fool out of me.
And you make our guests laugh.
I know that you're hiding it behind your back.
And then you hit me with it.
Sorry.
Let me get back at you at least once.
At least tell me why you were hitting me.
Tell me.
This is a trauma that affects me every night.
Why did he hit me?
In my nightmares...
Have you ever woken up to a sound like this?
To this sound?
Have you ever woken up in a cold sweat to this sound?
—Never.
—Right?
—Figures.
Let me do it once.
At least just once.
I know you were doing just that.
—I guess that could—
— Huh?
—That's Onita.
—Onita. (EN: 6)
Onita?
What's wrong? What do you want?!
What is it?!
No, it's just that...
We were playing a game, you know so...
You were getting pretty warmed up.
We were.
—Sorry.
—What's going on?!
It's just that we were playing a game so...
So if you're going to complain well...
Just let us know.
Are you Onita?
I am...!!
— Ah, Onita.
— Onita-san, right?
Hirose Alice!!
No you're not.
Got that? Hirose Alice and...
Hirose Suzu are family!! (EN: 7)
Well, yeah, they are.
Sit down, Manabe.
—Manabe?
—From TV Asahi?
Manabe...
Well... wait a seocnd.
I'm not even Manabe.
Got anything to say?
Speak up.
You should wait.
No, well...
I was just wondering why you're here.
Are you sure you're in the right place?
This is Alice's lifestyle.
— Alice?
— You're Onita, though?
Are you sure you're not Onita-san?
Onita...
You're supposed to be Onita-san, right?
You got the gender wrong...
But you're Onita-san, right?
You think...
I have a cock?
I think you do.
You're dead wrong!!
So you do?
I do.
Just a little.
So you're a guy, right?
You're not Alice.
I'm Alice.
So what was it you wanted to say?
Well... they had been hitting me for a while...
so I wanted to get back at them.
But I may be able to do it with Onita-san.
—He's got nothing to do with it!
—I was watching you from the back.
But you know?!
I, Hirose Alice, cannot do anything
against you people's injustice!
He can't do anything?
Please do something, please.
I'm an actress!!
Let me do it at least once.
Tell me everything you want to say.
He told you earlier.
Yeah, I did.
I was being hit by this guy...
...all this time. So I want Onita-san to...
You were saying you wanted to get back at them, right?
Exactly.
—You want to hit them back?
—I want to do that.
To get back at them for hitting you?
I want to hit them for hitting me.
But you know I'm an actress, right?!
I can't do anything!!
Then why did you ask?
Why did he tell him?
—Why's he here?
—You wanna tell the actress?
Someone weird showed up again.
— Suzu!
— Huh?
— Hirose Suzu-san?
— Hey, Suzu.
That's... isn't that Don Frye? (EN: 8)
—Don Frye?
—That's Suzu.
No, that's Don Frye!
Suzu!
—Don Frye?
—Tell me what you want to say!
Just who's... Don Frye?
I'm Suzu.
— Suzu-san?
—How are you Suzu?
I'm Don Suzu.
— Don Suzu?
— Not Hirose Suzu?
This guy's... an actress!!
Nice to meet you.
—That's not an actress.
—Not an actress at all.
You're not even a woman.
—An actress, huh?
—Hey!
Wanna try something, sis?
Listen, we're doing the Suzu gag now.
Hey, just sit down.
There?
Everyone, make sure you can see.
"Whoa! I'm falling!!"
So he's not going to read them?
"Yay! Saved by Hiro's nape from Yasuda Dai Circus!"
So he's reading this part?
He's reading, listen!!
He's not saying anything.
—So she fell on Hiro, right?
—As a surface.
Oh, she's Hiro's lover!
It's stretching.
What's going on?
So it's pulling on it?
Is that a puppet?
It's a silhouette.
A silhouette? It's getting closer!
There it is, there it is!!
Is that Hiro?
Of course it's Hiro. It has to be.
It's Hiro.
Hiro...
That's Hiro.
So now Hiro's eating?
No, he became a table, right?
— I don't get it.
— I don't get what's going on.
This angle is too confusing.
I think he might be a table.
So it was Hiro.
What's going on?
Hiro... having dinner.
Yeah, he is.
That's curry?
Ah, spilled the water.
He spilled the water!
— Whoa! That's scary!
— Ah! The eyes!
That's scary, man.
The end.
Huh?!
Thank you very much.
The end!!
Tell me what you thought one by one.
This is hell.
Tell me what you thought of my sister!
—No, well...
—Speak!!
That original punchline really reached my heart.
What an... awful opinion.
—Ouch.
—Come on!!
I didn't really get it at the end.
—What an awful opinion.
—Ouch!
Stop it already!
I'm freaking out here.
I didn't really understand the end...
Hiro-kun crying felt...
profound, just like his link with the water.
It truly got to me.
More of that.
Those tears could bring happiness to people,
and the end was wonderful.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I almost felt like crying.
Give me more, give me more.
I want to hear your opinion more.
Why?
You can tell that Hiro-kun's kindness
would reach the children,
and I think that very kindness means the world.
An awful opinion.
Well, if I say anything bad about it,
you're going to hit me with the mic, right?
Fujimon...
I think you should just give your honest thoughts.
Well, to be honest, I want to see the sequel.
That might work!
— I want more...
— Like...
Um... I've been wondering what might come next.
Tell me more.
I kind of got really excited at the end.
She's my sister, she's my sister.
I want you to have this.
This is my sister.
He's gonna give it to him?
—Giving it out?
—That manuscript?
Yay! I got the manuscript!
—An awful opinion.
—Ouch!
An awful opinion?
Why was that an awful opinion?
I was complimenting you.
I knew it.
I don't get it at all...
Wanna see something?
Go ahead.
Ah, the hat!
He's pretty close!
Pick up that hat.
I wasn't expecting that.
Please continue.
That's a catchy tune.
I took off his collar,
so my dog ran away.
He got run over...
my one and only friend.
— Whoa!
— Huh?!
It stopped
The Mira Parco (EN: 9)
So I went to get revenge
with my brass knuckles.
I picked up a cigarette butt and ate it.
Opened the car door,
and there was a woman trembling,
because she rammed into my dog.
Huh?
Love, love.
It was love at first sight!
— Love, love!
— This guy's an idiot.
— I'm a Tokyo boy.
— A complete idiot.
Love, love!
My dog's name was cupid!
Love, love
You're a dog murderer
I need you, I need you
Bunnies die when they're lonely
Woo-want you, want you
I'm a Tokyo boy
Love, love
Okubo, Joban street
The door's closing
but I slip in
before it does.
It's wrong, it's wrong (Jp - Chigau n desu chigau n desu)
I's wrng, I's wrng (Jp - Chiau su, Chiau su)
Chance, Chance
Chance, Chance,
Chance's dog died.
Thank you very much!
Huh?
You sure can sing.
Don't do that in front of my store.
Sorry, I'm just paying a visit.
Don't get closer, I'll kill you.
—Come on!
—Who's that...
Who's that wench of a woman?
You were listening?
You're not listening!
The other day, the other day,
you see, the other day, the other day,
—the other day
—we can hear you.
No, no, the other day,
you see... um...
You... you know Hankyu Umeda? (EN: 10)
—In Umeda, right?
—Hankyu Umeda...
There's a station near... near... station...
Near Hankyu U... U...
—Hankyu Umeda, right?
—Ume... Umeda's
—So what about it?
—Umeda's...
St... Station.
—What's going on?
—Are you okay?
Wanna drink something?
Umeda's station...
Right, Umeda's station.
I... I was... walking.
That's the whole story?
—Yeah.
—What a masterpiece.
Are you insane?
Who's questioning it?
—Well it's just that...
—Why?
—There's no punchline.
—You were just walking near Umeda's station.
You were literally just walking.
—Yesterday?
I told you about it yesterday?
No... uh... yesterday?
See... yesterday, I... see...
There was this famous... famous...
Who came.
That... Madoka-san, Madoka-san.
Madoka Hiroshi-san. (EN: 11)
So Madoka-san started talking...
Madoka-san came back...
Madoka-san... came back.
And opened the door, and I was at the door.
The door... the door...
Why are you getting stuck halfway there?
So... the door... the door...
—Right.
—It was—
It was closed.
—That's a masterpiece.
—What are you on about?
—Madoka-san came and closed the door, that's all.
—That's—
It's a pretty normal story, huh?
Earlier...
What happened earlier?
Sh- Sh- Sh-
—Sh?
—Sho...
— Shoes?
— Shoes...
What's up with shoes?
Shoes... put them on...
Well, putting on your shoes is normal...
—Don't hold back
—You're holding back, so...
Holding back?! Holding back?!
Don't talk like you're some kind of pro, kid!
Putting on your shoes is a true masterpiece.
What are you even talking about man?
Of course not, since he's holding back,
we're waiting far too long for a punchline.
Don't critique like you're some kind of pro!
What do you think about him?
Ma- Ma- Ma-
Man?
Can't you tell?
What do you think about him?
Huh?!
That's scary!
He has a lot of eyes.
He has some crazy eyes.
That's freaky man!
— Wow!
— Whoa!
— Oh!
— Whoa, that's scary!
A boy showed up...
A boy...?
No way!
It's so freaky when it deflates...
He can't breathe.
Seems to be at his limit.
That's some crazy breathing.
How did he come up with this?
What? What? What's he doing?
— What's that?
— Can he talk?
— He can't talk.
— I don't think he can.
He's making some gestures because he can't talk?
— This is getting serious.
— Hey, watch out, watch out.
— This is getting bad.
— Watch out, watch out!
That's scary!
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
That's dangerous, he can't breathe.
—He's running out of oxygen.
—Like...
Can you gesture something to us?
You want us to do something?
Damn it, damn it, damn it,
No man, oh no, watch out.
This is the scariest one we've seen so far.
—Watch out!
—He was at his limit!
We knew that already.
Is that one of those vegetable containers
they're selling at Costco?
—The ones that are like—
—The vacuum ones, right?
Yeah, one of those.
They're super tight.
Isn't this a Tenga thing, though?
A Tenga Egg, right? (EN: 12)
What are you trying to do?
Wanna talk?
Can you talk? You can't talk?
You're not able to talk?
—Calm down.
—Damn it, damn it!
— This is bad.
— There we go, there we go!
Yeah, this is the scariest part.
There he goes again.
— Ah, it didn't work.
— That's pretty bad!
No way, no way, no way!
—Stop it...
—Who was it?
—Fujita, right?
—Fujita?
By the way, what time is it, Fujita?
I don't have the time.
And the pizza's still not here.
That was pretty funny.
Isn't that pretty cool?
—That was fun!
—I know, no way.
I was laughing all the time.
For real?
I was having fun all the time.
— Who was that?
— Who laughed?
—Fujita.
—I knew it!
—He was laughing for sure!
—Did it many times, too.
Yeah, right, many times.
You laughed earlier for sure.
That's earlier, right?
With Shouji?
So yeah...
—Calm down!
—Damn it, damn it!
—This is bad!
—There we go, there we go!
Yeah, this is the scariest part.
—Ah, it didn't work.
—This is bad!
No way, no way!
No way!
If you're gonna do that just laugh already!
He didn't even fully—
— I was breaking a sweat back there.
— Is this the first time?
— First time, yeah.
— I see.
It was scary but funny.
Fujita... what did you have?
I'm already.
—You had this?
—Yeah, this one.
Can you take this, Fujita?
I cannot take it.
You got yourself in this mess.
It wasn't me.
—This is yours.
—It's not mine.
You only get this today,
but I'm going to get an ever thicker one next time.
—No, come on!
—Full platinum!
Something that looks like the real deal!
—Why do I get special treatment?
—I'm getting a professional one just for you.
There's no professional card,
this is the real deal!
This is the professional card already.
It's too thin, yeah.
Fujita, you're out!
I can't believe you all managed to stand
Chance's songs!
—They were good songs!
—It was pretty good!
That was a mess.
—They were great songs.
—How was that?
—Pretty good!
—"Tokyo Boy", yeah.
The three of them were original!
That's great.
What if Fujita is the one to make us laugh,
now that he became a zombie?
Yeah, right?
Okay,
—good job, everyone!
—Good job, good job.
What if Fujita actually makes us laugh
as a zombie?
— I think he could be the scariest.
— That was good.
I think he could be the scariest.
I'm not impressed with my results.
I never felt like
anything I did hit them
or made them really laugh.
Not once.
—That's no fun!
—It's fun.
—Then hurry up!
—Why third place?
Just do something already!
—Get them right, then!
—Just show us third place!
Get it right!
What you usually regret is not being able
to do what you had planned,
and then feeling bad because you couldn't do
this or that,
or you didn't try something at the right time.
So I'm glad I took so many swings.
They just didn't land.
Alright...
It's like you don't—
—Right?
—Oshiro, Oshiro.
Should we call in the Zombies?
— Here we go.
— We can always go one time per person.
"Zombie time!"
It's time!
Get ready for zombies!
Whoa...
—That's a sweater to get laid, for sure.
—Really...
This looks like trouble.
Didn't take him much to get here.
Just one second after the "Zombie Time", huh?
What are you eating?
That looks really good?
—They're popping!
—They're poprocks, huh?
Keep it up.
Ready?
You gonna talk with poprocks?
Sounds like you're chewing on aluminum foil.
Like pop pop pop!
Whoa...
—Popping sushi?
—Popshi?
— Whoa!
Are you a woman?
Are you a guy?
Don't make that face.
Especially that sound...
It's annoying to hear...
Can you answer any questions?
You're a girl?
Grab his ass, and you'll find out.
That's a nice ass.
Stop it with that face.
That's an impressive way to move his eyes!
They're like angled
but somehow smiling?
What about his tits?
This is pretty stupid.
—They're all idiots, for real.
—He has a nice rack, huh?
Fujimoto-san, I'm sure it's been a long time, huh?
Not really.
—Who are you?
—Huh?
Who are you?
—Me?
—Yeah!
I'm Pachio. (EN: 13)
What?
—Pachio?
—I'm Pachio.
—Ah, because of the sound?
—Yes.
So you're a guy?
Whoa! That's pretty loud!
That's crazy.
It's really like biting on aluminum foil.
Just like...
—It's like he's frying tempura.
—For real!
Why did you come here, Pachio-san?
—Sorry?
—What are you doing?
Why are you here, Pachio-san?
Did you have any business with us?
—I just thought you looked troubled.
—About what?
Did you come to cheer on us?
Yes, you looked troubled.
There's nothing you can do,
so you may leave already. We're fine.
You haven't been doing anything.
Just leave already.
Wanna do some Mario gag once Pachio-san leaves?
—Let's do that.
—Right?
Wanna watch, Mario-san?
Mario-san?
Didn't you just call me Mario-san?
You got them mixed up.
Yeah, I just called him Mario-san,
because he's Pachio-san.
Right. I said Mario-san.
Right. Oh, you stink!
Sorry, wait a second.
Your breath stinks!
Okay, I'll get going.
Thank you very much!
Stop that already.
It's not that bad anyways.
Then come and smell my mouth.
I'll shut up if it stinks.
I don't care if yours stinks.
Because I know mine doesn't.
Stop lying about that.
Okay, it's a promise then.
—Stop if it it stinks, then!
—Okay.
Here I go.
That stinks man!
—What's your problem?
—Stop that already!
That was fucking gross!
— That hurts, so stop it.
— Ouch!
It really hurts like hell.
I had to do that earlier.
I promised, though.
That almost knocked me out.
Yeah, that's dangerous.
Aren't you exaggerating, Koumoto?
Maybe!
Huh?
You're making way too big a deal
out of this!
Come on.
That really hurts!
Wait, Koumoto.
This guy's really...?
—He's really going at it.
—For real.
Okay, I'm going to increase the strength gradually,
so tell me when you reach your limit.
—He's for real.
—I know, right?
—And stop after you reach it.
—Just after reaching his limit.
You can make me suffer all you want
if I go beyond your limit.
They've hit me 20 times already.
You know how many?
I'm getting a bruise already.
With this?
Yeah, it's fine.
—How's this?
—That's fine.
—How's this
—That hurts!
Ouch!
—Ouch!!
—You're smiling a little, aren't you?
I'm not smiling.
Not at all.
This is getting fun.
You're not gonna do it any more?
We're almost out of time anyways.
You're right. Time's out.
Yeah, this is pretty bad!
Are we gonna keep going from the middle?
—What do you mean?
—The game of the head.
Ah, that's right.
We've been ignoring it all this time.
Shouji, you have to look.
I was looking.
I can see everything from here.
I've been thinking about the Mario all this time.
I can see just fine.
What's that below his head? (EN: 14)
There he goes.
That was wrong?
You have to watch the head man...
Stop it with the "Ah!" already.
We've seen this already.
How many times are we gonna do this?
I love this.
Okay, let's keep going.
How many are there?
—Look there, right there.
—There it is.
This is what you wanted to see, right?
— Okay, next one?
— No, that's not it, right?
We saw this earlier.
Ah, that's right.
I think you haven't seen what comes next.
—It's the same!
—No, this is different.
—This is different?
—Yeah.
Are you seeing this?
Huh?
I have another one.
I don't think I can take the hand.
—This is the one with the hand, right?
—This is rough.
This is pretty different.
Moto-san sure is slow, though.
He's just a little cautious.
Isn't this the one with the hand?
It's a different version.
There's the one with the hand
and another one.
Ah, it was the one with the hand.
Sorry.
Alright. I was waiting for a new one.
—This is different?
—What's this?
—We hadn't seen this.
—You have to jump?
I think it's the same.
It's the same.
That's something else.
I get it now.
That's...
So he still dies?
How many do you have?
Why did he die after riding on Gucci-san's head?
This is still just level 1-1.
What's that sound?
What's that?
Something's spinning?
Isn't that Takahashi Meijin? (EN: 15)
Takahashi Meijin...
—Ah!
—Endless bouncing.
—This is endless.
—He keeps going.
So 16 shots?
—Huh?
—The ground's fucked.
Wh-Why?
He did that himself.
Why?
Come on... why?
Listen.
—What's going on?
—Huh?
She's cute.
Huh? What happened to Fuyuki-san?
This one's actually kinda scary.
That's enough, that's enough.
—This is scarier than Moto-san.
—We had enough, right?
The cute one's scarier.
Watch out damn it!
— Come on...
— Not that.
Stop it, Coo, that's enough.
Come on. That's good enough.
You're always at 0 points.
That's enough Coo.
Stop it already, please.
Sorry, you got 200.
That's not it?
— What's going on?!
— Ah!
Don't die right away, man!
—This is a different screen!
—You didn't clear it, though?
It's impossible, for real.
This isn't normally possible.
That's enough, Coo.
Really, I've had enough.
—Damn it.
—Huh?
—Only 16 minutes left.
—Ah, that's weird.
Which one was better?
They were all good.
—Zombie time.
—Huh?!
This sucks!
Whoa!
This is pretty gutsy.
Yeah, it's pretty tight already.
We're really tight on time.
We have an expert here.
Huh?
You're still here, Toku-san?
—The boss told me to stay!
—Okay.
He told me to write a report
on this list right here.
Of course it's going to be a pain in the ass
for a detective
who has been working on his feet
all this time, like me.
What are you talking about?
This is pretty easy to use
if you just take the time to learn.
I like their acting quite a bit.
—It's just that...
—Yeah?
My daughter's husband bought one for me.
That's a nice son-in-law!
And you don't use it?
I only open it to look stuff up.
—I see...
—For the most part...
it's just sitting there gathering dust.
—Hey,
—Yeah?
How's your mom doing?
Thank you for asking.
Thankfully, she's getting discharged in two days.
That's good to hear.
Have you been visiting her?
I haven't.
Visit her, you idiot!
—Okay.
—Listen, man,
You think someone who doesn't appreciate his parents
can do a good job?
—Well?
—You're right.
So visit her tomorrow, okay?
That's enough,
go home already.
He's pretty good at acting.
What are you doing?
I'm staying with you.
You're like a father to me, Toku-san.
And I can't do my job if I don't take care of my parents.
What are you talking about, man?
Okay, here I go.
Sunglasses.
Sun... Sun...
...gla...sses.
Leather gloves.
Lea... ther...
...glo...ves.
Organizer.
Or...ga...
...ni...zer
—Brassiere.
—Brassiere...
Scarf.
Sca... rf...
— Panties.
Fruit knife.
Fru...it...
...kni...fe...
Lubricant.
— That's quick!
— Extremely quick!
Suzuki Kyouka. (EN: 16)
Su...zu...ki...
...Kyou...ka...
Ayase Haruka.
A...ya...se...
...Ha...ru...ka.
— Mitsuura Yasuko!
— Mitsuura Yasuko.
Her? Really?
Nagasawa Masami.
Na...ga...sa...wa...
...Ma...sa...mi.
High Heel Momoko. (EN: 17)
High...Hee...lu...
— Huh?
— No.
High...Hee...lu...
High...He...lu...
— No, what?
— Why?
High...He...lu...
...Mo...mo...ko.
—Morisanchu Kurosawa.
—Morisanchu Kurosawa...
Tomochika.
To...mo...chi...ka...
And Morisanchu...?
They get along, I guess.
To...mo...chi...ka...
Yuriyan Retriever.
Yu...ri...yan...
Why, though?
No way, why?
Yu...ri...yan...
Re...trie...ver...
Huh? It's too vague.
— Yamada Kuniko.
I don't get the rules.
Harisembon Haruka.
Ha...ri...sem...bon...
No way, Haruka too?
Ha...ru...ka...
So not Haruka?
— High Heel Ringo.
— Huh? Huh?
— Huh?
It's not just chubby girls?
I don't get it.
Okay, Shinbashi's Hostess.
Shin...ba...shi's...Hos...tess...
Even with this?
— It's wrong?
— Well then...
Ginza's Hostess.
— Gin...za's...Hos...tess...
— It's wrong, too?
Gin...za's...Hos...tess...
Seems like it.
Maid cafe employee.
— Ah, no.
— Huh?
Maid... ca...fe...
— Ah, no.
— Huh?
Maid... ca...fe...
— employee.
— It worked with "employee"!
Why did "employee" work?!
Employee...
He likes inexperienced girls?
—Huh...
—Is that it?
Shop employee: Female.
Sh...op...
Employee
Fe...ma...le...
Only employee?
So "female" didn't work?
—He loves employees.
—Maybe it's the uniform.
The uniform?
The uniform.
Nurse!
—Nur...se...
—Huh?!
It's too vague. Employment?
—What about CA?
—CA? (EN: 18)
—CA
—He loves that!
Employee and CA.
CA...
All...
—All Nippon Airways?
—All Nippon CA.
All... Nip...pon...
Huh?!
CA.
And CA, yeah.
—JAL CA.
So it's JAL!
JAL, huh?!
—I love it!
—JAL?!
Can I try another one?
It might not be just about CAs.
Read from here, then.
Big tits large enough to look like
giant armadillos...
What are you talking about?
How long are you gonna keep that up?
Hey.
Well, a long time ago,
we went drinking to an Umehara bar.
And this lady with two huge tits
big enough to be armadillos
like that around her chest,
ended up leaving with us.
I've heard that before!
That was quick.
So he ended up taking Takahashi's girl?
Junior did that?
—The girl Takahashi wanted...?
—That was how years ago?
That was like 2 years ago, right?
—Liar!
—Two years?!
It was more than ten years ago.
Two years?
How tall was she?
She was like this tall.
—I knew it.
—She was pretty short.
Like 145cm...
And her legs were bending inwards
like this.
Yeah, she really looked
like one of those statues from the Osaka period.
No way.
There was also another girl
with a forehead bigger than President Ohashi's.
It was really sticking out.
So in the end I ended up
leaving with the girl with the forehead bigger than
President Ohashi's.
It was like this.
And they were making out when
I came back from the bathroom.
When was that?
That's pretty nasty.
Only eight minutes left!
So what now?
There's no way now...
It was Cookie by far, right?
We gotta do something about that.
But Oshiro also has a good chance!
—Oshiro does, yeah!
—He got a few points in the beginning!
He did?
And he doesn't have many cards.
You're right, Oshiro...
He has no cards at all.
But cards cost a lot in the end.
—You win by points, so...
—Right, with points.
It's not by card number?!
Points obviously count when you have too many.
I made you all smile, though.
I couldn't help but smile even a little.
Smiling just a little is against the rules, right?
What are you doing to my ass, man?!
What are you doing, idiot?!
Stop it!
Can you stop that?!
What are you doing?!
I think even force won't be enough...
That'll only make me twitch like that!
Can you... can you stop that?!
Can you stop that?!
What are you doing?!
Earn a proper reaction!
Win fair and square!
Yeah, that's not really fair.
Win fair and square.
Can you stop that?
Damn it, look at the time.
How should we end it?
—What do we do?
—What do you want to do?
—What?
—Hey, hey!
—Hey!
—Who is that?
Hey!
Kamayatsu, Kamayatsu
Kamayatsu, Kamayatsu!! (EN: 19)
Oh! Kamayatsu?
Hey, hey, hey!
—Hey!
—He's pretty good!
The wife with the scabby nipples
gets upset at her husband
and puts betadine on him every day.
The wife with peeling nipples
gets upset at her father-in-law
and puts mentholatum on him every day.
Guess anything's better than having
shitty nipples.
The women with scabby and peeling nipples.
They're always upset
and putting medicine on someone else.
Rock n' roll!
What's next?
Come on, Cookie!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
— Wait! Damn it!
— He's going to keep attacking?
You gonna take my child away?
You sure blabber on, huh?
How can you say that to my child?!
Can you do that to my child?!
He's kinda cute.
Okay, take a good look.
Poor thing...
That's freaky.
Look, it's so freaky.
That's one freaky dude.
—It can't be helped...
—Because kids...
No, this guy isn't a child.
What do you think you're—
What are you going to do?!
—Here we go.
—Boy, come—
Ouch, damn it!
The sun's rising outside already?
It did, right? Hey.
I'm done.
Where are you going? Hey!
I wanted to do something,
but I don't think we're doing anything.
This is pretty good.
Give it back, give it back.
—Damn it.
—Give it back.
—Give it back, man.
—Damn it, damn it.
I'm not giving it back.
—Give it back.
—No.
Give it back.
If you're serious,
then take down that guy.
—Who?
—That guy.
Fine. Come here.
No way, no way.
I'm giving it back, here.
Go, go. Go on.
Stop, stop!
—You're gonna get hurt!
—Stop it already! Stop!
—You're gonna get hurt, you're gonna get hurt!!
Sorry.
Stop it, stop it.
Stop it.
—Good job!
—Good job, guys!
Well done!
This is the most tired
I've ever been.
That was intense.
The big shot's here!
It was worth it, though.
I'm exhausted.
The winner is...
Come on, man, give me a break.
I don't even have to say it, right?
—Cookie!
—Whoa!!
—Fuck yeah!!
—For the second time.
—Second time, right?
—Yeah, it's my second time.
—Well, well.
—Yeah!!
He was too good.
Alright!
His double takedown...
Yeah, he was great.
—That mario game was effective.
—Mario was just...
—It was too much.
—That was great.
I laughed enough for two whole months.
I'm glad to hear that!
—He destroyed us today.
—He totally did.
That was too much.
Especially with great laughs, right?
I wanted to watch everything, to be honest.
Right? Just watching was already hilarious.
You really wish you didn't get
disqualified for laughing, huh?
—Like a spectator.
—I wanted to laugh so bad.
Thank you very much!
Hell yeah!
—Good job!
—Good job out there!
Well yeah...
My brain was running at full speed today.
I couldn't stop for a single step.
That's what it felt like.
The moment I got the orange,
I felt pretty blown away, I guess.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper—
Maybe I lost my mind,
but I actually felt more at ease
after that happened.
—This is pretty bad!
—There we go!
Like, I was losing from the beginning.
So I kind of felt like
it wasn't a big deal anymore.
This is bad, this is bad!
No way, no way!
But I became incredibly self-conscious
for the past 20 minutes.
"If I get through this,
I might pull it off."
—Good job!
—Good job to you too!
I feel really tired
just from laughing today.
I was really crying for real.
It was insane.
I guess that they weren't laughing that much,
because everything was funny all the time.
That happens sometimes.
And Chance Oshiro with that guitar...
To be honest, I was underestimating him.
I thought he was out of place.
But it was hilarious.
Love, love.
It was love at first sight.
—Love, love.
—This guy's an idiot.
—I'm a Tokyo Boy.
—He's a total idiot.
And of course, I don't even have to talk about Cookie.
I could watch him forever, seriously.
I guess this time...
it might've been better than usual
because we got scolded by Amazon.
Right?
It made us pay attention.
Like we had to be a bit more
honest about our gags,
and it ended up being incredibly good.
You said they scolded you, so...
Did you ever feel like a lingering
aura or something?
Like some sort of mood?
To be honest, well, I...
I like to say that I...
left things behind.
I got over that already somehow.
Though I think there were some people who might've liked it.
So uh...
I think that...
And I guess we reached the limit
of what we can actually do.
So I think that I'd like you all
to be able to watch it.
Though it's rated like R60+. (EN: 20)