THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
Of course, they'll come with game plans.
But things don't always go as planned.
That's how it is on Documental.
Was I laughing?
When you look at a comedian's
offensive and defensive strengths,
I think you can see a strong correlation.
The funnier they are,
the easier they laugh.
Come up with one already!
I'm sure they'll bring ammunition,
but choosing when to use it
is another thing.
How much do you use at the start?
What if you wait for the right moment,
but it ends before you shoot?
Not like you have a machine gun
with an unlimited number of bullets.
It's about how you use your ammo.
And there's also the question
of who you target.
Choge choge passion
"A gum-like substance came out."
CONTESTANTS ELIMINATED SO FAR:
JIMMY ONISHI
-These cards are a bit unusual.
-Give one back.
I have three...
Tamura.
What? It definitely wasn't me!
Okay, I'll look.
-Okay?
-It's just an ordinary egg.
It's just an egg.
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
I haven't done anything yet.
Here we go.
Shall I do "PPAP"?
An over-exaggerated "PPAP." Shall I?
-Go for it!
-Here I go!
How does the regular version go?
The regular one. The regular one...
I have a urethra
Urethra pen
I have an anus
Anal pen!
Urethra pen!
Pen urethra anal pen!
How was that?
That's nothing like the original.
That was funny.
The pen doesn't go into the urethra.
Really? That wasn't it?
When you said "urethra"
you pointed at your anus.
You said it so cool. "Urethra."
I didn't say it like that.
You said it like you were so hot.
"Urethra."
That's not how I said it.
Right, Kano?
How did he say it?
"Don't use the urethra, dude."
I didn't end in "dude."
I never say "dude."
Junior...
What's this?
What?
-He's making quite a face, isn't he?
-He is.
-Do "Perfect Human" for us.
-"Perfect Human"?
Enough already!
-Get close to him.
-Hey.
Junior is really on the ropes.
-Please watch him.
-Leave me alone.
Na, ka, ta. Nakata
Na, ka, ta. Nakata...
I'm a per...
I'm a perfect human
We live in Tokyo
Na, ka, ta. Nakata
I'm a perfect...
human!
Good, good. He held out.
-Can you impersonate anyone?
-I can do Viking's Nishimura.
-Without exaggerating.
-Then do that.
Viking's Nishimura?
Coming back to school after so many years
sure brings back memories.
Nothing has changed.
It sure brings back memories.
Is Mr. Kotouge still here?
It's me! Nishimura! Nothing has changed!
You sounded just like him.
I can do Kotouge too.
You can? Really?
Teacher, I'm Nishimura. Remember me?
No, I don't.
I'm Nishimura. Don't you remember me?
I don't remember you.
Like that.
You're good at impressions.
I am good.
Otoko-ume?
Otoko-ume.
-Good impression.
-Your other one is better.
Zakoshi is amazing.
-Which one?
-Fist of the North Star.
The Famicom game Fist of the North Star.
There's a scene where he goes back
into the cave.
From the video game.
He went back.
Good thing I never saw the original.
He really hits the spot.
I'm defenseless against Zakoshi.
Who's this?
Last year, in the Kansai region alone,
I filmed TV shows
at more than 300 locations.
I did many at osteopathic
and chiropractic clinics.
I learned how to check how likely
people are to get a bunion.
Please, Jinnai.
Me? Sure, check me out.
-Bunions?
-You can tell?
If you get a bunion,
it can lead to an ingrown toenail.
That causes problems with how you walk,
and affects your total health.
I just need one foot.
Does it affect men, too?
Men can get it too.
Many men visit clinics
with this condition.
Put your right foot up here.
What can you find out?
Whether you're in danger
of getting a bunion.
All right.
Is Jinnai losing it?
He just scored a very high point.
You can't do that!
-That was the same as tickling.
-Yeah. You tickled me!
-No, it wasn't tickling.
-Is that allowed?
Wait a minute!
That was the same as tickling!
It was different from tickling.
Mr. Matsumoto, that was just tickling!
Well, I think
Yamauchi scored a huge point.
It was the same as tickling!
I think it was more about
"betraying expectations."
Now wait just a minute.
That was not fair.
It's impossible not to laugh.
He was licking all over...
You're kidding me, right?
Wait.
That's not right!
I laughed my head off,
but I couldn't help it!
-You're kidding me. Not yet.
-You laughed out loud.
-Not that! Not yet!
-Let's watch it.
-That was...
-Let me look. But I'm not sure.
-He tickled me!
-You laughed hard.
Was that just a yellow?
Having that done to you
would make anyone laugh!
Whether you're in danger
of getting a bunion.
All right.
There.
He was licking me.
He was pretty much smiling there already.
But that was tickling!
Tickling wasn't the objective.
-His tongue went crazy.
-He made him laugh.
-It wasn't tickling.
-It was the situation.
He was licking between my toes.
Oh, please.
He's getting one.
That's harsh.
That hurts.
You laughed.
I laughed?
I wouldn't say I laughed...
And afterwards you did this.
I didn't like that either.
But...
I didn't like the way you tried to hide.
Anyway, Yamauchi scored a big point there.
-I thought so.
-Thank you.
Let's go.
-I don't need a checkup.
-I'm okay.
-I'm okay, too.
-Tamura?
I already had surgery to fix
my ingrown toenail. I'm okay.
-You should check Jinnai's left foot, too.
-No. I'm fine.
I don't care if I get a bunion.
Takahashi,
your posture is raising a red flag.
You're right.
Let him check your left foot.
Doing the same thing to two people
is wrong.
I wouldn't say it's wrong.
You should let me check, just in case.
-Make him the last.
-But you know what he'll do.
So you'll be fine.
-I didn't know.
-Good point.
-Let me have a look. Before it's too late.
-If you didn't know, you'd probably laugh.
Yamauchi is serious.
He's serious.
Please. Either foot will do.
Your dominant one might be better.
-This is really...
-How does he do that?
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
I don't like this kind of...
Wow. How can they not laugh?
-This doesn't look good.
-What?
You're fine.
-He needs to lick that much?
-You really lick all over.
-That much?
-I was a bit worried at first.
Wow.
Sorry about that.
You're completely fine.
I'm sorry.
Yamauchi is amazing.
-What's wrong?
-My shoulder.
-It hurts?
-He had to fight it.
-It hurts.
-Are you okay?
-Huh?
-Maybe your other foot is causing it.
-It comes diagonally.
Let him check your left foot, too.
Just to make sure.
I don't think you'll find anything
in my garden.
-Let me check.
-He swallowed the foot whole.
That was poetic.
What?
How is it?
How is it, Doc?
Wait a minute.
And lastly...
-No way. What was that?
-I nearly lost it.
You can't do that.
Well...
Yamauchi was amazing.
That was too much.
Yeah, that was too much.
-It was a fierce battle.
-How do you all hold it in?
It wasn't just tickling.
He was trying to make me come.
-It was foreplay.
-That was amazing.
-After considering a number of things...
-What?
How is it, Doc?
Wait a minute.
And lastly...
-That did deserve a yellow.
-That's harsh.
I think Jinnai laughed, too.
-No, I didn't.
-He did.
No, I didn't. Are you serious?
Getting a red card like this
would be so wrong.
-Let's go.
-What's that?
-It's a tag.
-What does it say?
What is it?
"Yamauchi [Kamaitachi]
Chiropractor Costume Set."
Take it off.
So you borrowed it?
Who are you?
It's hot!
It was "Mister It's Hot."
You know him?
Zakoshisyoh keeps coming.
What's that?
I'm hooked on Instagram.
-You take photos with that?
-You can't.
-You can't post photos with that.
-Why not use a smartphone?
-This takes photos with character.
-So you develop the photos,
-then you shoot them with your phone?
-I upload them to PC.
-Do you take Instagram-worthy photos?
-Yes.
-What kind of photos?
-I post people, too.
May I? It's a great chance.
May I take you, Tamura?
Can you... That's good.
Please pose for the photo.
-Will "Cha!" do?
-That would be great!
Okay. Here we go.
Ready. Say cheese.
Okay!
Great. Can I have one more?
Can you take one step back?
Great. Say cheese.
Okay!
-You took yourself.
-I've seen him do that before.
-At a paid gig?
-It's part of his set.
-At an Aeon Mall.
-I've seen it, too.
-Right.
-I saw you do it at Aeon.
Do audiences laugh at that?
They do.
Sorry about my reaction.
I look up when I do "Cha!"
so I couldn't see you.
Hey there.
-He's short.
-So short.
Mr. Umemiya, you're so short.
Aren't you kind of short?
He's about 4'5".
I shrank.
Hey there.
Can people shrink that much?
He tap dances?
You're light-footed.
So light-footed.
With your hands in your pockets.
Do you think there's a chance
Mr. Umemiya might get a bunion?
He is so annoying.
So annoying.
Junior's defense is really weak
when it comes to Zakoshi.
-Is that the Sayama version of Tiger Mask?
-Yes.
It's his "Tiger Step."
He takes great care with his "Tiger Step"
when he passes that area.
He gets super careful there.
-I wonder why.
-Because there's delicate equipment there.
Because of the delicate equipment,
and because Junior's standing there.
He's super careful with his superiors.
What is he actually doing?
-He's such a straight guy.
-What's he doing?
He attaches his mic properly
even when he won't speak.
He's coming at me.
-He's so close.
-He only breathes through his nose.
I don't like this.
Only through his nose.
I think...
-Too close.
-He's onto you.
I'm fine, thanks.
Can you do a sobat kick?
I want to see one.
You kicked me.
It didn't hurt at all.
What a small kick and low jump.
So low.
He's still using his nose.
Only his nose, the whole time.
His mouth's shut.
He won't open his mouth.
See, he's nasal breathing.
Even though he moves so much.
It's really deep nasal breathing.
-He took a break.
-He's tired.
-But I don't know him.
-Me neither.
I don't know anything about Satoru Sayama.
I wonder what's under the mask.
Shall we rip it off?
Yeah, tear it off like
Kuniaki Kobayashi did.
It was just Sayama.
Ouch.
He's saying, "Ouch."
Takahashi! Takahashi!
You can have your mask back, Sayama.
Ouch, ouch.
Tamura, lie on the table.
Weren't you trying to do that to Jimmy?
No, no. You see...
-What do you want me to do?
-Put your head down here.
Like this?
You can still hear him breathing hard.
-Oh, it's oxygen?
-What's this?
Relax.
-I'm not sure what will happen.
-Okay.
It's Isojin, the medical gargle.
It didn't hurt at all?
It hurt a little.
Are you completely relaxed?
I am. Yes.
Maybe he's waiting for it.
-It's better if he doesn't expect it.
-Just relax completely?
Maybe the table's too soft to hurt.
-Maybe.
-Maybe it's too low.
I felt that in my nose.
That hurt my nose.
You recorded the whole thing?
What are you doing?
What was that?
I broke an egg.
My head was getting heavy,
so I put it down, but I broke an egg.
Oh, my.
Firstly, it was moved here.
Then it came over here.
Wow.
Is it my fault?
Was it me?
-Let's wipe it up.
-I guess we should clean this up.
Was it my fault?
Was it me?
Want to play "The Masters Card Game"?
-What's that?
-Sounds fun.
We have to say a phrase the masters
have said, or are likely to say.
When I flip the card,
whoever touches it first says the phrase.
-A sort of oogiri game.
-Do we start now?
Sure.
"I just blew my load!"
"Get undressed, Helen!"
"I only came in because nobody was here."
"Louis XIV, are you open today?"
What's that? A shop?
-His friend.
-His friend?
He asked Louis XIV his plans for the day.
The real Louis XIV? The actual guy?
Yes.
"My, my. Is this sweet Ruriko?"
You can't say that.
It's a banned phrase?
Why?
I think we're trying to avoid
the "My, my" bit.
Time for the next one?
-Yeah.
-Next.
-What's that?
-It must start with "O."
"Okay!"
"Outside there are too many parked cars!"
"Oversized vehicles, I love 'em."
He got me.
Who was that?
-Kano?
-What was that?
I didn't see it.
Kano?
Junior only just held on.
You were close.
I was.
He laughed first.
So close.
I wasn't able to see it clearly.
He clearly laughed.
-Didn't I hold it in?
-You laughed.
We could hear you laugh.
Let's look at his face.
I couldn't see it clearly.
The color of the card will change
depending on how hard you laughed.
He got me.
What was that?
He laughed like some
rich housewife in Shirokane.
Because they locked eyes.
Well, that deserves
an orange!
Yeah, an orange.
-That was a big one.
-How harsh!
Keep up the good work.
If you get hungry,
you can always order out.
I am hungry.
-How about sushi?
-From the fridge?
-Let's order it.
-Over there?
-Sushi is the easiest to eat.
-Yeah. I want sushi.
-Sushi sounds great.
-Finger food is better.
-They have so many varieties.
-They do!
Let's continue.
Order an assorted sushi platter.
How about this?
The 9,000 yen "Mutsuki" set.
Let's have that.
-Shall I call?
-Yeah, call them.
Nothing else?
Mommy?
Mommy, Mommy?
Mommy.
I did.
I truly loved Eiichiro Funakoshi!
Just order the Mutsuki set.
I thought I'd be with Eiichiro Funakoshi
until the day I died!
Leave her out of this.
But!
Eiichiro Funakoshi betrayed me!
He uses Viagra!
He has a penis sticker!
-It's Ms. Matsui.
-Kazuyo Matsui.
-Ms. Matsui, can you place our order?
-Sure.
-We'd like some sushi.
-Sushi? Okay.
-You're actually dialing.
-Yeah.
-What do I say?
-Mutsuki--
-Hello, this is Koi Sushi.
-Er, Mutsuki?
-Mutsuki?
-Yes. Two sets.
-Two?
-Thank you.
-Two 9,000-yen assorted sushi plates?
-Yes.
-Mommy--
-What is your address?
What? The address? The address is...
-Kinuta Studio.
Studio L1.
-L1?
-Yes.
Okay. May I have your name please?
It's Mommy.
Mommy.
-Mom...
-Mommy.
-Sorry?
Mr. Mommy?
Yes, Mommy.
Mommy.
-Got it.
-Mommy, Mommy.
-Okay.
-Mommy.
-To L1 Studio.
-Yes, please. Mommy--
Okay. Thank you very much.
Thank you, Mommy--
Sure. Thank you.
Mommy, Mommy.
Zakoshi is dangerous.
-That ended up like a prank call.
-Yeah.
No, no. She got the order. It will come.
Shall we play?
-Let's continue.
-Really?
Why not? Just until the food arrives.
-It'll take a while.
-Here goes.
-My turn?
-Kanpei really took me under his wing.
I think Kanpei's
a hard one to have fun with.
-He says crazy things as it is.
-Exactly.
You're right.
"Turn me upside down."
He says that.
"You were saying something a while ago.
What was it?"
"You were saying something."
"What did you say a while ago.?"
"You were saying something a while ago."
"Somebody's Night"
Eikoh, just blurt something out.
-Next card.
-It's a speed thing?
Okay.
"Don't put your arms...
around my waist."
That was a tough one.
That laugh came from someone
we didn't expect.
-It was a surprise.
-It knocked him flying.
Yamauchi is so tough.
I thought, "Is that the image he evokes?"
Because Eikoh doesn't know him.
Eikoh doesn't know much about
Master Kinshi.
That was really unexpected.
Akiyama.
Of course.
Let's take a look.
"Don't put your arms...
around my waist."
-Why?
-Exactly.
It started kicking in afterwards.
-I thought, "What on earth is he saying?"
-It wasn't funny at all.
I don't think it's funny myself.
What color should I make it?
He laughed pretty hard.
Yeah, he did laugh hard.
-He laughed out loud.
-It was pretty hard.
-That's harsh.
-Really?
Laughing out loud was a big factor.
-That's harsh.
-Many of us are on our last life now.
Let's go.
So far, I'd say Yamauchi is doing
quite well.
He's scored a lot of points
and he has no cards.
I think that's remarkable.
And Zakoshi is doing a great job.
This time Kobayashi is putting up
a good fight, too.
He has no cards either.
-Do you want to play a game?
-What?
-A game.
-You have one?
What kind of game?
It goes like this.
There's a comedian in Osaka
named Biyori Moriya.
He came up with it.
It's really popular backstage
at all the theaters.
It's called "Fartmonica."
You hold a harmonica in your mouth,
then your opponent gives you a butt poke.
If the Fartmonica makes a sound, you lose.
-You can't exhale?
-If you do, you lose.
If the poke goes too deep,
wouldn't that be impossible?
Even if it goes deep,
you have to hold your breath.
-Can you breathe through your nose?
-That wouldn't make a sound.
He means, are we allowed
to breathe through our noses?
Of course.
-Or you'd die.
-Just don't make a sound.
Try it.
Go first, Yamaue. Tamura can--
It's Yamauchi.
Yamauchi.
-You called him "Yamaue."
-It's "Yamauchi."
We've been here for two hours now.
Maybe he got confused with
my partner "Hamaie."
I get it.
That makes sense.
Do you often confuse names?
Like when you're at home?
-You never say "Norika" by mistake?
-I'd never do that.
-You don't?
-I've never done that. Not at home.
-Who goes first? Yamauchi?
-Yeah, Yamauchi.
Will I be the one who gets poked?
-Can I leave my pants on?
-This sounds scary.
Okay, I'll show you how it's done.
I've done it before.
For starters. As a guide.
This is how you endure it.
Make sure you don't poke a bone.
You'll get hurt.
Aim right here.
-Right here.
-Okay. Are you ready?
Wait a minute.
-If I make a sound, I lose.
-Right.
Ready?
I'm gonna kill you!
That was a surprise.
Now say your "Cha!" gag.
I'm not that type of guy.
Sorry. I messed up.
But "I'm gonna kill you" was out of line.
I could forgive something like a kick,
but he looked me in the eye and said,
"I'm gonna kill you."
-I think he misunderstood something.
-It was an honest mistake.
It's his first time.
-Sorry.
-Try again.
Everyone's doing such a great job.
Here I go.
I'll smash you to death!
He's serious.
He really wants to do it.
Maybe something happened.
Did he buy your virtual currency?
Can't we play the Fartmonica game?
How does the Fartmonica go again?
You put this in your mouth,
you get a butt poke,
and you try not to let out a sound.
Get it?
Shall I do an over-exaggerated Harumafuji?
Why?
Dosukoi!
Karaoke dosukoi!
It wasn't that exaggerated.
Maybe that wasn't an exaggeration.
He may have hit him even harder.
That was funny.
So funny.
Ready?
I'm really going to do it.
This is the Fartmonica.
Ready?
Takahashi and Yamauchi!
Who laughed?
Who was it?
-That hurt!
-It wasn't me!
-You both laughed at the same time.
-I swear Yamauchi laughed first!
Absolutely!
-You're right.
-There were several at once.
This could be a double penalty.
That was nasty, Zakoshi.
What's with you?
It hurt!
Let the sound out!
That required high-level techniques.
It really hurt!
Let's look at Takahashi first.
He's still holding out here.
He's laughing.
Now let's look at Yamauchi.
He's already smiling.
Is it a smile...
He totally laughed.
It's a double penalty.
Him and Takahashi?
Takahashi gets this.
Good, good.
Is this Yamauchi's first card?
It's my first, yes.
It may be your first,
but I have to give you this.
You burst into laughter.
That's harsh.
I think I got a big point.
-You did.
-Right?
Right? You're supposed to blow it hard...
Anything else?
-Who's that?
-I heard a knock.
-Come in.
-It arrived.
Oh, Mommy.
Hello.
-Mommy?
-Thank you.
That looks delicious.
Thank you very much.
Thanks.
-The order wasn't too weird?
-It was fine.
Thank you.
May we have your name?
-I'm Tabuchi.
-Mr. Tabuchi?
You're not Mommy, are you?
No, I'm not.
What's in your fanny pack?
-Things I need to make deliveries.
-Like change?
Change and things like that.
No penis stickers?
Right.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
It looks delicious!
There's soy sauce.
It's exquisite.
It's amazing.
Who wants to play "Russian Isojin"?
-Russian Roulette with medical gargle?
-No way.
-Will the smell give it away?
-Put some in a dish.
How would it work? We dip sushi in it?
If they're the same color...
-It's the same!
-They'll use it instead of soy sauce.
-This is the soy sauce.
-You can't tell!
The color is a little...
Isojin is a bit paler.
What if you mix it with soy sauce?
Eikoh, why don't you try this?
Be the guinea pig.
Make an Isojin version of your gag.
-Yeah, it will work.
-"Iso-jin."
Iso-jin!
-It works.
-Pretty good.
Let's eat!
I'll have tuna belly first.
You should all try this.
-Looks delicious.
-It's super good.
The tuna belly's fat
should balance it out.
Yeah, I think so.
Looks yummy.
I'm going for it.
He dipped the rice, too.
What's wrong?
What is it?
He's scary.
-Is it that bad?
-Really?
That looks bad.
-Something black came out.
-What is that?
-What's that black stuff?
-What is this?
-It made a chemical reaction?
-It turned black!
-Creepy!
-So creepy!
-Why did it turn black?
-Show us.
The tuna had a chemical reaction.
It's black!
It's poison.
-How did it taste?
-Delicious.
It was delicious?
How can it be delicious?
It's a grotesque color.
-It's pitch black!
-For real?
-It's kind of purple.
-They held on.
Let's decide who goes next.
-Not after seeing that.
-For real?
-Not after that.
-No way!
Let's see what happens with sea urchin.
Every time I breathe through my nose,
I smell Isojin and fat.
Do they react with each other?
Maybe it's the fat.
Maybe that reacted to the Isojin.
-How did it taste?
-Delicious.
It was delicious?
Someone give it a try.
-How about the egg?
-The egg.
-E-G-G.
-Sounds safe.
-Easy?
-E-G-G and easy.
Easy? Then give it a try.
Huh?
-It's easy, right?
-Go for it.
-It's just the egg.
-There's no rice?
-But with Isojin?
-I know.
There's no rice underneath.
Oh, no.
Only egg. Wow, it turned red.
It's already reacting!
-Chemistry turned it red.
-It's already reacting, Shigeo!
Eat it!
Who said that?
Here it comes.
-This is not good.
-It slowly gets worse.
It's blackish.
-I told you.
-It really tastes gross.
That was plain egg.
It was yellow.
There was no chemical reaction.
How was the taste?
-Super delicious.
-Delicious?
You were waiting for that.
-It was written all over your face.
-Before the deed.
-What a turn off.
-It started way back.
But there was no chemical reaction.
-It didn't turn black.
-All thanks to the tuna.
Maybe it was Eikoh's mouth that caused it?
Eikoh makes it black.
It can't be.
Do you excrete ink or something?
But it really was purple...
Did you fart?
Was that you?
Yes.
That's how you timed it?
How honest of you.
So...
Do you know who this belongs to?
-Is it a school uniform?
-No, it's a suit.
-Is that Dr. Hattori's?
-It is.
-That Hattori?
-The chef.
How did you get it?
Why don't we see who looks best in this?
I think that'll be me.
Yeah, it might suit him.
Having a strong build helps.
Size-wise, it's me.
I think so too.
-Is he still wearing the pink vibrator?
-Yeah, the whole time.
I bet he's smirking about it.
Turning it on and off.
-He turns it on and off?
-Probably.
He's trying to look like Hattori.
How's the food?
Dr. Hattori's celebrating the New Year.
How festive.
Happy New Year.
-Happy New Year.
Yamauchi goes next.
-Okay.
-Yamauchi?
He should look good in it.
Yeah, maybe.
This sushi's good.
What are you drinking?
Breast milk.
No, seriously.
Calpis.
-He has tattoos.
-Dr. Hattori?
Yes.
-Are you really Dr. Hattori?
-Yes.
He had tattoos like that?
You have tattoos?
Yeah.
The culinary school president?
-The chef?
-Yeah.
Did you have a rough past?
In the past.
How about your back?
That's impressive!
-A koi.
-Is that a koi?
You can cook it.
Oh, a koi dish.
Your front has nothing to do with cooking.
It's a Prajna.
They're spread apart. Each one's separate.
Because I got them one by one.
From now on I'm always going to
imagine him without clothes.
Yeah, you're right.
I've been getting a tattoo
for each memory.
See this one?
It's when I crushed
all the teams in Osaka.
Teams?
-Motorcycle gangs. Crews.
-He must've been a member.
When did you get your back done?
When I opened the culinary school.
-As a memento?
-As a memento.
How about the one on your right chest?
This is the only one...
I got against my will.
Who did it?
Kawa...
Kawagoe.
The French cuisine chef?
Chef Kawagoe?
You had a falling out?
He came to your school once.
When he did, he did this to me.
He did that to you?
Sounds scary.
By force?
I'd say it was forceful.
When a bunch of French chefs got together.
Are French chefs that dangerous?
Be careful of French chefs.
Do you often have arguments among chefs?
No, they're not.
Don't you cook anymore?
I no longer cook at all.
I haven't for about 12 years.
Not at all?
He is so annoying.
Thank you.
I haven't eaten any.
I have a question.
What do you do with your pubic hair?
-What do we do?
-Nothing.
You leave it on, right?
Most of the world views that
as being super unclean.
-I heard.
-Why?
Only Asians leave it on.
I hear only Japanese people
leave it on these days.
What do you do?
Actually...
I went all the way.
-When?
-What the heck?
So...
Wanna try it?
Seiji does that too.
It's called a Brazilian wax.
He showed me. It was super clean.
-Right? It works.
-You could show this on TV.
-It's super smooth.
-But your skin's super rough.
I have a skin rash.
I've only just had it done.
-It's still rough.
-Should we connect the dots?
I think they might form a picture.
These dots?
Give me a pen.
Will you draw it for me?
-Maybe it's a secret message.
-Looks promising.
-I have MA, too.
-What's "MA"?
-"M"?
-"MA." Metal Allergy.
From your belt?
This looks awful.
It's because I have MA.
Don't you smoke anymore, Zakoshi?
I quit.
Why fart now?
That sounded like something else came out.
This is amazing.
-What?
-Let's all fart.
Can you see something?
Something has appeared.
Seriously.
-I just connected the dots.
-No faking?
No faking.
He connected all the dots.
Right? I seriously did.
-Suneo?
-It looks like Suneo.
I had Suneo on my belly.
It appeared naturally?
Something might be on your bellies too.
I keep my hair short, actually.
-You do?
-But I don't shave.
I brought some Brazilian wax.
But mine's short.
How do you do it?
Does it hurt?
-Mine's like...
-You cut it?
-I do.
-Why?
See?
-It's short.
-And thin.
It is.
Or we could do your armpits.
I keep mine short.
That's perfect.
It doesn't work if it's too long.
I'm well-groomed.
I can do this. Done it myself.
-It doesn't grow back for a while?
-That's right.
That sounds scary.
But yours is growing. How come?
It still grows, but there's less hair.
-That's scary.
-Scary indeed.
What is that?
-It looks like lube.
-I swear this takes hair off perfectly.
-You'll be moved.
-Yeah, it is like lube.
It comes right off?
Yes.
So scary.
It's just like mizuame candy.
That looks thick.
Is it supposed to be that thick?
It's so thick.
What do you do with that?
That must be enough.
Nori-ka.
-"Norika"?
-No, no.
You clearly said, "Norika."
-I meant, "Is that nori glue?"
-You still like her?
It reminded you of her?
Why would this remind me of her?
How do you remove it?
You put that much on?
What is this?
What a well-behaved penis.
It's a clever penis.
It's like mizuame...
What was that?
I'd totally forgotten about it.
I was flattered that he called
my penis well-behaved.
-You laughed so heartily.
-That was a hearty laugh.
Really.
I was so happy he called
my penis well-behaved.
That was such a well-mannered laugh.
I was just happy.
So, Kobayashi...
-It's his first card?
-It is.
That was a big laugh.
It was.
It can't be!
-No, it's not.
-You scared me!
But I get an orange?
I guess that deserved orange.
Yes. That was...
He laughed just like normal.
He got an orange.
But more importantly,
before that happened, there was Jinnai...
You said, "Norika."
-What a goof up.
-A total goof up.
That was awful of me.
-I want to give you a card for that.
-Wait!
-What did I say?
-"Norika..."
I said "Nori-ka" as in "Is that glue?"
-I was shocked.
-Sorry for that.
I almost lost it myself.
You put that much on?
What is this?
What a well-behaved penis.
What was that?
You looked so smug.
What a tender smile!
How can I put it?
It was nice to be praised.
You felt proud, right?
I took it as a compliment.
Are we all on our last chance?
-I am.
-Me too.
I've got one. I'm still on yellow.
Many are still on yellow.
-Except for Zakoshi.
-I have none.
Zero.
He has no cards
and he's scored some big points.
I have zero cards.
-It's ready?
-He can take it off?
It's ready.
It's gonna hurt?
It doesn't look good.
We left it on too long.
Let's go.
I'm in trouble? Then hurry up.
-Why don't you make it a "Harmonica Wax"?
-Good idea.
-With the Fartmonica.
-The Fartmonica.
Is he okay?
That looks painful.
Will he be okay?
-Won't that rip his skin?
-How does it work?
-Is this safe?
-He has a lot of hair.
This is scary!
Ready?
Who was that?
-It had to be Tamura.
-Definitely Tamura!
-That had to hurt.
-He's in pain.
-That hurts real bad.
-Are you okay?
That hurt!
What did you do to me?
That looked so painful.
Who laughed?
-That was the worst.
-Tamura has to take care of him.
-Look at it hanging.
-That really hurt.
-That hurt bad.
-No way.
What happened?
He did his bit and laughed at it,
all by himself.
This could end up a red card.
That's right.
-At the moment...
-This can't be true!
He has a yellow card.
We'll see if he gets away with an orange,
or if he goes straight to red.
-Let's take a look.
-But that was...
Why did I even start that?
No laugh, right?
-I'm not laughing!
-Yes, you are!
You were totally laughing!
He completely was.
He was smiling before that, too.
That harmonica.
You looked like Takuzo Kawatani.
That chin.
But you know what?
With it looking so funny,
and sounding so funny,
I totally lost track of
why I was even doing all this.
Red!
He got it!
For real?
-What happens now?
-That deserved it.
It's like mizuame.
So, guys, you need to do it for him again.
-Do what?
-We don't know how.
You stick this sheet on.
And then...
Yank it hard.
-You'd better lie down.
-No way. I'm scared.
-He should lie down.
-But look at you.
You have no choice now.
Someone needs to take over.
There are so many bits I didn't get to do.
You thought I had none left?
Then why did you invite me?
That was so quick. Was I the second one?
Yes.
I totally did it to myself.
I should've let someone else do it.
Kobayashi's penis had been
so well-behaved up to that point.
But when I yanked the sheet,
it popped out.
I really wanted to stay a little longer.
Just a little longer.
Hey, somebody.
Would any of you happen to have
a charger cable for this PSP?
Did they date before having intercourse?
Or did they have intercourse, then date?
Zombie Time!
Zombie?
The World Cup.