THIS PROGRAM IS THE RECORD
OF A "BATTLE" AMONGST COMEDIANS.
IN ORDER TO PRESERVE QUALITY,
IT IS MOSTLY UNEDITED.
AS SUCH, VIEWERS MAY ENCOUNTER
EXPLICIT CONTENT.
They might have a strong desire
to win 10 million yen.
Or maybe they just don't want
to lose their one million yen.
I'm sure each participant
has his own motivation.
For someone like Toro Salmon's Kubota,
one million yen must have been
a lot of money to prepare.
For well-known comedians like Fujimoto,
he's probably not as concerned about money
as he once was.
I think that will be a big factor.
-You don't need 10 million yen, Fujimoto.
-Yes, I do!
-Don't lie.
-That has nothing to do with this.
You already have enough.
You can never have enough money.
And this is no small change.
It's 10 million yen.
-It's a lot.
-It's too much.
Are you getting philosophical?
I'm off to the bathroom.
It's 10 million.
Ten million is a lot.
This may be the difference.
And I have a family.
-You do.
-But your wife earns a lot of money too.
-You say so yourself.
-But--
"My wife earns big."
A man has his pride.
You're always talking about
how shockingly large her salary is.
When you compare it to Yoshimoto's rate.
Right? Only compared to Yoshimoto.
You can never have enough money.
Who knows what will happen in the future?
Name a comedian
who's still popular in his fifties.
Are there any?
In their fifties, or sixties...
There aren't many.
How about the guy who always says,
"How tasty"?
-Is Ishizuka that old?
-Around 50, I think.
But I heard that when he does
those gourmet reports,
he leaves a lot of food.
-Why say that?
-He only takes two bites.
He laughed!
Right?
That was... All I did was cough.
Should we review the video?
All I did was cough.
You have to give me a break on that one.
-The chef said he hardly touched the meal.
-Don't be so disrespectful to Ishizuka.
But he said--
Fujimoto. Orange.
You have no more chances.
We all heard the "Hmph!"
You laughed from your belly.
Anthony has a yellow card.
-And these two still have no cards.
-None.
-I let my guard down.
-You did.
Let's focus!
That gets a card?
Kawahara, do you ever laugh?
I've never seen you smile.
-Neither have I.
-Never.
-Don't you ever laugh?
-Of course I do.
What made you laugh the hardest?
The thing made me laugh the hardest was
the TV show Gaki no Tsukai.
That's a funny show.
-Yes.
-Of course it's funny.
That's about it.
To make others laugh,
without laughing yourself...
I've never used my brain like that before.
Of course, I want to make them laugh,
so I'll seize every opportunity.
How do you laugh?
Show me your smile.
But then I'd lose.
You'd still be in the game
even if you got a yellow card.
Just once, then.
-You will?
-Are you sure?
I won't get a red card, right?
-No.
-Yellow first, right?
Really?
If you say so.
-Well, that's quite manly of you.
-Wow.
-He's a real man.
-Sure is.
Use this to hide your face,
then flash it at us.
-Ready?
-Wait! He'll just make a funny face.
He'll make us laugh.
Well, it's a game of funny faces.
Wait. You guys watch, too.
-Of course.
-We're watching.
Ready?
Which of them was it?
-Who was it?
-Not me! It has to be him!
Don't laugh out loud!
He laughed right before the siren.
No, I didn't. I laughed after the siren.
Yellow card.
-Fujimoto laughed after the siren.
-See?
-That was close.
-You were on the edge.
Everyone could've laughed just now.
There was the possibility.
That's what I was aiming for.
That was so close.
I thought he wouldn't make a face at all.
I thought so, too.
But he gave us a full on laugh.
It was so unlike him.
You're scary.
That was scary.
I'm hungry.
-They have ramen.
-I want some, too.
-You want ramen?
-Yeah!
That's just what I wanted.
Just what you wanted?
"Just what I wanted."
You laughed.
Didn't he laugh?
-He laughed as he did an impression.
-Right?
All I said is that it was
"Just what I wanted."
Who's that supposed to be?
Can I boil some sausages?
-Will you cook something?
-I'll just boil them.
-Cook us something.
-Something proper.
-You're not eating, Kawahara?
-No.
-Why not?
-I'm not hungry.
-He's full because he had wine.
-That's right.
I had a bit of wine.
There's still some left.
This is good!
-That must be good.
-It's good.
I bet it is.
Delicious.
You don't need to stare at me.
But it's really good.
You say everything is good.
No, I don't.
When we did that sausage gig together,
you said they were so good,
you ate about 20 of them.
We did a sausage gig.
-Twenty sausages?
-Yes, 20 sausages.
That many?
Can you stop saying "sausage gig"?
But it was a sausage gig.
-I've never heard of a "sausage gig."
-It was a gig for a sausage company.
That was good.
-Well...
-Delicious.
Kubota, doesn't this remind you
of when we were neighbors?
In Kita-ikebukuro.
It's a town most people don't know.
People know it!
Why are my noodles still uncooked?
Just leave it for a while longer.
-It's been over three minutes.
-You don't say?
What kind of response is that?
-You're going to fry them?
-It's tastier.
-Better than boiling, right?
-I want one.
Right... What?
-You said you weren't hungry.
-You did.
If it's sausages, I want one, too.
Damn.
He's trying to pick a fight.
No, I'm not.
You said you wouldn't eat.
That looks so good.
My noodles are still uncooked.
What is this?
This is so annoying.
They're so stiff.
They're stiff.
Why?
It's been five minutes!
Are the noodles too thick?
Wasn't the water boiled?
But it tastes great!
They're stiff but great!
-The aftertaste is awful!
-Shut up!
I don't know how to cut these.
These look good. Look.
-These must be delicious.
-Whoa!
Must be good.
You found the chopsticks.
That looks good.
I didn't know instant noodles
could be this good.
Yum.
Wow.
-That one doesn't work.
-Yeah, it won't turn on.
It doesn't turn on. Use this one.
Whoa.
-You're gonna make pasta?
-Yes.
Why?
Yummy.
Want some?
Well, if it tastes good.
-Did you work in a restaurant?
-No.
What's your best pasta dish?
It's an original recipe.
-How old were you?
-I was in kindergarten.
I grew up fast.
Hm?
Who laughed?
Who was it?
No idea.
Anthony.
You smiled, right?
I thought I held it back.
He was eating and smiling
like a normal dinner.
How old were you?
I was in kindergarten.
I grew up fast.
You seemed to be having fun.
THE JUDGING IS STRICTER
NOW THAT HALF ARE GONE
Orange, right?
Okay.
-I'll be stricter from here on out.
-Okay.
Fujimoto and Anthony have orange cards.
He's on yellow.
Yes.
He's still clear.
-No cards yet?
-I'm done for.
-Does he really not have a card?
-It's true.
-You won't win if you're not aggressive.
-Okay!
Kubota hasn't smiled yet.
I think it would be nice
if everyone knew me better.
So, would you mind
looking at some of my old photos?
My plan?
I guess, above all,
my looks are my strength.
As you can see,
I'll probably be the only one
of a difference race.
So, I want to use that to my advantage.
-When were the photos taken?
-Back in my early schooldays.
My first day of grade school.
-Old photos of you?
-Yes, please take a look.
My graduation from grade school.
Oh, my.
This is my dad.
The American one.
-Fujimoto, please take a look.
-Who's this?
That is my American dad.
Victor.
Professor Victor?
He's Victor.
Look at Victor.
-Show him this one, too.
-Who's this?
-It's Victor--
-Wait.
Kawahara should take a look first.
How is it?
Here.
Who was it?
-Who was it?
-I didn't laugh.
I did not laugh.
Hold on.
Kawahara.
Kawahara?
You smiled, right?
You smiled just like you normally would
when looking at a graduation photo.
Kawahara should take a look first.
How is it?
You smiled.
I was close, too.
If I'd seen one more,
I would have been gone.
He asked you to look at his photos,
but Fujimoto went to smoke in the kitchen.
-I don't think that was right.
-I agree.
-You tried to escape.
-Sorry.
-You have to look properly.
-Right.
But these photos are too much.
-They're too much.
-Hold on.
Well, they were quite a trap.
Trap? Take a look at this!
I don't think it's nice to call someone's
childhood photo a trap, by the way.
-Show him the other photo.
-It's there.
-Show it again.
-I'm scared.
Please take a look.
I will, but...
Don't bring it to me.
Why are you like that?
Look at his father for him.
Don't make it sound like he's dead.
He is dead.
Sorry.
He died when I was two.
What is Victor's...
What's his full name?
I don't know. All I know is "Victor."
Sorry, I don't know.
Please, take a look.
You've had your eyes closed
the whole time.
What was his job?
Professional boxer.
-How many matches did he win?
-He was ranked fourth in the world.
He's damn strong.
How did he pass away?
Cut it out.
-But...
-Stop asking questions.
-I'm curious.
-You're just feeding my imagination.
Please. I won't ask anything else.
It was gout.
-Boxers shouldn't get gout.
-He got it after he quit boxing.
He ate a lot on the rebound.
You two, take a look.
Why do I have to go first?
-Didn't Kawahara see it?
-I did. That's why--
-No, you didn't.
-That's why I got a card.
-Don't lie.
-He got a card for it.
-I got a card for it.
-That's right.
-Let's decide who'll see it first.
-By playing rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors.
No way.
He's so dark, you can't even see him.
He's dissolved into the background.
He laughed.
That was you, right?
It wasn't me.
It wasn't me!
That wasn't me!
I held it back.
-It was in your voice.
-It's not me!
-That was Fujimoto.
-No, it was Kubota.
No, I laughed after the red light.
-Kubota.
-Me?
-You laughed.
-You did.
-Your voice was...
-Exactly!
-It was trembling.
-You were trembling!
-You laughed.
-You trembled.
Your voice was trembling.
-It was me?
-That voice was funny.
I told you I'd be more strict.
But that battle was fierce.
I think you're all amazing
for not laughing at gout.
I definitely would've laughed.
I was biting my tongue.
There's only about one hour left,
so I'm going to be even more strict.
Let's go.
-Did Fujimoto see the photos?
-Not yet.
-Enough already.
-He hasn't seen two of them.
-I saw them.
-Two photos is a serious offense.
Kawahara has one to go, too.
I'll laugh even if it's not funny.
-Kawahara hasn't seen it.
-That's right. Don't lie now.
-I saw it.
-I want everyone to see.
-Did you really see it?
-Yes.
You're not looking at it.
You can't separate him
from the background.
You're laughing, Fujimoto.
He must have been healthy back then.
He's so sly. He's setting them up.
He was still a boxer in that photo, right?
No, he'd already retired by the time
I was born.
So he was still boxing, right?
No, he was retired by the time I was born.
Sorry for that.
You're so sneaky,
bringing those photos out at the end.
This is my family now.
Me, my younger brother...
Terumi and Masumi.
Did he have to wear a white shirt?
Enough with the photos!
I told you I'm not going to laugh
at your childhood photos.
This is me during a physical.
My nickname was "Rapist."
-Why such a nickname?
-I don't know. It was given to me.
It's because you look like a rapist.
You're scary.
Why are you first in line
when you're the biggest?
The biggest should be in the back.
How tall was the kid behind you?
Probably about 1.2 meters.
I was already 1.76 meters tall at age 10.
That's scary.
You should've played sports.
-I did.
-What sport?
Dodgebee.
What the hell is that? Not dodgeball?
It's dodgeball using a Frisbee.
Play a more popular sport!
You have the face for it.
What the hell is dodgebee?
-Dodgebee is a safe sport.
-How do you lose in dodgebee?
-When you get hit.
-When what hits you?
You use a Frisbee instead of a ball
in dodgebee.
Dodgebee is... A moth landed on my arm!
What the hell?
Is it a sign to stop talking?
It stinks!
It came because you stink.
It looks like I have a tattoo.
-It's because you stink.
-Then it should be in my armpit.
It came because your armpit stinks.
If so, it wouldn't stop here.
Your whole life is like a moth.
Who are you calling a moth?
Are you talking to me, or the moth?
Which one?
Your armpit.
My armpit?
You're an armpit moth.
What is an armpit moth?
So I'm an insect?
You are like an insect.
Then spray me with pesticide.
I won't die. Probably.
Try spraying me.
What is this?
Wow.
Why is it still on me?
-Still there?
-It won't--
Damn it!
Now the moth's sitting on my pants.
You're overcooking the pasta.
Look!
It looks like a logo.
Looks fine to me.
There's less than an hour left.
-What should we do?
-Any ideas?
-We have to fight.
-Yeah, let's fight.
Don't you agree?
Yeah...
Yeah
Tears flow endlessly
Yeah, oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah. Tears flow endlessly
You're good at rapping, right?
He is. He's really good at rapping.
-Why don't you two do it together?
-But I can't rap.
You do it.
-You look like you can.
-I can't! That's just my looks.
Don't judge a book by its cover.
I can't rap!
-I can't rap.
-You try, Fujimoto.
-You haven't done anything!
-What's going on?
-You give orders, but do nothing yourself.
-So far, he hasn't done anything.
-Neither have you.
-Do something.
-I did that knife joke.
That's the only thing.
You haven't done the knife.
Does everyone have to do it?
You don't have to,
but you haven't done anything.
I can do it, but it won't be funny.
It's not funny at all.
Not funny at all.
-Because you're not wearing the uniform.
-That's not the problem.
This prop isn't funny.
This just doesn't work.
-You forgot about the pasta.
-It's yours!
Oh, yeah.
I'm confused, too.
If you're going to eat, cook it properly.
Why did you boil it? Don't waste it.
This is such a waste.
How firm do you want the pasta?
But you've had it going for so long...
I'll check the firmness.
It's definitely too soft. Isn't that hot?
What are you doing?
Aren't there any ingredients?
You should add something to it.
You don't have to...
You don't have to eat it.
I'm checking the firmness!
You only need to try one.
Just one.
Hey.
He's gone crazy.
You're going crazy.
-Stop him, Anthony.
-Why me? I don't want to. He's crazy.
Don't say that. He's your senior.
Why do you make me do everything?
Because you're the youngest.
That doesn't matter.
Kawahara, stop it. What are you doing?
I can't watch this anymore.
Kawahara.
He's having a real feast.
Stop him.
Kawahara.
Thirty minutes to go.
Not much time left.
What's up?
What's he doing?
That's promising.
Go for it.
Keep going.
Where's he going with this?
You hit me.
You actually hit me.
Wait a minute.
That was not fair.
What happened?
No way.
No way!
Fujimoto, red card.
You laughed.
-He got me.
-You stole his idea, then laughed at it.
You're out.
We don't have much time.
When you get punched that much,
you can't help but laugh.
I thought, "What the hell am I doing?"
So, Kawahara's plan succeeded.
I realized nobody had
any more cards to play.
We were all feeling each other out,
wondering who would do what.
How frustrating.
Will we get a winner?
It would be nice if we do.
Yeah...
It is an experiment.
-We're on.
-We are.
Good work.
Nice, Kawahara.
It might be best to keep pushing that.
That may be the best strategy.
And where's Anthony?
The drum-drum man
The drum-drum man...
Go for it.
Go, go!
It's a fighting game.
A fighting game.
Anybody laugh?
Ouch!
Nobody's laughing? No laughs?
That one hurt.
Kubota's on the move. Okay!
Kubota's making a move.
There are still 16 minutes left.
That's enough time.
Okay.
He's filling it up with pasta.
He's putting the noodles in like a pro.
So, what's Kubota going to do?
What will he do now?
I admit defeat!
Keep at it.
Poop.
Poo...
I just broke all the toes
on my right foot.
I'm sleepy!
Why do your usual routine?
Who would do a normal set here?
What are you doing?
Could you tie this for me?
-Kawahara, tie it for him.
-Please.
That's too tight!
If I twist it, my dick will show.
Now I have two.
Oh, my. Which is the real one?
Which is the real one?
You? Oh, this is the real one.
I'm the real one.
-You are?
-Yes.
-I'm the real one.
-Which is it?
It's me.
-Which one?
-I'm the real one.
I'm the...
-I'm sleepy.
-I'm sleepy!
I'm sleepy.
Okay.
This is my last resort.
What is it?
-Sorry.
-What is it?
Forgive me.
This is going to be my final act.
Sorry.
Please forgive me.
Forgive me.
Mom and Dad, please forgive me.
Don't do it!
For 10 million yen,
I'm going to...
die.
If you have any questions, ask me now.
What? How... Will you die?
No!
I'm going to poop standing up!
Seriously?
-This is not good.
-Don't do it.
-No way!
-Poop is not the answer.
Poop is wrong.
It's not funny.
-Seriously?
-Poop is not funny.
I always laughed at poop.
That's why I became a comedian!
Don't poop. Do a gag.
A joke will do.
Okay, I'll write it with poop!
I'll write "Amazon" here with poop!
Not funny.
Damn, I'm only getting farts.
-Only farts.
-I won't laugh at poop!
But think about it.
You became a comedian to have fun
and get rich, right?
One poop can earn you 10 million yen!
But I won't laugh.
Poop is not going to make me laugh!
No pooping!
Wear a mask!
I've had enough of masks!
They're better than poop!
Seven minutes left.
We just have to fight.
Let's do something. Shall we use props?
Prop jokes?
Should we do that?
Good morning, sir!
Who are you?
I'm Kakefu.
You grew.
You're bigger now.
Kakefu wears pants.
I'm Mr. Tigers, Masayuki Kakefu!
But your crotch is a Panther.
Huh?
Your top says you're a Tiger.
What do your pants say?
I'm a Panther.
No way.
This is not good.
Not good at all.
Go for it!
We have to find a winner.
We're out of props.
Should we all do something together?
-Let's give it a try.
-Yeah.
Otherwise...
No point thinking.
What should we do?
What if we all go home with nothing?
We have to do something.
Should we try an impression?
Let's all imitate the same person
and see who's best, okay?
Who should it be?
-Takuya Kimura?
-How about Croket?
-The king of impressions?
-I don't know about Croket.
Croket is the one who does
the impressions.
-I think Kimura's okay.
-Okay.
-Who goes first?
-Kawahara.
-Me first?
-Yes.
So, is this is a serious impression?
Of course.
"Wait up!"
"Hey."
"Wait up, Croket."
What kind of scene is that?
Is Kimura chasing Croket?
Anthony.
"Wait up!"
Why does he have an accent?
Why the accent?
Your turn, Kubota.
"Wait up!"
You act like you're the best,
but you're hopeless.
Six hours and still no winner.
Ten seconds...
Eight, seven, six...
five, four, three...
TIME UP
(SIX HOURS HAVE PASSED)
It's over...
This sure is difficult.
It's really hard.
Good job.
-Thank you.
I think we've all had enough.
Should we talk in the other room?
-Okay.
The other room?
Oh, because we can't laugh in here.
Are we allowed to laugh now?
I guess it's fine now.
Whoa!
-This is amazing!
-Incredible!
-What is this place?
-I've seen this at a casino.
What is this place?
Six hours, but no winner.
IF A SOLO WINNER IS NOT DETERMINED,
NO ONE GETS 10 MILLION YEN
I guess there's always next time.
-How frustrating.
-That was...
-There should be a way to win.
-What were we lacking?
It just shows how hard it is
to narrow it down to one.
The fact we couldn't narrow it down
is part of the documentary, too.
If it was me, at that stage,
I would've pooped.
I punched my guts so many times,
but nothing came out.
I tried, but all I could do was fart.
And even then, they were silent.
But if you had pooped,
you would've got a red card.
If only they'd given us one more minute,
I would've won.
Thank you.
Is this the way?
I really should have pooped.
But it didn't come out.
Sorry for contaminating
your eyes and ears.
Hope to see you again.