THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
What kind of comedians do you think
are best suited to win Documental?
I think the answer to that question
will become a lot clearer this season.
I wasn't able to reach
a definite conclusion last season.
I'm still not sure, to be honest.
This is bad. Bad. Bad. Bad.
A monster has arrived.
Unfortunately, the more resourceful
comedians all have one thing in common.
They laugh easily.
This is a surprise.
Don't you all laugh too easily?
-He's right.
-How true. I'm a laugher.
I laugh so easily.
They have the same problem as boxers do.
Whenever they make an attack,
their guard drops.
The more moves they make,
the more they expose themselves to attack.
But if you don't mount an attack,
you won't land a punch.
That's the dilemma.
Who is it?
He's started already!
I'm not doing anything.
I'm not.
These are my normal clothes.
That's uncalled-for.
This time...
The time limit is six hours.
THE PLAYER WHO DOESN'T LAUGH
WINS 10 MILLION YEN
But if six hours have passed,
and we still have two or three people,
we'll implement the point system.
-What's that?
-Point system?
Over the next six hours,
the player who has accumulated
the most points becomes
the winner.
-This time we'll definitely have a winner.
-No draws?
IF THERE'S NO VICTOR AFTER SIX HOURS,
WHOEVER'S MADE THE OTHERS LAUGH
THE MOST WINS
So, be aggressive about getting laughs.
We will be recording who took out who.
These crackers are
a token of new friendship.
What are they?
-A token of new friendship.
-Why crackers?
-I'll go without.
-Crackers for friendship?
They make your mouth dry.
-Didn't you just laugh?
-I didn't.
The truth is...
That was quick.
That was probably Jimmy.
I was just talking.
-The talking bit wasn't a problem.
-But you laughed, too.
You kept on smiling,
and then you went, "Ha ha ha."
That's laughing.
-We can use the bathroom, right?
-You're acting too restless.
Let's all take a seat, okay?
-It hasn't begun yet, right?
-Not yet.
We're still safe.
You're acting too restless, Saito.
This is your second time,
but it's nerve-wracking for us.
Let's all sit down first.
Okay, we're going to restart.
That's the cue. We're on again.
-We've restarted?
-Yes.
Everyone, sit down. Take a seat.
Yeah, let's sit down.
Sit down, Yoshimura.
-Let me put my bag away first.
-Fine. Go ahead.
-My bag...
-Ashtrays...
Do I need permission for everything?
No, it's just that...
Anybody need an ashtray?
-We don't need ashtrays.
-We're fine.
-It's smoke-free.
-No, it's not.
We can smoke here?
Well, this is kind of
nerve-wracking.
Shut up.
Why say that?
-Pass the crackers.
-Put them in the trash.
-No, pass them around.
-We should get this over and done with.
Pass them around. I'll finish it quickly.
-Let's all take a seat.
-Want to smoke?
Let him do the cracker thing.
Just get it over and done with.
-You're all talking too much.
-Things are so cluttered right now.
-It's too confusing.
-Let's settle down.
Let me explain the crackers.
We don't need an explanation.
Take a seat.
To my lost little lambs,
He's at it.
Little lambs?
Pray with me.
Amen.
Enough already.
The tenth month...
I mean, we have ten months to go...
Watch him do his thing.
Merry Christmas.
It's time to light your crackers.
-Is that your joke?
-Yes.
Like a firecracker?
They don't make a bang,
so I'd like you to say, "Bang!"
The crackers don't make any bang sound
by themselves.
Bang...
-Is this your first time smoking?
-Yes.
-Listen, Jimmy.
-Yes?
This talk about crackers and firecrackers
is confusing.
It was a play on words, right?
Pack them up.
Put them away.
-Crackers and firecrackers?
-That was the joke. Sorry.
Isn't that too weak?
Well, you know. I'm...
-It's...
-Jimmy, stop.
Please take a seat.
You're bleeding.
Quit smoking! You're coughing!
Yeah...
Put it out. You've never smoked before.
Cut it out!
Can I get changed?
We told you to sit down!
But I want to change.
-There's no need to fight.
-What's wrong?
We all agreed it was getting
too noisy and confusing.
You guys, too...
Don't pick your nose!
Well...
-You're scary.
-Stop it, Kojima.
-Scary.
-That's not the point.
We all agreed...
Slow down.
But we all agreed to settle down.
Why has this become my fault?
Why are you worried now?
I always ignore you.
-Was that supposed to be funny?
-What's with you?
I'll never laugh at your reactions.
I won't laugh at them today either.
That's not what today's about.
It's not hard to keep a straight face
with you.
What does that mean?
-That means...
-We won't laugh.
To be honest, I haven't laughed at you
for the last three years.
The last three years?
Your act is one-dimensional.
You can't talk.
Your style is exactly the same.
-I noticed the likeness.
-What happens when they work together?
Yoshimura's act is similar, too.
-No, it's not.
-It is. We both yell a lot.
Stop it. Listen.
I was thinking that, as a way to start,
perhaps we could kick things off
by introducing ourselves.
I don't know the relationships
between you guys.
Maybe we should do something like that.
Is anyone meeting
Jimmy for the first time today?
I haven't met him before.
-I haven't either.
-Really?
It's my first time.
-We haven't met?
-It's practically my first time.
Really?
I've never seen him so close.
Look at him.
Yoshimura, don't be rude.
-He's your senior.
-He looks different up close.
-You'll never see him so close.
-No, thanks.
Yoshimura, face this way.
You're being rude.
-That isn't right.
-Yoshimura, you have to look.
You're not looking.
Look properly.
See how he bleeds?
It's his fault. Stop scratching!
Would you like a tissue?
No, thanks.
-Need a tissue?
-It's not bleeding.
Let's get self-introductions from
those who haven't met Jimmy before.
-Let me go to the bathroom.
-Okay.
-And I'll put my things in the locker.
-As you wish.
Today I want to learn how to smoke.
That's a cigar.
Just quit.
I went to my first cigar bar
the other day.
-A cigar bar?
-Yes.
It was so cool.
Which side are you supposed to light?
This one.
-You need to cut the end.
-Right, you cut this part.
Hot damn.
Hot damn?
That's your punchline?
Look at Fujimoto's face.
Fujimoto could be in trouble.
Does anyone want to drink this?
What is that?
Well...
What is it, Oshima?
Oshima is in trouble, too.
She is always putting something
in her mouth.
It's my breast milk.
For real?
-You're joking, right?
-I'm serious.
-That's real breast milk?
-Yes.
-Oshima...
-It's your milk?
-If your son knew, he'd cry.
-Is he an infant?
He's one year and eight months-old now,
but I still have milk.
Really?
That milk belongs to her baby, Efu.
What's she doing?
That milk was for Efu, but now he's like,
"Mama..."
-Have you ever drunk breast milk?
-No.
-Can I try some?
-For real?
Why not? You look like a baby.
Can I?
-Drink the breast milk.
-You don't mind?
Go for it.
You're amazing.
When else could I drink breast milk?
-You're amazing.
-Breast milk is good for you, too.
That's human milk.
-She's...
-Let me drink the breast milk!
-She's your junior.
-Is it really okay?
-Here goes.
-Okay.
From here?
Where else?
Don't get angry. I'll drink it.
How is it?
It's delicious.
-It's delicious?
-It's delicious.
Is it sweet?
-Delicious?
-Her breast milk is.
No way.
Jimmy, you look like you really want some.
Me?
-Jimmy.
-No, I'm...
You're undressing her with your eyes.
-I'm not. No way.
-But, if that's the case...
-You have unique tastes.
-No, I don't.
What fetish is that?
-It's not true.
-Shame on you.
I'm not into that, but...
I thought he's amazing.
Drink up. It's yours. Really.
-I can't drink all of it.
-Jimmy...
We've never had a chance to meet
like this before, so...
Please, take this.
-What did she give you?
-What is it?
-What did you get?
Jimmy, what did you get?
-Jimmy, answer us.
-Look at it.
No, no, no.
Look at it, Jimmy.
I don't know why, but...
She gave it to you.
What is that?
Jimmy, take a proper look.
Jimmy, look at what she gave you.
You have to look at it.
Seriously, what is it?
For some reason I got panties.
-They're huge.
-Are those Oshima's?
Aren't they huge?
-Her real panties?
-I guess so.
They are.
-Really?
-Yes.
-You wear pants like this?
-They're faded.
-The back looks clean.
-They're falling apart.
Did you play baseball in them?
They're covered in fuzz.
You definitely played baseball in them.
Wow.
You're laughing.
-You exploded into laughter.
-But who's out?
That will be a hard one to judge.
Oshima.
-You get a yellow card.
-Yes.
I know.
And you're always eating something,
aren't you?
-She's hiding her smile there, right?
-Yeah.
-That's cheating.
-It's not fair.
-We can't do that.
-It's not nice.
You can't do that.
Sorry.
Let's take another look.
-You wear pants like this?
-They're faded.
-The back looks clean.
-They're falling apart.
Did you play baseball in them?
They're covered in fuzz.
You definitely played baseball in them.
Well, I hadn't seen that angle.
He's laughing.
Jimmy's laughing right there.
No, I'm not.
-He laughed.
-Yes, he definitely did.
So Jimmy, you get
a yellow card.
-Bad luck.
-Yellow already?
You're in trouble.
But shouldn't Oshima get a yellow card,
too?
We already said that.
Yes, I laughed.
And Fujimoto is constantly...
How can I put it?
You're right.
I'm sorry!
What was that?
-What's so funny?
-What's with that apology?
-I'm counting on you.
-Thank you!
Restart.
We should put these away.
-There are no stains. Amazing.
-Put them away.
-But they're warped.
-They have fuzz.
-We should...
-Put them away.
Do they smell?
-Just put them away.
-Yeah, now.
But they really smell clean.
-She does her laundry. So what?
-That's enough.
-They're her white panties.
-Guys.
Is my ear bleeding?
-We said that before.
-Right?
-I offered you a tissue.
-All I need is this.
Kimchi?
He put that on standby ages ago.
Where am I bleeding?
Here?
-There.
-Don't do that!
That will hurt!
Kimchi stops the itchy!
That was a very high-brow joke.
You like puns, don't you?
I love them.
It started to sting.
-It hurts.
-You should wipe it off.
-It hurts a lot.
-First the cracker joke, now kimchi?
-Doesn't it hurt?
-It hurts. It hurts.
-Enough with the kimchi.
-Let me wipe it.
Don't use them! Stop it.
You can't use them.
Poor Oshima.
You ruined her panties.
Look at her.
Guys, I think...
-Wait a minute.
-What's with Oshima?
-That wasn't right.
-I think you went too far.
Oshima?
-Oshima!
-She's a lady, you know?
I'm sorry.
They're ruined.
My panties...
My dear panties...
You don't have kids.
You wouldn't understand.
-I treasured those panties so much.
-Right?
She probably wore these
when she was pregnant.
You don't get it. You don't have kids.
I had no idea. I'm sorry.
Those pants were so dear to me.
Fujimoto,
there's no need for you to wash them.
Fujimoto, why are you going that far?
Why did you wipe Jimmy's kimchi?
You don't need to cry that much.
You don't have kids.
You'd never understand.
-Does she have to cry?
-What happened?
Jimmy got kimchi on his face.
Saito wiped it off.
And you did it with my panties.
But he wouldn't use a tissue.
Guys. Stop. You simply don't get it.
I know what pregnant women are like.
These panties...
They remind her of when she was pregnant.
He's drinking her breast milk.
-Those panties are full of memories.
-Memory full panties?
Are they "memo-panties"?
They're "memo-panties."
Yoshimura?
She probably shouldn't have
brought them today, but...
-Yoshimura drank all of it?
-Yes, I did.
-Thanks.
-He drank all of your breast milk.
Thank you.
-Oshima, I'm sorry.
-It was delicious.
-The stain's coming out.
-From her memo-panties?
That's a bit much.
-That's not necessary.
-She'll cry again.
It's a tough stain.
Be careful with them.
You have dish soap on you.
That's... No.
Anyway, you're crying too much.
Oshima.
It's not that big a deal.
Yes! More. More. Go for it!
My memo-panties.
-Memo-panties?
-Beat them more.
Memo-panties require more care.
I'm using all my might.
Exactly.
Tell me if you see anyone laughing.
You laughed. You're gone.
You laughed, didn't you?
Not me.
Fujimoto, you should try harder.
What are you doing?
What purpose is that fulfilling?
Don't nod at us.
What?
I have to use my teeth.
I have to grind it.
Otherwise, the kimchi won't come out.
You wear a wedding ring and
you're biting panties?
They belong to the wife of another man.
-She's watching you do that.
-Stop sucking on people's panties.
She's my senior.
I never wanted to see a senior so sad.
Look at her.
Look how sad she is.
Someone's making a move.
So...
Let's end this!
RIght now!
-They're super-stretched now.
-They're clean enough.
I'm sorry!
I'm...
Kimc...
Jimmy...
-You're laughing.
-He is.
-No, I'm not.
-But you are.
-Take that off.
Kotouge, take it from him.
-You're laughing.
-I'm not.
I'm not.
You've seriously been washing
those panties for too long!
They're clean.
-What was that?
-Let's pour vinegar on them.
Vinegar!
-Hey.
-Don't do that.
-Vinegar should work.
-She'll cry again.
Just pour vinegar on it.
How dare you pour vinegar on my panties?
Because he was taking too long.
-This is too much!
-It's my fault for using them.
-I wiped the kimchi with the panties.
-But vinegar can clean them faster.
-It's all over.
Jimmy, stop it.
That's not funny at all.
-It's all over.
-Vinegar will...
Jimmy, stop it.
Oshima, you're crying too much.
They're clean now.
-No more kimchi.
-You've cried enough.
I washed out the kimchi.
Take a look. They're clean.
-They're okay.
-Now we'll dry them.
They are super-stretched.
-That's not a hanger.
-Hanger...
Hanger.
I'm going to... I'm sorry.
My priest act didn't work at all today.
No one laughed at my priest outfit.
Well, that's only because
you were dressed like that from the start.
Are there any hangers?
I'll quit being a priest.
Everyone, look.
He's going to quit being a priest.
I'm quitting this priest act.
-Watch him.
-I'm quitting priesthood.
Good idea.
-You're laughing.
-I'm not. Stop that.
Huh? What is that?
What is it?
I'm done for.
-What is that?
-I have no idea.
-What is it?
-It stinks!
It stinks!
-What is that smell?
-Konnyaku.
Elephant yam jelly?
It stinks!
But what is it?
What is that supposed to be?
Seriously.
-I quit the priest.
-You're poking out on the sides.
Because the priest bombed.
That was...
He has the full spectrum of comedy.
-From puns to this.
-Help us understand.
What is it?
Why did he make whatever that is?
That's unfair. It's too much.
-Himura.
-Me?
I only laughed after him.
-You laughed before, too.
-You did.
You were laughing about the panties.
Himura laughed so hard
when I did the panties.
No way.
Daisuke has been laughing the whole time.
I heard you go "kyu kyu kyu."
You went "kyu kyu kyu."
Seriously.
No way. This is wrong.
Everyone, look.
He's going to quit being a priest.
I'm quitting this priest act.
-Watch him.
-I'm quitting priesthood.
Good idea.
-You're laughing.
-I'm not. Stop that.
See?
-Who is it?
-Himura.
-That's definitely out.
-I told you.
Himura did laugh.
-Himura laughed.
-But look at Daisuke now!
When he looks down!
-I think that's safe.
-But he really did laugh.
And I only saw Daisuke laugh
after the red light.
Daisuke, did you think his yam-jelly dick
was funny?
Yes. It was extremely funny.
But it stinks.
It really smells bad.
Please take a few steps back.
What is it?
What's that supposed to mean?
It's konnyaku.
I can see that.
Why did you dig out the middle
and sew another piece inside?
I used kite string to sew
konnyaku to more konnyaku.
You're not making sense.
Imagine him making that at home.
That's what's funny.
Jimmy, wear some clothes.
-Wait.
-We can see too much.
-But I'm...
-That rash is gross, too.
I'm done with the priest.
Restart.
-You stink.
-That's really bad.
That really smells, Jimmy.
We can see everything from the side.
I don't mind.
You had four BCG vaccinations.
You shaved?
He did.
We really can see everything.
You really shaved all your hair.
If we keep having fun with Jimmy
we'll be stuck on him forever.
-Tuck it away properly.
-Let's all just ignore him.
-His privates are...
-Tuck them properly.
Ouch!
That was hot!
That was hot.
-That was hot?
-Don't you mean, "That hurts"?
We say, "It hurts."
Was it hot?
You said, "Hot."
It definitely wasn't hot.
Right, Daisuke?
It can't be hot.
No way was it hot.
What's wrong?
He's laughing.
Mr. Matsumoto!
No way. That was safe.
Why?
You were laughing.
-You can't complain.
-What was hot?
-I scored that one.
-That was quick.
Too quick.
You were too quick.
I don't want to keep coming out like this.
-We're sorry.
-You're right.
But someone laughed.
Daisuke.
-It was a brave fight.
-But you laughed.
But, before I started cracking up...
Before I started to lose it,
Himura had already laughed.
That's not true.
When Jimmy said "hot" you went "puh."
You went "puh."
-Himura is right.
-You did.
What's your problem?
You were on the other side.
But because he stopped
on the verge of laughing more,
I asked Jimmy what he meant by "hot."
-His privates are...
-Tuck them properly.
Ouch!
That was hot!
That was hot.
-That was hot?
-Don't you mean, "That hurts"?
-Look at him.
-He should've been out then.
-But I didn't show any teeth.
-To be honest, that's...
Did you see Jimmy?
Jimmy...
Jimmy was laughing, too.
That's out.
The cameras didn't quite get Himura.
I wasn't laughing.
-I was busy explaining.
-Right?
I explained how Jimmy
was wrong to say "hot."
-Okay. I got it.
-That's it.
Nice decision.
-Why did you say that?
-You laughed too hard that time.
But what about before?
-I'm counting on you guys.
-Thank you!
-Don't make me so busy.
-Sorry.
We laugh too easily.
You're allergic to something.
Jimmy, put on some clothes.
Yoshimura always hides his face.
-No, I don't.
-That's not fair.
And Jimmy, back then...
We should stop eating and drinking
when we're about to laugh.
You're right.
-Let this be an honorable battle.
-I agree.
Restart.
Let's change the subject.
Jimmy, are you changing?
Will you cook something?
No, I'm going Chinese.
Going Chinese?
-You look more "Italian."
-Put on some pants, please.
I'm going Chinese.
Your top is fine.
Cover your bottom.
I think we should stop focusing
on Jimmy so much.
Definitely.
But it's all your fault, Fujimoto.
-Don't blame me.
-You always put the spotlight on Jimmy.
Fine. I'll put on some pants.
Stop doing that, please.
-I'll put on pants.
-Let's enjoy this.
Kojima hasn't been funny yet.
What does that mean?
-Talk like that leads to fights.
-He's right.
-You need to make a move.
-We're avoiding fights.
You never make a move.
Big words.
If that's how you're going to be.
Hey.
-Going somewhere?
-Home, perhaps?
Move it!
You know where I'm going.
-Are you going home?
-Of course not.
See you next time.
I'm not leaving. Why leave now?
Give me a good "I'm Kojima!"
"I'm Kojima!"
-No.
-I really want one.
We haven't heard it yet.
I'm Kojima!
Me, too!
No, you're not!
What a day!
Shut up!
Hm?
What are you doing to my gag?
You're right.
That's not how it's done.
Pay more attention to the set-up.
Idiot! Why kiss me?
What sort of joke is that?
Why kiss me?
I'm sorry!
What is with that apology?
You keep saying it.
"I'm sorry."
Stop it!
That feels good.
-Stop it.
-He's a senior.
-You're turning me on.
-Shut up!
-Saito.
-Stop it.
He's your senior.
You're turning me on!
Your tongue!
Saito, licking is going too far.
Stop doing that, Saito.
That feels good.
Stop it. I'm getting worked up.
Stop. It feels good.
Don't look at me while you do it.
Stop watching me.
That feels too good.
Saito.
We don't need that.
That's the right spot.
-That's enough.
-That's not why we're here.
-It's Jimmy's fault, too.
-Don't spit.
Quit that.
That's messed up.
This is a baseball field.
Huh? What did he say?
-This is a baseball field.
-Baseball field?
Don't you mean "battlefield"?
Some people call it that, too.
Baseball field?
You think this is baseball?
-He said baseball field.
-He meant battlefield.
Watch his thing, Tsuda.
Everyone, come watch his thing.
But who's that?
Where are you going?
Who just left? That's not fair.
You can't just leave.
-It's Saito. Come back in here.
-I have a question.
Firstly, why did Kotouge leave
when I started to prepare this?
When we do something,
the unwritten rules say we watch.
-Who are you?
-I'm Kojima!
-Me, too!
-Listen.
-What a day!
-Listen to me!
You're screwing up my gag.
You have to mistake my name...
I'm doing something!
Something showed up.
It's creepy.
Kotouge!
Wait.
You totally screwed up my gag.
I apologize for that.
What's wrong?
When I saw the breast milk,
I said he looks like a baby.
-I didn't know he'd prepared this.
-Me, too. I'm sorry.
-It's my bad. It was my breast milk.
-No, I'm the one who ruined his joke.
You won't laugh now,
but I'll do it anyway.
Shove it in my face!
What a day!
-That's scary.
-It's not scary.
-It's noisy.
-It's not noisy.
I don't want to suck it now.
No breasts.
I don't want to suck it now!
-The jokes got into a traffic jam there.
-They did.
Yes, sorry about that.
Let's sit down.
Jimmy, how did that thing go?
You know.
With your phone.
You watched too much porn.
They sent you a huge bill, right?
It worked out.
How much was it?
400,000 yen.
That's a lot.
400,000 yen?
-What did you watch?
-You got shafted.
400,000?
A sumo wrestler.
-You got changed?
-Yes.
Weren't you about to do something funny
with that wood drum?
-Good point.
-You just whacked it loudly. It was scary.
-What's it for?
-Well, I didn't plan anything special.
-You just wanted to thump it?
-No, well...
I actually used one of these
the very first time I went on stage.
Show us what your first act was like.
Don't you want to see?
-I want to see.
Do it.
No.
Why won't you do it?
It's embarrassing.
Okay. Just show us a short version.
It wasn't long to begin with.
Do it.
-His first ever act?
-I'd like to see that.
-Do it.
-I don't want to!
Make it short.
It is short!
The long version will do.
I said it's short.
An un-long version.
That would be short, too.
A super-long version.
That's short, too.
-Semi-long?
-What does that mean?
Don't complicate things.
Super-long isn't short.
Doesn't matter.
It's all about tempo.
Do your act.
Do your act. We want to see it.
I've never seen you solo.
You went to the trouble of
bringing that here.
The thing is...
It's very different
from what I do with Anjash.
We don't need excuses.
Why not!
What a day!
What?
"What a day!"
That's the title
of my ex-girlfriend's porno.
By KING.
That's the title of my ex-girlfriend's
second porno.
Look at Oshima.
I'm coming all over.
That's the third. You know them all.
You know the titles
of all my ex-girlfriend's pornos.
Anri.
Yeah, that's her name.
Cat's Eye.
That's a different Anri.
How many jokes do you have about my ex?
-Kisarazu...
-That's another Cat's Eye.
Dog nose.
"Dog nose"?
Cat's Eye...
-Dog nose? I get it.
-That's a little far off.
Think of another one.
"Cat's eye."
"Dog nose."
Add one more.
Strawberry candy.
"Strawberry candy"?
What did he say?
"Strawberry candy."
That's not a wordplay on anything.
-Strawberry?
-"Strawberry candy."
Where did "strawberry candy" come from?
How long is your career?
Forty years.
Forty years?
You're scratching too much.
We'll see your brain soon.
-Unless you stop.
-That's too much.
You're already going bald.
-We'll see your brain.
-Don't get excited.
Hold on. I built up too much earwax.
-You built up too much earwax?
-I did. Sorry.
-Kojima secretly hid his drum.
-Don't tell everyone.
-Kojima's trying to hide his drum.
-Don't put it back on the table.
Let's see your solo act.
My solo act?
It's really not worth watching.
Are you saying you only brought that
to scare us by whacking it?
All it did was interrupt us.
Every time someone made a move.
When do you hit it?
If it's just for hitting.
This is just my image, okay?
My image.
What do you mean by that?
-I'll give you a cue.
-He'll say something for you to thump.
Try calling me "Oshima."
This is just an example.
Hey, Oshima.
I'm Kojima!
Do you follow me?
That's the full package?
-Is that all?
-You're wasting the drum.
No, I repeat this over and over.
-You'll do that over and over again?
-Right!
There was no reason for that.
There was no joke.
Don't you need a joke?
The rules are unclear!
Yo!
Jimmy, why wash your hands now?
They got covered in Tique
when I rinsed my hair.
-Chick?
-Cheek? He got covered in cheek?
-Cheek? Is that a dialect?
-Tique is...
It's a brand of pomade, right?
-Cheek?
-Tique.
It's like wax.
-Yeah. It's an old brand.
-You use Tique?
Don't hide it.
We noticed.
It's too big not to notice.
I've never seen a wooden drum
get so few laughs.
I've never seen someone use a wooden drum
and get as few laughs as you.
But he's that type of guy.
Not many people use wooden drums anyway.
But if we played one,
we'd get more laughs.
There's a wooden drum
standing right next to you.
You could play Kotouge a lot better.
-Play that other drum.
-He's not a drum.
Ow!
That hurt!
Who was it?
Who was that?
It wasn't me.
-I didn't laugh.
-It wasn't me.
That had to hurt.
-That's painful.
-Poor guy.
-You hit him so hard.
-Couldn't you predict that outcome?
People end up with fractured skulls
when you hit them that hard.
I might be out.
Oshima.
-Oshima laughed? Really?
-No way.
I'll give you an orange card.
-That was me?
-This is your last chance.
-Play that other drum.
-He's not a drum.
Ow!
That hurt!
You're laughing! That's a laugh.
You were all smiles.
Just like you were a pin-up girl.
You had a nice smile.
Like in a three-page full-color feature.
There's a bump. He has a bump already.
-It's a dent, actually.
-Yeah!
-He's dented.
If he was a kid, he'd be dead.
-I'm sorry.
-I'm fine.
-It's okay.
You really thumped him.
-I'll have to forget about that one.
-It's only been an hour.
Are any of you hungry?
-Will you make something?
I feel like something.
Only one hour?
Something would be nice.
Or is it too early?
Okay, here we go. Restart.
Who wants to eat?
We have sashimi.
Just like last time.
Jimmy, do you want some?
-You can have all of it.
-No, I don't like sashimi.
What a hit.
-How bad did it hurt?
-I'm sorry.
He caught me by surprise.
I went stiff.
Won't you guys eat?
This isn't the time for sashimi.
I don't need sashimi now.
How about bread? We have baguettes.
-We have rice.
-I'll bring it.
I think...
Before we eat, you should do your thing.
-As punishment for that hit.
-Yeah.
-It won't end otherwise.
-I don't mind, but...
What kind of act is it?
It's a short skit. It's one I do solo.
-Have you forgotten it?
-Not at all.
It's really short.
We don't mind.
-You're going to do it?
-Sure.
Of course, I don't want to.
It's called
Stories Too Suspicious to Believe.
"I heard this from
the friend of a friend..."
My old routines were all like that.
What did it even mean?
That was too difficult.
-Your old routines were like what?
-Okay...
What did that mean?
Try doing the whole thing,
until the punch line.
Don't explain how it works.
Just do it.
-It doesn't have to be perfect.
-Just show us.
Wait. I'm so nervous, I forgot it.
You forgot it?
-That killed it.
-Sorry.
-What did you heat up?
-Huh?
What did you heat up?
Strawberry candy.
No, you didn't.
-That's not what you heated up.
-It was rice, right?
You said something stupid,
then you laughed at it yourself.
-You laughed at your own joke.
-You laughed so hard.
-It was your own joke.
-It was yours.
Hey!
Stop grunting, Jimmy.
You guys keep me so busy.
You're in here so often this time.
You laughed.
I think Jimmy wins a point this time.
I won a point?
Yay.
The one who laughed was...
Saito.
Me?
It was you.
It was you, without doubt.
-Me without doubt?
-You without doubt.
-You must have laughed.
-Without a doubt.
-That killed it.
-Sorry.
-What did you heat up?
-Huh?
What did you heat up?
Strawberry candy.
You were out there.
That was out.
That was too suspicious.
Why else would you eat bread after
he said "strawberry candy"?
-Nice judgment.
-I'm clamping down on things like that.
That was great refereeing.
That's me. Sorry.
-What is it?
-Sorry.
-You suck.
-That was the worst timing ever.
-You totally screwed it up.
That was a close one.
That sure was close.
No, you screwed up. Completely.
-It wasn't close at all.
-It finished ringing.
Don't act like it all went to plan.
That one didn't work.
Restart.
This sucks. The moment I got changed,
somebody went and laughed.
-It was just a coincidence, right?
-Yes.
-Sorry.
-You can't help things like that.
Stuff like that happens.
Nobody's to blame.
-Let me try again...
-Didn't you guys see me laugh?
-We didn't.
-It's because you were eating.
But they have cameras on us
from every angle.
-I'm going to have some water.
-Actually...
My mother turns 70 years old this year.
She has this photo of when she was 15.
It's an old black and white photo.
She's using a hula hoop.
She has this really great expression
on her face.
Will you take a look?
Sure.
Who's that?
It's my mom.
The thing is, her farts stink really bad.
When we were kids, we nearly wet ourselves
laughing every time she farted.
We would all scream,
"That stinks! Open up the windows!"
But for some reason,
one day when she farted,
we were screaming like normal,
then Dad went up and slapped her.
My mom got slapped for farting.
How strong was the slap?
What does that matter?
-I'm just curious.
-Give us an idea.
-Make the fart sound first.
-She farted...
-Prrtt!
-Then my dad went up and said,
"Your bowels are rotten!"
-Wow.
-That was strong.
-Show us again.
-That was tough.
Who wants to be slapped?
-I'm curious to see how hard the slap was.
-Yeah.
-It shouldn't hurt with that on.
-Really?
If it's a clean hit.
First check where his cheek is.
So you don't swing and miss.
Be careful.
That's better.
Sorry.
Daisuke?
-Everyone okay?
-What's wrong?
You're okay?
Fujimoto is close...
My mum was 14 in that photo.
He's on the borderline the whole time.
I'll have to warn him.
She was a javelin thrower.
She was 14.
Amazing, right?
She was a javelin thrower.
She made the national championships.
-Take a good look
-Wow.
THE JAVELIN THROWER
-Fujimoto, did you see the photo?
-I saw it.
Take a closer look.
Take a good, proper look.
-Look for 10 seconds.
-The javelin thrower.
She threw javelins.
Hey!
Why didn't you all laugh, too?
Look.
This is so funny.
She threw javelins.
How could you hold back a laugh?
You can't bring in a photo like this!
-That one got him.
-It was a nice, clean hit.
-You're in trouble.
-Yeah, I laughed.
That was...
That was funny.
Yeah, I know. I deserve a...
You're kidding!
Wait a minute.
Wait just a minute.
-Just kidding.
-You scared me!
Well, I laughed so much,
I couldn't complain if it was red.
-That belongs in a textbook.
-Tsuda gets a point for that.
It belongs in a textbook for comedy.
That really was funny.
Why didn't you guys laugh, too?
You're right.
If you didn't find that funny,
there's probably something wrong with you.
You have to laugh at that!
Have you ever seen a black-and-white photo
so full of movement?
Is that thing glued to her back?
She can't really be twirling it.
-Fujimoto, did you see the photo?
-I saw it.
Take a closer look.
Take a good, proper look.
-Look for ten seconds.
-The javelin thrower.
She threw javelins.
You can't blame us.
-That hit the spot.
-It sure did.
They locked onto Fujimoto there.
But it was funny. You all are.
Tsuda did well there.
You're all funny. What can I do?
Here we go.
Tsuda earned a point there.
That one came out of nowhere.
I'll dry these.
Look at this.
Um, wow.
That's amazing!
Wow!
Does it work on konnyaku?
What would happen to the konnyaku?
That is way too lame.
I guess that's all.
Try under the konnyaku.
Why do that?
Here it comes.
Ow!
No doubt there.
-Nice work, Jimmy.
-Real nice.
You laughed so hard.
-Is that a red card?
-It must be.
-Where has your concentration gone?
-You're right. Sorry.
What happens if you laugh?
This will be his first card.
Kojima.
-I knew it.
-He laughed?
-What about Kotouge?
-Doesn't he get one?
-He laughed?
-I did, too.
He laughed the hardest.
-I did.
-We all thought it was him.
-He totally lost it.
-I have to admit that one.
I'll take another look.
Kotouge wasn't...
I thought you all saw Kojima.
Ow!
That's a laugh.
He laughed so hard!
You can't complain there, Kotouge.
-That's a nice result.
-What a laugh.
The judge is getting tougher.
Be careful about hiding your face.
And we all have cards.
It could be over in a flash.
Is anybody yet to receive a card?
I haven't got a card yet.
-Wow.
-That's amazing.
-Who has two points?
-I do.
Two of you?
-I have one yellow card.
-Me, too.
-One more, and I'm out.
-Jimmy, too.
If we get another yellow card, we're out.
One false move, and we're out.
Restart.
That vacuum was amazing. It's funny.
-That was spectacular.
-Let's do it again.
His balls were amazing.
They got sucked right up.
-Jimmy has huge balls.
-They got sucked up the tube.
I think they reached here.
-That far?
-I think so.
-They went up this far.
-Let's do it again.
-They couldn't go that far.
-They did.
Seriously. They did.
-You should take that off.
-Really?
Everyone should watch this.
-Seriously.
-Can I lift this up?
Do the balls.
-Balls?
-Balls.
Ow!
That hurts!
No more!
I'll go into rectal prolapse.
Only if we'd sucked your anus.
Why don't we fix that dent in your head?
-Good idea.
-Sorry about that.
It's somewhere around here.
-Will this fix it?
-Let's try.
Ow! Ow!
That hurts!
That really hurt. Again.
-The dent got bigger.
-Of course. That hurt.
We sucked his head right after
sucking Jimmy's balls.
You're right.
Suck his head up into the tube.
-It won't fit.
-Like Jimmy's balls.
Go slowly.
-Try your lips.
-That's contagious.
We just sucked his balls.
Use your tongue.
Go with the tongue.
-I'm not going next.
-Nobody wants to go next.
You sucked Jimmy's balls,
then he licked it.
-That's too much.
-Let's decide by rock-paper-scissors.
-I have germ phobia.
-No way.
Let's play that.
Before we play the game,
let's suck his balls.
To start afresh? Okay.
Why start with his balls?
-Do we need the balls?
-Let's play ball.
We'll do his balls to reset things
before we do rock-paper-scissors.
-That's better.
-Let's remove the pipe.
Won't that pull on his balls harder?
This stinks.
This seriously stinks.
It really does.
-That stinks!
-What the hell?
-That is intense, Jimmy.
-We have to play this.
It really stinks.
That's foul.
-That's foul.
-We have to suck his balls first, right?
We start with Jimmy's balls.
-It's like an opening ceremony.
-We can't start without it.
But his balls really stink.
Start with his pole.
That hurts!
Damn you. My pole...
He got your pole?
He got my intestines.
Your intestines?
-What happened?
-He sucked my intestines down.
Are you okay?
Of course not. That hurt.
-Are you okay?
-Like I said. Of course not.
What happened?
-Does it hurt?
-Is it "hot"?
Look at my balls.
They've been reshuffled.
They've been reshuffled?
What the hell does that mean?
What does "reshuffled" mean?
-Reshuffled?
-That sounds quite...
Your balls got reshuffled?
That's playing dirty.
That's not fair.
That's ridiculous.
This is getting ridiculous!
-We had a good laugh.
-You sure did.
Unfortunately,
I think I could call all of you out.
Really?
But there were two clear outs.
Tsuda and Yoshimura.
Now, you all have one.
It really is a coincidence.
Start with his pole.
That hurts!
Damn you. My pole...
He got your pole?
He got my intestines.
-Your intestines?
-Are you okay?
Of course not.
Look at my balls.
They've been reshuffled.
I took that "reshuffle" up close.
But it was true.
His balls had been reshuffled.
At first, I had no idea what he meant.
But after a closer look,
I realized they had been reshuffled.
Not just up and down.
There was a lateral transfer, too.
Restart.
Shall we continue?
If we're continuing,
we need to suck Jimmy's balls again.
His balls again?
-Or was that enough?
-I think so.
I think that's enough.
-He's at it again.
-Don't wash your head there.
-Stop it.
-Give me a break.
My head's too hot.
-It's too hot?
-There's no need to use soap.
-What are you washing it with?
-Dish soap.
Your hair will get stiff.
Wait up. I still have some kimchi.
-Kimchi?
-What do you mean?
-I'm covered in kimchi. It hurts.
-That's your fault.
But we need his balls
for the opening ceremony.
Let's decide who's next
by rock-paper-scissors.
Yeah.
Why not?
-What was that?
-You still have foam.
You're still covered in foam.
-Hurry up.
Hurry up.
This is my bubble dance.
Why won't it wash out?
Hey!
Quit that!
What's wrong?
-He keeps getting me.
-Oh, my.
Stop it. Seriously.
There's foam here, too.
Not much time has passed.
-An hour and a half.
-Is that all?
Was anyone out after 90 minutes last time?
Really?
I think there was.
Jimmy was out.
Can I wash my hands?
-No, thanks.
-Why? It's just...
...a towel.
-I let my guard down.
-You sure did.
Who was that?
Daisuke?
You, right?
What happened?
I just...
Seriously...
I was just talking with Jimmy
like I normally would.
-You can't do that.
-That's a no-no.
That's your bad.
Is this the end?
Your attention slipped.
It's your second time on the show.
-Daisuke?
-Yes.
Daisuke laughed.
Let's take a look.
I think there was.
Jimmy was out.
Can I wash my hands?
-No, thanks.
-Why? It's just...
He laughed!
Yellow!
-What a waste.
-That has to hurt.
That means he's out. You're out.
No!
-But you really did laugh.
-You did.
Don't do this to me.
Nobody even tried to make me laugh.
All I did was offer Jimmy a towel.
He said, "No, thanks."
I thought, "Why?"
I lose a million yen for that?
You giggled.
What was so funny?
We need an explanation.
-Well, Jimmy was soaking wet.
-Because he just washed his head.
So, I offered him a towel
to wipe himself dry.
But he said, "No, thanks."
But he was soaking wet!
-Why is that funny?
-It's funny!
That's what we call "everyday life."
We'll be making stricter judgments
from here on.
Well, he will.
He will be really strict.
Even just a smirk...
A smirk will get you a card!
You're not the judge.
-But he's right. I will be tougher.
-You will, right?
-Hurry up and leave.
-Bye!
I still don't get what was funny.
Jimmy was washing his head.
He was soaking wet.
When I gave him a towel he said,
"No, thanks."
That's not funny.
It was funny!
What is this?
Why did I eat a steamed bun,
then go and wash my hands at that moment?
What was that?
I don't find it funny at all now.
-No, thanks.
-Why? It's just...
I gave him a towel. He said, "No, thanks."
That was it...
I think I'd been numbed by it all.
Somebody laughed.
The alarm went off.
The thunder noise came and we restarted,
but I guess
I wasn't concentrating.
It's a six-hour-long test.
It's all about concentration.
And how long they can maintain it.
I think one's ability to concentrate
varies with age,
but two hours is probably
the best you can hope for.
But they must maintain concentration
for three times longer than that.
So, I imagine that keeping concentration
for that long would be no small task.
I think that can be said.
If that's what makes Documental tough,
what makes it fun?
It's fun when players
lose their concentration.
That may seem like a contradiction,
but when somebody lets down their guard,
and you sneak up on them,
you find yet another kind of comedy.
-You must be Director Izutsu.
-No, I am not.