THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
We don't have the formidable Cookie
here with us this time...
...but few players
are equally formidable here.
Each comedian has their strong suit.
It's becoming clearer
what kind of comedian...
...is best suited for Documental.
Seriously?
We had drinks the other day!
What do you think is
the ideal way for the show to unfold?
We're at the stage where you start to
consider all the possible scenarios.
One series could even end in five minutes.
Five minutes in,
everyone bursts into laughter,
and that's it.
Or everyone could laugh all at once,
and just walk out.
I've been thinking,
"That might happen one day.
I hope it does. But would that be okay?"
I have a lot of ideas regarding
the ideal Documental.
Hello.
I'm Junichiro Koizumi.
Junior...
Let's continue.
Is there a magic marker somewhere?
I want to write my name
on the water bottle.
-This isn't a permanent marker, but...
-That'll do.
Who cares which bottle belongs to who?
Will it write?
My mouth isn't that dirty.
Why did you write "Maya Hayashi"?
MAYA HAYASHI
Anyone's name will do.
-I know it's mine.
-He knows.
I know my bottle says "Maya Hayashi."
Okay?
"Passion Yara."
YARA
-That guy?
-Yes.
The guy who does this?
Choge choge passion
Please take a look.
-He said, "Choge choge passion."
-Junior...
Choge choge passion
Hey, you're not looking.
Takahashi and Junior are so fragile.
"Choge choge passion."
-Take turns writing your name.
-That's impressive.
Kobayashi is amazing.
-We have to know whose is which.
-Write so we know.
"Wankosoba Taro." Who's that?
"Wanko Sobataro"?
Who is "Wanko Sobataro"?
It's the fake name I use when
I try to make people laugh with a name.
"Wanko Sobataro"?
"Wankosoba Taro."
-"Wankosoba Taro"?
-Not "Wanko Sobataro"?
"Wan..." "Wankoso..."
"Wankosobataro"?
"Wankosoba Taro," right?
It's "Wankosoba..."
No, hang on.
Yeah, it's "Wankosoba Taro."
Not "Wankoso Bataro"?
Is it "Wankoso Bataro"?
"Wankoso Bataro"?
-"Bataro..."
-"Wanko Sobataro"?
That's it!
Who's "Wanko Sobataro"?
It's the name I always use
to make people laugh.
Like when?
"Wanko F. Bataro"?
No, that's wrong.
It's "Wanko Sobataro."
You know what I mean, right?
Sometimes you try to make people laugh
with a funny name.
This is the name I use on such occasions.
Reiji says he always uses "Riho Makise."
I understand.
It's something that changes over time.
Each era has its own.
Should we do something?
Let's finish writing our names.
We have to do that, right?
Well, any name will do.
But, Jinnai...
The bad thing about Jinnai is...
I shouldn't say "bad."
The one thing that worries me
about Jinnai is,
he's often considered an all-rounder,
but he totally sucks at oogiri games.
When I asked him to name a new superhero,
he said,
"Masked Rider: Policing."
What the heck is that?
I wrote mine.
-What is it?
-"Wanko Sobajiro."
They're brothers?
We have similar names?
What a funny coincidence.
Is it "Wankosoba Jiro"?
"Wan Kosobajiro."
"Wan..." "Wan Kosobajiro"?
-Then they're different.
-"Wanko Sobataro"?
And Jiro...
"Wankoso..."
Come up with one already!
Don't overthink it, Tamura.
How long have we been waiting?
Only you have to get it.
Okay.
"Ichiro."
That's the only wrong answer.
Jimmy, Jimmy, Jimmy.
Jimmy.
-You said any name would do.
-Any name would've done, except that.
Out of all the names in the universe?
Because "Ichi" means number one?
Number one was the worst...
Jimmy?
-Jimmy.
-Yes?
Jimmy!
What did you laugh at?
What was so funny?
I'd been holding it in since "Ichiro."
I know what you mean.
"Ichiro" almost got me too.
-What was so funny?
-Wait. "Ichiro..."
I don't get why you laughed.
After thinking for so long,
that's all he came up with.
-You couldn't let that go?
-It kept nagging me.
Then halfway through,
they started looking at me.
"Ichiro."
Jimmy?
-Jimmy.
-Yes?
Jimmy!
Junior and Takahashi were borderline
the whole time.
-What? During that last bit?
-You were close.
For real?
Junior almost lost it
with that Passion Yara bit.
-You laughed at Passion Yara.
-I didn't.
-He covered his smile.
-I didn't laugh.
But Jimmy did. So...
You were smiling most of the time.
-No, I wasn't!
-The whole time.
-He smiles every time someone speaks.
-That "Ichiro" bit wasn't funny at all.
Not funny at all!
You don't have to point fingers.
-That guy.
-Jimmy laughed anyway.
Who drags it out so much
for something so unfunny?
Wouldn't you have laughed?
After being made to wait for so long.
-He thought so hard.
-Well.
-Let's be careful.
-We're all okay?
Do be careful.
-Junior laughed a little.
-He did, right?
When you said
"Ichiro" was the worst answer.
-You giggled.
-Really?
But I have a habit of smiling
when I talk, right?
-We can't do that either?
-Right. We have to be careful.
We can't do that either...
-I think we've had enough of funny names.
-Yeah, it's a bit tough.
-But Jimmy kept one up his sleeve.
-No, I didn't.
-You wanted us to keep writing names.
-No way. I have nothing.
What did you write?
It's a little hard to read.
"Purin Hime."
-I know that name.
-She's a classmate.
-She's our classmate?
-At NSC.
She's the one that Zakoshisyoh
tried to lose his virginity with,
but failed.
-Really?
-Right.
-You held hands all night.
-Yes.
-You liked her?
-I did.
-She wore Gothic Lolita fashion.
-That's right.
She looked like she was good at blowjobs.
After that, since he was still a virgin,
he said, "I'll try picking up a girl."
He wanted me to join him.
So we went.
Jimmy...
-He picked up a girl.
-Jimmy...
They went to a love hotel,
but he wanted me to come.
Jimmy.
He wanted me to watch.
Takahashi and Jimmy.
Then he lost his virginity.
Jimmy?
And then...
He calls me "Bayashi."
He said, "I'm coming!
"Bayashi, what should I do?"
I said, "Just come."
I heard about it at the time.
Zakoshisyoh said he'd lost his virginity.
When I asked him how it was, he said,
"A gum-like substance came out."
Who was that?
Me?
It wasn't me!
-Was it me?
-I was close.
Jimmy, you were laughing before that, too!
-You were laughing the whole time!
-But...
What was that face?
It's Jimmy that almost makes us laugh.
With that face.
Hang on. Someone else must have laughed.
-Wait a minute!
-You laughed first.
-Let's ask the judge.
-You laughed in my face.
-When I turned you.
-No, no!
Judge?
Don't call me "Judge."
I don't think it was me. It's--
Junior.
How quick!
-Junior, you're on your last life.
-One more to go.
You're in trouble.
Was I laughing?
You were. Let's take a look.
When I asked him how it was, he said,
"A gum-like substance came out."
I'm holding it in!
I held it in!
I was on the edge, but I kept it.
That's why I'm not giving you a red card.
It's not a red card, but...
-He's in trouble now.
-That was out, right?
You were swaying all over.
You really need to tread carefully now.
Seriously.
-Junior, you're in trouble now.
-It hasn't even been 30 minutes.
I want Junior to stay longer.
-He only has one more chance?
-I'm in trouble.
The next time, he's out.
That was fast.
Part of me looks forward to seeing
Junior as a zombie,
but please try your best to win--
Hey, wait. Who put this egg here?
It's not that big a joke.
It's no big deal.
It's not that evil a deed.
What's the point of finding who did it?
I wanted to solve this mystery.
Who'd laugh at this anyway?
It bothers me!
Jimmy, please.
Has age made you far-sighted?
Near-sighted.
How old are you?
Fifty-four.
-I'm getting far-sighted.
-What did he write?
"Kano Hospital."
-Kano Hospital?
-Yes.
You go there?
You work there?
No...
I was hospitalized there.
Why were you hospitalized?
Yeah, well...
I can't say that on TV.
-You can't say it on TV?
-It's that bad?
No, it's okay. You can say
the name of medical conditions.
It happened to you.
What was it?
Well, first they examined me,
then they ran electricity through me.
-What?
-They ran electricity through you?
-Where?
-My head.
When was this?
When did that happen?
-Yamauchi...
-Well...
-Yamauchi.
-They told me to go to the hospital.
Who told you?
The police.
The police?
You did something wrong?
-No, I didn't do anything wrong. But...
-Out of the blue?
-They stopped you on the street?
-They stopped me...
-And they told you to go to the hospital?
-Yeah.
So I went.
-Were you hospitalized?
-Well, the hospital...
Or did you just visit?
In the beginning, I was just visiting.
I was hospitalized for three days.
Which is it?
-Was he an outpatient or inpatient?
-I was an outpatient first.
-Then you became an inpatient?
-I went from outpatient to inpatient.
-At Kano Memorial Hospital?
-Yes.
"Memorial"?
When did you think of writing that
on your bottle?
When did you decide?
Since "Ichiro."
When he wrote "Ichiro"?
Jimmy.
Like I said, Jimmy.
Does it actually exist?
You have such a cute face now.
-You came up with the idea at "Ichiro"?
-When he wrote "Ichiro."
-Wow.
-You must like Ichiro a lot.
-Do you like Ichiro?
-Ichiro...
Have you always liked him?
Cut it out.
-Sorry.
-I've had enough of that.
Kano Hospital was a surprise.
They're drinking a lot of water.
I told them to cut that out.
There are a whole lot of fish sausages
in the refrigerator.
Please lie down here, Jimmy.
-So many sausages!
-There are tons of them!
I saw this on a Korean TV show before.
Apparently you can fit
about 30 fish sausages in your mouth.
Why don't we see who can
put the most in his mouth?
-Like that? Uncooked?
-Like this. As they are.
Let's see who can put the most in.
-One by one?
-It'll make you gag.
-There are so many.
-How many sausages fit?
-Thirty?
-One guy can put 30 in his mouth.
-Who wants to try?
-What kind of TV does Korea have?
You should go, Takahashi.
You brought it up.
-You started it.
-Okay. Jimmy and me.
-Takahashi and Jimmy.
-Me?
We add three each turn?
-Is that how we'll do this?
-One-on-one?
It's not a team game?
Go for it like that.
-Thirty sausages?
-Yes.
-They won't fit.
-You're already full.
I think I'll be bad at this.
-You put them in yourself?
-Will you do it?
-That would be better.
-You can fit heaps more.
Three at a time, right?
Three shouldn't be a problem.
Ready for three more?
Three at a time.
We have to push them in.
-I don't think they'll make it.
-That's only six.
He's pretty full already.
Takahashi has three?
Kobayashi, give Takahashi three more.
-He's already full.
-What a small mouth.
-I don't think he'll even get to 10.
-That's seven.
Seven.
Jimmy still has space.
A lot of space.
Shigeo doesn't look good.
You're a seven-sausage man.
No, he can fit more.
Are you an eight-sausage man?
An eight-sausage man.
Eight.
Jimmy has heaps of room.
-The eight-sausage man is the problem.
-Shigeo's full.
He can't take any more.
-He'll gag.
-No more.
Are you a nine-sausage man?
Thirty of these?
Jimmy is...
He has plenty of room.
-Here might work.
-Nine-Sausage Man.
It's in. Okay.
Jimmy's ready.
-Ten.
-Ten sausages.
-Jimmy looks comfortable.
-It fits with such ease.
What about Ten-Sausage Man?
Can you make it to Ten-Sausage Man?
No way. He's done for.
This is a good match!
But the goal is 30, right?
He fits them in with such ease.
He must have soft lips.
They slip right in.
You're right. But he opened
his mouth really wide earlier.
You're starting to drool, Jimmy.
-You're drooling.
-Will it fit?
Let's do three sausages at once.
Good idea!
You did it yourself?
I think I'll get Tamura for that.
That was close!
So close!
He took out two at once.
Jimmy had me the whole time.
-He was shaking.
-It's him, right?
-It wasn't me. I didn't laugh.
-It was Tamura.
It was Tamura. I had these in my mouth.
My reaction wasn't "laughter."
It was "surprise."
Tamura.
What? It definitely wasn't me!
-Mr. Matsumoto, please look!
-I was just surprised.
The air in the room was virtually
dripping with laughter, but...
-But Tamura deserves a card, I'm afraid.
-So it was Tamura.
No way!
-You smiled.
-I did.
Looking at the replay, I see.
But that's out?
-That was out.
-Takahashi doesn't get one?
-But I think Takahashi laughed too.
-It wasn't a laugh.
But his mouth was full,
so it was hard to tell.
I see.
I was just surprised.
I was struggling so much,
but he slipped them in so easily,
and so quickly.
I thought, "Whoa!"
Yeah. I can see I smiled.
I have to be careful.
And today, if you get hungry,
you can order out.
You can order pizza, sushi, or Chinese...
-If you wish.
-That's dangerous.
I'm in trouble!
-I wasn't even aware I was smiling.
-I had no idea it was you.
-I didn't realize until I saw my face.
-You definitely smiled.
Okay, let's go.
-Akiyama's going to try?
-I will.
-How many?
-You can do 10, right?
-How many will you start with?
-Why not 10?
Instead of adding them gradually,
it may be better to go all at once.
Shall we go for 13?
-You should start with 10.
-Okay, 10.
-Here are 10.
-Thanks.
-Put them in, please.
-Oh, that thing.
That's what he wanted to do.
His mouth fits perfectly.
-I've never seen it so close.
-Takahashi.
Please open your mouth wider, Mr. Umemiya.
If you poke out your tongue,
the sausages won't fit.
I wonder.
Since you like fishing,
do you prefer fish sausages?
-I guess so.
-Yes, I do.
-You do?
-Rather than German ones.
-You prefer fish sausages?
-That's right.
If you had to choose,
you'd pick fish sausages?
But you like animal meat too, right?
I love meat too. I still eat steaks.
He keeps coming.
Jinnai, he keeps coming.
Mr. Umemiya, let's go one by one.
-He keeps coming.
-One by one.
What a small mouth.
It's smaller than I expected.
There you go.
How many can you take?
Go gradually. Let's aim for five or six.
Five... Then I'll put in three.
The older you get, the less you eat.
Don't push yourself too far.
-But you eat meat, right?
-I do eat meat.
-I eat to keep my energy level up.
-Right.
-So I eat meat.
-How much meat do you eat?
When I do, I eat about a pound of it.
That's a lot.
Go gradually.
But we've still only got four.
How's that?
-He's reached his limit.
-Maybe.
What's wrong?
Mr. Umemiya!
Mr. Umemiya?
It got in my throat.
It gets in your throat.
That's how it goes.
But you only had four.
-He spat it out.
-He can't see?
He can't see, right?
Who cares?
They won't fit.
They won't.
They reach my throat.
Right to my Adam's apple.
-Those look cute.
-What are they?
Well, this is a game I found.
"The Ducks' Eyes Light Up."
You pick them up,
and if their eyes light up, you win.
Only two of the four light up.
If you guess the exact pair, you win.
They light up when held?
You have to squeeze them. Let me show you.
You chose right.
The mouth lights up.
-The mouth?
-The mouth lights up?
The mouth lights up.
I got the correct pair on the first try.
Who wants to try?
So there are two of each?
Only two of each.
-You got it right on the first try?
-Yes.
Don't watch while I shuffle.
Okay.
Will someone please give it a try?
-I'll go.
-Okay.
It can't be that hard.
The chances are 50-50,
but there are a lot possible combinations.
-They both have to light up.
-So what you did was amazing.
-What happened?
-Well...
Well, they gave me an electric shock.
Takahashi, give it a try.
That was a surprise.
-Give it a try.
-Okay.
But you got shocked, right?
Yeah, well. I'm not sure.
It may have been a bad combination.
-But...
-What's he doing?
He scared me.
Be careful, Golgo!
-What's he doing?
-That's dangerous.
-What is it?
-Who's he aiming at?
-Jimmy.
Why is he aiming at me?
Isn't it hot in here?
-You're hot?
-Aren't you hot?
It's so hot.
I'm so hot.
-What's this?
-You squeeze two at once.
If they light up, you win.
Two of them? How do I do it?
-Choose your ducks.
-Only two of them light up.
The other two don't light up.
-Squeeze them on both sides.
-Both sides?
-Choose your ducks.
-Pick them up.
-I pick them up by the metal part?
-Yeah.
If they light up, you win.
Ouch!
I can't let go!
That's not what I expected.
-What's this?
-He's doing something.
-What's up?
-Do they all shock you?
What's wrong?
What?
Thank you
very much!
-Do they all give a shock?
-Sorry.
All of them shock you, right?
All of them? Were you just enduring it?
All of them lit up.
Aren't they shocking you?
What's going on?
Shigeo, give it a try.
Maybe they don't shock individually.
Let go of it.
Here you go.
This is scary.
It's scary once you know.
That was strong!
Are you really fine?
You're scary.
For real?
I guess some freaks can do it.
How do you handle
low-frequency therapy devices?
-I'm fine.
-Totally?
-If this doesn't hurt, they won't either.
-Right.
I can even hold all four.
-That's too much.
-Don't do it.
-Wow.
-You're totally fine with it?
Are you just tolerating it?
Is it tingling? Now?
I can feel it tingling.
It may look small,
but it's one of the strongest there is.
It's strong.
It's enough to make your legs give way.
It gives a shock
when you hold two at once?
That's right.
-This is scary. You squeeze both of them?
-Yes.
We told you that would happen.
What's wrong?
What's that sound?
What is it?
-Kobayashi...
-Something is whirring.
What is it?
What?
-I hear a whirring sound.
-I hear it.
It's not the birds.
They made something start whirring.
It can't be the birds.
They just give you a shock.
There's a whirring sound.
You hear that?
I had a pink vibrator in here.
How could you...
-That's dangerous.
-Which shocked you?
-Which gave the shock?
-The pink one?
-Squeezing them turned this on.
-How?
-How does that work?
-Wow!
Why don't you turn it off and...
-Who are you?
-What is it?
I was wondering what's up.
Who are you?
Me?
Talking to me?
I'm Sato Mascar...
Yojiro.
Sato Mascar Yojiro.
I'm half Japanese.
-Sato?
-Yes. Mascar Yojiro.
-Mascar?
-Yes.
Where are your parents from?
England and...
Canada.
-What's with the glasses?
-What about Japan?
Your chin is wet.
Well...
I ran here.
What were you were doing?
I squeezed them and ended up like this.
Try squeezing two of them.
-These?
-Squeeze their sides.
-Here?
-Yes.
-Both of them?
-Squeeze hard.
Ouch!
Give me a break.
-What?
-His eyes are blue.
-Are they colored contacts?
-I'm half Japanese.
They're colored contacts.
Couldn't you find contacts
with more color?
It's hard to tell.
-Are we supposed to laugh?
-Who'd laugh?
-I'm half Japanese.
-That was the setup?
So your eyes are blue?
Where are your parents from again?
Um, Itaba...
-England and Canada.
-You said Itabashi.
You came from Itabashi, right?
I'll go.
You're leaving?
Already?
Is that all?
What do you do?
For a living?
Um...
I work at Tokyo Station.
At a souvenir shop.
What do you sell?
Chicks.
-You sell these?
-Yes. I feel at home.
-Yes.
-You sell these at Tokyo Station?
-You do?
They're a new series that just came out.
-From Hiyoko Sweets?
-We sell them there.
They're from that store?
-What else do you sell?
-Chick Shock, Chick Sweets,
Chick Magnets,
Chick Pas...
Chick Pasta.
Chick Pasta?
-What's in it?
-Chicks.
-Chicks?
-You mean chick meat?
If you're ever nearby,
please come to level B1.
What's on B1?
Bullet train tracks.
-The bullet train?
-Trains run there.
Please stop by.
Okay.
-Thank you.
He was half Japanese.
He's brave.
He couldn't find contacts
with a deeper color.
-It was hard to tell.
-It was.
He's 0% Japanese.
-Do you want to play cards?
-Good idea.
I'll play cards.
Cards.
-What game?
-Well...
-What are we playing?
-How about poker? Wanna play poker?
Can this many people play poker?
Okay then, let's play President.
Okay, teach us the rules.
Just to make sure.
-You know the rules of President.
-I do.
The cards slide so smoothly.
He's like a real dealer.
-Jimmy, do you know President?
-I do.
Is this mine?
Twos are the strongest.
Threes are the weakest.
If someone plays a pair, you have to
play a pair with a higher number.
One for you... That's all.
We have to play all our cards?
-That's right.
-We just...
We play our cards, right?
I have more cards to start off with.
Give some to me.
You told me to deal two at a time.
-These cards are a bit unusual.
-Give one back.
I have three...
What happened?
What was that?
-What? Why?
-What did you laugh at?
He's laughing hard.
-What got you?
-What made you laugh?
No.
It was Junior...
Junior wrote this and showed it to me.
Just for me.
"Ichiro."
ICHIRO
You must really like Ichiro.
-What a way to go.
-That scared me.
I couldn't see what happened on our side.
It was that.
He wrote "Ichiro."
What's so funny?
How is that funny?
No, it's just that I've been
hooked on Ichiro the whole time.
I mean...
I never expected him to write "Ichiro."
Yellow.
I have no excuse.
Wait. It's not yellow.
-Orange.
-It's orange.
But I haven't done...
Want to see?
-I had no idea he'd do this.
-Okay, let's take a look.
-That was so sudden.
-I never thought he'd do that.
That pretty much goes for everything.
That's one of the fundamentals of comedy.
I mean, I never guessed
he'd write the same name.
But he kept going for it.
Like I said,
that's a fundamental of comedy.
"Doing the unexpected."
That's what's funny, right?
You told me to deal two at a time.
-These cards are a bit unusual.
-Give one back.
I have three...
He's totally laughing.
Totally laughing.
He's laughing, no doubt.
I couldn't help it.
After all, I never expected it.
Even if that is a fundamental...
-"Ichiro."
-You're all doing well.
You're holding back your laughter,
but still making it funny as a whole.
-You are.
-Thanks.
I wonder who put this here.
You are scary.
Here, of all places.
Seriously.
You are so nasty. I did nothing to you.
No way. That's definitely going to get me.
-You have no more chances.
-You can't do this to me!
You're setting me up to fail!
I'm not, honestly.
I'm really not.
That egg is of no importance.
You've got cards.
-Can we look at the cards now?
-Go for it.
Well, we've had some interruptions.
-There's one left.
-I know.
-Jimmy starts.
-He won't last.
-One more card.
-Pick up your card.
Jimmy won't make it.
It's like he's sprained both ankles.
It's hard to tell which cards are strong.
Try looking at the egg once more.
Once more.
-The egg.
-I will.
I wonder who put it there.
Kobayashi did.
Not "Ichiro"?
You know...
He said one look was enough.
I looked.
-One more time.
-I did.
-One more time?
-I already did.
-One more time.
-I did.
One last time. Please.
Okay, I'll look.
-Okay?
-It's just an ordinary egg.
It's just an egg.
For real?
Wait a minute, wait a minute!
Wait!
I haven't done any of my bits.
You can't do that!
-What was that?
-What was it?
You guys can't do that!
Who would've guessed
the egg would get him?
-You laughed out loud.
-It was there from the start.
No way!
I told you to stop talking about the egg!
What's funny about that egg?
It hit my funny bone!
-It's not funny at all!
-Not at all!
-It's just a plain egg, sitting there.
-No, it's not.
Usually when you put something
on a scale, it tips to one side,
-but this one stays flat.
-It's not a scale.
It's a candle holder.
It's a candle holder?
That's what got you?
He thought it was a scale!
I couldn't figure out why it didn't tip.
I was thinking, "That's wrong."
-"What's with this egg?"
-You made it funny yourself.
You thought, "What a light egg!"?
"What a light egg!"
That would be funny.
That kept nagging me.
This is unbelievable!
You are unbelievable.
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
I haven't done anything yet.
You laughed so hard!
-I've done nothing.
-You laughed hard.
-He laughed without even looking at it.
-No way.
-He didn't look?
-Not at the end.
-But I was...
-Imagining was enough.
-One more time.
-I did.
-One more time?
-I already did.
-One more time.
-Okay, I'll look.
-Okay?
-It's just an ordinary egg.
It's just an egg.
-You totally laughed.
-What's so funny?
Why couldn't you hold it in?
I brought so many things to do.
For nothing.
-But you can be a zombie.
-Okay, I'll be a zombie.
-Take 'em all down.
-He'll get us all.
-Zombies can laugh all they want.
-He'll be a scary zombie.
You're right. He will make a scary zombie.
A scary zombie indeed!
-He brought such a big bag.
-You all play dirty!
They did team up on you a bit.
No doubt... You, too!
But you were too easy to take down.
-You were so easy.
-For real? I was too easy?
It's a big bag,
but there's nothing inside.
It's virtually empty.
So, he's leaving.
-What the hell?
-Good try.
Go to the Zombie Room.
-"Ichiro" and an egg.
-That was fast.
I didn't do a single thing.
Junior and the other guys...
They use skills.
They kept going on the attack,
so I thought,
"I have to stay clear of them."
The plan was to bide my time,
and make sure I didn't laugh
in the meantime,
but they beat me, and now...
I'm disappointed, but...
The fact I'm so weak is...
It's like...
I mean...
Well...
It's...
Happy New Year.
-Happy New Year.