Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!
In the end it's all about the counters.
It doesn't matter who takes the offensive.
That doesn't decide anything.
That's why when the counter attack starts,
that's when it gets decided.
All players decide whether they want to lead,
or follow someone's lead.
And if they do so,
they can more or less get in control.
I see! I see! I see!
Seiji is laughing though!
I'm always ready to go first,
in that sort of mindset every time.
I'm almost never actively defending myself.
It's more like I want to at least survive.
I started getting ready yesterday and was done this morning.
So I'm sleep deprived.
I'm a little worried about that,
I might even fall asleep in the middle of it all.
So Sheena Mikan says...
"Wanna do a sixty-nine?"
That's an orange for the Chihara brothers!
This is bad.
Wanna play a game?
There's more?
Yeah, sorry.
I don't know how to use this controller.
It's kind of hard to figure out.
Keep it up!
Go! Go!
Start! Start!
That's the same thing!
He did it!
Let's go!
He did it.
Well, it's just that everyone...
You were all smiling somewhat.
So that's a yellow for everyone.
No way!
That's a lot.
Just... can you leave it for later?
Leave it for later. Seriously.
It'll be more effective later.
Yeah, that was kind of a killer blow.
Wait a minute.
Here we go.
Let's do it again.
You want to keep going?
I do.
Wait, just...
Chance, take a look.
Sorry, sorry.
Yeah, that yellow thing...
That's right, sorry, sorry.
Okay, here we go.
What's that below his head?
Is that a sock?
See?
That's the same mistake as before.
Why does his face get all huge?
This is just a mess!
It's the same as before!
You can't do the same thing.
Ah, it's different. It's different!
No, no, no.
That jump is impossible.
— It's huge!
— Isn't it impossible?
You can't make it!
You can barely make it, probably.
— No way, no way.
— It's too wide.
That's genius.
That's god's helping hand.
— Who was it?
— It wasn't me.
Not me.
— It's really not me.
— Not me either.
Not me.
— Who was it?
— No way!
So no one was it?
I managed to hold it in.
So did I.
— You, Chance?
— No, I didn't smile.
It opened.
— I held it.
— Who was it then?
So... It wasn't anyone.
There it is!
Again?
It was funny, so I just came here.
— It looked fun.
— Don't do that, man!
It looked funny.
I panicked back there!
That scared me!
I thought I would get sent off!
Please don't do that!
Isn't this game too deadly?
We still have many stages,
so why don't you join us at least once, Matsumoto-san?
No, no, no, no.
Fine by me, but someone might end up losing.
This is too much.
It's really too much.
But it's pretty fun, so why did you come here?
Why did you come here?
I just wanted to enter this world.
Are we little kids or something?
But you were all smiling just a little.
It can't be helped, though.
You weren't laughing out loud, so I've decided you're all safe.
I really wanted to laugh so bad.
I wanted to laugh too bad, for real.
I know, I know.
This is really fucking stressful!
Just give us a break already!
It can't be helped though.
— Are we gonna keep going?
— Please no more.
I'm scared.
— There's more?
— Wait a second.
This is rough.
Wait a couple more hours.
Do it after I come back from the bathroom.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Once we try a few other things in a couple hours maybe.
But we might not have much concentration by then.
Here we go.
He's puking.
Please stop this, man.
Right?
— Why did he eat so much?
— How many bowls did he eat?
— Eight.
— Eight?!
And he didn't even use any condiments or anything.
None at all.
I saw him use some, just a little.
Ah, really?
We're almost at 1:30 hours,
and there's a Hummer right there.
— Whose is it?
— Hide-san's?
I want you to see a reaction.
He's annoying.
It's just...
That's why we told him not to eat so many.
He didn't have to eat them.
There are six bowls here.
So he's going to keep going after puking?
He's a real monster.
Okay, ready?
The reactions goes like...
You press it here once.
— Okay!
I think he kind of gets it!
Yeah, well... I guess so, yeah.
So you're doing it yourself?
It doesn't have to be me, though.
No, no, I meant the controller.
Can I leave that to someone else?
— Should I do it?
— Sure.
It's better if someone else does it.
— You okay?
— Yeah, I'm okay.
Stop it already.
Fujita, stop it, man.
— But I'm hungry.
— You were puking.
— But it's out already.
— You forced it out.
— No, it just came out.
— Don't force yourself to eat.
Besides, remember Amazon is looking at us from abroad.
I see.
— I get it now.
— That's right, that's right...!
This reaction will be broadcast in hundreds of countries.
That's fast.
Wait till it gets there.
It's not there yet.
Not everything is there yet.
It's best if you tell us you're ready.
"Okay, ready" or something.
When it's done.
Ouch!
He's tying them.
Ah, he's pinching himself!
Is right here okay?
Okay?
Using all of them at the same time is better.
Like this.
That's right.
Wait, that one fell.
— Doesn't it hurt?
— It hurts, it hurts.
I got it on this one.
I can't get it on this one.
This one.
That's enough! That looks painful.
"It looks painful"?
It can't be helped, that's just how he is.
Are you okay?
That's a lot of them.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Wasn't there someone like this abroad?
I feel like there's a popular image like this somewhere.
Okay!
Junior.
— Do it.
— Ah that's Junior-san's job, right?
— Junior, it's the other way.
— Go ahead.
That doesn't hurt, though.
It's in reverse.
— Is that all it has?
— That's weak.
Pretty weak.
It's the tires...
They're not moving forward at all.
The tires are just...
They're stuck, they're stuck.
Wouldn't it be better to put something below it?
It's just sliding in place.
The tires shouldn't spin there like that.
Wanna throw something in there?
Are we gonna do it?
Hey, don't put that there.
I'm still eating it.
That's my ginger.
Look, Kawamoto.
Ginger's not going to work.
I just said that I was still eating it!
It's to stop it from sliding.
Ah, I get it.
I see.
That might work.
I'm still eating that.
You're spreading it the wrong way.
Maybe mustard would've been better?
— Ouch, ouch!
— Throw in some with the ginger.
Maybe a leek would've worked better.
It would've been the same.
We just need some moisture to prevent it from slipping.
A leek would've been worse, Kawamoto.
Ready? In that case...
That looks good.
It looks delicious.
It looks awful, though.
— Ready?
— "Dat's Tephanyaki!"
What's "tephan"?
Ready?
Aren't you waiting too much?
Give us a signal.
Do it.
That was the signal.
No, Koba.
Go ahead.
Just...
— You know the controls?
— I don't.
Then don't use it!
It's really easy!
I mean, I played with stuff like this a lot when I was little.
That's your generation, right.
I'm sure people your age did a lot.
It's a really simple controller.
It's easy to understand...
That's forward.
Give us the signal when you're ready.
Okay, go!
Let's go Fujimoto-san.
Hurry.
Go forward.
What are you doing?
Go! Go!
— Go, go, go, go!
— Hummer go
Go, Hummer, go.
Come on, let's go.
— There it is.
— It's just turning to the side.
Time to go, let's go.
Go forward, go forward.
No, no, not like that.
You just have to go straight ahead towards the camera.
— Go!
— You just have to—
Go! Please!
— I don't get this.
— Go!
Go!
Go...
— What?
— What kind of game is this anyways?
What the hell are you doing? What do you want to do?
Just move it forward.
And then we can get the reaction.
Do it yourself.
— It can't be helped.
— I don't get this.
— It's our first time.
— You just had to drive forward with the signal.
— Do it yourself...
— Just say go.
Say "Go" yourself.
Go!
It's not enough. It's not enough at all.
— It needs more horsepower.
— Something's not enough.
It's not moving at all.
Doesn't seem to be 4x4.
It's not enough, yeah.
It might work on the floor.
It's slipping.
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Something's just not working.
It doesn't have enough power.
— Sorry, it's just not...
— Even though it's supposed to be a Hummer.
It's supposed to be super powerful, though.
Yeah, but it's just not enough.
It's not meant to take this long though.
It's just weaker than expected.
Can someone else do it when it's down here?
Sure?
This is just...
Oshiro-san, get a little closer.
I just wanted this to pull on the clips,
have it hurt like hell and then get it over with.
Are you sure that's going to work?
Not even a Hummer could do this, though.
Do you guys have anything in mind?
For the meantime?
Well... this isn't recent, but...
This is the story from the first time I went to a brothel.
— You gonna tell that?
— In the meantime?
— Are you sure?
— It's not recent, though.
I was like 19.
It's from a long time ago, then.
That's right, that's right.
It was a brothel in Kawasaki.
Ah, in Kawasaki.
It was my first time, so I was like...
So I wanted to touch the girl, right?
Right, so... we entered the bathroom,
and I was going to touch her.
— Right there?
I thought it would be fine.
— That's annoying.
— That noise...
Is something triggering it?
I think it's the other way around.
Like the trigger is...
No, I mean, I think the original conversation is getting in the way right now.
This is the main event right now.
Junior-san is the main event.
So you tried to touch her?
I tried to touch her, and she slapped my hand,
and said "no way."
"Don't take the hand—"
I'm getting distracted.
It's an annoying sound.
So "no way"?
"Why are you touching me with your hands without washing them first?"
— She got really mad.
— That's just the etiquette.
It was the first time they told me I had to do it—
You didn't know since it was your first time.
That's what happens if you touch her out of nowhere.
It can't be helped.
So I washed my hands, and they were now clean.
Now I wondered if I could touch—
So you get it going when he raises his hand?
Maybe.
Every time he puts up his hands.
That's the trigger?
Maybe.
So she says "no way."
Ah, I knew it.
With the hand, yeah.
That's right.
Try speaking without doing that.
Try it.
Speak up normally without raising your hand.
Without raising my hand, right?
Just stay right there.
And so she says "no way!"
"You have to wash your entire body,"
"and touch me on the bed."
So she went to bed.
See?
We've confirmed it.
I guess that's it then.
Lower your hand and keep talking.
Just do it.
Like this?
Right.
Yeah, yeah. Try talking now.
So I washed myself thoroughly and went to bed.
And I was thinking she'd let me touch her now.
So I tried touching her—
Huh?
— Didn't you just smile?
— I didn't.
You definitely did.
He did it himself.
He sure did!
He self destructed!
Wait, you self destructed!
You definitely smiled!
He was smiling a lot!
No, that's just how the story goes, you know?
That's normal.
Yeah, but you can't do that either.
It's not "just normal".
There he is.
He was smiling, right?
But that was just how the story...
you know.
What a liar.
I can't do this either?
You were smiling knowingly.
You should've pressed the switch yourself.
Having junior press it was...
it's pretty much suicide.
Besides, you were smiling pretty obviously back there, even with all those clips!
For real.
I don't know for sure.
Why don't we take a look?
He was smiling for sure!
So I washed myself thoroughly and I went to bed,
and I was thinking that I'd be able to touch her.
So I tried touching her—
He's obviously smiling!
He's smiling a lot!
Even though it wasn't funny at all!
What the hell was I thinking?
The story wasn't funny at all!
Just what was I thinking?
Even though you couldn't really see his face,
you could just tell.
This has to be a red!
Wait a second!
Wait, wait, wait...
Okay, so...
What was the story about in the end?
I can't take these off.
That's your own fault!
You should've practiced at home.
Practiced?
Of course you should've!
I should've practiced this stuff?
Of course!
At least check its power!
At least check if it was enough.
Or stand on the chair and drop it from there.
One time was...
It might've been clean and funny.
Especially without knowing your expression.
Just once...
Okay, take them off.
Try to be gentle.
This is a bother.
There's no point if you go that far and don't know what to do.
You should've ran a simulation.
That's right!
These are full of drool, man!
Do this before getting revived.
The drool's just...
These are so slippery!
It couldn't be helped!
They were there for a long time!
And he had his mouth wide open.
They're full of drool.
That's right.
Thanks, bro.
What bro?
Don't call me bro.
Bro. Bro.
No, no, I'm more like your dad.
Isn't Shinsuke the dad?
That's how Misono calls him.
You drool far too much!
Sorry, bro.
Don't call me bro.
Stop it with all that Hexagon family Fujimon nonsense. (Editor's Note 1 - Check out the Patreon for in-depth explanations)
The family's not active anymore.
And they used to get along so well, too.
The family's not...?
What do you mean they're not active anymore?
So they don't call themselves that anymore?
I guess so.
But they got along really well!
Wait, what family are you talking about here?
The Hexagon family.
They don't do it anymore.
So the entire family dissolves without the wife? (EN: 2)
Stop it. It's getting dark.
Give me a second,
there's something I want to practice.
— Sure. Go ahead.
— Is it okay?
Can you help me out?
Let's do it.
Anyone here have a good swing?
A bat swing.
— I'm not great.
— Not at all.
I used to play baseball.
Shouji?
Wait...
A swing?
Is this an experiment?
Not really an experiment but...
More like practice.
See, I can cut the nerves in my ass.
My lower body in general.
— What do you mean by "cut"?
— Like it doesn't feel much pain.
Can you get rid of pain altogether?
So it's like a paralysis?
So I've barely managed to do this by myself.
And I think I'm starting to get better.
So can I ask you to take a test swing?
You just have to swing at least once.
What are you going to do?
That's it, that's it.
It's great like that.
That's pretty intense.
What if you do it facing that way?
Yeah, this way.
If he's right handed.
— Are you gonna do that?
— Are you sure?
Wait a second.
Until my nerves are numb.
Are you sure I can do it hard?
Make sure you do it as hard as you can.
— I'm gonna do it for real.
— Yeah, choose a good place.
Around here?
Here I go.
Wait a second. They're not fully numb yet.
So that's how you do it?
So he's blocking his pain receptors?
What's he doing?
Is he stopping his nervous system?
Wait, not— not yet, not yet.
It still hurts!
— Ouch!
— What are you doing?
You didn't wait at all!
I was just in the middle of it!
Do it after that!
— Is your ass numb right now?
— I guess, kind of.
You wanna go?
Ready? It's one strike.
Are you sure?
Are you really sure?
Yeah, since my ass is numb anyways.
— It's numb?
— Fucking hell!!!
— He's really pissed off.
Fucking hell! Fuck you!!
— That's a bad pun.
— He's pissed off.
Fuck fuck!! Don't get pissed off!!
He's pissed off.
I'm not pissed off at all.
Sometimes...
Sometimes it's okay to have a little fun.
What was that?
So after they destroyed his ass with the bat,
he said his ass was numb,
and that's pronounced the same as being "pissed off" in Japanese.
So that's what you were talking about?
It's a pun with his ass being numb and him being pissed off.
I wasn't pissed off, though.
I don't wear Gucci clothes either.
I wasn't affected at all.
So you just do that sometimes?
I don't do shit that stupid.
But I know this guy wears Gucci for stupid things like T-shirts and stuff like that.
Right?
Not at all. I don't buy Gucci T-shirts.
You do that? I guess it's just because you have this
kind of crazy approach to life in general, huh?
I mean, you can interpret it like that if you want to.
One of the cute things about him is how easily embarrassed he gets, though.
Yeah, that's true.
But he's also more experienced than any of us.
Thank you Koba-san.
Come on, leave me alone.
Picasso was also kind of weird.
Come on, just...
— You're a genius!
— Are you numb?
I'm numb.
Why do you just thank Koba?
Wait a minute.
Yeah, it's fully numb.
Are you numb?
That's sad.
That strike was just...
I thought my grandma had bumped into me.
Like when she was walking behind me.
That's about how much it hurt.
A silver car?
One of those electric silver car things.
Electric?
I didn't know they were electric!
Yeah, I guess.
I thought those weren't electric.
I didn't expect that at all.
When your grandma bumps into you,
it hurts... it hurts about this much.
So it was like a grandma, then.
Try doing it one more time.
How? How hard?
A grandma hurts about this much, right?
And an electric cart hurts about that much.
I wasn't smiling! I was holding it in!
You've been struggling for a while!
I was holding it!
You were smiling!
It was pretty close.
I held it!
You couldn't do it!
Eh?!
You were smiling the whole time.
All the time!
He was smiling all the time.
He was smiling all along.
I held it in!
You were smiling.
No way anymore!
I guess this means...
Well, let's just take a look.
How? How hard?
A grandma hurts about this much, right?
And an electric cart hurts about this much.
He's definitely smiling.
He's smiling right there.
I'm holding it, I'm holding it!
You were absolutely smiling!
He was fucking beaming!
Damn it...
Okay, Chihara Junior.
So he's out?
You're out!
— In two hours?
— Two hours!
So this point goes to Coo-chan
He's gaining points.
So this means that he's becoming quite powerful.
That's right.
Yeah, we still have four hours left, too.
— Still four hours?
— It's over!
Let's go, Junior.
Ah, that hurts.
I didn't think you'd be the first to go, though!
That hurts.
I'm bad at this!
Who the hell pops their mouth with their fingers
in this day and age anyways?
That must be the first time I've seen it in this era.
Stop it Fujimoto-san.
What?
To be honest, if anything, I'd like to see him react to something.
Yeah, let's try to pinpoint who's closer to laughing.
There's a technique to it.
It's impossible to figure out how to do it
this close to other people.
Who was close to laughing?
You're eating again?!
Didn't you puke earlier?!
We heard you puking like crazy from here!
You definitely puked earlier!
You were puking, right?
I was just slurping.
What? Slurping from a toilet stew or what?
Yeah, I was slurping from the toilet.
That's why I have to...
Of course you weren't.
Of course not.
What the hell?
Mind your own business!
I can't do whatever I please?
Well, I guess...
Yeah.
Instead of butting in why don't you play along?
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, I don't like Fujita to start butting in.
Because you're probably going to laugh eventually!
That's right!
I get it know.
I'm going to play along with you from now on.
I'm going to play along now.
You're really going bald! Look at this!
He's just like a baby!
It really looks like a baby's head!
He's totally a baby!
That's so cute!
He's really adorable.
Just look at this!
It looks totally different from this angle.
He's adorable.
He's really adorable.
And he does this face at a time like this.
That's what he looks like when you turn him that way.
When you turn him...
That's right, that's right.
But despite that, he's a serious cheater.
That sounds like a threat but it's meant to be a compliment?
— I saw it in Nagoya and Chiba.
— And a double in Chiba, too.
— A double?
— Like with two different people?
So like a threesome?
That's just what I heard.
Not at all, not at all.
What the hell are you saying?
— Not at all!
— So you did them in order?
There was no overlap at all!
And where did they like you to touch them?
You should ask them yourself! I'm not telling you!
— Why not?
— I'm sure they told you anyways.
You want me to ask you where your ex wife liked it?
Well, that's...
I don't really care.
— That's normal with a couple.
— Yeah, couples talk about that stuff.
When it's someone else...
What do your partners like about you, then?
Like, if you're, if you're...
If you think about it,
what do you think they liked about you?
Everything!
Of course not.
— Are you stupid?
— I'm sure you just had beads in your cock.
I didn't!
Then they wouldn't like you, normally.
You guys fuck? Like, you know how when you get older...
— You don't fuck and—
— They just cuddle!
Yeah, they just cuddle, pretty much.
Like when old guys go to a brothel,
and don't do anything, instead just talk,
hold hands and stuff like that.
Is it like that?
We fuck like rabbits.
Well, guess that's why you're not working.
Like rabbits?
Can you do something else at least?
That's nasty...
Haven't heard that in years.
So you don't kiss?
We start with a kiss.
You start with a kiss?
Isn't this kind of embarrassing?
It's true, though.
Can you show us how you kiss?
Just kiss the air or something.
— Why, though?
— Then do it with Kawamoto.
Do it with him!
— Where's your vest?
— Over there.
Should I do that next?
Want to wear the vest, Kawamoto?
You're wearing the vest?
My vest?
You don't mind, right?
Sorry for touching it.
It's heavier than I expected!
It's for protection against junkies and thugs.
Look at the back, though.
The back's just fabric.
You can only get away if they attack you from the front.
It's heavy.
What was that?
It looks good on you.
So what kind of kiss?
Just imagine you're kissing your mistress.
You know that term's kind of fucked up.
It's not that great, yeah.
Then how should we call her?
— Your lover?
— Your girlfriend?
— By her name.
— Because if we called her your girlfriend,
wouldn't your wife get angry? Your main wife?
That's still kind of...
Kind of weird.
My wife is my wife.
Then what do we call her?
— His partner...
— His, his girlfriend.
— What's a good word, then?
— Your pussy?
— I think "pussy" might work here.
— That's too much.
Stop it with this "pussy" bullshit already.
Come on.
— What did you call her?
— He said by her name.
— Of course, of course.
— So by the name?
Then just call Kawamoto by his name.
No way! Doing that at this age?
I'm feeling uneasy.
Why the hell is your mouth dry?!
Are you nervous?!
Kawamoto will be your partner.
Does he look like her?
You're grabbing his head and everything?
With your huge hands?
Yeah!
Don't grab his head like that!
Isn't this getting kind of erotic?
I love this kind of shit.
— Okay, show us!
— He's getting pretty aggressive.
I'm the kind of guy that opens his mouth before getting started.
I go like "mm".
And then you dive in?
Do it already!
That's lewd.
— What the hell is going on?
— Something came out.
— Ginger?
— Ginger.
That's dirty...
Did you put it in your mouth, Seiji-san?
Let's stop this already.
Yeah, that's enough.
That's like when spies get poisoned and shit.
No, I was just wondering...
Why did I end up becoming Seiji-san's cheating partner?
You just give off that vibe!
— For real?
— You're just a symbol.
Since she's—
Since we don't have any fat grannies like that.
— Who are you talking about?
There was this big fat granny,
And she always ate full of snot and everything.
— Sugawara-san?
— Yeah, Sugawara-san!
No, Sugawara-san was more like...
— Her tongue would stick out?
— Regularly?
So her tongue was always sticking out?
Her tongue...
I've heard her tongue tends to stick out, yeah.
It's sticking out!
There it is...
Huh?
Why are you sticking yours out?
Why are you doing that?
That's a huge tongue.
What the fuck are you doing?
No clue, I just...
I was just told that I looked like Seiji-san's cheating partner.
And then I also just...
He does that a lot.
How do you do that?
— With my tongue.
— You use your tongue as a flute?
The tongue flute champion in Europe told me
I was the first Japanese he had met that could do it.
What's a flute champion, anyways?
It's not in Japan. In Europe it's some sort of performance.
Can I do one more short sound?
— Do it, do it!
— Alright!
He's god's tongue.
Kawashima-kun. Can you help me with one?
Kawashima-kun?
This was half a year ago.
There was this elementary school kid going to school,
I love kids by the way.
And I was telling him to do his best for the day,
— You called out to him, right?
— Right, so I was patting his head,
— Telling him to do his best,
— You shouldn't do that
Especially in this day and age.
And he had this alarm on his backpack,
— like an anti-theft alarm or something?
— Yeah, I know what that is.
And it started ringing.
You made it ring.
And that anti-theft alarm sounded like...
— So Kawashima-san is the school kid?
— Right.
What should I do?
Good luck at school!
Do your best today!
Good luck at—
He's great!
He's really good.
That's amazing!
And so I ran away.
You can't run away like that!
Well, I just...
I was just patting his head.
Can you do something really loud?
Like a bomb sound or something.
Like those really huge sounds.
Wait a minute, okay?
— He has something?
— No way!
No way he has an actual bomb or something.
So what if we have Ikko-san do the anti-theft alarm?
Like if Ikko-san did the alarm...
Oh, he's back.
You okay there?
I'm fine.
Alright.
Which one?
Okay, Ikko-san.
You, you do it.
You can do it, Chance-san.
I'm okay.
I'm just watching now.
Chance are you doing something?
I was just watching. Go on, do something.
Just go with the flow.
What the hell are you doing?
What are you trying to say?
Do it.
Just say it with your mouth.
That's a huge trophy.
A shakuhachi? (EN: 3)
I won the shakuhachi contest.
You do the anti-theft.
No, no, no.
Oshiro, you can't just bring up that sound out of nowhere.
— Since you're doing the shakuhachi already.
So don't start just like that.
Wait, why are you getting naked all of a sudden?
Why- Why are you getting naked?
— The last one in my sound series.
— Why did you undress?
This is a loud sound.
I had it wrong.
— Right, sure.
— It's loud.
So why did you get naked?
Okay, are we doing this?
Okay, make a sound.
So this is what we're doing now?
This is the last one in my sound series.
Sorry for the trouble.
Wow, you've got a pretty fit body, huh?
Are you insane?!
This?
It's just that...
So I'm going to do a few sounds with my back.
— With your back?
— Yes.
You were doing this at the 2nd street theater, right?
He's been doing it for that long?
I haven't seen this since about my debut.
Okay, this is the sound of a toilet plunger.
A toilet plunger sounds good.
I told you.
That sounds like a fart.
Next comes the sound of a horse galloping.
Neigh! Neigh!
No, that sounds like sex.
This is hell.
Next comes a toad.
This is a toad.
Whoa, it's coming from here.
Croak croak!
I don't understand that.
The "croak croak" isn't necessary.
This doesn't sound like a toad.
What are you doing?
Are you making a vacuum?
A vacuum.
You can't do it without some fat.
You have to gain some weight.
A creaking door from a horror film.
Those old doors, right?
— Is it coming?
Ah, sorry, it's just not...
— That's not it at all!
— One more time, one more time!
— Can you do this?
— Yeah.
— What's he doing?
— That's just a fart.
And finally, the sound of a cessna landing. (EN: 4)
— That's the last one right?
— A cessna that's—
The one right now was just air?
Matsuo...
You let some air out.
Here goes the cessna.
Ah sorry, just one more time.
Sorry, I let it escape.
One more.
Just one more time like...
There it is, there it is.
Ah, it went that way, sorry.
Last one, a last one.
Should I take them off altogether?
I wonder about this, though!
— Who was it?
— Fujita, right?
Fujita was smiling for a while already.
— And Fujimoto too.
— No, I held it.
That was pretty good!
It was rough.
You all managed to hold it in for a while.
I saw Matsuo do it...
He was smiling all the time!
I didn't know at all!
And also Fujita.
To be honest, I was in a pretty tight spot at the end.
Don't say it.
This is a fart.
And finally, the sound of a cessna landing!
— He said the last one, right?
— A cessna...
Are you making that sound with air?
You let some air out.
Here goes the cessna.
I'm sorry, just one more time.
The air's going out, sorry.
Just one more time.
It's gonna go like...
There it is, there it is.
Sorry, it went that way.
One last time, I'm sorry.
Fujita was in trouble, huh?
Fujita, you were screwed!
No way!
Wait a second!
Come on, come on!
At least make it work out, come on!
Okay, Fujita and Matsuo get...
Come on!
It's getting pretty warmed up.
Everyone else has a yellow?
— Yellow.
— I'm orange.
— Orange.
— Orange too.
Only Ku-kun has nothing.
— Nothing?
— No color.
He has none.
He's been sneaking a laugh here and there.
But I've been holding it like.
He's gotten like this.
I've never done that!
Never!
Everyone has a yellow?
I got one.
Okay, let's watch some porn to change the mood.
You're gonna watch here?
At least pay some money.
They're free, though.
I guess so, yeah.
Damn, it was too hot.
His nose is bleeding.
Damn it, yeah.
It's too hot.
It's close, but the color's a bit off.
It's from Tokyu Hands? (EN: 5)
I made it myself.
— How?
— I used some pigment and... it hurts.
You mixed in some shrimp, too?
Yeah, it looks like shrimp.
When you boil them.
It hurts!
Looks like boiled shrimp.
Recently, I got a call from a friend.
Yeah?
— So...
— Excuse me.
My friend's company wants some work with Yoshimoto or something.
— You have a lighter?
— We don't have any here.
— I was wondering
if I was in the wrong with something that happened recently.
Whatever it was, you were in the wrong.
For sure.
It's over. It's over!
Listen, listen.
I was riding the bullet train.
— The bullet train.
— Yeah.
So, I had to go to the bathroom.
That's your fault.
— It's over!
— So I was in the wrong?
No wait, no way it's my fault!
And so...
I went to the bathroom.
— Why did you take it?
— What did you do?
So the sign read vacant, right?
So I opened the door,
and there was this like twenty year old sitting on the toilet,
and he was using some earphones and looking at his phone,
and he was jerking off.
— Where was that?
— The bullet train's toilet.
He was like this on the toilet.
I think he forgot to lock the door.
So I opened it and he was just like this.
And since he had earphones on, he didn't notice at first.
But I guess he noticed the air, turned,
and closed the door.
I didn't really understand, but after seeing him jerking off,
I just apologized and closed it.
But thinking about it...
Was it my fault?
What do you think?
He was jerking off.
— It was your fault.
— I think it was your fault.
Because you wanted to go to the bathroom at that moment.
It's your fault.
I didn't do anything wrong, though!
He was the one jerking off!
What do you mean by jerking off?
Jerking off is jerking off.
Isn't it jacking off?
It's jerking off.
Jacking off?
Honestly, both are the same.
Are you sure he was doing it?
Do you know what he normally looks like when he does it?
There's no way you can tell he was doing it!
I think you're a little weird.
I think you're onto something.
Since you don't know what he looks like
— When you apologize,
— I'm telling you he was jerking off.
You have to say that out loud, man.
I thought that was a ticking time bomb.
— What happened?
— What are you doing?
That scared me.
— What's wrong?
— What happened?
— Matsuo...
— Something happened?
Something happened.
What is it?
— Where?
— Matsuo?
— Where?!
I'm asking you where!
— Where you are?
— Where?!
This is...
The studio.
— Well, this is the studio.
— I'm asking you where!
I'm telling you this is the studio!
The "Documental" set!
I'm asking you where!!
— It's the studio!
— It's Wangan Studio! (EN: 6)
I'm asking you where!
We're telling you!
Where?!
— It's Wangan...
— I'm asking you where!
Where?! Where?!
— Wangan!
— Shut up! It's Wangan!
— Where?!
— Shut up, idiot!
— Wangan!
— Where?!
Where?
Wangan!
Where?!
Where did you come from?
— Where do you want to go?
— Are you talking about this place?
I'm asking you where!
Where?!
— Shut up for now!
— Where?!
What? Tokyo...
I'm asking you where!
Where?!
Tell me where!!
— What do you mean?!
— I feel sorry for him.
Where?!
Are you talking about this place?
I'm asking you where! Tell me!!
— What's with this guy?
— Where?!
Is he stupid?
Isn't he spitting on you?
I'm asking you where!!
I'm begging you!! Tell me!!
I'll tell you, I'll tell you.
Where?!
I don't know that guy.
I'm begging you!
I'm beggin you!! Where?!
No, no. What are you...?
I'm asking you where!!
Are you talking about Tokyo?
Well, we're in Odaiba.
Or more specifically, in Wangan Studio.
— He's really Aladdin.
— Broadly speaking.
— He looks like an aunt.
— For real.
Calm down.
Where did you come from?
What?
I'm asking you where!!
Calm down, calm down.
Have something to drink.
I'm asking you where!!
— You don't remember anything?
— Drink some tea.
You don't remember anything?
Where did you come from?
Yeah, yeah.
Huh?
You remembered?
Where?!
I'm asking you where?!
It's okay, it's okay.
— Where?!
— We're telling you!
Please tell me!!
— I'm begging you!
— Wangan!
We're in Wangan!
We're in Wangan, man!!
That's good, that's good.
— We're in Wangan!
— Where?!
That's good!
— This is Wangan!!
— Where?!
— We're in Wangan!
— We're in Wangan!!
Ah damn it.
You have to top him, somehow.
— Where?!
— We're in Wangan!!
This is a good duel!
They're dying, they're dying.
— They're gonna die.
— This is a good duel.
Where?!
We're in Wangan!!
Wangan Wangan Wangan Wangan!!
— Wangan!!
— Come on!
He's gonna die.
— Wangan!!
— Come on!
He's gonna die.
Wangan Wangan! This is Wangan!!
Wangan Wangan Wangan!!
Wangan Wangan!
Huh?
Alright! He did it!
— He did it! He won!
— Nice!
That was amazing!
Really nice!
— That sucked.
— Amazing.
That was completely amazing.
— Great!
— What an amazing power!
That was powerful.
What a great counter.
Come on!
That was amazing!
It was great.
It was incredible.
That was power vs power!
— Thank you very much.
— Pushed to the edge.
That was a nice try.
And you tried from the very beginning.
— It was an amazing counter.
— It was too hard.
It was terrible.
I had to put an end to him.
You're all hoarse now!
His voice is done for!
His throat is all messed up.
I guess this is just that...
Shouji is amazing.
I think this raises Shouji's name.
Where?!
We're in Wangan!!
Wangan! Wangan!
— Wangan!!
— Come on!
Wangan! Wangan! This is Wangan!!
Wangan! Wangan! Wangan! Wangan!
Wangan! Wangan!
Alright! He did it!
It was too rough!
It definitely looked rough, yeah!
It was too hard!
That's Shouji's specialty.
And even though there was some assistance,
this is just completely
We had to take him down.
— Huh? Matso?
— This is your first one?
No, I got an orange earlier.
Really Ma-chan?! An orange?
— That's right, Matsuo.
— One from earlier, right?
So I had to attack since I had an orange.
So you ended up falling for the counter.
Matsuo! You're out!
Shouji's points look like trouble!
And also Fujita's awful nosebleed.
I'm never going to forget that.
It should've been a little thicker.
— Yeah, right.
— Yeah.
— I guess I was losing in a way.
— It's like looking at your sheets
after she finally goes home.
Kinda gross.
You've had girls like that over?
I love them!
No, that's not what I meant!
Are you still a virgin?
And we're still joking with Ma-chan!
Are you okay? Aren't the big shots at Amazon gonna get mad?
I'm taking this with me.
That was my most recent "love story".
You liar!
That's a filthy love story!
That's not about love!
That's frustrating.
I was ready to do a lot more.
I wanted to go further than that.
— Where?!
— Wangan!
— Wangan!!
Where?!
We're in Wangan!!
Wangan!!
I wasn't expecting Shouji-san to get there.
We're in Wangan!!
The moment Shouji came running towards me I was already in trouble.
I kept thinking that this was bad.
I think that was the moment I realized I was screwed.
I was thinking that it was impossible to get out of that.
I was just hoping he'd get it over with soon.
Wangan! Wangan! Wangan! Wangan!
Alright!
I didn't expect to get such an amazing counter.
I couldn't think about it.
That hurts like hell!!
He's gone already?
Is he a dying cat?
This is...
Come on you...