THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
Kasuga is amazing, isn't he?
It may seem like he's just our puppet.
We give him the ideas.
We tell him what to do.
But his ability to fulfill those requests
is incredible.
He's always there with
just the right intensity.
He's mind-blowing.
Even just listening to his voice
is enough to crack me up.
My groin has never been featured
so much in my whole life.
-It fits right inside.
-It's curry rice.
That's too much.
Nobody can keep a straight face at that!
I actually feel as though
I've now gone on to
a higher level as a comedian.
-Show us again.
-Where is it?
It's right here.
LAST EPISODE'S LOSERS:
RG, TERUMOTO GOTO, YOSHIMASA IWAHASHI
RG, red card!
-Are you moving the markets to Toyosu?
-Not anymore.
-Really? Where will it go?
-Jakuzure.
Goto, red card!
LAST EPISODE'S LOSERS:
RG, TERUMOTO GOTO, YOSHIMASA IWAHASHI
Iwahashi!
Red card!
I'm finished!
-Here we go.
-Okay.
Ready, start.
Yamamoto.
There's something
I never quite understood.
Why did you take time off?
-Me?
-Yes.
Do you really want me to tell you?
I never heard why.
I just stopped seeing you on TV.
-It happened in 2006.
-Okay.
I tripped up.
You tripped up?
You fell over?
Down the stairs?
-Not exactly.
-Okay.
It was exactly 11 years ago.
Okay.
I was...
I just...
What does that mean?
Did you do something?
I suppose you could say
that I did something.
What did you do?
Sexual misconduct.
What do you mean by "sexual misconduct"?
Akiyama.
He's in trouble already.
-Sorry for bringing it up.
-No, not at all.
What are you sucking on?
Those pills from before.
No, no, no.
-Akiyama?
-Probably.
-Why?
-I'm in trouble.
Seriously, he's been sucking on
those pills the whole time.
-Don't you have a few?
-A few what?
Cards.
Seriously? That wasn't anything...
-Is that an orange?
-I thought I'd be fine.
But when I saw those two dots...
I really am still sucking on them.
But how could you still be sucking on
those pills?
The atmosphere was great there.
It was a good atmosphere, right?
That's what we want.
There was tension in the air, too.
And Kasuga has been away the whole time.
The fact he's been away the whole time
is what's funny.
He can't stop fiddling around.
Let's take a look.
What are you sucking on?
Those pills from before.
That was Akiyama's laugh.
When you think about it,
the fact he's still sucking on
those pills is really...
-That bit ended ages ago.
-Right?
Chewing them was part of the joke,
but he didn't chew.
I know.
Damn!
Akiyama, red card!
-Damn!
-It's getting real now.
It sure is.
You really do have a chance of winning.
Less than two hours remain.
-Don't come back as a zombie.
-I will return as a zombie.
Don't return as a zombie.
-Don't come back.
-I will. As a zombie.
Don't you forget it.
I'm so disappointed and frustrated
right now.
I still had a lot of tricks in my bag.
It feels like I didn't give it
everything I could have.
This is so frustrating.
But there really was nothing
that I could do.
You can try to hold back,
but when it's funny, it's funny.
My whole body started to crack up.
It was impossible.
It's time to restart.
When will the zombies...
-It's a little bleak in here now.
-Yeah. Things were more lively before.
-Has it begun?
-Yes.
What is he doing? Seriously.
He decided not to wear that top?
Actually, he gave up on wearing
that whole outfit.
That Roman gladiator look.
He decided on a cowboy. No?
If Kasuga doesn't hurry up,
we'll never get to do Zombie Time.
He put on that hat again. After all this.
He really wants to wear
that hat, apparently.
Now it's off again. He changes his mind.
Then he picks up something else.
And he'll put it back down.
Come on, Kasuga.
This is funny too, but look.
Now he's got that back on.
He was wearing a matching top before,
but he took it off.
And what's that thing around his neck?
That protector thing.
You're going with that, right?
You'll go back, right?
Let's go with that.
Come on.
You changed your mind?
What's his problem?
Seriously. What is with him?
He's been doing this for ages.
You've made up your mind?
Okay. Bring it on.
Huh?
Where is Akiyama?
He left while you were gone.
Oh, he's out?
That's too bad.
-Can I say one thing?
-Sure.
You were away for so long just for that?
Exactly.
Yes.
-Did you tweak your neck?
-What happened?
-I sort of tweaked my neck.
-How?
-That held me up, too.
-You were gone for ages.
-My helmet was...
-It was nearly half an hour.
Yes.
I couldn't choose between
this and my Cuban hat.
If we're all ready,
I would like to start Zombie Time.
Let's start!
Zombie Time!
Here they come!
What's going to happen?
And how long will it be?
This is bad.
-There they are.
-Yes?
-The zombies are here.
Who is it?
Welcome to "Now and Then."
I'll have hayashi rice.
Long time no see.
Hayashi...
rice.
-Kobayashi?
-Coffee, please.
Coffee.
-Iced coffee too, please.
-Iced.
-Make mine hot.
-Hot.
I wrote "hot" with the orange pen.
I wrote "iced" with this one.
He's laughing to make them laugh.
What a prick.
Is that why you have so many pens?
Who is this?
-He's a gladiator.
-Gladiator?
Mr. Gladiator.
It's your first time, right?
-Yes.
-Nice to meet you.
Are you the warm-up?
Are you today's warm-up act?
What do you want to eat?
What do you want?
-I'll take an iced coffee, please.
-Iced coffee.
You could have Kilimanjaro coffee.
-An iced coffee will do.
-Iced coffee.
Okay.
Long time no see.
I've been watching you in that drama.
What would you like?
-Yakisoba, please.
-Yakisoba.
I use two colors to write "yakisoba."
Yakisoba...
He is so annoying.
Let me check that.
-We have one hayashi rice.
-Right.
-Iced coffee... Hot coffee. Iced coffee.
-Yes.
And yakisoba, right? Okay.
Thank you.
-Excuse me, sir.
-Yes?
Punk Booboo said that
you didn't give them oranges.
Punk Booboo, right? Those guys.
If they tried a little harder
I would give them some, but not yet.
So, Punk Booboo want what?
-To be on your orange list.
-Okay.
Okay.
You think they're safe?
-I'll be right back.
-They all made it? Okay.
That was close.
Zombie Time is scary.
RG is pushing that impression.
-He looked just like him.
-He sure did.
Just like him.
-He really said that to me this morning.
-When you arrived?
-"Long time no see."
-The owner did?
-At "Now and Then"?
-Yeah.
For some reason,
he always knows when we'll arrive.
He always wanders around in that area
at the entrance to the studio.
Okay, let's go for it.
At this timing.
Zombie Time!
They might come together.
Here we go.
Hello, I'm Terence Lee.
I brought a teddy bear with me today.
Teddy Bear.
Come in, Teddy Bear.
Kasuga is in big trouble.
Come on.
It's okay. Don't be shy.
-Daddy!
-Come inside.
-Come on, Teddy Bear.
How cute.
You're so cute.
-That's bad!
-That's really bad!
Wait a minute!
-That was wrong.
-Wait! That was too much!
Who was it?
It must be Kobayashi.
-It was Kobayashi, right?
-Yeah, it's Koba.
-For starters.
-That really was...
Yay!
Wait. That was Kobayashi, right?
I know how you feel. This is too much.
We got him.
-We did it.
-They are too much.
-Give us a break.
-I made it this far!
There were two people.
They will both leave.
-Wow!
-That was powerful.
Kobayashi and Kasuga!
-Damn!
-Red card!
-I held out for so long!
Damn.
I really messed up.
Zombie Time really is dangerous, right?
The very idea of "Zombie Time"
made it worse.
Firstly, let me say it was amazing
that you withstood "Now and Then."
-I couldn't do it.
-You held on well.
That was impossible.
So, let's take a look.
It's okay. Don't be shy.
-Daddy!
-It was already too funny at this point.
Come on, Teddy Bear.
How cute.
That was a blatant laugh.
Why did you have to walk like an old lady?
Now let's look at Kasuga.
Really?
It's okay. Don't be shy.
-Daddy!
-Come inside.
-Come on, Teddy Bear.
How cute.
-Is that out?
-Well, yes.
-You're right. I laughed.
-You sure did.
-They got me.
-You exploded.
So, less than an hour and a half remains.
-I lasted for so long.
-Only two people left.
But this also means that both
Kasuga and Kobayashi can become zombies.
-We'll have more Zombie Time?
-Yes.
If the zombies take everybody out,
we get our million yen back, right?
-That's right. It will be a "No Contest."
-Let's aim for that.
Okay!
That was too funny.
We did it.
I think it's a shame that we didn't
get to see more of them,
but that's enough for now.
Nice zombie work.
On a serious note about
a somewhat technical matter,
Goto was eliminated, right?
When I thought about who would
initiate the conversations without him,
out of the guys left,
I thought I had to take that role.
So, I started having these weird,
extra thoughts going through my mind.
-Can I say one thing?
-Sure.
You were away for so long just for that?
I had to provide Goto-like jabs.
Like "Hey, what's that?"
In the end,
I guess I lost my concentration.
It's a shame.
If someone wins this competition,
I won't get my million yen back.
All I can do now is try to get that back.
But now I know exactly how frightening
Zombie Time can be for the players.
Compared to when I was
just one of the players,
I think I'll be able to
go on the offense more.
Come on, Teddy Bear.
How cute.
You're so cute.
The pressure was unreal.
But I can't believe it.
I thought only Kasuga could make me laugh.
Kasuga--
Let's go.
This is not good.
We're on!
-This is a strange pairing.
-We're not on Zombie Time, right?
This sure is tough.
Maybe I shouldn't just wait.
Yeah, I can't just wait.
The next time Yamamoto laughs,
Kinoshita will win right then and there.
That really is amazing.
-This is bad.
-This is really bad.
They're scary.
The zombies seem to be having fun.
We still have a long way to go.
One hour and ten minutes.
There's still a full hour.
Okay!
This is an opportunity, right?
Let's bring it on.
I'll bring it on.
He has no idea what to do.
He wants to be that little bit funnier.
He's trying to make himself
that little bit funnier.
And what is Kinoshita doing
on his side of things?
He is completely lost.
I have no idea what to do.
None at all.
Yamamoto?
Did you cut this?
-It's Sento-kun.
-Did you cut this?
-No, I didn't.
-Look at it.
-What?
-It's totally ruined.
You cut it, right?
When you were back there.
I didn't cut it.
It's in tatters.
Completely shredded.
How could you?
-I didn't do it.
-You can't do this. It's so wrong.
Honestly, I didn't cut it.
Then what is this?
I don't know.
But I haven't even touched your locker.
The whole thing is...
This was my funniest bit.
Yamamoto seems to be on the ropes.
You have a croissant-like thing there.
I think we should put all of this on hold
for a moment.
This isn't right.
I think we should stop filming.
It's been shredded.
We'll end up with no rules in here at all.
I can see that croissant thing.
This isn't about croissants.
He held it in.
That was close.
Does everybody shave down there?
He's back.
One hour left.
There's still plenty of time.
There is, but there are only two of us.
-You're right.
-Right?
-Do you want to do that?
-Shall we?
There are two of them.
-Shall we zap each other?
-Okay.
Is there any point to doing that?
Where do you want it?
Wherever you want.
But isn't this place the only option?
It's a little strong.
-Too strong?
-Yes.
Yamamoto?
-Don't laugh at something like this.
-That's not good.
Not now. Not at something like this.
-This is "squeeze."
-No good?
Is it squeezing?
Wait!
-It's on "squeeze."
-Wait.
Any stronger than that will...
It's kind of strong.
That's a bit...
Doing that is only going to put
Yamamoto under pressure.
This is "tap."
Yamamoto, think about it.
You're not attacking him there.
You are the one being attacked.
Are you aware of that?
That's a bit strong.
The offense and defense are
the wrong way around.
-This is level eight.
-Can you turn it down a bit?
This is seven.
This is level seven "knead."
From level seven to...
level 10!
There is no way Kinoshita
will laugh at this.
Level seven "knead."
Yamamoto?
Yamamoto. Watch out.
You have a slight smile.
Yamamoto, you have a slight smile.
Seriously? Do you get this?
That's definitely not a good idea.
What if I use the timer?
That's not the point, Yamamoto.
That will give us a time limit.
You should be asking him
to do that to you.
-This is "tap."
-See? He's going to make you laugh.
Is he okay?
Yamamoto. Are you okay?
-Cut that out.
-Level nine.
-That hurts!
-"Knead."
Level nine, "knead."
-Seriously, that's enough.
-It's on four now.
Enough. No more.
-What is he trying to do?
-Okay, let's take a break.
I'm exhausted.
But you look healthier.
It helps your circulation.
-Is that what this does?
-Yeah.
It should be good for you.
They're low frequency waves.
Well, that's my theory.
-I may be wrong.
-What the hell?
I am so tired.
Hey. Hey!
Again?
He's really shaking now.
Can you really stand this?
Do you really think you can win with this?
You have no more lives.
See? Look what happened.
Now Kinoshita can do whatever he wants.
-He could be faking this.
-I'm done for.
See? He could be faking that.
What the hell is this?
-I can't take this anymore.
-Yamamoto?
-Don't you get it?
-I give up.
Don't you?
-Sorry.
-Not yet.
But Yamamoto seems okay.
As far as this bit is concerned.
I don't know about Kinoshita, though.
Yamamoto won't laugh.
Yeah, he's okay. He won't laugh.
Yamamoto...
What are they doing?
Please! It hurts!
That hurts! It really hurts!
-Can I wipe my sweat?
-Sure.
That is amazing.
This is the real thing.
Need a towel?
Thank you.
They're building a nice relationship.
Let me attach it first.
Okay.
-It goes to ten. These are the levels.
-Is this "tap"?
That's "tap."
-I think it is.
-This is the speed?
That's it.
That's the speed.
I'm being tapped.
That's it.
Right. Right. Right. Right.
Hey!
It's tapping. It's tapping.
-It's tapping.
-I'll use this mode. "Tap."
Now it's on "knead."
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Okay.
-Next is "grab." A big grab.
-Okay.
-A strong grab?
-Right.
-I'll start at four.
-All of a sudden?
Five.
Six.
-Seven.
-It's grabbing.
-Eight.
-It's grabbing!
-Nine.
Ten.
Ten!
-It's grabbing!
-How is it?
It's grabbing!
-Ten.
-It's grabbing!
It grabbed. It's still grabbing.
-Ten.
Ten. Ten. Ten. Ten.
-It's grabbing.
-I already turned it off.
He's in real danger.
Nobody is there to laugh.
But that really is amazing.
-We have less than an hour.
-An hour.
I think it's time for Zombie Time.
Zombie Time!
Here they come!
Bring it on!
I'm scared.
I go in through here?
-Go to the booth at the end.
-Okay.
-Mister, do you want to shower first?
What's this?
-Put your wallet in here.
-Okay.
Put your wallet inside.
Take a shower. I'll wait.
-Okay. Thanks.
-Was it raining outside?
Outside? I think it's stopped now.
-So, it's not raining anymore?
-Right.
Okay. Take a shower.
-You're handsome.
-Thank you.
-Do you still have work?
-I'm finished for today.
Is your office nearby?
My office is nearby.
But my home is closer, actually.
Then you must come again. It feels good.
-Take a shower, mister.
-Okay.
Hang your clothes while you take a shower.
There's a hook.
Here.
Lily, Lulu, Yuyu.
All of our girls are cute.
All of the girls are really cute.
Lily, Lulu, Yuyu.
All of the girls are so cute.
-Can you use the shower?
-Yes.
Can I come out now?
-Yes. Okay. Come on out.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Is it cold?
It's a bit cold.
Go into that booth. Okay.
-It's not your first time, is it?
-It's my first time here.
-I see.
-Right.
What time do you usually come?
It must be late. After work?
That's right.
-Who were you with last time? Lily? Lulu?
-Lily.
-Lily, Lulu. All the girls are cute.
-Yes.
-Lay face down.
-Sure.
-Look at this big body.
-Thank you.
With a body this big, you must get stiff.
They always do that.
How is this? Where are you the most tired?
I guess it's my head.
-Your shoulders?
-Okay.
You're so stiff.
-I'll start the oil massage now.
-Thank you.
-Here we go.
-Thanks.
This feels the best.
-Stop squirming.
-Sorry.
You won't be popular with the girls.
Mister.
Mister...
You want a 30-minute extension.
Okay.
-A 30-minute extension.
-30 minutes? Okay.
This will feel good.
It's a special service.
-Then I'll have 30 minutes.
-Right?
Right?
Okay. On your back, mister.
-Sure.
-Okay.
-You're having a 30-minute extension.
This feels very good on your nipples.
Okay?
Mister, you don't need to move that much.
Sorry, I just...
-Now I will massage your lymph nodes.
-Okay.
-Ready?
-Thank you.
Okay. Here we go.
This will feel really good.
Your legs are so stiff!
-He's a complete idiot.
-Don't tell me you will fart.
Here we go.
-That feels good.
-My stomach hurts.
Ow. Ow. Ow.
Mister, this will feel really good.
Good, good, good.
Guys...
But Kinoshita is doing amazingly well.
Is this allowed?
-Is it really okay?
-They're really doing it.
-It feels good, right?
-Is it really okay?
-It's okay?
-It's a special to make you feel good.
-Good, good.
-It's okay?
The lymph nodes feel good, right?
We have to get it flowing.
Can they really survive this?
-Is that too strong?
-No. Thank you.
Do you want hot tea or cold tea
when we finish?
-Is it over?
-Why ask?
-What?
-Sorry?
Well...
Is this the end?
Special service...
-Okay. 30 minutes, please.
-It will feel best in another 30 minutes.
-I'll take another 30 minutes.
-Okay.
-Mister, is it your first time here?
-Sorry?
This is so embarrassing.
-Okay.
-This is embarrassing.
Is Yamamoto in trouble?
How is Yamamoto?
This is a good one.
Hey.
-Wait.
-Okay. All done.
-The feel good special is done.
-Is that all?
It's over, right?
Time up, right?
Or you can have another 30 minutes.
Then I'll take the "Double Dip Course."
The Double Dip Course feels the best.
Wait.
I'm going to blow.
Is that okay?
You do the last bit yourself.
-Do it yourself.
-Right.
If I do it,
I get in trouble with the owner.
Sorry.
-You do it yourself.
-Okay.
Okay?
-Do it yourself.
-In the shower?
Do it yourself in the shower. Okay?
-My stomach hurts. Ow. Ow. Ow.
-Don't forget this.
-Thank you.
-That was intense.
-It felt good, right?
-Yes. Thank you.
-Come again. Your office is nearby.
-Okay.
-Mister, do you want your tea hot or cold?
-I'll have it hot, thanks.
That was crazy. Well done for holding on.
Did you come together?
-You mean us?
-Yes.
No.
Who do you want? Have you chosen a girl?
We aren't here for that.
All of our girls are so cute.
Lily. Lulu. Yuyu.
They are all so cute.
They all come from Dalian City.
Everyone from Dalian is cute, right?
-What's your name?
-That's a nasty sweat.
My name is Yuyu.
Yuyu.
Have you been here long?
Of course I have.
I've been working here for ages.
I mean...
Mister, is the shower warm enough?
Are you okay?
Mister?
Don't worry. I'll be waiting outside.
He's taking a shower.
This guy is so annoying.
Both sides were amazing.
That went on for so long.
I am so tired.
-Wasn't that amazing?
-That should be against the rules.
I'm exhausted.
-That wasn't fair.
-I really am exhausted.
Right, Kinoshita? I understand.
-That was exhausting.
-I'm completely drained.
-We can hear the shower.
-Yeah, you can.
It's funny to hear someone
really taking a shower.
-That was too much.
-It sure was. That was wrong.
-That wasn't fair.
-That really was too much.
-He was touching him.
-He really was.
-Kobayashi was enjoying it, too.
-Seriously, what are you guys doing?
Damn.
Kinoshita, orange card!
You guys truly are insane.
-So, Kinoshita.
-Yes?
Let's look at the moment
that you actually laughed.
He held it in so much, he was sweating.
What the hell is that song?
That was impossible.
That really was funny.
But he really...
-He really played with my dick.
-He was doing it for real.
When you reach the utmost limits
of holding in a laugh,
you actually sweat.
-Yes, I was sweating.
-That was amazing.
I mean, it was like...
It became difficult to breathe.
I couldn't breathe properly.
-And about that low-frequency device duel.
-Yes?
Every time you attacked him
with zaps from that device,
you were the one who was under attack.
You were confusing offense with defense.
-Right?
-Yes.
He's right.
And only an audience can laugh at that
"I already turned it off" joke.
Seriously.
That wasn't laughable from the start.
It was like,
"Who is he even doing this for?"
But this is more exciting.
-They're square.
-Same color cards.
-You two can go.
-Okay.
The zombies that came once
can't come back, right?
-I don't know about that.
-It wouldn't be the same.
-Same zombie, same trick.
-Well, yeah.
-I'm not sure. I can't say yet.
-Same zombie, same trick, right?
-That was tough.
-Bye.
I can't take this.
That went on for so long.
-Great work.
-Thank you.
-That was amazing.
-That was funny.
-It sure was.
-Wow.
This will go down in history.
It was superb.
Okay.
Here we go.
-That was the wrong place to sit.
-We're on!
COMING UP NEXT
THE SEASON THREE FINALE
Zombie Time!
They're back already?
Well, that was insane.
Those zombies. They were just...
That was impossible.