Translated by kentranslations
Timed/Edited by blakeo_x
You know...I'm actually
pretty good at this.
Isn't it hot?!
I never thought Nana-chan
would give me a run for my money.
She's ruthless.
She gets to me every time.
I was thinking, this
show is truly terrifying.
I don't want to come on this show anymore.
It's so scary!
The first one out is...
Shizu-chan!
Was I moving?
And the other person...
Iwao!
It wasn't just hot. That
hand pushed me to the side!
Let's go in.
Let's do it.
Oh dear, oh dear.
What?!
- What's this?
- It's already soaked.
- You've gotta be kidding.
- It's full of water.
What about our shoes? Do we take them off?
Can we take them off?
These shoes are
actually kind of expensive.
It's full of water!
What should we do about the shoes?
That startled me!
Why are you scaring us?
Alright everyone, welcome!
Thank you!
It's already full of water.
That's right, you'll have to
take off your shoes in this room.
Please sit down with your bare feet.
You can leave your shoes at the back.
Where should we sit?
You can choose for yourselves.
Where should I? Maybe there.
It doesn't matter. You won't have
any advantages or disadvantages.
- I'll sit here then.
- I'm all fired up today.
- By the way, how is my pulse doing?
- So cold!
Morohoshi-kun, your heartbeat...
- It's been beating fast all along.
- Fast?
Really?
It's super fast.
I feel like I've been running a marathon.
I wonder why it's so fast.
It's so cold!
- What's gonna happen?
- Please plant your feet firmly
on the ground when you freeze.
And Suzuki-san, you changed
your clothes, didn't you?
Yes, my previous outfit got dirty.
So I changed.
That's such a normal answer...
I also fixed my makeup.
Alright, let's start the 3rd stage!
- What?
- It's starting already?
No! What's gonna happen?!
So suspicious.
No, no, no. Hold on. I'm so scared.
Right...
Isn't it so hard?
You don't know where
to focus your attention.
Right, let's get started.
I'm sorry!
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
This is really scary!
The snakes are slithering around.
Is it really that scary?
I thought they'd be fine with this.
So scary...
No, it's too scary!
This guy's just looking straight ahead.
Oh no!
I'm sorry, I'm so scared.
These two are amazing.
Yukai is awesome.
Release!
- What the heck?!
- What are they?!
- Aren't there too many?
- They're not eels.
It's not eels.
It's snakes.
Look at their faces. They're snakes!
I can't!
My shoes! My shoes!
I can't stand up!
- I can't stand, I'm too scared!
- They're all over the place!
They'll come to you if
you keep making noise.
I can't, I can't.
Look, they're all up in those shoes!
Matsumoto-san, what about our shoes?
I can't deal with this.
That stage was so dangerous.
The snakes came out of nowhere.
It was like being in a nightmare.
I was pretty scared.
To tell you the truth...
Yeah.
That was unbelievable! So crazy!
I don't even want to remember it.
Since the floor was full of water,
the snakes kept moving
and swimming around!
A ton of them started
trying to cling to our feet!
That was so unpleasant.
I couldn't handle it.
I'm getting a panic attack
just thinking about it.
I just wanted to get out of that room.
Here we go.
The temperature's rising.
Bobby's already out.
Suzuki's doing great this time.
Oh no, it's starting to fog up!
So steamy...
Whoa, Morohoshi is amazing.
It's about 50°C (122°F) now.
We can barely see.
We can barely see them.
What was that?
So hot!
- Crazy!
- We got soaked.
Soaked!
What was that?
- It was cold water at first, wasn't it?
- Yes.
Why did it turn hot?
It was pretty hot.
Hot water didn't come out last time.
(Translator note: I have no idea who he's referencing.)
You look like Roppo-san!
- Who is that?
- You look like him!
- You look like Roppo-san!
- I'm Yukai.
He's changed!
Give me a break!
It was pretty hot.
I didn't think they would go this far.
What was the deal with the sprinklers?
Cold water was coming out,
then suddenly it got super hot.
What was the purpose of that?
To clean us?
I wanna get out of this room.
Here we go.
Diamond Yukai is so funny.
Shall we continue?
I can't see Yukai-san anymore.
This is nice.
Let's throw in the yellowtail.
- What was that?
That's so funny!
It's gone to the side.
I look like a poodle.
WHO MADE IT TO THE FINAL ROUND?
Where should we sit?
Wherever is fine.
- Someone else is coming.
- What?
- Someone else?
- Then, should we sit on the sides?
- Sandwich them?
But then you'll be in front of me.
- I'll laugh if I sit in front of you.
- Why?
- I'll sit here.
I was too scared, so I
gave up at that stage.
I was so tired from the 3rd stage.
I mean, normally I'm
not such a scaredy cat.
Alright, the losers are back!
- What?
- Excuse me.
It's been a while.
We're finally back here.
Where should I sit?
Here?
Alright.
We have a great mix of
celebrities and variety show guests.
We made it.
- Who will win?
- I wonder if the artists are better at this.
The artists are strong.
Have they always been good?
They're so amazing.
They're not normal.
Isn't it hot?!
The artists are so strong.
You guys changed.
You're right!
- Yes.
- This is her third outfit.
- What?
- I didn't have any changes left.
- No changes left?
- Yes, no clothes left.
- I see, did you have to...
- He's here, he's here.
Alright everyone, sorry for making, um...
Here's what you've been waiting for.
A lot has happened, but the winner
of this stage will advance to the finals.
Alright.
One person here still has a
chance at the 1 million yen prize.
Please give it your best shot.
I'm definitely going to win.
But you guys are
already used to this, right?
I don't think you'll be
surprised by what's next.
Kuro-chan and I lost
on the first stage, so...
- We were clueless.
- We were so scared in the
waiting room.
I see.
And you already know
the finalists are strong.
They're too strong.
Those two are not normal.
- But we still want to win.
- Give it your best shot.
We'll try our best!
I'm so scared! I'm so scared!
It's kinda cramped in here.
Cramped?
- For the number of people.
- It was way more cramped last time.
What's gonna happen?!
- But you guys seem pretty used to it now.
- No way, I'm so scared.
- I don't want to get used to it.
- I can't get used to it.
Right, you can't.
I can't, I can't, I'm so scared.
This is nice. It's been a
while since we've been here.
It feels like a long time.
But you could say everyone's
been "sharpening up".
They've honed their
skills, and even their poses.
This is good.
Let's go.
He's so interested in Shizu-chan.
She's in trouble.
Someone's gonna end up laughing.
Shizu-chan was so close.
Shizu-chan and Non-chan too.
Shizu-chan and Non-chan.
They might be in trouble.
Now he's approaching Kuro-chan.
He's smelling them one by one.
Such a good boy.
You know, this is more
of a laughing test...
Compared to the usual jump scare test.
He really is going one by one. So smart.
This one might be a
bit of a drawn-out battle.
I wouldn't want this.
Hold on, this isn't that kind of show.
But in the end, he
didn't look at Non-chan.
Huh? He's back to Shizu-chan?
What's going on?
It's over.
They're already laughing.
- He peed! He peed!
- Don't laugh!
Of course I'd laugh!
I couldn't keep a straight face!
- He peed!
- A little bit.
Did he?
- He chose that spot.
- Why there?
What was he looking for?
He was marking his territory!
Translated by kentranslations
Timed/Edited by blakeo_x