Translated by zeus777
Timed/Edited by blakeo_x
It was way too much.
He took things to a whole new level.
I seriously thought "you've got to
be kidding me, Matsumoto-san!"
I was like "damn you, Matsumoto-san!"
"Give me a break!"
He was laughing the whole
time, right? Like hehehe.
He was watching everything through
the monitor and having fun.
Just a rich guy entertaining himself.
Makes me want to shoot him.
Shall we?
However,
two of you have been eliminated.
Fujimon!
You moved too much.
No, you're supposed to move!
Kuro-chan is out!
Me?!
That's unexpected!
- Because of the drone.
- Yes, he moved from it.
The knife hit me between my eyebrows.
Tada!
So we need to pause
everything at "freeze", right?
- We need to get serious from here.
- Hey Yukai-san, where are you sitting?
- Oh, right, we have our own seats.
- Anywhere is fine.
I wanna sit across from Yukai-san.
I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
Why is Suzuki so scared?
Would you be scared?
- Isn't the circle smaller than last time?
- You're right, it is smaller.
- It's really small.
- Scary.
Judging from the size of the room,
I don't think they can use
crazy large gadgets and such.
I was wondering where they'll come from…
Alright then, time to get started.
Yeah, but still…
Shizu’s face is hilarious.
OK, let’s do this.
I can see why they're scared.
They're so close too.
Smack Yukai's foot.
Try it again. Do it twice,
like "smack smack."
Yukai is amazing.
OK, that’s enough. You can come back now.
What was that?!
That darn dude!
He wasn’t even close!
Sheesh, that really hurt.
What is this anyway?
- What a surprise!
- It’s like a bomb!
It’s all over my clothes.
I really wasn’t expecting the
watermelon to blow up like that.
The watermelon exploded!
None of us expected that.
It was like "bam!"
- I’m tired already.
- Me too.
That really wore me out.
Go ahead.
Straighten out.
Keep frozen, Bobby.
Ow!
That must have hurt.
Everyone is doing well, though.
Try tickling her ear.
Go in.
Wait, wait, that's enough.
She’s amazing.
Good, good. OK.
I think I can stay still. But I'm
really sensitive in some areas.
Sensitive, huh?
The right breast is more
sensitive than the left.
What is that? Stop it.
This is great.
Everyone is really tough.
Can you play with Non-chan's hair?
Put your fingers through it.
OK, go to Morohoshi next.
Can you stick a finger up his nose?
This is good, Morohoshi senses something.
He knows. He knows something
is up, and it’s gonna be bad.
He knows. He totally knows.
The finger...
Amazing.
What was that?
That damn thing slapped me! I got slapped!
That’s wrong! What was
that? No touching please!
What was that thing
trying to do with my hair?
It actually came after my right boob...
because I mentioned
earlier that it's sensitive.
Was it OK?
No, it was pretty bad.
That thing got in my
nose and slapped my face!
Their facial expressions
really showed in this round.
I had to move when it slapped me.
I’ve never felt a hand
that was so rock-hard.
- Did it hurt?
- Yes, it hurt!
Morohoshi-san, that
thing went up your nose?
It did.
It didn’t feel ticklish?
I managed to hold it back.
Amazing!
I thought it was kinda funny that
the machine was giving
you the middle finger and...
This is long. It really is.
I’m sure it's tough to wait this long.
What the heck?!
That was scary!
I've had enough!
That was scary. What was that?
- What was that about?
- What was that?
Can we get through this?
I'm going crazy.
This is mentally draining.
You know, it’s only natural for us humans
- to react and move based on our instincts.
- It's unhealthy not to.
- And why doesn't Macchan come out anymore?
- You're right.
What's he doing?
- Is he even watching anymore?
- Maybe not!
- It's mind games at this point.
- I wanna quit. I'm tired.
- There he is!
- I am watching!
What now?
You guys were doing well,
not reacting to that robot arm.
I mean, that finger was way too hard!
Oh, was it?
Yeah, it was the hardest
finger I’ve ever, uh...seen...
How many fingers have
you stuck up your nose?!
Morohoshi, your heart
rate is through the roof.
Did it go up?
Just yours went up by
nearly twice as much.
I’m not at my best today, that's all.
But, you know, this is good. Really
good. You guys are doing great.
Alright, let’s go!
No, I wanna quit!
I wanna quit!
This is scary!
I've had enough!
What's next? What's next?
Come and get us, damn it!
I wanna quit!
You’re the one with
the abnormal heart rate!
This is funny.
You know something bad is coming.
This is bad.
OK.
Let's go.
Bobby...
Bobby isn't taking this
well. Toughen up, Bobby!
OK, now what?
Oh, that’s how you’re gonna do it?
Wow, you’re being pretty rough there.
The fish cake with the
burdock root looks good.
You can pick that up.
Oh, it got the fish cake.
Give it to Yukai.
It’s locked on to Yukai,
it's locked on to Yukai.
I think Yukai is mentally
prepared for this. Right, Yukai?
Are you ready, Yukai?
Wow, he looks cool.
I can see the steam coming out.
Go on.
Isn’t it hot?!
It must be.
OK, put it back in the pot…
Let’s go for Non-chan then.
Something is stuck to its finger.
OK, go ahead.
Ah, good, good. Let’s give it to Non-chan.
Go for Non-chan.
That was scary.
- Was it hot?
- Of course!
- It was hot, right?
- Definitely.
Look at it! Even Dacho
didn’t have it boiling this much!
(Translator note: Dacho Club was a comedy trio. The
towel gang from GNT no-laughing batsus was based on them.)
I’ve never seen a hot
pot boiling that much.
I saw the steam and everything,
but that thing was really hot.
It was some seriously hot stew.
It really worried me. I
wasn’t sure how far they'd go.
- This really is mentally draining.
- It's really stressful. It really is.
Ah, this is so…
OK, here comes the next machine.
I feel bad. I feel bad for them…
Get pretty close.
Get closer to Bobby.
OK, I’m gonna release them.
Why me?! What was that?!
This is funny.
It's really funny.
- What IS that?!
- I dunno, but it stinks!
It stinks, stinks, stinks!
- Something stinks.
- This stinks!
Alright everyone, thanks for your time.
The second stage is now over!
I have decided who will be dropping out.
The first one is...
Shizu-chan!
Was I moving?
Shizu-chan, you lost points for enjoying
that nipple-tickling a bit too much.
And the other person...
This one was a hard decision.
It wasn’t easy, but in the end…
Iwao!
Come on, I got puked on!
There was the hot pot too.
It wasn’t just hot, that
hand pushed me to the side!
To be clear, it was a hard
decision. It was really tough.
Also, the losers will get a second chance.
OK, on to the next stage!
What the heck!
It stinks! How can you be so cruel?
I don't want to go through anything
worse than the puke thing, so...
I mean, if I'm going to get puked on, I can't
stop imagining what comes next.
You know, maybe something
toilet related might come out.
I couldn’t stop thinking.
It was really frustrating.
The watermelon explosion
really got to me. I hate the sound.
No matter how much I
hear it, I can't get used to it.
I'm also mad at myself for not keeping a
straight face through the nipple-tickling.
Translated by zeus777
Timed/Edited by blakeo_x