The Gaki No Tsukai dressing room
You seem to be obsessed with watches lately, Yamazaki. - I guess I have.
But I'm not wearing one now. Sorry about that.
You aren't going to give any excuse, are you?
And then, this man came...
Good morning.
Sorry to bother everyone.
Itao Itsuji
What's wrong?  - This is your wife?
This is my wife. - Of course.
A new one?
How many is this for you?
His kid changed too.
Yeah, this is a new wife...
I'm asking to that you guys be nice to our entire crew here.
What the hell was that?
Shouldn't your daughter be happier?
She's just a little tired today.
When she kissed her, she turned away!
Well, sorry Itao, but we...
Wait a minute...
For a while now, and you guys may already know this...
In the spirit of those 24-hour Net Shopping sites...
I've started a show called Ittsuji Shopping.
Is that so?
If I could...
I'd like to show the format to Nihon TV...
Then maybe you should be showing to someone else, like Suga over there.
That may be true, but the newest internet
Shopping shows are only about 10 minutes long...
So if you could come and check it out, I'd be glad.
We get that, but we don't have time,
we're about to start filming.
Well until you have to do that
(filming), you should come and watch.
Wife?
Is this something we should participate in?
Of course.
Is that so? - That why we came here.
Everyone try to act excited too.
We're only staying for a little while, Itao.
Then you won't mind coming with me?
Where are we going to tape a show like that?
Ittsuji Shopping!
It's time once again for Ittsuji Shopping!
Today, in a live show, we'll be looking at goods set to take the world by storm.
Now I'd like to introduce today's new item...
And Gaki No Tsukai's here too. Nice to have you!
That seemed a little odd. Like we really aren't welcomed here.
Moving on, please watch this video.
Ittsuji Shopping!
The birth rate is on the decline!
We're facing a birth rate problem!
Erectile Dysfunction is surging too!
The dissatisfaction of wives is only growing!
It's becoming dangerous for men.
But now there's a savior for all those tired men!
That savior is today's product: Erection King!
How can they just say that so frankly?
We asked a few customers about their feelings.
All I have to do is put some on
before bed, and I wake up just fine.
It even cured my migraines.
But the part that surprised me the most is...
the increase in my erections.
Up until now, my wife has never looked at me like this.
But look at her now, she's begun smiling like this.
Sorry, but talking about it... I got a little hard.
Erection King!
Have YOU been hard lately?
Stand up like the men throughout the world!
They've managed to pick up women!
The ultimate potency stimulant creme
has arrived to power up Japan!
Using it simple.
All you have to do is rub it on...
And the Sleeping Lion will awaken!
This is the beginning of a new life!
A great future is waiting for the new, reborn you!
Erection King!
Incredible power! What is Erection King's secret?!
Using their large mouthes to scoop it up,
this incredibly nutricious product
is even eaten by the queen bee.
We start by finding some illusive premium Royal Jelly.
The person who found this is... Erection King's Founding Father: Paul Franklin.
From there, he headed to South America and
achieved an exclusive partnership with the locals
All for a plant that only blooms every
four years: Male Hormone nuts.
Mixing these two products together,
you get the best product available.
Through experimenting and improving over a span
of ten years, we've come up with this miracle cream!
That is Erection King!
Since your wonderful cream made my lower half warm.
We are finally able to have a warm, loving family.
To verify Erection King's stunning claims,
we will thoroughly examine its secret!
When we take a thermographic picture of a
crotch after Erection King has been applied...
Normal crotch
Crotch with Erection king
The crotch looks like this!
That is the power of Erection King!
Now we will listen to customer's authentic
accounts of Erection King's effectiveness!
After getting the surveys given to the
people who purchased Erection King...
My life has changed.
I was able to father a child, even at 90 years old.
And now this person!
Suzuki-san said that had results as soon as he ordered it!
Akio Suzuki-san
As soon as I started talking to the Operator...
When I thought about the Erection King
coming, I happened to get a woody!
Our product didn't even arrive,
and he already felt the results!
That's the power of Erection King!
98% of people surveyed said that they were satisfied
with Erection King's results! A surprising number!
The other two percent had been castrated
and forgot that they had imitation parts.
Even celebrities around the world
are becoming fond of Erection King!
It's a favorite among 80% of Hollywood stars!
Plenty of Japanese Celebrities love it too!
Umemiya T-tsuo! (Umemiya Tatsuo)
He's going to be mad!!
T-chi Hiroshi! (Tachi Hiroshi )
Fujinami T-tsumi! (Fujiname Tatsumi)
T-kawa Danshi! (Tatekawa Danshi)
Even a group called T-kawa Ichimon use our
product! (Relatives of feudal lord Ieyasu Tokugawa!)
The person who spread Erection King
throughout the entertainment world is...
The man who founded Erection King Japan in 1998:
Tateyama Tatsuaki!
He started the Erection King Cup golf tournament
and noticed a large niche in the entertainment world!
From there the product underwent a huge boom!
Here, Tatsuaki Tateyama Tatsuaki speaks from the heart!
I have experienced first hand Erection King...
and this is a product I can be proud of.
If you use Erection King, I promise
you will get an erection quickly.
Promised by Tatsuaki Tateyama himself,"If you use Erection King, you will get a firm boner!"
That is Erection King!!
Well everyone, how do you feel about that?
Those were amazing testimonies about Erection King.
Did you guys understand all of that?
To be honest, it had its questionable points...
There were some things that were hard to believe?
I would say I couldn't believe them.
But everyone can you use Erection King,
even impotent Matsumoto-san can.
If someone like him used Erection King, even he can get one.
Really?!  - Yes, according to our results, he can.
You can use it too, Endou. Like when you're trying to make up with your wife.
You can show Chiaki (Endou's ex-wife) I'm so sorry...
And maybe she'll come back to you, won't she?
There's no reason for her to come back for that.
Now everyone, regarding Erection King's results...
I'd like to explain more about its amazingness.
Try not to keep clasping your hands over your
crotch repeatedly if you happen to get a boner.
What the hell?!
Everyone, please close your eyes for me.
Now try to think of something unpleasant.
I've already got my boner.
That was fast!
Honestly that doesn't matter does it?
Did you guys get excited by those unpleasant things?
Those don't matter...  - It should be obvious now to everyone...
The brain is slow.
You couldn't think of them because your brain is slow.
Please look at this.
Japanese who are worried about erections
About how many do you think there are?
About 100,000 people?
Lets look. The number of Japanese who are worried about erections is:
100,000,000 people! (One Hundred Million)
Shouldn't we ignore women? (There's
only about 127 million people in Japan)
One hundred million people is hard to believe.
If these one hundred million people rubbed on some Erection King...
They would all feel the warmth that we showed in the earlier results...
Even wives will notice the results...
And then they'll start doing all sorts of erotic, erotic things...
Sexy, sexy, things...
Even you started to feel it, right?
I can't think of anything except erotic things~!
She can't say things like that.
- What is she talking about?
What we mean is that its something that both the male AND his partner will benefit from.
Again, I'd like to show some more of Erection King's testimonies of results.
Erection King's stories of experiences
This is an Erection Apparatus.
Could you please try these
on, Hamada and Matsumoto?
I can't think of anything except erotic things!
She can't say that.  - What is she saying?
We can't show these things on TV!
Those are vulgar, aren't they?
Once you apply Erection King...
you'll enter this kind of state.
When you get like this, your head will
feel all sluggish. (From lack of blood)
You can't sell that kind of medicine!
But while you're in this state...
As you may have noticed, it's a little dangerous.
For example, you could hit it on the side of a table...
You can't walk down the street like this.
So we have something else to unveil.
It covers everything up.
So it's protected. It's also got a cooling effect.
Just in case you were worried.
But like this, you can't walk around.
From now on, if I want to go out walking, I can't put on Erection King.
But even so, things do come up and the effects are fairly long, so sometime you will have to go out.
For example if you have to go to work.
Try these on for me please.
After this, Erection King's stunning effects!
What the hell are these?
Those look awful!
Those have a weird look to them, don't they?
What are these things? Seriously.
Those things are just creepy.
Could you two go over to that wall for me?
Then try running over here.
What do you mean?
- I mean an all-out sprint over there.
Huh? Together?
Okay, now go back.
How was that?
It was exactly like I thought. Exactly like it.
But it felt protected though, didn't it?
Other than that...
There's the question of what happens when you do some strenuous exercise.
But if you're wearing these, and you try to dance, you should be okay.
To show just how much you can dance in these...
Now, if you would, MUSIC START!
Itao, your wife is always dancing.
Both of you do it.
How does that feel?
Feels good doesn't it?
What is that all about?
Try to feel just how easy it is to move in them.
And this is, by no means, a difficult dance.
Okay, thank you!
Thank you very much.
So even if you're doing something strenuous, you should be okay.
After that, if you should go to the store...
You can do like this...
and hang the shopping bag.
You can't walk down the street like that!
You can't do that at all.
Although I hope that you all want to buy our products by now...
but you'll only have to wait a little bit longer before you can start getting erections.
Have a look at this.
Ittsuji Shopping!
Erection King!
To this date, millions of men have been able to stand up thanks to Erection King.
However, it doesn't only increase your erections!
Sydney, Australia
What's Erection King's surprising claim?
After arriving from a drive, he had an accident.
You've hit the door without noticing.
However!
If you apply a generous amount of Erection King...
The panels on your car will get erect!
Your car will be brought back.
Sparkling and shiny!
It will even surprise your girlfriend, that's the power of Erection King!
Also, Erection King is...
OK to be used as a UV Ray sunscreen!
It can't do all that!
Isn't she putting too much on?
When unexpected company comes over...
Welcome, welcome.
It's OK to serve Erection King as an hors d'oeuvre.
It's delicious!
It's got hundreds of uses and no flaws!
But if I had to chose one...
it would be that using it is hell!
This is Erection King!
So, how is it, everyone?
Do you have blood-rushing
erection when having an erection?
Well, there's no problem about that.
I don't know, but I want to see this in studio.
Yeah, I really wanted to see it here.
Well, this is a personal opinion...
Also, there's much more impressive effects hidden in this.
Here, this is when it is used to a phone.
A phone...
When you think there's bad connection,
putting the cream Erection King.
It has the strength to make
the talking easier with 4 connection bars standing up.
Then let's do it here.
But this place is out of reach...
Can't you also do this in out of reach place?
This doesn't work in out of reach places.
It works at places with weak signals.
Did you just change it?
She just said yes.
If you use the Erection King with your family
members, the telephone charges will be very cheap!
Will it become cheaper?
It won't change for the charges...
This is just absurd.
There is also other effect with the cream.
Well, oily stains are in the ventilating fan.
If you put on the cream, it will be really clean like this.
I think this is wrong.
For the ventilating fan, it wasn't meant to be like this.
So, it becomes clean somehow.
What a surprising effect!
Let's do this here! I would really want to see this on live.
This can also...
make it OK for 30 minutes when you're late.
If you mix it with water and spray it.
It couldn't be useful with time problems.
But why?
This cream is just amazing!
It works for everything!
You can eat it too, right?
Yes, because it's made from natural things.
The Ittsuji Shopping still continues!
So, I think everyone is erecting
unable to endure it right now, but...
there is much more video to show.
Here it is.
Ittsuji Shopping!
The fearsome power! Erection King!
The founder of the Erection King
Erection King's Founding Father
Paul Franklin
Paul Franklin and 10 years of
experiments, made a miracle cream!
Erection King:
Representative of Japan
Even the Tatsuaki Tateyama
promises it gives a huge erection!
Experience a whole new start for your life!
A notification from Erection King!
There is lately a fake copy of
Erection King called Pokki King.
If you use it, you will have a small rash.
Don't mistake with the fake copy!
Yes, the only thing that can rescue you is...
Erection King!
What was that?
So, how was the power of the Erection King, everyone?
Also, the greatness of Erection King doesn't stop here.
So, this magazine which businessmen read.
You know it?
I don't know this magazine.
This magazine talks about the Erection King.
It's in the common topics: Erection Drugs, talking about tomorrow.
It's introduced in this magazine.
It's being called the erection drug's king?
So the people from each drug company talked together.
And Erection King is talking too.
Look at this!
At the start, everyone is talking
together, but from the 2nd page.
Only Erection King's people are talking.
It seems like it's in the Erection King's
pace, and everyone is getting pushed by it.
Well, I don't really care about those things.
And from this page, only Erection King is talking.
So what's the price for the Erection King?
Yes, that's about it.
So, everyone, this Erection King's price is...
I was curious about that.
Today, this Erection King...
Erection King Cream
and an extra.
Here, the Erection King, the stick type for portable use.
Erection King Lipstick
This is totally lipstick!
This is also added.
There's still more!
Also, this...
Wet tissue type for it, yes.
Erection King Wet Tissue
So the drug is soaked in?
Yes, it's soaked lightly.
I get it!
Also this, which we showed you before.
Sweat pants with cooling cover
A sweat pants with cooling cover.
I don't need this!
So this sweat pants...
This is a set of 4.
It's 1,980 yen exactly!
Wow, so cheap!
Is that possible?
It's totally possible!
We're waiting for your call.
It's first come, first serve!
The phone is ringing.
So quick!
This is totally fake...
The call is too fast.
Not much to happening.
There should be a pre-order now.
Ehm... thank you very much!
Right now, the 30,000 of Erection King is out of stock!
Thank you very much, again.
This is it, the Ittsuji Shopping! Please come again!
ITTSUJI SHOPPING END~
The phone is ringin'.
After the live broadcasting
Did it finish?
Yes, it's done.
Oh yeah, it was on live, right?
Because of your cooperation, it's out of stock.
So, let's go now.
So, you said you would buy the set, so please...
Wait, you have to talk to Nippon TV about this.
Sir, it is OK that you are going to buy this?
I'm not certain about that with the
terrestrial broadcast (for Nippon TV).
Do you only have these kinds of goods?
I think so, because this is the
recommended goods to sell for now.
But we can change the name to
something more appropriate.
Isn't the name very important?
No, not really...
Because it's really recommended?
Yes, it's OK to change in this range.
We ordered a lot because it was for Nippon TV.
We have to at least sell that much.
But didn't you say it's not out of stock for today?
It's sold in high rate now, right?
It's amazing.
The next stock's money is for me, so...
The first stock's money doesn't go to you?
It seems the first one isn't for me.
So it goes to Paul or something?
Yes, it does.
So who is the Erection King in Japan?
Mr. Tateyama.
He makes a lot of an aphrodisiac-kind of things.
He doesn't actually make it, right?
Not much, I think...
It's a point you should care about much.
We're curious.
You need to buy this, please.
But really... you serious?
It sounds dangerous.
Thank you very much...
I confirmed the guarantee fee, thank you, again.
So... thank you for today.
Little tired?
Sorry, and thank you for today.
I'm going.
That was unreasonable.
Try using it.
I don't want to, really...
I think this real one makes you rash too.
This dance isn't that hard to do.