Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Backstage before the recording session...
His hip hurts...
Whose?
Tanakas's.
I have pain in my lower back.
What happened?
Some time ago on this program, I had to carry Heipo on my shoulders...
2003/11/30
Heipo Rodeo
Oh, that was quite a few years ago.
Uh, ten years...
Your back still hurts since then?
15... wasn't it around 20 years ago?
Sounds about right.
Seriously?
You should demand compensation.
From Heipo?
Should I write him a letter?
Make him face his consequences.
I can't do that.
Housei's here.
Good morning.
Greet us properly.
Sorry.
What the hell is "Yo, Yo"?
What's "Yo, Yo,"? You've got to greet us properly,
But the way I greeted you
Housei Tsukitei
was fit for a rapper.
I thought about it last night, and I've decided to become a rapper.
I've gotten a really good grasp on the Japanese language.
Since i've been trained in rakugo, I have great command of the
Japanese language and its rhythm. Isn't that perfect for rap?
Let's head into town right now.
I'll be wearing this outfit, and when people
approach us from the front of town...
The 'front' of town?
The front...
You really have no grasp on this language!
The 'front' of town...
So once they approach us, I'll diss them.
Oh?
I'll diss them one by one,
and maybe get into a few brawls.
And once they've been provoked, I'll traumatize them completely.
With your rapping?
With my rapping.
So without using violence...
No, there won't be any violence.
No violence.
Just rapping.
I'll traumatize them all with my rapping skills.
So, could I get you all to get changed?
We're not getting involved in this.
I don't know you.
Just more or less... Look. I'll do all the
talking, and you guys can be my hype men.
But I'll be doing everything, of course. I'll put on my toughest expression.
Agreed?
I have a feeling this won't be able to be broadcasted.
Can he win against people
in the shopping district!?
Housei Tsukitei's
rap battle Challenge!!
Translation: TL @ dailymotion.com/Tsukitei
Timing + typesetting: BQ00
HOUSEI TSUKITEI'S
RAP BATTLE CHALLENGE
Going along with the glow of the rhythm and
battling his opponent with nothing but words,
Housei expresses his desire to hold a rap battle challenge!
Amidst the terrible, rainy weather,
the member, who have finished changing,
follow Housei to the shopping district.
Is this really okay?
What is?
Can we rally diss our audience?
It's important that we keep an audience.
Wait a minute.
If you're wearing that you might get recognized, people will follow you.
Why am I the only one wearing a wig for disguise?
Um, can you take the wig off, please?
Wait a minute, that's kind of...
It's a nice wig...!
We're disguised as rappers, It'll be fine.
We're rappers, aren't we?
Do you want to wear the wig that badly?
No, no, no!
Wearing it is fine, right?
He really wants to wear it.
Just take that thing off already!
I'm begging you! Let's do this properly...!
Yes, you should.
You should.
He's definitely going to run off by himself!
No I'm not!
This undedicated person?
That's right!
Don't mess with me!
No sense of teamwork! None...!
What the hell...
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
LIGHTNING
Whoa!
That's loud!
Shouldn't we stop filming? It's going to be real noisy.
No, we're not stopping. This actually just builds the atmosphere.
Well, yeah. It'll raise the tension.
That's right. It adds to the vibe.
We haven't done anything like this for a
while so we've got to make a grand entrance.
That's right.
Even so...
We'll try our best.
Wait - wait - wait a minute.
Before we start, you need to be my hype men.
Can you give me a demonstration?
Be my hype men.
Yep. Just like that.
That's right.
I'm good at this, right?
Absolutely not.
It's like this, isn't it?
This rapping motion.
Like this.
Let's go.
Honestly, Cocorico are doing the best.
Aren't they?
Yes!
So who's doing the worst?
You can tell just by watching. Isn't it obvious?
This colorful guy!
Apart from him, we're all good, aren't we?
So while I'm rapping, you'll be acting like...
Let's stop filming!
Let's stop!
Wouldn't it be better to just stop now?
Let's just go to a café.
We're still doing this.
This isn't the type of weather we can shoot in. Let's just go to a cafe.
The thunder will just get louder and louder.
Like "whaaaa!"
It's definitely gonna happen!
RAP BATTLE START
Amidst the rolling thunder, Housei's challenge starts now!
Say ho, ho!
It's coming along! Terrific!
He's getting into it!
Isn't this rapping project great?
But it probably looks like we're searching for a fight.
Alright, someone come at me!
Anybody will do.
Housei Tsukitei
Greengrocer
I've caught you! I've caught you!
I've caught you outside with Gaki no Tsukai!
The peak in your career was 5 years ago!
When you got whipped with some burdock 5 years ago!
It's heating up!
He's saying some grand things.
What the hell do you know about the peak in my career?
You know absolutely nothing about me!
Absolutely, absolutely nothing!
Oh, What the hell did you just say?
I couldn't hear what you said at all, YO!
This isn't going to happen today.
Alright, let's leave.
I'm not getting into this at all.
Your popularity has gone straight down!
Your acting skills have gone straight down!
The only show you're a regular on is Gaki no Tsukai!
That's the simple truth! I pity you!
When you gonna quit? Quit Gaki no Tsukai!
That guy scared me more than I expected.
He went in hard.
He wrecked you!
What did I even say during that?
Nobody remembers. Not even the audience.
Nothing that you said left any kind of impression.
All I really heard was the thunder rolling up above.
It's probably gonna do that every time you get into a battle.
Definitely.
UTTERLY
DEFEATED
With no good points in his rap, Housei was utterly defeated.
It's really pouring down.
It just keeps falling.
Let's quit!
We're not quitting.
Not quitting.
We're gonna keep at it?
I mean, if we were doing it outside I would want to quit too.
But we're not really outside.
We're doing it under the shade.
Someone's coming.
Oi, seriously?
You've got to be kidding.
Housei Tsukitei
Old lady
Summer this year has been ridiculously hot, it's pissing me off!
I can't sleep at night because I'm soaked with sweat,
Mosquitoes bite me, it's itchy! Itchy!
My appetite goes down, somen is more than enough for one meal!
Yo, don't you think so too?
What the hell do you think?
A chance!
This is your chance!
Make a comeback.
He can win this one.
They're on the same level.
Where is your house even at?
What you just said was completely wrong!
The location of your house is completely wrong!
Do you even know why you have to go to work?
Most of your friends are bad people, Yo!
He sucks.
I'm fed up with how hot this summer has been!
I'm fed up with my husband's low salary!
I'm fed up with my useless son!
But Housei, I'm fed up with you the most!
Oh, that was good!
That was good.
Good-for-nothing summer!
Hey! Good-for-nothing summer!
Say something back.
Good-for-nothing summer!
He went along with it!
He's going
along with it!
Good-for-nothing summer!
She won.
I think she won.
Just now...
Good-for-nothing summer!
She beat you...!
Yep. You... you lost...!
Good-for-nothing summer!
She came up with a really good phrase, that "Good-for-nothing summer".
See, there she goes again.
Amazing.
I think your rap phrases lack originality.
You need phrases that people will take in.
You're not saying anything memorable.
Actually, I'm hungry so...
I'm hungry so my rhythm is bad at the moment.
So you're saying that you'll do better after you eat something?
That's right!
Let's head in here for a moment then.
For the sake of Housei, who claims that his rhythm is being
affected by hunger, the members take a break at a soba restaurant.
Thank you for waiting!
5 seiro sobas.
How do you think we went?
After we eat...
5 seiro sobas.
Ah... I dissed them real good.
Did he really?
No, I don't think you dissed them that well...
It kind of feels like you're at a disadvantage.
Housei stole that old lady's phrase at the very end there.
Thank you for waiting!
He took her best phrase and kind of went along
with it. Maybe he'll do better after we finish eating.
This soba looks delicious!
It's because I was hungry. I'm just hungry.
Housei Tsukitei
Salaryman
Yo, hold up, hold up, do we have here
the comedian who changed his name?
Your new name... uh... what was it again?
Your name change leaves no impression at all!
Nobody knows your new name!
What's your name anyway?
What the hell...
So you don't know my name?
Where did you guys even come from?
Tell me, that's all I wanna know.
Before we move on, Yo.
Where the hell did you guys come from?
Cause I have no idea.
No one cares about your new name!
What did he just say?
He dissed you hard.
Those two old ladies were great.
This is delicious.
About those old ladies just before... Were you
trying to get their addresses or something?
"Where did you come from?"...
That "Where did you come from?".
Can you really say that?
He sucks, doesn't he?
Absolutely.
Saying that is no good. He's really bad at this.
I didn't quite know what to say...
You had nothing to say?
I really didn't.
Defeated 3 times in a row with his unmemorable raps,
Housei heads into the shopping district once again.
Let's try to win at least once.
High school girls...
Housei Tsukitei
3 high school girls
Well, well, what do we have here? Yamasaki?
Totally boring as always (Obviously)
Well, well, haven't you gotten skinnier?
But in the end, you still look gross (Obviously)
Tell him!
Y'all, y'all, what do y'all even know?
I don't think you know anything at all, Yo!
What do y'all even know?
That's right, nothing at all!
Nothing! Your pigtails are dragging the value of your raps.
Down, down, down, down!
Doesn't this suck?
He can't rap at all.
Baldy! Baldy! Baldy!
Baldy! Baldy!
Make a comeback!
Your body just keeps on deteriorating!
You're becoming an old man, hahaha!
Your sense of humor just keeps on deteriorating!
Make a comeback, make a comeback!
He's crying.
He started crying.
Your face looks like Ichiro Mizuki.
Note: Ichiro Mizuki is a singer famous for writing anime theme songs.
After the break
That man joins the rap battle...
Who is the next opponent for Housei, who has not
been able to construct a memorable rap up until now!?
I'll heat up the opponent and then beat them down.
Housei Tsukitei
Mother and child
Seriously?
These kind of people are joining in?
Wow! Wow! It's Downtown!
Wow! Wow! It's Cocorico!
They're really, really, really cool!
I love them, yay yay!
Boo, boo, Housei boo!
Really boring, seriously annoying!
Do your best, Housei!
Don't make such grand claims.
While your nose is running! Your nose is running Yo!
Your nose is running Yo!
When Housei shows up on TV, change the channel!
Your nose is running! Your nose is running! Your nose is running!
ZAPPING! Change the channel!
Your nose is running! Running! Running!
When Housei shows up on TV, change the channel!
Running! Running! Your nose is running!
Running! Running! Running! Your nose is running!
When Housei shows up on TV, change the channel!
ZAPPING! Change the channel!
Running! Running!
Your nose is running! Your nose is running! Yay!
No, that was nothing to celebrate.
You said nothing but "Your nose is running".
Don't say that.
You didn't go with the rhythm at all.
That's right.
The only thing you said was "running, running, running, running"!
Eh?
Seriously?
Housei Tsukitei
Old man
Housei!
Listen to my dream yo, yay, yay!
My dream is to collect figurines, yay, yay!
Housei, let me hear your dream too, yay!
My dream is to live in a room full of curtains, Yo!
Do you get it? Do you understand?
I want a lot of curtains in my room!
And, you get it don't you?
I understand that much, yay, yay!
Let's fulfill our wishes!
Thank you!
I'll try my best too.
So Housei, try your best even when you lose, Yo!
Try your best, Yo.
Laters.
How did I do?
The part about the curtain was unnecessary.
The moment you said that, you both started rapping together.
That 'curtain' part.
You've been sweating a lot though.
When I got to the bit about the curtain, I just exploded in a ball of sweat.
Well in the end,
we both found some common ground.
Common ground is no good.
But that's what rap is all about, isn't it?
Seriously, let's stop now.
Let's go back.
It just went "bang" up there.
Before we leave, Yo.
What the hell is up with you? What are you doing Yo?
At least say one word, Yo! What's with that face?
Housei Tsukitei
Producer Nakamura
What are you doing with that face? At least say one word, Yo!
I am, I am this show's producer.
You're just a comedian!
Please come through.
How can you be making these unreasonable requests Yo, Yo, Yo!
Sorry.
We're sorry for the inconvenience.
Oi, tell me about your personality!
What's your personality like, tell me Yo, Yo, Yo, Yo!
It's almost...
My, my personality is always the same.
That's it for today.
I've got guts, I've got guts, yay!
What guts? What guys?
What guts do you have?
Tell me, what guts with that same old personality, Yo?
The way I act at work, at home, and anywhere else.
Is exactly the same!
Was today's project a success?
Even if it wasn't, I still did it!
I did it, Yo!
Look at that group of children.
What you just said makes no sense!
They're going to traumatize the children.
Subbed by J-Hive
j-hive.weebly.com
Yes
Few days ago in the meeting, Matsumoto-san said that
if we did a Kiki Starbucks, he'd get it hands down.
Do you remember saying that, Matsumoto-san?
Honestly, it ain't even funny...
so you'll get it right for sure.
There won't be anything happening.
Seriously, I'll get it right like nothing happened and just end it.
We'd like to see it.
That just goes to shows us how much you consume it.
Yes, yes.
Emergency Planning, Matsumoto's "Kiki Starbucks" Challenge!
Out of the 10 coffee shop chains, will Matsumoto identify Starbucks' coffee?
First of all, I can pretty much tell from the foam in the coffee.
You're doing it without sampling it first then.
Without sampling?
Looks like you've already got this one in the bag.
The ones without foam are wrong.
The ones without the foam isn't from Starbucks.
StarBucks' coffee has foam on top.
In that case, the ones out of the question are E and H.
"I" as well.
You can just exclude them.
We'll now be looking for the right one.
There's no foam.
You can stay in the back.
※ Please enjoy without knowing the correct answer
Please tell us the correct one.
You can take em off now, Matsumoto-san.
The ones without foam are wrong.
Yeah, yeah.
Starbucks' coffee has foam on top.
There's no refuting it!
Anyway, have a taste and tell us if it's wrong or...
It's not even going to be funny, is it alright?
We'd like to see you get it right.
You sure?
Yes.
Then I'll really get it, like nothing happened.
If I don't get it right then I might as well be dead.
If that happened, it'd be quite the surprise.
How about he never drinks from Starbucks again?
That's right.
Why don't we settle on it.
I'm totally fine with it.
No joke.
Totally wrong, what the hell is this?
Is it alright, going through it as usual?
Just don't say, 'I'm going to the store' midway through.
How many times a week do you drink coffee?
Do you have it daily?
I don't know about per week.
Yeah, sorry. It wasn't the right way to put it.
I've never thought it as weekly intake.
You drink a fair amount then, how many times a day is it?
I'd say, about 2 - 3 times a day.
2 - 3 times a day?
So it isn't once a week.
Yeah, when he's coming to shoot for Gaki, he's at it right away.
Going by order, it seems.
Even so, since he hasn't sampled it...
This one is terribly wrong.
This one too, totally wrong.
Not this either, it's too acidic.
I'm not sure about this one.
This isnt it either.
This is probably wrong.
Totally not it.
Sorry, this isn't gong to be any fun at all, since i'm going at it seriously.
Then, the ones on the bottom are still...
Those might be the one.
It's the last one now.
It's been narrowed down to three.
Well then, it's gotta be amongst these three.
A, B, F.
Will Matsumoto be able to identify Starbucks' coffee out of the ten varieties?
It's been narrowed down to three.
Well then, it's gotta be amongst these three.
A, B, F.
Yeah.
He's taking it seriously, isn't he?
...in all earnestness.
B might be it.
Not this either.
A or B?
Whoa, damn!
So quick.
I've got it, right?
Can't say until you pick one.
B, it is.
B, is it?
Starbucks' coffee...
Please say it then... Starbucks' cofee is...
Starbucks coffee is B.
Just, what was that?
You suck!
Gimme a break!
Can this just not be aired?
Nope!
This will go on air.
Aren't you just something?
What now?
Want me to reveal the correct one?
The correct answer is G.
I'll just say this.
Starbucks has various blends.
It's not like they use the same beans.
It's different everyday.
What blend of Starbucks is this?
Coffee comes in a blend,
what I just drank could've been from Congo.
It's not the same everyday!
Are you all fuckin' idiots?
Go home!
You can't be serious.
Go home! Go home!
What's wrong with you?
Don't ever come back, idiots!
Go home!
He got angry instead.
Third-class comedians!
Go home!
Third-rates!
Go home, third-rates!
It was prepared since you're '1st-class'.
What's with him?
He got really angry instead.
This better not get aired!
For real?