Leaving the NTV building, where are these 5 going?
I'm so hungry
Yeah my stomach is growling
I haven't eaten anything since last night
- Why is that?
- To make myself hungrier
Just for this episode, I made myself hungrier
I'm just straight up hungry
Yeah I'm just hungry like always
I can keep eating forever
I don't need to make myself hungrier or anything
Tanaka ...
you're not that hungry right?
No no that's not true
Are we there yet, Endo?
The restaurant?
We'll find a nice place soon
I'm so goddamn hungry
- How hungry?
- How much sushi could you eat?
I could eat 100 pieces
- For real?
- Yeah 100
100 ... isn't that much
- 700 pieces
- That's right
- Now you're talking
- 700 pieces?
I could eat 700, 1400 pieces
"Up ahead there is a Kentucky Fried Chicken"
- Kenta?
- Kentucky!
- That's a great idea
- Let's go, let's go!
- Let's gooo
- KFC is pretty poggers right?
- It's OK if we go then?
- Yeah for sure
How many pieces?
How many pieces could I eat?
- Not the pieces?
- The fillet sandwich
Yeah I'll order that
If you eat something like that ...
- Eh?
- What do you mean?
it's just ..
It's really something!
- Here we go
- Be careful
- Oh here it is
- This is it
Uwah looks delicious
- Looks damn tasty!
- Tasty!
Let's order whatever we want
- So hungry
- Yeah super hungry
For now can I get two coleslaws?
- You need to get some meat
- OK you order then
Just keep ordering after each other
Can I get one piece of this?
Cut it out man
You're barely eating!
This is just for now
Make mine a combo please!
Chicken fillet
So loud
What drink would you like?
A big cola just for him
Get a large
This is just the first thing
Chicken cutlet sandwich
I'll get that too
Do you want a combo, or just the sandwich?
- The sandwich
- The combo
For the moment, the sandwich
"For the moment"?
Alright that's good for now
Wait, wait a second
You didn't order yet
I'm ordering, I'm ordering
The Smile Chicken Combo
That item is for children unfortunately
I guess that's not happening then
For someone turning 50 next year, that's not happening
Then I'll just have this
I'm a gourmet eater
I want to eat lots of different things
Whatever they are
I hope my jaw doesn't hit the table
From opening too much?
I think you'll be fine
I've been anticipating this!
I'm absolutely starving
"Of course, the hungry five devour their meals"
You're fine with that?
Here are your large fries
(sorry no idea what they said here)
You're good with just that?
I don't think this is gonna be enough
but she already left
We can call her back for you
No no let's not bother her
"Hungry Drive has only just started,"
"there's no way they can be full already"
What happened?
Hamada-san ...
- Oh this is mine?
- Yes it is
You put it in my basket
Oh my bad
"Was this a joke to lighten the mood?"
He said "This is so fun"
I'm saying this banter is so much fun
I'm saying Yoshimoto is so much fun
"The 5 were eating at a good pace,"
"then that man shows us how big his stomach is!"
This is so warm!
I'll eat that for you
Stop that, please
Are you serious? I ordered this
You're not just like, passing this off to me right?
I wa- I wanna eat that, please!
I wanna eat it too, let me have it
Yummy!
A brand new taste for me
Stop it!
We're pretty much done aren't we
What do you mean we're done?
This energetic-ness
The fries are finished!
You can have the last one
Didn't see this last one in there
Are you sure, I can have it?
That wasn't enough food!
That was a lot of unnecessary ad-lib
This is bad
- What do you mean "This is bad"?
- No no I mean
It means you're hungry right?
There is no break from the Hungry Drive
They get in the car and seek out the next restaurant
We've been doing this show for so long,
I don't remember you guys saying "I'm hungry" this often
- You were just tolerating it?
- Yes exactly, exactly
We thought it would be rude
Oh that's why?
They got caught up in "compliance"
I see, you were just tolerating the hunger
I'm reading Iida-bashi as Iida-meshi (meshi means meal/rice)
The bridge might be made of rice
I'm talking about rice man!
What the hell is IIda-rice?
"There is a PRONTO up ahead"
What is PRONTO?
It's like Satin (Cafe)
I wanna go there
Let's go, let's go!
They have like cakes and stuff
They have spaghetti too
Really?
We're here!
Pasta is great too
You think they could make me a large?
I came here before on a Drama location-shoot
"219 Locations around the country"
They have stuff like this too
"7 minutes since they ate KFC"
"What will they order?"
Stuff like this too huh?
Let's just get some Pasta, right?
2 servings, for us to share
- I wanna eat this
- That looks good
- This is good too
- Yeah it is
We could just order everything, you know?
Try everything
Wait wait wait
We have to drive again,
and we'll get hungry again anyways
So let's just try one thing here
- OK then let's get this
- One serving
Just one is good right?
You're not hungry are you?
I am, I am!
That's why I'm asking if just one is good?
- Well, just one?
- It's a bit unfortunate right?
So let's do this,
Does that have volume?!
Of course it has volume
If it has volume then it's good
Alright, so let's order this
We don't want like cake or anything?
- We don't
- No we don't
"Endo will order for everyone else"
"What did he spot?"
That looks good
"Unexpectedly, a side order for the pasta?"
"Will he showcase his hunger here?"
- I ordered for us
- Number 28 right?
- Will they make us a large size?
- No unfortunately ...
Uwah, really?
We might have to order again
"The pasta isn't here yet ... this is the peak of their hunger"
- This uh
- A short cake?
I see why you want that
Tell us if you're gonna get something like that!
Not letting us have any
- Oh you can ha-
- No whatever man you eat it
Please go ahead, this is good for me
Eat some man
He's not letting go
I don't this guy is hungry man
Just dig in man
But the junior is supposed to serve it!
He took so little
The hell is this?
That's a kids meal
Delicious!
"Their hunger does not seem to fade"
"Matsumoto, who wants even more food ... "
Allow me to enjoy this eel
Matsumoto-san is really slurping!
Alright then give this to him
Please eat this dish as well
I don't want them to mix together in here
Is it okay if I eat all this?
I don't want to be an entitled senpai
- No please enjoy
- It's no problem at all
Really?
- It's not just "compliance" ...
- No nothing like that
We should have ordered a bit more
That is really true,
that is, completely correct,
That is,
That is, so true
Just two dishes, right?
This was nothing to me
- Shall we go?
- Let's go
Let's go and prepare to eat again
Cause we're still hungry, right?
So hungry!
"They ate all this in 45 minutes"
I just wanna eat something with volume!
Is there any all-you-can-eat?
Something like a buffet
I've been banned from a few buffets, you know?
Oh cause you ate too much?
You can also get banned from those places that give you a prize
I've literally never done that
"So far it's been easy on their stomachs ... this next restaurant should change that"
- "Up ahead, there is a Baskin Robbins"
- Finally!
I've been waiting for this!
Hell yeah!
I really wanna eat that, sir!
I was wondering what might have been here
That's it!
"But first, a hearty ramen!"
Goddamn, I am hungry
Makes you hungrier, right?
Looks so tasty
Wow, it's like this huh?
"You will get addicted to their hearty ramen!"
We should let the hungriest guys just start eating
What do you normally order from here?
I want to try their basic ramen
What about the fatty pork?
You guys are really something
You youngsters are amazing
Then I'll have the asari clam ramen! (A light dish)
Ramen is a great choice
So that means, we're sharing a bowl right?
We're sharing the clam ramen, right?
Is that really proper?
5 men sharing a bowl
Eat from the same bowl one after another?
Yeah just one bowl is ...
That doesn't really jive with the "compliance"
You're using that word wrong man
First choice then,
The tontoro
Which size?
Standard, or large?
Extra large?
The standard right?
- The price is not that different Tanaka
- It's cheap!
The standard-
Be a man, dude!
I wanted to try the Gyoza too
But it's too late now
Excuse me, server!
- No no, no need to bother
- Sorry can we order some more?
Is it too late for Gyoza?
No it's no problem, just 4-5 mins more
I want you to take your time though,
But we're on a schedule, so just forget it then
I think it will be fine
I can make it in that time
I really want you to take your time though
Let Matsumoto have his Asari Ramen
I'll that some of that too though
We're not splitting this?
We're all on this table though
How about I just pass this bowl down?
Don't pass it down after one bite!
You're passing it back?
Of course, we ate some of it!
The bowl returns?
I thought it ended after the first bite
Please dig into the pork!
Are you sure I can have it?
I'll try the noodles then
No we said the pork
Give that to Matsumoto-san
"Give that to Matsumoto-san"
Endo, everyone should eat this
Is it okay if I eat it all myself?
You don't want this?
Ignored?
He ignored me?
Yamasaki?
Yamasaki!
Hold on I have to eat it twice? That's unfair
What's unfair?
That I get to eat two, is that OK with you guys?
I guess that is unfair, but I decided on this system
There's no helping it I guess
Isn't it better to pass this heavy dish around a bit more?
I mean this in a good way,
the noodles are not decreasing!
Is it OK?
That I get to eat all of these leftover noodles
No no please dig in
This is a good quantity, right?
Tanaka you can finish that
I wish I could finish it, but oh well
- Looks tasty
- So tasty
Stop splashing them around
You barely ate it!
You ate so little!
I don't remember it having this much fat
Ok let's go goddamn I'm hungry
- Different stomach for desert!
- Baskin Robbins!