[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
The First Gaki-no-Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
The First Gaki-no-Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
Sangenjaya Edition!
Let's go!
What number is this?
It's our third... no, our fourth time!
Hold on.
We're in the correct shoot, right?
It's not something else, right?
We did prank you last time, didn't we?
Oh right, we didn't do any of the stuff we wanted to do last time.
It was my bad, I'm actually sorry.
But I don't trust you guys anymore.
You don't trust the staff.
But we thought you wouldn't come back, you know?
He doesn't trust us.
You've stopped trusting us!
What a shame, Hamada!
I'm not leaving!
He says that, but didn't he go home super early back at Jiyugaoka?
Right.
You were too free! (Jiyu = free, Oka = Hill, Jiyugaoka = Hill of the free)
This very same program was filmed back in March at Jiyugaoka, the high-end residential area.
I'd never do this in February.
This great search took 5 hours!
And in the end, the guys didn't find a single celebrity.
And finally, Hamada sneaked out!
This left a deep wound on the member's hearts.
Now, in this new town, the guys are looking for revenge!
It's Setagaya ward's, Sangenjaya!
Rows of shops line the side of the streets.
It's Setagaya's most popular entertainment district, where people gather in droves!
Many celebrities are said to live in this area, and the boys cannot leave until they find one!
A ruthless challenge awaits them!
I'm just gonna come out and say it, that shirt is too much man.
What do you mean?
Hold on, hold on...
I wasn't trying to be funny or anything lik that!
An oblivious airhead is funny, but gets old once he's aware of it.
Hold on, hold on, I'm not trying to do anything!
I'm not pulling anything here!
I'm serious!
What is it then?
There's someone with a mask over there, who is it?
You're right!
Is she a celebrity?
She's wearing a mask.
There's someone over there.
Who? Who? Who?
Ah, excuse me.
Let's stroll around until we find a celebrity!
Sangenjaya Edition!
These are the rules: The shoot won't end until we meet a celebrity.
However, all members have to know the celebrity's name.
And naturally, we also need filming consent from their respective agencies.
The time is 4:06 PM.
The search begins under the sunny sky!
The setting sun!! The setting sun is hitting me!
We actually found some celebrities in Jiyugaoka.
I asked them later, you know?
NONSTYLE's Ishida was there.
That's great.
Oh, really?
And Akihito from Porno Graffiti.
Right, right.
NONSTYLE's Ishida was getting some work on his teeth at that dentist on the second floor, wasn't he?
Oh, is that so?
He was watching the shoot from the second floor, but that brat didn't wanna come down.
I see!
That was the worst.
He really didn't want to come down...
The guys get right to work as they set a path towards Carrot Tower.
And then Matsumoto does this...
You never know, there might be a poetry class there.
We might find someone.
A poetry class?
Nothing but old people attend those classes!
Look, look.
Look at the poetry class.
We can't go in there.
It's fine, don't worry.
Try going in.
Look at this!
It's fine, try...
You never know, they could be doing some rad poetry in there.
You can't go in there, it's totally blocked.
For real?
We can't?
Yeah...
Not even the owners can get in there.
Right?
See? It's locked.
Don't go opening up other people's homes.
It says, "We teach a variety of poems".
I barely touched the knob and look at how dirty my hands are.
That's why we told you!
Oh, we're at the cinema now.
There was a movie theater here, look!
-A retro one.
-Oh right, it was here.
-Which one was it?
-This one, this one.
-A retro one.
-Oh right, it was here.
-Which one was it?
-This one, this one.
This one, here.
-Which one was it?
-This one, this one.
This one, here.
This is the one.
And there was another one over there.
Oh really?
I wonder what they'll do with this one...
I think they're demolishing this remaining one.
The atmosphere around here was really good.
Even so, I think we'll be done fairly quickly today.
You think?
Yes, definitely.
We're gonna have too much free time, we won't know what to do with it.
You have a feeling?
Yeah.
Endo, keep an eye out cause a lot of them just run away.
I'm looking!
Sure, sure.
Endo, keep an eye out cause a lot of them just run away.
We can't let them get away this time.
I'm keeping my eyes peeled.
I feel like there's tons of actors and musicians around here.
I don't know about that...
Look out for the ones wearing hats.
Hats and masks.
Masks, right.
Where do people go in this area?
In Sangenjaya?
We're right in the center.
Here?
Let's walk around here.
Who's most familiar with this place?
I think that's me.
Hosei, you?
Where are we going?
Do we have a destination, like Tsutaya?
(Video rental store and bookstore chain)
We can aim for Tsutaya.
-Let's go to Tsutaya.
-Can we even go in there?
We can't film inside Carrot Tower.
We can't go in, he says.
We'll have to wait outside Carrot Tower then.
That's right.
The guys go around Carrot Tower and arrive at the stoplight opposite Seiyu.
(Seiyu is a Group of supermarkets, shopping centers and department stores)
There's a Seiyu and a Tokyu store, lots of people buy their groceries here.
Celebrities have to be buying their groceries here.
You're totally right.
There's tons of stores on this street.
Our researchers have told us this is the most likely place to find a celebrity.
For example:
Yumi Adachi.
Yumi Adachi?
Or Dragon Ash's vocalist.
Dragon Ash's vocalist?
Furuya, right?
Furuya?
Yes.
With the staff's tips, the crew keeps searching.
There ain't nobody!
Wait, wait...
We've just arrived, you know?
That's right, they have barely just begun!
This sun drains your stamina right away, don't you think?
Yeah, it does.
Yeah.
This is the perfect place, Muji.
(Muji is a retailer that sells household and consumer goods.)
Right, Muji!
But we can't go in.
But one of us can go in and check, right?
Oh, right.
Should I go?
-Sure.
-Okay.
I'll tag along.
Let's go then.
Go ahead.
Wait, what if someone walks by and all of you are inside?!
Then, should I stay?
Yamasaki, you stay too.
We'll go ahead then.
Cocorico, you guys stay too.
Oh, then we'll stay behind.
Alright, then.
W-W-What?!
What are you doing?
Everyone's staying.
No, no, no!
Hamada, you should go in.
You idiot!
I don't know what's happening anymore.
I don't know what to do anymore.
I told you guys to go!
I don't know either.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Matsumoto and Yamasaki, just go.
Okay.
We'll go as well, okay?
No, you guys don't all have to go!
We have to keep searching!
Then, are you going in alone, Yamasaki?
Sure.
Sure, he can go in alone, I don't care.
Then, I'll go in as well.
Me too.
Let's all go in together.
What the hell are you on about?
What if someone walks by?!
I got confused, sorry.
What the hell are you guys thinking?
I got confused.
In the end, Matsumoto and Hosei search the store.
Hamada and Kokoriko search the streets for celebrities.
You never know, they always run away.
-Yeah.
-Yes, it always happens.
Personally, I think they'll sneak around more easily once the sun goes down, so we have to be quick.
You're totally right.
I don't wanna experience Jiyugaoka again...
5 minutes after they started searching...
Let's go, let's go.
You didn't find anyone, right?
They did not find a single celebrity.
Damn it!
Celebrities~!
Next up, the guys head to Chazawa street, the main road lined up with tons of stores!
So freaking hot!
Let's find one soon!
It's so hot.
But there are plenty of stores all around here.
Ah... I hate this sun...
It's so hot.
Maybe they start coming out to the bars at night...
-No, I don't think we'll go that late...
-Right, we wanna finish earlier than that.
They could be in there.
This place is pretty popular.
Cocorico goes inside this popular Pachinko parlor!
Meanwhile, the remaining members are left outside to keep the search going.
Yama, make sure to take a good look inside the cars as well.
They're definitely there.
Sure.
Yama, make sure to take a good look inside the cars as well.
They're definitely there.
We can't let them slip between our fingers.
They always run away.
And then...
They said there's no one famous today.
But sometimes they see Seiji Rokkaku.
That's so like him!
Mr. Rokkaku.
That's so funny!
Mr. Rokkaku would definitely be in there.
I really wanted to find him there!
I kinda feel like meeting him now.
Let's try going after him.
Going after him?
There ain't nobody around...
I mean, we're just looking for a single celebrity...
It's been 46 minutes since the search started.
With the sun shining down their faces, the guys have started to show some signs of fatigue.
My stamina gauge is starting to deplete, you know?
-You're already tired?
-Yeah.
That was fast!
The sun burned right through me.
The sun, huh?
You're kidding me.
Huh? This bump?
This one.
On this?
Yes, that's the one.
It's all the sun's fault, you know?
The sun is really draining my stamina...
I can't believe you tripped over this thing...
On this...
See how much they're digging into him for such a small thing?
I have to be super careful when I walk, you never know what they're gonna say.
This thing is also super inconvenient.
I was thinking: "Where are all the celebrities", when I tripped on that thing...
It's been 1 hour since the start of the search.
Oh no, it's starting to feel like Jiugaoka all over again.
I'm also starting to get this bad feeling.
-It really feels like Jiugaoka.
-There ain't nobody!
Nobody!
There ain't...
Don't you guys feel like a break already?
Should we have a strategy meeting?
Yeah.
Should we stop somewhere?
Should we look for Damemoto at that OB GYN?
He could be there, you never know.
With that being said, the crew heads to a cafe in hopes to make up a strategy.
Over here, on the terrace.
-Huh?
-I figured.
We'll sit side by side, right?
Over here?
It's gonna look like The Family Game. (1983 Japanese movie directed by Yoshimitsu Morita)
We just need a place where we can look at the street.
Okay.
Then I'll sit in Juzo Itami's seat.
(Actor that starred in "The Family Game")
Those who aren't seated will be directors.
Who does he play in The Family Game?
-The father.
-The dad.
Oh really?
Yeah.
May we order?
One dark roasted coffee.
And one cafe au lait.
Cafe au lait.
And a ginger ale.
Ginger ale, okay.
Ice coffee for me.
Sure.
-One ice tea, please.
-Sure.
Hold on, this is no good.
There's definitely some celebs around here, but they've sneaking past us.
You think so?
They're definitely around us.
Yeah, I'm sure of it.
There were definitely 1 or 2 celebrities around.
Ishida said it was pretty scary.
What was scary?
Downtown.
Don't joke around.
He said he was scared of you guys.
He doesn't know what we're filming.
Once they see Downtown, they just run away.
Downtown-itis.
Downtown-itis, yeah!
Some say everyone has caught it.
Downtown-itis.
What's this?
Oh, thank you.
Their drinks have arrived.
They wet their throats looking for another battle.
It's really good.
It's super good.
Mine is super good as well.
-This is such an authentic ginger ale.
You're right!
Right?
Hey, try this.
It's super authentic!
This ginger ale is super good.
It's the real deal!
It's super dense.
There's tons of ginger in there.
Yeah, a ton!
This is amazing.
Oh, it's so refreshing.
Right?
It tastes like Hiyashiame.
(Sweet ginger drink that is popular in the Kansai region)
Right, right, right!
Like the ones in Kansai.
Totally!
It's super good!
What's the name of this place?
Why aren't you using your own straw?
Everyone was being considerate by drinking from the rim...
And you don't even use the straw... Who's gonna use it now?!
Once again, the guys begin their search.
That's where I wanna head to next.
Even if we go through there, it's hopeless.
Are we all going?
You were all: "It's super good" earlier...
But you're leaving a lot of it!
Let's just try going that way.
The ginger is a bit too harsh for me.
Thank you for the drinks!
We have to put everything back.
You know, I'm the kind of guy that always puts stuff back into place.
I really hate when people do this.
Right? We should take care of this stuff.
It bothers me.
Thank you for the drinks!
And I always thank the staff afterwards.
The other four left Matsumoto behind and pushed onwards.
-That's probably the main street, right?
-Yes.
It's super hot.
And so humid...
I bet some celebrity owns this Benz.
Sure looks like it.
You might be right.
It's like the CEO's car, no?
Yeah, the CEO's car.
You never know, one of our members might get run over and end the shoot.
But then Hamada spots something!
There's someone with a mask over there, who is it?
You're right!
Is she a celebrity?
Hosei runs up to the masked girl without hesitation!
Hello!
Are you a celebrity?
Have they finally found their long awaited celebrity?
Thanks!
What's going on?
It was just a normal person.
But she was wearing a mask...
-Right?
-Yes, she's wearing it because she has the sniffles.
What's with that?
Then why'd you run back to us with such a face of shock?
I don't know...
She had the sniffles, huh?
Alright.
I think it's about time we took a break.
The 246 is that way...
I think we can search that way as well.
-Oh, really?
-Yes.
With that, the guys move towards Don Quixote on highway 246.
We're already here.
Yes.
We're here.
If we can't find anyone here it's over, you know?
Tokyo is done for.
There's no one around, huh?
It just means there's no more celebrities in Tokyo.
Don Quixote is a treasure trove of celebrities.
Oh right, we've returned.
They guys have arrived at Don Quixote.
That's ones really good.
And then...
Should we go have a look?
There's Don Quixote.
There's someone over there.
This girl totally looks like it.
Who? Who? Who?
Ah, excuse me.
Do you have a minute?
You're a celebrity, aren't you?
Have they finally found a celebrity?!
Should we go have a look?
There's Don Quixote.
There's someone over there.
This girl totally looks like it.
Who? Who? Who?
Ah, excuse me.
Do you have a minute?
You're a celebrity, aren't you?
A model?
Model?
I have work now, I have an audition.
What kind of audition?
It's for makeup.
Makeup? See?
I told you!
Hold on, just give us 1 minute.
What's going on?
She's got an audition for some makeup.
-Hamada!
-Please hold on.
She's got an audition for some makeup.
-Hamada!
-Please hold on.
I'm actually in an agency already.
Is he inside?
Just a minute... Are you okay on time?
But you have an audition right now, don't you?
She doesn't wanna be on camera without makeup!
I don't think that's true.
I'm not famous or anything!
Could you just tell us your name?
I'm A-Azusa Azuma.
Azusa Azuma!
I dunno!
I have no clue.
It's Azusa Azuma!
It's Az Az!
Is that Ms. Azuma?!
She is a model, Azusa Azuma!
However...
Could you take off your glasses for us?
-She's called Azusa Azuma.
-You're very cute.
Azusa Azuma.
She's got an audition.
-Yes.
-Oh, is that so?
You'll be late, right?
Sorry about this.
But I'm so happy I met you guys.
I knew immediately.
She was a no-go from the start.
But I like how proactive you are.
Right?
Let's split up.
Some of us go to Don Quixote and the rest go around the block.
Alright, I'm going to Don Quixote.
Cocorico will search the inside of the store.
This one's also a Don Quixote.
-Oh, really?
-Yes
Yeah, this one's also a Don Quixote.
-Oh, really?
-Yes
Yeah, this one's also a Don Quixote.
Downtown and Hosei will look around the block.
This has got to be the center of Sangenjaya!
I say this because we just ran into Azusa Azuma, Az Az.
Ah!
You found someone?!
Who?! Who?!
Gaki-no-Tsukai News!
Shiodome Paradise will be unveiled on July 25th!
This bus will be full of Gaki-no-Tsukai fun!
We'll dive into the uncharted territory of comedy.
We'll be waiting for you!
This has got to be the center of Sangenjaya!
I say this because we just ran into Azusa Azuma, Az Az.
Ah!
You found someone?!
Who?! Who?!
What are you doing here?!
You've got tons of tissues!
Hold on, this is so raw!
It's totally unadulterated!
Hold on, what's going on?
That's amazing!
It's so raw! Super raw!
Excuse me.
What were you doing?
I was just doing some shopping.
Why do you have this many tissues?
Well, they were pretty cheap so...
Would you even use this much?
You didn't buy anything hard.
It's all soft stuff.
You're a softie!
But I'm so happy!
You'll get the clear if all 5 of you can name him.
Sure, of course.
You have to say the group's name and his name.
Huh?
I know it, I know.
Don't worry.
Then let's start with Endo.
We can't do that!
We have to all do it together.
We all have to say it together!
You guys don't remember me?
Of course we do! We remember you!
Of course we remember!
You're Matsuo's partner, aren't you?
Right?
He's Matsuo's partner!
That's right.
You have that bit where you go, "So frustrating!".
So frustrating!
Will the guys be able to say his name?
One, two, three...
Zabungle's Kato!
You guys know.
Okay.
That's amazing!
We did well.
I knew it perfectly!
Say again then.
Zabungle's Kato, right?
That's right.
Now, all that's left is to receive approval from his agency.
They said it's okay.
It's okay!
Watanabe Entertainment said it's okay.
We got the clear!
After 1 hour and 52 minutes, the guys have completed the mission!
Did you park your car nearby?
Not at all, I just walked.
Is your house that close?
Yes.
So you're walking home?
Yes, of course.
Your house is super closeby, right?
Yes, it's very close.
Then let's go to your house.
What?!
-We have to!
-Should we?
For real?!
You live super close, we have to visit.
Let's go then.
-Is it close?
-Seriously?!
Is there someone home?
-Sure, let's go, let's go.
-Well, my wife's home.
Which way? That way?
-Sure, let's go, let's go.
-Well, my wife's home.
Which way? That way?
You have a wife?!
I do, and 2 children.
I see!
You looked super shocked.
Well, that's just natural.
With that being said, we decided to barge in on the Kato household.
How long were you shopping before we found you?
Well, I got out of the house about 10 minutes ago.
10 minutes?!
We found you very quickly.
But what a coincidence!
I'm so glad!
We can finally go home.
That's amazing.
I thought we'd never go home.
-Please let me put a mic on you.
-Oh sure.
I thought we'd never go home.
-Please let me put a mic on you.
-Oh sure.
Of course!
But we really caught you in the wild.
I'm sorry about that.
No, no, don't worry.
But we really caught you in the wild.
For real...
We caught you right in the middle of your daily life.
Celebrities do hang around here.
-Right?
-Right!
It's about a minute away.
Don't you have to buy that one?
I already bought this much.
But that one looks pretty cheap.
-This one was cheaper.
-Are you sure?
Come on already.
Stop it.
We arrived at the Kato household after a few minutes.
Excuse us!
What?!
We're here with your husband...
-Hello!
-Hello.
Oh, hello!
-We just found him doing some shopping.
-Right.
He was holding a mountain of toilet paper.
Is that so?
Oh, there we go.
Ma'am, excuse our intrusion.
Excuse us. Sorry!
-Excuse us.
-Oh, hello there little guy.
How old is he?
He'll be 1 soon.
1 year old!
That's amazing.
Is he a boy?
-Yes, he's a boy.
-Sorry, sorry.
Ah, he's crying.
Yama, stop it.
You can't be doing that.
Right.
Guess he doesn't like being touched.
You just scared him.
Were you scared?
Poor guy.
Right? I wanna crash right here.
How long have you lived here?
About 4 years...
4 years?
She's cooking and we barged in here...
We're bothering her.
We have to go home soon.
We're not eating?
How many nights can we stay?
What are you on about?!
How many nights will you have us?
-But anyway, thank you for inviting us is.
-Oh, you're welcome anytime.
Sorry about all this.
Thanks.
We will be using this footage.
Right?
Sorry, I don't think my agency will allow it.
Ouch!
His dad is getting smacked and the son goes like this.
He never sees this!
He was so shocked when he smacked him.
The Yamazaki vs Moriman series is finally getting a Blu-ray release!
Yamazaki's wonderful defeats are making a comeback!
A selection of the best shows and a talk-show compilation are getting re-released!
For more details visit our webpage!