Yamazaki Hosei's super-ass-magic!!
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi  Hamada Masatoshi
Good Evening
Good Evening!
So... what is it today?
I really didn't understand, actually, though I had a phone call
But they told me this will be a great success
~Opening~Today, Yamazaki will use his butt to perform various techniques
Actually this does remind me of our youthful cold-resistance contests
Is this going to be about coldness?
No, I don't think it would be so
But it probably would have been better that way.
Shall we call him here?
Yeah, let's call him
Please come here, Yamazaki-san!
What the hell?
Ass Magician Yamazaki Hosei
He doesn't seems anything mighty at all
Those are some nice dancing moves!
Totally nice, really!
So, this new kind of performance is about to begin, we're looking forward to it.
Right, our average-new-to-comedy-business Yamazaki-kun?
Yes.
Your hand is kinda wet all over.
Are you really supposed to act that cool?!
Translation, Subtitles, Encoding, Timing etc. etc. by Shion (youtube.com/user/ForegroundNoises)
Cocktail
What the hell...
What is this opening for?
Cocktails
Ass-produced cocktails.
What the--
What happens now?
It flied away!
Why did you do that?
There's nothing in there, Yamazaki-san
That strawberry flied away, you know...
It must have hurt a lot!
There isn't absolutely anything
The one you used wasn't fit to get in between properly, this one will do it better!
Hide it carefully, in the center!
E-excuse me for a moment, please
What now?
Wait a second...
It hurts like hell!
There's nothing again!
Ah!
Eventually he was able to make a cocktail!
He succesfully made a cocktail!
I don't want to...
Ehh? Are you serious?
You're the worst.
Makes me wanna kick you another time
You're really the worst
I can't even make a comment about what I've just done.
Lifting the Hot Pot
Ugh... Yamazaki-san... that's so...
Oh! He's shaking!
He's totally shaking!
HOT!!
What are you exulting for?
Is it over?!
Impressive!
Long Pole Folding
His willpower vanished completely.
Is everything ok?
A long pole?
What the hell is he...?
You call yourself a comedian, right now?
Right now?
Let me try again.
Long Pole Folding - Second Challenge
Impressive.
Oh, shit.
Are you ok?
A comedian, a comedian!
Right now Yamazaki-san is nothing like a comedian!
Are you sure you're ok?
You're right?
What are you doing? It's impossible in this way.
It got inside!
Candle Service
What is he up to?
He's pointing his ass to us with such a resolution!
Why am I doing this?
I have no idea, you're the one who wanted to do it.
That's for the candle service, uh?
Oooh! Amazing!
He's shaking
Please don't move around, Yamazaki-san
Ok! it's lit!
Aww, isn't it lovely?
♪ I'm walking, crossing my arms~♫
HOT!!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Forgive me!
I beg your forgiveness!
So, that's what happened, uh
Fart
What the hell are you laughing for, uh?
Don't laugh!
Fart firefighter - candle challenge
Awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome!
Again?
That's impressive, he is accustomed to this.
He took it out.
Don't cry, don't cry!
Did I made it?
No more of this from now on
I'm begging you
Ok?
Uh-uh.
This looks very gay.
Not sure about this sentence, since I can't hear it very well. I do believe he says ゲイ (gay)
I want to go home and sleep as soon as possible.
Do you want to sleep?
A revel, uh?
Subscribe so you won't miss any new subbed clip!     Follow me on twitter: @PaintThemBlack