Tonight's Gaki is ...
Let's rendezvous without using your smartphones: Special with Takanori Nishikawa and Alice Hirose.
Downtown started at Alta, right?
You're gonna leave me for a younger woman?
We will show you the unreleased parts that we had no choice but to cut due to the air time!
I watch every show they are on, it's like my obligation.
We have a different background than they do.
We have class.
Let's make a meeting of nobility.
We are gentlemen.
But you were just trash-talking me earlier.
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]
This segment is not finished until everyone has met, each going to the place they imagine from the theme presented.
They were joined by guests Takanori Nishikawa and Alice Hirose, making a total of seven people trying to complete the game.
Furthermore, if they encounter Matsumoto Iyo, who is the Joker, with two or more members, they have to disband.
What was the first theme?
They got into a cab and the game started at 12:10.
The closest one from here is Juntendo.
A while ago, when I caught a cold, I used to go to Kosei Chuo in Ebisu.
And it's a hospital that is accustomed to dealing with celebrities.
I think they would come to mind.
I see.
Then I think Sanno Hospital.
They headed in their car to their destination to meet with someone.
I'm sure there are plenty of people out there who think I'm right.
After all, this is a game of majority rule.
So I want to play this with smart people.
They're not, right?
They are less educated.
Isn't that what all five of you are?
Even if they were, I went to Amagasaki Technical High School.
I was in the mechanical department there.
The academic deviation for that is about 32.
What did Houssei, always prone to disease, talk about?
Could you tell me again what illness you have?
Peyronie?
That's terrible.
I'm still...
well...
A man's penis has three prostates, okay?
*At an bar, after Hosei told Matsumoto that he was suffering from the disease, Hosei cried and said something unintelligible: 'I have to cut off my penis. But then I can become a psychic medium.'
That's why my corpus cavernosum is hardening.
This is a rare disease.
One in half a million people get this disease.
How's your jaw these days?
It healed right after we finished recording "Don't Laughing."
- Nothing hurts?
- Yes, it does.
But if I hear there is another "Don't Laughing" recording I will be sick again.
What was Matsumoto talking about when he was heading to Juntendo University Hospital?
The theme is hospital.
I haven't been to hospitals much.
Hamada-san likes hospitals, right?
Yes, he does.
But he often misses work even with a slight fever.
He takes very good care of himself, but he is physically and mentally weak.
That's why he misses work when it's a little hard for him.
I rarely miss work.
I've worked for about 36 years and have hardly missed a day of work.
I've only missed two or three days of work because I was sick.
I've missed work a few times because I was sleepy.
Everyone arrived at their destination.
They called to confirm their locations.
For all intents and purposes, you guys should go to Juntendo Hospital.
Juntendo?
I'm at Tokyo University Hospital.
Where is that?
You guys haven't been watching the news lately?
I'm at Nihon University Hospital.
Nihon University Hospital?
If you're in a place like that, you might see former coach Uchida.
They couldn't meet someone on the theme of hospital.
And what is the second theme?
"Places where people who moved to Tokyo go for the first time."
On this theme, they talked about their memories.
First, Hamada talked about his first time in Tokyo.
- Had you been to Tokyo before you came there on business?
- No.
Wait, I have.
But it was in Kitasenju.
Kitasenju?
A classmate of mine from high school lived there.
I stayed at his house in Kita-Senju with my friend.
And we went to Ginza for lunch.
I wondered what he would treat me to.
He said, "Let's have pizza."
I said to my friend, "What's ‘pizza'?"
"What the hell is ‘pizza'?"
That was the first time I ate pizza.
Tanaka talked about his memories of Shibuya.
When I first came to Tokyo, I had a part-time job in Shibuya.
- What kind of part-time job did you have?
- I was a waiter at a coffee shop.
There were many young female customers there.
However, I had thick arm hair.
A customer complained to me, and I had to work in the kitchen.
"He is gross."
"That waiter is gross."
I thought Tokyo was tough.
Housei, who was heading to Alta, talked about his memories of Waratte-Iitmo.
Have you ever appeared on Waratte-Iitomo?
I never appeared on the show as a regular, but I appeared a few times as a guest.
The first time I appeared in the talk show section with Tamori-san, suddenly an audience asked, "Is it true that this show will end soon? "
- That was during a recording, right?
- Yes, it was a live broadcast.
An audience said in a loud voice, "Is it true that this show will end soon? "
The studio was abuzz.
Then it went to commercial.
I had prepared a lot of topics to talk about.
But the commercial break came soon after.
Tamori-san, the host, said to me, "Your aura must have brought in some strange audience."
He was forced by security to leave during the commercial.
That's terrible.
There was a teddy bear in the seat he was sitting in after the commercial.
That's pretty funny.
That was Tamori-san's ad-lib.
There used to be a live children's show called Romper Room.
One kid yelled, "Penis! Penis! Poop! Poop!"
He was gone after the commercial, and there was a teddy bear in his seat.
That happened a long time ago.
Meanwhile, Hirose was talking about his hobby, comics.
When I first met Matsumoto-san, I told him about comics and he was disgusted.
I see people with different tastes from mine as perverts.
- What do you think of Matsumoto-san's muscle training?
- He is a pervert.
He uploads pictures of his muscles on SNS at the end of the year and at the beginning of the year.
Yes, he uploads them on Twitter.
So, I think he is a pervert.
They chose "Place where people who moved to Tokyo go for the first time" with their own memories.
Hosei arrived at Studio Alta in Shinjuku a little earlier than the others.
My memory of this place is Waratte-Iitomo.
And I used to meet up with girls here.
- Did you used to pick up girls in the past?
- Yeah.
Matsumoto-san would wait in the car and I would talk to the girl I was interested in.
"Hi!"
- Did you tell her that Matsumoto-san was in the car?
- Of course.
"There's Downtown."
"There's Downtown right there."
He was talking about his memories of picking up girls when he was younger, but one question came to mind.
If Alice-chan had come here, would a lot of people have gathered around her?
I wonder.
They don't gather with me at all.
They really don't gather at all.
- I think they're being reserved, don't you?
- Is that so? Don't be shy!
That's insane.
Hosei was surprised that he was so unpopular.
Later, Matsumoto met up with him.
After all, the topic was that.
- Hey, there's no one here.
- Yeah!
- Nobody's gathered around you.
- Oh, is that what you meant?
- No one is making a fuss.
- Yes.
But since you came, people have been gathering.
When I was walking towards here, I thought there would never be any celebrities here.
If there were a celebrities here, there is no way there would be such a vast space.
You can still meet up with a girl here even now.
I said to the staff, "They would leave even if they noticed me or not. Don't you think they're terrible?"
Then he said, "This is how Tokyo is."
"This is how Tokyo is."
People are gathering here.
I was over there thinking, "There will never be any celebrities here."
That's enough!!
How many times are you going to say it?
Let's rendezvous without using your smartphones: Special
Two pairs were formed under the theme of "Place where people who moved to Tokyo go for the first time".
The next theme was university.
Hamada and Hirose talked about Hirose's private life in the car.
- Do you drive a car?
- No, I don't.
I know where I want to go, so I use a cab.
- But aren't you limited to the places you can go?
- Yes, I am.
I don't go out far.
It's too much trouble.
I don't think it's nice of you to say "it's too much trouble" when you're so young.
You should go to more places.
I started cooking because it's too much trouble to go out to eat.
I see.
There is Meiji University right in front of us.
Why are you suggesting this?
You think we're going to Meiji University on this theme?
Oh, sorry, this is rude.
And what were Matsumoto and Hosei talking about?
I never thought about going to university.
Really?
- Why?
- I don't know.
- You had a job lined up when you were in high school, right?
- Yeah.
- Was it a technical high school?
The deviation was 69.
Don't lie.
But the teacher said, "I don't know, but I think that's about right."
"I don't know"?
He's a messed up teacher.
Were you nervous because you thought you might be alone with Nishikawa-kun?
Yes, I had a feeling he might be there when the theme was the hospital.
I was thinking what I would do if I was alone with him.
Why on earth would you think that?
You wouldn't want to be alone with Alice-chan, would you?
But I'm quite a bit older than her, so it's okay.
More than that, I would have a hard time if someone like Shino-san was with me.
- Shino Ikenami?
- She's Nakao-san's wife.
I wouldn't know what to do if I were alone with Shino Ikenami.
That's for sure.
How about Natsumi-san? (Hamada's wife)
If that happens, I have no choice but to change my mind and do my best.
I have to consider that it will be aired.
I only think about how to make it interesting as show.
What was Nishikawa talking about at the time?
I think we should do this in a foreign country or in a rural area, although those two would definitely not like it.
Those two would dislike working with an overnight stay.
It's like doing Strange Town with everyone separated.
I would like to do Strange Town, too.
Oh, let's do it together.
Do you watch a lot of this show?
I watch most of their shows because you never know what those two will ask me at any given moment.
- All the stations?
- Yes.
It's like my duty.
I feel as much as Inomoto does.
- Do you consider yourself as their junior?
- Yes, I feel the same way as Inomoto.
When I talk to them, I don't say, "Oh, really?" I want to say, " Yeah, of course I know that."
They will be annoyed if they have to explain.
They could meet 6 people on this theme at the Tokyo University except for Endo.
It's the only place to be!
Then all that's left is Endo!
But!
Is this for real?
Sorry, I'm late!
Sorry I'm late.
Here comes the joker, Iyo Matsumoto.
The six of them must split up.
They are back to square one.
Hey, I told you guys first!!
I have an appointment at 3:00 PM.
Don't make appointment!
- But I told you guys that.
- What appointment?
Let's rendezvous without using your smartphones: Special
Starting from zero.
The fourth theme was department stores.
Come to think of it,
it's pretty hard to make a situation where all seven of us are together and only Iyo-chan is in a different place.
So sorry for being in a hurry, but let's make Endo the joker.
Then everything will be solved.
- If that's the case, we're finished with that earlier.
- That's right.
So, let's re-record the opening and make Endo the joker.
Then it's over.
The rest is up to the editors.
Matsumoto, Hosei, and Tanaka went to Mitsukoshi in Nihonbashi, while Hamada and Hirose went to Isetan in Shinjuku.
Matsumoto was the first to arrive at Mitsukoshi.
This is the only place to go.
Anyone who doesn't come here is a fool.
Anyone who doesn't come here is over.
- Hi!
- Oh, hi!
- Good luck!
- Thank you.
I'm doing my best, but...
But...
I didn't recognize you at all!
- It's the only place!
- Yes, it's the only place I can think of!
Speaking of department stores, this is the place to be.
- Because this is the first department store in Japan.
- Yes, from a historical point of view, it's also here.
This is the place to be!
We have a different background from them.
And we have class.
As you can imagine, I don't expect everyone to gather here.
But we can share with each other the nobility of our fellowship that has come here.
That's great.
Let's make a meeting of nobility.
We are gentlemen.
But you were just trash-talking me earlier.
The three of them met up in Nihonbashi, the city for adults.
Matsumoto was pleased.
I hope this part will be aired.
Something is being communicated from us to the viewers.
I still think we are neat.
They couldn't stop praising themselves.
We are not dirty.
We are virtuous as human beings.
It doesn't matter if we are educated or rich.
That is not what we are about, we have something special.
- Nobility.
- Class.
I also consider the balance of the show.
I feel like a producer, and I think we need the Nihonbashi as one of the spots to shoot.
"You want a scene like this, don't you?"
"Hey director, you want this, right?"
- Viewers will want to see many different places. It's a kindness from you to the viewers.
- Yes, it's kindness and grace.
So our body odor doesn't stink.
We don't smell at all.
Their body odor just smells bad no matter what.
How did Alice Hirose, who chose Isetan in Shinjuku at that time?
She got to meet Hamada again.
You can see the result on the theme of department stores.
Endo did not meet anyone because things did not go well.
Let's rendezvous without using your smartphones: Special
The fifth theme was a golf practice range.
Hamada, who loves golf, went to Jingu Gaien with Hirose.
I don't play golf, so I am not familiar with it. Are there any golf ranges other than Jingu and Kasai?
There is Himonya in Meguro, too.
But Jingu Gaien is the most famous.
Yes. This theme is an opportunity.
That's right.
Endo knows all the places I just mentioned.
So it's up to him to choose where he wants to go.
And it's up to Nishikawa.
We have to meet Endo-san soon.
Yes.
This is weird, right?
We haven't seen him for a long time.
He's been recording alone all day.
Meanwhile, what were Matsumoto, Hosei, and Tanaka talking about?
Alice-chan would love to be alone with me.
But that's impossible.
That wish will not come true.
Hamada is always in her way.
This is a natural order of the world that has existed since ancient times.
Is that so?
Of course.
There will always be someone who gets in the way of that.
That's what a love story is.
Indeed.
Can you turn up the air conditioning a bit?
Talking about Hamada made me feel physically hot.
Alice-chan is probably disgusted with Hamada.
She'll be sitting in the middle.
He's probably getting too close to her
Hamada will be thinking about touching her whenever he gets a chance.
He is called the last sexual harasser in show business.
it's said that if he dies, sexual harassment will disappear from the show business.
At that time, at the Jingu Golf Range...
It's Matsumoto, Yama-chan and Tanaka!
All seven successfully met up with each other.
Where is Iyo Matsumoto, the joker, headed?
Where is Iyo-chan now?
I'm at Himonya Swing.
She is in Himonya!!
All seven of us are at Jingu Golf Range!
I met Sanma-san by chance.
Oh, you met Sanma-san?
Huh?
- You met him at Himonya?
- Apparently, Sanma-san also goes there.
Why do you look so disappointed!?
No, no, no.
If all of us had gone to Himonya, it would have been great.
Don't say that!
[Subbed byRAIDEN1017]