Team Gaki Presents - A TG Mini
Typesetters
Sacro
Rich
Translator
Mickstar
Shoji-sensei can't come back for a little while so
we're going to use an English teaching video now
Okay, I'm sticking it on now
Lets Read In English
Marco Polo
Marco Polo - Lets Read In English
English instructor
Jimmy Onishi
Give me a break...
This is just...
There's no way it can be 'es'
I was in serious trouble here...
This is just...
This is where it begins...
This is going to be tough
Marco Polo - Lets Read In English
I mean, it's totally wrong
How did he get 'lotion'?
How can he get lotion from that?!
I can't do this anymore
You did so well here
Marco Polo - Lets Read In English
He's so persistent
There's no way it's Victor
Absolutely no chance
He said "Victor"...
He's something else...
He said "Ven..."
He said '"Ven"
And then ended with "Victor"
Lets Count In English
1 to 100
Enough man...
This was so tough...
1 to 100 - Lets Count In English
No way in hell...
This is not on at all! He's wrong!
It's impossible to not laugh here
I'm in trouble
1 to 100 - Lets Count In English
How long is this going to carry on for!?
Matsumoto, you can't do that.
This is not on man
I can't take this anymore
How long is this going to carry on for?
I can't do it anymore
1 to 100 - Lets Count In English
This is not on, right?
No way
We're not in the wrong for laughing here
Ow man, I can't do this
At least it's finished
It's done, finally, we got to a hundred.
No more, please, no more.
Yeah, seriously
Surely, that's it
We got it, it's fine
No seriously man, shit!
Lets Say In English
Days Of The Week
It was so long!
No, please, seriously, no!
Days of the Week in English
I'll start with the ones I know
This is not on!
What is he on about?
Please go easy on me!
I can't do this anymore.
I can't do this anymore, sensei.
Days of the Week in English
He should say which day he's going to say
I was done here
Endo!
I was just completely done
Come on, Endo!
I'm sorry!
There's no point unless he says it in order...
He's changing the order...
That hurts
Days of the Week in English
What's the last one?
Tuesday...
Tuesday?
Tuesday is...
I've never been taught it
You've got to be kidding me
"I've never been taught it"?!
This was seriously