At a certain hot spring, there is an inn where liars gather
I kinda forgot about this, it's been a while
Yes true
When was the last time?
1 year? 1 year
Oh it's been a year? Hmm I don't really remember much...except Yamasaki really sucked
That's as much as I remember
Time to explain the rules for Liar's Inn
They pick a card with small, medium or massive written on it along with someone's name. That person nominates someone else to tell a lie
Whoever is nominated must maintain the lie until it's time to stop
I think it would be better to have an audience for this
Yeah for sure, it would be better if there was an audience
Well the staff here aren't that bad
You guys are depressing!
So god damn heavy hearted
They're depressing, and they're old men, they way they think
They think like old men!
They can't keep up
Yeah for real
Ah so Endo
Endo nominates someone to tell a massive lie
Endo picks a massive lie
But a massive lie right away...
A massive lie is hard to do...
This is something that really surprised me when I heard it
I was eating dinner with some people,
And someone said something that made me go "Did that really happen?!" Matsumoto-san
Did a meteorite really fall on your family's house?
It was a pretty long time ago though
A while ago? When
I think it's been 7 years
7 years?
There were a ton of them!
Oh, it wasn't just one?
One of them fell right on my mom
Wait if it hit your mom...
On my mom, here, it smacked her like BAAAM
But that would kill you...
Here?
We were all watching Kōhaku on TV
My mom- Was it this side or this side? I can't remember for sure,
It hit like BAAAM
And she went like OWWW
Surely Ow isn't enough
It was amazing actually
Were you there?
We were playing Domino (Shichi Narabe)
7 years ago...
And my mom's hand stopped right at the 6
And we were talking about whether that was a foul or not
My mom refused to play the 6
I really remember that moment
I said "Who did this?!" and then it hit her like BAAAM
And then when her cards fell I saw it was my mom's fault
Ah she was holding it back after all
Yeah it was all mom's fault
Basically everyone was really pissed off about the game,
So like we had a talk like "It's bad to ruin the fun like that" ... and it's become a great story in our household
Mmm.  Mmm.
I understand. I see, I see.
Sorry Matsumoto-san, your sweating is just...
Sorry, umm, uhh
Even though you gave me a massive lie...I'm sorry I turned it into something so small
Timed & Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
Fully Improvised Liar's Inn
They must maintain the lie no matter what!
Fully Improvised! Liar's Inn
They pick a card with small, medium or massive written on it along with someone's name. That person nominates someone else to tell a lie
Whoever is nominated must maintain the lie until it's time to stop
Alright here I go
Endo nominates someone to tell a small lie
Wow!
It's you again
Tanaka, are you alright? Your rib is broken right now right?
Are you good?
Ah, now that you mention it, it makes it hard to continue
Is it a crack, or is it broken?
It's broken
It's totally broken? I don't think I could hold the pain back for that...
Oh? He's not really speaking that loudly either
He was speaking pretty loudly just earlier though
Could you try making a loud noise?
Wow that hurts...
It resonates?
If I'm not lying
"If I'm not lying"?
You're enduring it you mean?
What did you do that made this happen?
I kinda started doing Martial Arts recently
That sounds like a true story
I didn't know about that
I was in a state of no exercise
"A state of no exercise"?
I don't really do any exercise, which I thought isn't good. So I started doing Martial Arts.
What kind?
Mixed Martial Arts
Like what kind of stuff?
That's amazing!
Yeah, Mixed Martial Arts
I do know some stuff about this,
Oh yes Matsumoto-san you do martial arts right?
Where?
In Ebisu (District of Tokyo)
Ebisu already?
Ebisu
You don't mean the location, but the Organization right?
Organization? Oh they said they're not associated with any organization
Well forget about the organization, what's the place called?
It says "Ebisu Mixed Gym" on the sign
Ebisu Mixed Gym, that's where I go
Who are you getting to teach you?
I, uh, my Missus
Missus? Your wife?
Yes
What do you mean?
Then just do it at home. You don't need to go to Ebisu.
You don't need to go to Ebisu
Does she have any qualifications? Your wi-Missus
Wi-Missus?
Yes she does, she got her qualifications a while ago
Your wife has a trainer's license?
Yes yes yes she has a trainer's license
Doesn't it hurt to do that?
It's fine it's fine
Oh, so it's fine?
It's fine, this is my job after all
Yeah
I can't really go "Ow Ow" here
Yeah of course
So I'm forcing myself, for lack of a better word
Your wife does it too then?
Yes, she does it too
It must be awful to get into quarrels with her
Oh no no yes, just one hit is all it takes
Oh she hits you? Yeah that makes sense
She just high kicks me
That's scary
Why did she high kick you?
... Well to sum it up, I had an affair
You cheated on her...
Well, in some sense, a high kick to get it over with is good
Yes, yes exactly, after the kick she forgave me
Here I go
Matsumoto-san nominates someone to tell a medium lie
Matsumoto-san's medium
I heard this, Yamasaki,
Apparently, Yamasaki found some STAP cells
STAP was a proposed method of generating stem cells discovered in Japan that was later found to use falsified data in its report
What?
There's no way that's true... Not after everything we know
Even though they said they don't exist
But apparently it's true!
My wife found out after Yamasaki's wife sent her a text
She sent like "My husband found some STAP cells!"
With a laughing emoji
The sweating laughing emoji
Man I told her not to tell anyone!
It's a lie right?
This is, this is the truth
But I kept it secret, and it became a big thing, like the Japanese scientists and stuff
There are scientists outside of Japan!!
This is a major global discovery
I told her, you know, this will become a big deal scientifically.
I did tell her...
What the hell are you saying?
But isn't it a good thing?
Yeah if it's true
When Obok*ta-san announced that they exist,
If she's saying STAP cells really exist, then let's go out and try to find some
You went on a journey to find STAP cells?
Yes
But that was disproven right?
Like I said, I found some
How did you find them?
Uh, you know, I was shocked myself
I was so shocked ... I just kept walking
Ok...
You were walking?
To where?
I uh, I made it all the way to Kyoto
Why'd you go to Kyoto?
Well cause, it's an ancient city, and they have lots of temples
By yourself?
By myself, of course
To find a new discovery, he goes to an ancient city instead
Yeah instead
I really wanted to show that STAP cells are nothing new,
But they are a new thing...
What did you do?
So I was just walking through Kyoto, and I went to a temple first and asked them,
"Excuse me, have you ever heard anything about STAP cells?"
You asked like you were looking for a missing person?
Missing person...
This is so messed up
Well, in the end-
You might as well ask?
I might as well ask. I really had nothing to lose.
"Excuse me, have you heard anything about STAP cells? In this area"
"Is there nothing about that from the past?"
"No"
I said "Oh is that so"
At around the 8th temple I went to though,
They said "Why are you searching for STAP cells?"
They knew about it this time?
"Well actually, I really like STAP cells..."
You like STAP cells?
"So I'm looking for them"
It's like he's talking about japanese sweets
No no, really
Where did you find them then?
Can I be honest?
Be honest
Please
It was ... behind the Jizo statue
The STAP cells?!
Enough already
You found STAP cells behind the Jizo statue?
So annoying
Wow, in such a place
This one
Matsumoto nominates someone to tell a massive lie
Hamada?
I heard Hamada is genuinely the Kamen Rider
TN: Kamen Rider is a superhero
I thought he was supposed to be a cyborg
But this is for real
Your wife said it on a TV show in Osaka
Yomiuri I think it was
Really? Well she did reveal it in Kansai
Why did she say that...
Which means...
Please tell us!
So it's real then? What I don't understand is why you became a Cyborg
Well it's the same reason as Hongo Takeshi (Kamen Rider's protaganist)
Hongo Takeshi had a motorcycle accident or something-
No, he was kidnapped by Shocker (evil organisation)
He was kidnapped by Shocker
Woke up strapped down like this
Oh yeah. Eh? You were kidnapped by Shocker?
What else would it have been!
When?
"When"? ... I've kept it secret for so long I think I've forgotten
Maybe grade 8?
So young!
You got caught in grade 8?
Before the middle school trip
Wow they caught you back then
But you came on that trip right?
I did, I managed to convince them to let me, somehow
Oh you asked them?
But they told me they just finished so "Don't transform at all"
They said there's still some parts they didn't attach yet
Didn't attach?
What wasn't attached?
Like properly you know
Oh not properly?
They didn't attach the cyborg parts properly, so if I transform now they'll come off
So on that trip, well you were there, we went to different places, and sang and danced like this,
I couldn't move like that, they told me side to side movements like that
You couldn't even move side to side?
Cause it's like, my hip would slip and return, slip and return
That's terrifying!
So I didn't even like doing this
Maybe I wasn't developed enough in middle school
Have you transformed a bunch of times before?
Well one time I did think "I should be fine" and did try to transform
You tried? How do you transform?
Well they didn't tell me anything, so of course I just tried saying "Transform!"
But it barely did anything. My upper body was the same, but my lower body went like *cyborg noises*
Eh your lower body? What happened to it?
It looked sort of like compression pants
That's not very cool...
You don't know what it was though right? It looked like Egashira?
I didn't really know
Yeah yeah, I thought something would happen to my upper body. But it was lame, it was just compression pants.
Oh you were just normal from the top
I just thought "this sucks, I don't want to be seen like this"
It's just embarrassing
It's just embarassing
"Enough" I said "Nope!" and *cyborg noises*
You said "Nope" and it went back?
So you didn't fight any monsters?
I did fight them
But I do remember them saying it depends from person to person
Person to person?
If you train well then you can get good in about a month
But my physique wasn't good. And I had side effects.
There are side effects?
You had side effects? What kind of side effects?
What do you mean side effects?
What kind?
Like, it makes you fat
Seriously?
That's a relief. That's a relief really.
I guess we wouldn't know the side effects of being a cyborg
Ah, Yama-chan's medium
Hosei nominates someone to tell a medium lie
Endo, your beauty parlour,
You go to the same beauty parlour as Maeda Bibari-san?
Maeda Bibari
Yes, the same as Bibari-san
Did you pick that one on purpose?
On purpose? Well Bibari-san was already-
There's nothing wrong with that
It could be a true story
Yeah that's true
It's not a big deal
It's not really unbelievable
It is totally possible isn't it
It's not really a medium lie, it could be true
Yeah, it's not a big deal
It's totally possible
Yama-chan's massive!
Hosei nominates someone to tell a massive lie
Tanaka, I've heard you've got a perfect memory of your past life
It's not something I've ever told anyone, but yes yes, it's true
Yama-chan's massive!
Hosei nominates someone to tell a massive lie
What does a massive lie really mean?
Tanaka, I've heard you've got a perfect memory of your past life
If I ever talk about this, people go "Are you serious?" or "That's so weird!", so I've never talked about it before but,
But, yes, if I had to say so, it is true
What happened?
In my past life?
I was, well my appearance was mostly the same, I was still tall
But yeah I was a woman that had this same sort of look
Pretty tall
Huge!
A 181cm tall woman
What nationality?
An Argentinian girl
Do you remember the name?
I think it was Argentina if I'm right
Ar- Argentina
Her name?
Tanaka Naoki used to be Argentina?
An Argentinian named Argentina?
Isn't that strange? Argentinian Argentina, that's like being named Nippon Tarou
Yes, my name was Argentina
What kind of job did you do?
Umm
Well basically, I was a daughter, I didn't do any work
What do you mean?
Well that's possible for a girl right? Not working part time or a job or anything
But you did work a little?
I didn't, I wasn't suited for that
I was free, I really did nothing, I lived a life of no worries
You were a noblewoman?
I was a noblewoman
So your parents were...
Yes, my parents were-
Eh? What did your parents do?
My parents, were on the street corner doing real estate
Why mention the street corner
The street corner?
Forget about the street corner
They did real estate, they didn't own that much land, but they did have some
Real estate huh?
You didn't have any siblings?
I did I did
Oh you did?
Us 3 sisters were pretty close
Oh really?
Please tell us their names
Their names, I think, Bibi? Yeah Bibi Argentina
Argentina is the last name?
Bibi Argentina?
Argentina isn't the first name, it's the surname?
Bibi Argentina, and ... Lopes Argentina
That's a boy!
That's boys name isn't it, Lopes?
And Tanaka what name did you have?
I (boku) - I (watashi) was named Argentina
Does that make sense?
I didn't have a last name, I was just Argentina
You didn't have one? Wow
You were married right?
I was married
What kind of man were you married to?
He really was like Argentina-Man like right out of a picture
Argentina-Man?
What was he like?
Sounds like a monster's name
Well, that's, well how do I say,
What was his name?
Hmm...I think was Lopes Argentina
You mentioned him before! You just mentioned him!
Wasn't that your older sister?
Sorry, it was Gomez Argentina
Gomez Argentina?
Gomez Argentina
Kids?
I had them
A daughter?
What was her name?
Mummy Argentina
That's the mom!
Mummy Argentina?
Mummy means mom
Mummy Argentina...
Here I go
Tanaka nominates someone to tell a medium lie
Tanaka
Tanaka Medium
Matsumoto-san
Yes
Is is true that you've recently started drinking with Tagawa Yosuke-san?
(Actor and former idol)
Ah, yeah
That's unexpected
That legendary Onii Tag is finally coming to Nintendo 3DS!
"Don't get caught" Gasuu Kurobikari Rando
Coming out 12/17
Here I go
Tanaka nominates someone to tell a medium lie
Tanaka
Tanaka Medium
Damn, I wonder if this is true
But I guess I'll ask
Matsumoto-san
Yes
Is is true that you've recently started drinking with Tagawa Yosuke-san?
Tagawa Yosuke
Ah, yeah
That's unexpected
How did you meet?
He came to me for advice,
He was asking me "what is Yoshimoto Creative Agency like?"
Coincidentally, at the hospital
Hospital?
While I was waiting for my medicine at the hospital,
Ohh you were at the same hospital?
Same hospital. And he went like "Hey Macchan"
And Tagawa-san said his dick hurt or something
There's no need to mention that
So he was waiting with for antibiotics, he told me "You should be careful too Macchan"
No, why were you-
"It stings you know" he said
Basically he kept saying his dick hurt
And that's when you made plans to get drinks?
Ah that's when you planned?
Yeah, like "Let's get drinks"
"Once I'm off the antibitotics I can drink alcohol"
"I gotta take antibiotics for about 2 weeks"
"Basically it hurts"
And the whole time he was talking he was, touching his dick
"Are you alright?" I asked
"I'm fine I'm fine!"
Wow!
"I'm fine! DAHAHAHA"
And I said "You're being kind of loud"
He is that kind of person
Yes, he is
He said something like "It's the 7th time this year"
That's awful, why does it happen so often
"But forget that, how is that Creative Agency, huh?" and kept hitting me like this
He's acting like a drag queen
They called for him "Tagawa-san!", and he came back with a ton of antibiotics
It was sticking out of the bag even
Seriously? That really is a lot
Yeah, there must be a variety of them
Tagawa-san was explaining it to them
"You've messed this up"
What do you mean?
There's probably bunch of different ones, he probably couldn't cure it so he got a lot
Like "You forgot about this one!"
"What is it Macchan, for real huh?"
He's not how I imagined at all
He was going like this
No way, he put you in a headlock?
Not how I imagined him at all
"How do you like it~"
That's all he says huh?
Not at all how I imagined...It's amazing you went out for drinks after that
That's ALL he says
I think after that we started
It's just you two when you go?
Yeah just us 2
You don't invite others?
"If we invite others, it's soo, you know, soo annoying right?" he said
What is annoying?
"So much stuff, it's so not it you know"
"Let's go~ Let's goooo~"
But if it's the 7th time that's happened to him, he must like it right?
Ohh, I didn't ask anything about that
Don't know the cause after all
When I asked why it happened he said "SHUT UP YOU!"
"WHO THE HELL ARE YOU ASKING?"
But, that's a natural question
"Are you an idiot?!"
So that's just off limits
It's not like it's always for that reason, sometimes he gets fractures
He gets fractures?
It's not always his dick then?
Of course, that's something I'll say for his sake, it's not always about his dick
Sometimes he just needs a compress
A compress?
One time he got a fracture too
You can just buy a compress
Did he get antibiotics
He did get antibiotics just in case
He's just always got them
"I wanna get some~ What do you think about that?"
I'm gonna get scolded aren't I?
Timed & Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband