I used to eat sweets last time
It was pretty harsh.
This time it's starting with aro and let's eat it as a side dish
Matsumoto, look at the end
Yes, the image of this project is an image of children playing
Only he is pushing his character
There is no good day like this
Fujiwara, the gluttonous comedian
Endo is 8kg under the stress of divorce.
This time, the subtitles like beggars start :)
Gogo!
Rule- 7 people eat a single meal with a side dish that starts with a child picked from the drawing
7 men's fight against Han-Bob begins
First, what side dish will start with Tanaka A?
Didn't you eat lunch today?
-Didn't you even get the Matsumoto Prize? -I only have a side dish
What is the first one?
Tempura crumbs
It's nice to fry
It's fried!
By the way, you can add tea.
Rule- How to eat is free even if you eat it with Ochazuke.
Oh really?
-Eat as it is.-Yes, if you eat it with Ochazuke...
Eat fast
It's quite long when Tanaka does it
Supplementary Rules-No side dishes left
It has no taste
I can eat one bowl
Just eat
Eat it fast
Ochazukero to eat some tempura fritters without taste
It's easy to eat
You eat pretty lightly
But I put it in a normal way
1 bowl
What is the side dish that starts with Hamada?
what?
Too much
Andean melon! (One of the house-grown melons developed in Japan)
What should I do
in a bad mood!
It might be like cucumber
Bad mood
The third is what is the license Inomoto side dish
Now, what
what is this
Anchovy (Anchovy fish on the coast of Europe)
This is a perfect match
I can eat this
You shouldn't eat 3 or 4
We're 36 now
It's Hamada 51.
Taking advantage of youthfulness, Inomoto aims to complete the rice
Isn't it possible to continue eating 1 bowl?
Can't you just go ahead and eat 1 bowl?
I'm still a burden today
Endo continues to lose weight due to the stress of divorce.
Whoa this
Almonds
-How many did you hear? -Five overviews
All right!
Wow, this is another stress
-Is it different from divorce? -It's different.
I can't see each other
Is not it? Not as hard as everyone thinks
Did you eat with yesterday?
Indeed
What are you talking about?
You don't have to say
It's not as hard as Sagan thinks.
You don't have to say that! Hama-chan!
The appetite has started to rise right now.
What about the Yamazaki side dish?
reel!
-clam! -It's pants.
Is there something like this because it's a clam?
After all it's a burden
Let's leave
delicious
I can eat this
How many bowls did you eat with this?
Are you saying this (shell) 1 bowl?
Eat more
I've seen this
1 bowl
Will there continue to be delicious side dishes starting with Matsumoto A?
what is this
Later, Matsumoto's surprise side dish appeared!!
what is this?
It's red miso! (Made with barley yeast)
It suits you
This guy is real
I'm only focusing on bullying.
That's why everyone gathered.
Still, this one goes well
Isn't it nice to mix all this?
Wow this is hell with this
You must not eat too much
Matsumoto doesn't end with a bowl of miso
The second is rice with capsules and miso chazuke
I tried hard because I didn't want to use this cap
And Fujiwara with the expected glutton
What's the side dish
Oh what is this meat
-fat? -Bad mood
This is a winner
It smells really good
Ah, I can eat it with the smell first
Today's Versus Awards is something different.
indeed!
Whoa-chan is really?
Surely Fujiwara 4 bowls
He showed that the top of the bowl was different with 4 bowls.
I'm coming in
Second, Tanaka picked the thick salt
This is the same as miso
I'm not putting it at all
It's the same as Yamachan
The next side dish of the second Hamada?
It's the worst!
Since then, Hamada has a face change!!
Almond caramel
It's hard even with 3 caramels
what is this
-Meron and caramel. -Andes Melon!
I feel bad just by putting it in here
It's only sweet
right
-It's just that. Melon and caramel.-Andes melon!
come
It's dangerous to enter this mode
This will be hard
Where are you looking?
The red bean bread that seems to go wrong with rice
Because the red beans are juicy
No bread
Rendezvous Rendezvous
What is the side dish that begins with the endo pick?
Grandma came out five times.
Came out!
Wait a minute!
Number 5 is Gamju!
You can eat this in the sense of Ochazuke
Crisp
I'll do it
Whoa
This will be hard
Think different
What do you think
I think it's honeymoon.
When you think about the honeymoon... but the results are bad.
1 bowl
What is Yamazaki's side dish? Yamazaki, work hard.
I'm working hard
You don't work hard at all
How did it go?
Listen to this for a second
what is this!
-Wait a minute! -It's very heavy
In the shell
Are you eating this?
what is this
Plus tight
What's in the spark
What meeting did you have
Wow
Are you into a sweets right now?
Really
I have a lot of sins...
What did you say
Who made this?
Fall into hell
If you do something like this
Feverish
Hell
10 minutes later
Eat fast
Please forgive
Dad and Mom forgave!
Oh I ate it
Yama-chan, eat all the stuff on the rice
What side dish did you choose next?
Sorry please look at this
-what? -Evil this
This is completely oil
Wow this
This is no good!
Are you stupid!
Do you eat with these things!!
TV humans have their heads turned!
Woo Wak has become quite small
There is a problem there too
Because this is not direct
Ugh this is hard
How about scaffolding
Does it have a taste?
Does the taste change?
The taste of oil
Tasteless and odorless
Here is also a sin
This is malicious
Do you mean this? I put it in here and covered it with something
I can't even think about this
What education did you have
Pour the tea to make the oil a little smaller
It doesn't melt at all
Can I eat oil?
-Sure-Really?
Oh! I ate it!
okay! Awesome
Apple Pie is the second thing Fujian Fujiwara picked
indeed
The movement of the chopsticks is slower than the first one that finished 4 bowls of rice as a side dish.
Belly full
-Eh? -said
You're angry
In the third, Tanaka finished a bowl of rice with dried squid anyway.
What's the next side dish of Hamada who continued to eat only sweet food?
what is this
Acerola
Really, pretty
I wish you
No matter what you eat
Whatever
What is this without being sweet
No acidity?
But it will never be bad for you.
Yes
I ate something bad for my body
No
It's a scream I've never heard of
Never before
It's a southern bird.
Idiot
1 bowl
Inomoto completes one bowl with anzubo (apricot)
Endo's side dish: Annin Tofu
While watching TV on the top in a formal house
Indeed, I want to do that too
Wow looks delicious
Should I buy Annin Tofu and go home?
lie
1 bowl
Yamazaki, who is addicted to Japanese sweets these days, is made of anamato (sweets boiled with soybeans, soaked in sugar)
Oh it's so good
really
This has no comment
Afterwards, can I have one meal of rice?!
What Matsumoto chose was an ankake that goes with rice
(It looks good) But this guy was using Ochazuke
Should I eat this Ochazuke again?
Look, the upper part of the Ochazuke.
It's like the last bath in a large family.
About the fifth
Former Ochazuke judges it to be unreasonable and pours water
This is delicious
It looks delicious
There is some oil in the ankake
You have to drink 4 of these
Do it in an endo way
Don't let chopsticks go
I'm going to eat some
Exciting rice 1 eating plan
The last Fujiwara that will shine the last
Which side dish starts with ah?
No. 22 is green juice.
If this is unsuccessful, it's a penalty with Matsumoto.
We ate
If you don't do it quickly, the mission will fail.
Really hard everyone
Matsumoto complete
Isn't it the same if I eat green juice?
No, this is the end
Why? It says 4.5.6 (th).
No, no, you're alone.
There is no side dish
Then I can tell you.
KY (You can't understand the atmosphere)
Roger Fujiwara
Another side dish
First of all
What are you doing
number 3
Grandmother~3
It's Akama Mushi.
It's impossible
Why?
My stomach is full
Penalty decision!!
What are you going to eat?
Came out for a long time
Even if you are an adult,