2nd Gaki- no-tsukai-ya -arahende!!
Duo Competition! Comedian Quiz Grand Prix!
The comedians who will be participating are here!
- Let's do this!
- I won't lose!
Now, let's welcome today's special guest!
Downtown!
Hi.
How are you feeling today?
- I just talked with Hamada for about 4 hours in the dressing room.
- 4 hours!?
We just want to enjoy this.
And not just aiming to win, but hoping that the duos can have fun, be close, and stay healthy.
Stay healthy?
Yes, that's important.
Today, you will compete in a quiz using this panel.
Each duo will take turns choosing a panel and answering a quiz.
For example, if Cocorico chooses "Riddle's 10," only Cocorico will have the right to answer the question.
- Do we have to stay quiet?
- Yes!
The duo with the most points will win a trip to Hawaii!
Hell yeah!!
Enjoy this trip for five days and three nights!
Let's get started!
[subbed by RAIDEN1017]
First, Downtown, please choose a question!
Yoshimoto's 30!
Okay, Yoshimoto's 30!
Q. What did Kanpei Hazama achieve over the course of about two years?
- They get 30 points for such an easy question?
- Is this a question for just us?
Only Downtown has the right to answer this.
Earth Marathon.
Yeah!!
We could end it now.
Next, Cocorico!
We could end it now, time-wise.
It's just getting started.
- They've already got enough usable footage, right?
- No.
There was just one question, and you answered "Earth Marathon."
Really?
Let's go, Cocorico.
Yoshimoto's 20!
[Buzzer Quiz]
This question is open to all teams.
I see, buzzer quiz.
We have a chance to do the same.
Why wasn't that a buzzer quiz earlier?
This is strange. Why is 20 a buzzer quiz and not 30?
Now, I'll give you a question!
Q. Who is the rakugo performer famous for saying "Welcooome" ?
Can I answer that?
Master Katsura Sanshi!
Correct!
Isn't that strange?
We all knew the answer already.
- You all knew the answer to this, right?
- Yes.
Is this just a quiz to see how fast we can answer the questions?
That's what a buzzer quiz is.
Also, I don't think it's good to add "Master"  to the answer.
It doesn't matter, though.
I think for an answer, you should say "Katsura Sanshi" without adding "master" or "san".
I was thinking about how Master would feel when he saw this.
Huh? What do you mean?
When master watched this broadcast, I think he wouldn't have wanted to be referred to as "master" in the answer.
That's just how he is.
So, considering Master's feelings, I don't think it's good.
But it's okay to give them points, right?
Hmmm, we need to discuss it.
No, they will get points.
You guys get the points.
Don't worry.
Let's move on to the next , Jicho-Kacho.
Riddle's 10.
Q. The top is a flood, the bottom is a fire. What is it?
Excuse me.
This is a question for Jicho-Kacho.
This is a question that only Jicho-Kacho can answer.
You should have said that from the beginning.
I thought we were starting a buzzer quiz from the previous question.
That's not the case. It only becomes a buzzer quiz when "buzzer quiz" is written on the back of the panel.
It's confusing.
I explained it earlier.
- You're a bad host.
- Yeah, it's confusing.
I explained it earlier. Please answer the question.
Bathtub!
I don't understand the meaning.
What does this mean?
That's exactly what it means. The answer is a bathtub, which is heated by burning fire underneath it while filled with a large amount of water.
I think there are other things like that.  There are other things where the top is on fire and the bottom is flooded.
It's the opposite if the top is a fire...
We can't move forward like this. Let's focus and do it properly.
- Okay, let's move on!
- This guy is a really bad host.
Football Hour got animal's 10 right without difficulty.
You guys get 10 points!
Now it's Downtown's turn!
It says "game", but what kind of game is it specifically?
I wonder what is written on the backakulalu....
Cocktail...
Yeah, I wonder what is written on the back of the panel.
Is that a bar drink?
No, it's not a cocktail.
-  Then, Game's 10.
- Okay, let's do Game's 10!
"What's in the Box?"
Wow, they have this kind of game too.
Now I will remove this board.
So...
- I'll do this.
- Then I'm here watching.
Matsumoto-san should not look what is in this.
Really?
Can't I just watch it here?
Hamada-san will do this?
Yeah, but....
Don't look inside.
But...
So?
Which of you two would do this?
Hamada can't look inside?
Of course.
Then I won't do it.
- Hamada is not good at this kind of game.
- I can't do this.
"He is not good at this"?
Hamada can't guess something by touching it without knowing what's inside.
- But that's what a game is.
- If I can look what's inside, I'll do it.
Don't look inside.
Please, let him look inside.
I can't let Hamada do that.
This is a game where you touch and guess something you don't know what it is.
But Hamada is not good at that!
I can't do that.
If I could look inside, I would do that.
Please don't look inside.
He didn't look inside.
So, are you forfeiting this and not getting any points?
Then, I'll do it
He will do it for me.
So Matsumoto-san will do this instead of Hamada-san?
This is what's inside!
[A. Germman]
(This is a character from an animated cartoon for young children.)
This is insane.
...Germman.
- This can't be a joke!
- This is so scary!
I don't know what it is...
But isn't it a germ one?
"A germ one"?
I have a feeling that it's something like that.
It's eerie that I know it without touching it, right?
But I know what it is.
I guess "germ one" is a little confusing, so maybe Germman?
Booyah!
You're amazing!
You may think it's eerie, but somehow I figured out what was in it.
Man, you're amazing!
Hamada-san told Matsumoto-san the answer from behind.
No, no, no...
Hamada-san was looking at the inside from behind Yamasaki-san.
Did he really do that?
Is that true?
He would never do such a thing.
I didn't see that.
Hamada definitely didn't do that!!
He definitely did that.
Hamada definitely did not look at it!!
Did he look at it?
He looked at it.
If Hamada looked at it and taught it to me, it's only natural that I could answer it.
Then why am I so happy?
I'm really happy because I got the answer right!
Hamada would never say that!
And he has grown up so healthy and strong.
He's working so hard!
Don't say like that!
We can't do anything if you say that!
That makes us sound like we're just a bunch of cheaters!
When I looked at this box, I could see the germ inside.
Can you still see it now?
Can you tell the color of it?
Oh, I can't see it anymore now.
You could see it earlier, right?
Oh, that's all right.
Then I'll give them the points.
Thank you.
Now please return to your seats.
Next, Football Hour!
Okay, let's try a high point question.
Want to try?
- Can we try the higher scoring questions?
- Sure!
Then...
-Game's 40!
- Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
Wait a moment.
What's wrong?
Hamada-san stepped on my foot.
- Really?
- It's okay. Sorry for stopping this.
Are you okay?
He's saying he got stepped on.
Hamada would never do such a thing.
I think so too. But...
I think Tanaka did it.
I would never do such a thing.
If that's the case, then Hamada would be even less likely to do something like that.
I didn't do that.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, I stopped the proceedings.
The next game is concentration.
Players take turns flipping over pairs of fruit cards that have been shuffled and placed face-down. The player with the most pairs at the end of the game wins
Let's start.
- Inoue seems to be good at this kind of thing.
- Yeah, he is good at games.
Next is Downtown.
This one and this one.
Please show me the face of the cards.
- Matsumoto-san?
- Hamada-san?
What are you doing?
Is it right?
- I can take whatever I like, right?
- No.
I took this one because I like oranges.
I like oranges and cherries.
- Hamada likes this the best.
- I like this so much.
He eats this all the time.
Isn't that what it means?
If you can turn over two cards with the same picture, you get the cards.
We took this one because we like it!
So it's ours!
We really like it!
We really like it more than Yamazaki thinks!!
We should do this properly.
- Please return the cards.
- Let's shuffle again and do it properly.
His face is making me irritated.
- You mean Iwao?
- Iwao's face is annoying.
Don't worry, Iwao.
Football Hour turned over the cards for pear and muscat, so it was a miss.
Oh, I saw this card just a moment ago!
- No, no, no, no...
- Matsumoto-san!
Now it's Jicho-Kacho's turn.
The rules are vague.
You knew there was a pear here, didn't you?
That was the card that was turned over the turn before.
I'm sure some of you guys couldn't remember where things are.
Sorry, give it back once.
You remembered it was here, didn't you?
So, which card did Inoue turn over?
Inoue turned it over by coincidence.
And I got a match!
No, you did not get a match, Matsumoto-san.
Okay, by the rules, Inoue gets this.
Hey, can't we just stop this already?
If the cards are face down, I won't know what's drawn on them.
There are still lots of questions left.
So, please pick one, Downtown.
- How about a riddle?
- Good.
Let's pull ahead of them.
50!
Q. What animal doesn't like the number 9?
What's the answer?
The animal doesn't like the number 9.
Disnina.
Yeah!
"Disnina"?
Of course not.
What is a disnina?
I don't know, but it is an animal named disnina.
You don't know that?
Anyway, the correct answer is a skunk.
That makes sense!
*[Sukan (Don't like) + Ku(Nine) = Sukanku(Skunk)]
That's the animal that dislikes 9, right?
It's a Disnina.
*[Ku (Nine) + Iya(Dislike) = Kuiya(Disnina)]
It dislikes 9.
Do you even know what that means?
It dislikes 9!
I know what it means.
The animal that dislikes 9, the disnina.
- But it's not real, is it?
- What kind of animal is a disnina?
I don't know, but it's an animal that dislike 9, so it's a disnina.
That kind of animal!
That kind of animal!!
Then give me half the points.
It has a tail!
Listen, it has a tail.
You have to answer a real animal.
Then give me a few points.
- Just give me 10 points.
- Yeah.
I am not asking you to give me 40 points.
I should be allowed to get 30 points.
That's not possible.
If you had answered skunk I would have given you 40 points.
But they didn't answer anything.
Only I answered disnina.
So please give me 30 points.
- We have no right to answer this question.
- And let me say one more thing.
Also, I couldn't see riddle's 50 at all because it was blocked by a flower.
In that situation, the answer I came up with after thinking hard was "Disnina".
Indeed, I couldn't see it from here.
I couldn't see it at all from here.
But I answered without any complaints!
It is an animal called disnina!!
It's not real.
What should we do?
Opinions are split down the middle.
Are you going to give us 30 points or not?
That's not a split.
I won't give you points.
Yamazaki can decide that.
If you want to give us 30 points, you can do so, and if you can't, you can give us 20 points.
I won't give you guys any points!
Are we not able to receive any more points!?
No, I will give you points if you answer correctly.
Gotcha!!
Now let's go to Cocolico!
They were convinced!
Then Yoshimoto's 40.
Q. The comedian of the same generation as Kiyoshi Nishikawa who is still unmarried is the Sakata the *****?
Sakata the idiot.
That's not good for a senior.
You guys get 40 points.
You're lucky.
This is no good.
This can't be broadcast.
Master Sakata is not an idiot.
Of course I know that.
I don't want to be on the air with you guys.
Master Sakata is not an idiot at all.
- I know that.
- That's his comedy style.
I have seen many things that he is not an idiot.
He eats both the main dish and the staple food.
He never eats only main dish.
That's fine, I don't care.
But this is the kind of question this time.
So Goto thinks Master Sakata is an idiot?
I don't think so.
He calls himself an idiot because of his comey style.
Then who here thinks he is an idiot?
Raise your hand if you think he's an idiot.
No one.
But look at the question, it says, "Sakata the *****".
- The answer is nothing but an idiot.
- Do you think there is any other answer than that?
It's Sakata the bald.
Wouldn't he be more angry if you told him that?
- He hasn't actually been told that by anyone.
- I think he would be more angry if he were told that.
But that guy doesn't have much hair.
"That guy"!?
Then raise your hand if you think Sakata is bald.
What do you think?
He's definitely bald.
He looks like it, though.
He's bald, right?
See!
We all raised our hands.
Raise your hand if you think he is an idiot.
Not one.
About four years ago, Master Sakata came up to me and said in my ear,
"Macchan, I stopped putting hair fibers on my head."
He said that.
The less said about that the better.
He has never been called Sakata the bald.
Please give me the standard answer.
Okay,
Please give us 10 points for raising this problem.
I can't be done.
Give us 10 points because we noticed that he is bald.
We knew that, too.
We've all noticed that.
Is that so?
Hang in there, Jicho-Kacho!
Animal's 30!
It's a buzzer quiz!
Q. We asked...
So fast!
Downtown, go ahead!
I couldn't hear the question.
The question was cut off.
Please let us hear the whole question.
You buzzed in before the question was finished.
Okay?
I don't know the answer yet because I only heard part of the question.
This is a buzzer quiz.
So, may I count that as incorrect?
No, no, no...
You have lost your right to answer.
Once you lose the right to answer.
I wasn't informed about that!
You told us to buzz in quickly, so I did.
But then I lost my right to answer.
Even though I was only told "We asked," I was asked to give some kind of answer.
Can't you see I'm nervous!?
Are you nervous?
I make mistakes like buzzing in too quickly because I'm nervous!
- May I answer something?
- Sure.
Polar bear.
Of course not.
Could you please repeat the question?
Q. We asked 100 elevator girls. What is the ranking of animals they would want as pets?
#1: dog, #2: cat.
So, what's in #3?
Football Hour!
Rabbit.
Downtown.
Can you answer quickly?
Downtown, go ahead!
This is a buzzer quiz, you know.
Time's up!
Shut up, asshole!
"Shut up, asshole"?
Aquatic.
Incorrect.
- Jicho-Kacho!
- Hamster!
Downtown.
Terrestrial.
Please provide a proper answer.
Cocorico!
Turtle!
Hey, I buzzed in!
Time's up!
The correct answer is tropical fish.
That's unfair!
Those are aquatic!
If you answer with aquatic or terrestrial, it includes all creatures
I answered aquatic and it was wrong, so we were excluding aquatic animals from our consideration.
You guys don't do that, right?
Yes.
You should have said "close" to him.
Yeah, Itsumi-san would have said so.
-  Itsumi-san would have said so.
- I don't think so.
This is the final question.
If you get the answer to the final question right, you can get 100 points.
Really!?
It's a 100 points question?
Animal's 40!
[Buzzer Quiz]
Everyone has a chance to participate.
Q. What is in a camel's hump, which is essential for traveling through the desert?
Jicho-Kacho, go ahead!
Water!
Downtown, go ahead!
Some kind of extract.
Cocorico!
- Tanaka should know the answer!
- Alright! We can win this!
Fat!
So, the winner is...
Hey, hey, hey...
Can we really end it with "fat"?
There were a lot of things going on, and it ended with "fat".
Let's decide it with rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors?
What's the purpose of playing it?
It's to determine the winner.
On purpose.
Who will be playing?
Hamada and Tanaka.
Hamada-san and Tanaka?
Anyway, let's play rock-paper-scissors once.
Even if you lose, it doesn't matter.
Right.
It has nothing to do with anything.
This is just for fun.
Yes!
Okay, let's play, Endo!
-  It's just for fun, right?
- Let's play, Endo!
Rock-paper-scissors.
Yes!
Congratulations!
Wait a moment!
We haven't done it with Hamada and Endo.
It's okay.
This is just for fun.
Rock-paper-scissors once.
Yes!
Alright, congratulations!
Wait!
The winner is Cocorico!
We will give you a trip to Hawaii as a prize!
Thank you!
This segment is tough.
Because I have to do it while thinking, "What the hell is this guy talking about?"