First Ever on Gaki No Tsukai CHIKI CHIKI!
It's not 10,000, or even 50,000!
You can definitely win this; 30,000 yen competition! (~$300)
So Matsumoto-san, what are we doing this time?
Well .. this time ... uhh
These comedians will showcase a talent worth 30,000 yen
They say a salaryman's monthly allowance is around 30,000 yen
Also, if you go to a brothel,
a ****-job is around that much, desu ne?
- A ****-job?
Yes, if I were to see something worth that much today
I will be very grateful
Showcase your 30,000 yen talent!
All three judges need to agree your talent is worth 30,000 yen to win this prize money!
If you show us something really amazing you might even win 100,000 yen! (~$1000)
- Oh so we can win over this amount?
- Yes think of it as my "special service"
And of course, we have guest stars for this episode
- yoroshiku onegaishimasu
- yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
But uh ... him over there
- Eh?!
I genuinely did not notice him
He's been there the whole time,
he was there before we arrived,
and has not spoken a single word
What technique of being unfunny is this?
I will perform some tap dancing for everyone here today
I've practiced to the point where I think I deserve at least 30,000 yen
- So that's what I want to show you
- A 30,000 yen tap dance?
Endo will tap dance to the Gaki theme song!
Will he win the 30,000 yen?!
Ok here we go, onegaishimasu!
- It's not in sync
- Is it in sync?
It doesn't match the music
- He's just messing about
- It's supposed be like this?
So lame LOL!
Ok judges, write down his prize money
While he was dancing, you guys were all,
"What the hell is this?"
- I thought I did pretty well!
- Looks like the judges are done writing
So with that said, present your impressions!
- 10K yen, 8K yen,
- 600 yen
- 600 yen?! (~ $6)
Wait, wait, wait really only 600 yen?
Well my impression was,
exactly enough
to not afford the toll road fee
I will, in the crevices of my neck,
store some liquid
Uhhh, sorry but,
I have no idea what the hell you just said
Yeah I made less sense that I though I would
This - look at these please
I can make crevices here, can you see them?
In here, I will put the drinks
Understood, please begin!
- Oh I see
- He will do it himself
- Oh it's working
- He's putting a lot in!
- Oh it spilled
-It's spilling
You're kidding right?
He's spilling it already?
I get he might spill it, but he's already spilling it?
It's too soon
What the hell is his plan?
you can do it!
Why is his hand like that?
He's trying to make them deeper
You're kidding right?!
I'm to take this coffee, mix it with the milk,
and make a cafe au lait
Well, I don't think you can do it
There's not enough coffee or milk
- He can do it
- It might work
It won't reach it!
Ok judges ...
Write down his prize money
That was amazing
What is this
Ok, present your impressions!
Well, if the previous one cannot enter the metropolitan toll road,
He can at least enter the ETC
This is pretty terrible right?
This has been terrible since the NTV opening
To rank this among NTV shows,
it would be faster to count from the bottom
Koutoge-kun, you failed to win the prize money
Honestly, I could have put more liquid in
I was nervous, and my hands were shaking, and I messed up
... This is just a normal excuse, I'm sorry
- How do I say this, everyone is taking this in the wrong direction
-This is tough
These three want to give you the money!
I'm just saying, If someone came to your house and did that,
Would you pay them 30,000 yen?
- No
- No we wouldn't
- Absolutely would not
- Right?
So, who will go nex-
Wait!
He finally spoke
Allow me to go next
Think you can win?
These guys need to understand what a 30,000 yen performance really is
- Yes I think it's about time
- License!
- Yes?
- Come help me out
- Ok, what should we do
Take this box to the stage over there
- We're gonna switch to the stage now
- Ok take him out front
When did he arrive to the studio?
(Housei has been on standby for 6 hours)
That guy, no matter what he does,
he costs us a lot of money and time
I guess you're right
Who the hell spends over 30K yen to win a prize of just 30K yen?
Looks like he's ready!
I'm a ninja!
That is my performance, a ninja!
a ninja?
Understood, please begin!
♩ Hide your, bo-o-dy! ♫
That's it?
- You're kidding right?
- This is a joke right?
Is that all this is?
Finished!
He's done huh?
How much prize money does this deserve?
Prize money for this?
The guy who did the art did the real work
He's smiling so much
The guy who did the art is amazing though
I was invisible for a second right?
because ninja
Maybe you could see me,
but you had no idea where I was right?
They matched! (~$1)
- But you don't win any money!
- They match though!
No, no, you need to get 30k from all of us!
- You won't get 100 yen
- Yeah that's right
- Of course you won't
- Please sit down
He's not satisfied with that at all
Yeah I like, really hated that
"really hated" ?
Ok next up, Naomi!
I will continuously receive volleyballs
I was captain of the volleyball team in middle school
I won't let them fall to the ground
- So if they fall to the ground, that's a failure?
- That's a failure
You better give out that 30k yen soon!
Says the guy who won 100 yen
This is the kind of thing we should see
- Woah that's close
- Kinda scary
Make it go faster
I guess it does hurt!
Spread it out
Use your hands!
No no no no !
She could only do it in the beginning
That's not the way to do it
That's enough, we're finished!
Write down her prize money please
Okay please present your impressions!
that was close!
What were you doing here?
I continously recieved volleyba-
You totally didn't though! Only for like the first three
well yes, but I didn't let them hit the floor
- She even used her feet for that
- That really hurt didn't it?
It really really hurts
Heipo what do you think of all this?
Volleyball right? I think most people could do better
- Heipo can also do it
- Really?
- I used to play volleyball
- Get it ready for him
You used to play volleyball?
I played soccer and volleyball
Please show us
That was so quick!
- Please allow me to go next
- Ok go!
You guys know what this is right?
Matsumoto-san you probably use this for working out; This is a medicine ball
It's full of sand, and weighs about 4kg (0.63 stone)
I just want to demonstrate its proper usage
Koutoge, come here a second
I just want to demonstrate the proper usage
This is used for strength training
- Wait that's 4kg?
- Yes 4kg
Boxers use this to train their body by having it dropped on themselves
Wait a minute, is his dick hard?
If you can get hard in this situation, you can have the 30,000!
So that was the proper way to use this
But using this 4kg ball, I will do lifting
If you can do that it would be pretty impressive
Here I go!
Honestly man...
One of you bastards, go next!
- Wait it's ok!
- He's still not done!
I'm still not done!
Hold on you didn't say how many times you're gonna do it
Well since it's a 4kg ball, 10 times
That was fantastic!
Okay, okay
Judges, this is how heavy the ball he just kicked is
So take that into consideration
So judges please write down his prize money!
Seriously though, if you guys don't get it together,
We're the ones who take the blame for this show right?
I'm counting on you
Ok judges, are you ready?
Present your impressions!
So close!
This is a good score
The best we've had today
It wasn't good enough for the full 30k,
but certainly, that was not something that anyone can do
Just a bit more huh?
It wasn't enough
It wasn't enough, but I've created some momentum haven't I?
Let's keep going from here!
That was almost good enough, let's improve on that!
Who wants to go next? Tsukajiro?
Keep this momentum going
What is your performance?
The theme of the anime "3000 Leagues in Search of Mother"
I will sing it full of emotion, and cry
This does seem like something he can do
Ready Tsukajiro?
He's already in the zone!
He has to keep Inomoto's momentum going
Here comes the chorus
The tears are coming
Anytime now they'll come
C'mon, fall!
Nevermind he lost it
This is gonna take some time
This is not what I imagined
Seriously?
Why'd he cry after it ends?
He's trying again right now for no reason
- He's trying to force it
- He can do it now!
No that's not right, what is he doing?
He's crying, tears are coming out!
This has nothing to do with the song
Uwah I'm just being lied to
I've been lied to!
This is impossible
Write his prize money!
- He might cry
- he might cry
Even if he cries now, who cares?
He was supposed to cry while singing
You failed!
- He's crying now
- Tears are coming
He cried after seeing his score
That anime was completely irrelevant huh?
If you ask me though,
I was simply lied to by my junior
The score went up a bit from Inomoto this time though
There's no point in crying now!
- This time for real!
- Did he cry?
- He did!
The song was absolutely pointless
My performan-
- We're counting on you man
- Don't worry
- I've got something really good
- What?
Using a pube I found in the dressing room,
I'm gonna make a bracelet
That is really good!
Ah wait,
Wait,
WAIT!
That's not it!
That's not it?!
- You got that mixed up with something else?
- Yes I apologise
Using this Shanghai here,
Ah wait,
Wait,
WAIT!
- You mistook that for something else?! -
Completely the wrong word
- Look at it properly!
- This guy is gonna raise the score?
This apple here right?
Normally you use a knife to cut it right?
So without using a knife,
A single bite size - exactly that size, I'll bring that over to you
- A single bite size?
- Yes I'll bring that right over to you
- So you see this case right?
- Yes
An apple bite just this size, I'll bring that right over to you
- Are you ready?
I guess, I, AM
- Ok, here we go
- Wait sorry hold on
- What the hell?
- Sorry my bad
You said you were ready
Here we go
- I guess, I, AM
- What the hell?
So a piece exactly this size
Take this seriously you bastards!
Just what is this?
- I-I'll do it again for you
- Do it again, I don't get it
Okay so you bite it ...
What are you trying to do?
This is something anyone can do LOL
I just don't get the rules
This so messed up
That piece is too big
Why the hell?!
I have no idea what you were trying to do
Just tell us whether or not he gets the prize money
Well it's true that I laughed,
If I was even a little bit sick, I wouldn't have laughed at all