No-Laughing Series' Famous Jimmy Onishi
Understand everything about Jimmy Onishi!
A 24 Hour Long Interview to reveal his true self.
Birth
Kindergarten
Elementary School
Middle School
High School
Performer Apprentice
Popular Performer
Switch to Painter
Return to TV
Every turning point in his life will be uncovered.
Jimmy's Elementary School Days
I wasn't able to speak at first...
In elementary school there was a girl I really liked.
So the first word I spoke was "like".
And from there I began to slowly learn how to speak Japanese.
Don't say that like a kid returning to Japan!!
And about his best friend back then...
Well, he taught me how to masturbate so...
He's my lewd benefactor.
I've masturbated without missing a single day since the 5th grade.
This must be scary for the interviewer.
We also saw a different side of him while eating...
What kind of Western-style food do you like?
Food like...
Salisbury steak...
Those are some bad table manners.
What's with those manners?
You're not my mom to be lecturing me!!
The first half was filled with indecent answers,
how will tonight's conclusion fare!?
And, will Jimmy be able to finish the 24 hour interview?
Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Tonight is the conclusion!!
His mysterious painter era will be discussed!!
Time: 8 hours 3 minutes
Jimmy Onishi's 24 Hour Long Interview
Tonight we'll start with his popular performer days.
Starting as a stagehand,
Jimmy was able to begin
his life as a performer.
After high school, Jimmy started working at a Yoshimoto theater.
Starting at 19, he spent two years as Bonchi Osamu's apprentice.
What happened after you finished your apprenticeship?
At the time, Sanma-san was asking "Any drivers here?"
He wanted to hire one.
It just so happened I didn't have a job anymore,
so I thought, "Alright, I'll become a driver."
He was 22 at the time.
To work as Sanma's driver, he headed to Tokyo.
How much did you get paid back then?
Between 200,000 and 300,000 yen.
And how did you spend that money?
Mostly on sex services.
There he goes.
Well, if I had 300,000, I'd spend 280,000 yen on sex services.
Just spend all 300,000 yen then!!
By being part of "Hyokin zoku" and then "Yatteru Yatteru"
Q. How did you get your big break?
Q. At the time, what was the harshest show?
Owarai Ultra Quiz was the harshest.
Getting tossed into the ocean
from a ferry was pretty intense.
From how many meters?
I'd say about 2.30 meters.
Q. Who is your favorite Gaki member?
Hamada-kun.
He's the most normal person.
What the hell?
Q. Any memorable moments with Hosei?
The showdown where we hit each other.
Halfway into it I actually started disliking him.
Q. Would you be willing to do a Jimmy vs Hosei again?
Sure, I'd do it.
If I did it now, I wouldn't...
I don't think I'd get angry at him.
Time: 11 hours 6 minutes
And so, it's been 11 hours since the beginning.
To change the mood, we go outside for dinner.
Of course, while they're on their way...
What do you like to eat when you go out?
I like to eat sushi.
Do you like ramen?
Yeah, I like ramen.
What flavor do you prefer?
Soy sauce or salt flavor.
So you dislike miso flavor?
Miso flavor is...
It's not that I dislike it, I just don't eat it.
You're getting a bit angry.
You really don't like that interviewer.
We've arrived to dine on one of Jimmy's favorite meals, yakiniku.
The interview is going to continue.
Right now, I refuse to answer any more questions.
Really, it's been enough.
Here, we will delve into Jimmy's enigmatic painter days.
I want to hear this.
It was 1996 and Jimmy was one of the most popular comedians, but...
he suddenly decided to become a painter.
For what reason did he do it?
At the height of your popularity, why did you become a painter?
A painting I did for a "TV Personalities" auction
sold at a surprisingly high price.
I thought, "Was my painting alright? Wasn't it too weird?"
Jimmy's first masterpiece was sold for 330,000 yen.
His work caught the attention of a certain artist.
I received a letter from Okamoto Taro.
What did the letter say?
"Go beyond the canvas."
That was all.
Seriously?
So those words became a strong motivation to become a painter.
That's amazing.
It's really amazing.
That's right.
Was it not possible to do it along with comedy?
I tried doing that but...
I started struggling with both of them.
Comedy and painting could not coexist...
and so, when choosing which one to go for...
I decided to take a break from show business.
What did Sanma-san tell you after you made your decision?
"Don't listen to anyone."
How did you interpret Sanma-san's advice?
That if I listened to what others said, my individuality would die out.
That I shouldn't let go of the good things in me.
Around the time you became a painter...
you immigrated to Barcelona, right?
Why did you choose to go there?
You moved to Barcelona?
I visited an art museum in Ueno and fell in love with Picasso...
so I thought about visiting Picasso's birthplace, Spain.
And I ended up going to Barcelona.
That's amazing, I knew there was more
to him than just perverted stories.
Was it hard to adapt to the differences with Tokyo?
Yeah, being far from Tokyo made me feel lonely.
But thankfully, despite being in Spain, in Barcelona...
I was able to quickly find some sex services.
I knew this phrase would be back.
What the hell?!
What kind of paintings did you work on (in Barcelona)?
There was a nudist beach in front of where I lived so...
I went to the beach every day but
every painting would end up becoming a naked woman...
Even when painting animals, breasts would pop up here and there.
Painted in Barcelona
"Paradise"
Well, that's pretty nice.
They would end up being really weird paintings.
Nonetheless, it was a solitary life overseas.
The devoted person who supported him was his female manager.
Eventually, the two got married.
Jimmy chose this young woman as his lifelong partner.
When did you develop feelings for your manager?
It was when I couldn't hold it in anymore, because I couldn't go.
You couldn't get sex services?
Yes, it was too much.
I couldn't just tell her, "I'm going out for sex services."
Stop.
How did you romance your manager?
This guy is wild.
I pinned her down.
He's saying this with his mouth full.
Afterwards, while traveling all over the word,
Jimmy immersed himself into the world of art.
Going beyond the canvas, he created all kinds of highly valued works,
which brimmed with his individuality.
How much do your paintings sell for?
Something around this size would sell for about 2,000,000 yen.
How long does it take (to paint them)?
At least 3 months.
There's times when I go too frequently for sex services,
and I struggle to progress on the paintings so...
I just end up spending all my money.
Would you say that the reason you returned to Japan was...
because you couldn't earn enough money as an artist?
Yeah, well... I didn't keep any of my paintings for too long...
I couldn't do one-man exhibitions frequently.
If I had done more, I could have earned more money.
But for someone like me who...
spends too much in sex services,
it's hard to keep my paintings around.
You're really unbelievable!!
Debt Repayment
The reason he returned to show business was surprisingly simple.
Time: 12 hours 58 minutes
It's 11 PM and we're back at the hotel.
Now, we will talk about his return to show business.
After a long break, what did you think about your return?
It's very harsh.
You're laughing a bit.
Out of every job I've ever done, today is probably the worst.
Today's middle school and high school students...
probably don't know about the things you've done before.
Yes, they don't know anything, but...
It's thanks to the annual "No-Laughing series" that...
I haven't been forgotten yet.
I always feel relieved that I accepted to appear...
I see.
I'm very thankful.
He's so annoying.
Taking advantage of your return...
is there any show you want to appear in?
Hodo Station
Doing what?
A discussion with a politician.
You already did that in a
"No-Laughing" batsu.
What would you talk about with a politician?
I'd tell him that instead of ending all sex services at 12:00 AM,
please let them stay open for 24 hours.
After a rigorous job like this one...
I always get a tired boner.
It's around dawn when I get more tired boners.
This is the first time I
hear that word on TV.
It's around dawn when I get more tired boners.
If they canceled the adult entertainment regulations, I could go get sex services.
If they canceled them?
I'm pretty sure that sexual crimes would also decrease even more.
That had more meaning than I though.
You think it would reduce sex crimes?
That's right.
You returned to show business last year around autumn, right?
Yes, around that time.
How much of your debt were you able to pay back?
It got bigger.
It got bigger?!
What made it grow even more?
I overdid it with the sex services.
Sex services again...
Time: 14 hours 8 minutes
The interview has gone over the 14 hour mark and it's taking its toll on Jimmy.
It's too long...
This is where it gets hard.
I'm getting sleepy...
Sudden drowsiness, in that case...
Let's wake him up.
Roof terrace
What's your favorite TV show?
It must be cold.
Definitely Sazae-san.
It's not Hodo Station?
Hodo Station is the show I want to be in.
But you don't like it.
It's a regular program so it would help me pay back my debt.
So that's what you're aiming for...
He hadn't smiled like that in a while.
Don't you want to appear in the show
"Wide na Show" with Matsumoto and Higashino?
I'd like to.
Do you watch the show?
No, because it's (broadcasted) very late in Osaka and I get sleepy...
Very late at night in Osaka...
Time: 15 hours 10 minutes
His drowsiness has gone away so we go back to the room.
We approach Jimmy with serious questions about his true essence.
His face looks different.
I'd like to hear about your personal philosophy of comedy.
Comedy is basically...
A certain feeling of tension that makes you laugh.
Maybe showing your butt at the pool isn't funny...
But at a funeral it would be funny, because there's that tension,
and it makes you laugh.
Comedy is tension and sympathy.
Erm, empathy.
Comedy is tension and empathy.
One usually talks about things everyone else is thinking.
If they're able to relate to that, then it becomes comedy.
So if there's empathy and tension, it becomes funnier.
Anything current comedians should be doing?
Organized drinking parties.
In the old days, there was no need to be careful...
so we had our fair share of fun.
Nowadays, you can get criticized or flamed...
on sites like Twitter and the like.
Are you also being more careful?
Um...
I have a driver come pick me up...
when I go out for sex services.
Another indecent answer
Let's digress from this.
As a comedian, what is the one principle that you will never break?
To never sleep with a transvestite.
Somehow another indecent answer
The question said "as a comedian".
The answers are mostly dirty jokes...
Of course, we can't have him continue answering like this.
Your answers have been mostly indecent
things, we'd prefer if you didn't...
They got angry at you.
Motion to ban indecent answers
The staff decided to ban these answers.
Now we looked forward to a proper interview.
However
Excuse me.
Good evening, I'm here
for the massage...
The massage...
Thank you...
Ah, this timing...
This won't be good...
We'll refresh and heal his tired body with a massage.
The director just told me to stop with all the dirty talk...
How am I supposed to do that with this?
You're really looking forward to it, huh?
What are you making me do?
A radiant smile
What the hell?
And so, he puts on disposable underwear and the massage begins.
Seriously, what the hell?
You're thinking too much.
How does it feel, Jimmy?
It feels so good. It's the best.
While you're relaxed like this, let's go over some things from before.
What are you most grateful to Sanma-san?
I'd say... um...
That it's thanks to him that I can have food on my table.
What is the most memorable story you had with Bonchi Osamu?
Erm... one day...
he told me, "Come to my place, let's drink tonight."
But something held him up that day so...
he called his wife and told her, "Let Onishi sleep there."
And then... uh... his wife...
she said, "I just got a call from him."
"He said it was fine for the two of us to sleep before he comes back."
So I took her up on her offer and...
I took off my pants and said, "Let's get started then."
I misunderstood her.
That's the most memorable...
Ah, that was another dirty story...
That's right, they're banned.
Time: 18 hours 6 minutes
It's been 18 hours since the start.
We've arrived at the period of time that is hardest on the body.
How will Jimmy overcome it!?
Q. How long do you plan to continue as a comedian?
Until I'm 65.
Why is that?
Because then I'll be able to live off my pension.
Q. What do you want to do after you retire?
Look for coffee beans.
In retirement, I want to drink good coffee and...
eat castella cake in the afternoons.
Q. What would you buy for yourself as a reward for your retirement?
This guy is just unbelievable.
A walking stick.
My knees have started to hurt when I go up and down stairs.
I'm starting to feel my age.
A few years ago you had plastic surgery, right?
Q. A few years ago, what did you change with plastic surgery?
Yes.
What did you change?
His chin.
My chin, it sticked out too much so I pushed it in.
Q. At this point, why have a plastic surgery?
At just over 45 years, I thought it was the perfect time.
The perfect time?
Q. If you were reincarnated, what would you like to become?
A dog, something like a bulldog.
Someone else will take care of me...
and they will fawn over me.
Tape change.
Can I take a quick break?
Just a bit.
Does everyone really do 24 hours straight?
They do... they do...
Seriously?
They don't just record enough and call it a night?
You're the only one who has complained.
It never ends...
All these questions... they're really...
Well then, let's go to the next question.
Naturally, the 24 hour long interview continues without breaks...
Along with the sunrise, comes trouble!!
Time: 20 hours 32 minutes
Dawn has come at last and it's time for breakfast.
Jimmy is good at cooking, so earlier in the interview we had a request for him.
Since you're good at cooking, could you make our breakfast?
Sure thing.
How about rice balls?
Sure, I'll make kombu rice balls... yeah...
So now, Jimmy will prepare rice balls with piping hot rice.
Hot!
Hot! Hot!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
They just made it,
he needs to let it
cool down.
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
He's so irritating.
Why is it so hot?
It's still hot.
Hot!
Why?
He really makes
me angry.
He didn't put any
kombu inside!
It looks like he just
mixed them up.
With his best effort, Jimmy finished making the rice balls.
There are my famous "Square Rice Balls"
They're neither triangular nor circular, they're square rice balls.
Thanks for the food.
It looks bad, but what about its taste?
They're really good, if I may say so myself.
They probably don't
want to eat them.
What do you think Kojima-san?
It's a ball of goo.
He used too much water.
Well, at least it's light on the stomach...
when it feels gooey like this.
Time: 23 hours
It's a little over 9 AM and there's only one hour left.
Alright, this is the last spurt.
Please tell us about the angriest moment in your life.
Um... I had a wound back here and it became a bald spot.
I was in the bullet train when this old guy...
started poking my bald spot with a toothpick, so I got angry.
In what way did you lose your temper?
I told him, "Hey! I'll tell the conductor and have him change my seat!!"
And I did so they changed my seat.
Which animal would you compare yourself to?
An animal...
an orangutan.
In what way?
Fear of extinction.
Fear?
Yes, about being on the edge of extinction.
What have these last 24 hours made you realize?
I think I said too many perverted things.
Ah, he's aware.
I became aware that I'm pretty much masturbation-man.
What the hell?
In 24 hours, Jimmy answered 4086 questions.
Is there anything else you want to say?
No, there's nothing left.
Nothing left to do or say.
I got everything out.
Time: 23 hours 57 minutes
And finally, the time came.
Well then, this is finally the last question.
After talking about it for 24 hours, what can you say about your life?
I think it's been an absurdly unbelievable life.
It's over.
Yes.
Thanks for the hard work.
Thanks, is it over?
It's been 24 hours.
Thank you.
24 Hour Long Interview Completed
I'm going home.
Are you staying here in Tokyo today?
No, I'm taking the bullet train to Osaka.
I'm going to masturbate in the train's toilet.
24 Hour Long Interview
FIN
Why do you have to say that at the end?
Look, I have no explanation for this but...
Don't you guys get aroused by being on TV?
What do you mean?
That feeling you get when you see all these people.
Like you get really excited?
Like when you see female performers.
Yes, like that.
And after you're done, you want to go to sleep but you can't...
What's this?
This.
I'm making a phone call.
You know, if this interview had been for an educational channel instead, could they have even shown it?