1st Gaki-no-tsukai-ya-arahende!!
Duo Showdown: Battle Across Various Competitions for 100,000 Yen Prize!
Hi guys!
The two duos participating in this are Cocorico and License!
Now, let's introduce today's stars!
Downtown!
Hi.
I don't really know what to do today.
Moreover, I'm not feeling well today.
What should I do?
- This is a 3 duos competit ....
- Hurry up and say it.
- Don't be so sluggish and say it quickly.
If you make it concise, I will understand.
- Really?
- You are indeed slow to speak.
- But...
You speak slowly.
I'm sorry!
Today, 3 teams will compete.
There are 16 panels here. Compete with the games or riddles written behind them.
The team with the highest points will receive a prize of 100,000 yen!
Is this given to the duo? Or is it given to each person separately?
That was unclear.
It can be taken either way.
- We will give 100,000 yen to the duo.
- 50,000 yen each?
Are you guys a duo?
I don't watch TV, so I don't know.
- We've been working together on this show with you for about 16 years.  Yes, we are a duo.
- Is that so?
Also, are the duos color-coded?
- Yes. Red, blue and yellow.
- I see it now.
I see.
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]
Anyway, the winning team will receive the prize! Good luck!
Now, Downtown, please pick one of the 16 panels!
- Then, I'll decide.
- Please do!
- Number 5!
- Open number 5!
Riddle!
This is a buzzer quiz for all teams to participate in!
As soon as you know the answer, press the answer button.
Okay, here is the question!
Q. Where is the scariest place in a house?
Go ahead!
The scariest place in a house.
The scariest place in a house?
Oh, I got it!
Go ahead, Endo.
- Stairs.
*Both stairs and horror stories in Japanese are
called "Kaidan".
Stairs: 階段(Kaidan) / Horror stories: 怪談(Kaidan)
Correct!
Is Endo scared of stairs?
Is your name Endo?
I'm not scared of it.
Horror Stories are called Kaidan, and there are Kaidan(Stairs) in the house too.
I don't think it's a good idea to suddenly say "stairs".
Viewers might find it hard to understand.
We understand, though.
But I think they can understand it too.
It's a simple.
I thought Endo might have a trauma with stairs.
What was your intention in answering that?
What do you mean?
Why are you laughing!?
Sorry.
Isn't a riddle supposed to be like that?
If that's okay, then Hamada knew the answer.
But if Hamada said that, everyone would be thinking, "So what?" I think.
Hamada has influence, so everyone is expecting what he will say.
- You can just answer as you are.
- But, considering Hamada's influence, he can't say that.
You have to understand that.
Hamada is a Tsukkomi! He can't say that!
- No, I didn't ...
- Hamada is really pitiful! He is missing out.
No, the riddle is fine with that answer.
We are missing out!!
Especially Hamada!
- He is not missing out at all.
- He has influence. I've said this many times!
This is just a riddle, please answer it quickly.
Cocorico earns 10 points!
They got ahead of them.
Next is Cocorico, please pick a panel!
- Then, number 12 please.
- Number 12, open!
Is the question changing from a riddle?
"We asked 100 people."
He didn't explain enough. Is this a riddle or not?
We interviewed 100 female college students.
Please see here.
"What is the popular dating spot?"
I see!
Please answer in order starting from Cocorico.
Cocorico has the advantage.
Amusement park!
Amusement park?
Okay, please be more specific.
You give Cocorico preferential treatment!
That's terrible! What the hell are you doing?
No, I didn't do that.
You are doing something suspicious with Cocorico!
You are doing something suspicious with them!
And it's got caught by me!!
No, it's not.
You should not let Cocorico answer again, you should let License answer.
Oh, my god!
I'm laughing so hard it's hilarious!!
That's so funny!
That's sooo funny!!
- But an amusement park would ...
- Oh, my god!
That's so funny!
- What does that mean?
- That's so funny!
You are doing something suspicious with them!
And it's got caught by me!!
Oh my god! I'm going to laugh!
We don't have to answer that, it's okay.
That's so funny!
It's got caught by me!!
It's got caught by all of us!!
- Let License answer ...
- That's so funny!
That's so funny!
Shut up!!
- Cocorico.
- Yes.
"Amusement park" has a wide range, so please give a specific answer.
- Can I answer?
- Go ahead.
Disneyland.
Is that ranked?
- What the hell.
- He answered twice.
Correct!
- It's a 1st place!
- Great!
It's a 1st place!
Eiga-kan (Movie theatre).
Licence's answer was "Eiga-kan(Movie theater)," earning him 10 points.
Next up is Downtown!
- It must be Odaiba
- Yeah.
Is that your answer?
Is this ranked?
There will be a lot of people there.
- Correct.
- It's no wonder.
The place names are also ranked.
It is strange that he carefully checks with our answer.
The place name Odaiba was in third place.
So...
We're talking right now!!
What have you been doing since earlier?
Say a wrong answer.
Say something unrelated.
Say the answer, not the spot.
Takoyaki stand.
No way.
No way, idiot!!
You are an idiot.
No way.
Incorrect.
It's no wonder.
What the hell is a "takoyaki stand?"
You have no sense at all!!
"Takoyaki stand"?
License, go ahead.
It's a  chance!
Suizoku-kan (Aquarium)
Aquarium!
Is that ranked?
Yes!
It's a common place, so there's no need to think too hard about it.
Technically, it's "Suizoku-kan."
He said "Suizokkan."
There is no place called "Suizokkan".
That place doesn't exist!
But I understood.
Next up is Downtown.
Could it be Tokyo Dome?
- A common place?
- That's right! It's so...
Is it domed?
I can't answer that.
Tell me that much.
Is it domed or not?
I can't answer that.
What do you think about that?
What is your personal opinion?
My personal opinion?
I can't give you my personal opinion, that would be a hint.
Well then, I'll also exercise my right to remain silent.
I don't understand what that means.
The answer is a common place.
There's no need to think so hard about it.
Karaoke.
Yup.
Are you alright?
Okay!
Is karaoke ranked?
This is ranked.
That is not ranked.
You have led us to the incorrect, right?
Time's up!
The current score is Cocorico with 30 points, License with 20 points, and Downtown with 10 points.
Why does License have 20 points? That's weird.
That's for Suizokkan(Aquarium) and ...
- It's "Suizoku-kan"!
- Yes.
And Eiga-kan(Movie theatre).
Suizoku-kan and Eiga-kan.
Everything has "kan" in it.
You appear in this and that's all you say. That's terrible.
- Congratulations! It's good that you earned 20 points.
- Thank you!
There's still hardly any difference in points.
Then, Licence picked a panel of Celebrity Association Quiz.
It's a game where you guess who is being referred to based on hints about a celebrity.
Here is the first hint!
"Brazil."
Please press the button to answer once you have figured out who it is.
License!
Ruy Ramos (former soccer player).
- He can't guess that quickly.
- There are many people who are originally from Brazil.
Hamada-san!
Coffee.
There was a café called "Brazil", right?
The answer is a celebrity.
- There was a café near the training school!
- Yes, there was.
Hamada, I thought for a moment that it wasn't there, but it was there.
- Yeah.
- Medaka-san often ordered coffee there.
They bring it in a cup with a cling wrap, right?
"Hi, it's Brazil."
- Maybe I should have explained that celebrity name is the answer at the beginning.
- It's written there.
The Brazil's lady was a celebrity around the training school.
And when I say "Brazil's lady," she's just an older lady from Osaka.
But she was a celebrity.
It's a top-notch comedian ordering that coffee.
Hamada didn't really think this was the correct answer!
He answered for this show!!
Is it not allowed to talk about the café's older lady on this show!?
Did this show become one where you can't talk about the café's older lady?!!
Give us points!
- That's impossible.
- Why!?
Isn't that unfair?
Why not? We've been embarrassed here!
You didn't answer correctly.
Now, Cocorico, please pick a panel.
Number 15.
Number 15, open.
[Battle: Fishing Game]
Battle  Gaaaaaaa!!
What's a "battle gaaa"?
It's a fishing game.
Please go forward.
Duos will compete in a fishing game.
The time limit is one minute, and the duo who catches the most fish will receive 10 points.
It starts from downtown.
- It's a disadvantage to be the first to do this.
- Really?
I don't know what kind of game this is.
- Since we are at the top, shall we do this first?
- I see.  Let's have Cocorico do it first.
- "Since we are on top"?
Hey, what's with the arrogant tone?
Then the juniors should go first.
- Then we will do this first.
Let's do it. We can't waste time.
- Hey, why are there no strings?
- Matsumoto-san...?
What are you talking about?
Say it clearly!
Matsumoto-san snapped the string before handing it over to us.
Do you mean to say that I snapped this?
Y-Yes.
There's no way I would do something like that. We're about to use this now.
That's right.
Oh, there's something lying over there.
Look, it has been lying there from the beginning!
This has been snapped off.
Since it was already like that from the beginning. Why are you so sure about that?
Why did you say "snapped off"?
"Snapped off"?
Hey, what's your point?
Hey.
- Hey, Endo, apologize to him.
- Sorry.
Why are you laughing?
- Endo.
- Sorry.
What are you talking about?
Why are you so irritable?
Why are you laughing?
- You've been strange since you came to the dressing room. Don't get annoyed!
- Sorry.
You definitely have some good qualities as well!!
Don't show your irritation on the show!
Yes.
Why are you holding onto stress by yourself?
- Hey!
- Sorry.
You'll be fine!
Okay, let's do this.
First, let's start with License.
Are you ready?
Start! The time limit is one minute.
What is this? It's creepy.
Well done.
Hurry up or you'll run out of time.
Please don't move the table.
I've only caught one fish so far.
That makes two fish now!
Isn't this too long?
Don't you think so?
10 seconds left!
Please don't touch the string.
You faaaaaaaailed!!
Hey, don't do that!
Okay?
Your record is three fish.
How was it?
- The table was moving.
- Aren't you guys the worst?
That's not a lot.
You guys are the worst.
Didn't you touch the string with your finger at the end?
- This is quite difficult, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Next, Cocorico's turn.
Okay, let's start!
Wow, you're good!
Hey, Tanaka!
Do your best!
Endo-san already caught one fish quickly.
Hey, don't move, Tanaka.
Keep it up!
Endo-san is good at this!
It's too long.
Wow, awesome!
You still have more than half of the time remaining!
Cocorico's two skillfully caught five fish.
Actually, I could have caught more fish.
But isn't five fish enough?
Hamada-san kicked my butt...
- I would never do that.
We're all competing.
- What the hell.
That makes us look really mean, doesn't it?
Hamada wouldn't do something like that.
He quite likes Tanaka.
Can I watch the recorded video?
[VCR Verification]
After this, that will happen.
What did you do to him?
- I haven't seen this in a while!
This is a habit of Hamada!
- Yeah.
I saw it for the first time.
Hamada has been doing it like this since the old days.
When he became a duo with me, he used to do it a lot.
He stopped doing it when Tomii-san(Yoshimoto's employee) told him to, but he did it again after a long time.
He is not kicking Tanaka.
Wow! Can I get a copy of this video later?
How nostalgic!
Okay.
Next is Downtown.
Alright, get ready.
Ready, start!
It has started.
It's quite hard!
Keep it going!
He caught one.
Please don't hold the string.
Can't I hold it?
30 seconds left.
Don't hold the string.
Keep it going!
He is catching fish with his hands.
20 seconds left!
- 15 seconds left!
-  Hosei-san!
He is catching fish with his hands!
Hamada-san, please don't catch it with your hands.
Almost! Let's go for perfect!
Close!
They were catching fish with their hands.
- Did you guys see that?
- Yes.
- Yama-chan didn't see that.
- I was just looking at the timer.
Is that true?
I'm just surprised.
We all saw that.
I didn't expect my junior to be so inexperienced.
You guys can say that to your senior so easily.
Are you trying to make a joke?
No one is laughing!
- Nobody is laughing at all!
- Yeah.
- That's terrible!
- This is not a joke.
It's hard when you say something out loud and no one is laughing.
You'll probably dwell on it.
But I'm not really bothered by it, to be honest.
This is not a joke.
- I just held the fish I caught with a rod with my hand
- Did you really catch a fish?
Was it really?
Downtown won the game with 7 catches.
FUCK YEAAAAAAAH!!
So they get 10 points.
10 points!
Huh!? Wait!!
- It's okay if it's just 10 points.
- 10 points is too low!
That's no good.
Finally, it's a paper-cutting battle!
Each duo representative must complete a paper-cutting art that follows the theme within one minute.
The duo with the best work will receive 100 points.
I will judge.
That's good, right?
Let's turn the winning team of this game into a victorious team.
Okay, that's fine.
But， we ．．．
This is a cliché.
Endo, no one is laughing.
Don't make such an easy joke.
Endo, no one has laughed since you woke up this morning.
You know that, don't you?
The fate of the competition is in the hands of the three of them.
What's the theme of the paper-cutting?
An elephant full of dynamism.
Elephant.
Let the paper-cutting battle start!
Give it your all!
Go for it!
- Make an elephant in one minute!
- Hamada, do your best!
Elephants are characterized by their shape.
Please have the buddy set the cut paper onto the mounting board.
There's only a little time left.
We finished within the time limit.
- We finished quickly, so take that into consideration.
- Sure!
Finish!
Please show us one by one starting from Licence.
- This is my elephant.
- Nice!
How about this?
It's so detailed, and it even has tusks!
This looks like a mite!
This is what it looks like when you magnify a mite.
The house dust mite looks like this.
If you look at that under the microscope, it looks like this.
This is great! I especially like how the trunk is raised upward.
- It's dynamic.
- It's quite good.
This isn't dynamic.
Next, Tanaka!
Yeah, this is an elephant.
- I see! What are the points where you made efforts?
- He likes animals, but this is nothing special.
This is a poor elephant.
- I've depicted the elephant's mouth carefully, with an upper lip attached to the trunk and a lower lip.
- Oh, Isee.
- If a child who woke up to go to the bathroom at night saw this at their pillow, they would cry.
- That's right.
All right, it's pretty good.  Then, please show us Hamada-san's work for the last
He is truly in a different league than you guys.
Then, please show us Hamada-san's work for the last
- This is scary.
- What the hell is this?
What did you make?
Hamada is truly in a different league than you guys!!
Excuse me, the theme is elephants.
Where is the elephant in this?
This just needs a little gap here, see?
Is this an elephant seen from the front?
He just didn't have enough of it.
Did you guys get scared of him!?
He's on a different level than you guys!!
Why did you make a silhouette of an elephant viewed from the front?
That looks like a girl's face.
This will determine the winning team.
And now, let's announce the winning team!
The winner is ...
License!
That's ridiculous!
That's ridiculous!!
Congratulations!
- You were really good.
- That's ridiculous!
Please take this.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!!
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!!
- He's extremely angry.
That's ridiculous!!!
What part of this is missing!?
Rather, what part of that is winning?
Congratulations, License!
Thank you!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!!
It might have been better to cut it a little smaller.
We should have had an expert evaluate this.
We don't want an amateur who has never done paper cutting to be the judge.
We should have asked Dyna Haruno to come.
- Do you know him?
- I don't know.
Did someone who doesn't know Dyna Haruno judge this?
Endo, what's wrong?
You're off your game.
Me?
- No one is laughing.
- Me?
Get it together!
Okay, let's go.
He took the money.
- Licence, are you guys okay?
- No!
Please return the money.
- Hamada-san!?
- Hamada-san!
Please return the money.
Even though he made such a terrible elephant.
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]