TPF
Gaki no Tsukai's First "Are their five minds connected?"
He's bothering the neighborhood.
"Meeting each other without phones!"
Text
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Tsukitei Hosei
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
You're bothering the neighborhood.
I'm not...
The people here...
They're right here.
I'm not shouting...
All the residents here...
I'm not shouting that loud.
They heard you all the way to TV Asahi.
It's impressive.
Matsumoto. This time, without using phones,
Yes.
we have to meet each other.
You know,
I was the one saying this was reckless
Can they meet each other without using phones?
Test
but the staff really wanted to do it.
And we decided we would go around trying to get back
together in this place, after being separated.
"Isn't everyone except Matsumoto a bunch of idiots?"
No way.
That's what everyone was saying.
They wouldn't say that.
Everyone in the coffee shop were saying that.
Who would say that?
What were you talking about?
The people in the table next to us were saying that everyone in Gaki except Matsumoto was an idiot.
That makes me angry.
That's irritating.
Yeah.
It's so irritating.
Rules Explanation
After getting a theme
they must head to the place that comes to mind
If they can get together
in the same place, the test ends.
Let's explain the rules.
First, the five must head to the place that comes to mind after receiving a theme.
Until everyone is able to reach the same destination, the test will continue.
Will they be able to meet each other?
We should know, we've been together for a while now.
Yeah, it's been a long time.
Their time living in Tokyo
Tsukitei
Matsumoto
Hamada
Endo
Tanaka
But right now, Yamasaki is from the countryside.
The countryside? Sorry, but isn't that countryside the place where you came from?
Living in Osaka for the past 3 years
Wait, you're not a resident comedian*?
*A term that originates from Yoshimoto Kogyo's project called "Anata no machi ni sumimasu" [(They will) live in your town],
text
Comedians living in each of the 47 prefectures, hoping to
Resident Comedian
reinvigorate each region with the power of comedy.
Osaka's...
Hey, wait a minute.
Osaka's resident comedian...
I always thought that was the case.
*where they made a comedian or TV personality actually move and live in one of Japan's 47 prefectures.
A resident comedian?
Nobody knows who Metal Luck or Dosaken even are!
Saga Prefecture's
Metal Luck
Yamaguchi Prefecture's
Dosaken
Ah, guess I was wrong. I see.
So if we don't meet each other it won't end?
Yes, that's how it is.
I'd like if they told us what the first place is.
Yeah, they should tell us.
It makes sense.
Just to kinda get an idea.
Yeah.
They could tell us, nobody will say anything.
I see.
Let's get it right the first time.
What will we get?
Everyone, look over here.
Don't say anything.
1, 2...
Speaking of a large parking lot?
Theme
You gotta be kidding.
Isn't this too difficult?
This sort of thing...
Right off the bat we got a hard one.
Wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
This one's hard.
Well, it's fine if we all go to that place.
Right?
Wait.
Let's all just go there.
Yeah.
Kojimachi Nippon TV
Moved to their starting locations
First, in order to prevent them from knowing each other's destinations, they're all placed
in different starting places around Kojimachi's Nippon TV office.
There's at least three places I can think of.
This is pretty difficult so
if I figure out the correct answer, I'll go there
But everyone else...
After all, their way of thinking is really shallow.
Taking that into consideration, that one place is pretty large but...
It's very risky.
Well, considering this type of show,
It's possible that we could get it right the first time.
Well, it is.
Is that fine?
But with this theme...
I don't think it's gonna be a parking lot attached to something else.
I was thinking that Komazawa Park's parking lot was pretty large but
that's Komazawa Park's parking lot, right?
It wouldn't be just a parking lot.
I don't believe that everyone else will think that way.
t
Will everyone be able to meet each other!?
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translator:
Typesetter:
Proofreader:
Jose
Derek
Otviss
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
____________________________________________________________________
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on youtube
(and other sites), individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own, please
go back and support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit.
You can download our episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching our videos!
Speaking of a large parking lot?
Theme
Without using phones, will they be able to meet each other?
First, they all head out towards the large parking lot that they thought of.
rec
Transportation by taxi
The time limit is 30 minutes.
This time, they'll use taxis for transportation.
What will be their destination?
Let's go to Akasaka.
Thinking of the time limit, Matsumoto heads to nearby Akasaka.
From here it should take about 10 minutes.
Or 15 minutes, right?
The time it takes will be just right.
If I wanted to
go all the way to Ueno, 30 minutes wouldn't be enough.
So there's no way that's the place.
Well, the term "large" is subjective.
It you asked me if it was large, I would say it is.
It's large, Komazawa Park's parking lot.
I think we've recorded there at least once before, the parking lot's size should still be in everyone's mind.
The size of everyone's range of activity.
That's probably the most important factor, really important.
Endo is using the expressway while traveling.
Where exactly is he heading?
At the same time, Hosei is...
Please take me to Yoyogi Park's parking lot.
That's the only place I could think about.
The first one that came to mind?
Yeah.
Are there other large parking lots...?
Well, I don't know but...
I don't think there are any other..
large parking lots.
Matsumoto reaches his destination
It's been 10 minutes since the start.
Matsumoto is the first to reach his destination.
This is it.
Akasaka Parking Center.
You can't tell from outside, but this is actually pretty big.
Hamada has to know this place for sure, he always comes for that.*
*It's a love hotel
Got permission to record here
We go inside the parking lot to check its size.
Look over here, once we turn this corner...
I think it's gonna be pretty big.
Look at this place, and there's also a floor below.
In the middle of the city, in Akasaka, there's really
no other place but here.
How many cars do you think it can fit?
It's so large.
Let's ask here.
Excuse me.
Can we... ah, hello.
There's another floor below, right?
Yes, there's another below.
How many cars can park when it's full?
About 150.
One hundred... one hundred and fifty cars.
redf
Parking: About 150 cars
It's pretty impressive to have that many in the middle of the city, isn't it? Especially here in Akasaka.
You could even say that this is the largest parking lot in this area.
Well, I don't think it's a large number of cars.
Right? Thank you.
And there you have it.
There you go.
Seriously, it's this place for sure.
I still think the
largest parking lots are those attached to a park.
But I don't believe that way of thinking is right.
Contrary to Tanaka's belief, Hosei is heading towards Yoyogi Park's parking lot.
Hey, driver.
Speaking of a large parking lot, which
place do you think about?
It'd say it would be Yoyogi Park, wouldn't it?
This is very reassuring. It's really this place, the large parking lot.
Yes it is.
Right?
Great.
Matsumoto just keeps waiting for the others.
If they still aren't here,
I don't think they'll come anytime soon.
They're not coming, are they?
'Cause they're idiots.
If they were...
already there,
"What took you so long?"
They would say something like that.
It would be great if I met them.
Hamada arrives at his destination
10 minutes after Matsumoto's arrival,
Hamada arrives at Komazawa Park's parking lot.
This place is big, right?
Look, if you want a large parking lot...
It would be this place.
Are you serious!? Is nobody going to show up?
Really?
You know, there was another parking lot that I was thinking about.
It should be coming up. It's by the next traffic light.
Right.
The parking lot to the right.
That one.
Here.
Yes.
This one's pretty big, isn't it?
It's big.
This one.
It's pretty big but...
I don't think everyone else would've thought about this one.
I thought at least one of them would come here.
That's why I told you they're all a bunch of idiots.
They're all idiots.
They've gone through here before and I'm sure they know this place.
But they must think that
only five cars fit in there.
'Cause they're idiots.
They're all a bunch of idiots.
Tanaka arrives at his destination
Another 5 minutes later,
Tanaka arrives at his destination.
Alright, please.
Please be there.
I know it. It's here.
Are you sure?
Yeah, there's no mistake.
It's this place.
They're not here...
They're not here.
Why don't you look inside?
Yeah, they might be in here.
Yeah.
Got permission to record here
Look!
This place is really large!
Look! It's amazing, right?
All that's left is to wait for them to get here.
Yeah.
No way, this is the worst.
Nobody came here.
Where the hell is everyone?
Matsumoto contacts the others to confirm their locations.
Hello?
Hello!
Hello.
Good job.
Hey, nobody... nobody came here.
This is Endo, there's nobody here either.
Endo, where are you?
Right now, I'm in Odaiba's...
There it is!
What?
Land floating on the sea doesn't count, Endo!
Let me explain.
No! No! No! No! No! It wasn't there in the first place so...
The parking lot here...
It's obviously going to be huge. I really hate you for going to Odaiba.
You're kidding?
Odaiba - Aomi Parking Lot
Parking: 598 cars
There's space for 598 cars.
Of course there is! It's land floating in the ocean, you idiot.
That's no good, no good.
Tanaka, where are you, Tanaka?
Well, Tanaka is at... I'm at Daikanyama.
Daikanyama?
The one by Hachiman street. The facade looks like a Japanese house.
Ah, the one with the gate.
That's gotta be small, right?
It's not small, it fits 44 cars!
That's small!
Daikanyama Parking Lot
Parking: 44 cars
44 cars? Are you trying to be funny?
Hey, hey, hey, are you serious?
You have to consider the place, besides, we've recorded here before.
Yama-chan.
Yes.
Yama-chan, where are you?
I'm in a pretty memorable place for all of us.
We've recorded here often, Yoyogi Park.
Ah, Yoyogi Park...
A park's parking lot doesn't really count.
How many cars can park at Yoyogi Park?
85 cars.
Yoyogi Park Parking Lot
Parking: 85 cars
85 cars?
85 cars.
Hamada, where are you?
We both almost had the same idea, I'm in Komazawa Park's parking lot.
I'm telling you that an "attached parking lot" doesn't count.
Yeah, it has space for 225 cars.
Komazawa Park Parking Lot
Parking: 225 cars
That's too far away.
No, it's way too far.
I mean, it's really far from Kojimachi.
And you, Matsumoto?
You know...
Yes.
You have to think about the distance.
I started a bit away from Kojimachi.
Yes.
Right.
Yeah.
It's Akasaka, Akasaka.
Akasaka...
Akasaka?
The one near TBS in Akasaka.
There's a love hotel, right? There's a parking lot right in front of it.
It has space for 150 cars!
Do you understand?
Akasaka Parking Center
Parking: 150 cars
If there's a parking lot that can fit 150 cars in Akasaka...
That'd be it!
Well, in this first try we all ended up in different places. It was obvious.
Yeah, we're all over the place.
It's a bit sad that there wasn't even one pair.
In the next one...
Yes, yes, yes.
In the next one, let's do our best to get together.
Yes.
Let's meet each other.
Please.
Tanaka is awful.
He went to a parking lot with 44 spaces.
You can find those anywhere.
What the hell is he thinking?
So, Hosei went to
Yoyogi Park...
He decided to go
with that "attached to something" pattern.
That way of thinking is wrong, in the first place.
Seems like Yama-chan and I had the right idea.
This is the next one.
Right.
Will this separate us again?
Speaking of a big billboard?
Theme
This is just... how am I supposed to figure this out?
A big billboard, huh?
Is there one?
No, this is...
This depends on the person.
Of course.
Well, yeah.
There's only one place
where I think, "Man, that one's big...",
so let's go there.
I see.
I could meet someone there.
The one near Sun Music.
Yes.
The Onishi Lion billboard that's near Sun Music.
I always see it.
Let's go. That's it.
Speaking of a big billboard?
Theme
Next, they must head towards to the big billboard they think of, starting from where they are.
Was I really that wrong with the parking lot? I was sure that I would find someone in Odaiba.
I guess everyone has their own way of thinking.
Endo went all the way to Odaiba.
I thought of going to Odaiba too, but then I realized it was too far.
That's why I decided against going to Odaiba.
But yeah,
this time
Cocorico are really awful.
Aren't they?
Yeah.
Tanaka, the parking lot you chose was the one with the least spaces by far.
Yeah, the parking spaces.
For a "genuine" parking lot, it was large, wasn't it?
I thought it was pretty large.
We were way off with the parking lots.
I wonder,
will we be able to meet?
Endo enters the metropolitan area while traveling on the expressway.
There are a lot of billboards.
There's Yuukorin's.
Yeah, there's that one, it was...
What was it?
Car Seven.
It's Car Seven.
I think it's there.
Over there.
By the corner.
This one, look. Car Seven.
Car Seven's...
I always see Yuukorin's Car Seven. It's big too.
Yes, this one's big.
It's big but it's on the expressway.
It might be difficult for this type of challenge.
It's hard to meet here.
Yeah, you probably can't see it from below.
Matsumoto arrives near his destination
And Matsumoto arrives near the vicinity of his destination.
There it is.
I can see it now. Look at it.
Onishi Lion.
This one's huge.
There's no way you can miss seeing Onishi Lion.
Look, it's amazing, isn't it? It's big.
Every time I pass through here I see Onishi Lion.
It's gotta be this one, right?
Onishi Lion.
I can only think of Onishi Lion when I go through here.
I read the "Don't worry" and then I get worried.
This billboard has been up there for a long time.
Radio Nippon.
I knew it was Onishi Lion because he always wears that, but I didn't know what it was about.
Is there anybody here?
There! Who's that? Yamasaki?
Yes, he's here!
There he is.
Alright!
That's Tsukitei, isn't it? Alright!
Of course it was this one, there are a lot of big billboards but
this billboard is really one of a kind.
It would be great if one more person
came here, but for now...
It had to be this one, right?
Of course!
I knew it was gonna be this one.
Ah, I'm so glad!
That's what I was saying,
Matsumoto and Hosei
join up
It couldn't be a billboard with a new musician's album.
Right, right.
There's a lot like that in Shinjuku and Shibuya but...
Yeah.
This is it.
This has been Onishi Lion forever.
Yeah, it's always been Onishi Lion.
Really.
You see it with its "Don't worry~"
Telling you everything's alright.
It does say "Don't worry~", but
This one for sure.
You can always remember it.
I do remember it.
I think, "Ah, it's Onishi Lion!".
That aside, the dumb thing about the others...
is that they're coming from really far away.
Like from Odaiba.
Yeah, there's an idiot who went to Odaiba.
Of course.
Going to Komazawa was dumb too.
They're not thinking about the next one.
Not thinking at all.
Right?
When I heard about Tanaka's 44 car parking...
You know,
I actually got scared.
It's scary, right?
I mean, going to a 44 car parking lot thinking it's large.
40 something...
That's what it makes you feel.
I got a bit
scared of him.
Is that it, Tanaka?
Tanaka arrives near his destination
Yes, yes, that's it.
That one?
Yes, that one.
That, that, that!
Isn't it hu...
Isn't it huge?
Look!
It's huge.
It was actually this big.
Was it actually this big?
This might even be
bigger than I thought.
Now I'm scared of Cocorico.
Is this duo called Cocorico okay? One of them went all the way to Odaiba.
Odaiba was never an option.
If you think about having to go to the next place, Odaiba was out of the question.
Right.
Endo arrives at his destination
This one's big.
This one, right?
Besides, there's two of them.
Really.
There's the one in the front...
Two of them.
See?
And the one on top.
Is there anyone here?
There's no one here. No way.
You gotta be kidding me.
This billboard is really big.
This is a really big billboard.
Surrounded by scaffolding.
This is what a big billboard looks like.
Hanada Masaru... Why aren't they here?
I mean, this is a huge billboard, seriously.
Is this no good?
Hamada arrives at his destination
And finally, Hamada arrives at his destination.
Here you go, see?
If you're talking about a big billboard, it has to be APA Hotel's with the picture of their president.
Could you even think of another big billboard?
There's no place more famous than here.
Are you kidding me? Seriously?
Isn't this too strange?
Really, where are they?
I mean, seriously...
Seriously...
Why aren't they here?
Hello.
Hello!
Hello?
Yamasaki and I,
have already met.
We're together now.
You met Yama-chan.
We're together now and we're enjoying each other.
Matsumoto and Hosei, you came across each other?
Really?
It was obvious.
Where are you guys?
Where are you?
Where?
We're in Yotsuya.
Yotsuya!?
On Yotsuya's 4th District.
On the building that was the former Sun Music office.
Ah, that one's big.
There's a billboard with Onishi Lion, right?
Yotsuya's 4th District Onishi Lion Billboard
Hamada, where are you?
Ah, I'm in Akasaka.
Akasaka?
Akasaka.
APA Hotel's billboard with the president.
Akasaka APA Hotel's President Billboard
There's a billboard with the president?
Was there a billboard like that?
I think that one's a bit unreasonable.
Well, I'm in
South Aoyama's 3rd District Hanada Masaru Billboard
South Aoyama's 3rd District. In front of Bell Commons.
South Aoyama...
The big billboard with the surrounding scaffolding, showing Hanada.
I can understand going there.
I'm right below it.
And Tanaka?
Tanaka is at Omotesando,
Omotesando
Samantha Thavasa Billboard.
right below the Samantha Thavasa billboard.
What the hell are you doing at a Samantha Thavasa billboard?
Wait, isn't that just a regular billboard?
It's freaking huge!
Don't say that, it's really big.
But right now, we're
closer than we were before.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah.
We're all close to each other, so we'll meet.
Probably.
I wonder if the rest of us will meet?
I want to meet you guys.
It's cold.
Let's meet at the next one, I want to see you.
Let's meet at the next one.
The next one.
Yes, let's do it.
But the right place was here.
I'm telling you this is the biggest one, the right answer.
So now they're both gonna work together?
Yes.
I see.
Let's see what's next.
This is the next one.
Alright, let's go.
1, 2, go.
Speaking of a frequent Gaki recording location?
Theme
Let's think about this one. Because now we can both think about it.
This one's actually really hard.
Because there are actually a lot, of answers.
I'm a bit intrigued by the "frequent" part.
Even if you say it's a frequent location...
t
Will everyone be able to meet each other!?
Will everyone be able to meet each other?
Next week, the second part of "Meeting each other without phones"!
Next Week
"Meeting each other without phones"! Second Part
Speaking of a frequent Gaki recording location?
We always go all over the place.
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
From 27 years of history with this show,
t
Which memorable recording location will they choose!?
which memorable recording location will they choose?
That's gotta be small, right?
It's not small, it fits 44 cars!
That's small!