The Future Century
Squadron: The Five Rangai!
I don't regret breaking with him.
But I feel lonely on weekends.
Hey, you have me.
Yes.
Dokuro-san.
- Evening.
I've just planted rice.
You have rice field?
- Yeah.
It's hard work.
By the way, Ryoko-chan.
Live UFO(music event), which
starred you was horrible. - Yeah.
The hell with Komuro
(a musician, her producer). He sucks.
I didn't really mean that.
- It sounded you really mean that.
Heeelp!
Stop!
Tangled Boobs!
Cursed Boobs!
Boobs that got run over!
Crispy Fried Boobs!
Sushi Boobs!
Our powers combined!
New Boob 5
Boob, boob, boob...
Ladies, run. Now.
1, 2, 3, 4, boob, boob, boob...
Stop!
Cut it!
You aren't synchronized.
What's this crap?
I have a low back pain.
What the hell is that?
Tell me.
- Cursed Boobs.
That's not what I'm asking.
You always make me sick!
I think this is my best work.
You guys are the same.
- The same?
We are the same
in good way?
You think that's funny?
It hurt my hip.
I don't give a damn.
1, 2, 3, 4, boob, boob, boob...
We did as we are told...
- I did tell you. But not in this way!
Shut up!
Are you OK, Sushi Boobs?
We thought you just didn't like
our boobs. Not boobs in general.
I didn't like it because
you didn't look like heroes.
Why do we need boobs!
Why are you sticking to it!
We don't need boobs?
Off course not!
What the hell is this!
Crispy Fried Bo...
My hip...
He broke Crispy hip!
You just never get it.
We thought it's good...
- Why boobs!
My boob!
Damn it!
You don't get me fight you.
Never.
I think we're fighting now.
You know this is not
what I mean by "unite"!
You are jealous because
you don't have it, aren't you?
You're supposed to be heroes
for God's sake!
What's wrong with Sushi Boobs?
- You're really pissing me off now.
How many times
do I have to tell you!
Hey!
What are you laughing at?
I... I feel you're going to
hurt me.
How many times!
- We are only trying...
This is what you get
for not listening to what I said!
You are terrifying me!
- You are so violent today.
I'll give you one last chance.
We have to give up boobs?
- Off course, you idiots!
I told them we shouldn't do
boob thing. But they insisted.
Yes, he insisted. He said
he came up with great idea for it.
Who "he"?
- Matsumoto.
No. He's lying.
So it's you, huh?
- No. It's not me.
I take this off.
You double-faced skunk!
You pathetic liar!
You designed whole thing!
You decided who play what.
You're the one who
come up with this.
But when I saw the slap...
You have to appeal to kids.
I was doing this for foreigners.
I can see.
You though I'll but this crap?
Please.
You are pathetic.
You are disgusting.
You make me sick.
- What?
Don't you have any pride ?
Please. Take this.
I'll excuse myself. I won't let you
down next time. - You shouldn't.
You better do it right
next time. - OK.
I'll punch you in the face
if you don't.
He's really terrifying me.
I'm sorry about this.
- Ouch! - Ouch!
What are you doing!
You skunk!
I couldn't help it.
I adore you.
We'll think hard.
- Goodbye.
If you do this crap one
more time. - I won't.
I'm really sorry.
You take this.
That's an absolute humiliation.
I gave you my underwear
and you throw it in my face.
Just go.
Think it over!
The Future Century Squadron: The Five Rangai!   To be con't.