GAKIFILES SUBS
www.echie7.blogspot.com
Facebook: GakiFiles Subs
This is Tsukimura, yes...
2014 Yoshimoto Head Office
Understood. I'll be there shortly.
Tsukimura Kacho...
Yes, what?
Um, 2 strange old men are here.
2 old men?
- Yes.
Um, what was it.. Downtown.. or something like that
It's been a while, huh?
We were just passing by and thought we'd stop in.
Nearby.
It's been a while.
- Can we sit?
Yes.
It's been awhile since our last visit.
Hamada-san?
Uh-uh.
Matsumoto-san.
You've changed quite a lot.
Have we? No, we haven't changed at all.
We're fine.
- Is that so?
We are STILL very fine.
By the way...
Shall I say it?
Well...Um...
We again..well, we haven't worked for a while..., but we are going to start again.
Yes.
So you've been stopping but
No need to do so anymore.
Stopping what?
Work for us that Yoshimoto has been kindly suspending...
will be... um...
accepted.
- Please feel free.
Yes.
Has someone been suspending your work?
Well...
That's right.
- Certainly.
Has someone? I had no idea.
I'm sorry.
We understand.
- You thought it was strange, right?
That's fine, now that you know it.
Is that so?
- Just to let you know.
I understand it.
What shall we start with?
What work shall we start with?
Hey, I heard he is now
a Kacho (Section Chief).
How many years ago was it? How many years ago did you start working here?
Let me see, it's been 20 years.
20 years?
I recall when you appeared in front of us for the first time.
You were like this, huh?
That's too small!
See?
My arm is not rusty yet.
* This means "Technique is not rusty" in Japanese
Not only his. Neither is mine.
That's wrong!
See.
See? We Still got it.
Let me see...
TV shows and stages are full for the time being.
We can't ask for TV shows so suddenly.
Yes.
Stage work should be more flexible.
Yeah.
Right?
Yes...
But stages are yet...
What about customers? I assume you
aren't getting a lot of customers lately.
- Are they satisfied?
Customers? Yes, we have a lot.
Lots of customers.
A lot?
Yes. A lot.
The 2nd floor is full too?
Yes, sure.
The 2nd floor is full too.
How much.. how much do you charge!?
We charge 3,500 yen now.
3,500 yen? And seats are full?
- Yes they are full.
The 2nd floor too?
- Yes.
The 2nd floor is full too.
Yes.
I bet no more standing fans?
Like I said...
Whe had a lot in our times, right?
- Yes, I heard about that. It's still the same.
In front?
- Yes.
Like this?
It's the same.
Hama-chan, how many were there back then?
Let me think... there were...
600 or something?
- 400 million?
So now ticket costs 3,000 something?
So cheap. It wasn't that cheap in our times, huh?
No no no...
3,500 yen now.
How much was it?
About 400 million yen.
That's too much!
My shoulder is so light.
First of all let us start with a sideshow act.
That sounds good.
We didn't like it back then.
- Yes, I've heart that.
Well... yeah.
Well well well.
Of course we don't go for silly ones.
Yes, yes.
No, we don't.
- No.
We can't lower ourselves.
But still, there should be something.
This one...
What is it?
Let me see.
Let's hear it just in case.
This?
- Yes.
I know it wont be good but.
- Just say it, you never know.
Just say it.
This sideshow act is at a supermarket.
Supermaket?
Yes.
What do you do?
Selling products of a small company at a cart
in Manzai style. That's what they want you to do.
Not bad.
We should do that kind of work.
Not bad?
- Nope.
It's just like a joke.
- Yeah.
Of course we won't take it seriously,
That's foolish.
- Yes.
We should just do it.
Well but...
Um...what to say, the pay..
We can't take it if it's too cheap.
No, no we can't.
Fans won't be happy.
Uh... so this is no good then.
But how much is it just in case.
This is...
That's OK. Just in case.
That's OK.
You'll receive 10,000 yen per one person.
Not bad.
- Not bad.
10,000 yen?
You think it's OK? Oh, is that so?
- No no no that's not too bad.
Don't worry.
- OK.
It's not bad, it'll be fun like a joke.
A joke?
- Of course.
A pro that goes the opposite way.
You're clever.
Purposely? OK, I understand.
Excuse me, I have to leave for a meeting.
I don't have my wallet with me!
Did I drop it!?
Oh, yeah. I saw you drop it.
What?
Did you see it?
- Yes.
Shucks! I dropped it.
I don't have mine either.
Oh, both of you don't have?
I'm sorry but can we...
Oh yes...
We can't return home.
- No..
Don't take it in a wrong way.
- No, I don't.
So I'm sorry but this will only be enough to pay
your travel expense, but 5,000 yen each.
That's...
Yes?
This is...
You can't return home?
A matured man would...
So.
10,000 yen each. Should be fine.
Umm...
I only have 22,000 yen...32,000 yen left in my wallet.
I only had like 50,000 yen with me.
I'm sorry. Just borrowing.
OK?
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
I don't have a penny now.
It's just a joke.
- Is it so?
Just joking.
- No no no.
Are you mad? Did we offend you?
- No, I'm not. No.
It seems like we came to borrow money.
Sorry.
OK then.
I feel bad, shall I come back tomorrow to repay?
Well, I'll be in Tokyo so I won't be here at the main office.
Are you going?
- Yes.
Even if you come...
- Why are you going there?
I'm visiting Fuji TV.
So then, shall we...go together?
Huh? What?
Can you call?
What for?
To book a hotel room.
Shinpuri (Shinagawa Prince Hotel) is fine.
Ah...ah...
Shinpuri and tickets...
I don't have it here.
Tickets..
- In my bag...
I have them in my bag.
- Just do it now.
Just call.
Just call. Hurry up.
- But actually I won't be staying  there over night.
You can come back. We'll be staying there.
Just call.
I can't...
YOU GUYS ARE WASHED UP COMEDIANS!
Don't make me say it.
To be continued