http://zurui.blogspot.com
Translations: Zurui
Ume-chan
Good morning
Mornin'
Oh, good morning
Imada-kun
Yes?
Um.. what happened.. your kids
They returned, thank you for asking
That's great
It was a neighborhood dog
Really?
Yeah
It was good
Well..
What's wrong? You look gloomy
No..Just my second son
What happened?
He was taken away by a crow
I couldn't help because they were in the sky...
Where do you live?
Around Tondabayashi
By the way I have something to tell you
Nope
Well..I'm sorry about the last time
Huh?
Um...
I'm mad
I know
I think you have every right to be mad
But this time I'm really confident
Are you sure?
How do you say it... we match
Really?
That's the best thing
Can he talk?
He is good at it
Are you sure?
Actually, he's here today
You brought him right?
Yes I did... but I really want you to see our performance
Are you really sure?
Yes
Sorry, everyone can you watch this
Thank you
Ume-chan!
This is Ume-chan
Huh?
Turn that off
What?
Turn it off
Turn it off?
Give me 1000 yen
Shut up... stop it
Hey Ume-chan
Introduce yourself
This is Hamada-san
Is he on TV?
Of course
I don't watch TV
I don't watch TV, so I don't know him
Is this him?
Yes, he is my partner
What's your name?
Ume-chan
Ume-chan..?
How old are you?
I don't know, I don't remember
Probably about 38 or so?
Do you have any family?
I wonder what they do now... but I'm sure they hate me
I may have to run away
I just have to tell some jokes, right?
Not really jokes... let's do our performance we practiced
Yes, do it
I'm Ko-chan
Eh..I'm Ume-chan
We are Yokojima..
Typhoon
OK then, let us start...it's getting warmer..and in this
season, what we young people want is girlfriend
Girlfriend? Do you want?
Of course I want
I don't really want one
Sure?
Well I want one
You do right?
Which is it!
I want to have a date
Oh date! I want to go to an amusement park
I don't care for it
You don't care for it?
I'm going tomorrow though
Are you going tomorrow..? So which!
Which is it?
As for an amusement park, there is a Ferris wheel that goes around
I don't care for Ferris wheel
Are you sure?
- Yea
I don't like that kind
Are you sure? I like it!
I'm going to ride on it though
The view from the top must be great
Yea, I think so
You can see a lot
I don't care for views
Are you sure?
I'll watch it though
I also like roller coasters
When you ride on a roller coaster,
Everyone..
Roller coaster is scary but fun, isn't it?
It's scary
But it's also fun
End it...That's it
What are you doing?
Let me see
What?
Let me see what you took from me
You took my watch, right?
No I didn't
Show me... check there
Check his pocker
Got it right?
I can hear it
There it is
What are you doing?
Hey come here
Come here... what were you doing during your performance?
You got more to show right?
Nothing more
You saw it right?
You did right?
You did right!
- WHAT!
You saw it right
You saw it right?
He took it right
He did right
What?
Did you put it on there?
No
It wasn't there, did you put it there?
No no no..it was there all this time
He put it there right?
Shall we go to the police?
Eh
Let's go to the police
What?
I don't understand
No..not that...it was all performance
Performance
Well... Koji-kun and I were planning on take stuff from
the audience and then give it back at the end
Is it true?
Or is he lying?
Yes he is
You took my money right?
Hey!
Damn you!
It doesn't make sense
Get him
What you are saying does not make any sense
Ouch
OUCH!
Hey you!
I have to apologize
Call the police...Go!
Forgive me already!
What the hell
Are you crazy?
Come here
What?
Come here!
Hey what kind of attitude is that?
I'm going home! I'm going home!
I'm going!
Get away!
Shut up
Give me back my radio!
Everyone, I'm sorry