Visit us for more Gaki no Tsukai - www.GakiFiles.blogspot.com
Well, Matsumoto-san.
-Yes.
The last time, we tricked Imada with the Harisame soup.
Yeah we did, that was...
the summer 2 years ago.
He was so happy he was going to buy a Ferrari.
After he was kind of depressed.
-When he found out it was a prank.
Well, it's been 2 years.
Today, we'll be tricking everyone.
Not only one.
-Yes, everyone.
It's everyone.
The prank.
The person behind this is.
GAKIFILES SUBS
Osaki Hiroshi from Yoshimoto Kogyo.
Trickster
Osaki Hiroshi - Producer
(Yoshimoto Kogyo)
I'm not a trickster, I'm just doing what they told me to do.
So you rank under Okamoto?
-Yes, I do.
I'm just a peon.
Anyway, we're going to be in the room together.
Osaki will come and talk to us.
He'll come out.
Because it's rare to see him.
-Yes.
He will ask to speak to us privately.
The 3 of us will talk in the back.
Then we start fighting.
We can show you now, what will happen.
Fuji TV - 6th Dressing Room
Team Fight Members Waiting For The Rehearsal
I don't eat this stuff.
Isn't it weird.
Hamada Appears As Usual
5 Minutes Later Mr. Osaki Appears
Hello.
We ate already.
Oh, we have sushi.
Let's eat.
I shall partake.
10 minutes Later Matsumoto
Appears and Looks Sleepy
Hello.
Osaki Starts The Prank
Can I talk to you for a few minutes.
What's going on?
The 3 Of Them Enter The Back Room
Hey Okamoto!  Where's my oolong tea?
Okamoto!
-Yes!
I'm sorry.
I told you about this before!
Yes, I'm sorry.
-I told you right?
Hamada also said that he doesn't want to do it.
Hamada didn't mention anything about it.
I didn't say anything.
What ever.
Masterful Performance
Don't have that kind of attitude.
It's not like that...
I doesn't matter, I just want to quit!
Never mind, cut it out.
Recently, Osaki explanations aren't making sense.
Why Is Imada Brushing His Teeth!?
I'm not saying anything weird, it's normal.
-Not true.
I don't like it.
-What?
Masterful Performance
It's hard to say, but it's different.
Anyway, just sit down.
-Never mind.
Sit down!
What!
Masterful Performance
Just listen.
Sit down!
-Am I the bad person?
A Heavy Atmosphere Fills The Dressing Room!!
I didn't say who's bad.
What!
-Anyway, just listen.
I just don't want to do it!
Masterful Performance
You can't just say that, you bastard!
It's really, never mind.
Stop that attitude!
-What!
What!
It's not what, just sit down!
It's doesn't matter!
-Just sit down!  Damn it!
I don't want to!
Stop that!  Stop!
What asshole!
What!
What bastard!
That's enough, OK.
Stop.  What is that!
What bastard!
What!
You bastard!
OK, Hama-chan wins!
No laughter at all!
You're supposed to be laughing.
Excuse me, but we can't laugh.
Not a laughing matter.
Sorry but we were fighting over this.
We did it so many times, that's why I didn't want to sit on the horse.
He said "sit down" so many times..
He was saying it from 3 months ago.
I was listening but Hamada wasn't.
I wanted 3 people fighting.
The look on Imada's face...
it was terrible.
In all these years, it's the first time seeing that face.
I thought Osaki had a bloody jacket on!
It's really blood, I thought.
I was really shocked.
I was going to change my pants too.
I thought I heard someone say "my thumb is hurt so I'm losing".
Stupid.
Why does Imada have tears.
Imada had such a terrible face.
He has watery eyes.
He's crying.
Imada is crying.
He's really crying!
Why?
He's crying!
Imada... Imada!
Imada, it's a prank.  Prank!
Imada, it's a prank!
Got it?
Imada, it's just a prank.
It was perfect!
Imada...
Imada, it's just a prank.
No, I understand his feelings.
You're too mean.
Didn't you go too far?
Apologize.
Hurry and apologize.
I'm sorry Imada.
We're sorry.
We're the ones fighting, why do we have to apologize to him?
You OK?
Usually he would be way over there.
When I saw him on the monitor,
he was brushing his teeth to try and peek inside the room.
That Imada.
Hey Imada...
everything is not perfect in life.
This is taking too long.
You're OK right?
I really thought Gottsu ee Kanji was finished.
I thought, "I'll just go home"
Like, what now.
The show is over?
-It's over.
What now?
You guys didn't even notice it was sugar glass?
-No we didn't.
3 guys with 3 different personalties all with hot tempers.
Nobody could stop you.
Let's ask Imada what he thought.
He cried!
Well...
with everything put together...
I guess it went really well.
It made me cry.
You sound nasally.
But really...
What did you think?
I just thought, I had to stop you guys all by myself.
Thank goodness though.
Yeah, thank goodness.
You guys were very good.
That was scary.
I just couldn't take it as a joke.
The CCD is amazing.
I thought when we broke through the glass, everyone was going to laugh.
I saw Imada, I thought what kind of face is that.
I kind of thought...
our timing was off.
-Yeah.
It was his idea from the start, evil person.
Be strong!
-Machan team...
Did you stop crying?
Please don't mention that!
We won't cut that part out.
-Please cut it out.
He was bawling earlier.
What he was crying?
The tears were just flowing.
Please don't air this.
We wont cut it out.
Please cut it out.
I'll pay you to cut it out.
I'll pay you.
We have enough money.
Such sarcasm.