Translation: SSSI
www.zurui.blogspot.com
Facebook: GakiFiles Subs
Kurapi
Hey Kurapi...
Yes?
I'm hungry, what do you want to eat?
Ryoko-chan, what do you want to eat?
I don't know.
Kurapi...
doesn't know either!
Kurapi!
What are you doing here?
You said you had to work today.
Hey, Kurapi, what's with this woman?
What's with THIS woman?
I'm Kurapi's girlfriend.
Whad did you just say?!
So..
Are you two-timing me?
No..
Huh?!
Two-timing?
- I can't believe it!
You have a beautiful girlfriend like me.
Why do you have to date a woman like this?
What do you mean?
What do you..
Never mind.
I'll give you to this woman, since you are the worst man!
I'll give him to you since he is so ugly!
What are you saying?
He doesn't even think he is ugly!
He's always like
"I'm tired."
"My head hurts."
"My stomach hurts."
You work only 10 days a month!
Don't even pretend like you are sick!
You purchased a cellphone.
No one even calls you!
You can have him!
Your face and style are old fashioned!
I don't need him!
Judgment.
I did it!
Take him!
I don't need him!
I don't!
You guys are rude!
What's with the noise!
Stand up, morons!
I'm crying for Kurano.
You said, "He only works 10 days a month."
I'm offended!
How do you know?
Okamoto-san told me earlier.
You were so excited that you won!
What about my mouth...
Your mouth is fine, just rinse it out well.