The Wild Kingdom
Professor.
Exactly what is this the pupa of?
Ah, this.
It inhabits the island of Madagascar in the African continent.
It's called the bald-monkey fly.
The scientific name for it is
"Papillion Madagascar Regina".
This is very precious footage
we are taking here.
This is the first time anyone has ever
successfully caught a hatching on camera.
Ah, it's starting to move.
Oh, you're right.
This fake pupa...
Yes?
It cost$8,000.
Is it finished?
Yes!
The Wild Kingdom II
Professor.
Exactly what is this the pupa of?
Ah, this...
It inhabits the island of
Borneo in Indonesia.
It is called the black-cross white butterfly.
This is very precious footage
we are taking here.
This is the first time anyone has ever
successfully caught a hatching on camera
Ah, it's beginning to move.
Yes, it has!
The scientific name for this is...
"Shiba dog"
I see.
How much did this cost?
This was...
...$8,000.
$8,000?
We used it twice.