facebook.com/shionnotsukai
HIGHSCHOOL
SCARY STORY
What a relief
Ya spyin' on us?
Ya know, I'm the type to stay behind
He's peepin'!
Got me, dude
Hey, hey!
Dontcha think it stinks?
Yeah, it stinks!
He's doin' it!
For real?
- You serious?
Come on man, taking a dump at school...
It stinks, dude!
Come on man!
Don't take a shit at school, man!
UNBABA!!
note: pun on "unko" and "baba" (both "poop")
Who made my toilet stall dirty?!
note: on the box: "unbaba"
That hurt
It's poop!
People always keep saying stuff like
"You could be lucky or unlucky"
But I just realized that's true
After looking at you punks!
Why did he skip that one?
No idea
"Fate" is not something you
wait, is something you grasp!
note: pun - "un" is both "fate" and "poop"
This--
Can we stop this?
This is harsh
This is painful
Painful...
- Dangerous too
- And scary
It's just... sad
Alright, let's stop this
Don't worry, you gave your best
Isn't that right?
- Yes, it is
- He gave his best
- He did good
Thank you
I tried to say something till the end, but...
You reached your limit?
He reached it
What if next week someone else does it?
That thing?
No one wants to, after looking at you!
You said that yourself
Higashino
- Unbaba, next week
- Unbaba next week?!
Yeah, I'm done
You just have to remember this dance
- I just can't---
- Alright, I'll do it
Let's do this
It's painful
- Let's call it a day
- Alright
You did good, man
Don't worry about it
It was clumsy
- Don't worry, it was fun
- Good job, guys!
- See you