Timer: Kannibleklown
Translator: GakiNoSuitGuy
Extra help: Royaltree1204
My First Errand. Cute overload special.
Hakusanrenpou
My First Errand has been on the air for 27 years.
27 years?
We've been all around from the north of Hokkaido down to Okinawa.
It's easy to think we've run out of places, but there are still places to explore.
There are?
Here at Ishikawa prefecture the water is delicious.
The water flows from the snowy mountain tops of Hakusan.
and it is called "the water of life".
It's our first time coming here and
it will be the first errand for someone...
This little girl.
She's wearing sunglasses.
Amazing.
She's too small.
Ao is almost 3 years old.
So cute.
2 years and 11 months?
She's so fashionable.
Ao and her red sunglasses.
The mother is a nursery school teacher.
This is also where Ao is enrolled.
The mother is in her 9th month of pregnancy, so Ao will become a big sister.
- I see.
- An important time.
She keeps asking when he will be born.
And as an experience before becoming
a big sister she will go on an errand.
But she's still 2 years old. Will she be fine?
I got it.
Did you get the stem? We will use it
to make scrambled soup. With tofu.
Ah, I forgot to buy tofu.
I forgot to buy scrambled tofu.
It's an errand.
Scrambled tofu?
At this tofu shop they boil soy milk and make tofu from it.
Scrambled tofu is served before being made firm from weights.
Absolutely tasty.
It's fluffly and delicious.
Can you go buy it?
I can.
By yourself?
I can go by myself.
Seriously?
She can do it?
Scrambled tofu.
Scrambled.
Go and buy one.
Yep.
The tofu is 250 yen. The mother put 500 yen in her wallet.
One more thing.
Also go and visit the shrine.
From the 500 yen she will get her
change and can use it at the shrine.
I see.
Heading off.
Yes, I can.
Can you do it?
Buy tofu and visit the shrine.
She's so reliable.
It's the same route as usual.
Buying scrambled tofu, getting change from the 500 yen and then visiting the shrine where she was told to give one coin.
Off you go.
Off I go.
Amazing.
So amazing.
- She's motivated.
- She's so focused.
She's merely 2 years and 11 months
old and moves with small steps.
Do your best.
Is she not getting lonely?
That's right.
The one who is getting lonely is the
mother who keeps watching her.
Wait, what's wrong?
The shop is straight ahead.
What's wrong?
She crossed.
She did.
Wait, she wants in there?
A shortcut?
The cameramen are chasing her.
They are hurrying after her.
Not as planned
Where is she going?
Actually, this neighborhood is full of houses and there are plenty of secret pathways.
Since she walks around every morning with her grandmother her mother is confident she can find the way.
So she knows what she's doing.
Is she worried?
The shopping part.
What about it worries you?
Since she doesn't have much experience with it, I'm not sure if she can pay properly.
I see.
But she's still heading straight for the shop.
She looks so serious.
She found something.
The house with a chimney blows its smoke.
A house with a chimney?
What's that?
Ah, the ladder. It's used to clear the snow in winter.
I see.
This is an area of the most prominent heavy snow fall.
Around town there are many ways to get rid of the snow.
Amazing.
How smart.
The big crossing. She will arrive
at the shop if she goes left here.
She trots along when crossing. But she went that way. That's not where the shop is.
She should know the way.
They are being played by a 2 year and 11 month old.
Run for it.
Where Ao is heading is...
Where?
The shrine.
She wants to visit the shrine first.
Why is she taking her backpack off?
She's taking out a blue towel.
She's grabbing the shaku.
Remarkable.
This is "the water of life" from the mountain top of Hakusan.
She's scooping it with the shaku.
She knows exactly how to do it.
Grabbing it closely and... perfectly done.
The one most moved by it is the cameraman close by.
After the purification, the stairs lead to the front of the shrine.
For a 2 year and 11 month old each step is a hurdle.
Does she know the rites of visiting a shrine?
Huh, she's taking her backpack off again?
Could it be...
Oh no, she's taking out her wallet.
There's only one 500 yen coin in it which is intended for the tofu.
Wait. Wait.
She's putting it in.
- She put it in.
What will she do?
She's praying with 500 yen worth.
I hope the baby will be big and healthy.
I hope that I will become a big sister.
I love my mother.
Her wishes echoed throughout the shrine.
What will she do about the tofu?
She's leaving the shrine and heading towards the shop.
She has arrived at the scrambled tofu shop with an empty wallet.
What will she do? She doesn't have any money.
She opens the automatic doors.
Welcome to the shop.
The old man who is always there.
What's up?
We didn't have tofu.
Tofu?
The same tofu as usual?
We ran out of the usual tofu.
The usual tofu?
Scrambled tofu.
She remembered.
This one? Which one was it?
This one.
She found the scrambled tofu however...
That will be 250 yen.
I don't have money.
You don't? Could you show me?
Doesn't have money.
You don't have money? What will you do? Without money you can't buy it.
You didn't receive any money?
Yep.
He's trying to get the crew to help out.
Why don't you go back to your mom and... What will you do? You can't buy it without money.
Even if she's asked what she intends to do.
That's right.
Can you go back home and retrieve some money?
Don't wanna.
Can't do it?
Can't do it.
She doesn't want to go home empty-handed.
That's right.
The old guy figures out a solution.
Then...
Go back home.
And get one like these from your mother.
A 500 yen coin. Like the one
she donated at the shrine.
Go back home and get one.
Okay.
I can do it.
Can you do it?
That's amazing.
You are amazing. I will keep the tofu for you.
Haha, can't believe it all came to this.
I couldn't get the tofu.
Because she doesn't have money.
Impossible.
She understands that you have to pay money to get things, but she doesn't understand how change works.
That's right. She's only 2 years old.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
She's still energetic.
You were fast.
Tofu   money   didn't get.
No money.
She couldn't explain it well.
She's only 2 years and 11 months.
Why didn't you have money?
What? What about the scrambled tofu?
No scrambled tofu.
There was.
The scrambled tofu that Aochan loves so much?
For Aochan, this kind of money...
There's so much she wants to convey
but she can't find the words.
The mother tries to figure it out.
Were you told the money isn't enough?
I was told the money wasn't enough.
Where did the money go?
The money disappeared.
Who did you give it to?
Well...
Even if you ask me "who" it's not like I've seen the spirits.
To the shrine. I gave it to the shrine.
You did? So you also rang the bell?
And then clapped your hands?
That's right. She gave the money and all.
I didn't ring the bell at the shrine.
What?
Which is it?
Just like Aochan is saying. She didn't actually ring the bell.
I didn't ring the bell.
What a puzzling conversation it turned into.
The mother thinks of changing her way of asking.
Aochan, which one did you go to first?
That's the one.
Umm.
Ring the bell.
You went to ring the bell first?
That's right.
I see. So that's what it's about.
I finally get it.
This time she's getting 3 100 yen coins.
Please go and get tofu.
Can you do your best once again?
Yes, I can do my best once more.
Alright. Her energy is coming back to her.
Toooooot
She's laughing.
Her fart shows that she's come back to life.
What an amazing character.
He's been waiting with the tofu in the bag.
Do your best old man.
I had money put in.
You did? That's amazing.
The old man is the one who's nervous here.
She brought 300 yen this time. It's fine.
Here's the tofu.
Here you go.
Oh, thank you very much.
But she only put out one coin.
Eh!? Only got one?
One of them was meant for the shrine.
I see.
Please show me.
Oh, there were more.
How great. There were more.
I will take all three.
You really surprised me.
Your change is 50 yen.
Can you take it?
See? This is what's called change.
Please don't drop it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Alright, she bought it.
How great.
I didn't ring the bell.
It's been on her mind that she didn't get to ring it the first time.
Is she going again?
This time she went directly towards the bell.
She's back at the shrine.
I'm home.
I'm home?
Oh, she did it.
Ring ring ring.
Today she's ringing it with all her might.
Alright.
Motheeeer.
Welcome home.
I'm home.
Did you purchase it?
I did. Here you go.
Amazing.
The scrambled tofu she bought
is served in miso soup.
Thank you for the meal.
The father came back during his lunch break.
It's delicious.
Go ahead.
Scrambled.
Did you say "scrambled please"?
Yep.
The taste of scrambled tofu that
you bought yourself is exceptional.
Aochan, you will become a big sister.
Aochan will become a big sister.
That's right. You will be a cherished sister.
Nom nom cherished nom nom.
She even asked the gods for it.
Then 2 months later...
The wish she loudly asked for came true.
- It's great.
- Isn't it great.
Happiness right there.
Can a single clip contain this much happiness?
- Yeah, wasn't it great?
- Yes, it was truly wonderful.
Let us briefly introduce you to our guests
Itou, the archetypical Japanese father
and Suzu the ideal young lady.
and next to her is Kadono Takuzou.
Male actor.
I'm not Kadono Takuzou!
- Thank you for being here.
- What did you think about it?
She's completely cute. From
what she does to what she says.
If the old guy at the tofu shop gave her the tofu and said, "Your mom can pay me later.", we wouldn't have gotten that fart.
That's right.
She's so mature. She even knows the shortcuts.
Father of a 5 year old.
- That's right.
- Thus perplexing the staff.
- And she raises her hand when crossing the street.
- She's much more mature than me.
Now for the next errand. With only a years difference the mission changes completely.
Ishikawa ● Hakusan city
Here we find the talkative girl who is almost 4 year old.
"Isn't the reason she knows many words because she reads so many picture books?" her mother says.
Mio
3 years 9 months
Since she's already 3 and a big sister
she frequents this place often.
Before going to bed she always reads one picture book and they even enact it.
In this bookshelve there is only on book that hasn't been borrowed by the library. A book they've written themselves.
By dad and mom: Thank you Mio.
A picture book from when Mio was born.
So much love.
And now she's showing the newest creation:
Mio's First Errand.
But it's not complete yet. They will
change it after today's errand.
I see.
Can I read a bit for you?
Yep.
See? It says: My first errand.
She's been reading the book before bed for several days to teach her how to go on an errand.
The soon-to-be 4 year old Mio will go on her first errand.
True, today is my first errand.
Give me a mackerel from Ishikawa with its head and guts removed, filleted into two.
If there aren't any?
Sounds complicated.
If there aren't any then dottybacks, sailfin or sandfish and if possible, from Ishikawa.
Not if possible. Definitely, right?
She's buying locally sourced ones.
Amazing.
And if they don't have any then she shouldn't purchase anything.
They only buy fresh laid Yanagihara eggs.
Furthermore... okra.
Okra.
And nameko.
Those two weren't included in the picture book.
She remembers the things in the picture book well but she's still only 3 years old.
You have money here and the loyalty card.
You are even making her use the loyalty card?
It's a simple route along the huge street to get to the shop.
But she needs to get mackerel from Ishikawa prefecture, eggs from Yanagihara, tofu, lotus root, okra, nameko mushrooms.
Even adults would forget.
Be careful. Bye bye.
Heading off.
She picked the straw hat at the shop
because she thought it was cute.
And she likes to walk without socks which she is used to so her mother lets her do it.
I can go on an errand.
It's nice autumn weather which the picture book didn't mention.
Huh!? What's up?
Hello.
The cameraman is surprised that she spoke to him.
All by yourself? You are awesome.
I'm going on an errand.
3 years old.
Only 3 years old?
It's rare to find such a talkative 3 year old.
Amazing.
Do your best.
Since the conversation could go on the camera man moves away.
Mio no longer has anyone to talk to.
Wait... is she going home?
She's running home.
A gust of lonely air hit her.
Oh, what's up?
You didn't draw me a map.
A map? You need a map?
Please put it in.
She doesn't know how to read a map or characters.
She always has to remember.
That's why her memory is so great.
She changed hats. This one is a camouflaged patterned. Ready for battle.
She's adding a smiley face so that
she can know which one is her left.
Okay? Remember to turn left.
I will be here for sure.
She departs with a new map and a smiley face.
Huh? That face. Could it be?
Is she feeling lonely?
Back to the spot where she last turned around.
She won't go.
She can't seem to cross this iron grate.
I'm lonely.
Turning at this corner she will
no longer be able to see her home.
Because she can't see back.
She's 50 meters from her house.
In her mother's book it says:
"It's alright. Do your best!"
And to cross the road.
She couldn't do like it says in the book.
Mommy.
She's walking back crying unlike in the book.
Why are you back?
Did you go shopping?
I feel lonely.
Do your best and go.
Her mother shows her determination.
I asked you, Mio.
I didn't ask anyone else to do it.
It won't be good if you don't go.
"I want to be a better big sister since my little sister was born." is what she said.
Perhaps a bit too optimistic
but she does want to be helpful
is how she wants to be seen by her mom.
Don't come back.
You understand?
She's strict.
Do your best and go.
Off you go.
You will soon be 4 so you can definitely go.
Go forward.
Yep.
"Big sister bye."
I'm lonely but...
She's lonely but.
Do your best.
Go forward.
I'm lonely but I will go.
Even if you are lonely then go.
I want to become a big sister.
Off you go.
Yep.
That's wrong.
Off you go.
Of I go.
Do your best.
The start of a big sisters journey.
Her sigh.
That iron grate.
Here again.
Take a step forward.
This is the borderline.
Left, left.
Yes, left.
Go along the parking lot.
The big sister has finally crossed the iron grate.
This is it.
Wonder if your sister left.
I wonder.
The map for good luck.
If you cry then wipe the tears with your towel.
She's busy.
She's lonely but she will go.
On a day with beautiful cirrocumulus clouds​.
Surrounded by lucious green.
She's walking way over there.
When grandpa came to visit from the countryside, she remembered walking down this road and singing.
The moon, came out out, the moon came out.
Because he's a grandfather.
What an old song.
A yoi yoi.
She has learned this song.
The chimney is so high up there.
Surely the moon will be covered in smoke. Yoi Yoi.
She remembers it completely.
Is she dancing the second chorus?
It's the shop!
While lost in song she's already arrived.
It's right ahead.
Eggs and lotus root.
I must buy a lot.
Her energy is back.
This supermarket is for locally sourced fish and vegetables.
That's nice.
She was asked to get many things.
How much of it will she remember?
She can't read yet.
Can she do it?
Did you give birth to eggs?
Eggs?
Yanagihara eggs.
Amazing, she remembers.
They are here.
There are some?
They are freshly laid today.
Since her birth she's only had these Yanagihara eggs.
It's been a while since Mio has seen them last.
What about other shopping?
I want to buy handaga tofu.
You want hankata tofu?
This tofu has a hard exterior but is soft on the inside. She also got this right.
And then?
Lotus root.
Lotus root?
Her memory is amazing.
She instantly remembers.
Not only does she remember their name...
It's better if they have many internodes.
She's a housewife.
She chooses the one that seems to be high in mineral content.
Is that alright?
Yep.
And then what?
And fish.
In the book:
Good day!
Do you have mackerel from Ishikawa prefecture?
Gut it and remove the heads.
I want 2 fillets, please.
That's hard.
That's what it says. I wonder if she can say it.
Even adults would forget.
Good day.
Do you have mackerel from Ishikawa prefecture?
This one.
Oh you!
Filleted into two, please.
Cut their heads.
Amazing.
Is it okay with just one?
Just one.
One cut into two fillets, right?
Please wait.
Yes.
I'm moved.
She was able to say it with vigor.
She didn't ask them to gut it but
she asked them to fillet it so the guts are already removed.
Is that all?
Only the mackerel.
Only the mackerel. Haha.
Thank you very much.
Please take care.
Thank you.
She even ad libbed a thanks outside of the book.
Only okura and nameko left.
So... Wait...
She went to the cashier.
Alright.
Heave-ho.
It looks like she forgot.
Her mother just added those two.
They were not in the book.
It can't be helped then.
Paying 2000 and receiving 940 yen back.
It's extraordinary that a 3 year old can do all that.
It is. Truly extraordinary.
Drinking cold bancha.
And then she remembers...
Ah...
I want to buy nameko mushrooms.
You need nameko?
She remembered.
I will show you to the nameko.
Let's go together?
Right th..
Mom also...
Ah, I will also buy okura.
She remembered the okura.
She remembered everything.
Small nameko would be better.
Small would be better?
Since there are sizes of nameko.
The big ones are for stir-frying.
But the small ones are good in miso soup.
There are various.
Let's go with this one.
This one?
Yes, these are good with miso soup.
And okura?
Okura is...
This is the last item. Where are they?
They usually can be found here but are sold out.
We don't have anymore today.
Will this do?
While there were eggs...
there were no okura. What a rarity.
That's true. Usually there are okura.
The hat on tight. Job well done.
Marvelous.
A suspicious cloud surrounds the mountain.
She talked with many and purchased a lot. Now she only needs to head home.
What's wrong?
She's dawdling.
My legs hurt.
The book didn't mention that
the groceries would be heavy.
Or that her legs would hurt.
The road along the rice field.
She's not singing the Tanko-bushi song this time.
Do your best.
She's 3. And a big sister.
She struggles between wanting to exert herself and wanting to be treated sweetly like a child.
Her heart is wavering.
I want to help her.
Did she reach her limit?
But wait...
Her tears stopped.
She found something.
What is that? The white thing?
That's bad. She spotted our drone.
She spotted the drone.
Stop right there.
She's looking at it.
It goes up and down.
It took her mind off the heaviness of the bag.
Good evening.
An old lady is picking flowers.
Huh!?
Good evening.
Ah, good evening.
It's not the afternoon yet but the old lady goes along with it.
Which one do you want?
Can I??
I want this one.
Pink and orange?
That's pretty.
Do you want only 2?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thanks to you the tears have stopped.
Your big sister is doing her best.
As soon as she sees the house
she lets out all the tears she held back.
Mommy.
Yes?
Welcome home.
Thank you. What's up?
What's up?
The important words to tell mom...
They didn't have okura.
They didn't have okura?
It was bothering her.
Then let's make tofu and nameko miso soup then.
She wants to be held like a baby.
Mommy. This is a present for you.
Thank you for the present.
You brought me a gift.
I'm happy. I'm happy.
Thanks. Thanks.
That's right. The picture book.
Must complete it.
Mio, tell me how you did it.
I missed you, mom.
Because it was so tough.
If you write it here.
And so, a lot was added to the book.
That she cried from loneliness before departing.
And that she sang Tanko-bushi with joy.
Or that she received flowers.
And much more.
Mom, you've completed a great book.
Well... It's all thanks to me.
She did well.
What a marvelous errand.
It's a top score.
A top score.
Walking aimlessly at first.
Mother of boys of these ages
The she remembered it all and to say thanks.
When she said: "They don't have okura"
She's truly laudable.
I want to go back to those times.
When she asked the shopkeeper
did you give birth to eggs?
That was really funny.
Things not written in the book are bound to happen.
During the errand of the youngest of 3 brothers the shop will be thrown into disarray.
Tochi ● Tochigi City
Here's a house that likes to keep thing neat and tidy.
Time for cleaning.
Inside the house looks like a showroom.
The mother's philosophy is to put everything orderly.
Everything has its place.
Amazing.
The youngest of 3 at 3 years and 9 months, Masashi.
The other two haven't returned from school.
Who wants to help?
Alright then...
There's a place in the storage room that she isn't satisfied with.
There is?
Listen up Mr. Masashi.
Mama wants another of those baskets.
What if there were 3 or 4 of those baskets here?
Yep.
I see. Measuring it so he can purchase the right size.
About this high.
Go and purchase them.
About thi...
That's right.
And adding an errand for the dinner.
For remuneration let's get the expensive bluefin tuna.
Does he understand "remuneration"?
Toro
Toro (the fatty belly meat of the tuna)
Does he understand toro?
For remuneration (as a reward) he will get toro.
On the way back from the fishmonger there is a home center close to home.
He was asked to buy 3 white baskets.
That's difficult.
Please help your mother in cleaning up.
Later.
It was raining until yesterday.
So she gave him rubber boots in case of puddles.
I'm happy.
He was looking forward to going on errand.
So he wanted to.
Usually his brothers are asked to do it.
The third in the row who is expected less of.
He's called cute and treated like a baby.
Masashi dislikes those times.
Closed?
Today is the first time he is being relied on.
The stakes are high, third son.
Do your best.
Did you come by yourself?
Where's your mother?
Welcome.
Home.
Waiting at home?
Aren't you usually with your brothers?
What do you want?
Toro as remuneration, right?
The similar thing as tuna, please.
Tuna and salmon?
Both?
He neither understood remuneration or toro.
Poor thing. It changed.
When the old man heard the word similar he gave him the same thing his mom usually buys.
Will this do?
What about the toro?
The lean tuna meat and salmon. Not exactly renummeration.
That will be 1080 yen.
Ended up being cheaper.
This triumphant face.
What a nice face.
It will do even if it isn't toro.
That's right.
The shop owners are observing.
Eaten together isn't it like Toro anyway?
He looks happy.
With great delight.
He picked something up.
A single leaf.
And now for the 3 white baskets.
He's arrived at the home center.
Going well.
It's so spacious inside. Will he find it?
About 19000 stock units are sold here.
Finding things can be hard even for adults.
Will he get it?
Isn't it faster to ask a store worker?
He should ask: "Where are the wide baskets?"
Welcome.
Ah, it's the store manager.
Pigeons
Pigeon: hato
Heart: ha-to
Basket: hako
The same pigeons.
Hearts?
Baskets for storage.
What did you come to buy?
Pigeon
The same pigeons.
What do you mean by heart?
The same one.
The same one?
Like that one?
Oh no, he shouldn't have brought this.
Pigeon.
Heart.
That's not it.
The store manager...
Pi-geon.
It's not a heart. A basket.
Manager, you don't sell hearts, right!?
Do you want to try and look for it?
Looking for a heart-like thing?
Well, it isn't a heart.
Do you remember what color?
Green.
You came looking for a green thing?
The green leaf is confusing him.
We have green things.
It's not like they have green hearts.
Like this...
It's heart shaped.
They did have it.
It's there!
It looks like that.
They did have such a thing.
It was a green heart, right?
That's wrong.
It's not this?
- That's great.
- Do your best.
We also have green things here.
The store manager is focused on finding green things.
It's not even green.
Green. What about this?
There are so many green things.
Or like this?
That's close!
Nope.
Besides the color
what do you remember?
Nothing.
In spite of being right next to it.
Since I don't know
can you ask your mother and come back?
Yep.
Alright, go and ask and come back.
I will be waiting.
He decides on asking her.
Their house is close by.
Do you understand what he needed?
I couldn't imagine it.
I apologize.
No need.
It's on us. Thanks for being polite.
My apologies.
Even though he managed to buy the tuna he returns dejected.
Mother.
Ma-.
I titn't unterstant.
He makes the same mistake here of pronouncing the k sound as t.
Did you go to the home center?
What did you ask?
Green pigeon.
You said green basket?
And he heart it as heart?
He heard it as heart?
But it's not heart is what I said.
Even if you said it's not heart he didn't understand?
So his mother thought of this...
You explained that this is a green basket, right?
But mama wants white.
That's right. It should be white.
I accidentally said green.
Next time say white.
Try to say basket.
I couldn't say taro (yam).
Try to say ka like in karasu (crow).
Ta as in tarasu.
Crow.
Tarasu why do you cry.
Ta as in tarasu, right?
Thank you very much.
It's ka not ta.
Masashi who can't say ka is kaming back.
The store manager was waiting.
Again the difference between "went" and "ask" is "k".
The manager picked up on it this time.
I went and came back.
You went and asked?
Do your best, manager.
What was it?
If you turn where the slippers are then it should be there.
Turning where the slippers are?
The slippers are over there.
Looking for it...
What do you use it for?
To put things in.
To put things in?
What do you put in it?
T(p)aper tand stuff.
Accumulations?
Taper (paper).
You put paper in it.
Taper!?
Paper?
That's right!
Taper.
You put that in it?
If it's something to stor
White.
White?
Back on track.
He noticed.
This?
No.
That's not it.
Those are plates.
Dude, he's not here for plates.
It can't be folded.
It shouldn't be foldable.
Is it hard?
A white stuare.
A white square?
He understood "square".
It's not disposable chopsticks, right?
Why disposable chopsticks?
What about a lunch box?
While white and square that's not it.
Nope.
I beg of you, store manager.
It can't be eaten.
Can't be folded.
Can't be folded nor eaten.
It's turned into a puzzle.
Right where they are at.
Down the aisle around the slippers.
They are here?
There they are the white taro (yam)... oops, I meant baskets.
Let's go back again.
Despite it being further ahead.
They came back.
Back to the slippers.
What's this?
He noticed something good.
The same thing.
The same thing?
A basket of this height.
Mama...
Mama told you to bring it?
Is this a hint?
Show your detective skills.
The hint is too difficult.
But you use this with pencils.
You use it with pencils?
Borrowed from his brothers' stationary.
An irrelevant piece of information.
A ruler, after all.
Do your best store manager.
Can you go back and ask?
Yeah.
This turned into the store managers' errand.
Will you? Go and ask?
I can.
Once more, go back and then tell me.
Yeah.
Why can't the man find him a taro (yam).
I apologize.
He has kids in primary and junior high school.
They've outgrown that phase.
I apologize.
No need to apologize that much.
Masashi is returning home.
Having so much fun.
Mother is waiting.
How was it?
Mama
It wasn't there.
What did you tell them?
They didn't have a single thing to put taper in.
You said "for putting paper in"?
The mother naturally hears taper as paper.
Basket, basket, basket.
Say basket while you walk.
Taro, taro.
Just like that.
Despite trying to say "basket" why doesn't the manager listen?
That's because he's not able to say basket at all.
The store manager is on Masashi duty today.
Again he meant to say asked not came back.
I went and came back.
Do your best, manager.
Do you get it now?
Yep.
It's around the slippers, right?
Let's go over there.
Let's go.
What did she tell you to say?
She said taro (yam).
Barrel?
Taro.
Haro?
Taro?
Stuare taro.
Barrel?
They turned where the slippers are.
Calm down.
To.
What if you try to say it slowly?
Tell me.
Pigeon.
He's back to pigeon.
Heart?
Something that you put things in.
You put things in it?
Pigeon.
Basket?
That's it!
Yeah.
Not pigeon but basket?
This is a breakthrough.
A breakthrough.
Like this?
They did it.
Found it.
There, there.
Will this do?
This is it.
This?
This? Did we find it?
He looks so happy.
He found the taro.
I'm so relieved.
Manager, about the height...
Isn't the height right for this one.
Yep.
The height is perfect.
Alright.
He finally bought it. Three white taro.
Be careful on your way home.
The manager's eyes are gleaming.
Thank you very much.
At that moment...
- Manager.
- Admirable.
Let's shake hands on it.
You really did well.
Thank you.
The manager is such a nice person.
He's no longer a baby.
He executed his errand properly.
He bought it. He bought it.
Finally.
Ma-.
His proud smiling face is dazzling his mother's eyes.
You are back.
See?
It's right.
The shop keep finally understood.
But he said heart again.
He said heart?
And for the purchased white basket....
Nice.
Will it fit?
It fits!
It fits nicely.
That's great.
Just how his mother wanted it.
Useful for a long time.
You did it.
Not how his mother wanted it with toro as a renummeration.
But it's salmon and lean tuna as they usually get.
How is it?
Nothing beats the usual taste.
What a childlike errand.
It's remarkable that he tried so many times.
That's how children run errands.
That's right.
The store manager has never been
so happy in his life to sell a basket.
He hasn't.
Like he was about to cry during the departure.
He was so happy.
Emotional bond.
During the entire thing
Mr. Tomida was crying the entire time.
Full of tears.
You can empathize, right?
Father of 2 sons with these ages.
That's right.
When I saw the on-air of me crying it made me cry even harder.
Annoying person.
How annoying.
During Halloween the Japanese who are thought of as being shy
have started wearing clothes and parading down the street.
It's a magical day where you get
the chance to overcome shyness.
Here's a household intending on having a first errand.
Shinyu   ●  Yuzawa city
The big sister tends to get easily embarrassed
Chihana
4 years 11 months
except for on this day.
Momoka
2 years 10 months
The 2 year old Momoka is always chill.
She doesn't know about shyness yet.
They will call over friends to their house today and have a Halloween party.
They will hollow out the pumpkin to use it as a cheese fondue bowl.
It's always the brother who goes on errands.
They insist on being useful to their mom, so the mom thought of this errand.
Momo, what about milk?
This is the little sister Momoka.
Milk is needed in cheese fondue.
Momokas role in the home is to bring the milk.
Then at first...
Please buy milk.
I want to go with mama and buy it.
Perhaps Momoka can't do it?
What about big sis?
Yes.
Can you go buy milk?
She can do Momokas part.
Yes, I will go an buy it.
The big sis was asked to get shredded cheese and a slab of bacon
and about the milk
unlike the usual one, the stronger unprocessed one will do.
The mom went for a difficult request.
Difficult indeed.
Unprocessed.
The shop is right there.
50 meters from the house.
The mom went with the closest option because of Momoka.
Wait, so Momoka is going after all?
Off you go.
Off we go.
Do your best.
Big sis, Momoka is now in your hands...
... then where are you going?
What, what, what.
Off the bat?
She's going out back. That's not good.
In front of our film crew campout.
Apparently there was a shortcut through the parking lot.
But there's an obstacle here.
This water ditch.
It's not a problem for the big sister but for Momoka it's impossible. And then...
Go down.
Do I have to go here in order to go to the shop?
Here we go.
Do this.
Momoka is already regretting that she went with her.
- Do your best.
- Do your best. Do your best.
Oh no, I got all dirty.
Momoka is pouting a bit.
That's right.
Because the milk has to be unprocessed
Momoka can't, but the big sister seems able to do it.
Milk first.
Cherfully running towards the milk.
It's not this one.
Since they need the unprocessed one.
Momoka can't but the big sister can.
This one perhaps.
Welcome.
This is the same milk as usual. Not the unprocessed one.
And what about the grated cheese and bacon?
That's right.
Momo wants to give it.
As the person in charge of the milk, Momoko wants to pay.
She wants to feel like she's the one who purchased it.
The sister knows about the melted cheese and bacon
but she's too shy to say anything.
She's too dejected to take the shortcut on the way back.
She's downtrodden from her embarrassment.
Is she embarrassed?
She couldn't purchase her part.
She couldn't say it.
Welcome back.
I could only get the milk.
I was too embarrassed to ask.
Embarrassing.
The magic of Halloween didn't do its trick.
Fine fine. It's so close so you can go as many times as you like.
Go see the lady again.
At first she intended to make her
go on the errand in a princess dress but
because of the rain she's wearing a rain coat instead.
The big sister will always hide behind her mom.
It's okay because you did your best so far.
Let's go.
Momo is cool as a cucumber.
Then Momo, can you go alone?
Yep.
By yourself?
This is the usual milk.
Not this one but unprocessed.
Ask for unprocessed.
Big sis, it's impossible for Momoka.
It's difficult.
- Unprocessed, right?
Yeah unprocessed.
Ask for unprocessed milk.
Yep.
Will she go alone?
Surely the big sister will worry and chase after her.
Her mother believes that.
She's going through the arcade this time.
Do your best.
Can she say "unprocessed"?
Please return this.
She understands returns.
Unprosshd.
Unprosshd?
That's a hard one.
Which is unprosshd?
She even remembers to say unprocessed.
Which do you always get?
Unprosshd.
She thinks she's saying it right but...
The old lady doesn't understand.
She's saying it.
Please give me the big cheese.
The big sister has still not changed her mood.
I was so embarrassed.
Embarrassed.
Too embarrased to ask?
Yeah.
The mom stops holding her.
But if you don't go then we won't be able to have a party.
Let's cancel it then.
Let's call them and say "hey, we can't do it".
Cancelling todays halloween party?
Or to do the errand despite shyness.
One of these two.
Go and look at how Momoka is doing.
Why don't you take a look if she's getting the unprocessed milk.
If it's only a peek then it's fine.
She's worried about her little sister
so she will go for her little sister.
Do your best for your sister.
The big sister has arrived.
Unprosshd.
She's still doing it.
The one your mom asked you to buy is...
She doesn't get unprosshd.
Unprosshd.
Now her big sister arrives.
Is it this one?
Unprocessed.
If it's unprocessed then it's this one.
She immediately understood thanks to big sister.
Alright.
Thanks to her indeed.
Yes, that's right. The unprosshd one.
Is this the unprosshd one.
The lady didn't think that a 2 year old was trying to say such a difficult word.
Sorry for not noticing.
The big sister started moving.
And melting cheese.
Melting cheese?
She overcame her shyness.
She only came to watch, but is she going to buy some?
Is this okay?
This is for putting on bread. It will melt but it's not enough.
I see.
What will you make with this?
Cheese fondue.
Cheese fondue? That's amazing.
The old lady doesn't know such luxurious cuisine.
Round bacon.
Not exactly round. It should be a slab of bacon.
This is a bacon slab.
We only have a big one.
What about this slab? Will it do?
Okay, please this one.
No, this is ham.
It's ham.
Will loin ham do?
She's so embarrassed that she can't stand it.
This is for toast.
Whatever. She just wants to leave.
It turned into ham and cheese toast.
But she was able to go to the checkout properly.
Hurry, hurry. I want to go home.
I see. She's too shy.
She can't even lift her eyes.
She knows that she got the wrong things.
She does?
She knows it's no good.
She's not even holding Momoka's hands.
Oh no no.
Oh, I see.
This is ham.
The mother isn't scolding them but greeting them warmly.
But it's no good. She won't go back.
I'm embarrassed.
It's fine because you did your best so far.
I will buy bacon for you.
Is that alright?
Momo will you go?
Yep.
Momoka will be useful again.
Well see ya later then.
Momoka.
Momoka is always cool as a cucumber. She can do anything.
She will be soaking by the end of the day.
Momoka come back.
What is it?
I want this kind of cheese.
For the Halloween party this won't be enough cheese.
Momoka won't understand. I better go with her.
There you go.
The big sister didn't take the shortcut for her sisters sake this time.
They've walked through this door so many times today.
Welcome.
Don't lose to your shyness.
Was it wrong?
Sorry to hassle you, old lady.
We need a bacon slab.
Where do you have bacon slabs?
You want a bacon slab?
What about this one from before? The big one?
This is the right one. No doubt.
That's great.
The big sister is finally laughing.
This slabs.
And the cheese was wrong too.
She's riding on a high.
Right right.
This small one.
That's right. That's the one.
With this they can make cheese fondue.
I did it.
Returning the wrong things and purchasing these. Perfect.
She has overcome her shyness.
She's smiling now.
Thank you very much.
She was even able to properly show gratitude.
It's done now.
How nice. A proper big sister.
A face full of pride.
The big sister takes the shortcut.
I'm going this way.
They are both walking different paths.
The mother is wondering why they are separated.
But it's okay.
Going each their own way they will still make the same memory of this errand.
"I want to be helpful."
She really did her best.
Welcome back. What's with that expression.
She's grinning.
This. This. This is it.
You did well carrying this heavy thing.
Welcome back Momo.
Welcome back. Enter. Enter.
Please enter.
Thank you for helping me so much.
To be helpful towards your mother.
I did try it.
Ah Momo, get your thank you hug.
Thank you.
You and your sister did well together.
The uprocessed milk from Momoka
melted with her sister's cheese.
Cheers.
As a Halloween specialty: "Pumpkin cheese fondue".
Looks good.
Their friends also came while all dressed up.
That's right.
The bacon is delicious.
Their big brother agrees.
She overcame and bought it.
She was able to help everyone out.
Yeah, we poured all of Momo's milk into it.
You are such a helpful child.
Also Momo.
Both of them love being sung their praises.
Right?
What a nice party.
Splendid.
Both of them are really well behaved.
She said unprosshd.
Unprosshd.
- If you say unprosshd in the milk aisle in can only mean unprocessed.
- That's right.
Suzu, if you had a little sister like that...
5 year older brother and
4 year older sister
I really thought that it was like my relation to my brother and sister.
The idea that the sister was without any fear.
While the big sister looks out and is serious.
She thinks about the bigger perspective?
That's right.
I have a big brother and our grandparents really were affectionate with me.
2 year older brother
They would take me out every day like department stores
or Japanese confectionary shops.
So it's all their fault how I've turned out.
Fault? Don't you mean thanks to them?
Yeah, thanks to them.
Speaking about grandchildren
both you, Tokoro, and Ito have them.
You will do anything they ask you to?
Of course.
The heck are you saying?
The same is true for me.
Nothing hurts when it comes to grandchildren.
No matter what they do to you.
Being hit.. like...
being stabbed with a toy sword.
Nothing beats that.
Nothing hurts.
Miyagi ● Matsushima City
The sunrise in one of the three beauty spots of Japan
Matsushima where you can also see the Shiogama shrine
a tradition that has been carried on for over 1200 years.
It's a shrine that draws attraction from all over Touhoku.
It's this amazing on the first day after New Year.
It's bustling.
In the past, only men of the Date clan were allowed to climb this.
It is here, they will climb these stone steps as their first errand.
The steps
stretch far here.
But it's a great view.
Children aged 3, 5 and 7 have come to visit on this autumn day.
The boy who will go on an errand lives at a candy shop.
It's like living in a dream.
To be surrounded by a ton of toys every day
Ramune, fugashi and dried apricot sticks.
It's like heaven.
The boy to envy is Naoki.
He's always energetic and his favorite game is to play house.
The one appearing here is....
Morning.
It's his girlfriend, Seina.
A month older, at 3 years and 11 month old
they've known each other from birth.
Let's go.
Don't go too far.
We were asked by daddy to visit the shrine and purchase a charm.
Nao.
Do you know of any good charms?
To smoothen things.
Huh? Ah yeah what was it...
What type of charm is that?
To smoothen things.
To smoothen things? Is there one like that?
The very popular charm at Shiogama shrine.
A charm to smoothen things.
Could be useful for the errand.
- What if you went together?
- Will you go?
I could even go by myself.
No way you could.
Yes, I can.
What are ya saying.
Okay but...
Can you go along with Seina? The two of you.
Yeah...
Here are two charms.
Hidden mic charms.
This one.
Boys prefer blue.
Huh!? He wants the red one?
Do you know what's on it?
Touch yours to Seina's.
So please get along all lovey-dovey.
How nice.
All lovey-dovey.
The soy sauce shop is at the foot of the shrine.
they were asked to get round-shaped konjaku called Tama-kon.
Then it is a 202 stairs climb up Omotesando.
*It was a hill only men of the Date clan were allowed to climb.
Mens' climb: The steeper one.
Womens' climb: The least steep one.
Then they enter the grounds to purchase the charm.
On their way back they will go down the women's climb.
Do you know which hill to go up?
The male climb.
And what about the return?
The female climb.
As expected from a local boy.
I've started craving dango.
That's nice.
Will you then go and buy some?
Yeah.
This adds a new errand. Dango, enough for 5.
Oh my.
Who will command the male climb?
Seina.
Seina will command the steep climb?
Who will command the female climb?
I will.
Nao will? Isn't it reversed?
Commanding officers do your best.
Hoping to get along. Smooch.
Off you go.
We will rely on you.
The long-established soy sauce shop.
Huh? The bamboo blinds are down.
Here perhaps?
Is it locked?
Ah, must be closed today.
It's before the opening hours.
They haven't opened? Let's tell mama.
Too early.
Nao, please wait.
Don't run.
Since they came all the way.
Ah, we must get the dango first.
They're running back and forth.
Will they have enough stamina for the climb?
Right at that moment the shop is opening up.
It's good that they went back.
Huh? It's opening now?
They were early.
"Phew, we made it" the camera man thought.
What do you want?
I want that.
Round konjyaku?
How many do you want?
The always reliable Seina.
3 please.
3? Alright.
Do you want it in a bag?
Yes, to go.
So adult-like.
She's amazing.
The Tama-kon steeped in soy sauce are only sold on holidays.
How nice.
Smells nice.
Here.
I will take the 500 yen. Please wait.
Since it's cold outside
please have one each.
The traditional preparation of konjac that has been steeped in soy sauce.
Delicious.
That's right.
Leaving the soy sauce shop they have a steep climb ahead.
Kids love to run.
It was delicious.
Yep.
The dango shop is next.
And the charm.
This is it.
202 steps.
Just as they said. It's 202 steps.
Not an easy climb even for adults.
Are you scared?
I'm not scared.
Please hang in there.
I will.
He's making her carry it.
I have no power.
What about Seina?
And she's the girl.
I do have power.
Where is the power?
Nao is losing.
It's a guarding lion-dog.
Guarding lion-dog.
But he's still buzzing full of words.
It's a guarding lion-dog.
He knows a lot.
Hurry, let's go up.
A guarding lion-dog.
Next let's go this way.
It's easier to go this way.
Is it?
I will climb this way.
It's smarter the other way.
It's easier this way.
It's easy, see!
It's not easier.
Nao is climbing the area where people stand to view the portable shrine.
I'm full of vigor.
Tough!
Just a bit more.
Not even close.
Seina is climbing the stairs
while Nao is climbing the area where people stand to view the shrine.
I'm full of vigor.
The 202 step climb to Shiogama shrine.
It would even exhaust adults.
Wait. Don't leave.
What?
Seina also ended up giong that way?
She did?
Today you win, okay?
They get along so well.
It's a horse!
Don't run!
A horse is there?
It's a cow, though.
It was a cow.
A cow.
I wonder if we can get a balloon.
Wonder if Seina understood Nao's wish to get one.
She did.
Nao also got one.
How great.
Yellow.
I wanted a pink one.
Go get one yourself.
We have to put money in, right?
Yes, money.
It's saisen.
We give all of our money, right?
No.
Seina puts 500 yen in.
And Nao?
There we go...
Next...
It doesn't ring...
Huh.
It won't ring.
He doesn't have the power.
Seina is thinking.
Ring ring
Ring ring ring
Nao, it rang.
Okay.
That was good.
Let's go. Next is the charm.
I see.
Let's get one.
They will buy a charm.
What a grand atmosphere.
It's a wedding.
How nice.
To be able to honor your ancestors.
Thinking that they might stand by and watch...
It's this one.
They weren't even watching it.
Not at all.
Not even a bit.
To smoothen things.
See?
They can read?
Let's buy this.
Seina bought the charm to smoothen things.
There are so many cute girls.
He's a boy after all.
I wanted a pink one.
He's still harping on that.
Nao, please don't run, okay?
Seina is getting tired.
Dango shop.
Don't run!
You were told not to run, weren't you!
He's being told so many times.
Nao, you will trip.
Ah!
There are so many!
He's sprinting.
Cotton candy too.
Yay, so much.
The adults can't keep up.
What about the dango?
Look!
Dango.
There's so much.
Won't you purchase dango?
They sell the masks at your home, don't they?
They were asked to get dango for 5 people.
Dango, please.
With this kind of money.
You were given this much money?
And...?
3 boxes? 2 boxes?
Or 5?
Yep, 5 boxes.
Wouldn't 5 be a wee too heavy to carry?
We can.
I see. Roger that.
Won't 5 be a bit too heavy?
Seina is worried.
We will eat for two.
And then we bring it to our mamas.
That would be nice.
I see...
They were planning to eat them all there?
If they both eat and take 3 back with them.
Looks nice.
We thought of a nice thing.
What nice thing?
If we eat for two and for out moms...
A present?
Yep.
I see. You will only eat your portion. Got ya.
Right?
For mama and papa, right? I'm writing
a letter to them so please wait.
She's writing a receipt.
This old lady will hold them for you so please give them
since you plan on eating dango first.
If the wind blows hard they will fly away.
That's right. Which is why this old lady will hold them.
Please wait.
But what if you forget them?
It's fine. I won't forget.
He's afraid she will keep them.
This is your spare change cause you gave me 3000 yen.
Tell them you purchased 5.
And the two of you will eat your part, right?
Wow!
So this is a freebie for your hard work.
Since you are such good kids.
Who understood it?
We did!
I love this dango.
Thank you so much old lady.
Grace.
What about saying grace.
Thanks to you the two of them are enjoying themselves.
How nice.
Two warm teas, please.
He loves dango.
Um, how delicious.
Mama is waiting...
Just like the old lady the dango has a kind taste.
How nice.
Is this free service?
Yes.
Thanks for the meal.
Thank you very much.
They properly said "thanks for the meal".
Since the dango they ate were freebies they are bringing 5 back.
Cotton candy.
Looks heavy.
They have cotton candy and masks.
Don't they sell lots of masks at the shop where Nao lives?
You forgot something.
The balloons!
This old lady forgot.
So close.
Just like he said.
They did forget it.
I can only hold 2.
Hold 1 and she will hold 1.
Glad she didn't have to chase them down the stairs.
Excuse me.
How many yen are these?
One is 100 yen.
I will get one for 100 yen.
Despite them selling so many at home.
It's still tempting.
Not the blue, he likes the red one.
I will get this one.
They have those at home too.
Must be different to him.
It's so loud.
Want to do it?
This is the smaller slope of higashisando.
Please go slow.
The cameramen are tired too.
Huh, what's going on?
It's fine. Thanks.
He called out to the cameraman.
This one is so loud.
Nice chance. Make use of the time.
Meanwhile the cameramen are running ahead.
This must be tough.
Wait.
We were able to get a shot from the front.
Nao, you might trip.
Our mamas must be worrying.
Errand errand how fun.
A dango order coming up.
It's Shiro from next door.
Shiro you can't eat the dango.
He's not even saying anything.
Go... errand...
They've arrived home.
I'm tired by now.
Yeah.
They didn't fall once and now that they are here.
Oh no, the tama-kons.
The tama-kons...
It's fine if they just wash it.
Mothers, the two of them did it all the way without any hiccups.
Let's wash and eat them.
Since the soy sauce has permeated it.
Did you buy a charm?
What's with this balloon?
How come?
Did you buy it?
Let's eat them together!
Nao is the one who settled things.
It's delicious.
I ate one of these.
Did you eat dango there?
Huh. How unfair.
They went on their first errand in 2008.
9 years later
from the errand when they were 3.
Shiogama was hit by the Great East Japan Earthquake
People had to evacuate to the hilltop shrine.
Seina and her family moved to Kanagawa prefecture after the earthquake.
In all those years it's the first time that she has returned.
First year students of junior high school.
Seriously?
They've become so big.
They still get along.
It rings this time.
Their moms are best friends so they'll always have a connection.
Since they've come all this way they better get a charm to smoothen things.
How nice.
As junior high students what do they wish will go well?
What do you wish will go well?
Club activity and study.
Study?
Studying doesn't matter.
What's he saying? Actually Nao is performing well in his studies.
He's completely into tennis after school.
"Please, only edit in the good parts" he told us.
Something he's more into is...
He wants to become a pâtisserie when he grows up.
Once he heard that Seina was coming he's been making cakes since morning.
With various decorations.
So?
Wonder which one is for Seina.
Huh? One of them is special.
This one is for Seina.
It's actually Seina's birthday tomorrow.
Surprising her with two gifts, eh? I see...
Amazing.
Seina is in the brass-band club.
She's playing the biggest instrument: The tuba.
Looks heavy.
After trying out several students she was able to play it best.
She's been playing since junior high school.
Before that was karate, gymnastics, swimming.
An instrument that requires force and lung capacity. A true match for Seina.
To carry a 10 kilo tuba lightly
That's heavy.
and to make it look fun during performances.
She's practicing that right now.
During the earthquake, it caused a tsunami so great...
that it carried tour boats, docked in the marina, onto land.
The two don't bring those times up.
The dango shop used to be right there.
And then...
You sure grew up.
The old lady has also become quite old.
It's been a long time.
How has everything been?
Good.
It's been such a long time since you tried my oden.
These oden will be a freebie.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming and visiting me.
I've made these.
He decided they will eat them at the dango shop.
Amazing.
Please eat the one you like.
I don't know if they taste good.
Incredibly delicious.
He won't give her the birthday special?
Huh. That's true.
What about the birthday present?
I forgot to bring it.
That can't be.
It finally came out.
Really?
Can't be helped. And he woke up early because of it.
When we get back.
When we get back?
This is Naoki who hasn't changed.
What was he thinking?
At such an important time.
His store managed to be spared, but...
the seawater came up to waist height and many of the shops were severely damaged.
This. This.
The important thing.
It's a bit early but happy birthday.
Thank you very much.
It's made from choco-chip banana.
Why are you speaking so formal?
This awkward distance is normal for first year junior high students.
Nice.
I got really nervous.
Just like Naoki all boys that age when they get excited they run around a lot.
She told him: "Don't run!"
He's so energetic.
Apropos Miyagi Prefecture, Sandwich Man you...
That's right, it's my home area.
Yeah, your home area.
I often go to Shiogama.
Does it bring up some memories?
When I was in kindergarten and living in Ishinomaki
there was a butcher not close by.
I was told to go get 500 g. minced meat.
I went by myself.
And when I arrived at the butcher
I said: "Please give me 500 g. of muscle."
I was told to go back and ask again.
And on the way back there was a big street that I had to cross.
And as I put my hand up to cross a taxi stopped by.
When a child rasies their hands
it's not to hail a ride.
I remember it vividly.
What do you think about the chance
if your kid could go on an errand?
I want to let them but I'm also afraid.
I would probably dress up like the staff here and follow him.
Yeah, the parents must be so worried.
That's right.
But there will be a day when they
have to be allowed out on their own.
A father who has made this decision is here today.
Special Guest will appear
Everyone, let's welcome him.
Papa, please enter this way.
Please enter.
Pro-boxing's former WBC World Bantamweight Champion
Yamanaka Shinsuke.
Yamanaka papa who was the strongest in the world.
Will send his children on an errand.
Heave ho!
He's different from inside of the ring.
I beg of you.
He's riddled with anxiety.
Totally worried.
You will continue to be moved.
A first errand in the harsh nature of Hokkaido.
A girl who gives it her all even in the face of challenges.
A whirlwind of emotions from the studio!
Let me introduce you to
the former WBC bantamweight world champion: Yamanaka Shinsuke.
Pleased to be here.
Welcome.
You made your young go on an errand.
Amazing.
How was it?
I never imagined this day would come.
My wife and I were in high spirits...
We were however...
just before the shooting
we were so anxious.
That makes sense.
4 days in advance we thought "it might not be possible".
Please let's not do it.
We didn't have the confidence.
And you haven't seen the footage, have you?
Of course not.
This is gonna be interesting.
Anxious
Please face camera 2 and
introduce the clip, please.
While my heart is beating fast, please enjoy this clip.
The pro-boxer Yamanaka Shinsuke
famously nicknamed "God's Left".
He defended the world title 12 times in a row.
The "God's Left" is strong.
For 5 years and 9 months he didn't lose once.
For such a man...
His first son was born merely 5 years ago.
Gousuke
When Gousuke was born
his father was already a world champion.
This is Gousuke.
Ririno
Winning and being able to hold my kids in the ring gives me great joy.
I'd still like to continue with one or more of these.
Just like he said.
Papa continued to win.
Let's play when we get home, okay?
Let's play.
Congratulations.
And the kids.
They grew outside of the ring.
Congratulations papa.
While defending his championship for 12 consecutive times.
Gousuke became 4 years and 4 months old.
And then during August last year.
Where he had to defend the title for the 13th time.
"God's Left" Shinsuke.
They had come to support outside of the ring.
Gousuke and Ririno.
Alright, round 4.... Hard left!
Right! Left! He's backing up!
The champion is backing up!
What is this!? My goodness!
What should I say? Oh my God!
Just keep swinging!
The champion swings back!
The towel is thrown!
My God! Yamanaka Shinsuke...
on the verge of a Japanese record...
loses by TKO!
Papa lost.
It's the first time seeing that.
The memory of God's Left will never be lost on fans.
This can never be forgotten.
Shiin-suke! Shiin-suke!
It's the first time experiencing the hardships of a loss since his birth.
The same as dad, no no, even more so.
That day...
he decided that he would fight along with papa.
The gong in Goutske's heart rang that day.
After the match.
Q: What will you do next?
I haven't thought about that.
Boxer Yamanaka began to avoid the media.
When he said he had lost, his son responded:
"But papa did his best 12 times".
Gousuke consoled him.
2 months after that match.
The staff of "My First Errand"
came to meet Yamanaka in his training room.
Good morning.
May I intrude?
Yes, please.
The fact that you lost, I think Gousuke
feels the same amount of hardships over it as you.
He suddenly said:
Papa, next time I think you will win.
That rang in my ears.
Those words sound great.
The kids want one more time
to be taken to that place again.
Yamanaka finally made the decision.
Yamanaka held a press conference.
Does that mean that you will continue being active?
Yes. Yes.
Once more
I want it to be thought that Yamanaka
still packs a punch with his left.
I want to win.
It was his kids that made him go back to the ring.
And as a thanks he wants to bring his kids back to the ring.
The thing that Yamanaka thought of
is a first errand
that he will have both of his children go on.
Ririno is a sweetheart who leaves everything to her big brother.
She uses her tears to get what she wants.
Gousuke has a sense of justice but he gets distracted sometimes.
The day before the errand.
The couple pay a visit to the shrine.
He always comes to pray before his match.
For my childrens first errand
I hope they make it out safe.
I beg of you.
Staff: Are you nervous?
I really am.
But it will feel good in the end.
That's right.
It's like with boxing.
Errands are like that too.
And now it's finally the day of the errand.
Yamanaka papa brought up the topic.
Both of you go buy... get this fixed.
Um.
Got it.
Go go!
Oh-!
And the errand has started.
Ey ey oh.
See you.
Bye bye.
Be careful. For real.
Yeah.
I will go for a run.
Okay.
Got it.
I'm asking you.
Yep.
Father, that's the eye of a champion.
That face reveals worry.
Too worried.
He's so worried.
I made that expression?
It's not only Yamanaka papa who has to do their best.
It's best to do you best.
Exerting herself in the harsh nature of Hokkaido.
Even the studio is moved to tears.
You did your best.
The errand that the father asked them to go on.
To get the broken scale fixed by a repair shop.
The scale is in Gousuke's backpack.
Many bicycles are coming.
Two of them.
Responsible big brother.
He is able to do the traffic safety check.
Looking right, then left
even though they get confused which is which.
That happens.
But it's fine today. They didn't make a mistake.
I've practiced so many times.
I probably got it.
That's right.
They've walked this path many times with your mom and dad.
What great siblings.
It's fine, isn't it.
Yes, it is.
And in no time they've arrived at the big street.
Checking right and left and...
go. No need to worry daddy.
Was it okay?
Completely fine.
Did they do it right?
For real?
They did. Yes.
I'm just full of wondering
if I forgot to teach it to them properly.
If I forgot something.
But it's fine.
Forgetting the father who is worrying by himself.
The two of them are proceeding on their route.
You are noisy.
Hey, Riri. Behave!
Riri always ends up crying when the two of them are fighting.
But she won't cry today.
She's holding it in.
Because her charm says: "Ririno won't cry!!"
She's looking at it and deciding not to cry.
On her brothers' it says: "You are strong"
So he's not just about arriving.
Come.
He makes sure to bring his sister with him.
Me too.
I will go work.
Running is his job.
To become a champion again
he needs to redo his training.
Oh, they made it.
They are crossing here.
It's not here.
He's not crossing here?
It's there. Can you see it?
There is another crossing ahead.
There.
From the convenience store.
There are several crossings.
Their mother has showed them various crossings.
But Gousuke doesn't remember.
Not yet.
It's green.
But they are crossing at just the right one.
Despite the big brother always running ahead...
not today.
That's why Ririno won't cry today either.
I can't fathom it.
Really?
This is the shopping street from the supporting hometown of Yamanaka.
This is the shopping street.
You got it?
Yep.
There's a small crying girl walking in front of them.
Really resembles Riri.
Though she usually cries she won't today.
Bakery.
Uuh, smells nice.
They usually drop by but not today.
Don't kid around.
Because today is...
Going on an errand.
their first errand, you see?
What a sense of responsibility.
Denka Land.
They've arrived at the electronics store.
The cameraman is waiting inside.
Papa's picture is on display.
So cool.
For real. It's papa.
Good day.
Thank you for the continued support.
Amazing.
How amazing.
After the greetings they take out the scale.
This.
What is it called?
This scale is broken so please repair it.
He carried this heavy thing.
Repair?
Yes. He was able to say it properly.
How about it?
Can it be fixed easily?
Ah, the battery is missing.
Battery?
The battery is missing?
Since there is no battery I will put one in.
So it was just missing a battery?
So there was no need to bring it?
For real.
Alright, try to step on it.
Yep, seems fine.
That's right. It was the battery.
50 yen, that's right.
Papa is being shown.
I hope this is not from the other day?
It's papa.
How great.
It's from his winning match.
Gouchan, where's papa today?
I was asked to go on an errand.
Ah, you were asked to go on an errand.
Remarkable the two of you came.
Yep.
He will have another match, right?
Thank you for your continued support.
We are the grateful ones.
Hope he does his best.
Yep.
Gouchan, hope you also support him.
When it comes to daddy's matches
he comes to watch.
It has been repaired
and they did the greetings
and they paid the bill.
The did everything perfectly.
At that time the father is...
Hello?
Phoning
his
wife.
He's fidgeting.
When you get home
He's rummaging around.
Do it properly!
Yep.
I was thinking about how to set it up.
He's planning to put them on a different errand.
200 g. of tenderloin and some shoulder roast?
Like that?
While he's planning that the kids are coming home.
We are almost back home.
They are already at their limits.
Forget the tenderloin...
He's still contemplating.
Make a decision!
You had to include this?
Yes we did.
Here it is.
They are already in.
We're home.
What?
Papa, we are home.
That's really amazing.
Yep.
What?
You were able to do it?
Yep.
Amazing.
How was it?
The father is in utter disbelief.
What did you say?
The scale is broken
please repair it.
You said that?
How amazing.
I can go on errands now.
Alright, check the scale.
Will it turn on?
Is it connected?
Now papa can continue to do his best.
Papa weighs himself 4 times a day.
61.9
That's right.
From here on...
For when mama comes home
let's make fried rice.
This is round 2 of the errand.
Gousuke.
There's no spring onion.
Will it be alright, papa?
And we also don't have rice.
We do have rice.
We have rice and eggs but
we don't have spring onion and
without it we can't make fried rice.
Here we go.
Spring onions and
to make papa stronger
meat is missing.
To become stronger?
I got it.
Leave it to me.
The brother can do it.
Alright
In round 2 he has to pay attention to Ririno.
About the spring onion.
The spring onion is Gousuke.
I will leave it up to you.
So the Ririno's responsibility will be
the tenderloin.
And then...
the thing both of you like
shoulder roast.
Shoulder roast?
Meat from the shoulder.
Yes, also get the meat from the shoulder roast.
Do you remember?
Yep.
I remember.
Alright what should you say when you arrive at Takagi Meats?
The worried father is double-checking.
Gousuke, do you remember?
Tenderloin and shoulder roast.
And the shoulder roast?
200 grams.
As expected from Gousuke.
If Riri doesn't remember
Gousuke will give a hint to Riri.
You got it?
By tapping her shoulders etc.
And saying "tend.."
Tenderloin.
Like saying the "tend" in "tenderloin".
Saying the "tend" of "tenderloin".
If you say that then Riri might remember.
Now it's practice time.
When you arrive at Takagi Meats.
Spring onion, please.
Also have to get onions.
Yep.
And Riri what will you say?
"Tend" "Tend".
Tenderloin please.
And what else?
Tapping her shoulder.
Shoulder roast.
Right right. Just like that.
However...
Can they do it.
The dad did perfect training for the second round.
Oh no, it's scary. One more time.
It's alright.
What will you buy, Gousuke?
Spring onion.
And Riri?
Tenderloin and
aaaaand...
Shoulder roast.
That's right.
That's enough already.
Alright. Say it one more time.
Yet again.
How many times.
Alright, say it one more time.
Eeh...
And how ever many times.
Do you remember?
Say it one more time.
Eeh.
He has knocked them out. What a champion.
Do your best.
We already got it.
You got it?
Do you feel like doing your best?
He wants perfection.
Because of his anxiety he allows no slip-ups.
This is how a world's best does it.
Alright, we are heading off.
Be careful of all the cars and bicycles.
Riri, I'm begging you.
What was it again?
He's still doing it?
Tenderloin.
You should just go then.
Shoulder roast.
This is the 15th time.
That's right.
Okay.
He finally said okay.
Leave it to me.
Believe in him.
Alright. Do your best.
They've finally been allowed to depart.
Be careful of the cars.
And bicycles.
It's like before a boxing match.
If they don't scurry away he will make them do it again.
He's too intense.
His stare is amazing.
I wonder if it will be fine.
Of course it will.
If you were to compare it to boxing?
It's alright.
Well...
with boxing I'm full of confidence before a match.
Now I'm full of worry.
Takagi meats.
We've arrived.
We are here.
Tenderloin please.
It's too fast.
She said tenderloin right away.
Tenderloin please.
Yes.
And the other thing?
Your father...
Shoulder roast please.
Alright.
How much?
Cause they did it 15 times.
She was able to say both.
200 grams.
200? Okay please wait.
The two of them are a nice combination.
See? Right on the mark.
Right on the mark.
The shoulder roast is for the kids.
And 100 gram of the luxurious tenderloin is for their father.
It's high on power but low on fat.
He often eats it prior to matches.
And spring onion.
And what?
Spring onion.
Spring onion?
And spring onion.
Ririno was able to do her errand.
Now it's his part.
The big brother was able to do all this.
One please.
With this papa will be ecstatic.
Yay.
I can do errands now!
It's the brothers responsibility to pay.
Please wait.
Since this is 2500 yen
I will go get your change.
Gousuke.
He has become a reliable man in no time.
Please hold this.
Ririno takes care of carrying the groceries.
Come come.
Please take care.
Yep.
Alright...
Father is waiting at home.
They are becoming adults.
The street to go home is that way however...
Where is Gousuke going?
If we go that way will we return?
Yep.
The cameramen are now running in the opposite direction.
What happened?
Are they going to the park?
Despite having made it this far.
Where are they going?
While holding Ririno's hands Gousuke is heading towards...
Okay, shrine.
The shrine!
Their father always comes here before a match.
Do not run.
Gousuke.
What will he wish for?
Hold this.
Let's hope that father wins his matches again.
How amazing, big brother.
Phew.
He loves his parent.
Gousuke did the errand to his best so that his father can win his next match.
So irresistible.
Wondering why Riri was able to do it today without crying.
I love papa's cooking.
Right, Gouchan?
Yeah.
Is that right?
She wanted to eat your father's cooking.
Both of their errand has been perfectly carried out.
That's right. Cause they rehearsed 15 times.
We are almost there.
Sparta upbringing.
Yay, we did our best.
Yay, you did your best.
We are home.
Did you do it?
He's so anxious.
The way he says "eeh!?".
Did you?
Thank you.
Papa.
Amazing.
How amazing.
I'm so surprised.
At Takagi meats.
You were able to go?
Thank you. Come here.
You two are amazing.
How great.
I'm so happy.
Gousuke.
Riri. I'm happy.
Thank you.
He cuts the spring onions using the "God's left".
Actually since becoming a pro
he's been working part-time at a Ramen joint.
Skillful movement.
The 1200 yen 100 grams of tenderloin.
Looks good.
And at that moment.
I'm home.
Mama.
It's their mother.
It smells good.
It's fried rice.
Pork shoulder roast and lots of spring onion fried rice.
Looks delicious.
Their fathers cooking is like a pros.
And as the soup is also ready.
Thank you for the meal.
This is the famous daddy's fried rice that he hasn't been able to make recently.
Delicious.
It's the best.
For this errand mom worked behind the scenes.
The meat is delicious too.
He ate the meat.
Gousuke.
He usually doesn't eat meat.
Ririno eats anything.
Aaah, delicious.
Papa can do his best again.
Yep.
Right?
I will become strong again.
For the next match.
One more time?
Yes, I will fight again.
We did it.
Let's do this.
Hey hey ho!
Riri.
It's with your left.
That's your right arm.
Do it with your left.
This one.
That's right. With the "God's left".
Papa will do his best from here on.
Let's go. Hey hey ho!
With a bigger voice.
Hey hey ho!
He always makes them do it many times.
Yamanaka gains his strength from... his family.
Bringing both of them in the ring
he will soon again be embracing the two like this.
You did it.
The rice looks delicious.
Yamanaka papa.
Yes.
First time seeing this. How is it?
I understimated my son and daughter.
You made them do it 15 times.
That was too much.
This is just how parents feel.
When you look at the clip
you get a clear sense that they got it however
and I made them do it many times but
I still feel like they didn't get it.
For real?
They got it by the 2nd or 3rd time.
It was excessive.
Even looking at it I was surprised at how persistent I was.
You really are persistent.
Since Riri practiced it 15 times the moment the doors open she shouted "tenderloin".
You overdid it.
As the doors were sliding.
When they went to the shrine to pray
and said "hope papa will win" and how they were holding hands.
I felt so good looking at this imagery.
That's right.
I didn't think I would cry while watching this clip.
You could cry at any point.
That's right.
Alright dad,
you have an important match coming up. Are you prepared for it?
Since my son and daughter did their best
next is my turn.
That's right.
You better do.
We will be supporting you.
Thank you very much.
Ah, it's snow.
An errand while waiting for spring.
With -20°C in the middle of winter.
The frozen plain of Shikaoichou in Hokkaido.
Hokkaido ● Shikaoichou
From November to April
the ground remains covered in snow.
The Tokachi Plain was first settled 120 years ago.
People used axes and saws...
to cut through the thick growth of bamboo grass and oak trees turning it into farmland.
What an amazing thing.
Anything that can be done will be done by the people themselves.
That spirit from the pioneer days is still rooted in their daily lives.
And the long winter comes to an end by the end of April.
Farmers get busy at once.
Fields, as far as the eye can see, all belong to them.
They've lived here for 100 years.
This is an errand among huge agricultural fields.
Their farmlands are larger than Tokyo Disneyland.
Cabbage, wheat, potato and more.
It's another world, like a storybook.
Here lives Mirei and Kaori who are siblings that get along.
The proper big sister and the shrewd little sister.
They help out in the fields every day.
They are given a lot of freedom by their mother.
They know no fear of strangers.
Which means...
at Mirei's house people come to learn about Hokkaido's agriculture from China, Taiwan, Indonesia, Australia and New Zealand.
People come to study from all over the world.
They eat with the trainees
and they live like a family.
And next to the log cabin where everyone eats is their home.
Today they are making food for 12.
They better go on an errand.
We have to prepare the stew already.
Yes.
Daikon.
They are making homemade stew for lunch.
Daikon, onions, carrots.
All ingredients are from their farm.
What else do we need?
Don't we need potatoes?
Ah, we do.
Yes, we do.
Will you get it at the storage?
Yes.
Which means...
Ah, good luck charms!
First their errand is to the snow storage.
Today is both of yours job.
That's right. This isn't a game.
What's inside the good luck charm?
Mama's feelings.
Show it.
No way I can show that. That's too embarrassing.
To commemorate this day
she made them yesterday.
Heavy.
Is it heavy?
Mama's heart is really heavy, right?
Right? It's pretty heavy.
I can't stand this.
It also has Shiji's feelings in it.
She will give birth to a younger brother next month.
Do you job right or I will be angry.
Don't play around.
The mother moved here from Kyoto after marriage.
She has placed her children in the care of the majestic nature of Hokkaido.
I'm relying on you.
Alright.
Please do.
One Two One Two
They are looking for their father to open the snow storage.
I wonder if papa is around.
There.
Asparagus.
Papa.
Growing it on your own is so nice.
What's up?
Please open the snow storage.
Why?
Because mama told us to get potatoes.
Weren't there any in the fridge?
Nope.
And we got good luck charms.
And mama's feelings are inside.
See.
Must be really heavy.
Because your mom does her best.
Doing her best.
And we will do our best getting the potatoes.
This is all is needed for happiness.
That's right.
It's like an anime.
The snow storage uses natural snow to freeze things.
The air inside is so refreshingly cold.
Where is it?
Over here.
Here.
At the snow storage the potatoes have been set aside for half a year
which makes them really sweet.
Even if you ask for just a little bit.
This is the portion.
It's heavy.
That's enough.
This is Hokkaido!
Let's carry it together.
Looks heavy.
They carry it together.
Since I have work to do please carry it.
Yes.
The two of them can carry it together.
Kaori will be back.
Where is Kaori heading?
Kaori is running.
Why is she running?
She doesn't want to carry them?
It always ends up like this.
Mirei carries the burden
while her sister does what she wants to do.
One could say that she's stubborn.
She will shout when things aren't going well.
If you don't hurry up and help then they will scold you, Kaori.
Kaori, hold here.
Yes.
One two and go.
That's right. Now both of them are carrying it.
Heavy ho, heavy ho.
Both of you carry it.
If they can do this they can also go to the neighbors.
Mama.
Yes.
We brought it.
Thank you.
It was heavy.
You really helped out. Wow, you brought so many.
What else does our stew need?
Now is the errand for real.
Oh that's right. We don't have any milk.
Can you get some from Mana's mother?
Mana's house is a dairy farm.
They always get milk in a pot.
Go to Mana's and get it half filled up.
Since it will be heavy half is fine.
To avoid spillage the lid can sit on tight.
Furthermore...
Also get sausages from the "Warm cafe".
It's pretty far away.
Mi you're the milk minister.
You're the Minister of Milk.
And what about me?
You will be the minister of Sausages.
Yes.
Delegating the important tasks.
Promoted to minister.
Fatty sausage.
That's right, fatty sausage.
Kao can say it.
Four of them.
That's right four. Four fatty sausages.
She has learned her numbers recently.
They will get milk at their neighbors'.
Which is about 1 kilometer away.
And the closest shop is 2 kilometers away.
Where they will get 4 packs of sausages.
- Hokkaido is so big.
- Huge.
Heading off.
If they don't get it before 8 the pickup truck will be there ahead of them.
They better hurry.
I have the duty of a mother towards you.
Heavy ho. Heavy ho.
Heavy ho.
Errand. Errand. Err
Wait.
Say: Errand. Errand.
Errand.
Kaori is bringing potatoes as thanks.
And her sister is bringing the pot.
Do your best.
If we don't hurry the milk truck will leave.
Mana's house
At this pace they will make it.
They can't see a sign of the big truck yet.
Mama.
Kaori.
She's becoming homesick.
You can't go after all.
Jeez.
Kaori, you are my little sister.
Since you are my little sister act properly.
Mana's house is straight ahead.
I wanna go by bicycle.
No good.
The three wheeled bike is for people who can't walk.
That's only for adults.
What about this kid. Can't they walk?
Yep.
Yes, this person can't walk.
Veteran staff member
The old man and old lady
they usually can't walk.
The old man and lady.
Got it?
That's why a three-wheeler
is faster but
She was curious.
Let's go.
The two young ones started walking.
Inside of the good luck charm
mom's heart and the gods are in it.
The gods?
Yes.
Kaori loves the gods.
Right? That's why I'm telling you to run.
I will run now.
See? You've become energized.
Yep.
And as they've become energized and all is fine...
Miiilk and...
It's so far.
potatoes
While it has become Spring it's still only 3°C.
The weather is rather volatile.
Everything is tasty.
This is amazing.
Over here.
Mana's house is a lifestock farm.
They've finally arrived.
They always get their milk from here.
They have a great neighborly relationship.
This house also delivers the neighborhood circulars.
Mana's mama.
Mana goes to the same kindergarten.
Kaori delivers the cold-stored potatoes.
Here it is. Potatoes.
You brought potatoes?
Fill it half up
with milk, please.
Half filled with milk. Let me pour some.
Mana's place is a dairy farm of the latest style.
We made it.
The cows go the milking machines by themselves.
And as they go round like a merry-go-round they will be completely milked in no time.
And this freshly squeezed milk
is collected in a tank in the adjacent room.
Ew.
Hey! Hey!
It's warm here.
Big sister with the compliment.
It's fine with this much.
It's so cold outside that the lens is getting foggy.
They asked for half so that they can carry it.
It's pouring.
I see.
That's why they're using a pot.
Who poured this?
By gathering it from the cows it adds up to this.
This is fine.
Too much and it becomes too heavy.
That's right.
That's enough.
The condensation from the fresh milk is covering the lens.
Let's bring it home.
The made it before the 8 o'clock truck arrives.
As expected from the minister of milk responsibilities.
Next are the sausages.
Huh?
What about the milk?
- Huh?
- The milk?
What will you do about this?
Aren't you gonna bring it?
Please keep it for now.
She will keep it?
When we come back please hand it over.
Where are you going now?
The "Warm cafe".
The two of them are here.
Going to the closest shop the "Warm cafe" is all the way over there.
I see. It's better to leave the milk
in their care and take it on the way back.
That's better.
We are heading off.
We will fill this bag up with sausages.
This is the minister of sausages.
Yes, 4 packages.
Bye bye.
Hurry up, minister.
They will be back.
It was a great success.
They also gave the potatoes
and the pot is ready for pickup.
They finally feel agile.
They've become light.
At that moment.
The truck that takes the milk.
How great. How great.
How great.
Today is great.
Kaori is dragging behind.
Michan, I'm tired.
I see.
Let's hold hands.
This way.
Jeez.
Despite their age difference their personalities are similar.
Even though Kaori can do it she pretends not being able to.
The little sister likes to be treated sweetly.
Let's go all the way there.
Let's go. A bit further.
Big sister can't help but look after her little sister.
The big sister is remarkable.
Who is walking to the "Warm cafe"?
Here.
The cows of the "Warm cafe".
The owner, Sei, is very kind and is loved by both of them.
She's looking.
Where your soul can take a respite and warm up: Warm cafe.
They will purchase the homemade sausages.
The minister of sausages is the little sister: Kaori.
Good day.
Seichan.
I'm Seichan. Good day.
What about mama?
Oh no.
It hurts.
Are you okay?
The minister has fallen.
- Minister of sausages.
- Do your best.
Are you okay?
She seems okay.
What about mama?
Mama has sent us on an errand.
Sei is giving them a wet towel.
Is mama not coming? Just you two?
Are you helping out?
Everytime we get hurt
she worries about us.
Minister of sausages. Please step up.
Kaori.
Did it hurt?
Fatty sausages please.
Her big sister said it instead.
But Kaori...
4 packages?
Yep.
She was able to say it.
But she was still able to say how many.
Money. Money.
The minister of sausages is carrying the money.
Money.
Amazing.
Here.
Are you giving me all this?
This is 2000 yen.
Seichan is making such a shady expression.
One is 700 yen.
700 yen?
That's right.
One package is 700 yen.
Not enough?
It's not enough.
There are four but these aren't the four to get.
Four packages.
2000 yen is just not enough.
What to do?
What will we do. We can't go home without it.
Yeah, you can't go home.
Their mother has miscalculated it.
Since 2000 yen isn't enough.
What should we do?
Giving them less or...
will Seichan give them for free?
Seichan. Seichan.
One of these two.
She's curious.
For the insufficient part
what should I do?
What a weird feeling.
What should we do?
Weird feeling.
Maybe I will just get it from your mother later.
Finally a new proposal.
I will write down the missing amount.
800 yen.
800 yen, right?
Seichan is so gentle.
Oh no. This isn't good.
Yeah, it started raining.
It's not only cold but it has started raining.
Seicchan is dressing them in the raincoats from their bags.
And he's giving them hot patches to warm them up.
He's so kind.
Seichan is so kind.
Further more, further more. He's also giving them warm milk for free.
How good.
Looks delicious.
Kaori and Mirei.
The milk is ready.
It's so warm.
Looks good.
It melts.
What a nice face.
It's warm.
How nice.
Kaori is also enjoying it.
It's warm.
Old man, are you also cold?
I'm cold.
It looks cold.
So kind.
Is it okay?
It's warm.
Giving it to the man?
Yes, it's warm.
So kind.
Kaori has been influenced by Seichans kindness.
Micchan give yours.
And Kaori's kindness has been conveyed to her sister.
Warm dr...
She's even giving hers to the camera man.
Is it okay?
It's warm.
A chain of kindness.
Everyone is feeling warm and fuzzy.
Seichan, I drank it all.
This is happiness.
Thank you.
It was warm and delicious.
Thanks to the cafe they've become warm.
I want to do this.
If you have a dream.
Goodbye.
And for the last time.
The two of them are departing with renewed energy.
Seichan is becoming soaked.
Bye bye.
At that instant
the rain has become stronger.
This is normal in early spring.
Despite having warmed up.
It's so cold.
- It's pouring down.
- Looks cold.
It's so cold that the lens has fogged up again.
In the harsh nature of Hokkaido.
If we don't hurry.
They are soaked.
If we don't go.
Makes me sad.
The big sister can't go ahead.
She's looking at Kaori's face
and adjusting her pace
while encouraging.
Do your best.
I can only do a tiny bit of my best.
Huh?
She's honest.
Will you go home?
Yeah.
"But Kaori can still go on"
is what her sister felt.
We don't need the milk?
I forgot.
Let's do our best.
Their mother always tells them
"It's more fun to give it your all."
So that's why...
Do our best. Do our best. Do our best.
Mana's house is within sight.
They will get the milk and take it back home.
It's warm again.
It's not here.
Ah, it's here. On top.
Will you take it?
Alright, Mirei do your best.
The big sister carries the milk.
Hard.
Kaori is carrying 4 packages of sausages.
I'm tired.
Everyone is bringing home their own things.
You would get tired from this.
Their house is within sight.
Just a bit more.
Their mother is waiting for them on the road.
If they turn around here their mother is waiting for them.
If she can power through then it's just a bit more.
Ah, the milk is heavy.
It must be.
I'm tired.
She wants to go to them
but she's holding that in.
Better than quitting, exerting yourself is the way.
I will do my best.
It's better to do my best.
At first she could easily carry it.
But it has become heavy.
Are you okay?
Kaori kept looking over her.
Mirei.
Kaori.
Do your best.
Mama.
Michan is crying.
Mirei, do your best. I'm waiting for you.
Mama.
Alright, wait a bit.
I will walk over there.
Big sister, I will do something for you.
Kaori has forgotten how heavy her own bag is
and is completely focused on her sister.
Mirei.
Mirei can't carry it.
She can't carry it?
Wanting to convey to her mother about her sisters situation
she's made it to the goal without even paying attention.
The sausages have arrived.
You did your best.
Yeah.
Micchan is still sitting over there. What should we do?
Because Michan is exhausted
I came to mama.
You came to tell me?
That Michan is exhausted?
Mirei.
The big sister
becomes decisive while seeing her sisters resolution.
Mirei.
It's better to give it your all.
Michan.
Papa and mama are waiting.
I'm doing my best walking over.
Papa was watching while hiding.
Mirei come over here.
Let's make this the goal.
Come here.
Just a bit more.
You are remarkable.
Thank you.
How great.
This is the goal.
Your mama has...
Did you bring the milk all by yourself?
It was heavy, wasn't it? You did your best.
You did your best.
Kaori also did her best.
That's right.
It was truly better to have given it their all.
You were remarkable.
Let's go home. To a warm place.
Since Kaori went to mama
I became decisive
You became decisive?
You were remarkable.
The two of them were able to do it till the end.
It was cold but everyone was warm.
Today's sausage stew will be a warm stew.
Looks delicious.
It's done.
Okay. It's done.
There are so much sausage in it.
They are bringing it over to eat with the helping hands from all over the world.
The stew is done.
Thank you.
The camera is fogging up again.
Thank you for the meal.
Everyone try and taste it.
Yes.
Sausage. Sausage.
Yes, the sausage...
It's huge.
Wow, it's delicious.
It's great.
Thank you.
The minister of sausages.
And...
thank you to the minister of milk.
Today I will sleep all day.
Thank you for your hard work.
She's so tired.
Because she's tired.
Next is spring
and after the short Hokkaido summer
and then they will be back to the harsh winter.
Due to the coldness of midwinter
The nature raises you to become stronger.
Ah, that's right.
Their younger brother Shinji was born.
The two of them will help out lots from now on.
The grandness of Hokkaido sure is nice.
That's right.
But the mother is remarkable too.
Insisting on not going over to her
but to declare her place as the goal.
This type of mother and father
will raise children who are happy.
Not only just saying that "doing your best is better" but they get to watch their parents constantly doing their best.
I have a big sister and we have a lot of fun together.
But when I think that things are tough just seeing my mother gave me a sense of security.
The sense of security at home
is truly something worth appreciating.
To look up to your mother, right?
It really influenced me.
It really influenced you.
For the last goal
Yamanaka papa, would you wait it out?
No, I would go right away.
I would.
If this entire segment was Yamanaka and his children then they wouldn't even start.
It wouldn't even work.
Wouldn't even work.
That's right.
The closest JR station is Katsunuma-budoukyo station.
Yamanashi ● Katsunuma-budoukyo
It is also the birthplace of Japanese wine.
During autumn many tourists come to pick grapes.
Three siblings have grown up at this vineyard.
The ones going on an errand is the 2nd and the 3rd.
Kaori who can take care of those below her is hoping to be the mature older sister.
Kozue just wants to be strong and happy.
For the grape picking customers, miso soup is offered for free.
Bringing the empty bowls back is how they help.
Kozue doesn't bring them back.
Is that right?
There's not enough tofu for the next customers.
What will we do?
Will you go and buy some tofu?
Five packages.
Five packages if they are small
but if they are large then five will be too heavy so only get three.
And you know that grandma needs her hip medicine...
That's difficult.
that she rubs on. If you mention it they will know.
Go to the pharmacy.
Yeah, I got it.
Her explanation is kind of crude.
At the pharmacy she needs to get medicine for her grandma
and tofu at the supermarket. Today is the grape festival so there will be many people.
The town is different today.
It's the once-a-year grape festival.
The sound of fireworks.
She looks surprised.
The big sister always reacts poorly to loud noises.
On top of her first errand the loud sounds are reverberating.
Do your best.
The always crying kitten...
That's not true Kozue.
The portable shrine has come out.
The adults are shouting loudly
and big sister's heart pounds even harder.
They are surrounded by a wall of butts.
While dragging her little brother by the hand they've finally arrived at the pharmacy.
Did you two come by yourself?
You did well.
It's medicine for her grandmas hips.
What have you come to purchase?
What will it be?
You rub on your buttocks...
Buttocks?
Grandma. Buttocks.
That you rub on, please.
For her grandmas buttocks?
Got it. For your grandmas behind.
TEXT5
It's not for her buttocks but her hips.
Close.
Must be based on the view.
Ah, because that's all she saw on her way.
Oh no, she gave her hemorrhoid cream.
And they purchased it.
I will bring the reward. Please wait.
Even though she doesn't have hemorrhoids.
The old lady always gives them something.
Be careful on your way home.
Today is big.
What's inside?
Mandarins and manjuu buns.
How great.
Manjyuu?
You going to be okay? Be careful.
Big sister doesn't have the composure to give thanks.
Sorry old lady.
They've arrived at the supermarket. They will get tofu.
There are policemen everywhere because of the festival.
Please be careful.
Please help us cross.
That's oka... huh?
Help you cross? Just a moment.
She has calmed down and finally acting like a big sister.
Please help us cross.
She said it properly.
Her mother told her to ask the cashier where the tofu is.
But she doesn't know when to ask.
That's difficult indeed.
She waited 10 minutes for the customers to leave.
Where's the tofu?
Where's the to...
It's to the furthest in this direction.
She finally asked.
If they are small then five packages
or three of the big ones.
She has picked the big ones.
They are given to the grape picking customers.
Be careful.
They're expecting a big group today.
They won't get any rewards here.
They are taking a route back where cars don't go.
But the road her mother told her to take...
Is overflowing with people.
Her mother forgot about all the stalls filling up the road.
Makes you hungry.
The sister is always really interested in toys but not today.
But Kozue can't take his eyes away.
It's all so seducing.
Hey hey, don't get carried away and dance along.
I get this mood.
Kozue.
They've finally beat the crowds.
It's not like Kozue is walking fast
it's the sister who is becoming slower and slower.
Is it heavy?
It's heavy.
Kaori the doooog
is in trouble woof woof wooof
woof woof wooof
Among the three siblings the sister is the most prone to crying
that's what the mother told us.
But even when she cries she carries out her duty till the end.
Do your best.
Suddenly her legs stopped moving.
And Kozue only looks forward.
Please notice her.
Kozue.
Aah, he noticed.
Kozue who only looks forward.
He runs to her in full force.
And tells her this:
It's okay.
Kozue is matching his pace with his sister.
But he doesn't help carry the bags.
And his sister insists on carrying them herself.
The two of them alone in the grape fields
arriving in the twilight of the mountain region.
We've arrived.
Mom is there.
They live in a grape field.
This is a shortcut to the front door.
Their mother has turned on all the lights in the house.
Kaori cried.
Even if she cried, she still did it till the end.
Kozue is tough even though he's only 2.
Is this the drug?
It's hemorrhoid medicine.
I completely forgot.
I forgot.
I asked for some cream for grandmas hips, this is slightly different.
But it's fine.
The customer have gone home for today but
the mother is making her specialty miso soup.
How is it? Delicious?
It's warm. Be careful.
22 years have passed since then...
A wedding!?
Which means?
Which one, which one.
Kaori is 27 years by now.
Kozue is 25 years old.
Which one?
Which one is it?
It's the younger brother Kozue.
It's Kozue.
She's marrying someone cool.
Yeah, he's handsome.
He was just 2 year old
He's grown so much.
and in no time 22 years have passed.
Mother.
Grown to a spectacular 1.85 cm.
He's tall and they've met at a volleyball club.
I'm sorry I didn't help you carry anything back then.
He has apologized by now.
That's right.
Where is his big sister?
There she is.
Kaori hasn't married yet.
That's fine.
Working as a travel agent
She lives on her own and helps out at the vineyard on her days off.
The one sibling who does it till the end even through tears
she still helps out at home.
Do you feel like continuing to help out here?
I have thought about this and that but...
This and that?
She's a reliable helping hand.
You couldn't do it without her?
Please advertise that we are looking to hire.
That's not needed with her around.
She has grown this much however...
She served as both the little and the big sister.
How nice.
Isn't that just nice?