Ouch, ouch!
Papa, hurry! I'm gonna be late!
I'm hurrying.
Papa, Sorata wet the bed!
What?!
Again?
Get changed, quickly.
Papa, the food is burning.
Crap!
I'm home.
Ah, wait a second.
Sorry, sorry.
Welcome home, Mama!
Welcome home.
I'm back.
Want breakfast?
No. I've worked overtime without sleep.
I'm gonna take a nap and go back to work.
Notice anyone
suspicious!?
Call 110 immediately
Take that!
Run!
Why you...
Hey.
Papa.
Don't talk to strangers.
He's not a stranger.
He's our friend. We'll introduce you.
How do you do?
Attorney:
Hakamada Yukio
Daichi-kun and his siblings let me play with them.
We're friends, right?
Yes!
Friends, friends!
It's dinner time. Let's go home.
Yes.
Don't go near that man again.
Why?
He's what you call
a suspicious person.
Suspicious person?
Bye-bye, Mister Suspicious Person!
Bye, suspicious person!
Suspicious person!
Bye-bye!
Huh? "Suspicious person"?
Oh... No, you've got it wrong.
You've got it wrong.
Notice anyone suspicious!?
Call 110 immediately
I'm not suspicious!
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Look, I sewed these today.
Misshapen somewhat, but not bad, right?
Here.
Petition to Divorce
Sakagami Takeshi    Sakagami Izumi
What? Why?
Let's get divorced.
What's with this, all of a sudden?
Do you know what day it is?
It's the day you got fired
from your last job.
I told you that I'd divorce you if you
couldn't find employment in a year.
Hang on a second...
Your name goes here.
Press your seal here.
But, I'm going to job interviews.
I'm making an effort.
I tell my subordinates daily
that their efforts are meaningless
if they don't produce results.
What'll happen if we got divorced?
The kids are still little.
They need a father.
Sorry to say, but the kids
already have a new Papa.
Huh?
He's the president of a partner company.
He's got money, he's reliable,
and he'd be far better for the kids
than a loser father like you.
You were cheating on me?
It's because you're spineless.
That's enough to make
you cheat on me?!
Don't talk so loudly.
Just press your seal here.
Children in wife's custody: Ikegami Daichi, Ikegami Yuna, Ikegami Sorata
You're taking the children
away from me, too?
Of course. I'm their mother.
Or do you think an unemployed,
inadequate man like you
could care for them?
Papa, I have to pee.
Mama will take you.
I gotcha.
Let's go.
Rock paper scissors.
I lost.
You lose.
Rock paper scissors.
Hello.
You again?
Daichi-kun talked to me.
He said, "Papa does all
the household chores,
and takes care of the three of us."
You're a homemaker husband, aren't you?
Something wrong with that?
No, no. Nothing wrong at all.
Daichi-kun bragged that
his Papa is always home.
Well...
my life with my children
might be coming to an end.
I know I'm overstepping
my bounds, but...
are you getting a divorce?
It's all my fault.
I couldn't find
employment for a year,
and my wife was the breadwinner.
But to be honest,
I don't want to leave my children.
Why am I telling you all this?
It's true,
that the mother has the advantage
when it comes to custody battles.
Even more so when
the children are young.
However, if you believe a father
can never be awarded custody,
that is not the case.
What?
With regard to marriage laws,
men and women are treated equally.
You've been unable to
find work for a year.
However, you supported your family
by doing chores and looking
after your children.
I believe you have a good
chance of receiving custody.
Are you serious?
A laid-off father can get custody?
I don't believe it's impossible.
Like I said,
men and women are equal under the law.
In your household,
the mother earns the money
to support the family.
In which case you can get
child support from her,
and you raise your children.
Is that possible?
Yes.
If we can prove that the children
would be happier living with you.
"Prove"?
Who are you?
Me?
I am...
Petition to Divorce
Divorce Chaser
~Let's Turn Your Tears into Money~
Divorce Chaser Episode 8
What Happens to the Children's Future? A Messy Custody Battle
Sakagami Takeshi (42)
Fired from an electrical company a year ago,
and became a homemaker husband.
Wife: Sakagami Izumi (38)
Interior decorator company
managerial assistant
Let's see...
Sakagami Takeshi, 42 years old.
This episode's client:
Sakagami Takeshi
Fired from an electrical
company a year ago,
and became a homemaker husband.
Homemaker Husband
Wife, Sakagami Izumi, 38 years old.
Office landlord:
Toyama Yoshie
Temp:
Shinozuka Rina
Interior decorator company
managerial assistant.
So the male-female roles
reversed after you were fired.
Um... and you two are?
I'm a temp.
I'm the landlord.
Landlord?
Everyone, please mind your own business,
and get back to work.
Yes.
What's the reason for the divorce?
Oh, I'm Sensei's assistant, Nonomura.
Well...
The reason for the divorce is...
That's an easy one!
The wife got fed up with her
jobless, pathetic husband,
and stuck him with a Petition to Divorce.
She jumped ship in
favor of a capable man.
You're being too blunt.
Please get back to your work.
Yes.
Please excuse them.
That's okay.
What they said is true.
I had been warned by my wife,
that if I didn't find employment
within a year after getting fired,
she would divorce me.
I thought she was kidding,
but I guess not.
Hakamada's Assistant:
Nonomura Kanae
She said she's going to remarry
the president of an associate company
as soon as the divorce is official.
That is an intelligent choice.
A hopeful company president
is better than a hopeless husband.
After all, a woman wants
a man to protect her.
Hey, you two!
If you keep it up...
I won't pay the rent or your wages.
I'm very sorry.
That's okay.
I'm useless, so it's my fault.
Sakagami-san, please don't worry.
If your wife admits
to an illicit affair,
we can sue her for compensation.
And the matter of being
useless isn't that important,
when it comes to the
determination of custody.
What's important, then?
In fact, there are three criteria
for determining custody.
Criteria for determining custody
Number one, quality of childcare.
(1) Quality of childcare.
Number two, mental and
physical soundness.
(2) Mental and physical soundness.
And number three,
affection toward the children.
(3) Affection toward the children.
In other words, the advantage
of custody goes to the parent
who does the best at childcare,
who is of sound mind and health,
and who is most affectionate
toward their children.
Yes.
The important thing in deciding custody
is which parent will ensure the children's happiness.
My children's happiness...
Sakagami-san.
Are you confident you can
make your children happy?
Absolutely.
I know can do better than
my wife in that regard.
Understood.
In that case, you are
officially my client.
Compensation. Custody. Child support.
Let's win them all!
I'm in your hands!
Now that it's official,
let's start by gathering material.
Material?
Sakagami
First, pertaining to the
quality of child care:
please keep a detailed record
that clearly shows who is
Takeshi's wife:
Sakagami Izumi
in charge of childcare.
The kids want to go on
a picnic this weekend.
Picnic
PTA meeting 15:00 ~
I'll be on a business trip.
How about on the parent
visitation day the week after?
I can't take a weekday off.
Understood.
Classroom Visit Information for Parents
Only the father will attend
Next, check on your health.
Detailed health evaluation report
Areas of physical examination  Evaluation
Internal examination: Good
Exterior physical examination: Good
Color perception examination: Good
Visual examination: Good
Auditory examination: Good
Blood pressure examination: Good
It is important that there is both
physical and mental soundness.
Health evaluation report
Mr. Sakagami Takeshi
Overall evaluation
And...
Affection toward the children.
Second son:
Sakagami Sorata
Shower them with it as usual,
without any reserve.
Hang in there, Sorata.
Oldest son:
Sakagami Daichi
Oldest daughter:
Sakagami Yuna
Hang in there.
Hello.
You haven't left yet?
I'm on my way home. I'll call you later.
Hello?
You okay?
Child Care Schedule
Is there enough here
to convince the wife?
Probably not.
What?
What's the point of this, then?
Usually, custody is determined
by mutual discussion.
But if they cannot reach an agreement,
it goes to conciliation or trial.
When it comes down to that,
appropriateness of custody
will be determined by a third party.
So you're getting ready in
case it goes to a conciliator.
Newly Published Examples of Legal Cases
Examples of supreme court hearings
The truth is that when it
comes to custody battles,
the mother has a distinct advantage.
The statistics say the mother is awarded custody
approximately 80% of the time.
Custody → Awarded to mother in 80% of cases
But, the mother is guilty
of an illicit affair.
Wouldn't that fact give
Sakagami-san an advantage?
Unfortunately, illicit affairs have
little bearing on custody conciliation,
because it can't be effectively argued
that she can't care for her children,
simply due to adulterous behavior.
So that's how it is...
In that case, what more does
Sakagami-san need to receive custody?
Let's see...
It would really help
if there's a neighbor
who assists him in childcare.
Have a nice day.
Takeshi's big sister:
Hara Misae
Thanks for babysitting today, Sis.
We always have each others' backs.
Good luck at the job interview.
Auntie, when's lunch?
All right, all right,
it's omelettes today.
Okay, let's do this.
Oh!
It's the suspicious person!
Mister Suspicious Person, play with us!
You've got it wrong.
This man isn't a suspicious person.
He's a lawyer.
What's a lawyer?
A lawyer is...
someone who helps those in trouble,
or who can't protect themselves.
Wow, that's like a superhero of justice.
Cool.
If anything troubles you,
you all can talk to Sensei.
He will solve all your problems.
Really? Promise?
Of course.
Pinky promise. If you lie, you have
to swallow a thousand needles.
It's sealed by our fingers.
You promised!
Yes.
Hakamada-sensei.
How was the job interview?
I got rejected. Again.
"Daruma-san... fell down!"
Please cheer up.
The investigation is
making steady progress.
Thank you very much.
At first I thought you
were just suspicious,
but you're actually an amazing person,
Hakamada sensei.
No...
the battle has only just begun.
The most crucial thing will be
when you tell the children about the divorce.
When you tell them, you must not,
under any circumstances
say anything disparaging about your wife.
Yes.
Though she is committing adultery,
though she is not caring
for the children,
Izumi-san is still
their mother, after all.
No matter how much animosity
lies between you two...
the battle between husband and wife
should never be revealed to the children.
I understand.
"Daruma-san fell down."
You're it.
Hakamada Law Office
I have the results of the
wife's background check.
Freelance investigator:
Umemoto Kurumi
She's having a ball with her cheating partner,
while calling it work.
She comes home early in the morning
because she's been in hotels.
What would the kids
think if they found out?
Looks like her daily excesses
are taking a toll on her.
Her health report isn't all that good.
Health Examination Report
Examinee name
Sakagami Izumi   Age 38
Grade
D
Overall evaluation
Follow up essential
In contrast, there is no problem with
Takeshi-san's childcare ability,
state of health,
or affection toward his children.
He's a failure as a man
but a success as a father.
Based on this, Sakagami-san
meets all the criteria.
Sensei, it looks like
he could win custody.
It's too soon to rejoice.
There is still one thing Sakagami-san
is missing to win custody.
What's that?
Financial effectualness.
He must be able to provide for his children
if he is to win custody.
He needs to find work soon,
so he can claim steady income.
It's going to be quite tough
for a man in his 40s to find work.
That's true.
I've got it.
What?
I got a job. Finally.
They gave me an
unofficial letter of hire.
Mister Sakagami Takeshi
Informal notice of hire
No way.
That means...
Looks like we're ready for battle.
Horsey. Horsey.
Okay! Giddyap!
Hey, stop playing around.
Go play in the other room.
Yes.
Sorry about that.
No problem.
This is from summer last year.
We were still a close family, then.
Hey, hey.
When are we going on the picnic?
You promised, remember?
You said we're going on a family picnic.
I wanna go!
I wanna go! I wanna go!
I'm home.
Look after them, Daichi.
Yeah. We're going to the playground.
Bye.
Have fun.
A lawyer? What's going on here?
Hakamada Yukio,
Attorney at Law
Did you hire him using
the money I earned?
Sakagami-san hasn't paid me anything yet.
I will get a portion of the
compensation you will be paying.
Compensation?
Compensation for illicit activities.
This photo was taken
on Saturday, February 15th.
Daichi-kun and children
wanted to go on a picnic,
but you lied and said you
were going on a business trip.
Instead, you were having a secret
tryst with your illicit partner.
This is from the day of
classroom visitation.
This is from the day of the PTA meeting.
You have spent time
with your illicit partner,
under the pretext of working.
And what about it?
That man means more to you
than your children, doesn't he?
So why do you want custody?
I'm their mother. Of course I do.
"I'm their mother. Of course I do."
Is that so?
You're in a position of responsibility
in your profession.
You will continue to work
after you remarry, won't you?
Of course I will.
Who will look after the children, then?
About that...
I have definite plans.
In case Sakagami-san gets custody,
Sakagami-san's sister, who recently
moved to the neighborhood,
will help out with the kids.
Do you have anyone who can help you out?
Well, I...
You don't have anyone.
How do you plan on
raising your children?
I'll hire a babysitter.
You won't raise your own children,
but have someone else do it for you?
Will the kids be happy with that?
Who the hell do you think you are?!
You're a total stranger.
Stay out of our family's business!
I am not a total stranger.
I am Daichi-kun's friend.
Friend?
Yes.
Daichi, hurry up and pack.
Yuna, Sonata, be quick about it.
Stop it.
Let go of me!
Mama, what's the matter?
Let's go to your new Papa's place.
What?
New Papa?
Is our Papa old?
Let's not stay with
this no-good Papa.
Let's live in a new house,
with a new Papa.
You'll have lots of goodies to eat.
He'll buy you tons of stuff you like.
Okay?
I don't want a new Papa.
I'm not going!
Daichi!
I'm not going, either!
I'm not going!
Stop being difficult,
and come with Mama!
Come on.
I don't wanna go!
I'm not going!
Stop talking like that to the children!
I'm coming back for all of you.
I got a call from Sakagami-san.
The wife left the house
without the kids, after our visit.
Isn't that really lucky for us, though?
Leaving the house and her kids behind
will put her at a disadvantage
in the custody battle, right?
Yes, well, that's true, but...
What's wrong, Sensei?
You look worried.
I may have made a huge mistake.
What do you mean?
Your clients are here.
Come on in.
Cute clients at that.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Daichi-kun.
What happened?
Here.
Pocket Money
Please!
Please don't let Papa
and Mama get divorced!
Huh?
Mister,
please make Papa and
Mama be friends again.
Please!
We want to live with Papa and Mama.
We don't want to be separated.
Daichi-kun,
Your Papa and Mama will live separately...
but your Mama will always be your Mama.
You're a family, and that will never change.
Your Papa, Mama, and I
want you all to be happy,
That's the most important thing.
Liar!
If that's the most important thing,
why are they getting divorced?
We want to be together
with Papa and Mama.
Isn't your job, Mister,
to help people in trouble?
Aren't you the superhero of justice?
You said you'd help
me if I'm in trouble.
You promised!
You promised, didn't you?
Daichi-kun, I...
Forget it!
Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's go to your
new Papa's place.
New Papa?
Is our Papa old?
I'm not going!
I don't want
a new papa!
I don't want it!
Children are the victims
in custody battles, aren't they?
Editor at Tokiwa Publishing:
Tabata Misato
Misato-san.
You're crying while reading my manga...
Here.
Cafe waitress:
Mizutani Sara
I see them. I feel them.
Spores spreading out into space.
The cause of your tears is...
cedar.
Or perhaps cypress!
Do you have hay fever?
It will get worse in spring.
My handkerchief will need washing.
Enjoy.
Delicious.
Which means... things aren't going well.
He makes good bread
when he's distressed.
I just heard,
Sakagami-san's wife has
a legal representative.
They called about the conciliation.
I see.
Sensei, are you worrying
about the children?
Yes. You could say that.
Sensei, you did nothing wrong.
I know they'll eventually understand.
Daichi-kun, too.
No. It's my fault.
I told Sakagami-san that the children's feelings
are of utmost importance, and yet,
they heard about the divorce
in the worst way possible.
That's because the wife got
angry and left in a huff.
I'm the one who made his wife angry.
It was my mistake.
Yes, Hakamada Law Office.
Sakagami-san?
What?
Daichi-kun and the others?
They left quite a long time ago.
Hakamada
Law Office
Hakamada-sensei.
Sakagami-san.
They're not at school or the playground.
What about your sister's house?
Not there, either.
I bet it's my wife.
My wife kidnapped them!
Do you know where her new residence is?
I've got the address. Let's go.
Sakagami-san.
The divorce is not yet final.
If the divorce is not yet final
She can't be charged for kidnapping.
If the wife takes the children,
she cannot be charged with kidnapping.
Is that so?
Not only that, if your children's life
with your wife stabilizes,
there's a possibility that
your wife will get custody.
That can't be...
Please, give the children back!
You're stubborn.
I told you, they're not here.
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
If you don't believe me,
go look inside, everywhere.
It's true that I approached them
and asked them to live with me.
In front of that lawyer's office.
But...
They wouldn't come with me.
Really?
Really.
Then, where could they be?
How would I know?
It's your fault for neglecting them!
Don't make it my fault!
It's all your fault!
You'll be held responsible
if anything happens to them!
This is no time for quarreling.
Let's split up and look for them.
Daichi-kun!
Yuna-chan!
Sorata-kun!
Daichi!
Yuna!
Sorata!
Brother, I'm cold.
Let's go home.
No way. We're never going home.
Where's the picnic place?
We'll never get there.
Brother.
What's that?
I'm scared.
Don't worry.
Ghost!
Who are you calling a ghost?!
Hakamada-sensei,
I've got the kids. They're safe.
Thanks to Iron Spy Woman
Marilyn, season 15, episode 7.
Iron Spy Woman
Marilyn
Finding missing persons
is easy as pie.
Because...
99% of missing persons have left
a clue behind in their homes.
Daichi, why did you do this?
I won't know if you don't tell me.
I think Daichi-kun
yearned for this place,
where he and his family went together.
Is that so?
Daichi.
Please, don't give
your Papa a hard time.
You're the one giving us a hard time.
I want to live with Papa
and Mama. That's all!
Papa, you're stupid!
Daichi-kun.
Don't touch me!
I hate you!
Daichi.
You liar!
Mama told me about you.
You're not a superhero of justice!
You're a villain that's splitting
Mama and Papa apart!
I'm not your friend anymore!
Daichi, enough is enough!
Papa, Mama, and Mister,
I hate you all!
I don't believe you did
anything wrong, Sensei.
Huh?
You're doing everything you can
to the best of your ability,
for the sake of
Sakagami-san and the kids.
You've done nothing wrong.
No, he's not entirely incorrect.
From the perspective
of the children,
I am a villain.
Because I'm helping their beloved
Papa and Mama get a divorce.
It's only natural that children
will want to live as a family.
I always felt that way
when I was a child, too.
But, it was the wife's illicit activities
that broke the family apart.
She doesn't participate in household duties,
or caring for her children.
Instead she's out committing adultery.
How can the children be happy
living with a mother like that?
Regardless, she's their
one and only mother.
They want to live together as a family.
Lawyers are powerless
at a time like this.
Sensei is so gloomy lately.
Tomorrow is the conciliation.
I wonder if he's ready for it.
The children running away
might reverberate loudly
at conciliation court.
And if that happens,
the mother will get custody.
If that happens,
how will he pay the three
months worth of rent?
Court of Law
We will now commence the
conciliation hearing.
Family Court: Conciliation Room
Both parties have their
respective attorneys.
Both parties have wished for them
to be present at the discussion.
Hence, we have arranged
the session accordingly.
According to the family conciliator,
it would be appropriate for the mother,
Izumi-san, to get custody of her children.
Izumi's lawyer:
Shoji Akiko
The other day,
there was an incident wherein
the children ran away from home.
The children were under
Takeshi-san's supervision at the time.
If Takeshi-san were to get custody,
something like that could
very well happen again.
I cannot rely on a person like that
to watch over my children.
And with regard to the
financial situation...
pardon me for asking, but Takeshi-san,
what is your annual income?
I plan for it to be around
three and a half million yen.
You recently found a job, correct?
Yes.
At an electrical engineering company.
I will work hard and get promoted.
Or get fired, again.
Izumi-san's annual income
is six million yen.
The partner she would remarry
earns 12 million yen.
That makes a total of 18 million yen.
In terms of affording a good
education for the children...
they are nowhere lacking.
Sensei, are you all right?
If I may.
Please.
Firstly, concerning
the runaway incident.
Izumi-san is the cause of
the children running away.
Izumi-san revealed the
plan to divorce to them,
and thereby hurt her
children's feelings deeply.
What's that supposed to mean?
The most careful one must
be when divorcing...
is when that fact is
revealed to children.
But Izumi-san lost
control of her emotions.
She disparaged Takeshi-san
in front of them,
and deeply hurt her children's feelings.
Let's not stay here
with this no-good Papa.
Let's live in a new house,
with a new Papa.
She could very well have
such outbursts again,
neglecting her children's feelings.
I merely spoke the truth.
There's no point in lying to them.
Next, with regard to the
financial situation.
Indeed, Izumi-san's new partner
is the president of an associate
company, isn't that so?
Have you changed your
mind about marrying him?
I have not.
I see.
We have a problem, then.
His annual income may
very well be 12 million yen.
But his company is in debt
far beyond that amount.
What?
They've been in the red
for several years now.
They have been delinquent with taxes.
Federal Income Tax Delinquency:
Foreclosure Warning
They have unpaid salaries.
Bill for Unpaid Wages
They have been delinquent
in paying back loans.
Final Notice
Thus, their bankruptcy
is only a matter of time.
That can't be.
Eventually, Izumi-san's income
will be redirected to paying back their debts.
You had said you would hire a babysitter
to look after your children.
That is looking rather difficult now.
How will you pay your attorney fees?
Also,
your partner has a child
from his previous marriage.
His ex-wife has custody of the child.
Do you know why he gave her custody?
Because he knows it's better
for the mother to have custody.
Wrong.
It appears he doesn't
like his child much.
His violent actions toward his ex-wife and child
were the cause of their divorce.
The police became involved
on multiple occasions.
Will your children
be happy living with a person like that?
I will now express my
opinion as conciliator.
Gauging the overall situation,
the custody of all three children
should go to the father, Takeshi-san.
Izumi-san, is this agreeable?
I cannot accept that.
If you cannot accept it,
we can dismiss the
conciliation as undetermined,
and you can take it to court to
have a judge make the decision.
You can appeal it,
but I doubt you'd get custody.
It appears both parties
are in agreement.
I now declare the
conciliation as determined—
One moment please.
What is it?
I am sorry to say,
but I think both Sakagami-san and
Izumi-san are unfit to take on custody.
Hakamada-sensei.
If the two of you really
care about your children,
why did you destroy their happiness?
All you were concerned about
was who would win custody.
Children are not your possessions.
The children are innocent.
Children always end up the victims.
If you truly care about your children,
then you must first ask their forgiveness,
for having destroyed their happiness.
You need to keep your heads bowed,
until their wounds are healed.
And you must wish for their happiness,
from the bottom of your heart.
Isn't that where their happiness begins?
You.
You're a lawyer.
What do you know?
This is ridiculous.
We're going to be living
apart from Mama.
It's Papa's fault.
This time it really is.
No! I don't want to
live apart from Mama!
Why is Mama going away?
I want Mama to live with us!
I'm sorry.
Hakamada
Law Office
I'm so glad for Sakagami-san.
He got custody and child support.
But why did he withdraw
the compensation fee?
He must've taken Izumi-san's
future into consideration.
He's a pushover.
If it were me, I'd mercilessly
collect what I could.
I'd chase them down to the pits of Hell!
Me too, to the pits of Hell.
Oh! Rent comes first.
My wages come first.
Um...
Your wages come last.
Never mind that.
Where is Hakamada-sensei?
Oh, come to think of it...
I bet he went into hiding.
Unforgiveable. I'll chase
him to the pits of Hell!
Oh, it's Mister!
Stop, Sorata.
That guy's not our friend any more.
Let's go play over there.
Daichi-kun!
I am sorry.
You're right about me, Daichi-kun.
I was a liar.
I'm not cool at all.
I'm a no-good lawyer.
I couldn't keep my promise
with my precious friend.
I am truly sorry!
Mister.
I already knew you're no superhero.
I knew it.
I knew it, too.
I never thought you were cool, either.
I never thought so.
I never thought so!
One, two...
But we'll play with you anyway. Come on.
Let's go.
Why you...
Wait!
You better run!
Why you...
Hey!
Wait!
Next episode
We're not officially married.
Get your hands
off my husband!
Unofficial wife VS official wife
You're the one
that started this!
Which one is the real wife?
I'm his wife!
Please stop it, both of you!
This drama is a work of fiction
You're both the victims here!