Namu Daishi Henjo Kongo!
"This programme was broadcast
25 October, 2020"
The Quest has started.
Tonight, it's rare animal hunter
Imoto's Japan Tour,
and Ganbareruya's diet project.
"Ayako Imoto, Tetsuro Degawa,
Daisuke Miyagawa, Asako Ito"
"Kazuko Kurosawa, Tomoko Murakami,
Miyuki Oshima"
Now, Imoto, where did you go
this time?
I went to Kagoshima,
the southernmost tip of Kyushu.
- It was one great place.
- That's a nice place.
People from Kagoshima
are interesting.
People were great. I mean the food
and the view are great too,
but I'd like you to focus
on the people I met down there.
- That much?
- Yes.
It was loaded
with interesting characters.
Speaking of Kagoshima, that's where
Lotti Nakaoka did the high dive.
That's right.
- That was Kagoshima!
- That was Kagoshima?
- It wasn't very Kagoshima.
- I don't recall that part.
He has Sakurajima in the background
and did the dive.
That made him into
a top-class comedian.
Fantastic.
Let's take a look.
- The Quest!
- The Quest.
- Let's go!
- Yeah!
Just to verify, you're a woman?
- To a certain extent.
- To a certain extent?
"Imoto Japan tour in Kagoshima"
"Full of interesting characters"
My hand hurts.
Wait one second.
"Ganbareruya diet project
challenge to lose a total of 10kg"
Let's conquer
all 47 prefectures of Japan!
Rare animal hunter Imoto's
Japan Tour!
She headed to Kyushu,
which consists of several islands.
- Hello, hello! Here's Imoto!
- That's Sakurajima.
- I'm currently in Kagoshima.
- That's pretty.
- Now, where am I?
- Hot springs are great down there.
- The usual, find Imoto!
- There she is!
- It's that red...
- That red thing in the centre.
I'm here!
- I'm right here! I'm over here!
- That was good.
The correct answer is, I was part
of the Torii of Kamafuta Shrine.
I'm not someone suspicious.
Kamafuta Shrine is sacred to
Susanoo no Mikoto,
the god of valour.
You come here if you want to win
at something.
Many athletes and celebrities
visit this shrine.
It's a super popular spiritual spot.
This shrine is magnificent too,
but please take a look at this view.
Look at that cool mountain.
It's a beautiful mountain,
known as the Satsuma Fuji.
- Do you want to climb it?
- I do want to climb it.
I want to climb that!
That's a great mountain.
Of course, I want to climb that.
So lots of people come here?
Sawa of Nadeshiko Japan came here
just before the World Cup.
She then went to the World Cup
and won?
- This is one impressive place!
- That's impressive.
Its worship routine is very unique.
You place the lid of a pot
on your head,
you walk through the Torii,
and if you can make a wish
without dropping it,
it's said your wish will come true.
But why did they start worshipping
the lid of a pot?
We asked the locals.
- It came flying here.
- What?
- The lid came flying here.
- They're great.
- What?
- That's a great start.
Didn't you know?
I didn't know.
But those two seem
like they've never heard it before.
- I've never heard it before.
- Oh, you haven't?
It happened a long time ago.
Where did it come from?
Well... from abroad?
From abroad?
The truth is unknown.
When you come here,
you get like this.
You get pregnant?
Yes.
Good luck to you.
I'll do my best.
You'll do your best?
Imoto will make a wish too.
Now, let's get started
with the Kagoshima tour!
First, let's introduce
Kagoshima's best in Japan.
Everyone, what do you think it is?
- They have farmed--
- What? Eggplants?
No! Of course not!
- This is it!
- It's eel.
Wow! They're going at it!
It's eel!
40 percent of domestic eels
are from Kagoshima.
They catch so many?
Their annual production
is about 7,000 tonnes.
Now, this may seem random,
but here's an eel quiz!
Eels have a great something.
Degawa, please answer!
Yes!
I finally realised that I'm now
a regular on the show!
The correct answer is...
"Eels have a great sense of smell"
- Eels have a great sense of smell.
- Really?
Eels have four nostrils.
To compensate for their small eyes,
eels' sense of smell is advanced.
Their sense of smell is just as good
as that of dogs.
These eels are processed into
Kabayaki at the next door factory,
and shipped out all over Japan.
- Should I put it on for you?
- Thank you.
"CEO Yokota"
"Should I put it on for you?"
- Wow!
- It's freshly made?
- It looks super delicious.
- It's huge!
- You can't eat this right away.
- No!
It's now!
Now is the time for me to eat it!
You'll have a contest with someone,
and when you win, you can eat it.
No! I'll have to eat this now!
Of course,
it's an eel grabbing challenge!
She will go against this person!
Wait one second.
Who is that coming?
Who is this? Who is this?
I'm Donko Saigo!
Satsuma clansman Takamori Saigo
was known to have been expert
at grabbing eels.
Mami Matsunobe here is the winner
of Sego1 Grand Prix,
where they determine the best
look-alike of Takamori Saigo.
She displayed great eel grabbing
techniques at the competition.
Just to verify, you're a woman?
- To a certain extent.
- To a certain extent?
"Ha ha ha ha"
The rule is to grab as many eels
as possible in a minute.
What I had in mind is
that our eyebrows are pretty much
the same, right?
Yes!
If Matsunobe loses,
she'll dress up like Imoto.
- I'm really confident here.
- Oh!
- I'm going to win for sure!
Ready, go!
- She wasn't listening at all.
- They're serious.
Eels are hard to grab
since they're slimy.
However, the rare animal hunter
grabbed two to start!
How magnificent!
Matsunobe on the other hand,
is struggling.
Come on!
I'm going to win this!
Imoto grabbed a whole bunch here!
Three, two, one.
Yes!
Oh, no!
Now, the results.
It's 13 against five,
and Imoto wins!
Yes!
That's Imoto for you!
I came starved too!
I'll eat.
Imoto will have an eel bowl
for her victory.
That acrylic board
is about to break.
I feel bad for you.
Now, Matsunobe has a penalty.
Hello!
I'm Matsunobe.
Now, can you tell where I am?
- Let's go! Find Matsunobe!
- Where is she?
- She's over there.
- The face?
I'm here!
I'm right here!
I'm over here!
"Japan's number-one personage
Takamori Saigo"
That step is dangerous.
I'm Imoto!
Cut!
- Wonderful.
- Thank you very much.
I'd say she's more like Hibiki
than Imoto.
Kagoshima is a treasure trove
of seafood besides eels too!
So let's go follow the fishermen
of Kagoshima.
First, it's Amami Oshima's
traditional "drive" fishing.
These are the fishermen
of Ikedamaru.
We will all dive, and we will all
drive the fish into the net.
That person too?
- The boss?
- The boss too?
Boss, the way you wear your cap
is very youthful.
How long have you been doing
this fishing method?
- About 50 years.
- 50 years?
Boss Ikeda is 67 years old,
but is still active.
Let's go!
Ikedamaru does traditional fishing,
but there's someone
with an interesting history.
He was a host at Kabukicho.
Are you originally from here?
Yes, I am.
So you went from Amami
to Kabukicho in Shinjuku?
I was ranked number two, maybe once.
That's amazing.
He's so flashy.
They arrived at the destination.
What exactly is this drive fishing?
One will search for fish.
Yes...
Above him is a person
who signals the boat.
So it's done visually?
You don't use a fish sonar.
Once they find a school of fish,
they set the net along
the direction of the current,
and they drive the fish in there.
Wow, boss!
He's seriously awesome!
Yuya, go on in!
Go on!
He's super cool!
Here!
Nets that have been divided
into sections
are all thrown in.
All the fishermen then grab the nets
with unbelievable speed,
to form them into three dimensions.
Their teamwork is remarkable
even under water,
where communicating is difficult.
Their execution is too good.
It's like a construction process.
This is amazing.
The sack is made.
The trap of over 50 metres
is complete.
They drive the fish
into this sack part of the nets.
What are these?
This is called "Surushika."
- Surushika?
- It's called that.
When we shake this,
then the fish get scared...
So you tease them and scare them?
Imoto, what's the matter?
- Oh, the camera is here.
- What? What's the matter?
- I'm urinating.
- What?
I'm urinating!
She has no other choice.
I feel bad for her.
"Ha ha ha ha"
You only have one chance
with this method of fishing.
The fishermen are determined too!
They're fast.
They're all super-fast.
They proceed underwater right away.
Wait for us!
No one can catch up to them.
When Imoto finally arrived...
Oh, it's all done.
- They have a large catch.
- Amazing!
- Were you keeping up with them?
- No, I couldn't keep up.
- Maybe none of us saw it?
- Of course not.
You can't catch up with a camera.
I wondered why
they couldn't film that.
Why didn't he go
to the trap beforehand?
If he was already positioned
at the trap...
Why would he try to follow them?
You're so right.
He should have been waiting
at the trap.
I wonder why?
Why won't The Quest crew realise
stuff like that?
Next, the most powerful fisherman.
- Hello, nice to meet you. Oh?
- Hello.
I know who you are!
What? You know who I am?
You are Nagano.
Yes, I am.
He's a legend that completed Sasuke,
Makoto Nagano.
He's actually a captain
of a fishing boat in Kagoshima.
That's awesome!
It's incredible.
Could I see your abs too?
Excuse me.
Thank you very much!
This is great!
What's even more incredible
is Nagano's home.
Wow!
What is this?
What?
What is this setup?
This is Nagano's proudest
training set.
I've never seen anybody with
a warped wall at their home.
And the ones who train with Nagano
using this training set are...
Hey, kids! Come out here!
Kids?
- Hello!
- His three kids!
Do you love this since you have it
at home?
Yes.
Let's start the training!
- Amazing.
- Nagano works on strengthening,
using the set he built himself.
His athletic ability is unbelievable
for a 48-year old.
Kids can do this too.
- Can you take the challenge?
- Yes.
Let's go! It's Imoto versus
the eldest son, Kaio.
The one to finish
the 50-metre course faster will win.
Kaio will go first.
Start!
He easily cleared
the quadruple step.
He's light.
- Go on man!
- Amazing!
Amazing!
"Jumping bar"
Kaio has incredible
athletic abilities.
- Amazing.
- He's so light.
Go!
He's now at the pipe slider.
Pipe slider!
- He got it.
- He's amazing.
- Hang in there.
- It slips.
Do it, boy!
Nagano is actually pretty strict
with this training.
- Don't fall!
- You can do it.
Hold on!
Next, he clears the cliff hanger.
Amazing.
Now, the last obstacle
is the warped wall.
Will he succeed?
Grab on!
That was so close!
But he won't give up just yet.
- Will he succeed?
- He got it!
That's it!
He's reached
his physical limits here.
It's frustrating!
You've used up all your strength.
How do you feel right now?
- I'm frustrated.
- Look, he's crying.
"He's crying"
"I'm frustrated"
- Oh, no!
- He was so frustrated
that he cried.
It's fine.
If this was the actual Sasuke,
you'd be super frustrated.
You're right.
You only have one chance.
He's right.
Next, Imoto will go.
- Go for it!
- I will win against Kaio!
She cleared the quadruple steps
with no problem.
Imoto! Imoto!
She can't embarrass herself
in front of the kids.
- But then...
- One more.
- Then--
- Oh, no!
- Her pelvis...
- Oh, no.
- Ouch.
- That must hurt.
I hit my pelvis...
My precious Ayako's Ayako is...
I think I'm going to cry
for a different reason than Kaio...
I'm so ashamed...
Finally, a coverage
of their famous club activity!
The club is at Kagoshima Jitsugyo
High School.
Hello.
There's a lot of you here.
What does your club do?
Men's rhythmic gymnastics club.
Their comical choreography
is very popular.
This is so funny!
Their start is very original too.
They sure are.
Their music and moves are so comical
it makes me smile.
However, the inter-high national
championship was cancelled
due to COVID-19.
So this may not be
what you expected,
but if you would allow me
to join you
in releasing your frustration--
Oh, the bell...
I apologise.
We will deliver
Kagoshima Jitsugyo's
entertaining rhythmic gymnastics
with Imoto!
The students will create a routine
that includes Imoto.
What do you think of Imoto?
It's not easy to learn the routines.
- She's very fast.
- Oh?
Now, please take a look at Kagoshima
Jitsugyo High School with Imoto.
Live commentary will be provided
by the same personnel
as at the actual competition.
I'm Sachiyo Kirita. I'm an announcer
and a former rhythmic gymnast.
Commentary will be done by two-time
national rhythmic gymnastics
competition winner,
here's Kotaro Yamada.
Hello, thank you for having me.
We will now see Kagoshima Jitsugyo
High School team and Imoto.
They appear in Dragon Ball costumes.
- This is great.
- They seem nervous.
A woman is among the male students
with shaved heads.
It's a mysterious sight.
But anything goes
for Kagoshima Jitsugyo High School.
They start with a head stand.
Yes.
It's Kagoshima Jitsugyo's
domino effect.
- They were in sync.
- They were.
They're off with a comical move.
On their back it says "Laugh."
They sure go far for a laugh.
- They sure do.
- Looking good.
Here's a compulsory move
for a team performance, balance.
They're maintaining it well.
Imoto might have been a little off.
Oh, she left the floor,
but another member came in
to do the tumbling segment
of the men's rhythmic gymnastics.
- How you land is important here.
- Amazing.
He had height,
and his landing was good as well.
Now, Imoto is back.
It's like she was out somewhere.
Now, the music changes
to "Ikkyusan."
Now a flip in the air,
synced to Ikkyusan's melody.
That was good.
- The ambiance is there.
- The ambience?
Imoto left again.
Now, they do crossing techniques.
In men's rhythmic gymnastics,
it's important to cross over
while tumbling.
That went well.
Yes.
Let's see what Imoto will do next.
Let's see...
The seven of them are doing
up-down calisthenics.
Now, it's coming.
They will do a forward flip
into the final pose.
It's called Kamehame-ha.
Now, the final pose of this climax.
Let's watch.
Ouch!
I think that's a finish.
- I think it was a good finish.
- Yes.
I think it went well.
I can see my surroundings,
but I think you did great.
I was worried about the ending,
but it went well.
It was super painful.
You went all out. Thank you.
I had so much fun.
Really?
Seventh prefecture,
Kagoshima, has been conquered!
Next up is this!
Ganbareruya will challenge
a diet project.
Yeah!
One day...
I looked at your homepage profiles
the other day,
it said Mahiru weighed 65 kg,
- and Yoshiko weighed 67 kg.
- What's with her face?
I find it hard to believe
that you weigh 65 and 67 kg.
Well, I don't get that at all.
People tell me I'm exactly
what my official homepage says.
Let's weigh them right now!
First, we'll start with Mahiru.
"Her profile says 65kg"
She weighs 71.1kg.
No way!
When I weighed myself yesterday,
it said sixty...
- five or so.
- Stop lying!
Next is Yoshiko.
"Weight on her profile, 67kg"
She's 10 kilograms heavier
than her official weight,
she weighs 78.7kg.
Since they eat what they want
to eat as much as they want to eat,
their weight continues to rise.
So they will challenge to lose
10 kilograms of combined weight,
within a month.
We prepared several different
programmes for them to try.
The first one is pole dancing.
- Amazing!
- Amazing.
That's incredible.
Pole dance requires muscle strength
to support your own body,
and a core for balance.
- It makes it perfect for a diet.
- I see.
Pole dancing has an impression
of a sexy performance,
but recently, they're aiming
to make it an Olympic sport,
so competitions are held
all over the world.
Amazing.
We want the two of them to master
a double's move like this,
and perform at the end
of their diet.
Amazing.
It will be taught
by world champions,
- the pole dancing duo Manjushage.
- They're so cool.
Could a fat person do this?
We originally started it
- for weight loss.
- Yes.
- What? Is that true?
Then does that mean
you were like our size?
Well, roughly yes...
Roughly.
Right.
The first move to learn
is the basic lock position.
You'll sit crossing your legs.
Then lower your hips,
and your core should be
twisted.
Thighs are locking you in place,
so when you extend your left leg,
it will stop in place.
Unless you can stabilise the pole
and the body like this,
it's impossible to learn any skills.
- Let's extend your left leg.
- What's with your mid-section?
- You're up in the air! Good!
- Great!
Yoshiko cleared it with no problem.
- Is it easy?
- That's it!
Yes...
Mahiru on the other hand...
- How about Mahiru?
- Your thighs aren't tight enough.
Bring your thighs together.
Could you twist your waist
towards me?
Mahiru's body is too stiff,
and she can't hold the pole.
Oh, that's too much space.
Let's take a break for now.
I can't do this.
It's impossible. I can't do it.
It's fine. You're fine.
It's impossible.
Even if you say that,
we still have to do it.
The instructor is shocked too!
See?
Next, they will try a double's skill
where one climbs up the pole
on the partner's shoulders.
Oh? There.
Aw...
This is nothing but abuse to Mahiru.
Amazing! It's perfect!
- Just give me a second.
- It hurts.
- I'm sorry.
- That's not safe.
I'm sorry.
Wait one second.
My hand hurts.
- Wait one second.
- What is that?
Stop that with your legs!
A monster has appeared.
I'm too tired.
What do I do?
This is no joke.
That's so gross.
That monster...
They try several
different techniques...
- I did it!
- I managed!
They can't do anything right.
This is hard.
- This is hard.
- It must be hard.
It is hard.
Every time I use the pole,
I see my ugly self in the mirror.
- You have no choice.
- It's so frustrating.
- It's frustrating.
- It's like your theme song.
I hate this fat here!
Their second programme is training.
You don't touch anything.
They will train
with a personal trainer
10 minutes a day, every day.
In addition, dietary restrictions.
- That would be hard.
- Show me your fist.
That is how big your servings
of rice should be per meal.
- For one meal?
- Yes.
- That's so small.
- It's tiny.
They change their gluttonous life
to having meals
with more vegetables.
And finally, fasting.
We are planning on three days
and four nights.
Wow!
So we won't eat anything
for three days four nights?
Yes.
Recently, fasting facilities
have become popular
as a place where they can diet,
as well as give a break
to the stomach and intestines,
to detox the body and the mind.
And the place where they will
discipline the body and the mind
while fasting is...
Chisoku-an in Kure, Hiroshima.
It's in the middle of the mountains
with barely any cell reception.
They offer fasting as part
of Buddhist training.
- Hello.
Hello.
This is Koho Yuhara,
the Buddhist priest.
Unlike the other facilities,
we don't just fast here.
There's more than fasting?
We walk the mountains
and meditate under the waterfall.
I want you to think about your
future life before you go home.
I do have parts of me
that I want to change.
I compare myself to others.
That's the worst thing you can do.
I compare myself to NiziU.
I want to be like NiziU.
- It's impossible.
- I just want to be NiziU.
That is not good at all.
That's the worst thing you can do.
Right.
Are we the only ones
doing the fasting?
You know how the crew should unite?
So now the staff will participate
in the fast as well.
Let's do this!
Hip hip V!
Do it!
First, they'll weigh themselves
before fasting.
AD Uchiyama
and Director Maekawa's weight
are as noted.
And Ganbareruya, who's been
on a diet programme for two weeks.
First, it's Mahiru.
It's less?
She's lost three kilograms.
That's amazing.
You're so modest.
Next is Yoshiko.
Oh!
"Before the diet, 78.7kg"
- She lost five kilograms.
- They're almost at their goal!
Yes!
No way! I've lost a lot!
The two of them have successfully
lost eight kilograms already!
What do we do? If we fast now, we'll
lose about three to four kilograms.
Will they be able to reach their
goal of 10 kilograms by fasting?
Today is your first day,
so we'll have you start making
your juice for dinner.
We can eat today?
- It's juice.
- Oh, juice?
It's fasting, but to supplement
the minimum amount of energy,
they're allowed to drink
carrot juice three times a day.
We shall gratefully eat.
Whether one likes it or not,
you will only get one glass
of carrot juice per meal.
How is it?
It's delicious.
I don't know if I can endure this.
It's fine.
- Her personality has changed.
- Let's do our best.
- Mahiru, you've changed already.
- Amazing.
She's easily influenced.
Their first day is now over.
- Okay.
- Nine o'clock?
Second day of fasting.
They wake up at five in the morning.
- That's early.
- Five in the morning?
Komyo Shingon.
They chant Buddhist sutras
at the main temple.
"Chant Buddhist sutras"
And immediately,
they go on a mountain walking
training called "Kaihogyo."
They don't give them time to think.
This is Tatsu, their guide.
This is your first day,
so I'll walk slowly,
but it's not a morning stroll.
It's a training called Kaihogyo.
Yes.
It's not a morning stroll.
- They're headed for Kobo-ji Temple,
- Aren't they going fast?
- close to the summit of Mt. Noro.
- He's moving fast.
I'm hungry.
It's an hour walk. It's a long way
to walk on an empty stomach.
There's a great shooting spot.
Over there...
we'll go in from that area
next to the bathrooms.
You can go on the opposite bank.
How about you get a shot
from that side too?
Taki is very familiar
with TV coverage.
Once I see the videographer,
- I'll start walking.
- I see.
He's considering
the camera angle as well.
They walked for an hour...
- Looking great!
- That's beautiful.
They arrive at their destination,
Kobo-ji Temple.
This place is where Kobo Daishi
Kukai came twice to train.
This is beautiful.
The view is magnificent.
We are above the clouds.
What's seen from the vista point
at elevation of 800 metres
is the beautiful Seto Inland Sea.
They can even see Mt Ishizuchi,
far away in Shikoku.
Consider how it would look
before you sit down.
Consider how it looks
before you sit down...
Please take a look at this scene,
with Taki's approval!
After they meditate here
for 30 minutes...
they walk again for an hour
to head back to the hall.
It's hard on empty stomach.
Someone is grilling fish.
I know. Someone
is grilling fish somewhere.
They smell it.
- I smell someone grilling fish.
- Their sense of smell is better.
- We're back.
- Welcome back.
We just came back.
Are you perhaps grilling fish?
Yes, I'm grilling it.
"Ha ha ha ha"
Oh, that must be nice.
However, trainees can only have
carrot juice.
Right, they're fasting right now.
During their training,
they can't have any solid food.
When I was climbing the mountains,
I was more exhausted than anything,
so I only thought about that.
Now that I'm back here, only thing
I can think now is that I'm hungry.
That's natural.
In that case, we'll introduce
Hiroshima's highlights
during their free time to keep
their mind off their hunger.
- We are here at Tomo no Ura!
- Who are they?
- What is that?
- What are they?
Tomo no Ura in Hiroshima
is said to be the place
where Director Hayao Miyazaki
spent time
to get his idea
for the movie "Ponyo."
It's amazing.
What a beautiful view.
It's exactly like Sosuke
and his mother, Lisa's town.
It's exactly like the animation.
- Is that so?
- Oh?
So you must be Ponyo, right?
You're Ponyo, right? I get that.
Who am I?
- Sosuke.
- Sosuke?
"Ponyo like Sosuke!" she says,
and hugs him like this.
What these two will try is...
- Ghibli plank.
- What?
It's a challenge where they
recite a whole scene
from a Ghibli movie
while doing a plank.
- You mean from Ponyo?
- What's with that face?
The only Ghibli movie I've seen
is Spirited Away.
Could you change it
to Spirited Away?
We have No-Face too.
So the title for this challenge
is "Spirited Away" now.
If they fail, they will be victims
to a bunch of mouse traps.
Now, let the Ghibli plank start.
This bath is reserved
for out filthiest guests.
It's caked with sludge.
This tub needs an herbal soak.
Sen, go get a tag from the foreman.
I can't waste that on you.
Good morning.
Feeling refreshed?
Certainly! A luxurious sulphur soak!
No point in standing there.
Scrub with your hands.
But it has to be an herbal soak.
You sure are dense.
Oh... A fragrant bath coming up.
Relax and enjoy.
Oh, no!
"No-Face bows to Chihiro"
Hello, foreman here.
Yes...
Thank you so much!
Go ahead and let go.
I'll get our breakfast!
Okay!
Well... The bath is not ready yet.
Ouch! Ouch!
Yoshiko couldn't hold it.
She failed.
I can't do it with that!
My bad.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it with this crew.
So they learned that from Ghibli,
and No Face made an appearance.
We heard the mouse traps go off,
and we heard the videographer fart.
What was with that footage?
That was a mysterious three minutes.
That was a mystery. It was the most
mysterious three minutes.
I'll watch it again Sunday night,
with No Face.
- The mysterious three minutes?
- Yes, the mysterious three minutes.
- It was a mystery, right?
- I'll watch it again.
I'll reflect on it again
when I watch it Sunday night.
Third day of fasting.
They will have miso soup
with no solid food.
- That much?
- It must be tasty though.
Headaches and muscle cramps
are common
during fasting
due to a lack of sodium,
so they supplement salt intake with
miso soup with no solid ingredients.
"Sodium"
It's delicious.
This miso soup...
is the best I've ever had.
After their breakfast, they head
to the highlight of fasting,
the waterfall meditation.
Waterfall meditation...
- Namu Fudo Myo-o!
- She's pretty loud.
- It's not hitting her at all.
- It's not hitting Mahiru at all.
- Namu Fudo Myo-o!
- It's hitting Taki only.
All the water is hitting Taki.
- Namu Fudo Myo-o!
- It's not hitting her at all.
Yoshiko is at her limits
with hunger.
Takoyaki! Okonomiyaki!
Beef fillet steak!
- Gizzards, gizzards, gizzards!
- Gizzards?
- Gizzards.
- She wants it that badly.
- But an incident happens...
- What happened?
Today is your third day,
so I will have you recite
"Unbeaten by the rain."
This is an assignment that's given
to all participants of this fast.
Please learn it.
I already know this.
Why?
I learned it
when I was in primary school.
You still remember it?
Yes.
Will one of you go ahead and recite?
Unbeaten by the rain.
Unbeaten by the wind.
Unbowed by the snow
and the summer heat.
Strong in body.
Free from greed.
Without any anger.
Always serene.
Mahiru does it perfectly.
Such a person I want to be.
That was 100 percent.
- Thank you very much.
- That's wonderful.
Amazing.
- Next.
- There she is.
- Is she okay?
- Actually, Yoshiko...
she completely forgot
about this recitation.
Whatever happens, consider yourself
last, always put others first.
She's telling her.
Understand from your observation
and experience.
- Never lose sight of these things.
"The proprietress of
a Japanese style restaurant"
Completely like the proprietress
of a Japanese style restaurant.
The Buddhist priest is listening
to her with his eyes closed,
so he doesn't notice.
Being neither praised...
- nor a burden.
Such a person I want to be.
All right.
Good job!
It was 99 percent, though.
- But the content
- Thank you very much.
was 100 percent.
- That was great.
- He knows it.
- There aren't that many people
- Then...
- that could get 100 percent.
- Oh?
No way.
What? Is she crying?
That's not their theme song!
Don't be rude.
You should reflect
on your own actions.
- Mahiru was telling me.
- Reflect on your own actions.
I thought that Buddhist priest
will be upset with me.
When I looked up, he said
"That was great!"
He didn't realise that Mahiru
was whispering the prose to me.
So I felt really...
guilty and I didn't know what to do.
That's why I was crying.
What's the matter?
Turn around.
That's how you get rid of spirits.
"The Buddhist priest thought she
was possessed by something"
- I'm sorry.
- You're crying again?
I'm sorry.
So...
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
I thought about telling him
several times.
Why didn't you?
The fact that you had conflicted
feelings means something.
Will I be able to change?
Yes, you can change.
Will I be punished?
You will be punished.
Then their final day came.
I'm sorry. I have something I need
to apologise to you about.
- What is it?
- Oh, you're going to tell him?
Yesterday...
I didn't...
remember to...
learn "Unbeaten by Rain."
You remembered it.
I cheated.
Then do you want to try it now?
Yes, I learned it.
Okay.
- Really?
- That's good.
Unbeaten by rain.
Unbeaten by wind.
Unbowed by the snow
and the summer heat.
Strong in body.
Free from greed.
Without any anger.
Always serene.
With a handful of brown rice a day,
we have Miso and a small amount
of vegetables.
Whatever happens, consider yourself
last, always put others first.
Understand from your
observation and experience.
Never lose sight of these things.
In the shadows
of the pine groves in the fields,
live modestly under a thatched roof.
In the East,
if there is a sick child,
go there and take care of them.
In the West,
if there is an exhausted mother,
go there and relieve her
of her burden.
In the South,
if there is a man near death,
go there and comfort him,
and tell him, "Be not afraid."
In the North, if there are
arguments and legal disputes,
go there and persuade them
it's not worth it.
In a drought, shed tears.
In a cold summer, carry on.
Let them call me a fool.
Being neither praised nor a burden,
such a person I want to be.
Good job.
Please hold on
to your upstanding heart.
- Yes.
- Good for you.
Now, the final weigh-in!
How many kilograms
did the four of them lose,
as a result of three days
and four nights of fasting?
First, AD Uchiyama.
"AD Uchiyama,
Before fasting, 66.6kg"
64.0kg.
Good job!
Uchiyama lost 2.6 kilograms.
Next is the director Maekawa.
How did she do?
63.5kg.
"Director Maekawa
Before fasting, 64.5kg"
One kilogram.
Were you eating something?
Next up is Mahiru.
"Before fasting, 68.2 kilograms"
66.7kg.
That means you lost 1.5kg.
Amazing.
I was told you lose
about a kilogram a day.
I feel like I'm more bloated
than before I started.
You're right. I don't have
the urge to go to the bathroom,
and I feel all the water I took in
is accumulated in the body.
We're all girls here.
Finally, it's Yoshiko, the only one
over the weight of 70kg...
"Before fasting, 73.6 kilograms"
You lost 1.3 kilograms.
Being the fattest one here...
Honestly I thought I'd lose
the most out of all of us.
- It was so hard too...
- That's true.
Maybe your body didn't change,
- but your heart changed, right?
- What is up with her?
It's not "Fasting had no meaning."
Through fasting,
- you've realised many things.
- Is she okay?
I'm sorry. You smell like a person
who hasn't had anything to eat.
That's a realisation too.
Fasting...
makes your breath smell bad.
Nevertheless, they still
went over their initial goal,
and was successful in losing 10.8kg.
Amazing!
They continued to do their best
for two more weeks.
Their one month challenge was over!
How much did Ganbareruya change
over a month?
Time to unveil!
What? That's amazing.
- They've lost lot more weight,
- I'm impressed.
- two weeks after the fasting.
- Mahiru is pretty.
Her makeup...
Yoshiko could pass for a Miss Japan
with the way she stands.
What's with them?
Before their final weigh-in...
What's with their swimsuit?
Please take a look at their
pole dance performance,
after a month of training.
There they are!
"Roppongi Hills Sky Deck"
- What a beautiful night view.
- It said "Roppongi Hills."
That's a great place.
First, a spinning technique
to show their teamwork.
That's pretty!
Amazing.
- Amazing.
- Incredible.
- That's great.
- And...
Mahiru wraps her arms around
Yoshiko and rotates.
Amazing!
Wonderful!
Before they went on a diet,
their body was too heavy to lift,
but now they're able to control it
using their own muscles.
And what's great is that the monster
is nowhere to be seen.
Amazing.
That's so graceful.
That's amazing.
This is amazing.
- Amazing.
- From here,
they will do a spinning trick
together on a pole.
This is pretty.
That's amazing.
That's incredible.
Amazing.
Then the finale...
Yoshiko will do a Y-balance
on Mahiru's thighs.
That's amazing.
Incredible.
That's incredible.
- That was amazing.
- That's incredible.
The last technique will test
their trust.
Smile. Keep smiling.
- Smile.
- Looking good.
What? You did this one?
Amazing!
It's amazing!
What a great smile.
Amazing.
Now, time for that fateful weigh-in.
Let's do this...
- First, Mahiru will be weighed.
- She definitely lost some weight.
- Before, she weighed 71.1kg.
- She looks completely different.
How much does she weigh?
I lost weight!
I lost a lot of weight!
- Amazing.
- Mahiru
- lost 6.8kg in a month.
- That's incredible.
Is this really me?
I've never been 64kg before.
You weigh less than your official
weight listed on your profile.
You're right.
Next up is Yoshiko.
She weighed 78.7kg before her diet.
"Before her diet, 78.7kg"
Wow!
Amazing!
Yoshiko lost 10.8kg all by herself!
Amazing.
From the side,
the difference is clear.
She lost a lot!
Amazingly, they lost way over
their original goal,
and lost a total of 17.6kg.
They lost a lot of weight.
If you want to be the person
you want to be,
then what's important is
not to compare yourself to others,
- but to face yourself.
- Be quiet!
I realised that.
That's it for
Ganbareruya's diet project.
Amazing.
- Amazing.
- You haven't gained any back?
- Right?
- You haven't gained it back?
Well...
I guess I got back about two,
three, four, five..
You've gained quite a bit
of weight back already.
I'm thinking of seven to eight
kilograms soon too.
Don't be like that.