"This programme aired
on 3rd of January, 2021"
The Quest Calendar Project!
Yeah!
Members of The Quest
visit different parts of the world,
and challenge taking
magnificent photographs.
Those photographs are compiled
to create The Quest 2022 calendar.
The Quest Calendar Project.
One day in October, 2020.
It's been a while, but we'll do
the mountain climbing club now.
Let's climb a mountain!
Nukita, thank you very much.
Your presence here says it all.
- We won't go abroad, right?
- Right.
This time, we'll head to a place
called Kurobe in Toyama.
Does it have something to do
with Kurobe Dam?
They have this secluded area
called Shimonoroka there.
Is that a mountain?
Shimono hallway?
Shimonoroka is a secluded area
in Kurobe.
It's in the Eastern area of Toyama.
It starts from Kurobe Dam,
the highest dam in Japan.
Then they go through Kurobe Gorge,
the deepest gorge in Japan,
along a 30-kilometre path.
No one entered that area
until the Taisho period.
It's the most secluded area.
It's said to be secluded,
because its hiking season
is just one month out of a year.
What? You can only hike there
one month out of the whole year?
Its trail is only open for a month
from late September to late October.
Some years, you can't even go in.
It's very much admired
by mountain climbing enthusiasts.
I think the colouring of the leaves
would be beautiful right now.
That's why we're doing it now,
although it's for
the New Year's special.
By the way, have you been there?
- When was that? Around 19...
- 19...
72?
I wasn't even born yet.
- You weren't born yet?
- No, I wasn't born yet.
The plan is to take a photograph
for the calendar at "Odaiko,"
a scenic spot in Shimonoroka.
In addition, they'll head over
to nearby Toyama,
to Oyama in Tateyama Mountain Range
to get a photograph of the sunrise.
Let's climb to the top and show
a beautiful scenery to everyone.
I look forward to doing this.
I'll do my best!
Toyama's secluded area and
the sunrise from the mountain top...
How will the first photograph
for the calendar turn out?
October, 2020.
Mountain climbing team met at Kurobe
Dam to head out to Shimonoroka.
This is the New Year's
mountain climbing special.
This time, we are going to
Shimonoroka in Toyama.
What do we have to be
cautious about?
The path is made
by carving out bedrock,
so it's very narrow.
So, basically,
we'll travel in a straight line?
- We won't walk next to each other.
- Right.
How will it be for the camera crew?
Would it be hard to film?
It would be hard to film.
You can only get the back, right?
Most of it would be like that.
Is that going to be okay?
This is a special programme.
Imoto has 30 minutes
for her segment.
If we don't get 30 minutes,
we'll climb a few more mountains.
No, I won't do that!
She ends up going to Shimonoroka and
Oyama in Tateyama Mountain Range,
but she was hoping of just
going to Shimonoroka this time.
Right.
No, no, we should get at least
30 minutes' worth of film.
I figured it would be good if we
could get 10 minutes from here.
Ten minutes?
Do you know how dangerous this is?
The Ishizakis get some time
for the footage as a couple.
That's funny.
The camera crew
won't be able to film much.
Then why did we come here?
Now, let me explain their climbing
process to Shimonoroka.
They are currently at the lower part
of Kurobe Dam.
They will take a path of
30 kilometres
along the Kurobe Gorge.
They will spend a night in a tent
on the way.
Their goal is to go to Odaiko,
a scenic spot that's further ahead.
They won't be climbing
to the top of the mountain,
but they will have magnificent views
at their destination.
By the way, how long are we planning
to walk today?
Twelve to 13 hours.
- That's long!
- That much?
Right now, my emotional status
is leaning towards the negative,
but do you have anything positive
to say that will motivate me to go?
What's often said is,
there are no injuries at Kurobe.
That's great. No injuries in Kurobe?
That's a nice phrase.
They have no injuries,
but when you fall,
Oh?
it's way beyond an injury.
That's one horrible information.
What, they say that
about this place?
It's so you don't get injured.
It's either you die or you live?
Terrifying Shimonoroka,
what kind of a place is it?
Let's do our best.
Let's go with safety first.
They start off walking
in a narrow forest trail.
Amazing, the leaves have
changed their colours.
It's beautiful.
Look at that rock surface.
It doesn't seem that demanding.
- I'm thinking it's a hallway.
- It's a hallway.
This is the deepest gorge in Japan
surrounded by mountains,
of 3,000 metres in elevation.
Their course is obstructed
by treacherous ground.
I thought it was different
from an ordinary mountain.
The first thing that popped
into my eyes was
a sign at the entrance that said,
"Frequent fatal accidents."
That freaked me out.
This is super scary.
Frequent fatal accidents.
It says walking while doing
other things is dangerous.
Like while you are talking,
or while you're enjoying the view,
and while you're taking a picture.
It's dangerous, so don't do it.
Then what are we going there for?
Are we going to be okay here?
We'll be doing everything
we shouldn't do.
It was very unusual in 2019,
they had five fatal accidents
in 11 days.
An elderly person
should never go there alone.
What if other shows asked you
to take them as well?
I won't. I'll refuse.
The Quest's mountain climbing club's
teamwork of over 10 years,
I mean, there's history.
There's experience.
It would be impossible for
the other shows. It's impossible.
The dreadfulness of Shimonoroka
is gradually revealed.
That's something else.
We'll be walking that area.
- It's like walking along the cliff.
- It's not a path.
That's one scary path.
This is dangerous.
- They don't have any railing?
- They have nothing.
This is a completely different path
from regular mountain climbing.
From this point onwards, they'll
observe the rapids on their right
while walking along a V-shaped
precipitous cliff.
That's scary.
They don't have any fence
for sliding prevention.
The only thing they have is...
- This is the support I mentioned.
- This?
- Yes.
I feel super uneasy.
This thin four millimetres wire
placed at random places
are the safety tethers.
Even so,
we should definitely hold it.
I'm going to put my whole weight
on this?
- It's dangerous.
- It is.
- Let's be cautious.
- Yes.
Why is there a thin path
in this deep gorge to start with?
It was about 100 years ago.
Power companies from back then
dispatched men
to determine the feasibility
of building a dam here.
They spent nine years
to build Shimonoroka,
a path that's wide enough for
one person in this secluded area.
That's incredible.
It then became popular
as a mountain climbing path
because of this rare scenery.
What a superb view.
It could be in a PV.
This gorge, rocks,
and the autumn leaves,
create such beautiful scenery.
The path they take
isn't always levelled.
This is not what I expected
from this hallway.
I thought the path
would be more like a hallway.
Unexpectedly,
I was told we'll be descending,
but we're ascending right now.
Overall route descends,
but as you see,
it repeats going up and down.
That's tough.
In addition, this narrow path.
It requires physical strength
as well as strong focus.
No injuries in Kurobe.
I get it now.
Then...
Someone is coming.
A group is coming.
These are our support members.
They each carry about
20 kilogrammes of baggage
- to support the team.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Do you understand how this requires
thorough preparation?
There's still some snow left.
It doesn't melt in the summer.
It melts during the summer?
No, there's more during the summer.
The least amount of snow is seen
during autumn.
Oh, is that how it is?
It'll snow
before these are all gone.
- That's when we can climb here?
- Yes.
It really is limited
during the year.
Wow, this is scary!
Three hours since they started,
they now head to the core
of Shimonoroka.
You only have your hands.
- This is scary.
- No!
The only support are your own legs
and a thin wire along the rock wall.
This is scary!
You've got to be kidding me.
Now, we climb up a ladder.
The ladder is perpendicular
to the ground.
A log ladder is placed at locations
where a path couldn't be made.
It's better not to look down.
Wow, it's high!
This height is scary.
At the same time,
the determination of those men who
cleared this path is astonishing.
- Seriously.
- This is amazing.
After walking for five hours,
they arrived at Kurobebessantani,
six kilometres away from the start.
Okay. Be alert. It's a danger zone.
From here, it's said to be the most
dangerous area of their route.
Five hours since they started,
they arrived at Kurobebessantani,
six kilometres away from the start.
Okay. Be alert. It's a danger zone.
From here, it's said to be the most
dangerous area of their route.
This can't be just 10 minutes.
This is super scary.
The rocks are slippery, too.
The path is 50 centimetres wide.
Letting your guard down for a second
could be fatal.
- That's not a path.
- I know.
By the way,
I have no ropes attached to me.
How come Ishizaki is the only one
with all that?
They're looking after him.
That much?
They are taking care of the husband,
but the wife is on her own.
That's not the show's decision,
but the Ishizakis' decision.
This is super scary.
For the next three kilometres,
this is how the path is going to be.
That's narrow.
It's so high up.
How much is this?
That's amazing.
It's about 100 metres.
It's almost 100 metres, right?
It sucks you in.
This part is no joke either.
The ceiling is low here, too.
Watch your head, too.
You shouldn't just pay attention
to your feet.
Accidents could occur
from helmets and backpacks
hitting the rocks.
This is scary.
I have to stay alert.
That's something else.
However, this impressive
panoramic view
shows how wonderful
nature's environment is in Japan.
- Amazing!
- It's beautiful.
This is so cool.
Amazing. Japan is amazing!
This path is dreadful,
but what's even more dreadful is...
What?
From this point on,
it's just a simple repetition
of what we've shown so far.
It's "same as above,"
and it won't make the final footage.
After they've walked for 13 hours,
they arrive at their destination
at a cabin to spend the night.
We are here
at Asohara Hot Springs cabin.
Cabin is closed during this season,
so we'll spend the night in a tent,
and we'll leave for the second half
of the climb tomorrow.
So is this what you look forward to,
as it says here?
Hot springs.
There's a hot spring here?
- It feels nice.
- She's in it already?
It's heaven.
This is heaven.
You all took a bath together?
- This is so extravagant.
- Why?
Why do I have to enjoy it
with all these mountaineers?
This really is a treat.
Yes, it is.
Not everyone can make it here.
It's a treat. Only the one
who walked the path can enjoy this.
- Good work. Thank you very much.
- Good work.
We took our bath,
and it's time for dinner.
- That's the best.
- Tonight's dinner is
Tonjiru soup made by the owner
of the cabin.
That's the best.
It's super delicious!
It's so delicious I want to cry.
This is nice.
We've been trying too many
winter mountains before.
Are we above heaven?
- It's paradise.
Don't die.
The second day of mountain climbing.
This is the second half.
The gorge is wider today, and we'll
enjoy the scenery on the right.
I think the autumn leaves
will be pretty with colours.
It's more open,
so you can use a drone to film it.
Right, I want to use the drone.
They are approximately
five kilometres to Odaiko,
their scenic spot.
They'll challenge to get the best
photograph for the calendar.
The path is starting to look
different.
This path looks like
it's carved out of a rock.
This is not naturally made.
It's definitely man-made.
A stretch of road
on the face of a mountain
was made by people
about 100 years ago,
by carving rocks off the mountain.
It's called the horizontal trail.
It stretches over 13.6 kilometres.
I think we'll be at Odaiko soon.
And the best scenic spot
on the horizontal trail is here,
at their destination, Odaiko.
Amazing.
We'll just use this part
from this trip.
What are you saying?
This is the only part we can use?
We came to capture this.
Well, yes.
This is amazing.
On the right...
This is no joke. I'm nervous.
This is scary.
Wow, be careful over here.
This is so high! It's so scary.
It's scary!
A path made by carving out a cliff
that symbolises Kurobe Gorge.
In terms of a high-rise, I think
it's higher than Nippon TV building.
It really is a path
made by carving out the rocks.
It's for one person only.
This is dangerous.
It doesn't have any safety railing
or anything.
You only have your own feet,
and a support of your own hands.
This really is the path
of self-reliance.
Changing autumn leaves add colour
to the cliff and the gorge.
We took a potential picture
for the calendar with a drone.
"Ayako Imoto in Toyama,
Odaigo at Shimonoroka"
It's tiny.
"Secluded area
of Shimonoroka Odaiko"
That path was something else.
Scary!
- That's amazing.
- Take a look at that.
Nukita, be careful!
It's more scarier
to watch the others.
But because of that,
you get to enjoy
the biggest rock wall in Japan,
and the gorge.
This concludes the two-day
mountain climbing of Shimonoroka.
The total distance travelled
was 30 kilometres.
They walked a total of 23 hours.
I'm exhausted.
This hot springs is great.
- You went again?
- It was really long.
What shall we do next?
Wait one second.
This won't do?
Shimonoroka is not good enough?
We walked for 23 hours.
But can't make it
into a 30-minute footage?
That's a major problem.
They walked for 23 hours,
but the mountain climbing footage
is just 14 minutes up to this point.
It was filmed,
but only one percent of it was used.
We walked this much.
I'm going to tell Uchimura
as soon as we get back.
I'm going to say something.
I'm going to have Uchimura
handle it.
I'm going to have the superiors
say it.
Could you say,
"Please watch the second half?"
I don't want to.
Mountain climbing special...
Please watch the second half.
Go ahead.
Oh, we're here.
We're here.
What is this place?
What's with this view?
It's all snow here!
They came to Tateyama Mountain Range
in Toyama.
Their challenge is to get a picture
of the sunrise at the summit.
Hello, everyone. It's been a month
since I went to Shimonoroka.
That time, autumn leaves were
beautiful with colours, but look.
I'm here on a snowy mountain
right now.
It didn't work?
We didn't have enough time?
- No.
- We didn't?
I did my research.
I searched for old footage
of Shimonoroka,
but my judgement is that Shimonoroka
doesn't have much material.
That path has horrible
cost performance.
Nakajima, our camera crew
went to Shimonoroka,
and he was a victim as well.
You went there a week before us?
For a show?
I went filming quite a lot,
but it only came out
to three minutes.
Three minutes?
Let's not go there anymore.
We learned our lesson.
Shimonoroka won't produce
enough minutes.
So which summit are we climbing
to see the sunrise?
- It's behind us.
- Behind us.
Didn't we go there in the past?
It's Oyama.
I know that one.
It'll probably be fast.
It snowed, so it will be easier.
I see.
I think that won't have
enough minutes either.
I think we'll be on the summit,
just like that.
I think that's how tough
this mountain is.
They will stay at Tateyama Murodo
Sanso located at the foot of Oyama.
They will depart before dawn
to climb to Oyama's summit
at 3,003 metres
to see the sunrise.
However, 2:00 in the morning.
The weather suddenly changes
as they prepare to leave.
Right, it's going to rain.
It's starting to rain.
It's unfortunate, but we can't do
anything about it today.
They are here for the sunrise.
They'll have to wait for the weather
to improve.
However, they don't have much else
to do, so let's do this segment.
The Quest's
Let's Go Mountain Climbing!
We will present climbing items
recommended by Kuraoka, the guide.
What is this?
What?
- It's made of a mesh material.
- What is this?
It's a shirt.
It looks very indecent.
This shirt is very hot
among mountaineers.
It's "drynamic" mesh.
It's a mesh undershirt
that keeps skin dry,
and maintains body temperature.
It's a shirt that could be worn
every season.
When you layer
and climb a mountain in winter,
- you sweat.
- You do sweat.
This keeps you dry,
so you don't get cold.
I see.
- You can wear it in summer, too.
- That's awesome.
Divine gramps loves it, too.
Hey, it needs to be blurred!
This isn't allowed.
Your body is super fit
for a 69-year-old.
You can see his chest
through the mesh.
I should put bandages on here.
- No.
- So loud.
The weather improved two days later.
We can finally go.
We had to wait a total of two days
since we've arrived here.
We can see the stars,
so I believe the weather is clear.
I wonder what the conditions
are like.
It'll be windier
as you go up an altitude.
I see.
We're just concerned about the wind
when we get up there.
She thought it'd be an easy climb,
but the climb itself
was not what she expected.
This is horrible.
This is no joke.
No joke.
This is hell.
It's cold.
As they reach the summit,
the wind becomes stronger than ever.
I can't open my eyes.
Sensible temperature
is minus 15 degrees Celsius.
That's hell.
My eyes hurt. My eyes hurt.
Wind is blowing
at 18 metres per second.
The wind velocity
is as fast as a typhoon's.
I'll be blown away.
Looking back, she said this
at the base of the mountain.
I don't think we'll have
enough minutes.
I think we'll be on the summit,
just like that.
I think that's how tough
this mountain is.
She thought it was going to be
an easy hike,
but it ended up being harsh,
just like in the Himalayas.
This is hell.
Wind...
Oh, no. Oh, no.
It's cold.
They'll have to endure it for now,
believing that there's sunrise
ahead of them.
It's no joke.
The sky is gradually turning red.
I don't see any clouds yet.
That's amazing.
With all we've been through....
Come on out, sun.
Quarter to six in the morning,
they get past the heavy wind
and arrive at the summit.
They'll dodge the wind at the shrine
on the summit, until the sun rises.
What do we do?
It's no joke.
Thanks to all your efforts,
I think we can get a great picture.
A great picture will be taken.
The view seems great,
but the wind...
But because of this wind,
the clouds are being blown away.
The view might be great.
If I were able
to come here casually,
then I would be like,
"This is awesome!"
I get it now.
Considering all the hell we've been
through, we need to see this.
And at 24 past six in the morning,
it's finally time!
There it is!
The sun is rising now!
It's beautiful.
Sun rises and shines
on frozen mountains.
Swirling snow makes it look
even more beautiful.
There is hardly a cloud.
This is quite beautiful.
It's extremely beautiful.
Can you see Mount Fuji
towards the right?
This is rare.
You can't see Mount Fuji from Oyama
unless you're very lucky.
This is great. It's getting light.
This is one amazing sunrise
from the mountaintop.
It's an authentic sunrise
Recently, I haven't been
very emotional
when I went mountain climbing,
so I appreciate it.
The spray of snow is awesome.
It almost hides the sun.
It's dreamy.
This is from a time-lapse video.
They overcome
the trying blowing wind
to see the warm light
in the far distance.
This is definitely a superb view
you'd want to see in 2021.
I'm so glad we were able
to show this beautiful scenery.
This view is quite rare.
I'm glad we were able to deliver
this rare, magnificent view.
I believe we now we have enough
for New Year's Special,
and Mountain Climbing Special.
They take a picture for the calendar
with the best sunrise.
This is the sunrise
we deliver to you in 2021.
That's it
for The Quest Calendar Project
by the mountain climbing club.
- Good work.
- That sunrise was great.
- You climbed twice.
- Who knew
that I'd be climbing two mountains?
Yurina, what did you think?
I know that I shouldn't take
mountain climbing lightly,
but I like height
and dangerous places.
- Oh?
- What?
I'm a little interested.
- Should you say that?
- When you say that...
- They just heard her, right?
- That's not good. The staff here
are really crazy, so...
Really, they'll seriously
make you an offer.
Let's move on.
Take it away, Tetsuro.
Okay. Next up is this.
Female comedians, talent camp.
Yeah!
So it's a talent camp.
Female comedians
are in a different studio.
- Oh, that's their outfit?
- Hello!
We're all here!
Every one of them is cute.
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
Where did you go this time, Asako?
This time, we went to Tochigi,
and did this challenge.
No matter how I look at it,
those are cheerleading outfits.
You never know.
Is that an outfit
for your challenge this time?
Yes, it's unbelievable that
we blend in with the background.
- It's hard to tell apart.
- The red and white.
I'm more curious about your taping
than your outfits.
You can see that?
Your outfit is for cheerleading,
but your hands are those of
a sumo wrestler.
It's not just our hands.
Our knees and shoulders
are hurt, too.
This time, we will do a performance
to show our accomplishments.
Please look forward to it.
Let's get going then.
- The Quest!
Yeah.
Two-and-a-half-hour drive
from Shiodome,
Hot Springs Club special edition.
Female comedians,
talent camp in Tochigi.
They came to Nikko Toshogu,
a world heritage site.
We are here in Tochigi!
Female comedian group is here.
It's been a while.
We opened up at Nikko Toshogu
for Tochigi.
- It's wonderful.
- We are inside.
The Tochigi.
I'm glad you all came.
What?
- Well, I'm from Tochigi.
- That's right.
- Oh...
Welcome home.
Lots of them are here
for the first time, too.
It was the least charming prefecture
of Japan in 2020.
This was ranked last although
they have this magnificent place?
Exactly! Take a look.
It's best not to rush it.
- Oh, you're from Ibaraki.
- Ibaraki!
That's unseemly.
Darn it! We'll finish this off
in "Kenmin show!"
So, what are we doing this time?
This time, you'll wave flags around.
Flags?
Like as in flag signalling?
Is it possibly
where we do back flips
while we wave flags around?
What did you say?
- What do you mean?
- Ganbareruya will do it.
What is it?
I just stood out a little for now.
Now, Tochigi art talent camp starts!
They will be practising
at New Sunpia Tochigi for camp.
It will be taught by a dance
drill team, Pink Diamonds.
Is it like a marching band?
You twirl it,
and throw it in the air.
- You throw them?
- Yes.
It has a ball-shaped thing
attached to the flag.
I've never seen that before.
Is it like a twirling baton?
It's called a short flag baton.
A short flag baton?
Please watch the demonstration
of short flag baton.
They threw it in the air
from the start!
Wow!
Short flag started
in the United States.
It's a performance that combines
twirling batons and flags.
Amazing!
This is incredible.
Oh, that's pretty.
- This is no joke.
- It's no joke.
What is this technique?
How do you twirl it? It's amazing!
Wow, it's amazing!
If we could do that in sync,
it would be cool.
It's super cute.
We'll have you challenge this.
This was awesome to watch.
I think their shoulders
are dislocated.
Let's start with basic skills
for short flag.
Tomomi Hanzawa will be
their instructor.
They will use
two flag twirling batons.
A round grip is attached at the end
of an aluminium shaft.
- This is quite heavy.
- It's heavy.
It weight about 200 grams.
It's quite heavy.
You support the flag
with your index finger.
First, they'll learn the shape
of the arms,
and a basic movement
called "arm motion".
If this doesn't line up,
it doesn't look good.
You don't move your elbows
like this.
You lower it
with your elbows straight.
- That's hard.
- Lower with straight elbows?
It's hard not to bend your elbows.
What?
Instructor, it's impossible
unless you tighten your butt.
"It's impossible
unless you tighten your butt"
When I looked at the front row,
their butt was tightened.
It's really tight.
Next, is how to wave a flag.
You go down first,
and turn it to the back.
It's like dropping the wrist.
This is hard to do at first.
Oh, it hurts.
- My shoulders.
- My shoulders are hurting.
I see. I see.
And the biggest obstacle
is the left hand.
I can't rotate with my left hand
at all.
My left hand won't turn at all.
What are we going to do with this?
My elbow and wrists
aren't compatible at all.
What is this?
In addition, both hands have to do
the same movement equally.
That's difficult.
First up is Asako.
- What? Amazing.
- That's amazing.
- She's doing it.
- She's good at these things.
I don't know how she does it.
She's amazing, although she's 50.
Amazing.
- She's older than Nobunaga.
- The way she said that...
Don't compare me to Nobunaga
all the time.
He's a human, too.
Her back is itching.
Shut up!
I can't concentrate!
I'm thinking while I'm doing this!
In the meantime, Ocarina is...
To the back.
an alien semaphoring to a UFO.
Hey!
She's communicating with them.
Now, they'll learn different moves
for the final routine.
However, the left hand
is the biggest obstacle.
I can't imagine being able
to do this at the same time.
They also have to learn
the throwing techniques.
That's fast.
Front! That's it!
- Everyone.
- Yes?
Shall we refresh for a while?
I'm glad to hear that.
They will divide into two groups
to share Tochigi's tourist spots.
One group went to Nasu Highlands.
This is heaven.
They came to a popular spot,
Nasu Trick Art Museum.
Is this the entrance?
- Really?
- This is a drawing.
- This is trick art.
- Don't be fooled by it!
It's cute.
Inside is a strange place.
- A bear!
- Human raised by a bear?
Right, a person raised by a bear.
It's packed with Instagenic art!
That hair type is Asako Ito.
Good morning.
Why do short people do that?
Right.
This is a room of mirrors.
I'm exhausted.
- Creepy.
- What?
- Oh, no!
- How does that work?
Was I...
this old-looking?
The other team
is at Kinu Green Park.
It's a popular park
with athletic equipment over water.
It's very popular in summer,
but they don't have much visitors
during this season.
- Of course.
- That's a given.
Now, let's take a look at
their water athletics performance.
- Go for it!
- First up, YuiP.
She's walking.
Her feet are on the ground.
- That's the ground.
- Is that your style?
- Are you sure that's okay?
- No way.
Oh, no!
Oh...
- She's in the water!
- YuiP, you're in the water!
- YuiP, I'm not in the water, right?
You're in the water!
Next, it's Yoshiko.
This is scary.
You need physical strength
and grasping power.
- So flexible.
- You're flexible.
Oh, no!
She has a rope on her crotch.
Her crotch!
Just like that...
It's exposed.
- It's exposed!
- How do you explain that fall?
- Wow!
- It's all-star.
No!
She looks like Momiji Yamamura.
I'll go.
Ocarina attempts to cross
on a barrel.
- Come on.
- It really shakes.
- It's at a diagonal angle.
- What is this?
It's tilted.
Amazing!
Successful!
She looks super happy.
- That was fast.
- They start to practise again.
That's fast.
Once again, Kawamura
is less talented than the others.
It's difficult.
It's like a broken flower rock.
My pointer finger
won't move like I want it to.
Why don't you just play with it
at first?
Like so. Don't worry about
the finger and turn it for now.
You need to be friends
with the twirling baton.
I got it.
- It might be a problem this time.
- Don't cry.
What do I turn to practise?
The instructor said
it's the centrifugal force,
so I looked it up.
"Centrifugal force is
an inertial force that appears
to act on all objects,
when viewed from a rotating frame
of reference."
I'm even more confused now.
Second day of camp.
On the second day, they will learn
more difficult skills.
They will also practise
their formation.
Short twirl flag
is a group performance.
When the right side goes by,
you chase after it.
Everyone's movements compile
to make up the technique.
Wait.
They struggled
with the throwing techniques.
One, two, three, four, five.
This is the highlight of their
routine where they take turns
throwing it in the air and catching,
but success rate
is less than 50 percent.
Yakko's struggling with joint pain.
This hurts.
It hurts when I squat down.
- Oshima on the other hand is...
- Oh?
Oshima?
Are you okay?
- What's the matter?
- Can I do something for you?
I'm starving.
So they came to a rice field.
- Welcome!
- What?
Welcome to Otahara, Tochigi!
Welcome.
My other job is this.
I'm an ambassador for Otawara.
- That's where she's from.
- Nine years ago,
Oshima took a post as an ambassador
for Otawara.
This time,
it's an Otawara gourmet tour
recommended by the ambassador.
We have four destinations.
- Oh...
- How grand.
But because of how things are now,
we'll split up and go.
They will go to four destinations
in groups of three.
Highlight is Otawara beef steak.
They'll catch a jet balloon
for a steak.
Only three of them can eat it.
That's harsh.
Wait!
When meat is at stake,
Yashiro is suddenly quick.
Yes!
Second balloon.
All of them chasing after a balloon
is like criminals
chasing after a string in hell.
Yes!
Kurosawa is showing
her presence now.
There's one more spot for the steak.
- It's fast!
- Oh, not yet!
Yes!
Fat ones are extremely obsessed
with meat.
Yes!
Now, let's start
the Otawara gourmet tour!
First, it's Oshima's
memorable natural ingredient.
What is it?
Okay.
We see it now.
We don't see it at all.
We see Otawara gourmet now.
I don't see it.
I have no clue.
What? Persimmons?
You're right.
It looks delicious.
Isn't its colour beautiful?
It wasn't what I expected,
so I'm perplexed.
Really?
They each picked one
delicious-looking persimmon.
Nice catch!
Let's eat!
Isn't it astringent?
These are astringent persimmons.
I made the same mistake
over and over again
when I was in middle school.
Didn't it look super delicious?
Next is a bowl
recommended by Oshima.
Oh, it says "Wakuwaku ramen".
- Yes.
- That looks delicious.
- Is that Oshima?
- Yes, that's me.
- Oshima?
The owner asked me,
"Can I make a poster of this size?"
This was it.
- It wasn't what you expected.
- It was completely different.
It looks like vomit.
No!
How could you say that
in front of the owner?
It's fine. He's laughing.
Oshima loved this dish so much
that she travelled 40 minutes for it
in high school.
This is the meat bowl.
Oh, a vomit?
- Right?
- It's someone who drank too much.
How does it taste?
What do you think?
- It's delicious!
- Yes!
I'm so happy!
- What is this?
- Then...
- Isn't it delicious?
- It's delicious.
She's so touched
by the memorable taste.
That's great.
I couldn't say anything.
Good for you.
Next is the highest grade steak.
This is "Gyucho,"
Otawara beef speciality restaurant.
Filet is 150 grams
and about this size,
and it costs 52,000 yen.
Let's get that.
- Are you sure?
- 52,000 yen!
One, two, three.
The three of you will share a steak.
Oh...
Let's see
if there's a cheaper steak.
Cheaper one is fine,
so we can eat one each.
Fat ones choose quantity
over quality.
This is the super special
filet steak.
It costs 52,000 yen.
How does the Otawara beef,
the first rate Japanese beef, taste?
- It's 12,000 yen.
- It's 12,000 yen?
Oh...
It's tender!
- That's too fast.
- It's seriously delicious.
- I'm done with it already.
- I'll go for it.
You must be starving still.
- I'm still starving.
- I'm hungry even more.
The last one
is a super spicy gourmet.
Otawara is the number one producer
of chilli peppers in Japan.
Its spiciness could be tasted at
Oryu, a Chinese cuisine restaurant.
Their speciality is this,
chilli pepper ramen.
Its spiciness level is 10.
What? That's no joke.
Its colour is...
It's the paste type.
It's like a rubber.
- It's like a rubber band.
- This is a rubber band.
This is a special spicy noodles
with chilli pepper mixed in it.
So it's all spicy.
Its soup has super spicy spice,
their secret recipe.
Loads of chilli peppers
from Otawara are used.
Let's taste the spiciness!
It's spicy!
This spiciness hits you fast!
You can't slurp it.
On the other hand,
Barbie who loves spicy food is...
This part of me is strong.
Really?
She looks like she can handle it.
Amazing!
- Amazing!
- I'm impressed.
It feels good.
It feels good?
Wow!
This is the speciality, right?
Right.
Who made this into a speciality?
This is no joke.
After the tour,
they go back to practise again.
They'll use "Gurenge"
for their performance.
This is great.
They gradually learned
their routine,
but they are too slow.
I can't do it.
We have the right vibe, though.
- It's fast.
- It is fast.
We're pretty much doing it.
It looks gorgeous.
This short flag is the most
demanding skill to learn
of all time.
They struggle to improve
no matter how much they practise.
I treat this as a mental workout.
As soon as I have to use both hands
or I have to alternate,
I'm like, "What?"
And my body stops.
In addition,
what makes it even harder is
their old age.
Stop that!
- Their average age is 38 years old.
- It's younger than I thought.
Asako is 50 years old already.
I can't leave Asako alone.
Isn't she something else?
When I go to get
a massage with Asako,
she'll be next to me...
Making groaning sounds.
She's moaning and groaning.
Yesterday, YuiP came to me saying,
"Oshima, I thought
I was going to cry."
When I asked her why,
she went,
"Asako is asking me to teach her."
She said she almost started crying.
When she asked me,
"Sorry to bother you,
but can you teach me?"
Asako used to be the one
to teach everyone,
and I was shocked
that she was asking me now.
- It was...
- What does it mean?
I mean, her expression
was something else.
She looked like a corpse.
She looked like a mud doll.
What is that?
I was shocked
that she asked me like that.
She's crying.
In addition, when they all started
to play dodge ball...
Watch out!
Murakami
just moved out of the way,
but she injured her knee
with this movement.
My bad!
Time out!
Murakami, what?
Murakami, what is it?
- What's the matter?
- That's not good.
You did this move right now.
No, it wasn't like that at all.
It's this slightest jump,
and her landing.
What?
She's done it.
They are all wounded,
all over their body.
It's because they were playing.
These middle-aged women
can't even do regular things,
but they eagerly twirled the flags.
You don't need touching music here.
Their camp was over.
Female comedians
continued their practise in Tokyo
during free time.
What kind of performance
will they do?
They edited out
most of the practise scenes.
They edited out a lot.
It didn't show you practising much,
but since you were all cute,
it was fine.
Oh, Tetsuro!
Asako, what are your goals?
Yes, 12 of us haven't mastered
doing it in sync the whole time,
but we will do our best to do
a cheerful New Year's performance.
- Thank you!
- We're looking forward to it.
Now, they will perform after this.
Short flag performance
by the female comedians!
Thank you!
- Relax!
- Come on!
Do your best! Have fun.
- Let's do it!
- Okay.
This is when I get most nervous.
Have fun!
- Do your best.
- Let's go!
Excuse me, Oshima's bra came undone.
Her bra came undone?
Oh, no!
Hide her with flags.
- Are you okay?
- Nice teamwork!
It's fine.
- Is it on?
- Is it all settled?
- It's okay!
- Thank you.
Let's do this.
- Nice!
- Now...
- Focus.
let's start.
Short flag performance
by the female comedians!
Amazing!
That's amazing.
That's good!
Perfect score!
Amazing!
That was great.
- Perfect!
- Amazing!
Asako, how was it?
It's done!
Amazing!
Good work!
They're relieved.
We have room for improvement
for sure,
and since I can't look behind me,
I don't know if everyone
was doing it right,
but I didn't hear
any dropping sound, so I'm glad.
That was incredible.
Yurina, what did you think?
I can relate to a formation movement
of a huge group
in a performance,
so I'm sure it was hard.
Thank you
for such a great performance.
- Thank you for watching us perform.
- Not at all.
I never thought she'd be here
to watch it.
When Asako stood in the front
and started her performance,
it reminded me a little bit of
"Drifters, Daibakusho".
Why?
That's wrong!
I don't look like that!
Great job, everyone!
Good work, female comedians!
- Good work.
- Thank you very much.