Three, two, enter!
- That's fast.
- That's incredible.
Three, two, enter!
This is no joke. This is hard.
"The Quest"
"This programme was broadcast
31 January, 2021"
The Quest has started.
Tonight, we have rare animal
Hunter Imoto Japan tour,
and Lotti Nakaoka's QTube.
"Daisuke Miyagawa, Soichi Nakaoka,
Asako Ito, Ayako Imoto"
"Kazuko Kurosawa, Miyuki Oshima,
Tetsuro Degawa, Tomoko Murakami"
Now, where did you go
this time, Imoto?
This was the tenth location
of Japan Tour.
- I see.
- I went to Shizuoka this time.
I went to places that are a bit
peculiar and not mainstream.
So we won't see any hot springs?
None whatsoever!
- It's not like with "Hirunandesu"?
- None whatsoever.
You won't be watching this and go,
"Let's go there next weekend."
Let's get going then!
- The Quest!
Yeah!
It sways a lot.
This is how wide it is now.
It's kicking. Kick won't stop now!
I'm coming up there.
"Collaborating with female
high school students, number two"
"Lotti Nakaoka's QTube in Fukuoka"
That's great.
Conquer all 47 prefectures of Japan!
Rare animal hunter Imoto,
Japan Tour!
She headed to Shizuoka,
of the magnificent Mt. Fuji.
Hello! Hello! It's Imoto!
I'm here in Shizuoka right now!
Now, where am I?
Now, the usual, let's find Imoto!
I'm here!
- I'm here! I'm right here!
- Over there?
I was peeking out of the window
of a neighbouring house
- near the suspension bridge.
- What is this?
Oi River in Shizuoka is known to
have several suspension bridges.
A suspension bridge without a pier
is perfect for a fast river.
You walk right over someone's house.
You can see cars driving below too.
This is scary.
This suspension bridge in Shiogo
was built 90 years ago.
Once, students rode their bikes
on it to go to school.
Its biggest highlight is that
steam locomotives run below it.
So we came up with this segment.
Hello, I'm Imolyn Monroe.
Now, we are going to take
a miraculous photograph
with Oi-River railways' steam
locomotive and I, Imolyn Monroe.
Marilyn Monroe's skirt fluttered
above a subway ventilation.
Here, they will experiment
with the steam from the train.
The steam locomotive is approaching.
This doesn't look too good.
- Boy...
- I think it's going to work.
- The skirt didn't flutter at all.
- That's too bad.
Let's start the Shizuoka tour!
First, let us introduce
an amazing expert!
Shizuoka is actually famous
for its canned goods.
In particular, you can say
that most canned tuna are made
in Shizuoka.
97% of it is produced in Shizuoka.
The expert works at a canning plant.
He's hitting the cans with a stick.
The sound changes
with the amount of air in cans.
So he's removing the cans
that sound different.
- At this speed?
- Yes.
- He is a tapping inspector.
- A tapping inspector?
If the can contains too much air,
the expiration date's accuracy
can't be maintained.
They have the skill to differentiate
the sound and the feel with a tap.
- That's amazing.
- Yes, that's part of the process.
So we came up with an experiment.
We will have one can of tuna
in cans of miso flavoured mackerel.
Will he be able to distinguish it?
He is a professional
at distinguishing the quality,
but whether he can tell
its contents is unknown.
I can do it.
You'll do it?
- You've never done it before--
- I can do it!
Will he be able
to get the right one?
"The correct answer is to select
the canned tuna"
- That's incredible!
- Really?
- It's this one.
- That's fast!
Wow!
This is incredible!
This is canned tuna!
- I got it right.
- That's amazing.
That's great!
I'm impressed.
What is the limitation
of this tapping inspector?
It has the same contents,
but its flavour is different.
We'll challenge him with plain
and miso-flavoured mackerel.
- Can you do it?
- I can do it.
It's correct if he picks
the plain mackerel.
If he picks the plain one?
"Plain mackerel
is the correct choice"
What?
Really?
How is that possible?
That's incredible.
That's amazing.
No way!
Incredible!
That's incredible!
This is amazing.
You are correct!
I did it!
You went beyond your limits.
What do you think, plant manager?
That's awesome!
It is, right?
Could we try the bonus round then?
Are we going for that?
Yes.
Here's the bonus challenge!
One can contains a 10,000-yen note,
and the other nine cans
contain 1,000-yen notes.
He got one.
So Kitagami, you think this one
has the 10,000-yen note?
This one...
This one has the 10,000-yen note.
So this is 10,000-yen.
- Which one is it?
- Come on!
Come on!
There.
That's too bad!
Here's your guaranteed fee
for today.
Thank you very much!
Next up is a report
on a rare insect.
She came to Ryuyo Insect Nature
Observation Park.
I see a suspicious looking figure.
- Hello.
She will be guided by Konchu-kun.
Do you dress up like this
on your own?
I'm dressing up like
an insect loving boy.
- I see.
- Yes, that's how I do it.
Can I take a look at your back too?
Ah, that's cute.
This is my golden stag beetle
backpack.
I didn't quite get that.
What he showed her was...
This is an insect called
Pheropsophus Jessoensis.
Pheropsophus... what?
This is a tiny insect that's less
than two centimetres long.
It inhabits in areas from
Hokkaido to Amamioshima.
You can find these insects
in rice fields
and along the river banks,
so they're not that rare.
What's so magnificent about
this insect?
Its fart is hot.
If you touch it directly,
you'll burn your hand.
- It's that hot?
- Yes.
It's said to be close to
100-degrees Celsius.
A fart that's close to
100-degrees Celsius?
Take a look at this.
What?
He picked it up right now.
- Oh!
- It farted.
It farted!
I think I saw steam come out
with it too.
If you sniff around this area,
maybe you'll smell that distinct...
It stinks!
It's fumy...
and it's smoky.
It generates two chemicals
in its body.
This fart is produced as a result
of that chemical reaction.
- Thank you.
- When we observe the thermography,
its hotness is clearly seen.
Oh! It farted!
It's their defence mechanism to
protect themselves from an enemy.
That's amazing.
Fart...
This fart is interesting.
This facility has another
unique curator.
I'm the cockroach
specialist Shizuma.
That's one shocking name.
This facility is known
for cockroaches.
Oh, this facility favours
and specialises in cockroaches?
I think everyone is disgusted by it,
but there are cute ones
and pretty ones too.
Right, I see.
If we see Shizuma's collection,
our bias towards cockroaches
may change a little.
- Here.
- It looks pretty clean in here.
The first one is
the Madagascar hissing cockroach.
This one hisses.
It hisses?
It forcefully expels air out of its
spiracle to make its hissing sound.
It hisses when it's threatened,
right?
Next one is Perispherus Pygmaea.
What? This is a cockroach?
It's like a roly-poly.
This species lives in Japan too.
It rolls into a ball
to protect itself from its enemy.
Can I take a look?
- Yes.
- The one who appeared on camera,
is assistant producer Hirata,
also known as "Mum."
I researched roly-poly when
I was a university student.
For real?
What's with your experience?
This is a cockroach?
Wait, before you get to that,
you were researching roly-poly?
I collected over 300 roly-polys,
to research its sexual dimorphism.
For real?
Next one is Blaberus Giganteus.
- What? This is a cockroach?
- Yes, it is.
Its smell is very unique. It smells
like dried Shiitake mushrooms.
That's great.
Wow, it really smells
like Shiitake mushrooms.
When I found out about this smell,
I was so impressed.
- He was impressed?
- I was like, "It's Shiitake."
- It sure is.
- Yes.
When I see Shiitake mushrooms,
I think of this.
That's what you think of?
That's not cool.
But it doesn't taste like Shiitake
mushrooms when you eat it.
- What? You ate it before?
- I have.
I didn't have any stomach issues.
Right. Shizuma is fascinated
with cockroaches,
and yet he's allergic to them.
His hands get itchy.
Shizuma is fascinated
with studying cockroaches.
Cockroaches he had
previously discovered
in the Nansei Islands,
were acknowledged as a new variety
last November.
You can only find it on display
at this insect museum.
It was all about cockroaches
and farts.
Not at all.
- We also requested it--
- We apologise.
Not at all.
Next, she'll participate
in a bird show.
- She came to Kakegawa Kachoen.
- I've been there.
I think it's rare for any place
to offer a daily bird show.
She'll attempt to participate
in a show of predatory birds
with sharp talons and beaks.
A hawk will land on your hand.
Its talons are sharp.
- Wait, do hawks have good vision?
- Yes, they do.
Then it can tell
these two colours apart?
I'm wearing similar colours here.
It's fine.
The one to assist her is...
This is Yoshino.
- Yoshino?
- It's a girl.
I know a Yoshino.
Yoshino kind of looks like her.
They both have that smart look.
Please always make sure to stand
with your left shoulder
towards the hawk.
This is how you stand.
It's prohibited to face the hawk
from the front.
When you look into hawk's eyes,
they will take it as a threat.
You should never look into
the hawk's eyes
when it's resting on your arm.
I shouldn't do that.
I'm glad to know that.
Yoshino!
It may attack you if you don't learn
its nature properly.
They won't peck your eyes
with their sharp beak, right?
It'll be fine,
they'll use their talons.
When they do it? That's scary!
Hawks tend to attack with their
talons to catch their prey.
So you don't have to worry about
them attacking you with their beak.
She will handle a falcon
and a secretary bird as well.
Now, the rare animal hunter's
bird show begins!
Hello!
- Good morning, everybody!
- That's great.
- I'm glad to have so many visitors.
- She has guests.
Thank you for being here
so early in the morning.
Are you all ready?
Number 73, are you ready?
Okay! Thank you very much.
The first bird I'm going to bring in
is this one!
Come!
Okay! Thank you, Yoshino.
Since we are all here,
let's have her fly by all of you.
She flew quite close to you,
its Japanese name is Momoakanosuri.
It means its thighs are red,
and it flies low to the ground,
and that's why it's called
Momoakanosuri.
Imoto found a job she can do,
even if she quits
being an entertainer.
- That's great.
- Yoshino!
Come.
Next up is "Archery,"
a Lanner falcon.
She uses a lure to show
how it hunts.
Okay, come Archery!
There it is.
It dodged the first one.
It dodged the second one too.
And...
the third time... Archery!
Archery!
Where did it go?
There it is.
Got it!
What a great catch!
Last one is "Kick,"
a secretary bird.
It shows its famous characteristic
of kicking a snake.
- That's disgusting.
- It's upset.
Kick is here!
- It's kicking! That's it!
- It really kicks it.
That's it!
That's it! If you would take
a look at its head,
it focuses its kicks around
the snake's head.
It kicks to get it with one blow.
This would be a disaster if a person
is kicked by an accident.
Kick! Kick!
Okay.
So you have these regular snakes,
but in Africa, they have cobras
that raise their head.
Then what do these birds do?
Please take a look.
Look, it's a cobra.
Its head is raised.
Ah, it kicked the camera.
It kicked the GoPro.
GoPro is not your enemy.
Kick! Look, that's scary.
Wow! It jumped.
That was a high kick.
- It could kick that high?
- There! Nice kick!
I made a couple of mistakes,
but I had a great time doing it.
I used to admire the ladies who do
the dolphin and sea lion shows,
so I felt like my childhood dream
was fulfilled. I had fun.
Next, it's amazing kids in Shizuoka.
These are the members of a rope
skipping team, E-Jump Fuji.
They are experts who hold
two Guinness World Records.
Imoto's challenge
for this part is...
- High-speed long rope skipping.
- Oh wow.
Ready...
That's fast.
That's fast!
They continue to skip rope quickly
in a figure-eight configuration.
They jumped 230 times in a minute,
to achieve a superhuman record.
This time, the challenge is to jump
for one minute.
No! No! No! That's harsh. What?
By the way, how fast
are they jumping right now?
About 180 times per minute.
It calculates to three jumps
per second.
This is how fast you have to jump
to call it "high-speed."
When I imagine myself being
in there, I only see problems.
You published
a book recently, right?
Yes, I published a book
called "Tanakara Tsubugai."
If you are successful
in this challenge,
we were thinking of giving it away
as a gift to all participants.
That's great.
I mean, I would love it if the kids
would read my book.
And the fact that all the viewers
will see it on TV,
makes me happy as an author.
She'll start her practise now.
What's important with long-rope
skipping is the four-four rhythm.
You start counting three jumpers
before you,
Three, two, and you enter.
You step into the rope and jump.
That's four counts.
So they're all counting
in their heads?
Yes, they are. When I say "enter,"
what I mean is...
So the ones swinging the rope
are called the turners.
You cross right next to this turner.
That is what we mean by "enter."
- I see. You go in at that angle?
- Yes.
You want to step in on cue.
Please land with your jumping foot.
So if you step in with your right,
you step in and jump.
- I see.
- Yes.
Okay.
- That's it. That's perfect.
- I see.
Let's start skipping!
Ready.
- Okay!
- Three, two, enter, and jump.
This is how fast 180 jumps
per minute is.
Okay, three, two, enter!
- Amazing!
- That's incredible.
Okay, three, two, enter!
This is no joke. This is hard!
This is... No...
Three, two, enter!
The rope hit Imoto's elbow
after she jumped,
and the jumper behind her got
caught in it and ended this round.
Oh no!
The biggest issue here
is not about jumping, but...
You know...
I'm sprinting right now,
but I can't keep up with them.
Three, two, enter!
She manages to keep up
for about 20 seconds,
at a pace of 180 jumps per minute.
- Okay! Applaud!
- That's amazing.
Amazing.
What's the trick?
I think my physical strength?
The more I do it, the more strength
I lose, so I'm losing power here.
I guess I'll have to get it done
in the first half.
So the first try is super critical.
It's super critical.
I'll get it done the first time.
Now, high-speed long-rope
skipping challenge!
Her critical first attempt.
Ready,
go!
Okay, three, two, enter!
Imoto makes short turns
to maintain her strength.
Three, two, enter!
Okay, three, two, enter!
- Okay, three, two, enter!
- I'm impressed.
We can do it!
Okay, three, two, enter!
Will she get it done the first time,
as she had claimed?
Three, two, enter!
Okay, three, two, enter!
Almost!
- Wonderful!
- Amazing!
Okay, three, two, enter!
You almost had it.
Did it hit my clothes at the end?
It hit you here as you were leaving.
You leave right after you jump,
but you were too tired to do it.
If you could run at the end...
You had two more seconds to go.
I could have done it,
but after this run...
I have to say...
doing another run
is too hard.
Now, I wish
I had messed up earlier.
Failing at this point is...
As expected, her physical strength
diminishes after this run.
An endless death road continues...
"15th attempt"
"27th attempt"
It's so much slower!
I'm sorry!
Their 34th attempt. They have
seven more seconds to go.
Now, the kids got caught.
No!
Honestly, they are...
Imoto, you're doing it perfectly.
- No! No! No!
- You're perfect.
- That was close!
- That was our mistake.
Coach Nishizawa couldn't forgive
the kids' lack of focus.
Oh no, they're being lectured.
You have to focus.
Why are you losing your focus
at the end? You messed up.
- It's all of you. Do you get it?
- Oh no.
You need to step it up.
It was your fault just now.
It was your fault for sure just now.
Imoto was doing it perfectly.
No, no.
When he puts it that way,
it adds so much more pressure.
Please stop, coach.
Make sure to get it done next time.
It's enough already.
Ayumu got caught in the rope.
He looks like the world is ending.
When Imoto saw that...
Look at him. I think it's that kid
with glasses.
His face is so...
It makes me want to cry.
Oh no. I'm going to cry.
When I see his face,
it makes me want to cry.
I mean, he... I don't know how many
times we jumped today,
but he only messed up
that one time just now.
He feels so responsible about it,
and his expression just now
is something else...
I feel really bad about it.
This is not something
he should be held responsible for.
Originally.
I feel really bad about it.
- He's under so much pressure.
- This must be hard.
Is he going to be okay?
This part was supposed to be used
to advertise her new book,
but unexpectedly, it became a drama
displaying tenacity in sports.
Failure is not an option anymore,
for Ayumu's sake.
- Go for it!
- Get it done!
Will they succeed?
- Let's do it!
- It'll be fine.
- Let's go!
- Yes!
Ready.
Okay, three, two, enter!
I feel really bad about this.
This is not something he should
be held responsible for.
Failure is not an option anymore,
for Ayumu's sake.
- Go for it!
- Get it done!
Will they succeed?
- Let's do it!
- It'll be fine.
- Let's go!
- Yes!
Ready.
Okay, three, two, enter!
- Okay, three, two, enter!
- You can do it!
Okay, three, two, enter!
- Okay, three, two, enter!
- 20 seconds have passed.
Okay, three, two, enter!
- Okay, three, two, enter!
- It feels so long.
- A minute feels like forever.
Okay, three, two, enter!
20 seconds left.
- This is where it gets tougher.
- Okay, three, two, enter!
Okay, three, two, enter!
Yes!
Okay!
Amazing.
They are successful in high-speed
rope skipping for a minute.
They jumped 186 times!
If it weren't for COVID-19,
I'd hug everyone right now!
I know!
- Let's do an air hug!
- An air hug!
Air hug! Air hug!
Thank you so much.
I got worried half way through.
I was worried
about their expression.
Do you still like rope skipping?
- Yes, I love it.
- I'm glad to hear that.
Do you get scolded like that
all the time?
But what do you do
when that happens?
I'm not worried. I'm not worried.
- We do that.
- Why didn't you do that?
- What is that?
- So it's all okay.
You should worry a little.
Show that you're worried.
Thank you very much.
This is my book,
"Tanakara Tsubugai."
That's it for our 10th prefecture,
Shizuoka! We conquered it.
Let's move on. Asako, please.
Yes, next up is this!
Lotti Nakaoka's Qtube!
Yeah!
I went to Fukuoka, Kyushu this time.
I did a collaboration with
a local high school volleyball team.
Oh no. Are you going to tie
your hair back again?
You're all too sensitive!
- You're going to try to act cool?
- No, this time I didn't do that.
Are you sure?
- I was serious.
- You were serious?
We all like to police around.
- It's fine?
- He'll be arrested.
They'll go "time of arrest,
so and so hour."
This world is full of YouTubers who
create and post interesting videos.
This project goes
on location with them,
to create a video
to make the whole world laugh.
This is...
QTube.
He headed to Fukuoka this time.
First, he will attempt
to do a boating technique,
going down the river at Yanagawa.
My impression of Yanagawa is...
I think I saw a movie with
Yanagawa when I was about 20.
I always wanted to visit this place.
I think it was "Tokyo Biyori."
It was directed by Naoto Takenaka.
I don't think so.
Don't be so sure.
I'm certain that they filmed
it in Yanagawa.
The scene where Miho Nakayama
is sleeping on a boat is beautiful.
I don't think so.
- It's in "Tokyo Biyori."
- Why are you so certain?
- I remember watching it.
- I remember "Tokyo Biyori."
It's a performance done
by Masuda the boatsman,
when he goes under the bridge.
It's low.
Wow! What?
He pushes the boat with his foot
to make it go under the bridge,
- What's going on?
- and he climbs up the bridge.
What's going on?
There he is! Amazing!
This is the bridge
climbing performance.
Let's have you challenge this.
I think I can do it.
First, let's start at beginner level
at Takemon Bridge.
A long bamboo pole is used
to push the boat forward.
Okay.
- It looks great.
- What's important is
to have the boat go straight
while going under the bridge.
Okay!
- I'm sorry. I'm coming up there.
- He's going too fast.
I'm coming up there.
Oh no!
- He crashed into the wall.
- He said "Oh no!"
It's cold.
Did I rush it?
You rushed it.
Next, an advanced level.
Josai Bridge is so difficult that
Masuda won't climb up that often.
It's high,
and there's nothing to hold on to
when I climb up.
- Will Nakaoka succeed?
- Come on!
- Go for it!
- You can do it!
Since the river is wide, it's easier
to let the boat go under.
What's left is whether he can
climb up the parapet that's high up.
Climb it!
- Go for it!
- He can do it.
Nakaoka climbed up,
with determination.
Go!
Now, he just has to get on the boat.
- Wait! Wait!
- Don't rush it.
- Wait!
- Jump on!
He sure is a first-class comedian.
He used everything he could here
to do this performance!
Wait!
- It's like that prankster show.
- Climbing up
went well.
- Darn it!
- Climbing up was...
- That's great.
It's...
My lower body...
is going to tear!
Nakaoka wants to shower
as soon as possible...
The boat can't come back
without a pole.
What did you say?
A boat can't return without a pole.
They need a pole for the boat
to come back?
A puzzling mission of delivering
a pole to the boat gets assigned.
That's no joke.
Darn it!
That was so close.
That was close.
Why are you running so fast?
They said they need a pole
for the boat to return.
It's back!
Next up is a video that can be
created at a low cost.
Nakaoka, the human compass.
Let's try it with a blackboard sheet
stuck on a wall.
I don't feel any pressure at all.
Should I carry that
for the heck of it?
"Should I carry that
for the heck of it?"
- Here I go!
- Can he draw a perfect circle?
Looking good.
Oh? It looks good to me.
- This is clean.
- So you can draw it?
I'm done.
It's good.
Amazing.
I did it.
You went unexpectedly slow.
Did you want me to do it fast?
I'll start over here, then.
He'll draw it faster now.
- I did it.
- That was impressive.
I drew another circle
of the same size.
That's amazing.
The next challenge is done
by a team of three.
Jumping through a hula-hoop.
Three people form a line,
and everyone jumps through
a hula-hoop thrown by the lead.
Kokura Minami Gymnastics Club
will help out.
We have a special instructor
for you.
Which gymnast do you think of
when you think of North Kyushu?
Orakio?
- It's not Dangan Jackie.
- It's not Dangan Jackie?
Speaking of North Kyushu, it's U...
It can't be? During this season?
I was told that Coach Uchimura
is here?
It's not Uchimura.
It's not gymnast Uchimura.
This is Ryu Matsuo, who is two years
older than Kohei Uchimura.
I apologise. Nice to meet you.
Assistant director Fujimoto
will join in to try this challenge.
- Ready!
- Okay.
- Here I go!
Ready!
Ouch.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
When this challenge is tried,
a hula-hoop actually hurts.
- Ouch!
- One more time.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Nakaoka takes the lead now.
I'll do this one.
Ready!
- Ouch!
- It hurts.
I'm sorry.
It directly hits the crown
of Fujimoto's head.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- That would hurt.
Do you have something bigger
than this,
by any chance?
We do.
You do?
Wait.
It's very subtle.
The difference is subtle.
"Déjà-vu?"
I thought you had something
much bigger.
This is a subtle difference.
Do you have another one?
What are you doing here?
There it is!
It's a subtle difference.
Challenge with a hula-hoop
that's slightly bigger.
Here we go!
Then...
Ready!
We did it!
Didn't we do it?
It hit Fujimoto's back,
but they succeeded!
We did it!
Didn't we do it? Yes! We did it!
You know,
I seriously just made it through.
This is how I jumped.
That was a miracle.
- He's right.
- That's incredible!
Next, it's the world's
amazing tricks on video.
The next video is...
Why do you have the cue card out?
- It's common to have it for TV.
- That is true,
but I've never seen any script
or cue cards for this show.
I see. That sounds interesting.
I'll do my best!
Why would I say that?
Nakaoka, flipping on a kayak.
It will be taught by Kawazu,
who placed eighth
in freestyle canoe in Japan.
Amazing!
It looks super hard.
- He will use a small single kayak.
- That looks scary.
His feet will be fixed in place.
So the instructor will save him
immediately if he capsizes.
This is horrifying.
Being fixed in position is scary.
There are things
you shouldn't do in a river,
- but this is a pool, so...
- Is it fine?
Let's do this!
I trust you!
He is all hyped up
to try his first attempt!
Let's go!
He capsized.
That's scary!
- That's so scary.
- That's no joke.
I quit!
I quit! I quit!
This is too scary!
I'm quitting!
Nakaoka is discouraged
at the fastest rate ever.
Of all the videos
I have done so far,
that was the fastest I've given up.
This is the fastest, right?
Comparing the probability
of being able to do this,
and
the probability of me dying,
I think the probability of me dying
is actually higher.
Degawa said that we don't have
the right to quit.
You have the right.
What do we do?
I'll do my best! Stop that!
"Nakaoka, I'll do my best!"
I can't do my best.
I can't read that cue card anymore.
Next, he'll attempt this challenge
at a popular Instagenic spot.
Hello! It's Lotti Nakaoka here!
I'm here
In Toyomae,
Fukuoka.
"Buzen"
What...
am I doing right now?
The correct answer is...
- I am sitting on a gigantic chair!
- That's something else.
What he will challenge
using this gigantic chair is...
Rebounding bottle catch.
He will bounce the ball
and catch the rebounding bottle.
- It's the Galilean cannon theory.
- It's going to bounce back up.
An object on top gains the momentum
of the rebounding ball,
to bounce higher
than its original position.
If you're unable to catch it,
this thing will shoot out
of your back.
There it is!
That thing misfires!
This is the new and improved
steaming hot PET bottle rocket.
Improved?
A string attached to the trigger
on the original one
was two metres long,
but this one is twice as long,
at four metres.
I don't think its length
has anything to do with it.
As long as the ball is dropped
straight down,
the bottle is sure to come back up.
I can do this.
It all depends on whether Nakaoka
can catch it or not.
If he fails, a steaming bottle
rocket will launch from his back.
I think I can do this in one go.
- Here I go!
- Will he succeed like he claimed?
One, go!
Come on!
Hot! It's hot!
It's hot!
What kind of a set-up is this?
Unfortunately, Nakaoka failed.
- It's hot!
- That's great.
That's the best.
Now, please watch this artistic
video of two falling bottles.
I think those super-hot bottles
- are great.
- It came back!
Now, it goes that way!
That's great.
Soichi, that's great.
This part is the best.
- That looks hot!
- Amazing.
- That's great.
- That looks hot.
This is great. Man, this is great.
This is horrible for my scalp.
My back can endure this,
but not my scalp.
- Seriously.
- It's horrible for the scalp.
It's smooth on the outside.
What?
Your hair is smooth on the outside,
but the centre part is soggy.
Don't describe it like a Takoyaki.
He'll collaborate with a local
volleyball team for the final one.
Is he going to behave?
The last video is the second one of
"Trying to Act Cool Nakaoka" series.
- What?
- Trying to act cool?
You're talking about the volleyball
thing I did before, right?
It's not like I was trying
to act cool that time either.
It just so happens
that I looked good.
He will collaborate
with Kitakyushu High School's
women's volleyball team.
It's a strong team that frequently
competes at national competitions.
The first-class comedian
makes his appearance!
Look at them!
Everyone at Kitakyushu High School!
Thank you for having me here today.
"Eek"
- I like this.
- He's at it again.
- Volleyball simultaneous shooting.
- It just feels so great.
Three of them will set the ball
at the basket simultaneously
to make a shot.
First, he'll challenge with three
volleyballs, like the video.
- Don't say it's impossible.
- Nakaoka exhibits leadership
- when it comes to club activities.
- Think that you can make a shot.
Let's get it done now!
- Yeah!
- Yeah...
No! This won't do! That "Yeah"
just now is unacceptable!
- Ready!
- Will they get three shots?
Whoa! Did mine go in?
Nakaoka is the only one
who made the shot.
Do you get it now?
My mentality is different here.
But when it's played in slow motion,
Nakaoka's ball is blocking
the other two shots.
- Okay.
- Now, Nakaoka
ties his hair back.
Again?
Okay.
I'm serious here.
Let's do this.
- Ready!
- This challenge requires control,
timing, and trajectories of all
three participants to be in sync,
for it to be successful.
They've been doing this
for an hour now.
What?
- I want a one-liner joke...
You want a one-liner joke
for a break?
They're so tough.
- Teacher!
- Yes?
Your students are being weird.
Please.
I've never done a one-liner joke.
I'll do a charming Kabuki actor.
"Poop"
Alright! Let's pretend like
it never happened.
That's when it happened.
Let's go!
Ready!
They made three shots,
simultaneously!
What do we do?
Is three enough?
That was just practice.
That wasn't for practice!
That was the actual thing.
Those three shots were amazing.
But your joke was seriously bad,
and if I edit out your joke,
it won't make any sense.
Then shall we try for four?
It was amazing just now.
Let's go for five.
Five?
Can you do five?
So now, they'll challenge
making five shots.
Let's go!
However, when they try it,
throwing five is significantly
harder than three.
It sure is difficult.
They tried it for two hours
with no success.
Now, for self-awareness purposes,
let's raise our hand
if we miss a shot.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Let's be strict with ourselves.
- Yes.
- Focus.
- Nakaoka gives a pep talk.
- Let's go!
- Then immediately after that...
- Wow!
- Amazing!
Captain's bitter mistake.
Currently, Nakaoka is scheming
to turn this into a laugh.
You know what?
This is not the time
to blame someone
for making a mistake.
One person's mistake
is everyone's mistake.
Okay! Let's inspire one another!
Failed.
They've been on location
for four hours.
The number of attempts made
was 355 times.
Nakaoka performed his joke
five times.
Volley-rina.
Someone say, "Hey! You shoplifted."
Hey, you shoplifted!
Did you see that?
- Okay.
- Let's do our best.
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
- Ready!
- Everyone in the gymnasium
gets united for success.
That's close.
- Come on!
- Let's go!
That's great.
Is it happening soon?
It's soon.
Let's focus this one time.
Let's get it in!
- Yeah!
- Alright, let's do this!
Let's do it!
And then...
- It's happening?
- No way!
They successfully made
five simultaneous shots!
Amazing!
- Amazing!
- Amazing.
Go!
- We did it!
- Amazing.
It went in beautifully.
- It really did!
- However,
excited Nakaoka makes
an unexpected comment.
Let's do six!
Okay! Let's do six
and intimidate them all!
What do you think?
I'm not wearing my glasses,
so I don't see your faces clearly.
The scenario was, you get in
five shots, you then get excited,
and I would say,
"Do you want to try six?"
Then it would end with you saying,
"No way!"
But you looked all enthusiastic
and proclaimed, "Let's do six!"
As a result,
this is how it ended up,
and I feel bad for everyone.
Unknowingly,
I might have tried to act cool.
That's it! Thank you Kitakyushu
High School volleyball team.
- His success was incredible.
- That was incredible.
It's just that when he took his
glasses off, he was pushing it.
He tied his hair back
before he took off his glasses.
I was thinking about
arresting him there.
What was that all about?
- Well, you know...
- "What was that all about?"
- Why did you tie your hair back?
What was that all about?
You gave up on the kayak
after just one attempt,
but you didn't give up
on volleyball.
You had the nerve to say,
"Let's do six!"
Then you should have attempted
to do the kayak thing 50 times!
He's right!