"The Quest"
"This programme was first broadcast
14 February, 2021"
The Quest has started! We have rare
animal hunter Imoto's Japan tour,
and Lotti Nakaoka's QTube.
"Asako Ito, Daisuke Miyagawa,
Ayako Imoto, Tetsuro Degawa"
"Kazuko Kurosawa, Miyuki Oshima
Soichi Nakaoka, Tomoko Murakami"
That doesn't look good.
"A local competition and
a major experiment in Ehime"
Three, two, one, go!
"Lotti Nakaoka's QTube in Hokkaido"
"Funny clips in the extreme cold"
Stop it!
It's freezing.
Conquer all 47 prefectures of Japan!
Rare animal hunter Imoto's
tour of Japan.
She went to west Shikoku,
known for its Dogo Hot Springs.
- Hello, it's Imoto!
- Shimanami Kaido is pretty.
I'm here in Ehime.
Now, where am I?
- Time for our usual "Find Imoto."
- Where is she?
I'm here!
I'm right here.
I'm being part of a stone monument,
next to this particular house.
Someone famous actually lived
in this house.
Miyagawa! Do you know who it is?
I guess a hint would be this statue,
and the ambience here.
- So do you know who it is?
- Who is that?
- What? Wait!
- Wrong!
You're completely wrong! Of course
it's not Kinjiro Ninomiya.
The correct answer is...
a major writer of the Meiji era...
- this is Shiki Masaoka's home.
- So it's Shiki Masaoka.
Shiki Masaoka was born
in Matsuyama, Ehime.
He set the foundation for
modern Japanese literature,
and everyone has heard of his Haiku,
"Eat a persimmon/
And the bell will toll/At Horyuji"
- Hello.
This is Ms Yamazawa, a haiku poet
who specialises in Shiki Masaoka.
So you're a poet?
- Yes, I am.
- Not an invalid, but a poet?
- So you're a haiku poet?
- Yes.
Since we are here
at Shiki Masaoka's house,
how about conversing
solely in Haiku form?
Won't that be hard?
There's a possibility
I won't say a word.
- Let's start!
- Wait a second!
Shall we go and view
Masaoka's house?
Yes, we should.
Let's head on inside.
This is so awkward to think
after every turn,
and this conversation
is so meaningless.
Now, let's learn about
Shiki Masaoka!
I see. It is much smaller
than I expected.
You're right. Only part of it
has been restored.
- I see.
- What about the Haikus?
In any case,
is it okay for me to go inside?
Yes, of course. You can go in
with your shoes on.
What?
It's too much work to come up
with a Haiku response.
I have seen Masaoka's picture...
in textbooks before.
You're right. His profile picture
is very common.
This photograph was taken
in the latter part of his life.
It was hard for him to straighten
his spine due to a chronic illness,
so they took
a profile picture of him.
And Shiki Masaoka was in love
with a particular sport.
- Shiki loved baseball.
- I see.
Shiki translated "walk"
as "four-ball."
These baseball terminologies,
still being used now,
were created by Shiki Masaoka
based on their English wording.
What is Shiki's position
in baseball?
Shiki's position in baseball is...
catcher.
I see.
A catcher...?
It is not acceptable for a person
to give incorrect info in Haiku...
about Shiki Masaoka.
Ms Yamazawa,
you've done your research.
I can't say anything wrong--
Hold on a second.
This is so wrong.
What am I going to do?
Am I...
going to be okay after this?
Yamazawa deeply respects this other
person besides Shiki Masaoka.
Ms Yamazawa, do you have
a Haiku master?
My master is Itsuki Natsui.
What?
The person who gives such strict
assessments in the Haiku show?
I hope Ms Natsui doesn't watch
this part.
I hope so too.
Let's start the Ehime Japan tour!
First, let's go to Ehime!
I think we all envision tangerines
when we think of Ehime.
Ehime is the foremost producer
of citrus fruits in Japan.
There are over 900 different
varieties of citrus fruits.
This Nakate tangerine
has different varieties as well.
Does it taste different?
This variety is called
"Nankan 20-go."
So this is Citrus Unshu,
Nakate tangerine's Nankan 20-go?
- This is called "Sumo Citrus."
- Sumo citrus is tasty.
It's actually
a variety called "Shiranui."
The product name is "Sumo citrus."
So it's like a real name
and a stage name.
- It's Shiranui in the mountains.
- Shiranui.
Once it's in town,
it's called the Sumo citrus.
When she's in Hokkaido,
she's called Kana Sasamori.
When she's in Tokyo, she's Barbie.
Is it like that?
Now, please take a look
at this book I have here.
It's called "Funny Ways to Peel
A Tangerine."
It's something you do while
you sit around a kotatsu.
It looks like fun. I like it.
Now, please have a look at
funny ways to peel a tangerine.
Ken Hirai's song.
"A caterpillar tangerine"
That's cute.
"Twinkling star tangerine"
That's cute too.
They did a lot there.
"A bracelet tangerine"
That's amazing.
"A ring tangerine"
That's cute too.
"A microphone tangerine"
That's cute.
"A basket tangerine"
How cute.
"A flower tangerine"
- I think that's cute.
- It's cute.
"A watch tangerine"
"A wood block tangerine"
"An earring tangerine"
- She's got a lot there.
- She's wearing them all.
Next, it's Ehime's local contest.
They've gone to Uwa Rice Museum.
They relocated and reconstructed
a former primary school.
We have a corridor-cleaning race.
A corridor-cleaning race?
They call it Z-1 Grand Prix!
A tourist did a corridor cleaning
race once, and it became popular.
And we, the youth league of commerce
and industry, made it into an event.
- So it started with a tourist?
- Yes.
This is the longest corridor in
an existing wooden school building.
This corridor is really something.
Its total length is 109 metres long.
- 109 metres?
100 metres are used for the contest
to see who's the fastest cleaner.
It's not just simple cleaning.
There's a lot more to it.
Is my form good?
You should make several adjustments.
Don't push with your hands
flat on the floor,
just touch it
with your fingertips.
When you touch it with your
fingertips, you get less friction.
When it comes to this,
it's not about cleaning here.
When you're cleaning, you want
to push with your hands flat,
and use that friction
to clean the floor.
If you lift up your hips,
you can move forward more smoothly.
I see.
And the most important advice is...
It's very long,
so never raise your face.
You will be discouraged.
I know. It's so long.
She will be competing against
Hiyori Sadayoshi,
the 2019 champion
in the female division.
I'm a bit worried.
I'm a little concerned
since Imoto seems strong,
from climbing mountains and stuff.
I think this is a great opportunity,
so I'm going to give it my all,
and defeat her.
Imoto, this is your chance to teach
failure to a middle schooler!
Ready...
- Both of them have a clean start.
- Looking good.
- She's good.
- Amazing.
- Go! Go!
- You can do it!
- Looking good.
- Amazing.
It's a close contest.
- It's a close competition!
- Amazing.
The second half of the race
determines the winner.
- Go! Go!
- She's going for it!
She's really going for it!
But now Imoto's feet start to trip.
- 100 metres is long.
- Go for it!
- Ah!
- That's incredible.
She put up a fight, but this
35-year-old lacked the endurance.
She's laughing.
She's laughing hard.
Darn it! I'm so annoyed!
That final 20 to 30 metres...
I would say so.
Around there,
this area was clearly...
I mean, my mind wanted
to move forward,
but my legs wouldn't.
I get that.
No, you don't get it.
You won't get it.
- Do you want to go again?
- I do not!
If we do it again,
you'll have an easier win!
However, we found another
local event just like this one!
The event is held
at a harbour town in Masaki.
We have an H-1 Grand Prix here.
So we had a Z-1, and now
we have an H-1?
Yes, it's H-1.
Hangiri race, H-1 Grand Prix.
Hangiri is a barrel for making miso
and sake, that's cut in half.
During the Edo period in Masaki,
people rode in these to go fishing.
This is a traditional race...
that started 50 years ago,
to maintain the tradition.
Imoto will compete against locals
in this event.
- She will be instructed by...
- She's very cute.
Yuri Kochi, a world record holder
of Hangiri.
What are you currently studying
at the university?
It involves carrying on Hangiri
and other kinds of old traditions.
This is incredible.
Kochi is beaming.
She's looking directly at me,
as if she's cheering me on
for this event.
I would like to match
your expectations.
- I'll do my best. Thank you.
- Thank you.
I'm ready, Kochi!
There are no tools involved
in this race.
You just use the Hangiri, or barrel,
to move forward.
For real?
Is that how it's done?
That's incredible.
It's a series of endless squats,
using the whole body.
Incredible.
Please cool down first.
Even a world record holder
is this fatigued.
That doesn't look good.
It's totally different
from what I had in mind.
Your arms stay straight and firm.
You bend your knees
and push out at the same time.
When you lean forward, the water
is pushed, making it move forward.
With that in mind,
here's the exhibition race.
How far will she go
against experienced participants?
I'm regretting now that I should
have taught you the rhythm...
by being at your side
during practise.
- You're regretting it?
- Yes.
- I see, I see.
- I haven't taught you everything.
- I'm really sorry about that.
- It's fine.
I think with your physical strength
and energy, you'll win at the end.
Yes, I got it.
I think Kochi
is an endangered species.
Have you ever met
such a nice, innocent girl?
Kochi taught Imoto alongside her.
Your elbows are bent.
You're getting tired,
and your knees...
Bend and stretch! You can do it!
She is so nice and innocent,
Imoto can't slack off at all.
Kochi and the pressure
she put on me...
Sincere pressure...
is exhausting.
So this is done at sea?
Yes, so if the waves come
from the side...
- it can affect your position.
- Right.
If the waves come from the front,
you can't move forward at all.
I'm sure.
You can't move forward?
But when you overcome that,
the goal is right there.
She's seriously so positive.
Now, it's time for the race.
Ready.
Set...
Go!
Go for it!
She's matching
the local competitors.
Squat more! Add more power!
Please squat a little more!
Ms Miyazaki in the outer course
goes off the grid.
Look forward! Squat a little more!
Squat! Squat!
A little faster! Faster!
Kochi is shouting out
encouragement!
Squat! Squat! With power!
Squat with power! You can do it!
However, she ended up
in second place.
The hardest placement to react to.
This is no joke.
That was a great effort.
About halfway through the race,
I knew I would place second.
I would just finish,
with no highlights whatsoever.
I thought about falling out halfway,
or going around in circles,
and thought maybe I should dive in,
but Kochi was in front of me...
going, "You got it!"
When I saw her eyes,
I had no option but to continue.
The fact that I was able to do it
with her will be a lifelong memory.
- She's such a good girl.
- I'm so happy.
- Thank you.
I'm so glad you feel that way.
When I see you on TV now,
I'll go, "Oh! I've met her!"
Wait. This is not good.
What am I going to do about that?
It's going to be tough from now on.
What am I going to do
after hearing her say that?
When I come in contact
with someone so genuine,
then I notice more
of my wickedness,
and I feel ashamed of myself.
For some reason, I couldn't look
directly into Kochi's eyes.
I'll do my best to be that person
you were happy to work with...
- when you see me on TV.
- Yes.
- Please stay the way you are.
Please.
Next is a major experiment
done in Ehime.
I'm in Shikokuchuo City.
This town manufactures the most
paper and paper products in Japan.
All the paper products other than
stamps and money are made here.
It's said to be the leading producer
in Japan.
Let's learn a bit about
paper products first.
This is Mr Ohashi
who's in research.
We have different
coloured papers here.
This paper won't dissolve in water.
These are commonly used around us.
What do you think it is, Degawa?
- What?
- It won't melt in water?
It has to be litmus paper.
The correct answer is...
tags for dry cleaners.
People usually think that these
are put on after cleaning.
- I thought so too.
- Right?
It's recorded before it's washed,
and it's washed after the tag
is put on.
- But it won't fall apart.
- It won't.
It's made by a local company here.
I'll be thinking about it now
when I have my clothes cleaned.
I'll think of Shikokuchuo City.
In addition...
- This thin paper...
- It's thin. It's like a tissue.
This is paper made
from a plant called Abaca.
It's thinner and lighter
than tissue paper,
but it's unbelievably durable.
Amazing.
When Imoto, who weighs 50kg,
hangs from it...
look at that!
Since it's so durable,
it's also used for monetary notes.
An experiment to be carried out
in this paper town is...
Do you know what a popgun is?
Popgun? Isn't that the one where
you make a sound with a flyer?
- Here.
- Ah! I remember this!
I used to make them!
Many of you probably played
with these when you were children.
It's called a popgun since it makes
a pop when it's swung down.
The vibration that occurs
when air enters the pocket,
is the cause of the popping sound.
We will make a gigantic one
and see how loud it is.
Will the sound be louder
if the popgun is bigger?
I wonder if it's going to create
an explosive sound?
It will be done in collaboration
with Maruyoshi paper.
What's the biggest size paper
you make here?
Paper made with this machine
has a width of three metres.
Do you think we can make
a gigantic popgun?
I think we can make it.
Will it pop or not?
- We've never made one, so...
- It's hard to tell.
It requires strength and pliability.
They will make it with paper
used for wrapping paper.
This is our project leader,
Mr Yamauchi.
Shall we try it with paper
as big as this room?
This room?
The anticipated size
is 13 metres by 9 metres.
They will attach three sheets
together to create one huge piece.
They will tape them together.
Now, it's done!
It's huge! I think it's about
the same size as a volleyball court.
We have to use our whole body
to fold it.
It's hard work to fold one part.
They spend about an hour
and a half...
to get to the final step
to create this gigantic popgun.
Amazing!
There!
A little forward.
Let me pull it a bit.
The gigantic popgun is made.
It's an isosceles triangle
with a base of 6.5 metres.
I'm actually quite moved.
- We still have an experiment to do.
- Right.
This machine will be used
to swing the paper.
The popgun will be attached to this.
- This is the set up.
- Three, two, one.
Go!
- It made a sound just now.
- It did! It did.
I feel like it's going to work.
It's about whether it opens or not.
And it's a bit windy today.
The wind...
The day was windy,
with the wind blowing at 7m.
It's like the size of a boat,
so it's affected by the wind.
I see.
There's confusion whenever
something gigantic is involved.
Oh?
- It's the opposite, right?
- Opposite?
- Okay, rotate it.
- It's this way.
Wait a second.
This is where we hold it,
so this should be taken to the base.
The paper popgun is in the shape
of an isosceles triangle.
It's confusing to figure out
which side to attach to the machine.
Hold on.
- That's not it! I'm sorry!
- This isn't it?
We put the grip in the wrong place.
What?
- So this thing is wrong?
- This thing is wrong.
- No way!
- Oh no.
This side opens up.
- No, it's right.
- It's right?
Is it right?
- This part opens up.
- That's cute.
So this part does open.
This is the base, so it's all good.
- That's great!
Mr Yamauchi got it
the wrong way around.
- It's a triangle, so...
- I know.
- Oh?
- I'm glad.
Will it make a popping sound?
They attach the paper popgun
to the machine.
- It's hitting it. Wait!
- Be careful!
I want this to be successful.
Now, the gigantic paper popgun
experiment, first attempt.
They use a pendulum swing
with a weight of 100kg for this.
Ready!
- Three, two, one, zero!
- Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Oh no...
- It didn't open.
The wind from the side twisted it
before the pocket opened.
It didn't have much momentum either.
It went up slowly.
I was expecting it to be faster.
Shall we add on a pulling force
from the opposite side?
- From the opposite side?
- Its weight slows it down...
so to accelerate it, maybe
we can pull it from the other side?
Is that done by the men?
Yes, it's done by the men.
Adjusting the machine and replacing
the popgun takes an hour each time.
Three, two, one, zero!
Go! Go!
Ah!
The initial speed was faster,
but the wind made it flap.
This side now?
So when the weight came down,
it had accelerated when it reached
the bottom,
but it seemed to slow down
from there.
- I think so.
- He's right.
From this point,
we need another push.
Without this part, I think it'll be
the same thing all over again.
Now they plan to have the men pull
throughout the whole process.
Three, two, one, zero!
Go! Go! Go!
Its speed increased.
Its rotation was bigger,
but it still won't open.
I think this is the limit, right?
Yes, I think so.
I wonder if we could
do something about it.
Can't we get it to open?
As long as the pocket won't open,
it won't make any popping sound.
What else can they do?
They continued with the experiment
the following day.
They tried several
different methods,
but the results were the same.
Zero!
- Go! Go! Go!
- It's looking good!
It looked so close.
All the men on site seem exhausted.
The sun is about to set soon.
The sun is about to set.
You're right.
For two days,
they had nothing to show.
This is probably the final attempt.
This is our last chance!
I hope it's successful!
Let's go!
Three, two, one, zero!
- Go!
- It's fast!
It opened up!
We did it! We did it!
"We did it"?
- That last one...
- I think we did it!
Zero!
No matter how hard we listen
to it, it didn't make any sound.
However, since the popgun
opened for the first time,
everyone on site seemed to have
a happy-ending vibe.
We did it!
- I think we did it!
- We did it!
They're cheering!
It didn't rip.
- It didn't rip.
- It opened up without ripping.
Just as we planned.
"Just as we planned"?
The project is to see whether
this popgun will pop.
It's not whether the popgun
will open up.
Do you mean this is a grand failure?
What?
However, I have no regrets.
You don't?
- Do you have regrets?
- To finish...
we tried different ways
of folding it,
so I would like to place it
down here.
- The paper, I see.
- Then...
I would like you to get
an aerial shot of it,
with a drone.
- As a memento.
- Oh, a memento.
Are you fine in terms of the popgun?
I'm satisfied about the popgun.
- I have no regrets about it.
- You have no regrets. Okay.
So here's the shot.
When you make a gigantic popgun.
The paper will open up,
but it won't make any sound.
Now, the 11th prefecture,
Ehime is done!
That was a huge experiment.
But didn't you realise it wouldn't
make a sound by the first day?
You know that's not going to make
a clean popping sound!
You knew that's not going to pop.
When you got that aerial shot with
the drone, it was already dark out.
It's not time for that tune.
That music was turned off.
What did you think, Tetsuro?
I want Kochi
as one of my Degawa girls.
Everyone on site loved her too!
When they did the first check
after the first edit,
the director's love for Kochi
was so strong,
that everyone was like
"What is this video for?"
What are we showing here?
- Kochi's segment was long.
- They were like, "What is this?"
- He was in love with her?
- He was in love with her.
They had the camera on Kochi
the whole time.
The world is full of YouTubers who
create and post interesting videos.
This project goes
on location with them,
to create a video to make
the whole world laugh.
This is...
QTube.
He headed to Hokkaido in midwinter.
Let's start with QTube! First up
is activities in extreme cold.
We found an activity like no other.
It's called the blizzard experience.
It recreates a blizzard using
a snowplough and a gigantic fan.
Will he be able to stand it
for five minutes?
Do they all enjoy it
Some of them enjoy it,
and some of them give up.
I'll show you the longest one.
I'll do it for eight minutes.
How long will Nakaoka endure it?
Start the fan!
First, they will start off
by using a shovel.
It's quite painful when the flakes
of snow hit him.
Ah!
Nakaoka is enduring it.
Now, the snowplough is mobilised.
It's a fierce blizzard.
The temperature created
is minus 30 degrees Celsius.
I'm dying here!
No! This is impossible!
Next is a popular performance video.
Nakaoka paints with ink using a mop.
Here I go!
Ha!
That was fast.
Isn't it too fast for that
to happen?
Mountain! Mountain!
It's cold!
He paints wildly for 30 seconds.
This screams failure...
so loudly.
It's impossible to paint well. Once
Nakaoka realises this, his aim is...
Just make it happen.
Make a miracle happen.
...to have some kind of a laugh.
How about I press my face onto here?
Last resort, a face-printing plan.
Is it on?
Make it funny! Make it funny! Yes!
There's nothing funny about that!
Oh no, there's nothing
funny about this.
There's nothing funny about this.
Next up is an action video
using computer graphics.
Nakaoka moves instantly.
How do we make it happen?
As long as you flip at the top.
As long as I flip at the top?
Then the CG will take care
of the rest.
Just flip at the top? I mean,
is that even possible?
First, he'll use a balance ball
to practise.
It will be filmed from an angle
where the ball can't be seen.
Where do you want
to travel to instantly?
Well... to a warm hot spring.
Will Nakaoka be able to travel
to a hot spring instantly?
I'm about to travel instantly!
Yoo hoo!
Ouch.
He slipped and fell.
Darn it!
This bit is slippery.
This is the main area
I have to step on, too.
I'll have to do it barefoot.
Maybe it'll work if I'm barefoot.
Another attempt with bare feet.
Let's go!
There!
It's a success!
Wasn't that good?
- It's so cold!
- That's amazing.
Nakaoka, now we'll get
the landing part too.
No, no, no.
I need a hot spring.
You travelled there instantly,
just now, right?
No, no. I didn't actually go.
Next is an experimental video
using static electricity.
For this, Nakaoka will build up
static electricity,
and touch a florescent light
to see if it will light up.
It's not shining.
However, since the process
is so simple,
please watch it in a story format
created and directed by Nakaoka.
A static electricity yokai
makes its appearance.
Once upon a time,
there was a yokai
who loved static electricity.
Hey, girls...
Give me static electricity.
The yokai summoned young women
on a nightly basis,
and made them rub PVC pipes...
to generate static electricity.
Let me see.
This is great static electricity.
All right, you two...
Generate more static electricity.
What he loved to do was
to light up a florescent light bulb,
using static electricity.
Three,
two, one...
and...
- It lit up!
- It lit up.
It lit just now, right?
It was faint, but it did light up.
Today's static electricity...
was 100 watts.
What is this?
- Next is extreme-cold funny videos.
- What is this?
He will be supported by a partner
to go as close...
as possible to the water surface,
and get back up.
This attempt is done
at a frozen fishing pond.
It's a success if he can use
his mouth to get that marshmallow.
Transparency, zero.
Omori, the camera assistant
will be his partner.
Trust challenge, start!
Nakaoka must trust Omori,
and put himself in Omori's hands.
It's fine. It's fine.
- It's fine. It's not fine.
- I'm bent at the waist.
Nakaoka is hesitant and ends up
bending at his hips.
He won't be able to reach
the marshmallow that way.
- Scold me not to bend my body!
- Okay.
Let's do this.
It's fine. It's fine. It's fine.
It's fine. No! don't bend!
It's such a horrible challenge,
but this is making me laugh.
Another attempt.
- Ready.
- Yes.
Okay.
Don't bend! Don't bend!
- You're doing it!
- Amazing!
You're doing it!
The marshmallow is getting closer.
However...
You're touching it already.
The front of his body
is directly in the water.
Wait.
I'm in the water.
Lower my head!
No!
Lift me back up once.
Lift me back up.
Omori is out of energy
and is unable to lift him back up.
Get me up!
This is enough of a penalty already!
Are you kidding me?
When I ask you to get me up,
then someone else should help too.
They rush over to the sauna.
They have one?
Hey!
Why is he running ahead of me?
Hey! Wait, darn it!
Hey! I get that this is hard.
But we should go in together...
at a time like this.
And why...
are you sitting in the only chair?
Next up, popular videos
from around the world.
Mr Kimura, an associate professor at
Hokkaido University, will assist us.
Let's start the experiment.
We set up a freezer at
a temperature of minus 25 degrees.
Water is sprayed onto his hair
to slowly freeze the hair.
It's already hard?
It is hard.
We even have a secret weapon.
Associate Professor Kimura,
what is that?
Super cooled water.
- Super cooled water?
- I'm thinking of making it.
Super cooled water is cooled
below zero degrees Celsius.
It instantly freezes with
the right stimulus.
This will be used to create icicles
in a short period of time.
I hear a dripping sound.
The water is still flowing
right now.
What? It's flowing?
Yes, it is.
- Associate Professor Kimura?
- Is there something wrong?
It's dripping down,
and the back of my knees are wet.
I don't like this at all.
With Associate Professor Kimura's
earlier simulation,
it went well.
This is not good.
- It was a failure this day.
- Oh no.
As a result, they continued
to mist his hair for an hour,
and Nakaoka was finally released.
It's nice and warm.
This is not good at all for my hair.
How do you expect me to go home?
You know...
It's going to break.
Next, a low budget video.
Just like the
pulling-off-the-tablecloth trick,
he'll pull the cutting board out
and get the eggs into the cups.
The cutting board didn't have
these bumps on there before.
Stuff like this bothers me.
Nakaoka will attempt to get
five eggs into five cups.
It's super hard.
This cutting board
is not stable at all.
The fact that it's tilted that way,
ah!
Boiled eggs.
They're boiled.
The cutting board is warped.
I know, right?
- We have other cutting boards.
- You do? Hold on.
You gave me
the messed up one first?
Is this how it goes?
- That's what it is?
- This is then...
- You can pour stuff into the pot.
- I see.
This is great. Can I have it?
He'll try again using
a regular cutting board.
This one is so much more stable.
Here I go.
Go for it!
Three,
two,
one! There!
- They went in!
- Success in one go!
Amazing!
I did it! It was so clean too!
- That was great.
- I haven't been successful lately.
It's been a while...
since I've felt this accomplished.
Next up are silly videos.
He will collaborate with
world champion tap dancers.
Nakaoka will learn
from them remotely,
and practise upper body moves.
How did it end up looking?
Surprisingly, Nakaoka is pretty
good with his upper body movements.
That's good.
"Seconds to miraculous
synchronisation"
Perfect!
That was perfect!
Next, an extreme-cold video.
His challenge is...
Bouldering?
He'll attempt to see if he can last
for a minute and a half.
However, the difficulty level
increases every 10 seconds.
It has different levels.
When it's on zero,
it doesn't move fast.
As we raise it up,
it will move with your weight.
That's an interesting set up.
Let's do it.
Oh, and if you grab an orange rock,
you'll get zapped.
No way! Stop that!
Nakaoka, bouldering in extreme cold.
Ready...
- Start!
- That looks scary.
Okay.
- Go for it!
- I can do this.
- Looking good.
I can do this.
The wall increases its speed
every 10 seconds.
Ah! There's the orange one!
The orange ones are out.
That's a problem.
- Be careful!
- Okay, it's here.
Now, the speed increases even more.
There are more orange rocks too.
There's another orange one.
Don't be scared of the orange ones.
There are too many orange ones!
It's deeper than I thought!
Pull me out! Pull me out!
Please pull me out!
Pull me out! Don't pull me anymore.
It's too cold! It's too fast!
What do you mean 30 seconds?
- How did it look?
- How many times did we see that?
- It looked like you could do it.
- You thought so?
I won't be fooled by such words.
If anything, we have wetsuits too.
Oh?
What?
Why didn't you say that
at the start?
For his second attempt,
he's geared up in a wetsuit.
- Ready, go!
- Will he succeed this time?
Go for it!
Looking good!
You can do it.
Go for it!
Ten seconds.
Looking good.
- Okay.
- Go for it!
The zapping rock appears.
He barely manages to avoid it.
Looking good.
- Amazing.
- Just one more minute.
- Thirty seconds.
- Ouch!
Ouch!
Nakaoka gives up here.
Wow!
How many seconds was that?
- That was 30 seconds.
- Thirty seconds!
This is no joke.
A zap followed by this cold is...
no joke.
You've never done it before, right?
Human being.
The final clip is Nakaoka's idea
and it's done in Nagano.
I thought of doing
different challenges,
with things I'm good at.
Do you know what I'm good at?
Hockey.
Nakaoka was played for Nara
when he was in secondary school.
This is Nakaoka's proud speciality.
He'll attempt to catch balls
with a hockey stick.
In addition...
- Nakaoka!
- Hello!
What?
This is Sakura Japan,
a team that represents Japan.
They've competed in the Olympics
five consecutive times.
At the world championships in 2018,
they beat New Zealand,
who rank fourth in the world.
This team is expected to do well
at the Tokyo Olympics.
We will do a collaboration
with their major players.
Sakura Japan at their training camp
and Nakaoka will connect remotely,
and aim for everyone to succeed
in a relay format.
Let's do it!
Once again, Nakaoka takes the lead
with his leadership style.
The surface of the stick is rounded
and is therefore unstable.
Oh?
So it's hard to catch the ball.
Oh!
The same goes for Sakura Japan
as well.
There's added pressure of doing it
in a relay, and they fail.
It was your idea to do this, but...
It's kind of a failure.
If players representing Japan
can't do it, then it's impossible.
The terrifying thought of it
being shut down enters his mind...
However, we have a backup plan.
Wow.
I didn't like it
when I saw this before,
but it'll be helpful.
This machine...
has been altered now.
It's a PET bottle rocket
with a powder remote.
This is helpful. Thanks.
Let's do this!
Sakura Japan has 30 more minutes
for this task.
Nakaoka will be the anchor of
the six players passing the ball,
and the rocket on Nakaoka's back
will launch no matter who messes up.
Oh no, I'm seriously nervous here.
I'd feel so bad if I mess up.
Let's get this done...
in one go!
Yes!
Let's show off hockey...
to Japan!
Yes!
Let's do this!
- Please start!
- They're all hyped up to start!
"Yu Asai"
"Yukai Mano"
However, something unexpected
happens with Nakaoka...
What?
- Oh no!
- Ah!
The wind blew so hard
that he didn't get powdered.
Oh no!
This may not make it on air!
And unfortunate events continue
for Nakaoka.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Oh? It stopped.
Their connection got worse.
Their computer shut down.
Their time is almost up.
Nakaoka is under the greatest
pressure he's ever experienced.
Please don't edit out this segment.
They are back online,
but this is their final attempt.
Go for it!
- Ready!
- Let's go!
Let's do this!
Will they succeed?
Go for it!
Sakura Japan continue to practise
during the equipment failure.
They smoothly connect the ball.
- Okay! You can do it!
- They are so cool.
Stay calm! Okay!
"Yuri Nagai"
Five players succeed.
Then it's passed to Nakaoka.
- Okay!
- You can do it!
You can do it! It'll happen.
Sakura Japan, watch this!
Yes!
Nakaoka manages to succeed
miraculously at the very end!
Yes!
I did it! Yes! Yes!
Did you see that?
- Amazing!
- Did you see it?
Did you see that?
I'm so glad.
Now this might make it
onto the show.
That's it for Lotti Nakaoka's QTube.
"QTube, the end"
We see more of Nakaoka's leadership
when we see him in person.
Today, Nakaoka's leadership
was on the weaker side.
When it's done remotely,
it's on the weaker side.
It's revealed that it doesn't work
that well when it's remotely done.
What? You said it was gross,
but now you're telling me
it's not enough?
- What do you want me to do?
- I'm sorry.
On top of that, I don't do well
when I'm doing it remotely?
If I don't do well remotely
in this day and age,
I'll lose my job.
Uchimura.