Now, off we go!
The Quest has started.
Tonight, we have "Imoto Japan Tour"
and the calendar project.
"Ayako Imoto, Tetsuro Degawa,
Daisuke Miyagawa, Asako Ito"
"Kazuko Kurosawa, Tomoko Murakami,
Miyuki Oshima"
This time, I went to Miyagi.
What is your impression of Miyagi,
everyone?
- Beef tongue.
- I'd say beef tongue.
- Masamune Date.
- That's a good one.
- That's typical.
- Yes, that's Miyagi.
So Miyagi is well-known for those,
but the atypical Miyagi...
I think people usually
don't know this about Miyagi.
I'm sure there's a lot
we don't know.
Yes, lots of unknown and
unexpected things were uncovered.
We also went ahead
and worked on the calendar project.
- So that's what you did.
- Yes.
I've had some rare
and special experiences.
Oh, I can't wait to see it.
- So this is a Miyagi special?
- Yes, it is.
This whole episode is about Miyagi.
- That's incredible.
- All right. Let's get started.
The Quest!
- Yeah!
- Yes!
There it is. It's coming.
They're like dolphins.
This is like a dolphin show.
Wow. It's like they're making
a tunnel.
Now, off we go!
"Boarding the Blue Impulse
Imoto Miyagi Tour"
Conquer all 47 prefectures of Japan.
Rare animal hunter Imoto,
Japan Tour!
The featured prefecture today
is in central Tohoku region,
Miyagi prefecture.
- Masamune Date, see?
- Hello.
Hello, hello. Imoto here.
I'm currently in Miyagi.
Can you see where I am right now?
Now, the usual "Where's Imoto?"
What?
Near that rock.
I'm here! I'm right here!
- I'm here!
- What a colour.
- The correct answer is a pathway
- What colour is that?
at Miyagi's beautiful Zao Mountains!
I apologise. I'm being a nuisance.
Please take a look
at where I am right now.
There!
- Is that real?
- This represents the Zao Mountains.
This here is the Okama Crater.
It's the vista point.
It's pretty intense here.
- It has "The Earth" feel.
- It sure does.
This basin was created as a result
of an eruption about 800 years ago.
This is a crater lake created
with rainwater, snowmelt,
and spring water from the mountains.
- It's a crater lake?
- It's amazing.
Its diameter is about 330 metres.
It's a rare terrain
created by nature.
My impression of Zao is where people
from Asako's generation
would come to ski.
- That's what I thought.
- The way you said that...
There is a specific reason
why we came to Miyagi this time.
- We'll do the calendar project.
- I see.
It will be taken
at JASDF Matsushima Airbase
in Higashi Matsushima, Miyagi.
This time,
you'll go on-board the Blue Impulse
to take a wonderful picture.
I'm going aboard the Blue Impulse?
May of 2020,
to show appreciation and respect
for all the medical professionals,
Blue Impulse flew
over the skies of Tokyo.
This is awesome.
Imoto will experience
the flight skills
of the Blue Impulse,
which will be photographed
for the calendar.
I'm in shock.
I thought that was for viewing only.
No kidding.
- I'm a bit nervous,
- I'd be scared.
but I'm looking forward
to riding it.
I'd like to get a good picture.
But before we get to that,
a little report on Miyagi.
Yes, please.
A rare animal that's found
at the foothill of Mount Zao.
This is it.
Ta-da! It's a fox.
I didn't know about it at all.
So Miyagi is known for foxes?
The zoo director, Sato,
will show us around.
I was told
there are lots of foxes here.
This is the only facility in Japan
that has foxes
running around freely.
They're running around freely?
Yes, they are. They'll come up
to you, like to here.
Many will come towards you.
What? They come flocking around you?
Today, they're so happy
that you came, they'll come up here.
Will they know who I am?
- They'll know who you are.
- Seriously?
Yes.
They head
right into the fox village.
They're out here to greet you.
- There's a lot here.
- So cute.
We have about 120 foxes
that run freely here.
- I just saw something horrible.
- Yes?
I just saw that sign,
and it says they bite you a lot
in this area.
Please move on.
- Do they bite?
- Yes, they do bite.
What?
- Does it hurt?
- You'll go to the hospital.
- What?
- No, no, no.
If you don't like it, then go...
- Does that work?
- Then they won't come.
- I got it.
- As long as you don't reach out,
- they won't bite.
- I got it.
Now, let's take a look
at a fox's characteristics
with Sato.
First, how they sound.
Wow! Did you hear that?
It's almost like a bark.
When they scream like that,
they're giving you a warning.
See? They bark like a dog.
They don't yelp?
They only yelp twice a year,
when a fox pup is calling
its mother.
A male and female will yelp
during the mating season too.
The next characteristic is...
Can you tell what they're doing?
What are they doing?
Are they fighting?
- They're fighting.
- Oh, they're fighting.
They show off their teeth
to one another.
They open their mouth
and show off who has better teeth.
Foxes threaten one another
by opening their mouths wide open.
Sometimes, a fight could last
longer than an hour.
Foxes don't scuffle.
They're smarter than humans
because they don't scuffle.
- They don't harm one another?
- No, they don't.
They're smart.
Then...
Oh, they're going at it.
What's going on?
You said they don't fight,
but they're fighting hard!
They figured
they're at the same level.
No, they're fighting hard.
They're still showing off
their teeth, though.
They're showing off their teeth,
but they're going at each other.
That's something else.
This is no laughing matter.
That was a scuffle, right?
That's not a scuffle.
No, that's a scuffle.
- Let's gather them around.
- It's too soon.
- Who was that?
- Who is that?
He's the owner of the fox village
and Mrs Sato's husband.
When your husband came,
look at what happened to the foxes.
Who is he?
Foxes have good hearing.
- Amazing.
- Therefore,
they recognise the owner immediately
by his footsteps.
That's something else.
All the foxes are gone now.
That guy took them with him.
I'm sorry all the foxes are--
"Ha ha ha"
He does this all the time.
It's such a problem.
Come.
They get the foxes back with food
to start over.
However...
That is not allowed.
The guests will try to do
the same thing.
That's not allowed.
You can't feed them.
I'm not feeding them!
What's more interesting
than the fox's characteristics
is the characteristics
of a married couple.
Imoto and I are...
Are you listening to me?
We fed them to get a shot of Imoto
and me being surrounded by foxes.
Don't interrupt!
You never told me that.
Are you two having an argument?
- We're arguing.
- Are you two showing your teeth?
It couldn't be resolved.
They report their characteristics
at the petting area.
This is Konta.
- Look.
- This is Konta. He's 10 years old.
The outstanding characteristic
of a fox is its tail.
Look how thick his tail is,
but the actual thickness
is like this.
The rest is all fur.
At the top of its tail
is a scent gland.
One theory is that it smells sweet
like violet.
If you rub it and smell it,
then I think you would...
This part is really...
It stinks!
It really stinks!
What is this smell?
Do you want me to smell it?
That is not that sort of smell.
No, no, no.
It has a floral scent.
It smells like violet.
No way. That's a lie.
You're defending the fox too much.
You love them too much.
This really does smell
like a violet.
Now that she said that...
- It smells really good.
- It stinks!
It stinks!
I don't want this part any more!
What am I going to do?
This part really stinks.
This joint at my index finger
is stinking bad.
Take it back to Tokyo as a souvenir.
No, thank you!
It'll be a nuisance
in the bullet train on my way home.
- Next, Miyagi's beautiful scenery.
- That's so funny.
It's one of the three views
of Japan, Matsushima.
Matsushima is one
of the three scenic views of Japan.
Let's enjoy
the popular aerial tour here.
Yamaya will assist us.
We'll fly using this motor?
- Yes, we'll use this motor
- There it is.
and a paraglider to fly in the air.
I've only seen it from the ground.
Would it be different from the sky?
It's completely different.
It's a completely different world
from what you're imagining now.
I can't wait to see this.
I wonder what it's like.
Let's go!
An aerial tour of Matsushima
in a motored paraglider!
That's nice.
Wow.
It's rapidly rising up in the air.
They quickly rose up to 300 metres.
However, the area
was suddenly covered in clouds.
That's a little scary.
- I can't see Matsushima at all.
- That's too scary.
However...
This is fantastic
in its own way, though.
You have about 10 days a year
where you can fly
over the sea of clouds.
What? So in a way, I'm lucky.
You've got it.
For real? Seriously, I've never seen
such a beautiful view like this.
This is strange.
This might be more magnificent
than Matsushima.
This is like Nausicaa
or Laputa's world.
Since we're here,
how about you compose a haiku?
- Like Basho.
- Yes.
- That's so sudden.
- Oh, Matsushima
- They ask you to do that suddenly?
- Where are you, Matsushima?
- You're right.
- Thank you very much.
- She ended it.
- The aerial view of Matsushima
will be shown later in the footage.
Next, she'll report on
the most unique ruins in the world.
They head to a place
15 minutes away from Sendai Station.
I'm going to present ruins
right now,
but take a look behind me.
It's an ordinary residential area.
Hiratsuka, a curator,
will show us around.
Is it really here,
at a place like this?
Actually, this location here
is the ruins
I'm going to show you now.
- Here?
- Yes.
We did an archaeological survey
in 1987 and 1988.
That's the place I'm taking you to.
- Then, you found it?
- Yes.
What is this valuable ruins
they found 33 years ago?
- It's huge.
- What is it?
What?
I wasn't expecting this at all.
- Is this a tree?
- Yes.
It's a tree from 20,000 years ago
during the Ice Age.
Lots of its roots
are found in this area.
This is the Tomizawa Site,
where a forest from 20,000 years ago
is preserved.
A tree from 20,000 years ago
remains in shape?
Groundwater is the reason
why these trees were preserved well.
The tree was submerged
in groundwater,
so it wasn't broken down
by microorganisms
and remained underground
for 20,000 years.
And in the forest...
It says "signs of a bonfire."
- Signs of a bonfire?
- Yes.
Back when this area was a forest,
a group of people thought to be
our ancestors were here
- and had a bonfire.
- That's incredible.
I wonder
how those people lived here.
Yes. We may be able to meet them.
- We might be able to meet them?
- That forest
is recreated around this building.
So I might be able to meet them?
They recreated the forest
outside of the building.
Then, there...
- Wait, someone is coming.
- What is that?
Aren't they from the Stone Age?
- Hey.
- Hello.
If you're lucky, you can meet
Stone Age people here.
What is that?
It's like a pole made of wood.
They put up a pillar?
Hello.
What are you doing over there?
What?
- FK.
- FK?
FK.
They don't understand me.
They don't speak the language.
I guess they're going hunting?
I see.
There it is. There's a deer.
There's a deer there.
There's a huge deer there.
During that period,
they threw spears with a stone tip
to capture their prey.
- Will he get it?
- That's amazing.
He threw it. He sucks.
Oh, that was bad.
The deer would have escaped by now.
On top of that--
Oh, they suck.
That's too close.
You suck.
This is a weapon made with a stone.
This is quite sharp.
- It's like a knife.
- That's incredible.
They used this to cut things, right?
Wow.
Incredible.
It's like a utility knife.
Seriously?
- Wow, it's super cool.
- Oh, my.
What they ate besides venison is...
Pine nut.
Pine cones.
Can you eat that?
They're showing it to the camera.
They ate meat, as well as kernels.
Then...
This is too close.
Being close is not good.
He said, "Being close is not good."
- Being close is not good?
- He's worried about
being too close to one another.
Hey, you're too close.
You're too close.
- Is it too close?
- Yes, it's a bit close.
You should spread apart.
Keep your distance.
- They had that back then too?
- Of course not.
With Corona.
Right.
Next, a collaboration
with a world-renowned entertainer.
The name is Shiro-A.
- They're super famous, right?
- What is this Shiro-A?
Shiro-A is an entertainment group
that combines techno sound
with digital images and performance.
Ever since it was formed in 2002,
they've performed over 500 shows
in 31 countries.
Tonight, Shiro-A and Imoto
will do a collaboration.
It's an original
The Quest performance.
These are Keisuke Kawashima,
Yohei, and Daiki from Shiro-A.
Are Shiro-A members from Miyagi?
The original members
are from Miyagi.
There are 18 of us now.
So the people back there
are also Shiro-A members?
Yes, the video artist,
sound engineer, and the director.
We're able to do a performance
with just us here.
I was told I can do a collaboration
with you today.
I want to liven it up with you all.
They have three hours to practise.
She will do
Shiro-A's notable performances,
as well as The Quest's
collaboration piece.
I have a lot to learn.
I want to deliver a perfect piece
and enjoy it at the same time.
However,
there's no time to enjoy it.
That's difficult. That's hard.
- That's incredible.
- That's a lot of work.
It is a lot of work.
- Where did she go?
- That's hard in such a short time.
I can't get used to it at all.
I can't miss a beat.
You can't miss a beat.
The images can't be adjusted
no matter what.
- So we need to move to it.
- They need to adjust to that.
I can't see anything from my side.
That makes it harder.
Please take a look.
Shiro-A with Imoto,
the special performance starts!
Go for it.
The opening act is a gorgeous
dance performance by Shiro-A.
That's wonderful.
That's amazing.
Imoto is about to appear.
There she is.
"Imoto"
She's on-beat.
- Looking good.
- Amazing.
Amazing.
It's coming back.
There's Imoto.
It was a close-to-perfect
performance up to this point.
Now, the dance move advances.
Go for it!
That's why Imoto is on standby.
"Imoto"
Now, Imoto will make
her appearance again.
Go for it.
- Looking good.
It's incredible.
- Wow. Amazing.
- It's amazing.
Next is the Movie Catcher.
- What?
- That looks hard.
Imoto can't see the image,
so she'll have to move
with the timing as she was taught.
That's something else.
- That's fast.
- This is no joke.
This is scary.
- Amazing.
You can't be off.
The last performance is Box,
a popular performance
that uses nine boxes.
This is The Quest's
original version.
You learned it well.
It's like a slot machine.
- Oh?
- I...
- Mo...
- To.
Imoto can't see the images
in this performance either.
If you miss the timing
and the order to hit the box,
it won't work as a show.
I'm glad.
Asako.
There's Asako.
Amazing.
What was that?
They're bouncing it.
Asako is all over the place.
What is that?
Interesting.
This is incredible.
Morisanchu.
Amazing.
The back screen is utilised well
to deliver this great performance.
This must be difficult.
What a timing.
This is fun!
- Amazing.
It's so interesting.
Amazing.
"Ro-To-I-Shi-Ra-A-Bo-Ko-Mo"
What?
- Imoto, Shiro-A Collaboration.
- Amazing.
- Oh, could that be?
- Oh?
It's coming.
It's amazing.
No way!
Another one.
- This is great.
- Amazing.
How could they remember all that?
Shall I eat you?
They performed well.
Amazing.
That was great!
I had fun doing it.
I think The Quest collaboration
was fun for the viewers too.
Because of the current situation,
you can't perform live
with an audience,
- but you hold online events.
- Yes.
So please go and check them out.
Thank you very much.
Finally, a calendar photo shoot
in the Blue Impulse!
Now, to take care of the main event,
let's head over
to JASDF Matsushima Airbase.
- Good morning.
This person who greeted us is...
Blue Impulse's 13th captain,
- ASDF Lt. Col. Yuki Ento.
- Amazing.
I was told that you were flying
the Blue Impulse
that flew over Tokyo?
Yes, I was flying the first plane
as the flight leader.
I was watching it in Tokyo.
- I was so touched.
- That's incredible.
Thank you very much.
29th of May, 2020.
Blue Impulse flew
over the skies of Tokyo.
Captain Ento was taking the lead
- of the formation.
- Captain.
What exactly is the Blue Impulse?
Matsushima Airbase's 11th Flight
Training Wing is the official name.
We call it Blue Impulse,
by its nickname.
It's an aerobatic team.
I see.
The squadron was formed in 1960.
They do aerobatic performances
during national events,
major events, or at an air festival.
This is cool.
They promoted the existence of JASDF
in and outside of Japan.
I was told
that I'm able to go on it?
By the way, can civilians...
It's not very common.
Only the famous people who've gone
to the top will go on it
to promote it to the world.
That's a major responsibility
for me.
If you could just do
your job well...
No, but...
Now, let's go see Blue Impulse.
Wow, there's a lot here!
It's full of Blue Impulse.
Are these all Blue Impulse?
Isn't it a great view?
- Wow, it's so cool.
- Amazing.
- It's amazing.
- It's incredible.
I like the blue and the white.
And at half past 6 in the morning,
- How did we manage to get it?
- every day at this time,
the Blue Impulse training starts.
It's like an opening.
- It's like a theatre.
- Yes, like curtains are rising.
Blue Impulse is cool.
It's like an athlete
of the airplane industry.
It has absolutely no body fat.
It has a trim body.
It's 13 metres in length.
It's a specialised
aero-acrobatic plane,
Blue Impulse T-4.
It's an all domestically-made
jet airplane, including its engines.
Its fastest speed
is 1,000 kilometres per hour.
What is this?
You know how Blue Impulse smokes
during a performance?
- Yes.
- This is where it comes out of.
- What? It's this small?
- Yes.
In here is a clear oil.
It instantly vaporises with the heat
to produce smoke.
And it looks like white smoke
to our eyes?
- That's how it works.
- She'll board inside the cockpit.
- That's amazing.
- It's tight in here.
It's super tight in here.
It really is a cockpit.
That index finger
is the switch for the smoke.
While that's pushed,
it's constantly going.
It stops when you let it go.
This is nice.
- Do you want it now?
- I want it.
Do you think I could get it
if I try hard?
I think so. It's 2.3 billion yen.
I can't do it.
You've gone to the top, you know.
They always have a briefing session
before their training.
We will check the weather now.
- Current wind, 0807 knots.
- So cool.
What's important here is to go over
the weather condition with everyone.
They have to get a grasp
of the wind direction
and the temperature
and utilise that in flight.
In addition, they have
several other matters they go over,
such as accidents that happened
in the past on that day.
What a cool meeting.
I think this may be
the coolest meeting in the world.
Have you ever said "abort mission"
in a meeting?
When you think about it,
entertainment industry lingo
is lame.
You know, lingo for "midnight"
and "mark" onstage.
I think I might stop using
those terms now.
I think saying "start time" is lame.
I'll say "entry" from now on.
My entry is at half past 1
in the afternoon.
They're going to have
a flight training,
so we'll be able to show you all
amazing acrobatic aerial acts.
Let's watch
the Blue Impulse's aerial training.
Amazing!
The take-off is a highlight too.
It's a low-angle Cuban take-off
where they just fly off the runway.
- That's amazing.
- It's incredible.
Incredible.
Look how close it is.
It's coming.
Amazing.
It's incredible!
One jet is coming.
Wow! That's perfect!
Wow. It's turned over!
It's incredible.
It's coming again.
Wow, it's rolling.
"Inverted and continuous roll"
Wow!
"Level opener"
Blue Impulse's pilots
are the best of their kind.
They're able to fly
several fighter planes,
and only the most skilful flyers
are assigned to the team.
Amazing.
They're rolling.
"Inverted roll"
They're like dolphins.
This is like a dolphin show.
There it is.
They fly in a straight line while
the plane is positioned at an angle.
This is called
the double knife edge.
"Double knife edge"
Amazing!
I see them coming
from the right and the left.
Opposite continuous roll is where
they cross paths at a close range.
"Opposite continuous roll"
A little imprecision,
and they will crash head-on.
And the last one is a power move,
the corkscrew.
It's coming.
Wow!
It's like they're making a tunnel.
- This is incredible.
- What is this?
- Amazing.
- And inside that loop...
Wow, amazing!
The G-force must be no joke
right now.
What a fantastic show.
Did you see any tricks
you wanted to do?
For now...
I didn't want to try
any of those tricks.
I prefer to watch those tricks.
They returned safely
after a 40-minute training session.
I enjoyed watching it.
I had the best seat.
- It was wonderful. Thank you.
- Thank you.
What did you think
of Blue Impulse's performance?
It was super fast.
I'm planning to have you undergo
training before you go on-board.
- What? Training?
- Yes.
That's right.
You can't just go on it that easily.
They need to gain knowledge
and skills to deal with the G-force
that's experienced inside the plane.
However,
Imoto is magnificently experienced.
Captain, I've been doing
some hectic things abroad
for this show.
G-force too.
If you think I'm qualified,
then let me know.
- Yes, I will consider it.
- Yes, please consider it.
She's talking about the wing walking
she tried in the United States.
The G-force and wind pressure
felt on the body are extraordinary.
- This is no joke.
- This is incredible.
Will she be able to bypass
the training with this?
This is me.
It's flying very slowly.
No, it was super fast.
If it's at this speed,
this jet will crash.
It will stall.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Then, how about the one in England
where she did a flip?
He should be happy about this one.
How about this one?
I see.
The G-force here was no joke.
- It seems that way.
- Yes, it is.
But you were able to raise your hand
with this G-force.
I worked really hard for it.
I think this is no comparison.
- For real?
- Yes.
- This won't do.
- That's amazing.
There's no way for her
to avoid this training.
I see.
The training will be done
at Hamamatsu Base in Shizuoka.
- Shizuoka?
- At a different location?
So then...
We're here now at JASDF
Hamamatsu Airbase in Shizuoka.
I'm standing in front of their gate.
Here, they study
aviation physiology,
- as well as other knowledge
- It's a classroom.
required to go on-board
a fighter jet.
She has a name card too.
The most important knowledge
is the breathing method
while enduring the G-force.
At JASDF,
we recommend hook breathing.
You say "hook" and do it
in three-second increments.
Hook.
When you utter the K,
you breathe out at the same time.
Once you're done breathing out,
take a breath in right away.
Hook.
- Hook.
- Amazing.
It actually makes me suffer more.
- They also watch scary videos.
- What is it?
What? Hook breathing?
It's not done properly.
He's not completely breathing out.
If they can't do the hook breathing,
they may pass out
due to the G-force.
Are you okay?
Oh, no.
Matsumoto.
He can't hear any more.
- Can you hear me? Are you okay?
- Yes.
He's not okay.
I didn't want to watch that.
That's terrifying.
Well, you might actually
consider that as fun.
No, that's not fun at all.
In addition, inside one
of the three special rooms in Japan,
they undergo low pressure training.
Oh, this should be okay for her.
This room is at an elevation
of 7,500 metres right now.
They have women in there too.
They take their oxygen mask off
to check to see if their brain
is functioning properly.
- However, Imoto has climbed Manaslu
- She's fine on this one.
- at an elevation of 8,163 metres.
- She has experience.
As a result...
I've got a certificate to show
that I've completed
the low pressure training.
- It's valid until 2025.
- Was this the connection?
I can go on it for a while.
Let's go on the Blue Impulse
and share how cool it is.
Imoto is finally going on-board
the Blue Impulse.
This time, I'd like to get
a great photo and a video
of me riding the Blue Impulse.
It's also for the calendar project.
You got it.
First, I need you to decide
- which jet plane you want to board.
- What?
- I can choose?
- Yes.
As you know, there are six jets.
Blue Impulse
has a total of six jets.
Each jet has a different role
and flight technique.
You can choose it by their face too.
Their face?
Each pilot has
their own characteristics.
- What? I can decide like that?
- That's what he meant?
Yes.
So, off to an interview
with the pilots.
Captain, I'm curious
about one thing.
- Should I not mention it?
- Go ahead.
He's one of the members.
He's alive, right?
Yes, of course.
Don't be alarmed.
He was at his wife's side
when she delivered their baby.
I hope they have a healthy baby.
I'm glad.
For this,
it will be a four-jet flight.
However, depending on which jet
Imoto chooses out of the six,
their moves and formation
will change.
Now, let's introduce the pilots
and each jet's functions.
Thank you.
There are three pilots
in the first jet taking the lead.
The first jet is in command
of all the members as the leader
and flies at the lead
of the formation.
The safety of all the pilots
is the priority during flight,
and so, this is the only jet
Imoto won't be able to go on.
So we asked about the TAC name,
the pilot's nickname.
By the way, what is yours, Ento?
- It's Cherry.
- It's Cherry?
- I'm originally from Yamagata.
- I see.
It's known for cherries.
What a great reason.
How about this "Jackie" for you,
Hirakawa?
I sort of look like Jackie Chen.
- I see.
- "Chen."
Gon...
I love Gon Nakayama from Shizuoka.
Oh, so this "Gon"
is from Gon Nakayama?
So the paperwork I received says
that a senior member said,
"You look like a primitive man."
- So this isn't it?
- That's it too.
Both of them are right.
When I try to make it short,
I mention Nakayama.
What's with that pattern?
That's the reason?
Next, the third jet pilots
are Yusuke Kubo
and Takaharu Onitsuka.
The third jet's function is to be
on the right side of the first jet.
We maintain the symmetry
of formation with the second jet.
We watch the first and second jets
to join the formation.
We have to be upside down
- while we approach the first jet.
- That'd be incredible.
It's so close that you think
you'd crash into it.
- So it's quite aggressive?
- Yes, it is.
I sort of like the third jet too.
Next, the fourth jet's pilot
is Kota Nagaoka.
I didn't notice it earlier,
but when I look up close,
you have a nice face.
You have a wonderful face.
- Thank you very much.
- Not at all.
Not at all.
The fourth jet is usually
at the rear of the formation.
- Okay.
- This might be interesting.
So that's the best place
to see Blue Impulse?
You can watch Blue Impulse
while enjoying all the moves.
The fourth jet might have
the best view.
- You're exactly right.
- It might be the case.
The pilot for the fifth jet
is Moritoshi Kawano.
Gabai. Gabai.
The fifth jet's position
is called the lead solo.
Lead solo?
It's in charge
of a solo flight performance.
That's the position.
So would it be the jet that does
the most acrobatic moves?
It rolls by itself
and does this on its own.
I see.
It's Blue Impulse's star position.
The solo acrobatic flight
has many highlights,
and the world's best flight
techniques could be experienced.
It would rise up rapidly
and roll around really fast.
You'll sweat your head off.
That sounds terrifying.
Pilots for the sixth jet are
Takahiro Sato and Naritaka Manabe.
I think the fifth jet's pilot,
Gabai, mentioned it.
Our two jets perform together.
So the fifth and the sixth jets
specialise in acrobatic moves?
The sixth jet's biggest highlight
is this spiral move,
in a corkscrew.
This is something else.
It's like constantly spinning
in 5G-force.
5G-force?
It actually feels nice
when you're experiencing it.
No, no, no.
Please choose jet number six.
No way!
I'm sorry. Not today.
- Which jet did Imoto choose?
- They all looked interesting.
I'll share my decision.
The jet I'm thinking
of boarding is...
- jet number four with Nagaoka!
- Yes!
After all that,
she chose based on his looks.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you. I'm counting on you.
- Yes, sure.
- Thank you very much.
The fact that you mentioned
how you can watch the three jets
while in flight...
I really wanted
- to see that view this time.
- I want to see it too.
Please enjoy the flight
on Blue Impulse.
Yes. I want to enjoy it.
I think I can enjoy
the view as well.
A final meeting before boarding.
Attention.
- Salute.
- Thank you.
Today, we'll be flying Blue Impulse
with four jets.
This is the meeting.
30th of September.
Call sign. Blue Impulse.
Take-off is "individual normal."
Come up into the air individually
in increments.
I see birds here and there
out there.
We will change the altitude
as needed.
Go up in 07, then make a right turn.
250 knots at 1,000 feet.
I think we don't have to worry
about the clouds right now.
But if you notice something,
just let us know, Gabai.
Tommy, you're basically
on weather check.
Yes.
Imoto, do you have any concerns?
So it's delta roll wide
and Opotra Lolicon?
That's exactly it.
Got it.
You took down lots of notes.
What did you write down?
Birds are here and there.
Now, the moment
we've been waiting for.
This is an opportunity.
It's not like you can pay for it
to go on the Blue Impulse.
I'm really lucky
to be able to go on it.
Salute to the mechanics.
Salute.
Thank you.
Your life depends on them.
They prepare to board.
It's so tight.
From this moment onwards,
this seat and I are one.
In worst case scenario,
I'll be ejected out of here
with this seat.
Which one shouldn't you touch?
This one.
Isn't it tempting to touch there?
They especially made this helmet
for Imoto for this day.
I'll do my best.
I'll go enjoy it.
Captain Ento's jet number one
in the lead will head to the runway.
They cheer for Imoto,
who will also be taking off
into the air.
They did the Q sign for The Quest.
I'm able to board this thing,
thanks to so many people.
This is also part of the promotion
for JASDF,
plus for enjoyment.
I'll make this flight
so that the viewers will have fun
watching it above them.
She finally takes off into the sky
with the Blue Impulse.
All right, shall we get going?
- Yes, finally! Let's go!
- Yes!
- Let's have fun!
- Let's be energetic!
Jet engine is on.
Amazing.
Take-off.
- It's so cool.
The first jet took off just now.
Go for it!
- We're heading up.
- Yes, please!
- Okay.
- And they're off.
Let's go!
Number four jet, take off!
- We're going up.
- Yes.
It just took off.
Amazing.
Wow!
We're approaching the two jets
to the left-front of us.
Wow!
Amazing.
We can get this close to them?
The two jet planes
- are right in front of us.
- Oh, man.
It's flying right in front of me.
Amazing.
- What a view.
- It's amazing.
- What is this?
And what started
to appear below is...
I see Matsushima
- that I couldn't see the other day.
- It's Matsushima.
Matsushima is clearly seen today.
Matsushima, 20 kilometres away
from the base,
- is only a two-minute flight.
- Low altitude is amazing.
The speed
is 800 kilometres per hour.
They keep the jets
within 5 metres of one another.
They're so close.
This is the flight technique
of Blue Impulse,
the best in the world.
Amazing.
Imoto, a final check.
How is your physical condition?
I'm fine.
"Ready"
They maintain a high speed
while turning to the right.
They maintain the same angle.
It's totally different
from a regular airplane.
The sensation of just sitting here
in the Blue Impulse now
is completely different
from a regular airplane.
It's speed, for one,
but I feel it all over my body.
Now, they release the smoke!
It's completely different.
Three jets are releasing smoke
right now.
Oh, they're releasing smoke
It's amazing.
Amazing.
Now, the three jets
will fly in formation.
- I'll approach them.
- Yes.
I sense G-force when we turn.
"One smoke"
Smoke is being released.
This is an echelon formation.
Okay.
It's a diagonal formation
with jet number one taking the lead.
This is an echelon formation.
That is so cool.
It's so close.
The jets are so close
to one another.
Imoto, how are you feeling?
- I'm fine.
- Yeah!
Lots of clouds are seen this day,
but the peak of the blue sky,
the ground full of greenery,
and the body of the Blue Impulse
shine beautifully
against the backdrop.
Right now, we keep our distance
visually to fly.
You can see the town clearly below.
Cherry...
It's very pretty.
Ash, is Imoto okay?
- She's fine.
- Okay.
Now, we'll start applying G-force.
Now, the acrobatic part is starting.
G-force is being applied.
Four jets form a diamond shape,
a 360 horizontal turn.
It's a diamond 360.
Now, it's 3G-force.
3G-force?
On. This is 3G-force.
Wow, 3G-force.
It seems elegant,
but inside the jet
is a harsh G-force.
This is incredible.
Wow, hold on!
- Hold on.
- Yes.
Now, we'll flip.
- I'm going to do two moves.
- Yes.
Here we go!
We'll be turning to the right.
Ready...
There.
Ready... There.
The body of the jet doesn't budge
at all. It's a magnificent turn.
Okay!
How was it?
Amazing.
It's something else, but I'm okay.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
Now that she's okay,
here's the real deal!
Now, we'll flip!
Yes, we're flipping!
This is double farvel,
where jet one and four are flipped.
- Okay, let's go.
- There they go.
I'm upside down!
- Let's go.
- There they go.
I'm upside down!
What an incredible situation.
I'm going to approach them.
He's approaching them
while being flipped.
They close in quickly where
they can almost touch one another.
He's approaching them
while being flipped.
That's close! That's close!
"Recover, ready"
Okay.
- That's amazing.
- It's incredible.
It's impressive.
- It's amazing.
Right turn.
- We'll do one more move.
- Okay.
The next one is the last move.
The finale
is Blue Impulse's signature move
that's been handed down
for generations.
- It's the falling combat pitch.
- Ready.
"One smoke"
- It's going to start now.
- Okay, it's starting.
There will be some G-force,
so hang on tight.
Thank you!
Please watch for
the rhythmical moves of the jets
and the smoke that forms lines
behind them.
I'm going to turn right.
Wow!
Amazing!
Amazing.
With the turn and a sudden fall,
she's feeling the maximum 4G-force.
- Amazing.
- 4G-force?
Imoto finished a 40-minute flight.
Blue Impulse is cool.
I'm so happy. I'm the first woman
to ride the Blue Impulse.
You know, as a civilian.
And the aerial view of...
That was Matsushima, right?
Yes, that was Matsushima.
I didn't get any view from the sky
the other day,
so I got to see it clearly today.
I was so shocked to see how it was.
It was gorgeous from above.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
I really had a great time.
He told me everything,
like what's going to happen next.
Ash gets motion sickness easily too.
He said that since he gets
motion sickness easily,
he was determined to fly it
so that we don't get sick.
He flew it gently
for a Blue Impulse.
I was truly grateful for that.
- Captain, thank you very much.
- Thank you very much.
It was very valuable. I am honoured.
- I'm glad.
- Honestly.
I actually wanted to go higher
and be more aggressive,
but because of the clouds...
- Well, maybe some other time.
- Right.
- Something wilder.
- You can do a lot more, right?
Thank you very much.
It was a great experience.
Thank you.
And for the calendar,
it's this shot!
That's it for Japan Tour.
Miyagi has been conquered.
That was wonderful.
I've done G-force experiments
with NASA before.
What's impressive about Imoto
is that she does an interview
like it's nothing
right after the flight.
It's unthinkable.
You know, you're the Tom Cruise
of The Quest.
No, not at all.
You climb mountains.
- You rock climb as well.
- Impressive.
You make "Mission: Impossible"
possible.
No, no.