"The Quest"
"This programme aired
on 3rd January 2021"
Ladies and gentlemen...
- Happy New Year!
The Quest, New Year Special
has started!
Yeah!
I heard through the grapevine
that Chen went all out,
so his footage is longer,
but mine was cut out.
- Is that how it works?
- Is that so?
Now, the first bit is this!
A New Year party trick tour,
challenged accepted by Uchimura!
Yeah!
A tour?
Acquire...
What? But it's a tour?
So we visit several places?
Yes, you'll tour around
acquiring party tricks.
- But, a tour?
- He's stuck on the word tour.
It'll take time.
Aren't you concerned about the idea
of acquiring party tricks?
I'm more concerned about the tour,
than acquiring party tricks.
He will go on tour to find...
three traditional and unique
performances around Japan.
Wait a second.
Am I doing this alone?
- It will be a lonesome process.
- He doesn't like that.
Actually, this time,
- since you get lonely easily--
- I don't get lonely easily.
I never said that
I get lonely easily.
I said that it would be
a lonesome crusade.
For this quest, he will have a buddy
for each trick he tries to acquire.
By doing this, we can avoid
periods of silence where we say,
"What? Is there any point to having
a mic on him?"
as we observe Uchimura on location.
They are totally dissing you.
Are these buddies nice people?
I won't know who they are
until the day?
Right, we'll let you know
who it is on that day.
I see.
Please look forward to it.
It's probably a crew member anyway,
right?
Challenges by Teruyoshi Uchimura,
56 years old,
is starting!
Amazing!
- So I'm not alone.
- Okay.
I went to challenge the acquiring
with a guest. It was reassuring.
The third guest is very special.
- I still can't believe it.
- What?
- Please look forward to it.
- I get why my segment is longer.
- What?
Who is it?
- Now... Well, please watch it.
- Who could it be?
Let's get started!
- The Quest! It's me.
- Yeah!
New Year party trick
acquisition tour!
He first travelled to Aichi.
What am I going to acquire here?
Here it is.
"Ikadashi raftsmen"
- Ikadashi raftsmen.
- What is that?
- What does it mean?
What is this?
It's a special trick where several
performances are done...
on floating timber.
Are you telling me
to acquire this in a day?
- Yes.
- Is that possible?
- Me?
- Me...
Uchimura has a lot going on
at the end of the year.
He only has three days
to acquire three tricks.
That means he has to master
one trick per day.
Remember we said you'll have
a buddy for each trick?
- Right.
- The Ikadashi raftsmen festival...
is a traditional festival
held once a year.
Oh, it's a festival?
So now, here's your buddy
for this event!
- Yeah! Now!
- Yes!
- There he is!
- We are here...
- in Aichi!
- He's doing it!
Please watch!
It's been so long, he's excited.
- This is the view...
- He's excited.
from the castle tower.
There's a location shoot
going on right there.
And he's waving at me.
Thank you very much.
Now, we intend to work hard
as a team.
Timber!
Bring it on!
Today, they won't be participating
in the festival,
but he's bringing his festive spirit
of "festival fellow" to practise.
Uchimura-san, if you would please...
That tracksuit is a bit...
- It doesn't have pockets either.
- Buy one with pockets, then!
It's like the cheapest kind!
The cheapest kind of tracksuit.
- Ah! This is great.
- It sure is nice.
All right! Give me a helmet!
- Give me a helmet!
- Oh, how nostalgic!
They head right away to the pool
where they are to practise.
Uchimura and Miyagawa,
please have a look over there.
- What!
What did the duo see over there?
A chap in dreadlocks rotating
a log on the water.
- That looks hard.
- What is this?
The Port of Nagoya in Aichi
flourished as a collection site...
for timber since the Edo period.
Many timber merchants
acquired this raftsmen skill,
while they worked on the timber.
Enthralling tricks were created,
along with its long history.
What is this?
I've never seen that before.
A three-point handstand
on the chin?
It's Shachihoko.
- Shachihoko.
- Shachihoko, since we're in Aichi.
Okay.
This is "Kago-nori."
This skill can only be done when
they are in sync with one another.
That's incredible.
Amazing.
It's amazing. It's too amazing.
No mistakes.
You will have five hours
to acquire this skill.
Impossible!
- It looks extremely difficult.
- Yes.
Those two didn't look like
they were enjoying it either.
I think it's difficult.
His hair is in dreadlocks
and he appears cheerful,
but his face isn't smiling at all.
- You have to concentrate...
- That's how much focus you need.
or you won't be able to do it.
Let's try to not get injured.
- Yes.
- I meant, three hours to learn.
- Let's practise.
- Let's get started!
This is hard.
They've shown too many tricks.
No, seriously.
Of course you can pick any of them,
as long as you can do it.
Any of them?
No, this is the only one.
That one done with two people
was cool.
This one is incredible too,
you know.
Why did you show that thing?
That was a mistake.
You know...
Five hours later.
Let's see how far they get
in five hours!
Their instructors are Ikadashi
raftsmen, Tejima and Kusaka.
You hold a long pole
to maintain balance,
and you place the arch of your foot
on the edge of a rectangular log.
That's amazing. It won't turn.
You're holding it down
with your right foot.
Here and here.
This is what you're doing.
Then you maintain this position.
Then all you do is turn it.
I mean, you're right, but...
The technique
was naturally cultivated...
as a result of managing
and transporting timber.
They learnt it through action,
rather than by thinking.
I think I can do it.
I got it.
Learning to keep their balance
on the log,
with the instructor's assistance.
Instructor, I'm moving farther
and farther.
Mr Tejima.
Ah!
It turned!
When your body moves,
the timber moves too.
Mr Tejima!
That was close, Mr Tejima.
That's hard.
I don't want to fall right now.
Next, it's Miyagawa's turn.
Oh, I see.
I see.
So this is it.
- That's good.
- You're doing good.
Miyagawa's balancing skill
is superb. He tries to rotate it.
Be careful! Okay!
- Okay!
- Wow! It's reversing!
Watch out! Oh no!
What? Wait a minute.
Why is the water so cold?
This is not a heated pool!
Huh?
- Hey! This is cold water!
- It's not heated.
It's a diving pool,
so it's not heated.
What kind of reason is that?
Why didn't you get a heated pool
instead of a diving pool?
We looked for a pool
that would let us put logs in,
we couldn't find any
that were heated.
Of course, that's only natural!
Where would you find a pool
that lets you put logs in it?
That's why it's done in rivers!
And the only one that let us
put timber in their pool...
- was Max Diving.
- Thank you very much.
It's turning.
Uchimura!
The water temperature
is 19 degrees Celsius.
That's how cold
the Izu sea is in winter.
I need to get used to this.
Is it all shut? Is it shut?
We need to ventilate
once in a while,
but let's keep it shut
as much as possible.
We do need to ventilate.
They manage to stand on the log...
- without assistance.
- That's good.
I get it.
When learning to turn it, the level
of difficulty increases at once.
Careful!
Careful! Careful!
It's freezing.
I poked a hole with the pole.
- Oh no!
- It's cold!
- Seriously. Seriously.
- Oh no.
- This is really so hard.
- He ripped a hole.
They've been practising for an hour,
but they can't see themselves
being able to do it.
I'm sorry.
I forgot to mention this...
What? He forgot to mention what?
- What?
If you place your feet here,
- Yes?
- you'll slip...
and it will be devastating.
You go from edge,
to edge,
to edge.
Got it?
That was crucial information!
You place your feet on the next edge
in a constant rhythm.
Then the log will turn in the water
and move backwards.
Their goal for this task...
is to rotate it eight metres
to the other side of the pool.
"Goal for this task.
Cross eight meters"
However, it's an infinite distance
for them.
- They're wearing wetsuits now.
- Oops.
Ah...
That sounded odd.
In a diving pool,
two men are taking turns
trying to rotate a log,
only to fall in the water,
over and over again.
Did you open it?
- Because it's hot?
- No, it's for ventilation.
It's freezing in here.
I'm sorry. I opened it.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you tell me?
I opened it for ventilation.
I'm sorry. Let's ventilate.
Let me know if it's Uchimura!
It's cold, and they must be careful
not to get injured.
- Right!
- Ouch!
He slipped and took a heavy blow
to his crotch.
- You did it?
- Yes...
I hit my bum.
In addition, Uchimura...
I twisted it a little.
- He injured his ankle.
- Oh no.
Do you have any tape?
We do.
I'll strap it.
However...
How about we strap it in a cross?
No one knows how to do it.
They don't have a professional
to handle this?
They are troubled.
It's sort of treated.
Whether this is correct or not,
no one knows.
As they continue to practise,
they start to cover more distance.
In addition...
They are practising...
how to strap up.
They make use of a smartphone...
to master how to strap an injury.
- Okay! This is good now.
- Good.
During their five-hour practise,
the two of them went on the log...
- a total of 146 times.
- 146 times?
Were they able to acquire...
this Ikadashi raftsmen skill?
- Party trick performance!
- That's fast.
We shall present the Ikadashi
raftsmen skill from Nagoya, Aichi.
We shall cross to the opposite bank
on the timber.
Please give us a huge round
of applause when we succeed.
Let's do this!
Yoh!
First, raftsman Miyagawa
will demonstrate.
Now!
Please understand why I'm wet.
Yoh!
It's eight metres
to the opposite side.
- It's started to turn.
- He's good!
Ladies and gentlemen...
- Happy New Year.
- That's amazing.
- He's good.
- That's amazing! Come on!
- Carefully, very carefully...
It's turning. It's turning.
He's unsteady, but he continues
while using a pole for balance.
It's turning. It's turning.
- Happy New Year.
I hope this year will be great...
- for everyone.
- We will pray... A little more.
And...
Yes!
- Miyagawa succeeds!
- Great!
- Next up is raftsman Uchimura.
- Come on!
- Yoh!
- Oh?
- Yoh?
- Yoh!
- Yoh.
Yoh!
- Now!
- He won't start.
Now he started. There he goes.
It's an Ikadashi raftsman skill
presented by Uchimura.
Once he crosses the pool
successfully, please clap for him.
- Yoh.
- It's looking good.
- Yoh!
- Come on!
- Happy New Year! It's turning.
- Yoh!
Yoh!
He fell in the water halfway.
That's it!
He wasn't able to acquire
this party trick.
Oh my... That's one done.
Yes.
I was told you have two more.
I don't know if I'll last.
But the presence of a buddy
is helpful.
I'll be driven into a corner
if I'm alone.
- Thank you for your help.
- Not at all.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Ikadashi raftsmen's skill.
Let's move on to the next segment.
New Year's party trick
acquisition tour! First one's done.
That's amazing.
Festival fellow is awesome, right?
- Not at all.
- He's amazing.
He managed to advance
that much in a day.
- No, no.
- While he's talking, too.
- Right.
- Not at all.
He really saved me.
If I went on location by myself,
I'd have to make it happen,
no matter what.
I just gave up.
That's rare for him.
He said "That's it."
That's it!
Uchimura heads over to Tokyo
seeking his next trick.
He'll attempt a unique performance
that's hot right now.
Here it is.
A balance ball skipping rope?
It's impossible!
He will use a balance ball
and skipping rope.
- This is your buddy for this trick.
- Okay.
Who is it?
Uchimura-san!
Nakaoka will accompany you!
Oh, you got me.
You got me. I had no idea.
It's the former
first-class comedian...
It's not "former."
Nakaoka.
- Former first-class comedian.
- Two first-class comedians co-star.
The balance ball skipping rope skill
will be taught by...
Hello.
Sisters.
Aki, who's in middle school,
and her older sister, Airi,
who's a university student.
I see.
They won first place in a national
balance ball competition as a pair.
They are Japan's best
balance ball sisters.
- Amazing!
- They have amazing cores.
And a wonderful performance
of balance ball skipping rope.
You hold the balance ball
between your legs,
and jump lightly.
That's super hard.
Amazing.
That's incredible.
It's impossible!
You'll practise for five hours
to do this.
Five hours.
The five hours will be condensed.
- Condensed.
- It will be.
- This is not good.
This kind of job is not good.
Let's start practising.
First, they get used to
the balance ball, with assistance.
It looks like a health centre.
Oh no!
- Oh no.
- When I looked up close,
I saw a man in his mid-50s.
They switch.
Don't look at me.
Don't look at me
with a smile on your face.
It's starting to become fun.
You're good.
I think I'm pretty good at this.
I don't like this.
I don't like this practise.
Now they'll practise holding a ball
between their legs and jumping.
It's hard trying to hold it
between your legs.
Uchimura.
- Uchimura.
- Oh no.
Uchimura.
- Uchimura.
- Don't keep saying "Uchimura."
Don't whisper my name like that.
You idiot!
They're finally doing it solo.
- Oh! You've got it!
- That's amazing.
Oh! Amazing.
Uchimura is steadily improving.
But it's a long process from here.
I get this party trick location.
He's right. He's going to attempt
to skip rope for this one.
It's necessary to jump higher
to be able to skip rope.
You stand behind the ball.
Then you jump on,
and you use the momentum...
to jump higher.
I see.
But that makes it harder
to maintain balance.
I wonder if I'm putting
too much force on it.
Oh!
Scary!
From this point on,
it's repetition as usual.
They repeat the same thing
over and over again.
Okay. It's hot.
It's hot?
It's hot.
It's tough.
It's tough. It's hot.
I'm tired. This is hard.
It's hard. It's hot. It's tiring.
It's tough.
Why am I doing this?
It can't be helped.
I guess we don't have
the right to quit.
Seriously.
We don't have the right?
We don't. That's what Degawa said.
- There's no freedom here.
- Nope.
It's a mystery.
We'll go on strike in the spring.
Let's do something New Year's-like
to refresh!
Speedy mochi pounding.
Let's do something New Years-like
to refresh!
Speedy mochi pounding.
Speedy mochi pounding?
I've seen it before.
It's super-fast and it's dangerous.
Yes, it is.
Nakatanidou, located in Nara,
is known for its Yomogi mochi.
Speedy mochi pounding starts now.
Yoh!
Look at the magnificent teamwork
of these two.
It's so fast you can't see it.
No, no, no.
Pounding sweet sticky rice
while it's still hot...
results in soft and chewy mochi.
So, now you two will try
this speedy mochi pounding.
What are your intentions?
We came prepared with this.
Oh, is it lighter?
It's a bit softer.
Ah.
No, it hurts.
- It hurts.
- This will hurt.
Speedy mochi-pounding performance.
- Let's show them.
- Okay.
- Ready?
Let's do it.
We did it, right?
- We did it.
What do you think?
I don't know what to say.
- They switch places.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Now, the balance ball
skipping rope performance.
- That's fast!
- That's fast.
Each of them will get
three attempts.
If they are able to skip rope
three times, it's a success!
- That's so random.
- That's fast.
Now...
It's Nakaoka's first attempt.
Come on!
I shall jump three times.
I'll start.
Ready...
That was close!
Oh my!
- Twice.
- You can do it.
Twice!
It's Uchimura's first attempt.
Come on!
- I'll start.
- Come on.
Ready...
Ah...
You failed quite miserably
on the actual try.
It's fine. We have more chances.
However, their second attempt.
Both Nakaoka...
and Uchimura...
failed.
That was close!
They have one more chance.
Here I go!
It's fine! You'll be able to do it!
Yes!
- Come on!
- You can do it!
- All right.
- Come on!
The fateful...
third attempt.
First class...
Yes, be first class!
Yes!
Here I go.
Ready, go.
- Did I jump three times?
- He did it!
You scraped three jumps.
It should be okay.
Yes!
Nakaoka tenaciously managed...
the balance ball skipping rope jump
three times.
It's a success!
Yes!
He shares his happiness
with the Takeuchi sisters.
You did it!
Sisters, good for you too.
However, the party trick acquisition
tour is Uchimura's segment.
Okay!
Everyone is waiting for the star
to perform magnificently.
Here I go!
Go!
Ah...
Uchimura's first attempt
lacked power and he failed.
Then his discontent
for this segment erupts.
Oh no!
You know!
- Could it be?
- Oh no!
Hey!
It's been a while!
- It's been a while.
- It's been a while!
- It's helmet guy in black!
- Oh no, we're in trouble.
Hey! The camera is too low!
This camera is too low!
Kids! Do you want me
to eat your zoni?
Do you want me to eat your zoni?
It's been a while!
I'm the helmet guy in black.
I'm against this segment!
It's impossible!
I couldn't stay on the log,
I can't stay on a ball either. Hey!
Both of my buddies
have been successful!
And it's my segment.
It's my segment, and yet my buddies
are the only ones successful?
I won't go tomorrow!
I won't go tomorrow.
- Ah...
- He's sulking.
I'm really upset.
The New Year's party trick
acquisition tour continues.
- That went fast in the footage.
- It did go fast.
We did it for five hours.
I expected it to be condensed,
but it was even shorter than that.
That was surprising, right?
Nakaoka is good, isn't he?
- He's amazing.
- Not at all.
There is a professional
for everything.
A professional like
the festival fellow, and QTuber.
- Both of them...
- You're right.
get their job done.
- These two are cool.
- Thank you very much.
I think you're back to being
a first-class comedian.
Thank you very much.
- He jumped three times.
- That was magnificent.
Now, it's the last segment
of the party trick acquisition tour.
We've come to Tokyo Meiji Kinenkan.
- We are at Meiji Kinenkan in Tokyo.
- I see.
But you'll be learning
a traditional act of some region.
I see.
Here it is.
Chikuzen Hakata-koma.
- No idea, but it sounds hard.
- A spinning top?
It's a juggling performance where
a spinning top is spun everywhere,
such as on your palm or on a ball.
It's been designated by Fukuoka
as an intangible cultural asset.
This is a serious party trick.
- It's juggling, right?
- Yes, it is.
And his buddy for this trick...
is a special guest who is not
a Quest member.
Is this person an actor?
Or a big shot?
I don't know what to give as a hint.
You don't know what to give
as a hint?
What kind of person is this that
you don't know what hint to give?
I don't know how to give it...
You don't know how to give it?
What?
Here's your buddy!
- This was Uchimura's secret idol.
- What?
He admires them?
There's clicking.
What? Who is it?
- A woman?
- That person is thin.
- Who is it?
- I suspect a woman.
Our special guest is actress
Yurina Hirate.
- Wow!
- What?
No, no, no.
- No, no, no!
- Is she real?
No, no, no!
Uchimura is a huge Hirate fan!
No way!
No way.
For real?
- Are you really her?
- Long-time no see.
- Yes, I am.
It's been a year since
they performed together...
- at Red and White Song Battle.
- Hold on.
I can't stand up.
I can't stand up right now.
She'll attempt to do Hakata-koma
with you.
Really?
It was unbelievable,
but I was very happy.
I thought this is how Imoto felt
when she met Namie Amuro.
The umbrella was bigger
than I thought,
I couldn't close it.
I was focused on doing that,
so I don't remember much
of anything else.
These two will challenge doing
Chikuzen Hakata-koma.
Here's our special guest,
Yurina Hirate!
Yeah!
- Happy New Year!
- Hello.
Yurina, these are The Quest members.
Hello.
- I admire her.
- Right.
We started after this, but I was
distracted for an hour.
His facial expression
was completely different.
Your voice was different.
You were speaking softer than usual.
We tried Hakata-koma,
how would you describe it
in one word?
It was difficult.
- So it was difficult.
- It was difficult.
I'm sorry, Chen said a special guest
that's totally unexpected,
so I was thinking it was Nanbara.
No way!
You're completely off!
Let's get started.
- The Quest.
- Yeah!
- Thank you very much.
That was great.
Uchimura and Hirate will attempt
to do Chikuzen Hakata-koma.
- Good morning.
They'll be taught by Shuraku Chikuji
and Saira Chikuji,
inheritors of the spinning top art
from previous generations.
Is she your daughter?
No, she's my wife.
Your wife? What?
- She's young, right?
- Yes.
- Seriously?
Mr Chikuji, you scored!
"28 years old, 45 years old.
Mr Chikuji, you scored"
I see.
First, the Chikuji clan will perform
top spinning tricks.
Hakata-koma doesn't use strings.
It's spun by hand,
which is one of its characteristics.
It's then placed on a fingertip.
- This is already amazing.
- Isn't it amazing?
He picks up a Japanese sword.
He will be demonstrating
the most difficult skill...
in the 470 years
of Hakata-koma's history, "Tobiume."
It's spinning.
It's on the sharp edge?
The spinning top moves across
the sharp blade as it's spinning.
Amazing.
There are no hidden magnets.
Excellent balancing skills.
It's impossible.
- It's impossible.
- He's saying it's impossible?
Here's another trick where it spins
across a string, "Daikoku."
This is "Suehiro," where he spins
the top on the edge of a fan.
Amazing.
There.
There are a total of 23 tricks.
- It's spinning diagonally
- How is that possible?
Why doesn't it fall?
The last performance...
is a cheerful trick that's perfect
to celebrate the New Year's.
- It's called "Mandou."
- Mandou?
When the top spins and climbs
up a string...
a kusudama is activated
by a special mechanism.
I wish for everyone to be happy.
Thank you very much.
That was incredible.
Amazing.
I would be pleased if you'd do
the last one I did.
If we could do that, it'd be cool...
I want to see you in action
and be cool, Uchimura-san.
Oh?
I'll do it.
The two of you
will practise together,
so if she could put on
the practise outfit...
What?
- This?
- Please give it to her.
What?
Don't make her wear this.
What's wrong
with what she's wearing?
I think it'll be hard for her
to move in that.
She's perfectly fine in that.
Why do we have
to make her wear this?
- What's wrong with that?
- I would like to wear it.
- I want to wear it.
- She said she'll wear it.
She said she'll wear it.
They begin their training.
The first thing is spinning a top.
Rub your hands together like
you're flying a bamboo-copter toy.
Just like that.
Then you let it gather momentum,
and you keep repeating it.
If you can feel the stem rolling
between your palms...
It seems easy...
That's right.
When it's done by an expert.
Hold on...
- Just spin it.
- This is quite difficult.
Whew...
Oh, she did it.
- She did it.
- She's amazing.
She learns fast.
Meanwhile,
Uchimura isn't learning fast.
Because inside his head is one part
spinning top, nine parts Yurina.
I really admire her.
- She's perfect...
- What is this?
with her dancing and her ability
to express herself.
I wanted to be that kind
of an entertainer.
- Do you understand what I'm saying?
- I don't get it much.
Of course you wouldn't get it.
I never thought...
I'd be spinning tops with her.
I was hoping the next occasion...
I'd see her would be
at some formal... you know?
Like on a talk show.
Like "Bokura no Jidai"?
Exactly! Like "Bokura no Jidai."
A show like that.
That's what I was thinking.
But, you have plenty of time to talk
while you're spinning tops with her.
After you get the segment...
you go to the studio...
Right, we watch the edited version
at the studio.
That's how it goes.
I mean, you don't appear much
on variety shows.
Right.
You only appear to promote
your shows pretty much, right?
Their conversation is too neutral.
Actually, it's a good thing
this isn't a talk show.
You don't appear much
on these types of shows.
- Get it together!
- Shut up.
I can spin it with one hand.
That's more advanced.
Huh?
In the meantime, Hirate is...
trying to advance to the next step
on her own.
What's going on?
I want to get to the next step
as soon as possible.
She can't wait.
I get bored easily,
and I'm already bored.
Hirate will perform this "Hagoita."
Seven, eight...
Female performers usually do
this trick on Hakata-koma's stage.
You need rhythm for this too.
This is it.
You look like you're miles away.
You just thought,
"This is what I have to do?"
I prefer not to know
what I'm doing beforehand.
I don't want to hear
all the instructions,
so I'll go,
listen and watch...
was what I was thinking,
but this was different
from what I expected.
It wasn't exactly what you expected.
The burden is tremendous, right?
If she never came on The Quest,
Hirate, Koma and Hagoita would have
never crossed each other's paths.
The Kusudama trick Uchimura is
going to attempt is called Mandou.
A top is placed on the palm,
then it's flipped.
It is put sideways,
- and thrown onto the string.
- Amazing.
Several steps are involved,
one little mistake
and it all goes down the pan.
It's a difficult trick.
- Like so?
- Yes.
There.
Wrap it. That's it.
He wants to spin the top,
but he's kept busy chasing after it.
Meanwhile, Hirate is...
She's doing it.
She advanced significantly
while our attention was diverted.
- She's good.
With Uchimura, the most difficult
part is to tilt the top sideways.
This part is difficult.
If you get it around
your index finger...
- then it won't fall, so you're set.
- It's spinning.
Unless it's completely sideways,
it won't catch the string.
That was close.
When you have it around your finger,
wait. Please wait.
- That's too soon!
- Too soon. That's too soon.
No matter how many times he tries,
he doesn't succeed,
but he's been smiling
the whole time.
Today is a special-- Oh?
Yurina is cheering him on.
Huh? Was the dance like that?
No...
It was super lame just now.
Can you edit it out?
It was so lame.
That genius dancer is...
Her cheer gave him power.
That's it!
Everything is prepared
for the final performance.
Since I had this opportunity
to appear with Yurina,
I want to make it happen...
so it turns into a great finale.
I never thought I'd be doing
any performing today.
I thought I was just here
as a supporting role.
I'm actually nervous,
like I'm doing a live concert.
- This is so much pressure.
- Pressure?
Now, the party tricks performance.
- Now, the party tricks performance.
- Here it is!
We ask you to watch
Chikuzen Hakata-koma.
It's a traditional act
where this spinning top...
is spun on places such as the hand,
and a string.
There may be less on the programme
than you expected,
but we won't accept any complaints.
We won't accept them.
Let's get started.
First up is spinning top
on the hand.
It's an act where a spinning top
is placed on the hand.
She's good.
It barely got on.
You were panicking a bit.
Congratulations. Congratulations.
It's spinning more than usual.
Congratulations.
Happy New Year.
I'm barely managing it.
I'm barely managing it too.
It's holding on.
That!
I'm holding on too.
This is how much we've improved.
Next up is "Hagoita."
It will be performed
by Yurina Hirate.
She had no idea she would be
performing today until she got here.
- She's good!
- She's doing it.
- Amazing!
- Amazing.
Once she's on stage,
her performance is magnificent.
She's good.
That's nice.
- It looks like it's on pause.
- She's good.
That's pretty.
Amazing.
It's on.
Yoh!
- Amazing.
- That was perfect.
That was Yurina Hirate,
performing "Hagoita."
The last stunt is a powerful one.
Splitting kusudama, Mandou.
The kusudama is set at 3.5 metres.
He will split it open
for a gorgeous finale.
Go for it!
Now...
His special trick,
spinning with one hand.
It's a new trick not passed down
by the Chikuji clan.
Now, he'll spin it with both hands
to increase its speed.
I see.
Now, it will be placed on his palm.
He's done an excellent job
up to this step.
- Looking good.
- It's incredible.
- It went!
- Go! Go!
The top didn't have enough momentum,
and it slowed down.
How disappointing
since it was perfect up to here.
My apologies.
Please allow me to lower it
by a little bit.
- He's lowering that?
- Right there.
Yes.
Uchimura was determined
from the beginning...
that he would challenge it as many
times as it took until he succeeded.
That was close.
From this point onwards...
he failed...
15 times consecutively.
Oops.
I'm sorry.
Oppressive vibes
are felt on the scene.
They are all watching.
No one can say a word to Uchimura.
The one suffering the most...
is Yurina, who's been holding
the kusudama for over an hour.
You neglected her like never before.
For real?
I'm truly sorry. I'm neglecting
a person I admire so much.
This is his 23rd attempt.
Go for it.
So, momentum is critical.
Exactly.
We want it to be a success
for Yurina's sake as well.
Oh?
- Go for it!
- It went up! Go!
- This time for sure...
- Go up! Go up!
Go up!
I don't think it will ever
reach up there.
Yurina...
Yes.
- Lower it.
- Yes.
- Lower it. Lower it. Lower it.
- There!
- Yes.
Now it'd be easier just to throw
the top at the kusudama!
Then, two hours after it started...
He's got it.
- It's looking good!
- It went up!
Yoh!
We wish for your year to be blessed.
- Happy New Year!
Chikuzen Hakata-koma, Mandou.
He managed to make it happen.
We can finally go home.
That last one was beautifully done.
The way you put it on. It was
beautifully done. It stirred me.
I'm glad.
Geez... This is too much.
I don't like party tricks.
I don't like them!
That's it for New Year's party trick
acquisition tour.
- Amazing.
- Yurina, what did you think?
The simplest thing of spinning it...
- was the hardest trick.
- That's the hardest.
Spinning it fast.
The most basic thing
is the hardest of it all.
Honestly, there are no issues
with your party tricks. You tried.
It was just that useless dialogue
between you two.
After you get this segment...
We watch the edited version
at the studio.
And his tone of voice?
What? Do you have
a problem with that?
Is there a problem speaking facts?
I have to say a typical person's
night out would be more exciting.
That was at quite a low level...
By the end, it was as high as
the lights in a Japanese style room.
- Seriously.
- That's funny.
It was like those low lights
at my parent's house.
When the kusudama broke,
Uchimura totally disappeared in it.
Well, then you go and try it!
In one day too!