The Quest.
All the Girls gather.
Degawa Girls Gathering Special.
One day,
we visit Madame at her home.
This time is the fifth popular
Degawa Girls Gathering.
Yeah? It's popular? Really?
Madame will decide the programme
of the girls gathering.
Let me think...
We made pottery the other day,
didn't we?
So how about doing glass art
this time?
But the pottery I made that time
wasn't displayed at the studio.
I made so much effort to make it,
why don't you show it today?
She's angry.
Make sure you show it this time.
Their journey will mainly be
in Saga Prefecture
where glass art thrives,
and will also go to hot springs
as Madame wishes,
and travel around Oita Prefecture,
all in this journey.
Also, starting this time...
- New girl, Yokota will join.
- That's right.
It was tough enough
when Yumeppe joined the other day.
If Yokota also joins,
there'll be trouble again.
Does Madame know Yokota joined?
- We've told her.
- You have?
What did you say?
A new girl called Yokota
will come this time.
Is that so? Why don't you
reduce the number a bit?
Mayuko will leave first.
What will the girls' gathering
this time be like?
Welcome to The Quest.
Today's programme is
Degawa Girls Gathering Special.
Wasshoi!
"Morisanchu"
Hello...
Hello!
Hello, everyone!
"Madame Dewi"
"Mayuko Kawakita, Akane Hotta"
"Yumena Yanai, Mayuu Yokota"
Mr Advisor, it's an hour
of girls gathering again?
One hour.
Thank you.
We're really happy,
but Madame said if
a new Degawa Girl joins,
- one old girl can go.
- Yes.
If we get one new student,
one should graduate.
New student...
We must let them graduate.
At first, Degawa Girls were young,
I thought it was nice and new,
but when the two young girls joined,
they suddenly looked old.
It's not fresh at all.
We're young! We're very young!
Yokota, it's the first time
you joined, right?
- Yes.
- How was it?
I had a lot of fun.
I went to steal the skills
of the older girls.
"Older girls..."
The three old girls
are in white costumes here.
It's not white costume!
Why? Why?
Like they're prepared to die
to do something.
It's fresh!
Saga!
Impressive!
Ow... hot...
It's difficult.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Ms Kawakita, do it again.
- "Yay!"
- It's horrible!
"Degawa Girls' Gathering
in Saga, Oita"
900 kilometres from Tokyo,
two new girls will also join.
Degawa Girls' Gathering
in Saga, Oita.
We've come to...
Saga!
This is Saga Castle History Museum.
The first iron cannon in Japan
was manufactured here,
it's also known to have led
the Meiji Restoration.
Madame, we have
another new Degawa Girl join--
Dewi Girls.
Yes, Dewi Girls.
Yokota, introduce yourself.
I'm Mayuu Yokota, nice to meet you.
I'm 21 years old.
Please call me Yokota.
- Okay.
- Nice to meet you.
- Did you apply for it?
- She's not interested!
I went to the same audition
with Yumeppe.
That means you were the first place
and you were the second place?
"1st place, 2nd place"
We were supposed to join together.
Don't make things awkward!
- Why do you stand like this anyway?
- No idea.
But somehow it feels like
the two of them were demoted.
That's so mean!
Let's start
the Degawa Girls Gathering.
First, it's the glass art
Madame would like to do.
It's said that
glass was first introduced to Japan
in the Yayoi period,
but manufacturing of glassware
started in the Edo period,
in full swing.
This time, they'll learn it
at Soejima Glassware,
which was founded in 1903.
Who will teach us?
It's him.
- Oh, he's our teacher?
- Yes.
What about you, sir?
I'm only going to watch.
Only watch?
Oh? Are you from the neighbourhood?
- The company's president, right?
- What?
He doesn't look like a president.
He totally does! His skin is fair.
What kind of glassware do you make?
It's called Hizen Vidro,
it's Saga's traditional glassware.
Saga's important intangible
cultural asset, Hizen Vidro.
"Vidro" means "glass" in Portuguese.
It is made by glassblowing,
without using any mould.
To shape the glassware,
crafters use gravitational force
and centrifugal force well.
It is difficult,
but no two pieces of glassware
are the same.
It's made into glassware that has
a warmth unique to handmade work.
This time, they'll learn from
the teacher for two days,
and make their own unique glassware.
Madame will make a champagne glass.
Now this part of a champagne glass
is narrower,
it's become the mainstream.
On the other hand,
the youngest Yumeppe...
Like this.
I'll make a vase for my grandma.
How wonderful that is!
- My grandma loves flowers.
- What, Ms Kawakita?
- I'll make a glass for my grandma.
- Shut up!
Stop it!
And Degawa...
What's that?
- Liar!
- I'm scared!
You've never bought your wife
souvenirs,
why do you do this?
This isn't right!
Day one is the beginner's course.
No matter what glassware it is,
the first thing they do is Tamatori.
The glass is melted into
a syrupy-state in the furnace,
it's rolled around
the tip of a stick.
The small ball has a diameter
of three centimetres.
Blow air into it little by little,
and the ball that forms the base
is done.
This is the core.
We'll put another layer of glass
on top,
and make it expand.
Madame tries it first.
Can she wrap a small ball around it,
like the teacher?
Madame, isn't it fast?
She secured 10 times the amount
of the teacher's.
She blows air into it,
but it doesn't' move at all.
It's difficult.
Actually, this looks easy,
but it takes three years
to master the skill.
Good...
Degawa is doing it quite well.
He'll shape the glass now.
Turn it...
Good!
- Good...
- Ow... hot...
- Wow!
It's hot!
Compete with time.
- Hurry, hurry!
- Hurry up!
You can't do it at all.
He didn't make that sound.
Anyway, I was surprised!
This isn't hot at all.
But you said it was hot.
To make it expand,
they need to wrap the glass
around the part
further from the tip,
like the teacher did.
Yumeppe showed the difference.
- Wow!
- Yumeppe!
New girl Yokota successfully
expanded it.
I made it!
Our new Degawa Girls are amazing!
What is it?
Maybe their breaths are fresher?
All the members still need practise,
so we'll show you the craftsman's
wonderful techniques.
The glass expands to the ideal size,
it's moved to another stick,
and it's cut away
from the original stick.
It's difficult.
The hole opened here will become
the mouth of the cup or the glass.
Expand it according to what
you want to make, and it's done.
In the case of making a plate...
It's impressive.
Centrifugal force.
It's finished by using
centrifugal force,
and this is the finished glass art.
The thing that can only be made
using the technique here in Japan
is this blue saké warmer.
It is done by using two sticks
together at the same time.
Blow into one stick,
and stretch the part of the mouth
using the other stick.
- That's difficult.
- Wow!
It doesn't break?
When the glass sets,
use gravitational force to shape it.
In Japan,
it's a traditional technique that's
only passed down in Hizen Vidor.
At the same time, the amateurs...
He's so noisy.
Wow, it isn't hot at all.
What was that, then?
The teacher's wife
is a rather good teacher.
She lets him do a little,
but basically, she does it together.
On the other hand,
Mr Fujii is a craftsman,
he never spoils his students.
That's how far it can get.
Mr Fujii, have a look.
Take it out.
- How is it?
- Hurry up.
It'd take 10 minutes to finish
if he helps,
but she spent 50 whole minutes
to heat and mould the glass,
repeatedly.
Her face is already oily.
He doesn't change
his educational principle
for Madame, either.
You dropped it with a thump.
We aren't going to become experts
of glass art.
Among them, the talented one
is new girl Yokota.
Only a few people can be this good.
The way she spins the stick
is logical.
The president suddenly appeared,
and praised the way
she turns the stick.
It is turned stably,
so gravitational force acts equally,
and it's kept as a beautiful sphere.
I have potential.
She has potential? Teacher!
She has potential.
You never said that to me!
I turned it 30--
On the other hand,
the one who has no talent
but made her presence felt,
is old girl Tani.
- It's hot!
- Oh, watch out!
Stop it!
Self-claimed burn.
Four people are looking after you
for your burn. What the heck?
Hey, Maria!
It hurts!
It's a tiny burn and you need
four adults to look after you?
It hurts!
Are you okay with that?
And Yumeppe...
She doesn't think about
being filmed at all,
and she's making effort
for her grandma...
That's the look on her face when she
makes something for her grandma.
But Yumeppe is also thinking
about various things.
Is there anything you want to learn
from the senior girls?
Like their reaction,
the way they fawn on the crew.
I mean Maria's burn
was nothing serious, right?
That's what I think,
but that's what Maria does
to gain her time on the show.
It's how each person
competes for exposure.
Day one ends with knowing
how difficult glass art is.
They'll go to film in Oita now.
Excuse me, may I ask something?
May I go home?
May you go home? That's new!
I'll return to Tokyo
to shoot a movie.
- Shoot a movie?
- Yes.
This is bad...
Which job actually came first
in your schedule?
- The movie.
- Oh... The movie.
We must let her leave, then,
if that came first.
That makes me feel frustrated,
though.
So Yokota
will join them again later.
Now it's the tour in Oita.
First, it's a popular local show.
They've come to an aquarium in Oita,
Umitamago.
The show is...
a walrus performance.
It's about 20 kilograms.
"Female walrus Michan"
She's so cute!
She looks like you!
She looks like Tetsuro.
- She doesn't!
- Yes, she does.
Do you two look alike?
Michan is prettier, right?
Michan is a surprisingly
skilled performer.
- She'll whistle.
- Whistle?
Let's do it.
- No way!
- Really?
- She's good at it!
- It's true.
It was perfect!
She can even distinguish
words of the human language.
Wait. Suck!
It was perfect!
She's so clever!
The last performance
is the powerful technique,
watermelon splitting.
I'd like someone to wear this.
If you've prepared a watermelon,
then I have to wear it.
Did you wear something like that
to ride a bicycle?
It's scary!
Don't move.
Wait... It's the first time
I perform with a walrus!
Will Michan be able to
burst the balloon successfully?
Let's do it!
Ready, go!
Hit!
Ouch!
Michan... Michan,
that was my shoulder!
Michan, I must thank you,
in a way.
Thanks, Michan.
One more makes his appearance.
He's huge!
He's bigger than Michan!
Weighing about one tonne,
this is male sea lion, Gentaro.
He loves fish.
Gen! Gen!
I'll throw it.
From there?
His special trick is fish catching.
He can catch the fish
no matter where I throw it from.
The distance is 30 metres.
Ready, go!
Catch it!
That's impressive!
As they've realised,
it's the caretaker Mr Sawada
who does the impressive trick,
but...
Gen, I'll throw!
That's our Degawa Girls for you.
They do it successfully
one after next at 15 metres.
I'm impressed by them.
I'll try that.
81-year-old Madame will try it too.
And Madame caused a miracle.
Gen!
A miraculous zero metres.
Wonderful!
Can it be funnier?
That's Madame for you.
Madame and Degawa will try to
perform in the walrus performance.
Will they do it well?
Okay, come.
He's gentle.
Come, Michan.
He feeds Michan too often
and they enter too slowly.
- Come, Michan.
- He feeds her so much!
Now, Degawa and Dewi's
walrus performance
is going to start.
A round of applause, please.
A round of applause.
The first performance
will be sit-ups.
- Yumeppe, please come here.
- Yes!
- Please hold her legs down.
- Her legs?
Tummy!
- They're her legs.
- Okay.
Okay,
sit up!
- Wow!
- Once more!
Sit up!
Next, it's a prank
played on the girls.
She's thirsty,
so let's give her some water.
- Wait.
- You give her too many fish.
Okay, water. Okay.
Okay, suck...
Spit.
Suck...
- Spit.
- Wow!
Suck!
Spit!
Madame is delighted.
And lastly...
Michan has a wonderful present
for you.
- We'll give it to Akane.
- Why?
- Akane, please come here.
- Okay.
This wonderful present is a kiss!
A kiss from the walrus,
it's Madame's
thoughtful arrangement.
Close your eyes.
Her whiskers are hard.
Do I need to close my eyes?
Okay, come...
Kiss!
Not yet...
You haven't kissed anyone lately,
right?
No, I haven't! Thank you!
Attention!
Bow!
Thank you! A round of applause!
Wonderful!
Teacher, how did they do?
They got full marks.
- Wow!
- I was impressed.
Are you crying, Teacher?
Teacher, why?
Why? Why, Teacher?
Mr Degawa and Madame were brilliant,
Michan did so well too...
The mystery of the teacher's tears.
The mystery of
the second person's tears.
Where will they stay tonight?
- What?
- Whoa...
It's impressive.
Large resort hotel in Beppu City,
Suginoi Hotel.
There's a buffet restaurant
that serves over 80 dishes,
and an outdoor hot spring
where you can enjoy a fountain show.
It's full of entertainment
besides the stay.
The room they'll stay at is...
Isn't this wonderful?
It's the Hermitage Suite Room.
The cost of one night
starts from 56,000 yen.
But they can't stay at this room
that easily.
Only the people who win the game
can stay.
- I knew it.
- Again!
Let's do it. The room goes down
four ranks if they lose,
Hotel Death Match.
Whoa, here it is.
They'll do our familiar
target hitting water game.
That one?
The first round
is between two fresh girls.
Yumeppe versus Yokota,
who is back from her movie shooting.
Mayuu used to play softball.
But you play baseball
with your younger brother.
Yes, I do...
The rock, paper, scissors to decide
who goes first will be the key.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yay!
The way you rejoice is young!
- That's awful. Do it once more.
- Yay!
- That's awful!
You have a new gag.
Former softball team member Yokota
goes first.
It's quite far away.
Yes!
You totally missed it.
She's got the powerful vibes,
like she could do it,
but she couldn't at all.
Basically,
Yokota is disappointing.
Yumeppe goes next.
Oh, I can't!
It doesn't hit at all!
I can't do it.
The moment she threw,
"Oh, I can't do it!"
"I can't do it."
Don't show that look on TV.
Next, Yokota disappointed again.
- Yokota! So poor!
- That was poor.
And then...
She did it...
Yokota is defeated miserably.
It was long.
It looks like an "M."
Take away your hands.
I'm sorry!
Look this way. This way.
That's long.
Next, a match between old girls
Hotta versus Tani.
Hotta goes first.
Say everything on your mind
before you throw, then throw it.
- Maria.
- Yes?
Will you not switch off your mind
in the middle of a conversation?
It's because what you say is boring.
Shut up.
Good! Good!
The first throw.
So close! That was so close!
Change of offence and defence.
- I'll throw.
- I'm scared!
So close!
It was so close!
The distance is shorter,
it's Hotta's chance.
I'll throw.
Tani is defeated.
It's long!
So long!
It doesn't stop.
That's an old girl for you.
She's even used to the way
to let water pour over her.
I'm impressed.
Wasn't that long?
I'm soaking wet!
Lastly, a match between the queens,
Madame versus Kawakita.
That was dirty!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
You played dirty!
You'll surely win!
You make a fool of me like that,
are you sure? Is it okay?
- It's started.
- Yes.
We hoped for Madame's miracle
for a moment, but...
Can she do it? Go!
That was close...
It's almost a rerun
of the clip just now.
And then...
I'll throw.
Don't.
Don't!
It's the true ability
of the 81-year-old
that exceeds the two girls before.
Are you kidding me?
You stuck your head there?
It's Madame's shower time.
It was a sexy shower scene.
Degawa Girls Gathering
will continue,
but we'll be back at the studio
for now.
What do you think, Miyagawa?
What I think Yokota
has room for improvement
is her reaction
when water poured on her.
Maria used the water pressure
to separate her fringe,
so that her face was visible.
Without getting too calculating.
- That's right.
- Make it just right.
I was impressed by her.
Madame even used the water that
poured down in front as a shower.
Impressive.
She put it back.
What about you, Imoto?
She was burnt so badly,
would anyone not get worried?
Indeed.
But in Yumeppe's eyes,
that was Maria Tani's time.
Everyone gains exposure
in different ways.
No, it wasn't on purpose.
Do you want to learn
how to make time for exposure?
I thought each person did it
in their own way.
Don't say we do it!
I didn't care about how much time
I had in a show when I was 21.
Making of Hizen Vidro for real.
After practising for two whole days,
the shapes of their glassware
are getting better bit by bit.
- Wow!
- Yokota is good at it.
Yumeppe is making a vase.
She rolls the coloured glass beads
around
to create a pattern.
Roast it over the fire
to blend them in,
and blow it into a narrow,
long shape of a vase.
- So beautiful!
- It's beautiful!
When it's cooled,
the colour becomes vivid,
as you can see.
After the mouth is opened,
it's almost finished.
Won't it be cute
if the mouth is at an angle?
Yes, it's cute.
On the other hand, Degawa...
Come here, please.
What did you do yesterday?
He doesn't even know
how to put it here!
He relied on Mrs Fujii's
gentle teaching on day one,
and he doesn't remember anything.
Oh, I need to keep turning it?
Hey...
- It's the most basic thing!
- Where were you looking yesterday?
Mayuko did this
about 40 times yesterday.
He aims to make
a heart-shaped plate.
He expands the mouth widely,
heats it to make it soft
and shape it.
It's beautiful.
Thank you for making me
delicious food every day!
If he also pulls
the opposite side...
Wonderful!
80 percent was due
to the teacher's help,
it turns into
a beautiful heart shape.
- You made it.
- It's pretty!
Everyone will finish their work
at this stage.
Yokota will use coloured glass
to highlight the saké glass' rim.
This is how you do it?
- Beautiful!
- Nice!
She's good at it.
Tani will highlight
her single-flower vase.
She turns the vase
and applies force,
and makes a twisted pattern on it.
Among them,
Hotta is struggling alone.
- What? Why?
- Oh, it's crushed!
It bumped into the furnace's wall
and is crushed.
From scratch?
What?
The shape is finally formed, but...
A bowl for somen noodles?
It's not at all.
We'll put it in the rubbish bin...
The teacher called it rubbish!
Teacher, wait! Wait...
And Madame...
She is certainly improving
after a lot of practise.
She is obviously
handling the glass well, too.
But when she is finishing it,
things gradually changed.
When you put a red line in
yesterday,
you added a lot, right?
Don't make it like that.
Don't add a lot of red at once,
please just add a little.
Can I do it?
Yeah...
She gives instructions
more than doing it herself.
Madame, do it yourself.
"Ho ho ho ho ho"
We make it together.
The glassware will cool
and be done two days later,
we'll show you the glassware
at the second part.
I'm looking forward to it.
We'll go to Oita again
for an activity in scenic nature.
They filmed a lot.
We have the help of our guide,
Mr Tanaka.
You'll go to a river
called Yufugawa Canyon.
- Wonderful! I love it.
- A river!
Yufugawa Canyon.
It's a river that flows
at the bottom of steep cliffs
that are 15 to 60 metres high.
It's dangerous,
so you couldn't go to the back
of a canoe till recently.
This packraft is light,
we've introduced it,
so we can go to places
we haven't been able to before.
This is an activity that started
in May, 2021,
we are the first group of
common people to use it,
so there's a bit of fear.
Can we really go in there?
First, they go down the difficult
mountain path to the river.
Oh! I'm sorry.
- There she goes again.
- I'm sorry.
Don't do that!
I really hate her scream.
Mayuko, I really hate your scream.
Before Yumeppe went down,
she texted her mum.
She's adorable.
She said she'd go and do her best.
You guys haven't talked to your mums
for two, three years, right?
That's not right...
15 minutes after they started,
they're at the entrance
of the canyon.
We'll go upstream in the river.
The further back we go,
- the narrower the river gets.
- It looks powerful!
Their destination
is three hours away.
The width between precipitous cliffs
is only two metres,
it's a mysterious scene.
But only 30 seconds
after they get on the packraft...
We have to carry it already?
Carry it upstream, get on it.
We'll repeat the process
till we're there.
That's tough.
They'll carry
the two-kilogram packraft on land
and go forward,
then get on the raft.
It's a harsh journey
that repeats that.
It's fast!
It's fast! Not there yet?
The natural environment
waiting for them
is beyond their imagination.
They must cross many big rocks
to get there.
The boat is in the way!
What's this self-service?
But the one who goes forward
without any complaint
is the 81-year-old Madame.
She walks at the front
and even helps the young girls.
Impressive!
If Mr Degawa has a hard time
climbing up, please help him.
But this man is heavy.
But we're a team, Madame.
This difficult path
brings back the teamwork
the Girls Gathering members
usually lack.
Even the three old girls hold hands,
which they usually don't do,
when they go forward.
Ready, go!
Okay!
Ready, go! Okay!
Are you an idiot?
They've been helping each other
in their journey for three hours.
Everyone, look up! Look!
Wow, it's beautiful!
- It's shining.
- Wonderful!
From now on,
it's the destination of the journey,
Oita Prefecture's famous spot,
Yufugawa Canyon's unexplored region.
Wow, it's beautiful!
The canyon is about
12 kilometres long,
there are over 40 waterfalls.
The beautiful scenery is called
Tyrol in the East.
When they go further back...
It's getting more like
Indiana Jones in real life.
It is the bottom of a great canyon
surrounded by precipitous cliffs.
It makes you wonder
what the usual unsightly dispute
of Degawa Girls' Gathering is.
It's so refreshing.
Let's stop the unsightly dispute.
- Let's stop.
Let's not compete for number one
or punish the others.
- Let's stop.
- Okay.
It's a mess.
But on their way back...
Hey, did you just push me?
I helped you go forward.
Hey, don't push.
Everyone shows their ego.
Okay, let's go.
Madame and Degawa go to a hot spring
to heal their tired bodies.
Wow!
This is Suginoi Hotel's speciality,
an outdoor bath with a stunning view
that sees the whole Beppu City,
Tanayu.
This really is the bath
for the winner.
- Really.
- Wow!
Did Degawa Girls' Gathering change
after adding more members?
They talk like friends
when they are having lunch,
but they get competitive
when the camera starts filming.
At the same time,
the Girls have a gathering
under the new system.
Amazing!
They've come to
a glamping facility that opened
in April, 2021,
GRANXIA Beppu Kannawa.
You can see the whole view
from the dome-shaped rooms,
and they all have a hot spring.
Also, you can try
Beppu's speciality, Jigoku Mushi,
which uses geothermal power
to steam food ingredients.
It's a stylish spot
with every service you'd want.
Wow, the view!
What's this, really?
Wait, where's my bed?
Yokota, what do you think,
after becoming a Degawa Girl?
I enjoy it.
When Madame opens her eyes wide,
you'd better be really careful.
She knows that.
What about Mr Degawa?
I thought it was cute that
he does this when he speaks.
It's cute?
I've never noticed that,
but he really does that!
He'd say this and that.
He says this and that.
She said, "Again?"
and this and that.
"Show me the photo, then,"
- Maria grew up a lot.
- Really?
She grew up suddenly
after you two joined.
She grew up so much that
I wonder what she had been doing.
She changed.
- I'm impressed.
Are you impressed by your seniors?
On the bus, I saw Senior Akane
reading a book called
"The Courage to Be Hated."
I thought, "I do need the courage
to be hated."
If you worry about
something on The Quest,
I really recommend that book.
They will show us the glassware
they've made.
They're done!
First, a saké glass made by Yokota,
the one who has most potential.
Ta-da!
- So pretty!
- Beautiful!
Isn't it pretty?
She rolled the coloured glass
on the rim of the glass herself,
it is a beautiful light blue.
It's not absolutely straight,
but it's also unique
to handmade glassware.
Next, it's Yumeppe's vase
she made for her grandma.
Ta-da!
It's a success!
But there's a crack here.
- There is!
- There's a crack...
Actually, when she removed it
from the stick at the last step,
it made a crack at the bottom,
but the shape and the colours
are really beautiful.
You can use as a decoration.
She can use it
if she doesn't fill it with water.
Next, it's Tani's
single-flower vase.
Wow, it's beautiful!
Amazing!
It's so pretty!
The single-flower vase
looks like a twisted milk bottle.
Its shape aside,
the beautiful light blue
of this glassware is vivid.
It was worth getting burnt.
- You put your hand on the tip?
- Yeah, I touched it.
So it was your fault.
Wait, the tip...
Next, it's Hotta,
who continued to fail.
It's beautiful.
- Amazing!
- It's pretty!
It's pretty!
A somen noodles bowl.
Of all places,
the part where it's held is sharp,
there's always the risk
of getting injured.
It's scary.
But it's cute in its own way.
I know, it's highlighted by that.
Next, it's Kawakita, who overcame
the roasting work of hell.
- It's done!
- It's pretty!
It's pretty.
It's pretty!
It's tilted, but the glass
is relatively well-made.
She took the trouble to colour it
and it became irregular,
but it made the glassware
look tasteful instead.
Next, it's Degawa's.
Here!
It's so pretty!
Wonderful!
- Isn't it the best?
- Indeed.
But...
There's a crack.
Oh, there's a crack.
It's a crack in a heart shape,
of all things.
That was close.
It would break in the usual case.
But the Degawa couple's bond
isn't broken.
What are you talking about?
There's a crack!
It's at risk.
It's going to be at risk.
- Is this bad?
- It's bad...
- It's a prediction!
- Oh my god!
Lastly, it's Madame's
champagne glass.
Beautiful!
This is too skilled!
Discussion! Discussion!
I made the top part.
A beautiful champagne glass
Madame took much effort to make.
That said, the whole lower half
was made by the teacher.
It's custom-made.
- It's not custom-made!
- Custom-made.
Madame was doing this and went,
"Make this rounder."
- That's what we call custom-made!
- Not custom-made!
At the last part,
they'll go all out for an activity.
This is the activity
we'd like you to do.
- What's this?
"Super Roulette."
They'll rotate and slide towards
the hole in the centre
of this huge waterslide,
Super Roulette.
It's scary.
This time, they'll compete to see
how long they can hold on
before falling into the water.
Who is going to win?
This is the activity
we'd like you to do.
- What's this?
"Super Roulette."
They'll rotate and slide towards
the hole in the centre
of this huge waterslide,
Super Roulette.
The three people who fall
the soonest
are going to take a thrill ride.
Oh, again!
It's BIRDMAN, which stands
in Kijima Kogen Park, Yufuin.
All three of them will be raised
30 metres above the ground
and fall in one go, suddenly.
Again...
- Oh no!
- This is awful!
- It looks fun!
Wait, the three of you love it?
We want to take that!
You three can go, then!
We don't need to play this game!
Let's do the water slide match.
Tani goes first after a game
of rock, paper, scissors.
Ready, go!
How many seconds can she stay there?
Where is she?
- Isn't she good at it?
- She's good.
Tani held on to it till the end.
What's her result?
6.45 seconds.
It's unfavourable to go first,
but her record is quite good.
Degawa is the second one.
Do you know how many games like this
I've played?
I'll stay there for 10 seconds!
And Degawa gets a surprising record.
He's so good at it!
- He's good!
- Impressive!
That was beautiful.
11.65 seconds.
That's the man, Tetsuro Degawa!
I stayed over 10 seconds!
The third one is Hotta,
who is afraid of thrill rides.
She flew out with a lot of noise...
Wait... Oh no!
But she fell down readily.
5.02 seconds.
Yes!
Her time is hopelessly short
and currently the shortest.
- Here I go!
- Next, Yumeppe.
Off you go!
It's a good start.
Oh no...
She couldn't hold out till the end,
and her record is 6.11 seconds.
"Yanai: 6.11 seconds"
Next, capable at a glance
but can't actually do it,
disappointing Yokota.
Disappointing...
She screams, but still disappoints.
Oh no...
Her record is 5.11 seconds.
The sixth one is...
It's not the weight, it's the spin.
But you stayed the longest.
It's longer if you're heavier.
I thought weight wasn't related,
but weight matters!
Kawakita is gradually getting
more like Madame.
How will she do?
Do your best.
She fell down at once.
- It was so quick!
- Super quick!
4.79 seconds.
For sure.
Gosh! You have to be lying!
Did you measure it properly?
At this point, Hotta and Kawakita
will ride on BIRDMAN.
Lastly, it's Madame's turn.
Do your best, Madame.
I won't let the young girls beat me.
- Here I go!
- Will Madame go to BIRDMAN?
Or will it be Yokota?
Oh, here she is.
Oh no...
Madame couldn't hold out.
What's her result?
4.88 seconds.
"Madame: 4.88 seconds"
So Madame will take
the BIRDMAN ride.
Okay, we're here.
- Whoa!
- Wow...
We've arrived
at a frightening place.
Oh no.
Oh, I hate it.
BIRDMAN.
Oh... I panicked.
"Anyone over 60 years old
can't ride this."
It's a circle.
- It's a circle!
- You startled me!
I thought Madame couldn't ride it,
but it's actually a circle.
Not at all...
Wait, it's a circle. A circle.
You can't get away.
When they go closer to the machine,
Madame starts finding fault.
One of the three people
will pull the start cord.
Who designed this? It's so stupid.
It's going to swing like this,
right?
Don't be ridiculous.
It's ridiculous.
Some people want to do it,
why don't we let them, Director?
Director...
They're already going to give up.
But here...
Madame, let the three of us
try together.
- Oh!
- How can you say that, traitor?
What traitor?
Madame, really,
why don't we hold each other's hands
and encourage each other?
Can you smile and say it's fun
up there?
I'll try my best.
Our old girls think about the show
after all.
Let's go! Jump! It's over.
How dare you say that...
No?
Let's do it, then!
- Wow!
- Madame!
You're really cool!
The 81-year-old Madame
finally made up her mind.
Instead, the two old girls
who persuaded her
are on the verge of crying.
But maybe it's going to be fun.
They finally take off.
You can do it!
I have motion sickness!
I feel sick!
Madame is still smiling.
Will they survive?
They're raised to the highest point.
Three,
two,
one,
go!
Here they go!
Go!
It's fun! It's fun!
Madame keeps saying it's fun,
like she's possessed.
It's fun!
Madame is amazing.
- You really are a psychopath.
- It was fun.
That's our 81-year-old Madame!
- Amazing!
- Wonderful!
The three of them survived.
I forgot to spread my arms
like a bird.
Don't bother...
Madame enjoyed
a first-time experience
to the fullest again.
That's all for
Degawa Girls' Gathering.
It's fun!
- You enjoyed it at last.
- I did.
Amazing!
She's superhuman.
When you three had to do it,
Mayuko said no once,
got her own time in the show,
- then went, "Let's do it!"
- I'm embarrassed.
The way she changed gear
shows she thought about the show.
How was that, Madame Dewi?
I think the new Degawa Girls
are good,
I'm so happy!
- It's fresher.
- It's become stereotyped, right?
The three girls are wearing
similar outfits today too.
They're all white.
Right?
It's full of stereotype.
I know.
It isn't just boring,
it's stereotyped!
Stereotype!
I haven't heard...
It's the first time I hear
there's a stereotype.
You guys are a stereotype!
I haven't heard.