The Quest.
First, it's a special project
of this episode,
Dewi Girls' Party.
One day,
we visited Madame Dewi's home.
Madame, happy 80th birthday.
Thank you.
Wow, this is new.
Madame Dewi turned 80 years old
in February 2020.
We planned to film something
in Indonesia to celebrate it,
but it was cancelled
due to the pandemic.
Is there anything
you'd want to do in Japan?
Go to different hot springs,
and I want to try making vases
and pottery.
I've never tried it before.
To celebrate her 80th birthday,
we'll let her try making pottery
as she wishes.
The stage of her challenge
is Shigaraki, Shiga Prefecture,
the stage of morning drama, Scarlet.
Actually, it can't fit into
Mr Degawa's schedule,
so you and the Degawa Girls will go.
Wow, that's lovely!
We'll have some fresh air.
In The Quest tonight,
we'll present Dewi Girls' Party
and The Quest Hot Springs Club.
Madame, happy 80th birthday!
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
- Degawa, you couldn't join?
- I couldn't,
and Madame said in the video
that they'd have some fresh air.
But behind the scene,
she complained about
taking the girls with her.
I see.
That's what she always says
to begin with.
The Degawa Girls too.
Ojo says
the other girls are unwanted.
I didn't say that!
Yes, you did!
- Their relationship is messy.
- Messy.
I'm really worried.
And this mess will make
Shigaraki pottery.
Is it okay?
Well then,
let's go to the ends of the world.
The Quest!
I'll pay 10,000 yen a day.
Will someone do it?
She's cut out to dig the soil.
It's absorbing a lot!
Hey! You idiot!
Amazing!
Just do it.
"The Quest Hot Springs Club"
Three hours from Tokyo
by bullet train and bus,
four women will try to make pottery.
Dewi Girls' Party
in Shigaraki, Shiga Prefecture.
We are here!
Shigaraki!
Looking forward.
Ladies, this is my 80th birthday,
so please make something lovely
and give it to me as a gift.
We'll be thinking about you...
- There you go again.
- and make it with love.
What do you mean?
- You will see.
-It has some profound meaning.
"Ho ho ho ho ho"
Darn, it's the first time I think
we need Tetchan.
How does it feel
to turn 80 years old?
I'm going to do even a lot more.
How old would you like to get?
Till I turn 108 years old.
It's a long way to go.
It's 28 years.
Follow me, girls.
- Yes.
- We will.
Somehow I feel
Madame will live longer than us.
Now, let's go
to the pottery training camp.
Potter Mr Shusaku Kanzaki
is going to help us.
At the workshop, Miharu Pottery,
he makes pottery
with his father and his wife.
He's the fourth generation
and has worked for 17 years.
First, they'll dig out the soil
used for pottery.
Is there any secret to the soil
in this area?
This place was under Lake Biwa
in the past.
- This is the bottom of Lake Biwa?
- Yes.
Lake Biwa was formed
about 4 million years ago,
near where Iga City, Mie Prefecture,
is today.
Tectonic shifting caused it
to move to the north bit by bit.
It's said that
it moved to where it is now
about 400,000 years ago.
Only this area has good soil.
It's called Kinose Soil.
Beautiful.
It's said to be
a kind of first-rate soil
because it contains
many alkaline substances.
It reacts with the burning firewood
to give a scarlet colour
close to vermilion.
This is a colour
unique to Shigaraki ware,
and this is the colour
called scarlet.
I see.
It's very heavy.
- It costs about 150,000 yen.
- What?
Whether it gives a beautiful scarlet
depends on the temperature
of the kiln and the soil's nature.
Therefore,
everything is one of a kind
and expensive.
Wow, it's difficult.
It's a tough job, huh?
Look.
Madame, can you dig enough
for four people?
I'm done.
It was too fast...
Good.
Hotta displayed her talent
more than anyone here.
You're scary...
"Ugh!"
What's wrong?
You have too much stress?
Wow, I think
I got the stress off my chest.
You're scary...
The soil is so good!
You're cut out to dig soil.
- Good, good. Very good.
You're all turning into Madame Dewi.
- Wonderful. Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
Now, for the process.
We'll dry the soil you've just dug
under the sun.
I see.
- For four, five days.
- Four, five?
- Yes.
- And then...
Oh?
- I've prepared sun-dried soil.
- This isn't right!
This isn't a cooking show!
What the heck was that?
To prepare clay for making pottery,
first, break the sun-dried soil
into fine grains.
- It's quite... Excellent.
- Just like that.
Does it feel good?
No, it's going to give me
tendinitis.
Let's try sieving it now.
Can't we just put the whole lot in?
You can.
It's heavy!
Wait! Don't flap it!
Will you stop that?
If you breathe in the soil powder
and it enters your lungs,
what will happen?
- She asks that?
- Is it okay?
People say it's not good.
"Ha ha ha ha"
The secret to a long life
is other people's misfortune.
Add water to the sieved soil,
and step on it to turn it into clay.
Hey, Maria, do it yourself.
Mr Kanzaki is doing it.
Mr Kanzaki, don't spoil her.
Don't be deceived by her seduction.
It's looking good.
Mr Kanzaki, you're a pro.
It feels like we're working
at a shop. Stop it, girl.
It's nice, Mr Kanzaki.
Kinose Soil is sandy
and there are many grains,
so it's blended with Ohara Soil,
which gives a scarlet colour,
and Shigaraki Soil, which is sticky,
to make the clay for pottery.
But this is somewhat heavy labour.
How much should we mix?
Till the colour is uniform.
What?
I'll pay 10,000 yen a day.
Will someone do it?
A day...
After wedging the clay
for 30 minutes...
Next, it's a process called
spiral wedging.
- We'll knead again?
- To get rid of air in the clay.
It's impossible for amateurs
to do this, so I'll do it.
Oh, thank you!
Spiral wedging is the first hurdle
for people who want to be potters.
Get rid of the air at the creases.
When I went to pottery school,
I did this process from morning
to evening for three weeks.
What?
When the clay is ready,
they'll finally use
the potter's wheel.
The first thing they'll do is...
centring.
By bringing the clay up and down
using wet hands,
the grains in the clay will line up,
and the clay will gather
in the centre of the potter's wheel.
Teacher, you're good at it!
Thank you.
Use the base of your thumb,
press here, and bring it down.
- Wow, amazing!
- It feels so good!
Who is this? He suddenly appeared.
You suddenly appeared
and kneaded my clay. Who are you?
This is their teacher's father,
Mr Tsuguharu Kanzaki.
He's a remarkable person
who is recognised
as intangible cultural asset.
There are only a few in Koga City.
Sorry, Daddy, I'm so sorry.
I asked who you are.
You suddenly kneaded my clay,
so it surprised me.
Now, like Mr Kanzaki says,
pottery reflects
the personality of the potter a lot.
I'm good, aren't I?
You're surprisingly careful.
Don't say that to embarrass me.
I'm assuming a wild character.
When they've gotten used to
the potter's wheel after centring...
- So good!
- Well done.
It's the basics of pottery,
making a teacup.
First, make a hole
on the top of the clay.
I've made a hole.
Next, put the clay between the thumb
and the middle finger,
and pull it out.
Amazing...
It's become wider.
The key of this process
is in the skill of the hands
and concentration.
It's thinner now,
so it'll collapse, right?
Yes.
Lastly, cut it quickly
with a thread,
and a teacup is made in no time.
- Amazing!
- Amazing.
It looks easy
when Mr Kanzaki does it,
but it is quite difficult.
The one who shows her talent
for making pottery is Tani.
- You're making it.
- Making it.
The gist is to keep the force
and speed stable when you pull.
- How did I do?
- Maria, you're good at it.
Yay! Really?
You're very good at it.
She successfully cut it
with a thread too.
She's so good at it!
- It's done.
- Amazing!
It's a bit round.
Didn't Mr Kanzaki do it?
I did it myself.
That's it for the first day.
Pottery Training Camp's
hotel tonight is...
an expensive hotel at the lakeside,
Ogoto Hot Spring,
Biwako Grand Hotel Kyo-Ohmi.
Wow, it's huge!
- Amazing!
It's actually a VIP suite
with four rooms.
It costs 48,000 yen per person
per night.
Of course, it has an outdoor
hot spring overlooking Lake Biwa.
It's gorgeous.
It's absolutely stunning.
But only Madame can't stay here.
Before they came here,
they actually had a mizugumo match
at Ninja Village,
and Madame
fell into the water immediately.
Oh?
"Ha ha ha ha"
Also, when they competed
to see if they can ride eFoil,
the most advanced activity...
It feels so good!
Oh, I can do it!
Madame was completely defeated
by the girls.
The three winners
are treated to this.
This must be the first time
you'll experience this,
so have fun.
It's Omi beef!
It's the first time
I'm trying Omi beef.
You eat the meat first?
Yes.
It really melts.
Well, enjoy it to the fullest.
Madame, let's go.
Sure, let's go.
Well, enjoy your night.
Excuse me.
Not that way.
Not this way?
"Madame mistakes the cupboard
for the exit"
And this is where Madame will stay.
Oh, a bungalow?
Something like a bungalow.
Lake Biwa Maiami Land,
Maiami Hama Caravan Park.
Let's have a look at the room.
Please take off your shoes.
No shoes allowed.
Wait a minute.
Madame, please take off your shoes.
Take off your shoes.
What? Oh, take off my shoes.
This is the bed.
It has an air conditioner.
I'll have dinner here?
This one? Oh, it's this one?
- This one?
- It's this one.
A hinged door?
- It's that one.
- Oh, this one.
She'll cook tonight's meal
with a mess tin.
Firelighter? What is it made of?
What is it?
What? You don't know?
You don't know either.
I don't. Firelighter? No way.
Aren't you doing it too quickly?
Come on, it doesn't light at all.
Shall we call Hiroshi here?
It takes about 30 minutes
for the rice to cook.
And then...
It's time for some champagne.
I'm thirsty.
At least get her some champagne.
That was a nice pop.
She looks like a witch
drinking a living person's blood.
Now life has been given to me.
Although her stomach is empty,
she keeps drinking champagne.
Amazing.
It's delicious. Exquisite.
And Madame is drunk.
I am Hiroshi.
Before I realised it,
I've been playing with
an elastic band for two hours.
I am Hiroshi.
None of you laughed.
Is it not funny?
It was funny.
- I was laughing.
- You didn't laugh at all.
You're lying. Not at all.
Nobody even chuckled. How rude.
On the second day of training camp,
they'll make some art.
First, they'll sketch
what they want to make.
I love flowers, so I'll make a vase.
The one with the tulip is better.
The long one.
This one?
Okay, I'll make the big one.
I heard beer tastes better
from a Shigaraki ware mug.
It makes the foam very fine.
This is mine.
I want to make two mugs and a plate.
It has opened petals.
Isn't it lovely?
Mine is very commonplace.
It's good.
Madame, you're so good at drawing.
It's also a vase.
It looks a bit like a basket.
But I actually wanted
a pair of parent and child frogs.
It's cute.
After deciding what to make,
they start making it.
Madame starts making a vase.
She presses the sides
to make it into her ideal shape.
- Lovely!
- This is good.
Let's cut it from here.
- Here?
- Yes.
- It'll look weird. Is it okay?
- It'll be fine.
Really?
"Trust no one" is the secret
to a long life.
- Here.
- Here?
Mr Kanzaki,
I'd like to make it a bit wider.
To make it wider,
put your hand inside,
then tilt your body to the side
with your fingers inside.
Please show me.
The street-smart girl can manipulate
anyone as she wishes.
If you tilt your body,
your hand goes with you.
Then press the edge in gently
with a wooden spatula.
How is it, Mr Kanzaki?
- It's cute.
- Cute? Yay!
Madame, I've made it.
What do you think?
She's too busy to look.
Tani displayed her talent
in using the potter's wheel,
and she's making a vase.
Keep going.
Keep it there...
Let's narrow it once.
- At one go from the outside.
- I see.
To stretch it upwards,
hold the clay between the hands,
squeeze with a bit of force,
and pull it up slowly.
- Isn't it nice?
- It's nice.
- It's just like what you sketched.
- Yes.
At the same time,
Madame is making a pot
with a method called hand-building.
Hand-building is done
by piling clay made into strands.
It is a technique
used to make big pots.
Madame spent about two hours
on this.
Amazing!
It's good.
Just when she is about to finish...
Oh, hang on.
That was a close call.
She started the potter's wheel
by mistake.
But she still finished making
a nice pot.
The other three ladies
also made some good pottery.
The third day
of the pottery training camp.
Madame had some business in Tokyo
on that day,
so they took a day off pottery.
So only the girls will go
and film somewhere.
They've come
to Lake Biwa Children's Kingdom.
- This is what we'd like you to do.
- What?
What's that?
It's quite... What is it?
It's called Free Fall,
a slide that is 5.5 metres tall.
The angle is 80 degrees,
but it looks almost vertical.
A right angle.
- Oh, no.
- The first one is Tani,
who likes thrill rides.
It's scary.
Now, let's go. Free Fall!
- Three, two, one.
- Go!
- This is fun!
Did she hit her head?
She hit her head?
- Why? Wait!
- She was floating!
She was, right?
- I was floating!
- You were!
- It was scary, right?
- It was fun!
It isn't fun...
Go, Akane.
Hang on.
You go.
I'm so scared I'm going to cry.
Stop it, Akane!
You're making me scared!
But I have to go. Here I come!
- Three, two, one. Go!
Oh?
- Go!
She hesitates now.
- It's scary.
- Wait.
And then...
- Amazing.
- Well done.
Stop it, Akane,
you're making me scared!
It didn't occur to me
I'd cry at Children's Kingdom.
I'll wear it.
Oh, I really don't want to do it.
There can't be reactions more
different than the previous two.
Stop it!
- Three, two, one. Go!
Wow, amazing.
Good.
As always, she did it for nothing.
The final day
of the pottery training camp.
- Let's finish the pottery off.
- Okay.
Today, we'll do some trimming
and make the handles.
To make the container
light and easy to carry,
the excess part at the bottom
is shaved off with a turning tool.
That's what it does?
What if you fail?
You'll open a hole, so be careful.
May I ask Mr Kanzaki
to just finish it off?
I agree.
- You're still doing it?
- Next, it's the centre.
It's likely to open a hole
in the centre.
That is what a pot looks like.
- It'll explode if it's too heavy.
- Explode?
- Explode to dust.
- In the kiln?
- In the kiln.
- I see.
If the bottom of a pot
is too thick or heavy,
it won't dry inside.
So when it's put in a hot kiln,
the moisture will expand,
and the pot will explode.
Now, to make the handle
of the beer mug,
pull the clay into a strand.
Wrap a wet towel around it
to mould it.
Also, apply mud as adhesive
to the place you want it to stick,
and put the handle on the mug.
If you don't apply a lot,
it'll fall off when you dry it.
No...
I don't want to give it away.
Four days have passed
since they made it from the soil.
Surely
she would've grown fond of it.
Also, by Madame's earnest request,
she made the frog decoration too.
It's a bit scary.
Scary...
After I made the frog,
it only looks like Mr Degawa to me,
so it's Degawa Frog.
Isn't it nice to have
a ridiculous frog?
"Degawa Frog"
The four days of training camp
are over now.
Well done.
Thank you...
How was it?
I worked so hard to make it,
so I'll be careful when I use it.
Madame, I'll give you this vase
and one more...
I made it with my love...
Love Madame.
I like the long one more.
But the real challenge begins now.
After they're dried for two weeks,
they're fired in an electric kiln.
If this isn't performed,
they won't be able to stand
the high temperature
of gloss firing.
One month later,
they're finally loaded in the kiln.
They're finally loaded in the kiln.
The pottery are put in the cave kiln
Mr Kanzaki built 15 years ago.
Firewood is added and burned.
Oh, it has been a while.
- How are you?
- Amazing.
I saw them!
The ones we made are awesome!
The colour is totally different!
Wait, doesn't my beer mug
look very good?
Wow, it's so lovely!
We've fired it unglazed once
to sintering,
and it has become stronger.
But it's still fragile,
so be careful.
I must handle it with care.
Just my own ones.
Clay is added to prevent pottery
from sticking to the kiln.
Let's start from Madame's.
- Where should I put it?
-Wherever.
The top then.
That will decide how it is fired.
Don't say something so scary.
The pottery are unglazed this time.
The colour and value are
greatly affected by their placement.
I'm nervous.
The best place is the lowest shelf
of the front row.
However...
It's quite likely
the firewood will touch it,
so 20 per cent will break.
But if it's fired perfectly here,
it'll have a wonderful colour.
This is art created
only with soil and fire.
I know. Let's put one of everybody's
in the front.
Madame's precious pot is placed
at the most risky place, in front.
By the way, the large pot
to its left was made by Mr Kanzaki.
How about this?
It's good.
Then the kiln is closed
using bricks,
and the fire is lit.
Please fire nicely!
Now, for four whole days,
the pottery will be fired
24 hours a day.
Firewood needs to be added
every seven minutes
and ten at a time.
The structure of Mr Kanzaki's
cave kiln is as shown.
Firewood is added from the front,
and temperature rises every day.
The inside of the kiln
was 150 degrees on the first day,
but by the second morning,
it's risen to about 340 degrees.
It rose to nearly
a surprising 700 degrees at night.
Amazing.
Then, when the fourth day comes...
Hey, look...
Wow, impressive.
There's fire coming out the chimney.
It's on fire! Fire, fire, fire!
Madame is worried about her pot,
so she went to Shiga on a day trip.
- Now it's about 1,230 degrees.
- Twelve hundred?
Can you see the inside?
Amazing!
The temperature inside is so high
that nothing can be seen.
- I can't open my eyes. It's hot.
- It's hot.
I've been doing it for four days.
Thank you for the effort.
About three tons of firewood
were burnt in four days.
It's hot!
1,230 degrees is as hot as lava.
- It's hot...
- It's hot... Madame, hurry up!
It's hot there and hot here.
- Oh?
- Madame!
Now our love for it
has deepened, indeed.
But the day it breaks,
I'll really...
- snap.
- You'll be angry?
Late that night, the firing is done.
Then Mr Kanzaki seals
the opening of the kiln with clay.
This cools the kiln down slowly
and prevents pottery from breaking.
It's ancient wisdom.
One week later,
the kiln is finally unloaded.
I like this thrill a lot.
It's like a time capsule.
I know.
We usually do the filming
of the show for four days,
but this took two months,
one-and-a-half months?
But they paid us the same amount.
Then the door is finally opened.
Were their pottery fired well?
It's the time of fate.
Were they fired well?
Now, it's the time of fate.
The first thing Mr Kanzaki takes out
is the pot he made.
Amazing!
However...
How cruel. It's broken.
The colour is gorgeous,
but the pot is broken.
I put it at a risky place.
Hotta put Madame's pot at a place
as risky as Mr Kanzaki's.
If Madame's pot has broken,
it's totally Akane's fault.
That's really the only thing
that scares me.
I'll start from taking Maria's.
Okay.
Is it fired well?
- So lovely!
- It's so lovely!
A long vase that looks just like
the sketch is done.
So cool!
When the base for firing
is taken off,
the surface has a beautiful gloss,
and the vase looks quite good.
However...
I can see Madame.
What?
It's a shame the bottom has a crack.
Next, it's Hotta's beer mug.
I'm so nervous.
I didn't expect myself
to get so nervous.
So, is it fired nicely?
Wow, amazing!
Thank you!
What?
Did you buy it?
A beer mug made by Hotta.
It has a beautiful shade of scarlet
unique to Shigaraki ware.
It's a wonderful piece.
Next, it's Kawakita's bowl.
Yours is lovely too.
- It's so cute!
- It's nice. Very good.
Kawakita's bowl
resembles flower petals.
- So cute.
It will wrap softly
around anything you put in.
What a gentle bowl.
- Now, I'll take out Madame's pot.
- Okay.
Oh, no! I'm so nervous.
It was fired at quite a risky place.
What is the result?
Here.
- Here.
- Amazing!
It's lovely!
It's so lovely!
Like one you can buy.
The pot Madame made
with all her might is done.
Thank goodness.
The part that looks like droplets
is glass that formed
when ash melted.
The scarlet colour and gradation
are beautiful.
It's so beautiful!
I'm so impressed.
I'm touched.
The last thing Mr Kanzaki
takes out is...
Wait, what...
Amazing!
A miracle happened!
A pot is stuck to Degawa Frog!
Whose pot is it?
Isn't it mine?
It became a joint effort!
- This is so cute!
- Amazing!
Made by Hotta and Tani,
Degawa Pot Frog.
- Amazing.
- So cute.
A miraculous collaboration was done
in the over 1,200-degree kiln.
- Amazing!
- Why?
Besides these,
many other things were fired
to celebrate Madame's 80th birthday.
- Amazing.
- So cute.
- Happy 80th birthday.
- Happy birthday.
But you all made so much effort
to make them,
so take those you like
and I'll have the ones
you don't want.
How kind of you.
We'll give
what we want to give Madame.
- Yes.
I'll give this to Mr Degawa.
Shigaraki ware...
A great success!
- Madame, happy 80th birthday!
- Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
That concludes Dewi Girls' Party,
Shigaraki Ware.
- Interesting.
- Wonderful!
Shigaraki ware is nice,
but the surfing we did
on the lake...
We did it again and again,
but you didn't show it at all.
What's that about, director?
There's the director.
Where? You cut all of that?
- The pot is more important.
- What?
Then just let us make the pots!
Yes.
Why did we have to do that?
It took us a whole day.
It took us one whole day.
- What do you think, Imoto?
- Well...
I thought pottery is only using
the potter's wheel,
but after watching this,
the whole process
of making it from soil,
I now know it's very difficult.
We worked so hard to make them.
Why don't you show them here today?
Oh, no. She's really angry.
You should just display it here.
Now, let's move on. Oshima, please.
Okay. Next, it's this.
The Quest Hot Springs Club!
Yes!
One day..
we gathered five comediennes.
We came up in a hurry with the idea
of what we'd film outside last time,
but it was surprisingly
well-received.
What?
- Who said it?
- Who? I haven't heard.
- Who said it was good?
- Nobody told me.
This time,
please decide it yourselves too.
- What?
- Wrong, wrong, this is so wrong.
- You're giving up your job.
- Indeed.
So they will also go
on a sudden trip
and decide the destination
the day before they set off.
Iwate or Yamagata is nice.
Is Iwate Miyagi?
Iwate is Iwate.
I heard there's a super amazing
shrine in Yamagata.
It's a place called Dewa Sanzan.
It's totally different
from all shrines you've been to.
- It has spiritual energy?
- So it seems.
When Jungle Pocket's Mr Ota
told Crystal Noda,
I was listening near them.
You eavesdropped.
We went to the Nebuta Festival
the other day, right?
Yeah.
Dancing during the summer holiday
is fun, right?
So let's go to a place
where there's dancing,
and we'll hold a small festival.
It sounds like an amazing project.
Asako can't help but think about
the planning.
The next day.
We have come to...
Yamagata!
They came to Tsuruoka City,
Yamagata Prefecture.
This time,
they all wear their own outfits too.
This isn't New York!
Yoshiko is the strange one.
- It's summer.
- It's autumn.
What does it mean, "JUST DO IT"?
Just do it.
You can't tease other people.
Yours is the T-shirt
of the 24-Hour Television
held not long ago.
They tried to come up
with various things,
but this is the most difficult
outfit to tease.
The tour of places comediennes want
to go to in Yamagata starts now.
First, it's Dewa Sanzan.
Dewa Sanzan.
It literally refers to
the three mountains
in north Yamagata.
It hasn't been shown in the media,
but the shrine
has amazing spiritual energy.
When we tried
and asked for permission,
we were told that we could film
if we go to visit formally.
This is the formal wear,
mountain priest style.
Originally, Dewa Sanzan was found
by the god that wards off plague.
It was 1,400 years ago.
Dewa Sanzan refers to
Mount Gassan, Mount Haguro,
and Mount Yudono.
One will be reborn after going round
the three mountains,
and they've been worshipped
since ancient times.
Priest of Mountain Haguro,
Guide Hayasaka, will take us around.
Please take the tour seriously
as mountain priests today
and be reborn at the peak.
Yes, thank you.
They'll reply "Yes, thank you"
to everything during training.
Let's go. Depart!
Yes, thank you.
Now, they enter Mount Haguro.
They enter the sacred area
through the gate.
Standing behind the cedar trees
is the National Treasure,
the Five-Storey Pagoda
of Mount Haguro.
It looks so cool.
The 29-metre tall tower
is said to have been built
by Taira no Masakado,
and no nail was used
when it was built.
Then they climb up an approach
of 2,446 stone steps.
Mount Haguro is said to have been
established to ward off diseases.
This is the very place
they should visit
during this pandemic.
Let's get some rest.
- Yes.
- Yes, thank you.
Yes, thank you.
It was the most positive answer.
This is chikara mochi,
the speciality of the teahouse here.
The rice dumplings
are all handmade here.
May we have this?
You're receiving training, so no.
We prepared it
for you to have a look.
It's very tasty.
Please don't tell us any more.
Staff members can try later.
- Thank you.
- What?
- There are five of them.
- Thank you.
- Okay, let's go.
- Yes, thank you.
Two hours after they set off,
they finally arrived at the peak.
They visited Sanjin Gosaiden,
which blesses them
with the same benefits
as going round the three mountains,
and their training is finished.
They let us enter
an extraordinary place.
It was great, somehow.
- It was absolutely amazing.
- It was, right?
My body feels lighter.
My pee was very concentrated.
If you say that,
I took a number two...
Shut up.
"Stimulated Oniyakko's
bowel movement"
It's like it had its own mind.
Five things that were like
comma-shaped beads
just dropped out.
Aren't they beads?
They looked so much like
comma-shaped beads,
I thought,
"They really are different."
Beads.
And it was five comma-shaped beads.
Did they have words like "faith"
and "justice" written on them?
It's "Satomi Hakkenden".
Faith, justice.
Now it's 2:00.
Their schedule is blank after this.
It's hot. It's hot and cold.
Maybe there's a chance
to go fishing today.
Last time,
when they filmed in Aomori,
the three ladies
caught many sea breams,
and they were delighted.
Encouraged by the success,
they called a fishing boat
renting service this time too.
Hello?
However...
We're expecting wind
of about 10 metres per second.
They can't sail a boat
because of the strong wind.
So they go buy some tools
and aim to catch bigfin reef squid
on the shore.
And then...
Wait a minute. Hey, wait a minute.
What's this? Hair?
A fishing visor.
I want to start from the looks.
Isn't it nice?
They went to a fishing port.
We planned it wrong.
Night fell
while we were having fun shopping.
Yeah.
So we don't need any cap,
and it's difficult to see
wearing sunglasses.
The three ladies
who caught sea breams last time
will catch squids.
Asako and Yoshiko
will just try to catch anything.
I want to catch some.
But bigfin reef squids aren't easy
enough for amateurs to catch.
They caught nothing.
But...
- You caught something?
- Yes.
Yoshiko and Asako caught something.
- All right.
- What's that?
Some cute horse mackerels.
Aren't they bait
for catching big fish?
It's hard to react to this.
Why? You guys caught nothing!
We're very grateful though.
- Better than nothing.
What? "Better than nothing"?
Will you not say "better than zero"
just once?
Glad you caught something.
Are you robots?
It's better than nothing.
What the heck?
Day two of the trip in Yamagata.
The comediennes
absolutely love buffet.
This is nice.
The buffet is nice.
You wear glasses?
My eyesight isn't good.
It's in the morning, I'm sorry.
"Chuckles"
What's she eating?
So good.
Grated yam, Yamagata's stock,
and natto.
I mixed the sticky food.
That's right, the middle-aged woman
loves her sticky food.
I think
my mum was very happy this time.
Yesterday, she kept...
rocking her hips
and dancing in the bathroom.
Of course she was naked
and kept doing this.
That's gross!
You do that in the bathroom?
It's only my mum who rocks her hips.
They start in Tsuruoka City
on the second day of their tour.
The place they want to go is...
I want to go to the Jelly...
- Jellyfish Planetarium?
- That's right.
It is located at Tsuruoka City's
Kamo Aquarium.
Oh, they're so cute!
Look, there's a tiny one!
The Jellyfish Planetarium
is the exhibition room of jellyfish.
There are over 60 kinds
of jellyfish here.
So cute!
The scale of the jellyfish display
is the largest in the world.
And the highlight is...
Amazing!
the huge fish tank,
The Dream House of Jellies.
- It's huge!
- Beautiful!
What jellyfish are they?
10,000 jellyfish are floating
in the fish tank
with a five-metre diameter,
and the sight is magical.
The one who was the most excited
at the aquarium was...
I heard
it's difficult to keep jellyfish.
Okarina.
Please have a look at Okarina,
who couldn't contain her excitement.
It's exhibited in Japan
for the first time.
Are they the same species?
Their names are similar.
Water needs to be flowing?
Most jellyfish with long tentacles
eat other jellyfish.
They aren't poisonous.
Their lifespan is about a year?
What's polyp?
It's what they are
before they become jellyfish.
That's enoki mushroom!
It's a small, cute underwear.
They aren't cute halfway.
Which is the tasty jellyfish?
Do they run away when enemies come?
Is the water turning in circles,
or are they turning in circles?
If they're living,
then I can give it my all too.
Next, the five ladies
go to Yamagata City.
They've come to the famous
Yamadera Temple.
They climb up the stairs...
This place...
"The stillness permeating the rocks,
cicadas' trill."
The poem was written
on a strip of paper and buried here.
Wow, is that so?
That's right,
the well-known haiku
was written here.
It's said that Matsuo Basho
had climbed the stone steps,
and there's a hall
with a long history up ahead.
Wow!
- Amazing!
- This place is amazing.
You can see a stunning panorama
from this place.
You can see on three sides.
As they've come to a wonderful place
like this, let's compose a haiku.
- Yoshiko goes first.
- Please read it.
In the large mountain,
I smell something like
pomander ball.
It's rap.
I made it rhyme a bit.
In the large mountain,
I smell something like
pomander ball.
Next, it's Okarina.
At Yamadera, a red dragonfly
looks down at the world beneath.
She wrote a proper one.
We started to write proper ones.
The mountains are laughing.
Leaf, leaf, leaf.
A primary school child
would get an award for it.
Sorry, I put in two seasonal words.
Is it autumn leaves?
When I look at my friend's hair,
I can feel autumn.
- Amazing!
- It's lovely!
I'm happy you've likened me
to autumn leaves.
It's still early.
She suddenly had an inspiration.
I'm glad the five of us
can travel together again.
Lovely...
Oh? It doesn't stop there.
Please read it out loud.
I'll be happy
if we continue to film here.
Where did you write it?
Then the five of them
head towards their next destination.
Our cameraman has strong arms.
His blood vessels
look easy to pierce.
"Vaccination by former nurse,
Okarina"
You see blood vessels like that?
- I do.
- Even now.
I feel so grateful
if it's straight and not crawling.
What about mine?
Miss Asako, yours...
That's how a nurse touches.
I might fail to draw blood
from you once.
You've never succeeded, right?
How dare you! Of course I did.
I did it every day.
I can do it well for everyone
when I'm on a roll. Honestly.
The five of them have come to...
the most secluded hot spring
at the back of a valley located
at an altitude of 1,300 metres.
It's a famous hot spring
with nearly 500 years of history,
Ubayu Hot Spring.
"Yamanba Bath."
The logogram is a combination
of "woman" and "old".
That's Asako.
Asako of the mountain.
"Asako of the mountain"
Wait a minute, it's impressive!
Surround by a magnificent valley
is Ubayu Hot Spring's Yamanba Bath.
It's irresistible!
It's the mountain.
They pour hot water on themselves
before bathing.
- From there...
- I'll pour it from above.
The cloudy water is a bit hot.
It's hot.
Be careful, you're showing your bum.
It's quite hot!
She's serious.
- She's scary.
- She's laughing.
The old mountain hag.
She looks happy.
The hot spring is a simple
acidic sulphur hot spring.
The soft hot water
can help to treat skin diseases.
They're earnest.
Yoshiko does a freestyle rap.
Old hag!
The old hag's food is tofu skin
Tofu skin!
Next to the tofu skin is an old hag!
There's an old hag!
Even during a sudden trip,
she can still make her joke fail.
It was quite bad.
Are you okay?
What's wrong with your eye?
It twitched during the journey
from time to time.
It twitched when I'd think,
"Oh, no. What should I do?"
Is it the pressure?
Yes. Not my face.
What did Miss Asako say?
This is bad!
The pressure is making
my left eye twitch.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
Please don't mind. I'm sorry.
What else did Miss Asako say?
Something is wrong with my eye.
What's that about?
It doesn't get any better.
Lastly, as Asako planned,
they'll dance
at the summer festival.
They hold a woven hat
adorned with red flowers
to perform the Hanagasa dance.
It's so cute.
"Hanagasa Dance Troupe"
At the annual Hanagasa Festival
held in summer in Yamagata,
over 10,000 dancers dance
to the Hanagasa Ondo in a parade,
and it's a special feature here.
Ms Fujima, the president
of their dance association,
- will teach the ladies.
- President.
Hit the knees nine times.
Step out, tap. Turn it, tap.
- And tap.
- Step out, tap.
Turn, tap.
- It's wrong.
Hit the knees nine times.
Now, they'll show us
the result of their practice.
Yoshiko, well done.
The two in front are good.
Choi, choi!
"Yonezawa beef hamburger,
Yonezawa steak, and Bistro Hikousen"
They were treated kindly
everywhere they went.
Thank you, people of Yamagata.
You went to Ginzan Onsen?
Isn't it fantastic?
It's amazing.
It's Haikara-San:
Here Comes Miss Modern.
Haikara-San...
She looks so fat.
She's really fat.
How rich is her family?
How spoilt is this girl?
Her parents would say she's lovely.
That concludes their trip
to Yamagata.
How was it, Oshima?
They had a lot of fun.
We've been doing scary things
in The Quest so far,
so I would root for them,
but I was totally relaxed today.
You see,
Yakko didn't call it "filming".
She kept saying it was a trip.
The three of you seemed to have
enjoyed yourselves a lot,
but after I saw the twitching
of Yoshiko's left eye, it was...
- It must've been tough.
- Yes.
It twitched most often
in the bullet train journey back.
It kept twitching.