The Quest.
Today's first segment is...
Ganbareruya's
Fighting Spirit Series.
They're given difficult tasks
like cheerleading and rock climbing,
Ganbareruya will overcome them
with their fighting spirit.
The task they'll do this time is...
What's this?
Rhythmic gymnastics?
That's right, the task this time
is rhythmic gymnastics,
where they'll dance like fairies
while using various apparatuses.
I'm so happy, hurray! I'm happy!
Hurray!
In fact,
Ganbareruya had been wanting
to do rhythmic gymnastics
eagerly in this series.
This time, for the ladies
who won't give up no matter what,
we'll be prepared to shelf it
when we do this.
Is there any concern?
We're flexible.
I see.
If I must say,
I think I gained a bit of weight,
but I can do it.
What's the matter?
I can do it!
I can do this.
Wow, impressive!
Impressive!
How good can they get in one week?
Welcome to The Quest.
Tonight, it's Ganbareruya's
Fighting Spirit Series
and the third Wazuma Tetsuro.
Wasshoi!
"Morisanchu"
Hello...
Hello.
V!
Okay, it's Ganbareruya's
Fighting Spirit Series.
It's rhythmic gymnastics.
Yes.
Fairy Japan did very well
at the Tokyo 2020 Olympics.
The Fairies of The Quest,
Ganbareruya,
this time...
Hang on.
What did you just say?
The Fairies of The Quest
Nobody calls you that!
What?
Don't "what" me.
Huh?
What the heck?
Can I watch it
like watching Fairy Japan?
Please do.
You can score our performance
if you like.
You're confident in yourselves.
Sure. Please do that.
You're heavy.
Heavy? Look who's talking.
Her knees will give in.
Let's come down.
"Ganbareruya's
Fighting Spirit Project"
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Are you stupid?
She pisses me off!
"Clumsy old man
takes up the challenge"
Already?
45 minutes from Shiodome by car,
It's so close.
Ganbareruya's
Fighting Spirit Series.
It's in Tokyo?
How good can they get
in rhythmic gymnastics in a week?
In Tokyo.
They've come
to Kunitachi City, Tokyo,
to Tokyo Women's College
of Physical Education.
Excuse me.
They're students
of the rhythmic gymnastics club,
who will be helping us this time.
Nice to meet you...
They accepted
the unreasonable demand
of letting Ganbareruya join them.
Amazing.
Let's now ask them
to perform for us.
How do they spin?
Tokyo Women's College
of Physical Education
won 59 times out of 73
in the Japan National
Rhythmic Gymnastics Championship.
Many students of this powerhouse
also joined Fairy Japan.
They're all in great shape.
They are.
They're so cool.
Rhythmic gymnastics
is usually performed individually
or in a group of five,
but this time, they'll perform
in a group of 21.
So cool.
Amazing!
It matches what we've been
wanting to do.
That was impressive.
I want to do all of them,
without leaving out any.
Yoshiko, are you as flexible?
Indeed, I am flexible.
Just a gross move.
They're so excited.
They'll be taught
by someone extraordinary,
Ms Erika Akiyama.
The way she stands
shows she was a gymnast.
Can I do this even if I'm heavy?
You can.
Machan's body is stiff.
It's possible.
Let's start the practise right away.
There are five kinds of apparatus
in rhythmic gymnastics.
These are
the five kinds of apparatus.
This time, among them,
they'll use a ball, a hoop,
and a ribbon for the performance.
First, the ball.
I think the ball is the apparatus
you're most familiar with.
As shown, it's thrown up, caught,
and the performer
uses her body to roll the ball.
Impressive.
When you throw or manipulate it,
points are deducted if you grab it.
We can't grab it?
Yes.
Let it stay on your body.
What?
Wow, that's a difficult rule.
First, they'll practise throwing
the ball behind the back
and catch it from the front.
Go.
Yes. Well done, well done.
On the other hand, Yoshiko...
It looks easy at a glance,
but throwing the ball
to the aimed spot is very difficult.
That was good.
From the front...
Well done.
Amazing.
Machan, I'm impressed.
How can you do that?
You're just clumsy.
She's suddenly harsh.
Next, it's ribbon.
Draw beautiful circles.
They'll try to do the shape
called spiral.
Make it look like there are about
four circles in midair.
If the ribbon falls to the ground,
marks will be deducted.
Keep it above the floor
all the time.
But it's difficult when they try it.
It became some random shape...
On top of that...
Is there a knot?
If the movement is bad,
it ties a knot instantly.
In a competition, many marks
will be deducted if a knot is tied.
Lastly, it's the hoop.
Amazing.
When the hoop rolls here,
jump over it.
Let's try it, okay?
Mahiru goes first.
She's good at it.
Next, it's Yoshiko's turn.
Okay.
Sorry.
Watch out.
Where did you receive it?
Will marks be deducted
if I use my crotch to receive it?
I don't know.
On the first day of practise,
the two are painfully made aware
of how hard rhythmic gymnastics is.
Would you like us to go easy on you?
No.
I want you to think of it as
a performance in the Olympic Games.
I want you to watch it like watching
a performance by Fairy Japan.
Day two of practise.
What the heck?
This is bad.
They'll practise with the students
starting today.
The students who will practise
together with Ganbareruya
are Succhan and Ayu.
They'll pack various techniques
into the 3.5minute performance
this time.
First, this is the technique
Mahiru will try.
After throwing the hoop,
she'll do a cartwheel
over someone and catch it.
One, two, three, four, five.
Okay...
Don't run away from it.
Keep your eyes on it.
It's scary.
Yoshiko will throw a ribbon
with her leg.
Incorporating a rotation skill
called Illusion,
she'll kick the ribbon up.
What's this?
How do you throw it?
I can't. I'm sorry.
Also, they'll do a combination skill
to exchange the ball.
They'll catch the ball facetoface
and bounce it on the back.
They bounce the ball this time?
What? I'm in a slump.
There is something
Yoshiko wants to do no matter what.
I'd like to do
an acrobatic technique.
A front handspring.
Yes.
Put your hands on the floor
and kick your legs forward.
Turn like this.
I want to do it.
That said,
this technique is too difficult,
so this time, she'll try
a front handspring with assistance.
I see.
But Yoshiko can't even do
the minimum requirement,
a handstand.
I can't do a handstand against
the wall because I'm scared.
So they will hold her up by force.
Wait...
Hang in there...
It's heavy!
Wait, it's heavy! My body is heavy!
It's okay.
My body is heavy.
It's okay, it's okay.
Put me down.
It's okay.
I'm scared. I'm really scared!
To get rid of her fear,
she'll let her body get used
to how it feels.
After one foot is on the floor...
There's no part of her
that looks like a fairy.
Oh, I see.
That's how you do it.
I don't know anymore.
While they're practising,
have a look at the video of the last
location we couldn't include.
They came
to a hotel that recreated the
stunning view in Santorini, Greece,
Villa Santorini.
The thing they did here was...
Mutual Trust Balance Challenge.
They pull each other in front
and behind in this position,
and it's successful
if they can balance in a V shape.
The V shape is what we do.
How can we not be able to do it?
But...
Aren't the back of your knees
sticking out?
Yeah, my knees stick out
at the back a bit.
You have your kneecaps
in front, right?
Mine are at the back.
Indeed.
My kneecaps are at the back.
Now, it's a quiz on Yoshiko's knees.
Is she laying down on her stomach
or her back?
Stomach?
On her stomach.
The correct answer is...
I'm lying on my back.
The people at the osteopathic clinic
were so surprised
that they took this photo
for reference.
Okay, let's do
the Mutual Trust Balance Challenge.
I'll stand. Ready, go.
And then...
Ready, go.
V!
But going back from here
is very difficult.
I was thinking, we'd fall
even if we do it successfully.
How are we supposed
to stand back up?
Next, they'll try
Doctor Fish on the Face.
I'm happy.
I've got a lot of dead skin
on my face.
Katsurahama Aquarium
helped us film this.
They can get rid of dead skin,
so it's very effective
if you have dead skin.
The fish will be delighted
and it's awesome for me.
This is a winwin relationship.
Mahiru tries it first.
They came close.
So cute.
Many come close.
The Doctor Fish go straight
to the feast that suddenly appeared.
Her nostrils...
Amazing.
It felt like they were kissing me.
It felt like a very deep
and passionate kiss.
Yoshiko is confident
she has old, dead skin.
They went there...
Many go to her chin.
The fish gather at her chin
for some reason,
but they aren't as eager
as expected.
How was it?
I wonder. Maybe it was few.
Yeah?
Maybe it's rotten?
It isn't even food?
Day three of practise.
They rehearse to the music
for the performance starting today,
but the amount of exercise
for 3.5 minutes is unbelievable.
Of course.
It's tough.
Yoshiko also practises
how to do a front handspring.
Wait a minute.
She can't breathe.
Shall I bring you some oxygen?
Sorry, I lack oxygen.
Thanks.
The music is playing.
Almost.
Why don't you raise your legs
one by one, Yocchan?
Too much. Too much.
Raise your legs one by one.
Raise my legs one by one?
Want some?
Not oxygen again.
It's too much.
Day five of practise.
It's the regular morning stretching.
I'm sensitive to spirits.
Is this place haunted?
It is. If you touch the doll
in the storage room,
you'll get injured.
Ayu touched it and got injured.
My tendon tore.
Fear. The cursed doll passed down
to the Tokyo Women College
of Physical Education.
Can you see it from there?
Yes.
It's the Japanese doll
among the two.
I'm scared.
I just felt a chill
run down my spine.
They go to look at it closely.
I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
At that time...
What?
Hey! Stop it!
It was you guys!
They became so close.
It was you!
Only you do things like that!
It's only you!
They're so close.
It was you!
Only you would do it!
Only you would do
something like that!
They've been practising like this
for five whole days.
They were total amateurs,
but it's starting to take shape
little by little.
Nice!
Impressive.
Amazing.
That's it.
Amazing!
You did it three times in a row.
But there's no sign
of a successful handstand.
Yocchan...
Don't cry.
You'll make me cry too.
You can do it.
Do your best.
You'll make me cry.
I'm sorry.
I feel so ashamed of myself.
Let's do our best.
Let your hands remember
how it feels.
Do this, then this.
Climb up.
Remember how this feels.
Her knees will give in.
Let's come down.
I'm sorry!
Hey!
Of all things,
Yoshiko farted directly
at the legend's face.
I'm sorry, Ms Akiyama.
It's okay.
They'll perform tomorrow,
come hell or high water.
Their bodies have reached
their limits long ago,
but they'll get in sync with
the rhythmic gymnastics teammates
and do the performance.
Everything is very difficult.
I have to throw the ball accurately
to where the other person is,
think about how I'm going to turn,
and throw the ball
precisely to where it lands.
When I think about it,
it's difficult to do.
Every part of my body hurts.
I stand on my toes on the mat
all the time, right?
So my calves are stiff,
and my back hurts.
Handling the ribbon
makes my arm hurt,
looking up makes my neck hurt.
My whole body is injured.
Even so, when the music plays,
they dance again and again.
I'll be happy
if you feel something
when you watch our performance.
Let's do it, then.
Ganbareruya's rhythmic gymnastics
performance
with Tokyo Women's College
of Physical Education's
Rhythmic Gymnastics Club.
Their costumes are lovely.
Let's do it, then.
Ganbareruya's rhythmic gymnastics
performance
with Tokyo Women's College
of Physical Education's
Rhythmic Gymnastics Club.
Their costumes are lovely.
The makeup.
Machan's makeup is heavy.
The performance starts
with using hoops.
So cool!
They perform the techniques while
keeping up with the quick tempo.
Oh, nice.
First, it's the highlight of Mahiru.
She catches the hoop after
a cartwheel over a performer.
She did it successfully.
She's calm.
Wow, impressive!
Then everyone dances in sync.
Mahiru throws a hoop,
and catches it facetoface.
Then it's Yoshiko's daring move,
a front handspring.
Amazing!
Now, they'll use the ball
in the performance.
It rolls away if they make the
smallest mistake while handling it,
the apparatus is difficult.
A backward roll
after catching the ball.
The fairy vibes
have suddenly vanished.
Mahiru does a cartwheel
over Yoshiko's spread legs.
From now on, their power
of expression explodes.
Well done.
Impressive.
Power of expression...
Then they exchange the ball.
They did it successfully.
And then...
bounce it on the back.
They finally use the last item
in the performance, a ribbon.
Beautiful.
A great exchange
by all the club members.
They're running out of stamina,
and they're dancing
by sheer fighting spirit.
You can do it.
Then an exchange of ribbons.
Good.
Finally, it's the climax
of the performance.
Yoshiko throws the ribbon
with her leg.
Mahiru throws three ribbons.
Okay!
Amazing!
Ganbareruya and
their friends from Tokyo Women's
College of Physical Education
have successfully finished
the performance.
Then when they reluctantly
say goodbye...
We enjoyed every single day
this week,
and we want to do more.
That's how we feel, right?
Yeah.
We've dreamt of doing
rhythmic gymnastics.
Although it was only for a week,
we actually did it
and it makes us very happy.
We must thank you all.
Thank you for this week.
And...
She's more like a temple guardian
than a fairy.
I'm sorry...
You guys work hard every day.
You could do more and more
every day,
it encouraged us to work harder,
and it also gave us power.
This week will be our treasure
for the rest of our lives,
and we will never forget it.
Thank you so much.
Students of Tokyo Women's College
of Physical Education,
thank you so much.
When the Captain said
the lovely words so emotionally,
I thought it'd make me cry,
but the look on Yoshiko's face
when she held back her tears
had too much impact on me.
You look like that
when you hold back your tears.
She looks like that
when she holds back tears.
I didn't want the younger girls
see me cry.
The girls all talked casually
to them halfway.
Exactly.
They played pranks on me
quite often.
They looked down on us.
Wazuma Tetsuro.
Magician Degawa,
the clumsiest man in Japan,
will try Wazuma, the traditional
Japanese magic in this project.
I see, here it comes.
Too late!
You must already know.
Know what?
Are you kidding me? You don't know?
Wazuma Tetsuro...
received the annual magic award
in 2020.
The performance of Wazuma
in the show
was recognised to have contributed
to the popularisation of magic,
so the Japan Professional
Magician's Association
gave Degawa a Fellowship Award.
There's a Japan Eccentric
Magician's Association.
Eccentric?
Yes.
It's...
It gave me a Melon Syrup Award.
This is the first Wazuma Tetsuro
after a year.
What show is it going to be?
Our advisor received an award.
That's right.
It's the Japan Eccentric Magician's
Association's Melon Syrup Award?
I think many things are wrong.
Not eccentric...
It's Professional Magician's
Association.
The Fellowship Award.
Yes, the Fellowship Award.
What does this mean?
To put it simply,
it's like the Academy Award.
It's that big?
But nobody knows what it is.
The director says it isn't.
Not the Academy Award.
What?
It's a comparison.
Comparison.
Forty minutes by train and on foot
from Shiodome,
the one who received
the Fellowship Award,
the third Wazuma Tetsuro
in Bunkyo City.
We've come to
Chinzanso!
The stage is a familiar
wedding ceremony venue,
a place in Tokyo where you can enjoy
a beautiful garden,
Hotel Chinzanso Tokyo.
What a beautiful place.
This is summer in Japan.
Yes, indeed.
Something has started.
Indeed!
The Sea of Clouds in Tokyo.
Artificial mist is created
several times a day in the garden.
Guests can enjoy a dayandnight
magical view throughout the year.
I want to go there.
It's romantic.
It's not only here,
up there too. Look.
That's right.
You can't see anymore.
I can't see.
People won't know
if you kiss someone here.
What's that cue?
And Maria, your costume this time
is overthetop.
Her socks are made with leather.
After I started wearing these,
Mr Daisuke and Mr Nakaoka
talk to me a lot.
Right?
What does Nakaoka say
every time he sees you?
Something like,
"Maria, you're pretty."
Wow, it's a terribly creepy episode.
Let's start the training at once.
His master this time is...
Hello.
Ms Moe Alicegawa.
She's one of the few
women Japanese magician.
This time, she prepared Wazuma magic
that even a clumsy man can learn.
This is an illusion!
First, it's a glass
and a handkerchief.
Into the glass...
we put an egg in.
Cover the glass
with the handkerchief.
Then, like this,
we tie an elastic rubber around.
This is its current state.
But if I cheer it on...
Slip, slip, slip...
The egg goes through the glass.
When?
I see.
I don't get it.
You know how it's done?
I'm interested to try though.
That's early.
I'll now put the egg inside.
It's in.
I'll cover it with a handkerchief.
When will she take it out?
Now?
Yeah?
I'll put an elastic rubber around.
She's good.
I'll now cast a spell on it.
Slip, slip, slip...
Then, even though it was covered,
the egg...
Wow, she did it.
I admit defeat.
Wait... I really don't get it.
Are you stupid?
She pisses me off.
We'll now reveal how it's done.
The trick is very simple.
When you cover the glass,
turn the glass over, that's all.
To prevent the egg from falling,
hold it with your little finger.
Now, it's Degawa's turn to try.
First, put the egg into the glass.
Use this handkerchief
to cover the glass.
Then, what happens?
I clearly saw how you turned it
upside down.
This is a bit difficult.
Once more.
That's not all.
Take the chopsticks...
No, not chopsticks.
Next, it's a wrapping cloth.
This wrapping cloth
is said to have been
used by Nezumi Kozo.
And this is a Kan'ei Tsuho coin.
It's worth about 50 yen if you
calculate its value nowadays.
Let's wrap the coin.
The anecdote goes, in the past,
Nezumi Kozo gave out the money
he stole to the common people.
We'll copy this ritual a little.
Clink, clink.
Let's open it.
It quickly changed
into an oval gold coin.
Impressive.
Let's reveal how it's done.
Actually, the oval gold coin
is in the wrapping cloth.
Hold it secretly with the right hand
and put it on the table
when you open the wrapping cloth.
Put the Kan'ei Tsuho coin
on the gold coin,
and roll them together towards you.
This switches the wrapping cloth's
upper side and lower side,
and when you pull the edges,
the oval coin below will show.
It is said that Nezumi Kozo
had used this wrapping cloth.
The Nezumi Kozo here...
He did something.
It's said that he had redistributed
the common people's money.
But...
It's there.
It came out.
Why is it here?
He gave this money
to common people... Oops.
What happened?
Wait a minute,
it isn't here.
What?
Oh, okay...
Now, the second teacher
makes his appearance.
Illusionist, Mr Magician Daiki.
He'll do a magic with chocolate,
which you can try as well.
It's called...
Infinity Chocolate.
Now, the second teacher
makes his appearance.
Illusionist, Mr Magician Daiki.
He'll do a magic with chocolate,
which you can try as well.
It's called...
Infinity Chocolate.
If the amount of chocolate
stays the same when you eat it,
doesn't it make you happy?
It does.
To make it easy to eat
the chocolate,
we'll chop it.
He chops at two more places.
This is its current state.
There's one missing.
Watch carefully.
We'll move this part here.
Then...
What?
Why?
Look. It's back
and there isn't any less.
Amazing.
This time, again,
Mr Degawa would like
some chocolate too.
Yes.
The doctor warns me not to eat
too much chocolate,
but I still eat it.
Okay.
He chops at the same places
as before.
Maria ate one square just now.
Yes.
This time, Mr Degawa ate one square.
That's impossible...
We'll rearrange it.
It is back
to its original form again.
Amazing.
What's this?
One square is probably
not complete.
That means it was an illusion
when we were watching?
Yes, an illusion.
It's bad if it's an illusion.
You think it was back to
the original piece of chocolate?
It was back.
You're a really good customer.
But how can that be an illusion?
It's bad if I see an illusion
at such a close distance.
As a person.
I'm telling you it's bad.
Tetsuro Degawa, 57 years old,
I'm not so senile that I'd see
an illusion at a distance so close.
The correct answer
is it's an illusion.
The amount of chocolate is less,
but if you cut it
and move the pieces like this,
it looks like it's restored
to its original state.
Look at the size
of the middle square!
What do you say?
Wow, amazing. It's smaller.
This time, he'll perform a magic
done with a secret trick
and the magic Mr Daiki teaches him.
For example...
Blow up a balloon,
and if you burst it...
a frying pan appears.
Why?
He puts a pan near his chest
beforehand,
and hides it skilfully
with his left arm.
When he takes out the bamboo skewer,
he holds the handle of the pan.
Then, at the same time
he bursts the balloon,
he pulls out the pan from his chest.
The difficult thing
is to blow up the balloon first.
My lung capacity
is close to nothing,
that's the first problem.
People say Wazuma Tetsuro's throat
is like a baby's.
Oh, it flew away.
This is the third time you perform
as Wazuma Tetsuro.
It's Fellowship.
A man who received this award
will go on stage
and stand in front of cameras,
so I can't afford to fail.
After all, what I'm carrying now
is different from before.
Mr Daiki, who came here today,
is running a ramen restaurant
half the time because of Covid19.
Business got worse
because of Covid19,
so he opened a ramen restaurant.
But after he opened it,
it became very popular.
In the worst case,
Mr Daiki will quit being a magician
and become a real ramen chef.
Now, please watch carefully.
Later, the Wazuma Tetsuro Show
begins.
You say what you're carrying
this time is different,
but what will the show be like?
Guys, if you insist,
I'll offer my award if I fail.
What?
You mean return it?
Yes, return. Yes.
You don't offer the award.
I'll return it.
Return it.
Let's return it at once.
Wait...
Well, then, Wazuma Tetsuro,
please get ready!
Thank you for your patience.
He is ready.
Here comes Wazuma Tetsuro.
Hurray!
Fellowship!
Wazuma!
It's been a long time
since I last performed.
I'm Wazuma Tetsuro who received
the Fellowship Award the other day.
Hurray!
Congratulations!
First, over here...
I'm going to use
this ordinary wrapping cloth.
First, I'll put it here.
There's a sound.
I heard a sound.
This is a Kan'ei Tsuho coin,
which is worth 50 yen nowadays.
Put this Kansui Kan'ei Tsuho coin
on top of this.
It is said that Nezumi Kozo
had used this wrapping cloth.
I'll wrap the coin
with this wrapping cloth.
It's said that Nezumi Kozo
would give out the oval gold coins
he stole to the common people.
I'll now wrap this around the coin.
I'm going to open it now.
Clink, clink.
Okay.
Unveil it...
Wow, look!
An oval gold coin
appeared from inside.
Amazing!
I'll check to see
if this is a real oval gold coin.
People get angry at you if you bite
something made with gold.
It's topical.
He added something topical.
He left the stage
after that topical joke.
He's here.
It's that one.
That?
Next, I'm going to use this balloon
to perform this magic.
First, I'll blow up this balloon.
Stretch it.
Is this okay?
No, he has a baby's throat.
It's a baby's throat.
He has a baby's throat.
You can do it.
Wazuma.
Mr Tetsuro, you can do it!
You can do it!
Wazuma.
It's getting bigger.
Wazuma! You can do it!
This is a balloon.
I'm going to use this
to open a hole in the balloon.
Three, two, one.
Go!
Here!
Wait...
A pan appeared.
That's not right...
Just now, after he burst
the balloon,
the pan came out.
Wazuma himself was startled
when he burst it.
"Whoa!"
The balloon.
Oh... Well... what should I do?
Who are you asking?
Do it once more.
He's leaving the stage.
Return the award. Return it.
Return it.
Here he comes.
The balloon...
Next, I'm going to use
this balloon oh.
Thank you for your patience.
Welcome.
"Welcome" isn't right.
The arrangement is a mess.
He pretends nothing happened.
I'll blow up this balloon.
He pretends it didn't happen.
Blow properly.
It's the crucial part.
You can do it...
I'm going to use this
to burst the balloon.
Three, two, one.
What?
It doesn't burst.
Three, two, one.
Hey!
This is a dream.
It is a dream.
Where are you going?
We'll talk later.
Please give up the award.
Return it.
The Fellowship Award...
We'll start all over again
and Tani will perform Wazuma.
I'm going to use this bag here
and perform Wazuma.
Could you confirm that there is
nothing unusual with this bag?
Indeed, this is an ordinary bag.
There is nothing
even if you turn it over.
There isn't, is there?
Mr Tetsuro, since this morning,
I've been worrying about the place
above your shoulder a lot.
I don't feel anything wrong.
Do you mind?
What is it?
An egg!
There's an egg?
There was an egg.
I'll use the egg that came
from Mr Degawa's shoulder
to perform a Wazuma trick.
First, I'll put the egg
on this piece of cloth and hold it.
When I blow on it,
this egg will vanish.
No way.
It won't.
It's gone.
Do you know where the egg went?
Don't tell me...
Please let me check
your shoulder again.
It's the egg.
It came out.
The egg is there.
Why?
There was an egg again.
I'll hold this egg in the bag again.
And then...
You can't deceive me
again and again.
The egg is in your right hand now.
Mr Tetsuro,
it isn't in my right hand.
What...?
Of course, inside the bag...
It isn't here either.
What? Where did it go?
It isn't here.
It's a piece of cloth.
Mr Tetsuro,
please give me your hand.
Here.
Look.
Smack...
It isn't here, is it?
We'll check the inside
and the outside of this bag,
just in case.
While we're checking it,
please confirm the egg isn't here.
There is nothing inside.
There isn't anything.
Mr Degawa, do you know
where the egg has gone?
Look.
The egg...
There is nothing.
You can't see it?
We can't...
I'm going to throw this egg
into this bag now.
I'll do it now.
Go.
What? There was
a tapping sound just now.
What?
Mr Degawa, please look inside.
There's no way
it's so conveniently...
An egg!
Amazing.
There was an egg.
I wanted to say "An egg!"
Good.
It won't be as interesting
if you think the egg is fake,
so could you crack the egg
into this glass?
It's a raw egg.
A raw egg!
Wazumaria is amazing.
Lastly, Wazuma Tetsuro will use
playing cards to perform
a prophecy magic.
I'd like to ask someone
to help me perform this magic.
Okay, Imoto.
Okay.
Please come here.
Okay, it involves the audience?
First, I'd like to ask Imoto
several questions.
You got married to the director
of this show, Mr Ishizaki,
what do you usually call him?
I don't know.
Well, his name is Shiro Ishizaki,
so it's Shikun.
Shikun.
Shikun?
It's Shikun?
It's the first time I hear this.
What do you love most about Shikun?
He is kind and reliable.
Well then,
how many children do you want?
Two No, three, if possible.
I see.
Based on the questions I asked,
I'd like to think about the unknown.
"It should be "Write a prophecy""
Something unknown?
About the future?
Does he mean prediction?
I wrote something here,
please memorise it well.
I'll perform the magic now.
First, Imoto, please shuffle
the playing cards here.
Divide them into two.
Okay, I've divided them.
Choose one pile you like,
either the left or the right.
I'll choose the left one.
The left one. Okay.
Please count how many cards
there are in the left pile.
He suddenly got angry.
He's angry.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
11, 12, 13, 14, 15,
16, 17, 18, 19, 20.
21, 22, 23, 24. There are 24 cards.
There are 24 cards.
Choose a card you like among them.
Any card?
Yes.
Can I look?
Yes, you can show everyone.
Okay.
Okay, what is the card?
It's three of spades.
It's three of spades, right?
As you've seen,
Imoto shuffled the cards.
Yes.
Imoto also divided it
into two piles.
Imoto also chose the first
and chose one card among them.
Imoto took the initiative
in everything when she did it.
Go back.
What?
What? It's scary.
Three of spades?
There are 24 cards here,
and the card she chose
was three of spades.
Yes.
Now, tonight, Azuma
Wazuma Tetsuro...
will outdo Nostradamus.
What?
I'll turn this board over.
What's written there?
24 and three of spades.
It was impressive though.
Impressive.
It's showtime!
He made it!
How did you know?
Oh? The reaction is rather different
from what I expected.
At first, I thought he should
return the award,
but now, I think Wazuma Tetsuro
deserves the Fellowship Award.
Thank you.
Brilliant.
I don't need to return
the award, right?
But halfway...
The pan.
You failed quite miserably.
Sorry that I told you
to return the award.
Three, two, one.
Go!
Okay!
Wait...
That's not right!
Oh... Well... what should I do?
Who are you asking?
Return the award.
You told me to return the award?
Sorry.
I panicked so much that
I didn't even hear you say that.
I had no idea.
It can't be helped.