The Quest.
The first one today is...
What is it?
Wazuma Tetsuro, part two.
- One day, we summoned Degawa.
- Degawa?
What is it this time?
It's Wazuma Tetsuro, part two.
Oh, there it is.
Wazuma Tetsuro.
Wazuma, yeah!
It's a project where Japan's most
awkward middle-aged man,
Magician Degawa, takes an attempt
at Wazuma, an old Japanese magic.
- That was amazing.
- However,
with a magic where he was to hang
the Tokkuri with a string...
Oh, no!
It's a dream!
I wasn't able to give it my all
with Wazuma,
so I actually appreciate the fact
I get another chance.
And what I really want to say
to everyone at the studio is,
do not talk to me
during my performance.
Do not talk to me.
Don't just casually talk to me.
Will he be able to deliver
Wazuma magic successfully?
"The Quest"
Yeah!
The Quest has started. Tonight,
it's Wazuma Tetsuro, part two,
and the 13th Miyagawa expedition.
Thanks!
It's a new four-kanji word,
Wazuma Tetsuro.
I was hoping for another chance,
- so it worked out well.
- It worked out well?
So you've improved a lot this time?
Of course.
Maria, this is your second attempt.
Yes, this is my second time
with Wazuma,
and I went to Milan once
for the Magician segment.
This was my third time,
and I'm finally getting the hang
of exposing how the tricks are done.
She demanded "Magician Maria."
And she flirted with the Master,
and he fell for it and became
her fan.
- He was like "Sure, sure."
- There's the Master.
You see how he has that grin?
- Master...
- So it's true?
Yes, it's true.
Master, get it together.
Nothing has started yet,
but he's already upset.
Let's get going.
The Quest.
Yeah!
Three plus two is five.
I give up.
What?
There.
"A second attempt
at traditional Japanese magic"
In Shiretoko!
I can't do this any longer.
This is no good.
"A."
Idiot!
Thirty minutes on Oedo Line
and on foot from Shiodome,
will he be successful this time?
Wazuma Tetsuro, part two.
In Motoakasaka.
- We are here at Meiji Kinenkan.
- Meiji Kinenkan.
They will practise at Meiji
Kinenkan in Motoakasaka,
a historic wedding hall
that's been designated as
Tangible Cultural Property by Tokyo.
Maria, you're the sexy one
in Degawa Girls.
So you wear this sexy outfit
for Wazuma.
Yes, but I'm actually worried
since it's so windy right now.
No, you want it to be
more windy, right?
I'm not.
- It's starting to get windy.
- Are you sure?
They will be taught by...
Ryusei Kamiguchi. He is one of
the few successors of Wazuma,
and he is also
a professional magician as well.
In the Edo period,
gambling was popular too.
Take this dice for example...
Could you take a look?
Yes.
It's ordinary dice.
- It's real.
- It is real.
What is this?
- It's two.
- It is two.
- Yes.
On the opposite side of two
is three.
Three plus two is...
- Five.
- Yes, it's five.
It's starting.
Amazing.
- It's two.
- How is that possible?
It's three.
It's two.
What's three plus two?
- It's five.
Master,
you are incredible.
Thank you very much.
Let's start the training.
They will start with Zeni Wazuma.
There are four old coins.
Let's use these.
In each hand,
I'll hold a coin.
Maria, could you take these
two coins
and place them on each hand?
- I'll put it on here.
- Put it on.
I have a coin in each of my hands,
and a coin on each of my hands.
I'll catch them
in the air.
- I'm sorry.
- One more time.
One more time.
This cuteness
is part of Master's charm.
I have a coin in each of my hands,
and I have a coin on both hands.
I'll catch it in air.
Okay.
Two coins each are now...
- one coin
- What?
and in this hand, I have one, two,
- three coins.
- How come?
How is that done?
One more...
I'll hold a coin in each hand.
Maria, could you take...
He's holding them for sure, right?
He must have them.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
- If he messes up again...
- Then I'll catch these
in the air.
- See?
- I'm sorry. One more time.
- Is this part of the trick?
- That's incredible.
I got it!
Let me do it again.
- I got it already!
- Then do it.
Now, Tani will give it a try.
You see how I have one each?
- That's amazing.
- I'll hold them.
Degawa, could you place a coin each
on my nails?
Yes, I'll place it here.
- One each...
- Now, I'll flip these.
- Okay.
- Ready?
It's the same.
I'm sorry. Could you do it again?
It's exactly the same.
Now, I'll place one here,
and another one here.
I'll hold them again.
Okay.
I'll add some power to it.
Ha!
This side has...?
One.
Okay.
- This side has?
- Three.
Oh, I give up.
Now, let's see how it's done.
Just as you guessed,
- I'm making a mistake on purpose.
- Right.
- I got that part.
- Yes.
He's making it look like he dropped
the coin on his nail,
but he's actually dropping two coins
in one of his hands.
That's it.
So if it's placed on his nails again
and he holds them...
it looks as though a coin
had transferred to another hand.
- I see.
- Three.
Now, Degawa will try.
This is Kan'ei Tsuho,
a coin from the Edo period.
- I'll hold one in each hand.
- I'll hold them.
Maria, could you place a coin
on each hand?
Here, I put them on.
- Now, it's been placed on my hands.
- Yes.
Now the fun begins.
Ready...
You opened your hand.
I dropped them.
One more time.
Ready...
I think you enjoyed enough
of this Wazuma trick,
so he won't perform it
at the studio.
- I failed.
- I would love to see it.
Next is a Wazuma trick using
a paper and a candle.
I have a blank piece of paper here.
I'll fold it in half like so.
I'll fold it in half again.
Then I'll wring the centre like so.
Then I'll light the centre part
with a candle.
It is burned now.
I don't like this...
- He doesn't like it.
- Of course, the fire is hot.
Now this hot fire, and the remains
of this paper will be moistened.
There!
Now, let's expose how it's done.
The burned paper is hidden
- Where is it?
- in his mouth.
No way.
A tiny piece of paper is hidden
in his left hand beforehand,
it's carefully placed in position
during the folding process.
Then this part is burned,
and it's hidden in the mouth
without being noticed.
Now, Degawa will try.
Over here is an ordinary Japanese
paper.
Now, I'll fold this Japanese paper
in half.
Then I'll turn it several times.
Now, I'll turn and turn...
Like a rocket,
- the tip is done like so.
- A tip?
Is your vocabulary limited?
Now, I'll light this on fire.
It's burned now.
Now, I'll blow it out.
There.
It's a bit hot.
It's now out.
Now...
Now I'll moisten this.
He remembers it now.
He ate it?
He ate it.
Next is clairvoyance,
using a wooden box.
This box is made of a thick wood.
It's quite sturdy.
Could one of you place an item
in this wooden box
without it being seen by me,
close the lid, and hold on to it?
I'll be looking away from you.
Two of them picked out
a dipping sauce
for Tempura in bento.
- That's a hard one.
- That's difficult.
- I'll give it to you.
- Thank you.
There's nothing suspicious
about this box, right?
- No.
- Please go back to your seat.
My clairvoyance.
I'll use my clairvoyance
to guess what this is.
If he guesses this right,
I think he's a real genius.
Now...
Then I'll insert my powers...
What?
Maybe this was too hard?
- What?
- Is this too hard?
I feel as though...
it's some sort of food.
This can't be.
- He's right.
- If he guesses this,
then I'll cast myself at his feet
for real.
Its colour is blackish.
- Amazing.
- It's blackish,
but it also has a reddish colour
to it. What could it be?
- No way.
- It's black and red.
- You're scaring me.
- Why?
Heaven and Earth!
Dipping sauce for Tempura?
I'm scared.
Incredible!
- Now, time to expose how it's done.
- How is that possible?
The key to this Wazuma is that this
wooden box is a cube.
When the box is hidden in the back,
the lid is taken off.
And tactfully, the box is brought
to the front of the body.
Then just check the content
while taking it to the table.
Now, Degawa
will make an attempt at it.
Now Maria, place whatever you like
into this box.
Yes.
She picked scissors.
I put it in.
- Please hand that box over to me.
- He's pushing it.
Could you hold it?
You know,
it's hard for me to hold it.
Okay, go ahead.
He's barely holding it.
- Now, I have the box.
- Yes.
Now, I'll use my clairvoyance
to see what's in this box.
Is something wrong?
He's growling.
When are you going to take a look?
When is he going to take a look?
"Tetsuro doesn't know when to look"
When are you going to take a look?
- When is he going to look?
- He's growling.
- Now...
If I put it there,
it would look suspicious,
so I'll place it on the black cloth
over here.
- He hasn't taken a look yet.
- He hasn't?
When is he going to look?
- Not yet.
- When are you going to look?
- He looked at it!
- He looked.
"Tetsuro couldn't see too well"
Please stop.
He couldn't see?
He's looking.
In addition, he'll learn
Western magic this time.
An Illusionist, Magician Daiki
will be instructing them.
He was the one who helped out
with Magician Degawa
when we returned to Japan,
with all the behind-the-scenes
stuff.
Magician Daiki will teach us
a trick that could be done
at school tomorrow.
- That's great.
- Here's a rubber.
I'll use this rubber here
to do an unusual magic trick.
First,
I'll take this cover,
and crumple it.
I'll make it disappear.
- Already at this point...
- What?
In addition...
now I'm going to say a magic word.
One, two, three.
- It's back to its original form.
- What?
- What? I didn't get it.
- I didn't get it.
Now, let's see how it's done.
This rubber has two covers.
And when it's rotated,
half of it is uncovered.
- That's what it is.
- This is the trick.
The removed cover is dropped
into the desk pocket.
The rubber is rotated
while in the hand,
to make it look like it's back
to its original form.
And lastly, you show the front
and back of this rubber.
But if you do it like so...
then it would look like
- the front and the back were seen.
- I see.
I don't know if Tetsuro can do this.
Now, it's Degawa's turn.
- This is difficult.
- Now, over here is a regular
ordinary rubber.
Now, I'll take it out like so.
There's no tricks here.
Now, I'll use this rubber
to have some fun.
First...
- we'll take this lid...
- Lid?
There!
- Yes.
- It disappeared.
That's not it, though.
I'll say a magic word
- to this rubber here too.
- Magic word?
Three, two, one.
There!
It's back to its original state.
I saw the white part.
I think the rotation part
is not necessary.
And a very special magic.
Every one of them.
He'll perform an illusion.
This time, I'll perform
Wazuma Tetsuro
and Magician Degawa.
It's very difficult
- to perform both of them
- That's incredible.
at the same showing.
- That's amazing.
- Oh, is it difficult?
Of course it is.
"Oh, is it difficult?"
That is so annoying.
Specifically speaking,
what's difficult?
it's Japanese cuisine
and Italian cuisine.
When you go to
a wonderful restaurant,
it means that they serve both
Japanese cuisine
and Italian cuisine.
Is there such a restaurant?
Oh, I'm starved.
First, I'll have ginger-fried pork.
Oh, it's delicious.
Next is Carbonara?
What?
Well, maybe some places have
ginger-fried pork and carbonara.
It's a dish that's much more
complicated.
Now, let me show you.
- Next, Wazuma Tetsuro Show
- Incredible.
- is starting.
- Amazing.
- It's so funny.
- What did you think after that?
I asked, "Is there a restaurant
that serves everything?"
but when I think about it,
casual restaurants have them.
That's right.
Please share your enthusiasm here.
I put so much into this
that I'm willing to retire,
if I fail this today.
I'll put retirement on the line.
- Retire from what?
- Is that
retirement from Magician Degawa too?
Or it is just Wazuma Tetsuro?
Or is it everything?
- Wazuma Tetsuro.
- Wazuma Tetsuro?
We got it.
Now, Wazuma Tetsuro's
retirement is on the line.
It's a crucial performance.
- Please get ready.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you for waiting.
They are ready.
Here is Wazuma Tetsuro!
Yeah!
Wazuma Tetsuro.
Maria.
It's been awhile.
- It's been awhile.
- I'm Wazuma Tetsuro.
Thank you for coming.
First, I would like to use this
disposable chopstick for some fun.
We haven't seen this one.
There, there, there!
What? Where's the chopstick?
Is it the angle?
- Is it under his arm?
- There.
Is it the angle?
It was all obvious to me.
I had fun with a disposable
chopstick.
- I couldn't see anything at all.
- Stop lying.
Up next is...
magic using this paper.
Okay.
First,
I'll light the candle.
Okay.
He sucks at blowing out the fire.
- Now...
- Who would've thought?
I'll take this paper and...
fold it in half.
- Okay.
- And I take this folded paper
and twist it.
- Twist it?
- Then...
I twist it and make a tip.
- Do this
- There's a tip.
and this.
Now, I'll light this.
It'll burn.
Exactly, it'll burn.
Okay.
I'll blow this fire out.
It's hot.
Now, I'll moisten this part
a little.
He's eating it.
- Now...
- He ate it.
- He said something.
- Take a look at this paper.
He's struggling to talk.
His saliva is being taken.
It's torn.
Your saliva!
It's weakened by your saliva.
It's torn.
It's hard to tell.
Isn't it too wrinkled?
- There!
- Oh, he scared me.
The paper is back
to its original form.
Amazing!
- My stomach hurts from laughing.
- That was funny.
It's done.
He blew it out gently.
He blew the candle out gently.
- Next magic uses this rubber.
- There it is.
It's the first magic.
There's nothing tricky here.
First, I'll do this.
There.
This is an ordinary rubber.
There's nothing strange about it.
First, I'll make
this cover disappear.
It disappeared.
That's not all.
This rubber is then...
When I say the magic word...
Three, two, one.
There!
Amazing!
- His right shoulder!
- That was good.
- Amazing.
That was great.
Thank you very much.
It's 100% so far.
It's amazing.
Next, here's an ordinary box.
There's nothing tricky about it.
Now, inside this box...
- Daisuke.
- Yes.
Pick whatever you want,
and place something in this box
while I have my back towards
this box.
I can't see anything.
I won't know what you put in there.
- I can put it in?
- Of course.
This was given to me earlier.
"A scorpion toy"
I think this is going to be hard.
Please put it in so I can't see it,
and place a lid on it.
Okay.
Now...
Could you bring your hands
a little closer? Thank you.
- Do you have it?
- Now...
I don't know what's inside this box.
Please go back to your seat.
Excuse me. Thank you.
He's not looking.
I have no idea
what's inside this box.
I'll use my clairvoyance to guess
what is inside this box now.
No way.
- Hey!
- It's impossible.
Now, what is inside this box?
I'll use my clairvoyance...
to guess what's in here.
- Good luck.
- You can't see it.
- It's impossible.
- Usually,
you won't know what's inside
this box.
- However, with clairvoyance...
- Isn't it sort of long?
I'll guess what's inside the box.
His shoulder blades...
Now...
- He has a horrifying look.
- Now...
- Isn't it too long?
- Now, there's something
- inside this box.
- Yes.
Okay.
I'll use my clairvoyance
and guess what's in here
from behind.
From behind?
I'll put it behind me
and show you what's inside.
Okay.
Now
what is in this box?
- It's very clairvoyant.
- There's so much eye contact.
I need to focus to succeed.
- His eyes.
- What's in here?
I'm going to put this box down now.
What?
I'll put this box down now. What?
It's a bit...
I'll put it down again.
I'll put this box down now.
Please put it down already.
Hey! I told you
I'm going to put it down now.
- I'm going to put it down now.
- Please don't get upset.
Please don't get upset.
He looks like he doesn't like it.
What?
What is it?
- Hey! I'm clairvoyant.
- He can see it.
He's clairvoyant.
Hey! Now, I'm going
to put it down here.
- I'll put the box down.
- Okay.
I'm telling you
to put it down already!
Hey!
- He sucks at it.
- Hey!
Put it down already.
- He's checking it right now.
- Hey!
- I put it down now.
- He saw it?
- Yes.
- That's good.
Now, I'll focus my mind.
Li Shang heigh-ho water spinach!
- What does he mean?
- Hey!
There.
- This is...
- It's a water spinach.
This is very difficult.
This is very dangerous.
- Oh.
- This is...
Okay!
I see it!
It's a scorpion!
Amazing.
- That was great.
- He was clairvoyant.
It's clairvoyance.
Now, please have
a pleasant chat for a while.
Next is Magician Degawa's
super illusion.
"Second part,
Magician Degawa's illusion"
It's the second part.
Now,
the next one will be
my last performance.
- Oh?
- Okay.
Over here is a tun--
a chimney like object.
It doesn't look like a chimney.
I'll open this and show it to you.
- There.
- I have no idea.
There.
When I open it up,
it's hollow inside.
- Okay.
- It's like a rocket.
Now, Princess Maria will
- go inside here.
- She's Princess Maria?
Is she going to be okay?
Will Princess Maria be okay?
- Now, I'll close this.
- Princess!
Now, Princess Maria is in here.
Now, I'll close each one...
of these.
Now, that's not all.
Ready, go!
A chimney with Princess Maria
is now sideways.
- That's dangerous, right?
- Yes.
That's not safe.
- Now...
- Oh no, don't turn it!
There's more.
Will she be okay?
Let's have some fun here.
Now,
bring me the thing.
No, what is it?
Let's take this dangerous
sword-like thing,
and insert it here.
Oh no!
- No!
- Stop it!
- There!
- Princess Maria!
Princess Maria!
- There!
- You're in danger!
Now, here's the final one.
- There!
- Hey!
Now, Princess Maria's body
has been cut into several pieces.
There's more, though.
Ready?
There!
No!
Now, Princess Maria's body
has been divided into seven parts.
There.
Head, neck, chest,
chest, hips, legs, legs.
Chest was a bit off, right?
- He said chest, chest.
- Now,
I'll put it back.
Ready, go!
Now, we'll take this chimney
again and...
put it back.
Now, I'll take it out one by one.
There.
- Now...
- Is it possible?
Maria's body
that's been shattered
I will put back into one piece
with my magic words.
Kushin, Shori, Todaiji!
Todaiji?
- The one in Nara?
- That's right.
Now, let's open it.
There.
I'll open it.
Amazing!
There!
Where were you?
Now...
It's showtime!
Wonderful.
It's wonderful.
Miyagawa, what did you think?
This last one was incredible.
But you know how he got upset
at us when we spoke to him?
When did I get upset?
When you were trying to place
the box behind you.
That was some clairvoyance.
I felt the malice of the staff.
You're right.
I couldn't tell whether it was
a scorpion or a crayfish.
That's what was stopping you?
I couldn't tell.
Asako, what did you think?
His magic words were so original.
- The first one was "Water spinach."
- It was water spinach.
- The second one was Todaiji.
- Todaiji.
"Todaiji"
Good job! That was Wazuma Tetsuro.
Princess Maria, thank you too.
Thank you.
Next up is this.
The 13th Miyagawa Expedition!
- Yes!
- Thank you very much.
Where will they go this time?
Shiretoko Peninsula in Hokkaido.
I see.
Provenance of life, that's been
continuing from the ancient times.
Shiretoko is registered
as World Natural Heritage Site.
I really want to go.
What do we do in Shiretoko?
The land, the sea,
and the river.
We'll go to all of them.
The land, the sea, and the river?
That's unheard of.
A terrifying hot spring
where your body is numbed.
I don't want to go to such a thing.
A divine fish
for the Ainu,
Chip Kamuy.
Chip Kamuy?
A large school of Pink Salmon
that fills up the river.
I see.
It's time for them
to go up the river.
- I wanted to see that once.
- Me too.
When they go up the river,
it's just before
the bears hibernate,
and they are at the river too.
They will be hunting away.
They will smack it
and eat just its belly.
Then they throw away the remains
and take another smack at it.
When they find us, it'll rush
over and smack us. It'll be the end.
- They'll smack us dead.
- For sure.
I'm off to Shiretoko!
I'll do my best.
What adventure awaits him?
A great adventure is about to start.
Miyagawa Expedition.
World Natural Heritage Site,
Shiretoko.
The 13th Miyagawa Expedition!
It's obviously incredible
in Shiretoko!
The expedition members
are Iwashita, Enjoji,
- and Kitami.
- Kitami?
It's been a while.
Member Kitami,
also known as Chap.
- Hello.
- Hi.
He is named after Chaplin
since his reactions are like him.
"October, 2017
The third Miyagawa Expedition"
You go there, then you go...
Oh, you managed to get there.
Watch out!
Are you okay?
How long has it been?
It's been about three years.
- It sure has been three years.
- He's gained weight.
- The size of your belly is no joke.
- Oh boy.
Enjoji.
Your dark spots are gone.
- What? He got rid of his spots?
- Yes.
I used laser to get rid
of my dark spots before.
Now there are no signs of it left.
I have clear skin.
So is it done now?
Currently, I have a friend
who has a hair removal salon,
and I was asked to be a model
for the facial hair removal.
Sample model
for removing facial hair?
But...
now that you mentioned it,
I can sort of see that your facial
hair is a little lighter.
However...
Oh? Wait one second.
You may be losing your facial hair,
but you have eggs
around your mouth.
I'm serious.
If you're concerned about your dark
spots, then as a mature person,
you shouldn't have any egg remains
around your mouth!
You idiot.
- An egg?
- A boiled egg.
Their adventure is three days long.
Their goal is to deliver
the phenomenon
that occurs at Shiretoko's land,
sea, and river.
Today, we'll head over to...
land!
The expedition will head
to Mount Io,
which is 1562 metres in elevation.
Their goal is to see...
Shocking!
A body numbing hot spring.
From Shiretoko Goko Lakes
to the foot of Mount Io is 11 km.
It's a two-hour walk.
What they have to pay attention
to the most during on the way is...
Leader!
You scared me. What is it?
That was scary.
Please take a look at this.
What?
Look at this mark here.
Isn't this from a bear?
You see how it's climbing up
the tree? See?
It's brown bear.
Here at Shiretoko,
brown bears are very common.
The only way to stay safe is to
avoid any chances of encounter.
I think this bear is about the size
of you, Chap.
- Like so?
- Exactly.
So it's pretty agile.
Right.
Wait, did you think to do it
just now?
That's not necessary.
You don't have to try so hard.
But seriously, do your best.
I really want you to be a director.
Leader.
- What is it?
- I'm a director already.
What? Is that true? My bad.
I thought you were still an AD.
I've been a director
for about a year now.
- You're a director?
- For a year?
They came to the foot of Mount Io.
Make sure to be careful.
We have no idea what it's like.
Yes.
- It does feel warm.
- The colours are...
They are going up Kamuiwakka River.
This is it.
This is it. It's something else.
- This is the rumoured hot spring.
- What? This is a hot spring?
Leader, I guess it's not good
to stay in it for too long.
What?
How is it possible
for a hot spring?
What is it effective for?
It's good for your heels.
What? For heels?
Why is it just that part?
Would you want to go if you knew
it was good for your heels?
You know?
Do you ever go
"Oh, my heels are tired"?
They are ready.
The temperature of the water
is about 35 or 36 degrees Celsius.
Let's go!
Yes.
He decided to go in the hot water.
Why am I the only one going in?
That's not right.
What? What is this?
Leader Miyagawa is experiencing
some discomfort.
What is this?
- What?
- What is this?
It's not tingling,
but it feels nasty.
What is it?
They all work up the courage
and go in the hot spring.
- It itches for some reason.
- It does itch, right?
- What does that mean?
- It itches?
- My legs itch.
- What is this hot spring?
This hot spring doesn't feel good.
It makes me feel restless.
This hot spring...
is made of strongly acidic
hot water.
This part itches. What is this?
- There's a unit called pH.
- Right, pH.
The lower the number is,
the more acidic the substance is.
So...
I can't take this anymore!
It's too long!
It stings like jelly fish.
Acidity here...
is more than lemon juice,
but less than stomach acid.
That's not good!
A little bit of lemon juice
in your eyes is very painful.
Here at Kamuiwakka hot spring falls,
volcanic gases dissolve into water,
making it highly acidic.
Rubbing a dirty 10 yen coin
in this hot spring will...
- make it super shiny.
- That was amazing.
This 10 yen was...
instantly cleaned. We shouldn't
be going into such water.
Think about it. Would you go in
when you squirt lemon juice in here?
Of course it would sting and itch.
Is that okay?
And all that happens,
but why is it just for heels?
I don't get that part.
Mount Io has hot springs
that are highly acidic.
Since they are there, they decide
to head over to its crater.
It's very steep here.
It would be great
if I had a stick or something.
It would make it easier to walk.
- Do you have any stick-like thing?
- Could it be...?
Yes, we have some.
Thanks.
That's right. This is it.
You go like so on this.
- Then you go, one, two, one, two.
- He's incredible.
Idiot!
I'm surprised I was able to do this.
I turned around while I was
on this and went "Idiot!"
I think that was genius.
This isn't it.
Give me a stick.
That's right. This is it.
With this, you go...
A.
I.
U. E.
- He can do it?
- O.
A.
Ho. Idiot!
You Idiot!
This is a hand flag.
This isn't it. A stick so that it
would help me climb this mountain.
Give me a stick.
That's right. This is it.
That is so detailed.
Seriously...
I hope...
He's doing well.
I hope-- You Idiot!
Hey...
This was for granny.
You know, granny.
This is no time for this.
A stick for climbing.
A stick.
That's right. Exactly!
Exactly!
- Exactly!
- He got it.
This is it!
Mount Io.
Former sulphur mining area.
Oh, is this it?
Oh, I smell sulphur here.
This is one of the leading sulphur
erupting mountains of the world.
That place was something else.
At the last eruption in 1936,
110,000 tonnes of sulphur
went down the mountains.
- They climb up rugged rocks.
- That's rugged.
They finally arrive at the crater.
Wow, it's yellow.
Seriously?
What is this?
Wow, this is amazing.
This is a rare footage.
Please take a look at this.
This is very rare in the world
where you can get this close
- to a crater.
- I see.
Leader Miyagawa is impressed
with this grand view.
However, there was another man
who was immensely touched.
Leader.
You know how we
finally arrived here,
with such magnificent view?
As a Director,
would it be okay for me to add
a narration to this scene?
- What? Come again?
- A narration?
I was shocked because
it was so sudden.
I edited this scene in my head.
Verification. A narration by Kitami,
who once came on as a director,
but with so many shortcomings,
he was forced to start all over
again from the bottom.
Let's take a look.
Okay, then let's hear
your narration.
Then what should we do?
- If you would just look at it.
- Is that okay?
My view is that you would come up
strongly from here,
and you immediately find it
and the narration will go.
Okay. Could we do it then?
- Let's go.
- How will it be?
There.
Wow! Amazing!
- Amazing.
- Incredible.
What did Miyagawa Expedition see?
Pon! Oh, I'm sorry.
"Pon" won't do.
What do you mean,
"Pon, oh, I'm sorry"?
That was a narration before
you go "Wow."
Right.
That was off.
It was supposed to go,
"What did they see?
Wow, amazing!"
But it was the opposite.
If you want to clear your name,
we can do it again.
That was a failure just now.
You still have three days.
Exactly. Let's say it's good
for now.
How could you say it's good?
They completed their journey
on the land,
and finished their first day.
- He didn't do it.
- The second day.
Miyagawa Expedition
charges ahead on a foggy sea.
- It's the sea now.
- It's the sea.
They are aiming to catch the fish
the Ainu regard as divine.
It's Chip Kamuy.
It's a carnivorous fish that could
get as big as 150 cm.
However...
they didn't get any hits at all.
They went at it for five hours,
but they weren't able to catch
Chip Kamuy.
However, there was an offer to eat
Chip Kamuy caught in a net,
so they headed over
to a nearby restaurant.
- What? Is this it?
- This is it.
What? Let me see this.
This is Chip Kamuy.
What's with this face?
It's huge.
Presently, it's called
the Bering wolffish.
As you can see, it has sharp teeth
and it manages to crush
hard shells of crabs
and shrimps as well.
How does it taste?
They will have it simmered
in soy broth.
That looks delicious.
It's delicious.
It's super delicious.
Its skin is so soft,
it's like collagen.
I mean we wanted to catch it.
But at least
we were able to see it and eat it.
I think that was great.
Right?
Now, could you do your narration?
- At the end of our second day,
- So it's happening here?
please finish it off
with your narration.
No results were produced today.
Will Miyagawa Expedition
be able to fully enjoy
the nature of Shiretoko tomorrow?
We aren't here for fun.
Are we here to enjoy Shiretoko?
This is not a company trip
of middle aged men.
The third day.
"Oronko Rock, The third day"
Everyone! It's our last day here.
As a leader, I consider today
to be the most important day.
We will find the Pink Salmon that go
upstream
from this sea, up the river.
The last adventure involves a large
school of Pink Salmon in the river.
They head to Kanayama River
on the west side of the peninsula.
This is it.
When they walk along the river...
Leader.
A staff walking
with a professional guide
- found something.
- What did they find?
That's bear excrement for sure.
That's something else.
In addition...
Look.
Maybe we can't air this part.
See?
They ate Pink Salmon
right here.
The remains of a Pink Salmon
that's still wet.
When they realise that they're
unfit to be called an "expedition,"
they all look like this.
They go up the river while
watching out for bears.
Hey, look!
Over there!
By the rock! Go for it!
There it is. It's huge.
The number of Pink Salmon
are increasing.
That's great.
Shall we go upstream some more?
Yes.
They arrive at a place they suspect
to be a spawning spot.
Everyone, please take a look
at this.
This area.
There's a lot here.
Look.
Leader goes underwater
to get the video.
Wait. This part is almost too scary.
Wait.
Wait!
It's super scary.
There are so many here.
There's a lot here.
Right, inside the river...
a life drama was going on.
- Amazing.
- It's like watching a water tank.
Even when their body is damaged
by rough waters and predation,
they go up the river
to find a new life.
That's amazing.
However, during their journey,
some will lose their life
being attacked by predators.
Japan has
this magnificent nature too.
It's just as great
as other parts of the world.
Leader.
What is it?
Next time,
could I come as the director
for Miyagawa Expedition?
No way!
That's it for Miyagawa Expedition.
That was great.
I've learned that even when
a director is promoted,
it's possible for them
to turn back again.
Was this edited by Director Kitami?
No, he didn't.
He went as a team member.
When I said he was an AD
and he went, "No, I'm a director,"
he got motivated
from that point onwards.
So he started to act from
the director's point of view...
I guess he wanted to give it a try.
The more he tried,
the more hellish it became...
That was super funny though.
But upon this viewing, I believe
the segment needs re-editing.