"The Quest"
All girls gather.
"Degawa Girls Gathering Special."
One day,
we visited Madame at her home.
What will we do this time?
This time, it's the Fourth
Degawa Girls Gathering.
- Degawa Girls Gathering?
- Yes.
Shouldn't it be
Dewi Girls Gathering? Come on.
We don't want Tetsuro.
Madame will decide the programme
of the girls gathering.
We can't go abroad now,
so if we'll go somewhere in Japan,
it would be Iriomote Island.
But the Miyagawa Expedition
has been there.
In the past, Imoto went
to all the places I wanted to go to,
and lately, Daisuke...
Sorry.
They all visit places
I wanted to go to, before me.
But we can do something else,
can't we?
So their destination
is Iriomote Island.
Madame said
she wanted to go to Iriomote?
She really has a lot of energy.
It's impressive for an 81-year-old
to want to go to Iriomote.
This time, there's a new Degawa Girl
named Yumena Yanai.
What does she look like?
You don't know her?
I've neither seen nor met her.
This girl? She looks very healthy.
What will their journey be like?
Stay tuned!
"This show was broadcasted
on the 16th of May, 2021"
Welcome to The Quest.
Today's programme is
"Degawa Girls Gathering Special".
Wasshoi!
"Morisanchu"
Hello.
An Punch.
"Madame Dewi"
Hello, everyone.
All the girls are here.
It's the first gathering
after Yumeppe joined.
Yes, it's the first time.
I experienced many things
for the first time on this trip,
so I was excited the whole time.
Were you?
I worried if you were okay,
it made me nervous.
The old girls...
- Hey!
- Don't say that.
We were nice.
She's just like Cinderella.
The step-mother and evil sisters.
That's not right!
Not right?
I think the old girls
have been treating her well.
"Treat her well"?
Is that in a good sense?
- We didn't bully her.
- The old girls...
"Degawa Girls Gathering Special"
Why did my body become like this?
Smile more cheerfully!
Stop it.
Come here!
"Enjoy the natural environment
in Iriomote Island!"
2,000 kilometres away from Tokyo,
the six people enjoy the natural
environment to the fullest.
Degawa Girls Gathering
in Iriomote Island.
Iriomote Island is Okinawa's
second largest island.
Most of it is a subtropical forest.
There are many
rare animals and plants,
so it's also called
Galapagos of the East.
We've come to
Iriomote!
So this time,
- Madame wanted to--
- Oh, come on!
come to Iriomote Island
no matter what.
That's right,
I've been longing to come here.
- What's wrong with you?
- Bugs!
There are awfully lots of bugs.
And this place is horrible.
- The opening!
- What happened?
That's nothing.
What are you doing, girls?
And what's surprising is,
there are many bugs
flying around the four girls,
but none come near the two of us.
Maybe it's because we're poisonous?
At Hirai Farm,
Peach Pineapple,
Iriomote's speciality, is grown.
"Peach Pineapple"
It's sweet.
Wow, it's juicy.
It is small,
but it has high sugar content,
one of the expensive pineapples
costs 1,000 yen.
And recently,
Ms Kawakita just got married!
Congratulations!
So I'm glad that Ms Kawakita
comes here again.
News online says, "Mayuko Kawakita
quits being a Degawa Girl."
Why?
Really?
They said, that is why
we have a new Degawa Girl.
- It's their imagination.
- How could you!
Now, Yumeppe, this is the first time
that you meet Madame,
introduce yourself
in the Fukushima dialect.
You're Fukushima?
Fukushima...
Hello, I am Yumeppe.
Nice to meet you.
Adorable!
Madame, before Yumeppe
joined The Quest,
she had never even travelled
on a plane.
The girl is pure.
Everyone asked Yumeppe,
"You haven't been abroad?
You haven't been to Hawaii?"
Then Ms Kawakita said,
"Do you know what Hawaii is?"
No, no, no.
If she doesn't know, she can go
to tropical islands like this.
There isn't any adult
who doesn't know Hawaii!
I was going to tell her about it.
I know what Hawaii is.
She's angry.
Let's go, Degawa Girls Gathering.
First, we'll go river trekking
as Madame wishes.
There are many rivers
in Iriomote Island,
and river trekking is popular.
Mr Nakagawa will be
our experienced guide.
- Are you our teacher this time?
- Yes.
Nice to meet you.
What time did you just say?
- This time.
- Oh, this time.
I thought I heard you say "society."
He'd be dressing wrong
in a ballroom.
That's why I was wondering
what you were talking about.
You don't speak clearly.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Actually, I have one good news
and one bad news.
- What?
- Which one do you want to know now?
- I want bad news first.
- Bad news first.
Are you serious?
- From bad news.
- You guys are on that side?
Along the way to halfway,
there are quite a lot of bugs,
the worst case is leeches.
- Oh, that.
- What?
Leeches?
They're all stuck here
before we realise.
Or they'll enter your nostrils.
"Ahahahahaha"
Or they'll go inside
your clothes here.
- Go inside your top.
- Inside your mouth.
They'll go in from your back.
You're a hole and they'll go inside.
And the good news is,
the Okugeta Waterfall
to which they'll go this time,
is an unusual place where even most
of the locals haven't been to.
Its beauty is guaranteed.
They go to the jungle
and towards the waterfall.
If you realise there's a leech
on your skin,
don't remove it by hand.
You'll bleed, right?
Can we use that for our show?
Of course.
Then you're okay with it?
Really, she has grown stronger.
If there's a miracle
and I get stung by one.
It'll be a good story.
You talk like you want to be stung.
No.
They finally enter the jungle.
Wow, I love places like this.
- Someone said she loves it.
- Lovely!
Someone crazy is here.
Don't call her crazy.
Mr Nakagawa tells them to pay
attention to something important.
For the next 10 minutes
in this forest,
you'll see many of this plant.
If you grab it and break the leaf,
- it oozes a white liquid.
- Okay.
If it sticks on mucous membranes,
like your lips or eyes,
you must be sent
to the hospital immediately.
What?
Also, there's a river
in front of them.
I have to get wet?
- I'll get wet right away?
- Be brave and get wet.
There'll be water
in the whole journey.
Oh, is that what this trip is?
Mr Degawa, be careful.
Wow, I'm scared. It's...
- Mr Degawa, you'll touch it!
- Watch out!
- That was close.
- Oh, stop it!
- Mr Degawa!
The mic isn't waterproof.
Is it slippery?
No, you can do it.
- It's shallow.
- I didn't get wet at all.
Really? I'm soaking wet.
I've had enough! Hurry!
- Guys, don't fall!
- Wait a minute!
Wait, Yumeppe, don't fall!
Is that a cue?
"Hahahahaha"
She's laughing.
- Laughing.
- She's broken.
Watch out.
While Degawa and the young girls
are screaming,
the 81-year-old Madame
is the best walker among them.
But I'm starting to feel good.
Then, the girls see the thing
they hate in front of them.
It startled me!
What the heck?
The microphone!
The microphone.
Microphone!
Worry about Mayuko, not the mic!
She did that fantastic reaction,
don't worry about the mic first.
Exactly.
The mic is expensive.
It's 300,000 yen.
But I think the way I fell
was great.
It was worth 300,000 yen.
Let's go.
Please wait a second.
Madame.
- I'll leave you behind.
- We're a team.
They walk for another 30 minutes.
Be careful.
Oh, here we are, here we are,
here we are.
They finally see a waterfall
in front of them.
But this isn't their destination.
We'll climb up there on the left.
What?
Can we go there?
That's right. They need to climb up
for 20 more minutes
to arrive at Okugeta Waterfall.
They've been here for an hour,
the 81-year-old isn't tired at all.
Impressive!
I'm exhausted.
A good walker.
No wonder she wanted to do
river trekking.
And finally...
Wow, beautiful!
Amazing!
I'm touched.
This is the stunning scenery
known only to a few,
Okugeta Waterfall.
It is about 15 metres tall.
Waterfall in steps like this
is rarely seen in Japan,
and if you look
at the opposite side...
Wow, beautiful!
I can see the sea.
It's the beautiful Sea of Iriomote.
It's a spot with a stunning view,
where you can admire
a waterfall and the sea together.
Wow, it's here!
The scenery is absolutely amazing.
- This is picturesque, Madame.
- Yeah.
Can our viewers feel it?
We spent a long time in the jungle,
then we see this
after we climbed up.
Ms Kawakita, look at the other side.
Wow, amazing!
It's awesome.
See? Everyone looks here first,
and goes, "Amazing!"
Akane, take that off,
turn around and look.
Wow, it's awesome!
Look, Maria.
Isn't that amazing? Look behind you.
Huh? What?
Each person feels differently.
Come, Yumeppe.
- It's amazing, right?
- Yes!
But Yumeppe, look to the other side.
Finally, they'll take a photo
for their calendar.
I hate getting soaking wet!
Stop complaining, just do it!
We'll take a photo of them six
standing on the waterfall steps.
Smile!
I'm smiling!
Smile more cheerfully, guys!
Smile!
"Wahaha"
It's a wonderful photo
with the six of them.
The flow of water
looks mysterious in it.
Tonight's hotel is...
Wow, amazing.
- Lovely.
- What happened?
This is Hoshino Resorts
Iriomote Hotel.
Iriomote Island aims to get
registered as a World Heritage,
so it's environmentally friendly.
They discontinued the use
of disposable amenities,
and provide rental
of water bottles.
Their hospitality
is environment-friendly.
Open sesame.
They'll stay in this room.
Wow, it's big!
This is the Luxury Twin Room
with a day bed.
It costs 40,000 yen per night.
This is bigger than my home.
Really.
I think the best part is--
- That one, right?
- Yes, that.
I know.
Come, Yumeppe, lie down here.
Bask in the sun here.
Is it okay to bask in the sun here?
I'll lie down.
"Ahaha"
She's adorable.
Okay, it's okay to lie down.
You can lie down.
- Do this?
- Yes.
The time this smile turns into
a fake one will come someday.
Stop it!
It won't, right?
We have some bad news for them.
Only Madame and Mr Degawa
can stay here today.
No.
Degawa Girls aren't united enough,
so you'll stay at a campsite
to get to know each other better.
Hey.
Campsite?
I've been doing this
for seven, eight years and finally,
I can stay at hotels
like the ones in Dubai,
but I have to start from scratch
after Yumeppe joined?
What is this?
It's all Yumena's fault.
And this is the campsite.
What?
What's this?
This isn't for people to stay in.
This is Mitrea Campsite.
- It costs 2,000 yen per night,
- It looks nicer now.
The view from the campsite
is its selling point.
They check their rooms at once.
I see.
It's very simple.
You have one room each.
We can have one each?
One each?
This isn't right, this isn't right!
What do you think, Yumena?
It looks a bit fun.
That's not right.
Your perception isn't right.
Do you remember the hotel?
We came here
after going to that hotel.
At the same time,
the elderly team...
- I'm jealous.
- Elderly team.
Delicious.
Wow, Madame, this is amazing!
What a feast!
A lot of food ingredients
unique to Iriomote were used
to make the luxurious meal.
Chachacha...
Tatata...
Madame is delighted.
- It's tender.
- Right?
What do you think about
the new member Yumeppe?
Isn't it nice?
When a girl
who is totally different joins,
it's refreshing.
Do you think Akane has changed,
Madame?
She became a bit sophisticated.
Ms Kawakita got married, right?
What do you think?
They dated for seven years
and didn't get fed up,
so they must really love each other.
Madame, can you love someone
for so long?
The President told me
every single second
that he loved me, he loved me.
I was happy and blessed as a woman.
That's why I had no idea
he cheated on me.
Cheated.
He cheated on you!
At the same time, Degawa Girls...
Have you gotten used
to being a Degawa Girl?
Gradually, things like
the arrangements...
"Arrangements."
I'm impressed to see how you create
highlights for yourselves.
Highlights!
Don't call it a highlight!
I do it naturally.
It's the first time you meet Madame,
right?
I was so worried that
Madame would not like me.
Why?
I think she stares at people
and can sense something.
In a way you haven't seen before,
Madame is going to...
shout.
She enters the mode suddenly
when she snaps.
To make things worse,
she'd tell you to do something,
then she'll go, "You!"
She'll go, "You!"
It really makes all of us tremble.
Then, the topic changes
to nice stories about Degawa.
Playing the rich lady character
makes me feel very inferior,
so Mr Degawa told me
to turn it into comedy.
He said that to me a lot,
then I stopped fearing anything.
Is it a good or a bad thing?
I was working as a model
when I started this,
I didn't like being teased at first.
But Mr Degawa told me
that people tease me out of love,
so I thought, he was right.
I started to feel grateful
for being teased.
He told me I can just be myself.
It made me instantly realise that,
and his words helped me a lot
after that.
He said the same thing to everyone.
- To sum up.
- In general.
It's copy and paste.
Copy and paste...
We realised.
I thought that he said what the girl
needed to hear,
but he said the same things to us.
Like saying that
would hit home anyway.
This is the end of day one.
Madame, I'm impressed.
Didn't you get tired to go that far?
Not at all.
I could've gone even further.
- You're 81 years old.
- It's so impressive.
Well, they just talked about it,
Madame's voice is very loud
when she snaps.
When she actually snaps, it's...
"You!"
Yeah, when we're at the counter
in the airport, she really...
- Really.
- No way.
Just go and film outside
with her once.
It's true.
Even when we told Madame
she'd better not be so loud,
she goes, "It doesn't matter!"
She doesn't care
when she is in that mode.
That's what they say.
What do you think?
- Well, that happens.
- That happens?
Day two of filming.
They go to a mangrove
with a stunning view.
A mangrove is
a general term for plants that grow
near the mouth of a river
where sea water
and river water mix.
70 percent of mangroves in Japan
are here on Iriomote Island.
Indeed, there are a lot.
It's all of that.
It's so beautiful.
Is that called a mangrove?
I knew it. I was thinking
why you were quiet.
You've been observing.
You didn't say anything.
Yumeppe, do you know
what a mangrove is?
I don't.
I only know Mitz Mangrove.
Oh, how cute.
There are many little ones.
So cute.
Did you bring a camera, AYA?
Take photos.
They do this every time.
Madame always gets angry and goes,
"AYA, take photos properly!"
"AYA! Take the photos here!"
When she said, "AYA!"
AYA finally said,
"I'm here to do makeup for you!
I'm not your photographer!"
She fought back once.
"Makeup is a part of photography!"
What?
Isn't photography
also doing makeup?
Is it the opposite?
That makes AYA a photographer.
Why don't you carry a camera
with you?
- I'm carrying one.
- Yeah?
You startled me.
- I panicked.
- What?
I panicked.
- What's that?
- It startled me!
- I thought a crocodile appeared!
- I thought so too!
Gosh, cut it out!
They'll go kayaking
as Madame wishes,
but as they're here...
We'll make it a race.
A race?
The rule is simple.
Three teams of two
will have a kayak race.
The last team will stand under
a waterfall as punishment.
How will they decide the teams?
The person who wins
a rock, paper, scissors game
will choose a teammate.
I have to win.
We'll choose.
I see.
The first winner is...
Hotta.
I'll choose Yumeppe.
Thank you!
Now, the fateful match.
Who will win?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Kawakita wins.
I won!
Winning rock, paper, scissors
means nothing.
It means something! I'll choose!
Who will she choose?
Degawa or Tani?
I'll choose Maria, of course!
- Hurray!
- We're going to win.
Hurray!
Thank goodness!
The good ones among us have to be
Yumeppe and Madame.
- Why?
- Madame's arms are very strong.
Are you guys stupid?
He's only a weight.
Who are you calling a weight?
Who is a weight?
What's your average age?
"81 years old, 57 years old"
Their average age is about 70.
Now, let's begin the kayak race.
The distance is 200 metres.
The team that arrives at the goal
that is the pier, wins.
Ready,
start!
Right, left, right, left.
They all started together.
But Team Kawakita
started to slow down.
You can do it.
Then, they suddenly changed
direction and went to the middle.
- You're in our way.
- You play dirty!
Right, left.
This time,
Team Hotta goes near Degawa.
Akane, don't come here!
Why are you coming here?
Right, left, right...
It becomes a triple dead heat.
Ouch!
They use the paddles
to shove each other.
Team Hotta is in the lead now.
Good!
Team Kawakita is also catching up.
There are 50 metres left,
they can see the pier, their goal.
Team Hotta and Yumeppe
are in the lead,
Kawakita and Tani
are in second place.
At this rate, Degawa and Madame
will go to the waterfall.
They'll be the winner
when they go up the pier.
Good.
You okay?
The girls are struggling.
Yumeppe can't go up.
Team Kawakita doesn't miss
the chance.
So the last team
is Team Madame and Degawa.
You all came to bump into us.
You bumped into us!
How dare you say that!
It's a race, so it's okay if we win.
By the way, my team won.
The 81-year-old poked
someone's bottom with her paddle.
Also, when a junior is in trouble,
these sisters-in-law
didn't help her.
So the winners go to the hotel,
the losers go to the waterfall.
It takes 30 minutes to walk on
a mountain path to the waterfall.
The girls have free time now?
They must be having fun.
- Probably now, Madame,
- Are you kidding me?
They must be back at the hotel
having lunch after swimming.
Oh, is that so?
Come here!
The girls are enjoying
the beautiful beach.
I would be happy
if I see a wild cat here.
- Indeed.
- Right?
Then the girls will be disappointed.
They will reflect
on what they did wrong.
Really, really.
We can scatter some biscuits.
"Do not do that"
That was the most horrible comment.
Madame, that was
the most horrible comment.
Was it?
After walking for 30 minutes,
finally...
Isn't it wonderful?
- It's huge!
- Beautiful.
This is the Nara Waterfall,
which is about 25 metres tall.
It's beautiful,
- but it's rather powerful.
- Yes.
I'm trembling with excitement.
Anyway, brace yourself
when we're under the waterfall.
Please go.
After you.
Senior, after you.
You're a man.
You really play dirty.
They go into the waterfall.
I can't see ahead.
Madame goes after Degawa.
That's the guts of an 81-year-old.
Amazing.
They start sitting
under the waterfall.
Go a bit more to the front, Madame!
I'll fall into the basin
of the waterfall.
Even so,
when Degawa goes to the front...
Madame goes into the waterfall.
Are any other old people
made to go through this?
What's this?
I've entered somewhere that hurts!
I can't breathe!
Okay, it's done!
Their sitting under the waterfall
ends without mishap.
Thank goodness
it was us who did this.
There's no way the girls can do it.
When they return to the hotel...
They're enjoying themselves.
You make sounds like
you're having fun on purpose.
How unpleasant.
Madame started to get annoyed.
"Hohohohoho"
Mayuko is the most stupid.
Stupid. Her act is so stupid!
She can't act.
"Hohohohoho"
How horrible.
Your effort is totally in vain.
Cliché, it's cliché.
Unusually cliché.
Cliche, it's cliche.
Unusually cliche.
Their petty fight continues.
We also saw sea turtles.
- Wild?
- Yes.
- We saw many wild sea turtles.
- This big.
- Really?
- Really!
They must be tortoises.
They weren't.
Judging by the size,
they were tortoises.
You're horribly sore losers.
The shell is round, right?
It wasn't.
That's a tortoise.
We saw some green turtles.
Yes, we did.
They're tortoises.
It's a mystery why sea turtle means
victory and tortoise means defeat.
We have a special project.
To commemorate Yumeppe joining,
Degawa Girls will have
a cooking competition.
How confident are they?
I cook better than before.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
- Can I see the recipe?
- No.
Of course, you can't.
It's not my priority,
but my cooking has improved.
What is your current first priority?
It's Pilates lately.
Pilaf?
"Pilaf?"
I help my mother cook every night
at home.
- What?
- Wow, good on you!
What a wonderful story.
Like a primary school child's story.
What did you say?
It's quite impressive that she helps
Mummy cook when she's 20 years old.
Isn't it natural?
You find fault with that?
See? You...
Okay, arrested.
What about Kawakita, then?
I've gotten married,
so I cook a lot, of course.
What does your husband say?
He says he's never had anything
so delicious, every day.
That's amazing.
The story makes me feel sick.
It's nothing unusual.
Madame is the judge.
They'll come up with a menu
using food ingredients available,
and make delicious dishes
within an hour.
There are many things.
Ready, start!
What will each of them cook?
Madame is the judge.
They'll come up with a menu
using food ingredients available,
and make delicious dishes
within an hour.
There are many things.
Ready, start!
What will each of them cook?
The food ingredients are all here,
it's first come, first served.
Akane took the whole bowl of...
minced meat.
Oh, I wanted minced meat.
I'll give you some
if I have any left.
Thank you.
She plays dirty.
This is Degawa Girls.
That girl is amazing.
She's true to herself,
it's cool, in fact.
And then...
Can I have a paper and a pen?
Akane needs a recipe
and she started writing notes.
You'll make it yourself,
why use a pen?
If I can't organise my thoughts,
I'll panic.
I don't know what to do first
to make it more efficient.
We can't expect much
from Hotta and Tani.
What about the married, Kawakita?
She chose daikon radish,
it makes her look like
she's good at cooking.
What is Yumeppe making?
Tomato sauce?
- I'm making a tomato sauce.
- It looks nice.
The problem is her. This girl.
She's gone.
Did she go to look at her phone?
Let's check!
What?
- She isn't there!
- We can do that?
That's not fair.
Hey, Akane!
What?
What are you doing, Akane?
- That's not fair!
- You're washing it?
- What?
- I panicked.
We thought you were
looking at your phone.
I'm not!
I'm not that petty!
Okay, Yumeppe started
frying something.
I don't know what she's making yet,
but she'll add chicken
to her tomato sauce...
It already looks delicious.
I'll drop it.
Oh my goodness!
See? She cooks.
Look, the false tooth.
Not false tooth.
Her chopsticks.
Look, the false tooth.
Not false tooth.
Her chopsticks.
Look, handling the pan
with one hand.
Look!
That's how Yumeppe cooks.
And there's lots of meat.
Yumena, you're a good cook!
On the other hand, Hotta...
Your hands are shaking.
It's dangerous. I'm scared.
I hate men who makes fun of me
when I'm cooking.
No, I'm not teasing you.
Really...
She's worked up.
I've snapped because of that.
Akane Hotta, 28 years old, has gone
through many things in life.
It happens a lot lately.
On the other hand,
the 20-year-old Yumeppe...
This idea wouldn't occur
to Maria and Akane.
Why do you say that?
- She's doing this.
- It's obvious.
"Hahahaha"
- She's only 20 years old.
- Yes.
I'll make the second dish.
Ms Kawakita is making
her second dish.
We have one hour,
so we'll see how many
we can make in one hour.
Wow, that's impressive.
Yumeppe is also making
the second dish, on top of that...
Yumeppe has started
deep-frying things!
- Wait, I'm making the same.
- Deep-fry?
She says she's making
the same dish.
I have absolutely no idea
what dish she's making.
- Akane.
- It's obvious!
She started to stir-fry
the minced meat in butter.
Oh, I want to go home.
- It means withdrawal, Akane.
- I want to board a flight soon!
General Dewi watches this girl
with a smile.
Maria started stir-frying something.
- Maria, it's burning.
- What?
The smoke is white, it's burning.
I'm so sick of it.
"I want to go home."
- The second one.
- The second "want to go home."
Things are going as we expected.
Maria, we have good points too.
Wait, don't lump me in with you.
You abandoned her! How could you?
Yumeppe, this is Degawa Girls.
Okay, she started putting
the boiled potatoes into a bowl.
Wow, what?
Oh, it's hard.
Then, Hotta encounters an accident
later on.
The recipe that my life depends on!
The recipe flew to the sky!
She's lucky.
Are you kidding me?
It's fantastic.
Excuse me, I've finished.
Will you try them first?
Kawakita has finished
making the dishes.
Stewed chicken and daikon radish,
stir-fried pork and cabbage.
She also made
miso soup with lots of mushrooms.
It's three Japanese dishes.
It looks delicious.
The daikon radish absorbed
the flavour.
Yes, it did.
As delicious as always.
Thank you.
The miso soup is delicious.
Next, what about
the 20-year-old Yumeppe?
She made two dishes
with pasta as the main dish.
Tomato sauce pasta
flavoured with garlic,
and a Western-styled plate with
enoki mushrooms wrapped in meat
and deep-fried aubergine.
I'm confident in the pasta.
Delicious. Absolutely delicious.
- It has a strong flavour of garlic.
- Yes, the garlic.
To be honest, I had no idea
Yumeppe is such a good cook.
- Absolutely delicious.
- So good.
Thank you.
In fact, I think we can stop now.
Oh no, I'm full.
Stop eating. Hey, stop eating.
Stop eating. I've cooked.
Stop eating.
Here it is. Her own luncheon mat!
I made the taste a bit richer
for the old people.
Old people?
- Shouldn't you make it less salty?
- It's the opposite?
I messed up!
The dishes Tani made are...
It's salad udon set meal.
- It's a set meal?
- It looks nice, though.
Oh, I got it wrong!
You prepared a luncheon mat,
and this is a set meal?
I said it wrong. It's a lunch set.
- Lunch set. That's right.
- Yes.
Do they taste okay?
It's quite tasty.
Really?
What about the cream soup
she had adjusted to taste lighter?
She made the taste lighter?
"Hahaha"
- He can't say anything.
- Speechless.
Is this milk?
- Yes.
- She made it too bland?
The chicken has no flavour at all.
- It isn't enough?
- That's right. The taste...
- Not enough?
- No.
No, it's because I heard
old people like a lighter taste.
Come on.
How dare you! What's wrong with you?
The taste was rich at first,
- then I added water into it.
- I see.
I see.
Because old people
like light-tasting food...
The last one is...
The recipe my life depends on!
The recipe of wind, Hotta.
The last one is...
The recipe my life depends on!
The recipe of wind, Hotta.
Over here,
is our restaurant's
special croquette.
We only sell croquettes.
I didn't make any sauce to let you
taste the potato's good flavour.
What?
Manager, it isn't appetising.
The shape is bad,
the shredded cabbage is thick.
Wow, it's awfully soft.
- It's what we call fluffy.
- Fluffy?
"Hahahahaha"
Why?
It's good.
What?
Well, I like how fluffy it is.
Delicious.
What? Are you kidding me?
- Unlike how it looks.
- Thank you. I'm often told that.
It's ugly...
Well, it looks so ugly.
Just give me a compliment.
Who is the winner
of the cooking competition?
Each of you has made an effort,
- all the dishes were delicious.
- Yes, indeed.
But the exquisite dishes
were made by Yumeppe.
What?
Yumeppe wins.
Your mother must be
a very skilled cook.
Your mum will be delighted
when she watches our show.
Are you watching?
I'm in first place.
Madame, if you'll rank the second,
third, and fourth places...
Obviously, the second is...
- Good...
- Ms Kawakita.
- Who's in third place?
- Maria.
What?
- What? Wait a minute!
- I'm in fourth place?
Personally,
I think Ms Kawakita is second,
third is Akane, and fourth is Maria.
Maria's udon was delicious,
- but the soup was too bland.
- Yes, the soup.
- I made it for old people.
- Shut up!
She says that a lot.
They will go explore a cave
on the last day of filming.
Their river trekking guide
will be Mr Nakagawa.
There are many caves in Iriomote.
The cave we're going to
is one you don't see in Japan.
It's a cave with an amazing scenery.
Do you know what Angel's Ladder is?
Angel's Ladder.
When sunlight shines into the cave
from a hole,
it looks like a ladder,
hence, the name.
It's a natural phenomenon.
They'll take a photo with it
for the calendar.
I can't bring myself to tell you,
but there's a very low chance
of it appearing,
about five percent.
Five percent?
Do the four of you have luck
like that?
I've been surviving
with only my luck.
I survived only by luck.
- It'll be okay?
- I'm going to show you.
I'm also very lucky.
- Really?
- Really.
You don't look like you are.
I also bump into many celebrities
in our paparazzi project.
In that case, maybe we'll be okay.
Say, "What about me? Hey!"
I...
- "I..."
I gave you a very obvious pass!
I also asked Maria and ignored you,
so when I come here,
you should go, "Hey! What about me?"
That's what I should say?
Now, the team sets off.
I've been a guide for over 25 years,
the oldest guest I've taken there
so far was 74 years old.
If we can go there this time,
the record will be broken.
Wow, Madame.
Let's break his record.
The entrance of the cave
is on the other side of the jungle.
It's so dark!
It's a real jungle!
You talk too much, little girls.
What? We have no help?
Please do your best.
What?
Doesn't our guide accompany Madame
too much?
Think calmly. She's 81 years old.
I see.
Mr Nakagawa tells them something
they should pay attention to.
- You'll see the entrance soon.
- Okay.
The moment you see it,
you'll be speechless,
it's beyond your imagination.
- What?
- Then,
there's only one piece of advice
I can give you at the entrance.
Do your best.
- Do our best.
- Wait...
What the heck? I'm scared!
After they go past
the gap between the rocks...
It's here.
Wait...
This is the cave's entrance.
There's no way I can go in this!
I'll go through easily.
How thick is your waist?
80 centimetres.
Mine is much thicker than yours.
It's 105, 105, 105.
Who is going to go first?
- I'll go.
- Amazing!
- You don't have to see how it goes?
- It's fine, I have nothing to fear.
So cool.
So the oldest in history,
81-year-old Madame, will go first.
It's narrow.
She's going forward.
Oh, she went through it.
Madame did it with a smile.
It's okay. This is nothing.
Yumeppe
and Tani also did it.
All right.
Then, Kawakita.
Isn't it narrow? What?
She's the noisiest.
She is.
- She's always the noisiest.
- She is.
Finally, it's Degawa's turn.
Will he be able to go through?
I can't do it, seriously.
I'll end my trip here
in the worst case scenario.
Degawa starts going in.
- Stretch your knees.
- Your arms.
No.
Don't talk altogether.
Ouch!
Push! Push!
Ready, go!
No... My belly is stuck here.
Do your best!
What's wrong with this belly?
Why did my body become like this?
You can do it!
That said, after the effort he
made, he managed to go through.
I did it!
- You can do it!
- I did it!
- Amazing!
- I made it!
Amazing!
I'm so happy!
I feel like I was born.
The last one is Hotta,
whom they completely forgot about.
Nobody is there.
Guys!
Yes?
Did you forget about my existence?
We didn't forget you.
Hurry up.
When they go further...
It's so cool!
There is a huge space.
There are hundreds of stalactite
hanging in the mysterious cave.
There are good stones in this cave,
a phenomenon that's special
among stones occurs.
It gives off light
even after I turn it off.
Wow, amazing!
The light stays.
Amazing!
This device is for research,
it gives off a special light.
If I shine this light
to the back of the stones,
the light will want to escape from
inside the stone after that.
The crystal will be in the way.
Diffused reflection occurs,
and it stays.
Yes, the light takes a long time
to look for an exit.
This is so interesting.
Then, finally...
It's our destination,
the room where the beam enters.
Oh, everyone!
This is our destination,
the room of the beam.
Madame, too fast.
Madame, it's too fast.
Wait for us.
The guide...
I can see it.
"Hole"
But there is no light
shining from the hole.
So we can only wait here.
I'll look for a place
that's easy to stand on,
and wait for the sun.
The girls are exhausted.
Hey!
You're surprisingly unresponsive.
But after waiting for two hours...
They have waited long.
It started for a bit.
- Oh, it's true!
- Wow, it's here!
It suddenly came!
Have a look at this.
This is the Angel's Ladder.
Light is reflected by
the water vapour in the cave,
and forms a beautiful ladder.
They moved there at once
and took a calendar photo.
- Isn't it wonderful?
- It's lovely!
It's stunning.
People who aren't in the spotlight.
Really!
We're all in the shadow.
The position Ms Kawakita takes
at a time like this is genius.
In 24 Hour Television, she always
goes behind Mr Yuzo Kayama.
Every time when he sings,
"Goodbye, Earth!"
It's Space Battleship Yamato.
What?
That's all for
Degawa Girls Gathering.
You went to the place
where Madame wanted to go,
so she didn't complain at all.
Right.
She was always positive,
she went to the waterfall willingly.
We walked on a tightrope
but they didn't include it.
Walked on a tightrope?
Exactly.
We jumped from a very high place,
what happened to that?
What happened to that?
Mr Takei films three extra ones.
I understand if it's one,
but he filmed three extras.
- Three.
- He filmed three extra ones.
Just one part.
Near the swimming pool,
fuelled by anger,
she went, "This cliche act."
How horrible.
Your effort is totally in vain.
Cliche, it's cliche.
Unusually cliche.
I'm impressed by Akane.
Her recipe flew to the sky.
That was wonderful.
- Brilliant.
- You were lucky there.
I was desperate, really.
You dare say that!
The moment the recipe flew
to the sky,
she had many chances to grab it,
but she did this many times,
and missed it.
Did you put it there
so that it'd be blown away easily?
- I didn't.
- I see.
Maybe she predicted
where the wind would blow.
- She's a pro!
- No pro does that.