"This show was broadcast
on the 21st of March, 2021"
Welcome to The Quest.
Today's programme is
Rare Beast Hunter Imoto Japan Tour
and Lotti Nakaoka's QTube.
First, Imoto,
where did you go this time?
I went to Hyogo Prefecture
this time.
I went to film somewhere in Kobe
that's well known to everyone,
and it was almost
my own cosplay show.
That's what it's composed of.
We don't want
your cosplay show at all.
What?
But on the contrary,
enthusiastic fans must stay tuned.
Enthusiastic.
Yeah, enthusiastic fans.
Enthusiastic fans, stay tuned.
Ranger!
Okay, okay, okay.
I'll clean the Shachihoko.
I'm Lady Sen.
A bit more... No!
All of you!
Are you going to film
a funny video today?
Aim to go around all 47 prefectures
in Japan,
Rare Beast Hunter Imoto Japan Tour.
She went to the Kinki Region,
in Hyogo Prefecture, between
the Japan Sea and Seto Inland Sea.
Hello! Hello, this is Imoto.
I have come to Hyogo Prefecture.
So where am I?
Let's do our regular search
for Imoto.
- The right.
- This boat.
I'm here! Over here!
- I'm here!
- Not where I thought.
The correct answer is
I was hiding behind
the boat's lifesaver ring!
What's that?
Okay, I'm now going
to catch something.
What do you think it is?
The boat Imoto is on charges into
the nets put on the sea's surface.
The amount of this harvest from
the sea produced in Hyogo Prefecture
is number two in Japan.
Here it is.
Do you know what it is?
We're harvesting seaweed.
Wow, impressive!
We're washing the boat with seaweed.
There is a cutter
on top of the boat,
and it harvests the seaweed
grown on the nets.
In the past,
people harvested it by hand,
but after the kelp fishing boat
was developed,
the amount of production
increased by a lot.
In Kyushu,
they usually put poles in the sea
- and put the nets there.
- Okay.
But the current flow here is quick,
so we put ropes here
and let the nets float.
It also makes the taste different,
right?
Seaweed grown on floating nets
is fleshy,
and it's resistant to moisture.
When convenience stores
and supermarkets make rice balls,
they use seaweed grown
in sea water for moist seaweed,
and seaweed grown on poles is used
for crispy seaweed.
Imoto tries
the freshly harvested raw seaweed.
Oh, delicious!
It looks a lot like wakame,
but the more I chew,
the more it tastes like seaweed.
It's very nutritious,
and it's good for beauty.
And good for hair too?
- Hair... I can't say anything.
- Wait.
Don't laugh.
I'm sorry.
"Effect varies
from person to person"
It's delicious.
Japan Tour in Hyogo Starts now.
First, we'll go to the theatre
Hyogo is famous for.
Here I am, everyone,
at the famous
Takarazuka Grand Theatre.
I have watched their play once
in Tokyo before.
It was fantastic!
It's so cool!
Founder of Hankyu Railway,
Ichizo Kobayashi,
founded the Takarazuka Revue.
It held its first performance
in 1914,
and 2021 is its 107th anniversary.
You can transform
into a Takarazuka star
at this grand theatre.
Imoto will play a male role,
and Mum, Assistant Producer Hirata,
will transform into a female role.
Imoto will go first.
Welcome to Takarazuka!
Isn't it nice? It's nice.
This is a feather costume worn by
the male in the play's finale.
When I wear this costume
with make-up on,
it really makes me feel like
I've become a top star.
I even speak with a voice lower
than my usual unconsciously.
What do you think, Mr Miyagawa?
It looks like Patalliro.
It does, right?
Oh, thank you for saying that.
On the other hand, Mum...
Is it okay?
Hello.
Hirata!
You look surprisingly good.
Your facial expression is good too!
What are your hands doing?
Good!
This is a costume of a female
character in Takarazuka Hanashishu.
- I can't move by myself.
- That's impressive.
How much better it'll make
the person look
will show how skilled
the photographer is.
Look up.
- That's the highest.
- I'll lift your head.
You aren't looking up. Try harder.
Make your hand a bit more feminine.
Make it look like you'll release
Kamehameha.
With little power.
Make your eyes bright.
Okay, smile!
- Lovely!
- You look pretty.
- Pretty.
- Very pretty.
- You're so pretty.
Okay, please smile. So pretty.
That's the most amount of "pretty"
I will hear in my life.
I've never been told that
so many times before.
I was so happy.
I guess I'm a bit too close
to this girl.
I was surprised
when I saw her up close.
I guess this distance is too short.
Next, we'll introduce the castle
Hyogo is famous for.
They went to Takeda Castle
in Asago City.
The sea of clouds you see here
is famous,
and it's referred to as
the Machu Picchu of Japan.
This is their guide, Mr Ueyama.
Today's weather conditions aren't...
That's not true. The temperature
will rise during the day.
If there's a possible difference
in temperature,
you'll certainly see it.
Your mask makes your glasses cloudy.
They look like a sea of clouds.
Imoto goes up the castle and tries
to see the sea of clouds, but...
It's here!
There is no trace
of any sea of clouds.
It's supposed to be edited out,
but we wanted to use this scene
no matter what.
Your mask makes your glasses cloudy.
They look like a sea of clouds.
But there is one more castle
in Hyogo
that is as famous as Takeda Castle
and the sea of clouds.
That is...
Everyone,
this is the famous Himeji Castle.
I am Tokugawa Ieyasu's
granddaughter,
Lady Sen.
Shut up!
Be quiet, everyone!
Lady Sen is the most well-known lady
of Himeji Castle.
She is famous for her beauty,
and she wasn't like this.
What is your name?
I am Assistant Director Kudo.
- Assistant Director.
- I couldn't become the director.
Why would you say something so sad?
Its beauty as a wooden building
is highly praised,
and Himeji Castle was the first
registered World Heritage of Japan.
We'll give you a quiz
about Himeji Castle.
Question one.
How many storeys does
Himeji Castle's main keep have?
Isn't it five?
Festival Guy Miyagawa,
answer the question.
From what I see now, it has
one, two, three, four, five storeys,
right?
Is it five? Five.
The correct answer is...
Seven storeys.
I can't tell. What?
There's one more
behind the stone fence,
and there are two triangular roofs.
The second one from above?
There are actually
two storeys inside that.
I see.
To confuse the enemy to make them
think there are five storeys
if they were to attack,
it was constructed like this.
You'd wonder why
it wasn't a five-storey building.
Good.
Deputy Division Head.
Thank you.
Please wait a minute.
The battery...
Battery?
- The battery is out.
You're demoted
to Assistant Director!
Sorry.
Next, a question about
the Daimyo's alternate attendance.
Feudal lords in the Sengoku Period
had to spend a large sum of money
to go to Edo every other year.
The lord of some domains had to pay
over 100 million yen
in present value.
A domain wants to spend as little
as possible no matter what,
and usually, samurai retainers
would accompany them.
But it is said that some of them
hired part-time workers.
There was a standard for paying
the part-time workers per diem.
What was the standard?
Well then, Lord Degawa.
- Lord Degawa?
- Yes.
Let me think...
Slay the people around--
Wrong!
That's incorrect.
The correct answer is
they were paid
according to their height.
Here, 167 cm or under...
In Lord Degawa's case,
it's the lowest,
so you can only get 7,000 yen.
But the scary thing is
if you're 180 cm tall,
look, you can get 28,000 yen.
It's about four times that.
But why did they use the height?
It's here.
Good appearance was prioritised
in this job.
What a horrible reason.
But Mr Degawa's appearance is bad.
At this historic castle...
Rangers, assemble!
Rangers.
Rangers assembled.
A new member will join us to clean
Himeji Castle. Let me introduce.
Good morning!
I'm Ayako Imoto,
Watanabe Entertainment's comedian!
Nice to meet you!
Ranger!
May I ask?
What did you just say?
Ranger!
We basically answer everything
with "ranger."
That's why?
"Yes" and "no" are also "ranger."
"No" is "ranger" too?
How do I interpret it?
That's our mutual relationship.
Are you serious?
Attention!
In position!
- Ranger!
She was slow.
The cleaning
of Himeji Castle begins.
Today's mission
is to weed the castle wall
and clean the attic.
Can you understand?
Ranger! Ran...
- Ranger!
- Please ask normally.
I won't understand
if you only say ranger.
They're descended by a rope
on the castle wall to weed it.
Safety ring checked.
Complete.
- Secure it.
- We'll go already?
Ranger!
Okay, okay, okay.
Imoto is useful right away.
After all, she had been climbing
cliffs all around the world.
No weed!
Impressive.
Weed!
- Remove it!
- Ranger!
Mission accomplished!
So cute.
The next place they go to is...
Scary!
They will clean the attic
of the main keep's top floor.
I'm at an incredible place now.
This is the roof of the national
treasure, Himeji Castle's main keep.
I'm so excited.
I'll start from this area.
Dirt accumulates easily
in the corners.
It's this place.
This part bothers me too.
It's the corners.
The corners bother me.
I'll also clean the Shachihoko.
I can brag about this
for the rest of my life.
I cleaned Himeji Castle.
Impressive.
It was the Air Self-Defence Force
last year.
I've seen various defence forces,
but they are all different.
The rangers are fired up
and have a fighting spirit.
- We're unyielding!
- And the air force?
- They were more stylish.
I thought it was interesting.
In fact, now I'm curious about
the Maritime Self-Defence Force.
The next place she went to
was the popular aquarium
Kinosaki Marine World.
She will verify
rumours about animals here.
The hearing ability of a sea lion
is incredible.
In a show of seals like sea lions,
the animal usually watches
the keeper's gestures and performs.
But the rumoured sea lion
can perform by only listening
to voices,
and she performs
no matter whose voice it is.
She can distinguish each word
and link it to
the corresponding trick.
She has gotten even better
and can perform remotely.
It happened
in the sea lion's world too?
This is the rumoured sea lion, Hama,
an 11-year-old female.
She can distinguish 40 different
words in the human language.
Now, let's verify it.
Imoto stands by in a different room.
She gives Hama instructions
through a speaker.
Hello, everyone.
The star of this show
is on the stage here.
Meet female sea lion Hama.
A sea lion is a kind of seal.
She has big forelegs.
How will she use them?
First, she uses them when she swims.
Go to the island.
Hama reacts correctly.
Let's ask her to come back.
Come here.
Mr Sasaki only gave her food
as a reward.
To the lower tier.
She supports her body's weight
and moves with four legs.
Come here.
Whether a sea lion
is on land or in water,
they move skilfully either way.
Lie down.
- Go!
- So cute!
Good.
Goodbye.
Throw a kiss.
Impressive!
Hama's performance is perfect.
But, Mr Sasaki,
you're a bit angry over how
unpopular sea lions are in Japan.
When you ask people about
their impression of sea lions,
most of them will say
scary, fat, and fierce.
But when we ask them
after they've done this tour,
about 90 per cent of the people
say sea lions are cute and clever.
We want as many people as possible
to know.
We were told we'd become sea lions
if we sleep after eating.
"Become a sea lion" is a compliment.
- What?
- It's a compliment.
The next rumour she'll verify is...
"Otter dung smells nice."
This has to be a lie.
This was reported by
an American online magazine.
Otter dung smells nice,
like jasmine tea.
Have you drunk jasmine tea before?
Jasmine tea is very fragrant.
It's like Asian palm civet's coffee.
Kopi luwak?
Use the Asian palm civet's faeces...
No! They're fed coffee cherries.
It isn't poop.
Nice to meet you.
Do you look after
the Asian palm civets?
- It's otters.
- I'm sorry.
The otters that will help us
are Momiji and Kaede.
Here they are.
So cute.
They're so cute.
They love her so much.
They stay so close to her feet.
She collects what she is here for.
It's wetter than I have imagined.
She uses the fresh poop
to verify it.
What machine is that?
I'll use it to smell?
Cover it so the smell will stay.
No need. This is no good!
I'll do it.
Is it jasmine tea?
It stinks!
It stinks! It stinks!
It does smell fishy.
There isn't a hint of jasmine tea.
It stinks.
- It stinks.
- Yes.
- I know that.
- You do?
- It stinks, right?
- Your job is tough.
Well...
Next, it's an invention
created in Hyogo.
She came to
Kobe City College of Technology.
This is Robot Lab's associate,
Professor Toshihiko Shimizu.
This is a robot hand.
The invention is a device
called Gripper.
- Can I have a look for a second?
- Please touch it.
Oh, what is it?
It feels good, though.
It feels a bit squishy.
- It feels like a bead cushion.
- That's right.
The machine uses a vacuum pump
to hold objects.
The impressive thing is...
Even if it has an uneven shape
like this
- and it's sunken,
- I see.
it can hold the object tightly.
Even if the object's shape
is curved,
it can do this.
It can change shape
to hold the object.
Impressive!
The powder of the beads
changes shape,
so it can grab objects
with various shapes.
Factories use many kinds
of robot hands for packing, but...
Our robot hand
can do two functions.
That's what it's for!
Gripper is a machine
that can hold anything.
The new invention created
using this is...
the Wall Climbing Assistant Suit.
You can climb up a wall
by pressing this part.
Wait, what did you make this for?
At a disaster scene
where an aerial truck can't go,
- it can be used for rescue.
- Cool.
That said,
nobody has used this machine
to climb a high wall yet.
So Imoto will check its performance
this time.
It's like I'm doing
an experiment, right?
It's scary.
I don't have that much faith
in its suction. I'm sorry.
I shouldn't say that
in front of the inventor.
She'll climb up a wall
at a theme park that exhibits
famous places in the world,
Taiyo Park.
Swan Castle, built using Germany's
Neuschwanstein Castle as the motif.
This is tall.
She will climb up the wall
and will reach the goal if she
can go into the lower balcony.
It's cool, like Mission: Impossible.
Maybe in the future,
someone might want to use it
after seeing this.
Imoto starts climbing up
Swan Castle's wall.
It's tall!
She will climb up the wall
and will reach the goal if she
can go into the lower balcony.
We asked professional climbers
to set up safety measures
like a lifeline.
Imoto starts climbing up
Swan Castle's wall.
Gripper sticks to the wall tightly.
I see.
- I put my weight here.
- That's right.
This is nice.
It's amazing.
Imoto's feet are hooked on belts
hanging down from the Gripper.
In other words, the suction alone
supports 50 kilogrammes.
But the first problem occurred
right after she started.
What?
All right, is it okay?
Okay.
Oh, no. I can't hear his voice.
The professor jots down
the problem at once.
Ten minutes
after she started climbing...
Oh, no. My arms.
It's heavy.
I thought I could climb easily?
I thought I could climb up
without using any force?
It's totally different
from what you told me.
On top of that...
It doesn't attach!
- What?
- That's scary.
- It doesn't attach!
- It's scary.
Will you knock it on the side
over there?
What?
Professor, I can't hear you.
The engine is too noisy.
I can't hear you at all.
I only hear the engine.
She struggled a lot
in the last 10 metres.
Oh, this part...
I can't attach it here.
Why doesn't it attach to the wall?
Why doesn't this attach?
The one on the right
doesn't attach at all.
What the heck is this?
Why doesn't it attach, Professor?
This doesn't attach.
What? The wall is the problem?
It really doesn't attach.
This is no good.
The subject of the experiment
returns angrily.
Professor!
I can give a lot of points
you need to improve.
First, the hair here.
If I shake this, it fluffs.
The hair sticks to this part,
so it isn't a vacuum anymore.
First, fix it so that
the hair here doesn't stick.
Ms Imoto.
"Stay calm"
- Yeah, first...
- Thank you.
If you continue, gravity will make
the beads go down.
It becomes empty up here,
so it's better to do it by hand,
but the situation doesn't allow it.
Tap it by hand.
It's what you need
to improve the beads part.
Also, the sound.
It roared the moment I started.
I couldn't hear anything.
The structure of the castle
wasn't good either.
The gap is too wide.
It should be improved.
It's what the castle should improve.
That's the 13th prefecture,
Hyogo Prefecture conquered.
- I saw Imoto in so many costumes.
- Thank you.
She looked so cool
in the Takarazuka costume.
It suited her.
It really did! I thought cosplay
like this was fun,
but Lady Sen next...
the make-up didn't sit well.
Indeed.
Around the world, many YouTubers
film and upload funny videos.
In this project,
we travel and film with them to make
people around the world laugh.
It's called...
QTube.
Hello, I'm Lotti Nakaoka!
I've come to Lake Megami in
Tateshina Town, Nagano Prefecture.
- Oh?
It's somewhere cold again.
Right away?
First, it's The World's Fool
Videos Winter Version.
Nakaoka, snow dive.
We'll film with the help of...
the staff of Kashiyama Industries,
who often help us film in Japan.
As a matter of fact,
its snowmaking gun has
the number one share in Japan.
The snow accumulated here
is all made by the machine.
Kashiyama made this?
That's right.
And you'll work with us this time?
- Yes.
- So many of you came here?
Does your company
have no work to do?
How can you say that?
Nakaoka, snow dive.
He'll dive into a snow mountain
that is two metres deep.
A cushion is made with Styrofoam
for safety,
and they accumulated snow on it.
Wow, it's cold!
It took five days to make.
Will Nakaoka be able
to jump beautifully?
- It's the underwear for jumping.
- One!
I'm sorry!
Wait a minute.
My feet are very cold.
He warms himself up.
I've seen this before.
Mugwort is cooked beneath.
The steam turns it into a sauna.
This is also
Kashiyama Industries' kindness.
I feel warm in no time.
Not bad.
But look, if you look from here,
I look like a pervert.
But I saw on Twitter, when
the show was on air the other day,
someone said only you can
make them laugh.
That's nice.
What?
I have to do it, then.
Nakaoka, can he jump this time?
Okay! I plucked up my courage.
It helped him.
This is what I wanted to do
when I was a child.
Thanks for making my dream
come true!
Here I go!
Three.
Two.
One.
Jump!
Amazing!
A round of applause.
Is he okay?
It's funny.
It's freezing cold!
There's more Styrofoam
than I thought!
Pull me up!
Please!
It. Is. Cold!
Okay, please!
A girl?
A girl? Are you kidding me?
About half of it was Styrofoam.
It would've killed me
if it was all snow.
They thought about my safety.
Thank you.
Have some mugwort tea if you like.
Mugwort tea!
Thank you.
I'm going to bring Kashiyama
to film with me outside.
You guys, disappear.
Next, it's a video uploaded
by Will Smith
that people talked about.
Nakaoka imitated and filmed
half of the video.
I made it! I made it!
The other half will be...
Aloha!
The Hawaiian guy?
Filmed by masters around the world
who had appeared on QTube before.
What is the video like now?
Interesting.
It starts when Nakaoka
drops the ball.
It's Will Smith.
"Nakaoka,
changing table tennis ball video"
- Nice!
- Nice.
It's good.
Good.
So cute!
Impressive.
It's fun.
Hello, Nakaoka. How are you?
I'm waiting for you in Hawaii.
The last one is Nakaoka.
He aims to hit a plastic bottle with
a hockey stick, which he's good at.
Go.
Oh, no! I missed it!
It's hot!
Nice.
Thank you.
This is bad.
It's no good. My scalp...
My scalp...
Hot water, space, scalp.
What happens? Look it up.
What happens?
Next, it's the video of
a challenge under cold weather.
Someone will hold his leg
from behind,
and he'll reach out his hand.
There's someone
in a green tracksuit.
His partner this time
is assistant cameraman Omori.
Challenge of trust, start.
If he can get the full-house bonus
floating on the lake,
he'll get 10,000 yen.
Can you do it?
I can do either one.
You're very confident.
Nakaoka must trust Omori
and put all his weight on Omori.
Okay.
Okay. I can do it.
I can do it. Slowly.
It's stable.
- Slowly.
- Okay.
- Slowly, slowly.
No! No!
No, stop for now. Stop.
Stop it first.
Oh, it's scary. It's so scary.
So scary.
But I might be able to do it.
He tries again.
"The second time"
His posture is stable.
Can he do it this time?
It depends on how you do it.
It depends on you.
Let's do our best. I'll...
- That's right. Go closer.
- I'll go closer.
Can you go closer?
- Can you do it?
- Yes.
- Almost there.
- Almost.
A bit more, a bit more...
They both fell in.
Omori. Omori.
Omori...
I can't get up! I can't get up!
They hurry to the bath.
The white briefs.
Is it briefs or panties?
Wasn't it panties?
How many times have we seen this?
Why? We nearly got it just now!
We could've made it, right?
Right?
Thanks.
Why is mine opened?
Yours is new.
What's this treatment?
Next, a video of
an amazing table tennis technique.
Roll it through the pipes
in the middle.
If the ball goes through
all the pipes and enters the cup,
it's successful.
First, practise
how to roll it straight.
Here I go.
They all bounced back!
Nakaoka's ability to play
table tennis is hopeless.
To make things worse,
the pipes will overlap
for a mere 0.1 seconds.
He can only count on
a coincidence in this challenge.
If it misses the pipe a bit...
Filming becomes a long battle.
How long have I been doing it
since morning?
Five hours.
- Five hours.
- That's dreadful!
He continues to hit it
for seven hours.
That must be tough.
At that time...
Here I go.
Three, two, one.
It went through.
Did it work?
So close!
- So close!
The timing and the track
were perfect,
but the cup's position
was a bit off.
- So close.
- Yeah.
So close!
What does Nakaoka think is
the reason behind the failures?
What?
It's the crew.
These people are careless.
They made the sliding board,
but they didn't fix it in place.
The pipe rolls down
when it's unstable.
After I do it once,
when they put the ring back,
they just threw it.
The pipes hit each other many times.
It happened many times,
and they make the same mistake.
The label of the pipe
is still stuck there,
and they could've used transparent
adhesive tape under the cup,
but they used a white one
for some reason.
They all don't care about it.
It doesn't work.
Next, he'll do a kind of sport
that he hasn't done for six months.
- The thing you're good at.
- Good at...
I don't even want to see it.
I just don't want to dive.
Nakaoka does
a forward dive and catch.
This time, he'll use
a one-metre springboard
and catch the frisbee.
I see.
You saw my bruises last time, right?
It hurts.
Will Nakaoka do it miraculously
in one go?
You can do it.
Three, two, one. Bong!
I remember it now.
It hurts a lot.
How did I do it?
I'm proud of myself.
Ow, it hurts.
It hurts-- Ouch!
This is awful.
The moment I jumped,
- I wanted to do that.
- It's best to catch it here.
It's a bit too low now.
Higher?
A bit forward.
He adjusts the position
of the flamingo.
Can he catch it this time?
I'll throw.
Three, two, one.
I didn't expect my back
to hurt so much.
The pain is dull.
It's so unexpected.
He continued to jump for two hours.
"Two hours later"
He tries it for the 26th time today.
How did I do it? Turn like this?
- I'll throw.
- Okay.
- Oh? Is he...
- Yeah.
Three, two, one.
I did it!
Nakaoka caught it successfully.
It feels so good!
It feels so good! I did it...
Now that I've done it,
this is my vacation.
Next, it's an action video
amidst cold weather.
Over here.
The scale is large!
It's Human Curling.
You spent a lot of money on it.
The course made on the frozen lake
is 50 metres long in total.
Nakaoka will gain his momentum
by sliding down the stand.
He passes if he stops on the Q logo.
Human Curling. How will it end?
On the Road of Victory
you made for me,
I will simply go towards the goal.
Looking forward to it.
Okay, here I come!
You can do it.
Go!
Slide!
Too fast.
It's very good. Very...
Amazing!
Amazing.
Beautiful.
Slide!
Nakaoka simply arrived at the goal.
It's very good! Very...
Impressive.
Amazing!
It's perfect.
Here he goes.
Oh, this song...
It's a huge loss.
You shouldn't spend money
on making QTube.
The amount of money you spent
doesn't reflect the laughter we get.
Amazing!
The last one is Captaincy Nakaoka.
This time,
it's Spring High's Top Eight,
Tokyo City University
Shiojiri High School
Women's Volleyball Team
who'll work with us.
Captain Nakaoka makes
his appearance from behind them.
All of you!
Are you going to do it?
Tokyo City University Shiojiri
High School Women's Volleyball Team!
Are you going to film
a funny video today?
The task he'll do is...
receive two volleyballs
simultaneously.
It's a video uploaded by the pro
volleyball team JT Marvellous.
Ready, go.
"Receive 2 volleyballs
at the same time"
Two players serve at the same time.
The other player receives them
with both hands.
This time, they'll change when
the ball returns to the setters.
They'll do it as a relay
and aim to do it successfully
three times in a row.
First, the high school students
will demonstrate it.
Is there anyone who is
the most suitable for this job?
Our libero.
Oh, the libero.
The libero is great.
Libero Kaho will do it.
Wow, this is so difficult!
You can take your time, the speed...
Somehow match your speed.
Wow, he's giving advice.
Wait, it's very difficult!
This is very difficult.
It's the most difficult challenge
so far. Will he succeed?
Let's do it.
If there are
three consecutive successes,
the mission is accomplished.
The tracks and speeds
of the volleyballs are different.
It's extremely difficult to catch
both of them at the same time.
- It's hard.
- It's difficult.
Okay, serve!
It's difficult to match.
No matter how many times they try,
nobody is successful.
It's difficult!
We've tried about 100 times,
but we haven't succeeded even once.
But 30 minutes after it started...
"First player, Kaho Araki"
You did it!
Libero Kaho did it successfully
for the first time.
- Impressive!
- One!
You're number one.
Will number two go?
Our show needs the second player.
Nakaoka isn't confident, so he asks
someone else to go first.
But a chance suddenly comes.
Ready, go.
You can do it!
That's one of Spring High's
Top Eight teams for you.
They keep it going.
Impressive!
Nakaoka is fired up
and ties his hair.
"Last, Captain Nakaoka"
He's doing it.
Please.
Please. Let's give it our all.
I'll hit them upwards.
Bring it on!
- You can do it!
- Good!
That's one of Spring High's
Top Eight teams for you.
They can even do the falling trick.
They're adorable.
- All of them.
- Together.
He started crying.
He's become a suspicious man
who broke into the gymnasium.
"Suspect, Soichi Nakaoka (43)"
Let's do it!
I'm sorry!
Chances keep coming.
Good! Good!
They have two successes again
right after they restart.
Okay, twice in a row.
Can he do it this time?
Okay, okay, okay.
Do your best.
Okay. Relax, relax. Let's do it!
Let's make it!
It's slow motion.
- Nice.
- Wonderful.
So close!
It hurts!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry!
After practising many times,
the students improved a lot.
Actually, the number of times
they did it is 532.
Impressive.
The number of times Nakaoka missed
after two successes is nine.
What do you say?
The director says it's enough.
You want to do it?
We want to do it.
You do?
Who wants to go home?
Who wants to do it?
Oh, we must do it.
"Oh, we must do it"
"Tokyo City University Shiojiri High
School Women's Volleyball Team"
Okay, let's give it our all!
Okay, let's do it!
All right!
Nice catch!
That was so close!
It's been four hours
since it started.
The time finally comes.
"Player one, Kaho Araki"
Yes! That's amazing!
"Player two, Sawa Enokizono"
You can do it! Yes!
Okay, go!
Okay, here I go.
All right.
I'm counting on you.
Please, please, please.
Here I go!
Bring it on!
Let's give it our all!
Yeah!
Nakaoka does a super-receive
with his foot.
Three people did it successfully
in a row.
We made it!
I can't go near, but we made it!
Oh, I gave you so much trouble!
City University!
Yeah!
Tokyo City University Shiojiri
High School Women's Volleyball Team,
thank you very much!
It feels so good!
When I was watching Nakaoka's video,
I thought, "How can we use this
to compete with TV dramas?"
Indeed.
How can we use this to fight against
TV dramas every time?
But that cameraman, though...
Who's that?
At last, he showed his underwear
and was funnier than Nakaoka.
Don't do that.
How can we fight against
Shibusawa Eiichi?
The one you hit the table tennis
ball through the pipes,
did you keep complaining?
There were cylinders, right?
They need to be in a straight line.
But if they hit each other
when they're put back,
they move a bit, right?
I was the one who fixed that
every time.
We did it for five hours.
It happened about 100 times.
I wondered how many times the
assistant director would hit them,
- but I had to do it.
- You're so noisy.
As the one doing it,
the misalignment was bothering me.
I did it 100 times, a bit of--
- That's enough!
- Shut up!
- Shut up.
- You're noisy.
But listen to me.
We understand.
When I did it when they
weren't perfectly aligned,
I missed it by one millimetre.
The last time?
If we had done it properly--
Yeah, that's your fault.
Me?
That's right.
- You should've fixed the cup.
- Yeah.
Do it if you had noticed.
"Me"?