The Quest.
Today's first segment
is a special project.
"Special"?
New Degawa Girls
challenge themselves
in The Quest's compulsory subject.
One day, we summoned Degawa.
What is it this time?
You'll do a dolphin show this time.
Didn't Madame Dewi and I perform
in a dolphin show before?
Eight years ago at Aqua World Oarai,
Degawa and Madame did a wonderful
performance in a dolphin show.
It was amazing.
I'll never forget that
in the actual performance,
the dolphin bit Madame.
Two or three days after filming,
she called me on my mobile
and went, "Tetsuro,
I'm going to sue The Quest!"
"I'm going to sue Nippon TV!"
She was furious when she called me.
I thought, "Why me?"
Many members of The Quest
had performed
in our compulsory subject,
dolphin show,
and our new Degawa Girls,
Yumeppe and Yokota
will do it together with Degawa.
The girls will have a harsh lesson.
Dolphin shows are rather tough.
They must become friends
with the dolphins first.
Madame and I became real friends
with the dolphins.
The girls will really be friends...
Wait, she was bitten
after becoming its friend?
What is the dolphin show
going to be like?
Welcome to The Quest.
Today, it's New Degawa Girls
Perform in A Dolphin Show,
and Asako Ito's Mystery Tour.
Wasshoi!
"Morisanchu"
Hello...
Hello!
Hi, everyone!
"Yumena Yanai"
"Mayuu Yokota"
This time, our new Degawa Girls,
Yumeppe and Yokota,
did The Quest's compulsory subject.
- Yes.
- A dolphin show.
They hadn't tried it before,
so it would be tough.
It wasn't the dolphin show
I imagined.
Many things were difficult,
but I enjoyed it at the end.
Different from the dolphin show
you thought?
Is that possible?
What do you two think about
how Tet-chan handled the dolphins?
Well...
- What?
- In the actual performance!
You'll be surprised.
"Yanai and Yokota
tries for the first time"
"Compulsory subject in The Quest"
You must be curious.
Start!
One, two...
"Mystery Tour in Kinki"
Three hours by car on Tomei
Expressway and surface streets,
New Degawa Girls
challenge themselves
in The Quest's compulsory subject.
Perform in a Dolphin Show
in Shizuoka.
We've come to...
Numazu!
It rained the moment we shouted.
It startled me.
Here at Osezaki coast,
you can see the famous Mount Fuji
on a sunny day,
and the view is stunning.
Hey, wait a minute.
What? The three of us?
What's going on?
That means they went filming
in another time?
I had no idea at all.
It really makes me feel that we,
the old girls, are unnecessary.
And we did our own makeup
and we're in our own outfits.
Isn't this wrong?
This time,
commentary by the old girls
will be added at the key points.
The three old girls
aren't here today,
so you can relax, right?
I'd like to see
our seniors' example.
For me, it's easier to talk
if they aren't here.
You say it so clearly
that it's refreshing.
Did you watch the dolphin show
Madame and I performed in?
I heard about it.
Do you mind?
These two girls claimed they've been
watching our show
and they're huge fans,
but I have doubts.
I do watch it.
- Yokota?
- I'll watch it.
I watch it. I watch it.
This is the stage
they'll perform on.
Izu Mito Sea Paradise.
Suruga Bay and Mount Fuji
are visible in this aquarium.
Actually, in 1930,
it became the first in the world
to have successfully bred a dolphin,
and it's an old aquarium
that is most established.
Now, let's have a look
at the technique they'll master.
This is the technique.
Two dolphins push a person up
on their soles in the move.
Lift.
Wow, this move.
Impressive!
It's a huge jump that goes
over three metres high.
They'll master this difficult move
in four days.
Their teacher is...
Nice to meet you.
Mr Yamada, who has been
a trainer for seven years.
The thing I'm most worried about
is the jump.
- Two dolphins do it together.
- Yes.
When Madame and I did it,
it was one.
If it's two, isn't it going to be
much more difficult?
To be honest,
I think it is very difficult.
But if it's successful,
- it's very high and it looks cool.
- It's scary.
Also, the difficult part
of this mission
is that instead of a pool,
the stage is the sea, which is
easily affected by the weather.
Also, Izu Mito Sea Paradise
has dolphin shows every day
throughout the year.
Because of the burden
on the dolphins,
they can't practise for a long time.
Let me introduce you to the two
dolphins who will be performing.
The one on the right is Sudachi,
the one on the left is Kabosu.
They're common bottlenose dolphins,
Sudachi and Kabosu.
They're both female,
but Kabosu is more shy.
Sudachi and Kabosu.
- Wow, they're greeting us.
- So cool.
First, they'll shake hands.
If they hate you now,
it'll be difficult later.
Okay.
Here they are.
Go shake their hands.
Why did you talk a bit like Madame?
Was that Madame?
No.
Here.
Yokota also did it successfully.
- Hurray!
- Wonderful.
But Yumeppe...
Here.
Amazing!
Oh, she hates you.
She couldn't make contact
with Kabosu.
That's right.
The dolphins will surely feel it
if you let them know how you feel.
He's full of confidence
after doing it once.
He talked like it's his job,
but he had only done it once.
- He only does it well at first.
- That's true.
First, the abilities of each of them
are checked in a pool.
First, it's swimming.
To perform with dolphins,
they don't flutter kick
to avoid scaring the dolphins,
and they must swim straight
with their arms only.
Don't make so much sound
in the water.
Be quiet, be quiet.
Regarding Degawa's swim,
the teacher...
makes this face.
He became The Thinker.
To make matters worse...
He can't climb up.
Degawa can't climb up by himself.
- Yumeppe, please...
- Yes?
I'm scared.
Why are you scared?
I'm asking you to pull me up.
Are you going to do your usual?
This isn't my usual.
I'm just asking you to pull me up.
Degawa fully intended
to pull her down.
Ready, go.
You can't beat me.
- She's strong.
- You can't beat me.
This old man
can't beat a 20-year-old anymore.
You can't beat her.
She's strong.
You're really strong.
The one who performed
the best among the three is...
Yokota did it the best.
Hurray!
Teacher, how was it different?
Her body was very straight.
She swam with her body straight,
that made it the best.
Next, it's diving.
I've never dived.
- In your whole life?
- Yeah.
Yumeppe, you too?
I used to dive into rivers.
Wow, you grew up in the wild.
How skilled is she?
It's rather good.
Yokota dives for the first time
in her life.
It looked clumsy,
but the teacher thinks...
Well done.
The teacher didn't use much power.
When the teacher jumps,
the water only splashes a little.
I'll just run there
and jump like that.
I'm scared.
- Here I go.
- Pull your chin back.
Okay, please dive.
It looks painful.
It hurts somewhere so low?
He's pulled out of the water
every single time.
Okay.
She's rather strong
if she can pull me up.
Also, they'll stay still
in the water.
When the dolphins push you up,
you have to stand straight,
push your legs up in front,
and keep them at this position.
When it's one dolphin, they can just
stand straight and wait,
but there are two this time,
so they need to spread their legs.
Good! Good!
But...
Wait, this is...
This posture is rather difficult
for a plump old guy.
The two young girls,
on the other hand...
Why is it so stable?
They did it easily.
Well done.
That face pisses me off.
Like, "I'm pretty, am I not?"
I'm not thinking that!
Or you wouldn't be able
to make that face!
- Okay.
Mr Degawa actually thinks
she's pretty.
Yes, for sure.
He wouldn't say it
if he didn't think she was cute.
Exactly...
Has he ever said that to you?
- No, no.
- No, right?
He doesn't think we're cute?
He pisses me off.
Day two of filming. They'll practise
with the dolphins today.
To learn how to lift,
the performer must get the dolphins
to push the soles of their feet.
Impressive.
Yumeppe goes first.
- So cool.
- Amazing!
It bent a little, but
it's successful on the first try.
Impressive! It's good.
Yokota is next.
Lie down... Well done!
She also does it successfully
on her first try.
People naturally tense up,
but if you can relax
right from the beginning,
and do it by feeling,
then you really have potential.
Hurray! I'm happy.
Maybe she is really cut out
to perform in a dolphin show.
Degawa is the last one.
What's the matter?
They don't come at all.
Why?
Really, why?
In that case, I'll join you.
We'll make the dolphins
get used to you first.
The teacher teaches him
step by step, and finally...
Oh, one pushes me.
That's good. Perfect.
It isn't perfect at all.
They didn't come near
at all earlier,
but now, one pushed your foot.
It's a great progress.
It started raining,
but they have many tasks to tackle,
so their practise continues.
Whether the rain pours
or a typhoon comes,
we have no time.
We have to do it.
This time, they'll practise Slider.
The dolphins will push them
when they're facing the front.
It's fast!
- Yokota, will you try Slider once?
- Yes.
If Yokota is next to try this,
it probably means
Yokota does it better.
Why are you provoking
her competitive mind?
I mean, it should be
Yumeppe's turn now.
If he changed that suddenly...
Because of the uncalled-for remark
Degawa made,
the atmosphere gets a bit tense.
Don't intentionally say things
that cause a falling-out.
- Really!
- Right?
He's a pro at making people quarrel.
He is, indeed!
We used to be close friends.
"Close friends"
doesn't sound right either.
Somehow, gradually...
In the middle of that, Yokota...
succeeded to do a Slider right away.
Hurray! I did it!
I think Mayuu really has potential.
Yumeppe?
It made me really fired up
- to do it successfully.
- I did it on purpose.
Can she do it?
Good, keep your body straight
and wait...
You're sliding.
Amazing!
Yumeppe succeeds.
Also...
Let go.
She even did a turn,
which hasn't been taught.
That's so impressive.
Wow, she's back.
Okay, I'll go now.
Please stay calm.
"Stay calm."
That's cool.
Come...
Relax, relax.
Hey, you stopped.
- Okay, come back.
- Are you kidding me?
Why?
Why don't the dolphins
go near Degawa?
Compared to the girls,
the way he dived was careless,
and he was unstable underwater.
- Teacher.
- Yes?
Starting tomorrow,
please focus on me.
- I'm in a bit of trouble.
- Yeah.
At the same time, Yumeppe and Yokota
finally start practising the Lift.
Teacher, we're in separate classes.
It's like we're
in different classes now.
We'll complete
one performance together.
- We're in the same class.
- Yes.
Day three of practise.
To become closer to the dolphins,
they start from looking after them.
Dolphins are as clever as humans,
they must look after the dolphins to
build a mutual-trust relationship,
or the dolphins
won't listen to them.
The girls in the Advanced Class
will practise the bold move, Lift.
After touching the dolphins,
spread the legs a little underwater,
stay still and wait,
the two dolphins
will push them up strongly.
But there are waves in the sea,
it's difficult to keep the body
still and wait.
It's okay, it's okay.
Or the dolphins can't push
when they go towards their feet.
Even if the dolphins can push well,
the force is rather strong,
so their knees will buckle
if they aren't used to it.
That's impressive...!
I felt like I jumped very high.
But you only jumped up this much.
You were startled
the moment you jumped,
and you backed away.
Your legs went to the front
and you fell down with your bottom
like you're sitting.
If you don't move back
and keep your legs straight,
you would've jumped higher.
I see.
Based on that, Yumeppe...
Amazing!
Instead of jumping up,
she was thrown to the front.
I see.
To improve, they'll keep practising
and get used to the height.
I still pull my behind to the back.
On the other hand, the dolphins
finally push Degawa's feet.
Okay, go left!
He's in another class.
That's the right side!
Amazing!
It's fast!
They're in two different classes.
- Hurray.
- Amazing!
And then...
Oh, it came out.
Oh, my contact lens came off.
We happened to film how Degawa
puts on his contact lens,
let's have a look.
This one...
Is it the other way round?
Is it okay?
- Darn it.
- I understand.
It doesn't go in if I don't look.
It came out.
It's the first time I see someone
spend so long to wear contact lens.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It goes in quickly when it does.
It won't go in
if you don't open your eye wider.
Is it in?
Is it in? It's in, right?
It's in?
The dolphins have also lost
their concentration,
so let's get psyched
and do it in one go.
He gets psyched
and goes in the water, but...
My contact lens came off again.
Please come up, then.
Why?
It ends as a failure.
If it comes off every time I dive,
it shouldn't be called one day.
It's one chance. One chance.
It costs me so much.
Contact lenses for one-day use
costs 100 yen, right?
I think you should worry more about
the dolphins not coming.
This is bad.
Day four of practise.
They'll practise with these today.
It's so cool!
Flyboard, an activity that uses
hydraulic pressure to stay midair.
It's perfect for getting used
to the power of the dolphins' push
and the height of the jump.
The young girls master it
in no time.
- That's impressive!
- Impressive.
I did it!
Oh, she went up!
Impressive!
She's waving!
The problem is this man.
He generally doesn't do
this sort of activities well,
and they're shelved many times,
but our Advisor this time
is totally different.
"1st TRY"
This is the real first attempt.
Amazing!
So cool!
He does it successfully in one try.
Why?
He hasn't practised,
if he can do it so well, we can
expect him to do the Dolphin Lift.
But...
Let's go.
It wasn't that easy.
But he can do it,
they're in the same class now.
I'm scared!
- Your contact lens fell out.
- What?
Your contact lens fell out.
I thought you were playing dumb.
This is my tear.
The two young girls
are struggling too.
It's different, after all.
They're done in different ways.
I wonder why my behind falls first.
That's how difficult a Lift
by two dolphins is.
She went higher, though,
the last one looked stupid.
I can't do anything
if water enters my nose.
I see. Do that when you practise,
but don't do it in the performance.
In the end, they couldn't learn it
in four days.
The training camp ends for now.
After that, they go to the aquarium
whenever they have time.
There are techniques besides jumping
they need to practise after all.
They'll stay still upside-down,
underwater.
- Cool.
- Impressive.
This is the result
of intense training.
Impressive.
So cool.
Do your best.
I'm in real trouble.
I'm saying "this is bad"
from the bottom of my heart.
I say "this is bad" on TV
all the time,
but there were times
I didn't think it was that bad.
Is that so?
But until the last moment...
I'm going to trust
Sudachi and Kabosu.
It's already a claim
of his dependence on the dolphins.
On the other hand,
Yumeppe and Yokota
each received intense training
for four days.
Who? Who? They also practised alone?
Yokota and Yumeppe did.
They couldn't do the techniques
during filming,
but they need to finish it.
Would you go alone?
- Sure.
- Of course I will.
It's filmed, right?
I'll go if you film me.
We'll go if they film us, right?
- You'll film, right?
- It's filming.
I'll be hesitant if you tell me
to just practise alone,
but I'll totally go if you film me.
Finally, it's the actual
performance.
"Actual Dolphin Show"
On the day
of the actual performance...
Finally, it's the day
of the actual performance.
What do you say, Yokota?
I'll do it.
Oh, you can do it?
And you, Yumeppe?
I'm very worried,
but if I'm very nervous,
the dolphins can sense it,
so the best thing to do is to relax.
Okay, let's show them the power
of our new Degawa Girls.
- Okay.
Yumeppe, say your Ondo.
- My Ondo?
- That's right.
Choose one you like.
Yumeppe does her best.
No...
Not Yumeppe.
The three of us will work together
and do our best!
What "Yumeppe does her best"?
But you told me to say my Ondo.
Okay, do it, Yokota.
What is "Ondo"?
Wait...
This is incredible!
The one that you do this?
No, that's Bon Dance.
Finally, they'll show the result
of their practise this summer.
Do your best!
Let's do it.
A dolphin show performed by
Degawa and the new Degawa Girls
starts now.
Hello, viewers.
Now, Tetsuro Degawa and...
the new Degawa Girls will perform.
Please watch our dolphin show!
It's show time!
- Do your best.
Okay!
First, they will work together
in Tail Flipping.
The dolphins
first raise their tails,
the three of them
will match their movement.
Ready, go!
- Yes!
- What?
Only Degawa's is sloppy.
Now, Yokota will perform.
Okay, let's do it.
First, it's the Slider.
She is smiling,
but she is determined
to do this project.
She had been shedding
tears of frustration
when she practised on her own.
I'm angry at myself.
Now is the time
to show people the result.
Wow, it's good!
Yokota's performance is successful.
She goes around the stage
in a big circle.
She performed well
as the first performer.
Next, she will ride
on a dolphin's back.
Impressive!
This is also successful.
Amazing. She's waving.
Wow, you're doing it.
Amazing!
I did it!
Lastly,
it's the most difficult Lift.
Has she overcome her fear
of heights?
- Let's see!
- You can do it.
Do your best.
Beautiful!
She even made a gesture
and did it successfully.
She fell straight down beautifully.
It's beautiful!
Well done, Yokota!
It was successful.
How was it, Teacher?
I think it was perfect.
Her smile was the best.
- I see, when she jumped.
- That's right.
It was brilliant.
I feel relieved.
Right?
What?
"An insensitive old man"
Don't do that, it's nasty.
- This old guy is awful.
- Exactly!
I know how Yokota felt
and I was touched.
What's wrong with that guy?
- Did you get emotional?
- Yes.
Yes. Yokota came to practise alone
on another day.
I see.
Okay.
- Next, it's Yumeppe's turn.
- Do your best.
After Yokota's success,
she can't perform worse.
How will she do?
That's right...
Wow, the body above her waist
is above the water.
It's a dynamic Slider.
Good! Good!
Next, it's the Ride.
Hold out...
- Good!
- She's holding out!
She's swaying,
but managed to do it successfully.
Beautiful!
Amazing!
She held out.
She swayed a bit halfway.
Lastly, it's the Lift.
Will she be able to jump beautifully
without pressing her nose?
Beautiful!
Yumeppe did a big, beautiful jump.
- Beautiful!
- Wow, beautiful!
- It was fantastic!
Yokota passed it to Yumeppe,
Yumeppe passed it to me.
Lastly, it's the anchor.
This is bad.
- Degawa is the last performer.
- He looks determined.
I haven't seen
your successful performance,
so please show me you can do it.
Okay, challenge accepted.
What is it?
First, it's the Slider.
Will the dolphins push him?
Relax!
Are they here? They are.
The dolphins pushed him!
"Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha"
It's a rather small circle,
but he managed to do it.
So small!
I did go in a circle.
And the Ride, which he hasn't done
successfully before.
Ride.
Make it in the actual performance.
Ride on the dolphin.
You can do it!
Good!
It was only five metres, but he rode
on the dolphin for the first time.
I did it!
The last one is the bold move, Lift.
It's this one.
Can Degawa jump?
So low!
He tried hard to jump,
but it was 20 centimetres.
He's raising his fist in triumph.
But the two new Degawa Girls
accomplished the mission
successfully.
Good.
The dolphin show is a huge success!
Hurray!
Advisor, Yumeppe, Yokota, well done!
Yokota made lots of effort.
It was difficult and it was quite
high up and I was scared,
and Mr Degawa attempted
to cause a falling-out.
I actually wasn't trying
to make you two fight.
He says no.
I wanted to ignite Yumeppe's
competitiveness
to make her succeed.
You didn't need to meddle.
It was uncalled for.
Let's move on to our next segment.
Imoto, please.
Okay. Next, it's this.
Asako Ito's Mystery Tour!
A two-hour bullet train ride
from Tokyo,
Asako Ito's Mystery Tour in Kinki.
Kinki!
You're curious, right?
The thing that catches my attention
is the mosquito near her eye.
A mosquito is here.
No way.
- It's swollen already.
- Amazing!
It's going to be itchy.
It's bothering me.
She has come to Tandenji Temple
in Kyoto.
It's a 300-year-old
historical temple, but...
This is bad. Look.
The wall of the hall
is full of scribbles.
The monk, Gyokaku Horio, knows why.
This temple is called Tandenji,
it's commonly called
the Scribble Temple.
- Scribble Temple?
- Yes.
There are Ema tablets when you go
to shrines or temples,
but instead of those,
we want Daikokuten
to see them more clearly,
so people write their wishes
on the wall.
- Oh, they're people's wishes?
- That's right.
The unique way of praying
started about 60 years ago.
If you offer 300 yen,
anyone can write on the wall.
- I wrote it.
- What did you write?
"I pray Imoto won't call Mr Ishizaki
"husband" in her radio show again."
Why shouldn't I?
I don't understand.
There's a comedian named Ayako Imoto
who married our director,
Mr Ishizaki.
- I see.
- I explained to the monk.
She keeps saying "my husband"
unnecessarily in her radio show.
It's out of spite?
The walls of Daikoku Hall
are painted white every December,
so visitors can write new wishes
on them again the next year.
So behind these wishes,
the wishes written last year
are still there.
- Lovely! They accumulate?
- Yes.
So if your wish comes true,
it's because various people
behind you helped you.
That's why it comes true.
Isn't this wonderful?
It's a place where a show like ours
shouldn't come.
- That's not true.
- No?
I agree with her.
The Mystery Tour in Kinki
starts now.
First, solve the mystery.
A mysterious man who draws
enormous portraits.
First, solve the mystery.
A mysterious man who draws
enormous portraits.
- Hello.
This is Mr Naoki Shimizu.
How big are the portraits you draw?
It's about two square kilometres.
I can draw anywhere in the city.
Wow, scary.
I don't get it at all.
What is the enormous portrait
drawn in the city?
GPS app.
The tracking function
of the running app
colours the places
I've passed through,
and I use it to draw pictures on
the ground. It's called running art.
- Oh, it's Bakatono-sama.
- Yes.
- Impressive.
- This is interesting.
Not anyone can be drawn.
It depends on whether
the map fits or not.
- It does.
- It does a bit, right?
Koshien Stadium
is in Nishinomiya City.
Two roads to its north
converge at the ideal angle,
so it's perfect to be the vertical
lines of Mr Degawa's chubby face.
That's it.
To draw Degawa, the running distance
is about 21 kilometres.
Go!
Oh, it's been a long time.
She only runs at this location.
By the way, you're drawing
Mr Degawa's mouth now.
The width of his mouth
is about 500 metres,
but she'll draw the upper lip,
the lower lip and wrinkles,
so she'll run six kilometres
only for that.
"Distance of the mouth: 6km"
Asako was full of energy
at the start,
but after running 10 kilometres,
every part of her body
starts to hurt.
May I announce
which part of Asako hurts now?
I've been feeling pain here
since the start.
Here, right? And here, and...
- At that time...
- What happened?
Here, and here...
- What?
- What is it?
Something came out?
Mysterious liquid came out
from Asako's body.
Was that sweat?
That's right,
it was a large amount of sweat.
What?
- No way.
- Where was it stored?
- You didn't know?
- Are you kidding me?
Are you kidding me?
That was scary.
When you saw that,
do you want to do something for me?
So she'll do a Bicycle Challenge.
You now run one kilometre
in 7 minutes and 40 seconds.
So slow!
From now on, if you run 1 kilometre
in less than seven minutes,
you ride a bicycle
for two kilometres.
If it's shorter than six minutes,
you get 4 kilometres on a bicycle.
We'll do this challenge.
Oh, no, I couldn't hear you at all.
I only remember seven and four.
Too many numbers?
Maybe.
The Bicycle Challenge starts.
If she runs one kilometre
as fast as she can,
she'll get a reward of a maximum
of four kilometres on a bicycle.
It's different.
Your pace is good. 60 metres to go.
- Will she make it?
- You can do it!
One kilometre!
Yes! One kilometre!
- Six minutes and 18 seconds.
- Impressive!
You can't complain.
She gets four kilometres
on a bicycle.
Good for you.
Ouch.
Her hip is groaning.
I should've kicked it up
before I ride.
Why don't you just go forward?
Will it go up?
Ouch.
Her whole body is worn out,
but she'll run again
in the remaining five kilometres.
Let's say,
can this be a triathlon?
What do you mean?
Running,
cycling,
riding on a car.
It'd be nice to have
a ride on a car.
What am I trying to solve?
The mystery of a man
who draws enormous portraits.
We've already solved the mystery.
A long time ago.
It's the last spurt,
the goal is right ahead.
It's late at night.
And then...
- The goal?
- It's the goal!
It's the goal.
The goal. The goal.
What will Degawa's portrait
look like?
Let's see it.
Ready, go.
Mr Degawa!
What?
She ran 21 kilometres
in Nishimiya City,
and it took about five hours...
to finish a huge Degawa
that's two square kilometres big.
Are you satisfied with the result?
Very satisfied.
This is how much I've run.
I'm scared to think
about tomorrow's shooting.
Mr Degawa, what should I do?
What will they make me do tomorrow?
It's sprinting tomorrow.
Why?
Next, a mysterious man who goes
against human evolution.
It's this person. Please come here.
What? What? He's fast!
Are you kidding me?
That's human, right?
A human who sprints on four legs.
Hello!
I'm four-legged Kenichi Ito!
Nice to meet you.
Mr Ito is the person who turned
quadruped walking into a sport.
Humans evolved from four-legged
to two-legged,
but Mr Ito goes against it.
We use our forelegs as hands
to use tools,
so we evolved for the convenience.
So regarding running speed,
from four-legged to two-legged
is devolution.
I've been running like this
for 18 years,
and my speed isn't any slower
than a two-legged runner.
First, they'll have a 100-metre race
to demonstrate Mr Ito's ability.
Besides Asako,
our filming crew's fast runner,
cameraman Odani, will join the race.
His record when he was a student
was 11.20 seconds.
It was in high school, right?
Ready, get set, go!
Asako is still exhausted
from the marathon,
and drops out early.
He's fast.
It's a race between the four-legged
man and our fastest runner.
Who will win?
So cool!
Mr Ito wins.
Mr Ito is a world record holder
of quadruped running.
His record at that time
was 15.71 seconds.
He's fast!
Really, it reminds me
of the summer day
I ran after my dog when it ran away.
It's called quadruped running,
but it's profound.
- Yes... I see...
- This is bad, her body...
- It's quite good.
- She ran for so long.
First, you'll learn how to trot.
What kind of animal?
Dogs, cats, horses... Most
of the four-legged animals trot.
You walk like this.
It changes to a form
called bounding halfway.
- It's like this.
- Yes, I did that.
Some of the crocodiles,
and wallaby do this.
- Wallaby.
- Yes.
Also, the foot and the hand on
the same side move together
that is the way that giraffes and
elephants walk and amble.
And knuckle walk, the way gorillas
and chimpanzees walk, are included.
Knuckle walk.
Start!
Mr Ito believes the fastest human
runner will be a four-legged runner,
so he's making effort to recruit
and train runners.
You're strong.
Very good! Very good!
For the time being, the number
of runners in the world is 150.
Let's see the result of her practise
today in Asako's
100-metre quadruped race.
Ms Asako, if you can run 100 metres
in less than one minute,
the quadruped running
women's section will be shocked.
Running 100 metres in less than
one minute on the first day is fast?
It's awesome.
They'll be shocked.
Ready, get set, go!
Asako started
with the bounding she's good at.
- Watch out.
- Do your best, Asako!
Do your best...
But she slowed down already.
Do your best.
And finally, she crawls.
She ran a marathon yesterday
and runs on all fours today,
but she still works hard
without any complaint.
That's what is good about Asako.
Do your best.
Good...
Do your best!
Then she reaches the finish line
by sheer determination.
Her time is far from
her goal, one minute.
It's 2 minutes and 38 seconds.
It's the goal.
"Record: 2:38.00"
Places that are different
from yesterday's hurt.
Next, mysterious luminous bodies
that run about in darkness.
She comes to a gymnasium.
And then...
Wow, amazing!
Wow, it's so beautiful!
Are they shining ribbons?
Numerous lights run around
in darkness.
So cool.
They are actually ribbons
with LED light.
It's so beautiful.
The latest device was developed by
Stage Technology Group, mplusplus,
and it's manipulated by dancers
to create a beautiful stage.
It's so cool.
Asako will try this
to conclude the tour.
I see.
Children might not know,
but ribbon is Asako's special trick.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Minami Asakura, 51 years old.
I'm so annoyed.
51-year-old Minami is annoyed!
She took the world by storm in 2009.
I didn't.
Nice to meet you.
She'll be taught by members of
the dance team, Via Colorguard.
In a performance competition
that uses flags, the Japan Cup,
they had been the national champion.
First, she'll use a common ribbon
to practise the choreography.
Raise your left arm gradually.
Ouch.
Wait, Ms Asako...
I'm sorry.
I'm going to say "ouch"
every now and then,
please ignore me.
I'll probably keep saying that.
The highlight is to wave the ribbon
and move acrobatically.
Your left leg... That's right.
Ouch...
Kneeling is already difficult.
- I'll stay like this?
- Yes.
- Right leg...
- Sit down...
Ouch! The transmitter.
Asako is hurting everywhere.
Actually, she had filmed at other
locations that abused her body.
First, she went to see the man who
lifts the tallest Styrofoam tower,
and became his pupil.
Asako aimed to take 10 layers
and got trained, but...
She couldn't do it
no matter how long she practised.
Her beige T-shirt changed colour
because of her sweat.
A lot of sweat.
Wow, that's messy.
You shouldn't wipe mud on it.
I didn't know what I was doing.
Also, in Osaka, she soaked
in a too-powerful hot tub.
Does it come right after I press?
It's a powerful hot tub.
Then, quadruped running,
and a 21-kilometre marathon.
Here, and here... what?
It's just adding insult to injury.
And the mosquito at the opening.
Ouch.
At the same time, a LED ribbon.
This time, Asako will be
the centre dancer.
If she makes a mistake,
it'll ruin the show.
This is bad.
The towel to prevent my sweat
from flying everywhere
is going to fall
after absorbing my sweat.
This towel is used to absorb
the sweat from Asako's scalp,
it's commonly called Asako Roll.
Can I change this?
I can't let anyone touch this.
It looks like a rubbish bag.
It's heavy.
She practised so hard
that the towel was soaking wet.
Now, the actual performance
by Asako with Via Colorguard,
a LED Ribbon Performance.
This is Asako?
Impressive.
So cool...
Maybe it isn't me... Is it me?
This is me?
Don't I look amazing?
It's so beautiful.
You're doing it.
Amazing.
Beautiful.
We can't tell where Asako is now,
but the show is beautiful.
It's beautiful.
It's impressive.
There she is.
"Asako"
Her name is shining.
Asako moves to the centre again.
The climax is her solo part.
Amazing.
So cool...
It must have hurt to do this.
She is hurting everywhere,
but she performed successfully.
Amazing.
So cool!
Ouch.
Ouch...
How was the tour?
Well, I think that
the programme wasn't right.
Have you forgotten?
I'm 51.
That's all for the Mystery Tour
of sweat and tears.
Don't use this to conclude it!
The editing was done
with ill intention.
Exactly.
The editing was really nasty.
She wiped her face with a towel
and opened her eyes,
but her eyelids got a bit stuck.
What was that?
They got a bit stuck
and went up late.