The Quest.
First up is a popular segment,
Degawa travel guidebook.
It will take place
in Yaeyama Islands,
which are 400 km away from
the Okinawa mainland.
Degawa has visited
this area several times,
and he boasts
that it's like a backyard to him.
Ishigaki Island,
Taketomi Island, Iriomote Island,
Kohama Island,
and Kuroshima Island.
That area is known for
its beautiful ocean
and beautiful islands.
There's a lot of them.
He proudly proclaims
what is common knowledge.
Why do you go there?
It's because I like it.
Only reason I go to the island is
because I love it.
When a mountain climber is asked
why they climb a mountain,
"Because it's there."
Why do people go to an island?
It's because they love it.
Well, but with this example,
it should be "Because it's there."
His travel companion is Madam Dewi.
Why would you use this picture?
I would like you to take a picture
of Madam Dewi for a calendar.
I see. I see.
It won't just be a calendar.
It's going to be a collection
of photographs.
The last collection of photographs
before her death.
Dewi and Degawa's trip.
How will the calendar turn out?
"This program was broadcast
29 November 2020"
The Quest has started. Tonight,
we have Degawa travel guidebook
and Lotti Nakaoka's QTube.
Yeah!
So we have Degawa travel guidebook.
So, Madam, how was it to go
on location with him?
Tetsuro said it's like his backyard,
but there were so many things
he didn't know.
- You shock me! Come on!
- He's just like me.
You immediately betray me on camera.
You shock me!
I see.
This is wonderful.
You're fighting. It's cute.
It's going to be a collection of
photographs. Look, this one too.
Hand power.
Hand power. Thanks.
I can't even button one.
Help.
1,950 kilometres away from Tokyo.
Madam Dewi and Degawa's trip...
Degawa travel guidebook
in Yaeyama Islands.
We are here
in Ishigaki!
Wonderful!
Ishigaki Islands, the entrance
to the Yaeyama Islands.
Their trip starts on the westernmost
tip of Ishigaki Island,
Uganzaki, with its beautiful
white lighthouse and cliffs.
What is this place?
Is it known for suicides?
No!
Stop it! That's horrible.
Shut up!
"Ha ha ha"
- She's laughing.
- It's a splendid view here.
Yes, it is magnificent.
I really want to show it,
but you stand out more.
Madam,
you sure don't disappoint me.
You're fluttering away again today.
I'm fluttering. Yes, I am.
I mean...
This time, Degawa will take
pictures in Yaeyama Islands
for the calendar.
That's amazing.
In addition, he'll challenge
using the selfie stick.
What is this? It says SOS.
Emergency SOS? What is that?
How do you press the shutter?
This? Two minutes later?
One minute later?
Now, let's go get a picture
for the calendar!
First up is Degawa's recommendation,
a miraculous beach where a boat
seems to float in the air.
It can only be seen in water
that's highly transparent.
We actually went searching
for similar scenery...
We have to walk for 15 minutes?
How about we go, "Wow, beautiful!"
and pretend like we saw it.
"Pretend like we saw it"
What is this?
The conditions weren't met,
and they failed.
So I thought about it.
If I think about it,
there's no need to go abroad
because Japan has such a place!
- Really?
- Yes.
That place is here, the Kabira Bay.
We're almost there.
- First, they'll go to Kabira Bay.
- They're such good friends.
Madam, please take
your eye mask off.
Ah! I see.
- It's wonderful.
- It's beautiful.
One of the magnificent views
of Ishigaki Island, Kabira Bay.
Michelin for travel rated this place
three stars.
It's a place you'd want to visit
at least once.
- It's beautiful.
- Isn't it really beautiful?
I like the islands too.
- I think we can be hopeful here.
- I agree.
Captain, you know how they have
a boat in the air
on a postcard and stuff?
I would appreciate it if you
could take us to that spot.
Right, the sunlight
has to reflect on the sand
to create a shadow for it
to look like the boat is in the air.
The sandy spots are desirable.
If we stop around there, it won't
look like the boat is in the air?
How about here?
- I see.
- I think it's good.
Captain, I think it's good.
- Stop! Stop!
- Drone can stop too.
Yes.
The staff will film them from afar.
Were they successful in taking
a picture of a floating boat?
Ah, but it's pretty.
It's beautiful.
It's really beautiful.
Madam, I can't see anything at all.
Ah! That's wonderful.
Yes, it's great. Stop it.
This one. This one is great!
Degawa travel guidebook.
Next, a meal.
It's a steakhouse
that may be the best in Japan.
Oh, you exaggerate everything.
- No! No!
- Best in Japan? Please!
Those who know, know,
but those who don't, don't know.
That is usually the case.
That restaurant is located on
the eighth floor of this building.
Steak &amp; Restaurant PAPOiYA.
Chef Ozawa is the owner chef.
- I'll have my usual.
- Your usual?
Which one is your usual one?
It's filet steak.
Just trust me on this one.
I want you to trust me.
Then I'll have that too.
Wonderful. You're very compliant.
This is the filet steak
of Ishigaki beef
that Degawa says
is the best in Japan.
They'll have it medium rare
with beautiful red meat.
- That looks delicious.
- Please enjoy your first bite
without anything.
Please add some salt
for your second bite.
After that, please enjoy it
whatever way you like.
Madam has enjoyed delicious steaks
all over the world.
What is her opinion?
It's delicious.
I'm glad.
Her face is beaming with a smile.
She never reads between the lines.
You know, she's this...
She'll say whatever
she wants to say.
I'm so glad. That smile is sincere.
She can't fake her smile.
Seriously.
Since they're here,
I think I'll try these sauces.
Please.
How does it taste with sauce?
Oh...
I guess she doesn't need the sauce.
Exactly.
Degawa travel guidebook,
tonight's lodging is...
here.
This traditional, old-fashioned
Okinawan house with a red roof
has been converted into an inn.
It's a villa.
- This is great.
- That's cute.
Living and dining rooms are right
there after you enter the house,
and on both sides
are two Japanese rooms.
You take one,
and I'll take the other.
Huh?
What? What's wrong, Madam?
She's not saying anything.
And when she sees the bathroom...
There's a tub that's there.
What? the tub is just there?
You can stay here.
I'm going to a hotel.
Madam, we are both staying here.
Emergency meeting!
I got this place for you to get
the full Ishigaki Island experience,
with this typical
Ishigaki-style inn.
No, thank you.
The exterior is great.
It seems clean, and it's very nice.
I think this place is great
- for students to come in a group.
- Right, I agree.
Madam, do you really prefer
to stay at a hotel?
Really seriously.
On the second day, they leave
Ishigaki Island for Taketomi Island.
It's six kilometres away
and 10 minutes on a ferry.
While they wait for departure,
they'll go to Degawa's usual spot.
Degawa's travel guide style
is to eat something sweet here.
It's delicious.
It's really delicious.
- Thank you very much.
- Then...
This is cute too.
Oh, no! She'll take it.
She'll take it?
Could you sell it to me
for 1,000 yen?
Dewi's travel guide style is to buy
whatever she likes immediately.
- Madam, really?
- Yes.
- No, that's fine.
- No, no.
- No, no, you better take it.
- It's fine.
For sure.
It actually costs 3,000 yen,
you know.
Honestly.
Oh, should I give you more?
Should I give you 2,000 yen?
No, it's fine.
Then they finally head over
to the ferry station.
- What is that a statue of?
- Cute.
Ah, I'm impressed that you noticed.
Former WBA light flyweight champion,
a living legend of Ishigaki Island,
the statue of Yoko Gushiken.
They get a picture for memories too.
Ah! That fighting pose is great.
You're fighting! That's cute.
It's cute.
- That's great.
- She's cute.
I don't know why, but it seems
like a really good calendar.
That was super good!
And the Taketomi Island
that Degawa adores is this.
The circumference of the island
is nine kilometres.
Its population is 350.
However, they get
500,000 tourists annually.
The most common way to enjoy
the island is to rent a bicycle.
I always go to this bicycle shop
whenever I come here.
And I call the lady of the shop
my Taketomi mum.
What she always says to me is
not "Welcome"
but "Welcome home."
There you go again!
- Isn't that great?
- Are you serious?
I can't help but come because
I want her to say, "Welcome home."
That bicycle shop
he's talking about is this.
Tomori rent-a-cycle.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hello, excuse me.
Is Mum here?
She's not here right now.
She's at home?
- I think so.
- I see.
- Then I'll go see her at the house.
- Okay.
- What? You know her home?
- Yes.
Mum's home is five minutes on foot.
This is Mum's home,
with those cute flowers.
Now, will his Taketomi Mum
say, "Welcome home," to him?
Mum.
- Oh!
- Mum!
"Taketomi Mum, Tami Tomori"
Welcome home.
See? She said, "Welcome home."
Did you hear that, Madam?
Welcome home.
This is Madam Dewi,
my special guest.
I don't know why...
It seems like a different show now.
Madam here is 80 years old.
I'm the same age!
Then I'll get a picture
of Mum and Madam together.
- We will keep our distance.
- You keep your distance.
It's no longer "The Quest"
but "Kazoku ni Kanpai."
"Kazoku ni Kanpai (NHK)"
Madam, you learned how to ride
a bike on The Quest before.
Right. I forgot it already.
- What?
- To get on it at first is...
- I need you to hold it.
- Please be careful.
Okay, I'll hold it.
Now, will the Madam remember
how to ride a bike?
Oh, no!
I'm going to let go now.
- Okay, let go.
- Yes.
Good job!
All right!
I'm going to chase her now!
I'm going straight.
Madam can't stop,
so she's going to keep on going.
"Ha ha ha"
She can't stop once she gets going.
That's her life.
Excuse me, did you see Madam Dewi?
She went that way?
Thank you!
There she is!
- Madam!
- Degawa finally caught up with her.
One word?
TV.
Then...
Madam, I see something.
I prefer that over a bike.
- Let's go on that.
- Buffalo.
So now they ride
on a buffalo carriage.
This is pretty too.
They search for scenery
suitable for a calendar.
- This is pretty.
Those flowers...
Mizutani, what do I do?
Those flowers
are hard to take...
How do I focus on Madam?
You just touch it a little.
As long as you see a yellow square.
You totally suck.
Now, here's a collection of photos
taken on Taketomi Island.
First, Madam tries Yaeyama Soba,
a recommendation by Degawa,
for the first time.
How do you like it?
The whole family is watching you.
It's delicious. It's very light.
- The soup is very nice.
- Yes, it is.
A man is watching Madam Dewi eat.
"What is she going to say?"
He looks concerned.
A fresh pineapple juice that Degawa
says is the best in the world.
That looks delicious.
That's great.
Isn't it delicious?
It's delicious. I'll compliment you.
Shall we get the shot
of you drinking it?
This is definitely not
calendar material.
Look at this old man and old lady,
drinking pineapple juice.
Who would want a calendar like that?
And boarding
at Taketomi Island is...
This is it.
- I see.
- Hello.
I've been expecting you.
Hoshinoya Taketomi Island.
It's a high-end resort
with a traditional-style settlement
in a lot that's
approximately 20,000 tsubo in size.
Mr Degawa, welcome home.
Oh, it's so touching.
Stop lying!
You're making her say it!
No, I'm not making her say it!
I think "Welcome back" is good.
"Welcome home" is a bit...
That's what's heart-warming
about it.
The room they'll stay in is a villa
with traditional architecture.
It costs 11,000 yen per night.
- The bathroom...
- Isn't this bathroom cute?
It's cute.
They get lots of couples here?
- They were all couples.
- You're right.
We are like a couple too.
Lovebirds?
And the last calendar photograph
they aim for in Taketomi Island is
a sunset on the west pier.
A great view of Iriomote Island
can be seen from the pier.
It's an Instagenic spot
of Taketomi Island.
I've been to Taketomi a lot,
but I haven't seen the sunset
on the west pier.
- I see.
- So I wanted to go as well.
But, you know, sunsets
happen every day.
They happen 365 times
on 365 days a year. You can see
the sunset all over the world.
It's nothing rare.
That?
I'm shocked. I thought you
would say it has 365 colours,
365 faces. I thought it was going
to be a good story,
but, surprisingly,
it was the opposite.
- Ah, but it's great.
- It's great.
It's nice.
Ah! It's like a mirror.
It's very still.
This is magnificent.
Madam,
we might not belong here.
You're right.
It's full of couples!
Why don't you two become a couple?
I see.
That was a wonderful idea just now.
So...
They take a picture
with the feel of a couple.
It's wonderful.
- See?
- It's pretty.
I went too far.
What is this?
I only touched it a bit,
and it went off.
I know.
Convenience is an inconvenience.
They took pictures
with different poses
until the sun set completely.
This is great.
- Oh, this one is pretty too.
- It's pretty.
This is cool.
This is no joke, Madam.
It's going to be a photo collection.
How about we use our pictures
for all 12 months?
- Good work.
- To Taketomi's night.
- Magnificent dinner.
- What is this?
Hot pot with Ishigaki beef, pork,
and seasonal vegetables,
Shabushabu style.
Their speciality is this vegetable,
Peucedanum.
When you eat a bunch,
your life extends by a day.
- There.
- However...
Longevity, there.
Some meat too.
Meat over greens!
You go ahead and have some pork.
There she goes again.
I really do question your human
nature when you say stuff like that.
- I gave you plenty of meat.
- You have.
I just got a little bit. One-third.
- It's not just a little bit.
- I gave you two-thirds.
- I gave you meat too.
She's 80 years old,
but she still argues over meat.
That's the best secret
behind longevity.
I think so too.
To finish the trip,
they head to Kohama Island,
the belly button of Yaeyama Islands.
The photograph they aim for is...
We'll go to phantom island.
- Phantom island?
- Yes.
Those who know, know this island,
and those who don't, don't.
You say it like you've seen it,
but it's your first time too, right?
Yes, it is.
It's about 30 minutes by boat
to the island.
Captain, are you a little worried
about the weather?
Yes, it looks like it's going
to rain today. So it's hard.
Say we go there,
but what if it's a boring island?
What are you going to do about it?
If you aren't pleased with it,
then please scold me.
And the moment the camera
stops rolling, I'll scold the staff.
Just like the captain said, both
the weather and the sea are rough.
And Madam starts to lose her temper.
Oh, no!
Look at those waves!
Did you location-hunt properly
beforehand?
Did you take a boat like this?
And 10 minutes later...
It could be seen towards
the right side.
We see it now, Madam!
Which one?
Is it that white place?
That's not an island.
It's not an island?
Oh, no. Oh, no.
This?
Are you ridiculing me?
Your calendar is the main thing,
right?
If you would stand there...
and we take a picture of you
from afar, I think it'll be great.
- Like she's standing in the sea.
- I mean...
What?
However, Madam seems hesitant,
but something changes her mind.
It was the mermaid costume.
We were so certain she'd scold us.
- Mermaid?
- I think you'd be a great mermaid.
Oh, how pretty.
If I put on this costume, it might
make the photograph interesting.
She is able to do anything
for a laugh.
That's what's magnificent
about Madam.
Amazing!
The staff leaves the two of them
on the island and backs off.
Then...
miraculously, the sun shows up!
"Miracle"
Please take a look.
This truly is the phantom island.
Also known as South Barasu Island.
Coral pieces were gathered
by the current
to create this island.
Wow! It's beautiful!
The sun came out!
Yes! Miracles do happen!
Dewi and Tetsuro
make miracles happen!
- The island is getting smaller.
- It really is.
That's fast.
We take a calendar picture before
they become seaweed themselves.
- Pretty!
- This is nice.
This is the calendar shot!
Help!
This island is soon gone!
Rescue me first.
Degawa travel guidebook.
Calendar project is a success!
Madam and Tetsuro, great work!
That was wonderful.
There's something wrong
with this director.
He barges in
while I'm taking a bath.
It was total chaos,
but those scenes weren't there.
- Director!
- Again!
He's done it again.
I think that was edited out
because her chest was exposed
when she went,
"Cut it out, Tetsuro!"
They were exposed?
You just put those round things
on there.
- Those round things?
- Does that work?
Coming up next,
Lotti Nakaoka's QTube.
Yeah!
Nakaoka, where did you go this time?
I went to Kumamoto,
where you are from.
Previously, you took back my title
as the first-class comedian.
He tried to be cool.
Because I tried
to act a little cool.
He was trying to act cool in front
of those female volleyball players.
He was trying to act cool.
- Your status was stripped.
- Right.
So this time, I'm going to try
to get that status back.
I did my best.
Then I'm going to watch
with my eyes wide open.
Okay!
The world has several YouTubers
that film and upload funny videos.
With this project,
we go on location with them
and aim to make a video that makes
the whole world laugh.
It's called...
QTube.
Hello! Lotti Nakaoka here!
I'm here in Aso, Kumamoto,
right now.
Now, can you guess what I'm doing
right now?
- What is with this angle?
- He's walking.
"Promoting Kumamoto's sights"
Is he on Mount Aso?
- He's walking the summit.
- The correct answer is...
I'm enjoying
a Japanese plume grass maze.
Aso's somma is the number one site
for Japanese plume grass.
Japanese plume grass maze
is a seasonal feature of autumn.
First, he'll use this maze
for a challenge.
There's a B course that's 150 m
long. Can you finish it in a minute?
150 m in a minute is a sure thing.
By the way, if you can't reach
the goal in a minute,
this will be flying
out of your back.
That's scary. What is that?
What is this?
It's a PET bottle. It's hot.
It's hot.
It's a backpack-style super-hot
PET bottle rocket.
I honestly don't want
this hot water on me,
but then again, I sense the passion
of the staff...
- who made this.
- It is a nice feeling.
Nakaoka's super-hot PET
bottle rocket. What will happen?
This is scary.
The rocket will be launched by
the staff who will run behind him.
If you go too far from me,
the rocket may launch from tension.
So make sure to keep
within two metres of me.
Can't you control that part?
- That would be irritating.
- Start!
Oh, boy... Go for it.
This is so annoying.
Oh, the path is split.
Which way? Oh, no! I don't know.
Oh, no! A dead end.
- It's a dead end!
- Oh, no!
30 more seconds left,
but an incident happens.
- What happened?
- Which way?
This way?
It's hot!
The staff couldn't keep up with
Nakaoka, who suddenly turned,
and the rocket misfired!
It's hot!
I'm sorry. That was a misfire.
Don't misfire!
It's because you're holding
a camera as well.
Have someone else launch the rocket.
He's super annoyed. That's great.
Second attempt.
Ready, start!
- This way!
- Go for it!
It's hot! You idiot!
It's hot!
- Third attempt.
- Start!
Okay!
It's hot!
How many times
are you going to do this?
There's a limit
to trial and error, you know!
That is when...
Nakaoka, stop!
There's a bee on your back.
Get rid of it! Get rid of it!
Get rid of it!
It's better not to move.
It left. It left.
Let's run!
Bees will chase you
once they select you as a target.
What is this?
I'm done with this!
What?
You have lots of hot water ready.
How much were you planning to do?
Next up is a silly video.
Nakaoka ripping tight shirt.
When he first started QTube,
he was thinner.
Let's use his costume
from back then!
- He was thinner!
- Totally different.
I don't really want to come out.
- What?
- How much weight did he gain?
- Oh?
- It's super tight.
Oh, that doesn't look good.
I'm seriously depressed here.
Oh, my...
I can't even button one.
- Let's do it.
- Yes.
- Ready...
- Okay.
Go!
Oh! I did it!
Instant.
- I did it.
- That's incredible.
- He's laughing.
- This is actually sad.
Nakaoka is depressed...
- It's heartbreaking.
- He's gained 15 kg
in the past eight years.
"Currently weighs 80 kilogrammes"
I see.
- He's completely different.
- Time is...
very cruel.
Stop it!
Next, a collaboration
with Kumamoto's super kid!
- Oh?
- That looks great.
- I don't need that footage.
- I see.
- I'm Hinata Uchida.
- She's cute.
This is Hinata Uchida, and she's 11.
She's good at
long skateboard dancing.
Dancing?
That's incredible.
They dance to music
on a skateboard,
and they compete on composition
and difficulty of skills.
That's amazing.
Amazing.
Hinata is the overall
female champion of Japan.
Hinata, I'm ready.
Okay...
- What?
- Well, it's just...
It's perfect.
She chose her words.
It is extremely hard to balance
while dancing on the board
when you actually try it.
I'm sure this is super hard.
- Ouch!
- Oh, that hurts.
He's put on every possible piece
of protective gear, but...
Oh, I didn't have
this one on correctly.
Ouch...
Now, please take a look at him
after five hours of practice.
Oh?
He has great speed!
Woo-hoo!
First is switch step, where you
switch the front and back feet
and change the direction
of the body.
- She's good.
- That is cool.
How is it?
Ah...
It's awkward,
but he manages to do it.
He did it.
Next, feet are crossed over quickly
to do this step.
She's really good.
All right! Okay!
- How about this one?
- Oh?
Go!
Yes!
These are the only skills
he managed to do.
Now, please watch Hinata's
magnificent skills.
Thank you very much.
That is so cool.
- That is so cool.
- What is this?
What is this?
What was your dream again?
A patisserie.
- Isn't this her dream?
- It's surprising, right?
Don't you want to be
in the Olympics?
No, the Olympics are a bit scary.
Why?
There will be lots of people there.
- You don't like to be in public?
- No.
Why don't you ask the star for
advice on not getting nervous?
- Do you want to know?
- Yes.
You get used to it.
She's laughing.
Next, the super kids of the world.
Virtual QTube with Dandan in China.
He balances on the board
placed on a cylinder,
and he stacks a plate
on top of his head.
No way.
- No way!
- This is incredible.
This is no joke.
From your outfit
and from what you do,
I think you're part of
an acrobatics group.
Yes, I am.
Of course he is. Of course.
It's a success for Nakaoka
if he stacks two plates.
First, he'll balance and stabilise
on the board.
Wait. Wait.
This part is fixed.
- I see.
- Let's do this.
I'm going for it.
Ouch.
- That would hurt.
- That hurts.
This is super hard.
He is not even close
after two hours.
"One hour later"
"Two hours later"
Ouch!
Then Dandan, who's been
watching him, has a tip.
- Dandan has advice for you.
- Yes.
The bowl you put on the board
should be facing down.
- Like so?
- Yes.
That's how it's done?
You should have said that sooner.
But with this advice,
the bowl's projection is consistent.
I need to watch it.
Here's his 156th challenge.
That's amazing.
- Is it good?
- I think he did it.
- That's great!
- It's looking good. There you go!
Wow!
Nakaoka was successful!
Yes! Yes!
What did you think?
"Lotti Nakaoka's
QTube in Kumamoto"
Practise some more.
Why?
He's strict.
Next is an amazing technique video
from Kumamoto.
It was submitted by Jun Noda, ranked
second in vaulting box in Japan.
This is the trick.
When you play this in reverse...
"Playing in reverse"
Let's have Nakaoka do
this reverse jumping too!
Here!
Go for it!
First, he'll do
a regular forward jump.
He barely manages
to do a forward jump.
Now, can he go in reverse?
- Go!
- Go for it!
This is super hard.
Nakaoka's jumping ability
is hopeless.
We have one
for elementary school kids.
- You do?
- Yes.
What will you do?
Will you jump the big one,
or will you eat your pride
and use a small one?
Right. If I choose this immediately,
I feel as though
I'm lowering my standards,
and I hate that.
Even if I use this,
if I manage to float on here,
I don't think people will notice
the difference in size.
"Suggests to switch"
So let's not say anything
and pick this one.
- We won't show them we switched it?
- Nope.
They won't know.
They're so similar.
- Here I go.
- What a nasty professional.
It's obviously smaller.
Oh?
Nope.
Cute.
Next is a popular challenge video.
CDs are placed between
four stacked bottles.
A CD is removed by a roundhouse kick
without knocking over the bottles.
He'll try to remove two CDs.
I see.
Oh?
- Where is this?
- It's someone's yard...
So cute.
Hello.
Thank you.
Hand power.
- Hand power.
- So cute!
Nakaoka's roundhouse kick,
removing CDs.
So cute.
It's hard to judge the distance
of a roundhouse kick,
and only half of a CD
is available to be kicked.
Gurenge.
Will he succeed in one kick?
Yes!
Miraculous kick on the lower stack.
- Yes!
- It didn't move at all.
Wasn't that amazing?
It's not even shaking.
I'll get this one next.
Next, the upper level.
However...
Ah, darn it.
That was close.
He was off to a good start,
but what was unexpected was...
What?
that the set-up
takes a very long time.
It's tilted this way.
- It's dark already.
- It's dark.
It is.
It got dark while they were trying
to stack it up straight.
I'll get it in one shot.
Okay.
It's getting late,
so this is his last chance.
- Okay.
- Will he succeed?
Here I go.
Ha!
Ouch.
A heavy blow to his heel.
Ouch!
That hurt.
It seriously hurts.
He sure is a first-class comedian.
Finally, he'll challenge doing
an impressive Olympic skill.
They came to Aqua Dome Kumamoto.
He will be assisted by...
Are you my instructor?
I'm the mysterious masked
water polo player.
I'm Maskman W.
What's with this get-up?
His work doesn't know about this.
It's cumbersome to hide his face,
but he's an amazing player
who once represented Japan.
He'll challenge doing a skip shot.
This is the shot.
Wow, that's amazing.
He jumps high in a deep pool.
The ball is bounced once off
the water's surface to make a goal.
Nakaoka is to master this
and hit the target above the goal
to call it a success.
Oh? Is that Kumamon?
What do we practise first?
We'll practise egg beater kicks.
- Egg beater kicks?
- Treading water.
Water polo is played in a deep pool
where the feet won't reach.
So unless you can tread in water,
it can't be done.
How many seconds can I go on for?
Here I go.
Nakaoka once did
synchronised swimming on QTube.
How is his skill?
This looks gross.
Instructor...
help me...
Help!
He is at his limits in a minute.
Help me!
No! This is no joke. Help.
However, the Maskman
corners Nakaoka.
Maskman!
Instructor! The board!
What did you do that for?
Seriously!
- Oh, no!
- Seriously.
You guys better quit it!
You know, this instructor...
when I tried to reach for this,
he flipped it like that.
So then I thought I would go here,
and when I tried to approach it,
he pulled my hand.
You know, instructor...
I can't do this
unless he apologises to me for it.
I want you to push your limits.
Huh?
Unless you go beyond your limits,
you won't be able to do it.
Then the Maskman gives a present
to Nakaoka to get him hyped up.
Mysterious water polo player
Maskman N!
Maskman W.
The two of us are
water polo brothers!
Maskman N!
He tries to tread water again.
Can you breathe like that?
Wait!
Wait.
It's really hard to do with this.
It's really hard to do this.
His mask doesn't have
the bottom part.
My hole is this small.
The water comes right in.
And the water that came in
comes right into my mouth
without exception.
Next, he'll practise
shooting the ball.
Let's do this.
He'll first use a flotation ring
to get the hang of it.
- Here I go!
- Then...
It doesn't have much height,
but he is successful in bouncing it.
I can do it.
On the other hand,
Maskman's power is...
- Okay!
- Here I go!
What? From there?
That's impossible.
He can easily score a goal
from 25 metres away.
If you throw it from here,
then it gets too low,
so if you could release the ball
at a higher point...
Then...
He can do it.
I hit it!
Yes!
It was a nice shot
that hit the goalpost.
That was good.
Yes!
However, without a flotation ring,
it's a whole nother story.
Here I go!
Not even close.
Seriously?
It's hard to float
in a pool when your feet
can't reach the bottom.
This is no joke.
It's completely different.
Completely different.
Now, a surprise for Nakaoka,
who's feeling down.
He eats bread a lot lately.
Actually...
Kumamon came to cheer him up
as a surprise.
- Is it hard?
- It's hard.
I don't know what kind of bread
this is, but it's super delicious.
It's so good
I don't want to finish it all.
It must be good.
Look back.
- Thank you, but
- Look behind you.
now that I've eaten this...
Wow, you scared me! What?
What? What's going on?
It's Kumamon!
He's been here since you had
half of your doughnut.
What?
Now he'll film a funny video
with Kumamon.
Let's film QTube!
- Woo-hoo!
- Oh! He got me!
Gigantic rubber release jump.
What? He'll do it?
On a count of three, a gigantic
rubber band will be released.
Can they avoid it by jumping?
Can Kumamon do it?
Three, two,
then you should jump around 1.5.
Let's do this.
Nakaoka and Kumamon's
rubber band release jump.
- Ready?
- Yes.
Three,
two,
one.
Go!
Kumamon, you jumped too soon.
- He's already on the ground.
- He jumps quite high.
It hit Kumamon good.
You jumped way too early.
- Thank you very much.
- That's it?
I feel so much better! Thank you!
Thank you!
Thank you.
I'm so glad.
Now, the main event. Will he hit
the Kumamon target with a skip shot?
His first shot.
Okay!
It's not good at all.
What Nakaoka lacks is the height
when he throws the ball.
No matter how many times he tries,
he doesn't have the angle
to let the ball bounce.
My physical strength...
I'm sorry... I need a break.
He's physically exhausted.
Then...
Maskman, do you have a ball
that bounces more?
I do,
but it won't be
a ball for water polo.
It'll be a ball
for playing dodgeball.
Dodgeball...
I see.
You can't tell.
There he goes again!
It's his second time.
How would you explain it?
Oh, we won't explain it.
"We won't explain it"
It's fine.
- Do you want to try and see?
- Yes, let's try it.
Please be happy if I hit it.
- You got it.
- This is incredible too.
- Here I go!
- He threw a dodgeball...
Go!
- Wow!
- Yes!
Yes!
There it is!
- That's incredible, right?
- It is.
Yes!
That was hard.
Oh?
He doesn't seem pleased.
How is that?
Is that considered okay?
Don't you still have some more time?
About 15 minutes.
- I got it.
- It's short.
I'll put everything
into those 15 minutes.
Nakaoka decides to redo it.
I just can't say, "Yes! I did it!"
and mean it.
It was changed.
I just can't say it.
I'm more motivated than ever.
- Are you?
- Yes.
I'm embarrassed that I did that.
I'm going to make this one.
I'm so ashamed about what I did.
There's not much time left
on location.
Will Nakaoka make the goal?
I'll try to go up higher.
Go!
Oh?
I'm done!
"I'm done"
It's impossible.
Nakaoka, are you serious?
Everything you've done
goes down the drain.
What a horrible look.
I have the right to quit.
That's it for Lotti Nakaoka's QTube.
You now, I would say this one
was pathetic.
With the vaulting box
and with the ball...
He finished with a stuffy nose.
"I have the right to quit."
Oshima, what did you think?
I would say it was pathetic too.
Right?
How his eyes get so small when
he has that horrible expression...
- His eyes get really small.
- They're small.
- It's annoying, right?
- Those eyes!
Well, you know, for this part,
I really want all of you performers
to be on my side.
Wait! I did it several times!
You know, that water polo segment
is short,
but I spent like two whole days.
I was in the pool the whole time
to practise.
It's not just a few hours.
I did it for two days.
My body was all messed up
from the start on the second day.
But it was edited
like I hadn't done anything.
- That's editing's fault.
- Are you kidding me?
But then you guys are saying,
"It was pathetic," too?
What is the point of me
being here, then?
No, no. We can't tell
with all that editing.
We can't tell you were doing it
for two days.
And that instructor would throw
the floatation ring,
and when he pulled me back,
I was really at my limits.
But you shouldn't lose it, though.
- You're right.
- Right.
Yes.
I shouldn't lose it.
Mentally,
I know I shouldn't lose it,
but I lost it.
You guys better quit it!
- You can't lose it there.
- Nope.
There, you should be saying,
"Stop it," to them,
but you thank them in your heart.
That's the way to do it.
He's first-class.
This is first-class.
Right...
What you've done is third-class.
"Quit it!" is third-class.
Darn it!