"This show was broadcasted
on the 30th of May, 2021"
Welcome to The Quest.
Today, it's Rare Beast Hunter
Imoto Japan Tour
and "The Quest" Calendar Project.
Wasshoi!
Hello!
Anpan!
This is how fireworks are made.
We will finally launch them!
- Light it!
It's beautiful. Here I am.
Hammerhead River!
They're so close. I'm impressed.
Aim to go around all 47 prefectures
in Japan,
Rare Beast Hunter Imoto
Japan Tour.
The stage is Akita Prefecture,
the vast natural treasury
where Lake Tazawa and
the Shirakami Sanchi are located.
Hello! Hello, hello.
I am Imoto.
I'm now in Akita Prefecture.
Where am I?
Let's do our regular search
for Imoto.
- Beneath?
- Left.
The blue demon.
- I am here!
- No?
- Here! I'm over here!
- What?
The correct answer is,
I became part of the rock!
Oga, Akita's folk event,
Namahage.
On New Year's Eve,
men romp around and yell,
"Are there any crybabies around?"
and ward off evil.
The commonly known part ends here,
but actually,
Namahage continues after that.
Welcome.
Are you thirsty?
Please have a drink.
Namahage suddenly calmed down,
and received hospitality
from the house's owner.
Isn't that Imoto?
The Namahage knows who I am?
They take out a Namahage Record.
The residents' daily activities
are recorded.
According to my record,
at this time,
Imoto is doing intermittent fasting.
She does not have breakfast,
and during the day,
suddenly, her movements
and comments get worse.
How does he know that?
How does he know I'm fasting?
- Hey, Imoto!
- Yes!
Are you working seriously?
And it enters round two.
The house's owner reprimands them
and sends them back to the mountain,
so his wife and children
respect him,
and this lets the owner
maintain his dignity.
By the way, to bad-mouth you,
we asked Mr Ishizaki
the evil deeds you've done lately,
and he said that you don't turn
the toilet's light off
So cute!
What's that?
He said he couldn't think
of other things.
So cute!
I don't think it's okay for
a variety show's director, though.
As a husband, he's perfect.
Now, let's start our tour in Akita.
Let's go to Akita!
We have come to Oga Aquarium, GAO.
In December 2020,
baby polar bears were born here.
I'll now go to meet them.
This is Mr Taguchi, the caretaker.
We haven't let the public meet them,
the two cubs have been staying with
their mother in the room inside.
I can't wait to see them.
They're unusually adorable.
- Irresistible?
- It's extraordinary.
Really?
But only one person can go in.
I'll take the responsibility
and go film something cute.
We entrusted Imoto
with the filming of the babies.
The babies are here.
But...
It's blurred.
- What?
- What happened?
- Why?
- Oh, no.
Focus on the bear.
Focus on the bear cub.
The iron bars look too clear.
Oh, no. It looks like it's filmed
with a stylish SLR Camera. No...
Oh, it's gone.
It's cute.
This is difficult.
But finally...
Oh, finally?
It's here.
The baby is coming here.
This is a 3-month-old
polar bear baby.
Wow, it looks like a plush toy.
It's so adorable.
The breeding of kept polar bears
is very difficult.
In Japan, only 30 cases
were raised successfully.
I'm so excited.
It's growling.
It really loves its mum.
It's so adorable.
It becomes the idol of the zoo
in an instant. Irresistible.
Then, the iron bars become
the main star again.
But there are many
adorable animals in Akita.
So cute!
That is Akita's protected animal.
Oh, it's nice to meet you!
This is an Akita.
It is big.
They are the Japanese dogs
designated as protected animals.
Among the six breeds,
Akita is the only large dog breed.
The famous loyal dog, Hachiko,
was also an Akita.
Recently, one was given
to Russia's President Putin,
and one to Ms Zagitova,
it's rather well-known.
- Masaru stayed here for a month,
- Okay.
The dog given to President Putin,
Yume's father, also came from here.
Mr Motose is a great breeder
who is known by all Akita breeders.
There are some puppies Mr Motose
highly recommends now.
So cute!
Look at them.
Have a look, everyone.
This is a 2-month-old Akita.
Was it tiny when it was born?
They weigh 350 to 400 grams
on average.
And they grow this big
in two months.
Look how thick its limbs are.
It's very sturdy.
You can bring it home.
I do want to bring it home.
Asako doesn't want
to keep dogs anymore?
That's right, I don't think
Asako wants that anymore.
Ms Okubo's dog, Pakomi,
ate the hair here,
Ayako said she was satisfied.
Pakomi kept tearing away
the hair here.
- So only the hair here is thin.
- Stop it.
Does Pakomi look down on her?
No, that's her toy.
Her toy.
Next, it's Akita's food culture.
I'm at a common supermarket
in Akita,
but look at this corner.
They are all agar.
First, this is fruit agar,
this is milk agar.
I can somehow imagine
what these taste like,
and I think I've tried them before.
But look at this.
Shiitake mushroom agar.
What's this colour?
This is egg agar.
Like this, in Akita,
they use various things
to make agar.
In southern Akita,
it's their culture to turn
everything sweet or salty
into agar.
- Akita is a snowy place,
- Yes.
so it's mostly made as
a kind of preserved food.
The agar loved by people
of all ages is salad agar.
It looks delicious.
Add sugar and mayonnaise
to vegetables you like,
pour in melted agar,
and it's ready when it hardens.
Here I go.
Did she take it off? She did.
It's so beautiful!
So pretty!
- This looks so pretty!
- I want to try it.
- How does it taste?
Delicious.
- So good.
- I'm glad you like it.
It isn't watery at all.
- It's delicious!
- It's nice.
- Pretty and delicious.
- It's beautiful.
If you do the branding well
and sell it at a shop,
maybe you can earn a fortune.
I want to get involved.
You'll recover the cost
if you sell it at 500 yen.
While she films around the country,
this woman is always on the lookout
for business opportunities.
This is brilliant.
Yeah.
It's got to go well.
Let's make a sweet one.
The idea of crepes.
It's nice.
Next, a summer feature in Akita.
We have come to Daisen City.
You're going to make fireworks.
What? You can make fireworks?
The fireworks festival held
in Omagari, Daisen City,
Nagaoka City in Niigata Prefecture,
and Tsuchiura City in
Ibara Prefecture,
are the three major
fireworks festivals in Japan.
This time, Imoto will make
her original fireworks
and launch them
into the sky in Akita.
Hibikiya Omagari Fireworks'
president,
Mr Saito, will help us.
Are fireworks dangerous?
Sure, they are.
If there's static electricity.
No static electricity?
No.
Ms Imoto, you're wearing clothes
made with chemical fibres,
- there's a chance it'll explode.
- What?
If it goes, "boom,"
the whole workshop will be gone.
Like that?
Scary.
Before they go to the workshop,
Imoto changes into
pure cotton work clothes, which
doesn't cause static electricity.
Is your outfit okay?
It's pure cotton.
Really?
If you explode, we'll all die.
- Have you checked the tag inside?
- I have.
Wait. Really?
"100 percent cotton."
The tag is so unique.
Oh, I don't like this.
I wanted her to wear this.
No fire is allowed beyond here,
so don't bring a lighter in.
Mr Odani,
have you put down your cigarettes?
Mine is electronic.
- Electronic too.
- Not allowed.
The first step is the composition
of gunpowder.
By mixing tens of chemicals,
it'll create various colours,
lights, and sounds.
There's a mixing ratio.
It varies from company to company.
Different companies
have different ratios?
Next, it's granulation.
In a firework shell, there are
gunpowder pellets called stars.
The process of making
the stars is granulation.
Gunpowder dissolved in water
is used as glue,
and gunpowder is sprinkled on top.
The process is repeated many times.
They start as
1-millimetre granules,
we sprinkle gunpowder on top,
and they gradually grow bigger.
Does it take long
to make them this big?
It takes one month.
They're gone in six or seven
seconds.
So short-lived.
The stars made are stuffed
in a container called Tamagawa,
layers of craft paper are stuck
on top to finish it.
By the way, this is my wife.
Wow, this is your wife?
How did he propose to you?
He didn't propose.
He didn't launch any fireworks?
Didn't he talk about a big finale
and whatnot?
I have an older brother.
When I saw him do that,
I thought it was cringy.
Today, Imoto will do Tamagome,
loading the shell with stars.
- This is a number 3 shell?
- Yes.
It flies to about 100 metres
up in the air,
its diameter is 90 metres
when it explodes.
A diameter of 90 metres.
- The one you'll stuff today
- Yes?
is a number 10 shell.
- What?
- It's called Shakudama,
the diameter is 30 centimetres.
When it explodes,
it has a diameter of 300 metres.
It's launched in the second half
- to liven up the atmosphere?
- Yes.
Only number 5 shells
have been launched at Sumida River.
- Really?
- Yes.
It's a city, there wasn't enough
safety distance,
so they can't launch big fireworks.
Line up the finished stars inside
the Tamagawa without overlapping.
Is this okay?
Yes, perfect.
What about Mr Anzue?
He can do it too.
This is Mr Anzue who has been
a fireworks master for four years.
He stuffs a shell for the first time
today with Imoto.
Does it look okay?
It's also Mr Anzue's first time
making this.
When the shell
is 80 percent full of stars,
put a smaller Tamagawa shell in,
stuff the stars further
and leave no gap.
If you don't line them well here,
when it explodes, you'll see a seam.
There'll be a line.
But the height isn't uniform.
Mr Saito's is generally uniform.
Anzue's is uneven too.
Anzue needs to improve.
He has to start making an effort.
It's assumed that
making fireworks is bold,
but in fact, it's rather delicate.
Then we'll put Wariyaku,
that is the gunpowder that
scatters the stars in the centre.
Oh, no... Again.
It has the sonority of sound.
It's nice. Listen to it.
It's when fireworks makers work.
Isn't it the sonority of sound?
Totally.
- The sound is nice.
- It's nice.
The Quest isn't over yet. Not yet.
Wrap the Wariyaku carefully
in Washi paper,
and half of it is finally finished.
This is half?
Then, when the other half
of the shell is finished,
they'll finally be put together.
We'll put them together
at this angle.
- In one go?
- Yes.
It makes me very nervous.
I'm getting nervous too.
From this state...
If the content spills,
we have to start from scratch again.
Anzue will try first.
Anzue.
- Okay.
- I'm so nervous.
Can Anzue do it?
I'll do it.
- Oh, no.
- Anzue, you can do it!
Anzue!
- It's okay.
They don't line up.
Oh, no.
Beat it and fix the position.
Can it be fixed?
It's okay.
Can this be used?
Anzue!
Mr Saito mends it
and somehow finished it.
Next, it's Imoto's turn.
I'm scared.
- They're heavy.
- They are.
I can't hold them any longer.
I'll do it!
Ready, go.
Well done.
Anzue, sorry!
Imoto did rather well by imitation.
Okay.
She looks smug.
This time, she'll do one more thing.
It's the firework Imoto designs.
This is me.
- I think we can see this pattern.
- You can make it?
Shaped fireworks of pictures
or symbols are called Katamono,
they're made in a way totally
different from usual fireworks.
On a firework shell
with Wariyaku placed inside,
draft the picture of the firework
you want to launch.
Glue the stars according
to the picture.
Your brows are connected.
I guess so.
Unlike usual fireworks which are
round no matter where you look from,
Katamono Firework isn't guaranteed
to face forward.
Whether we'll see it as Imoto or not
will totally depend on luck.
This is done.
I've done it.
60 layers of craft paper are pasted
on the fireworks made.
By making the firework shell tough,
it'll create a strong pressure,
and it'll explode as a circle.
The firework Imoto made will be
launched five days later.
It costs 70,000 yen to launch
one big number 10 firework.
Yes, it costs about 70,000 yen.
- We want a lot if possible.
- Thank you.
We have to talk
to our show's producer.
While the craftspersons are working,
we'll report about
Akita's traditional performance art.
Wow, impressive! What's that?
Wow, what's this?
Huge lanterns are hung on a pole,
he's supporting the pole
with his forehead.
This is Akita's traditional
performance art, Kanto.
The pole on which the lanterns are
hung can be as long as 18 metres.
It is perfectly balanced,
and the amazing feat has been
passed down since the Edo period.
It's bent so much!
Amazing!
Every August,
to pray for abundant harvest,
around 280 poles bearing lanterns
are featured
in the Akita Kanto Festival.
The scene is praised as the lights
of ears of rice
that decorate summer.
Now, Imoto will try it too.
This is a Kanto of a size
called Chuwaka,
which is held by middle school
students in the festival.
Ready, go.
Oh, no.
This is bad.
There's no way I can do it.
It looks light, right?
It's heavy if you hold it.
It looks easy
when the performers hold it,
but it weighs 30 kilograms.
You can't do it only by strength.
Four parts strength,
six parts skill.
Skill is more important?
The balance is more important.
Proving it,
the festival executive committee's
president is 71 years old,
but his performance doesn't look it.
It's impressive.
Imoto is influenced by him,
her talent suddenly bloomed.
Hold it up quickly if possible.
Okay. Keep holding it up.
- Hold it up.
- Suddenly?
Impressive!
I can't...
Dokkoisho, dokkoisho.
- Sorry, help me.
- Watch out.
I could do it, surprisingly.
Try to do an even more difficult
performance, then.
I think I know what this is.
- This is a gym wheel.
- Gym wheel.
Rhonrad uses this wheel to perform
various techniques,
it's a sport that originated
in Germany.
Scary!
Mr Yasuhiko Takahashi here
is the current world champion
of Rhonrad.
His body is strong.
Also, he was the world champion
not just once, but three times,
and he's the world's
number 1 Rhonrad athlete.
Awesome!
Wow, impressive!
How does he do it?
He absolutely wins. The champion.
You do it gracefully,
but you use a lot of muscles
to do this, right?
That's right.
I use many muscles.
As usual, Imoto tries it, but...
- Oh, no.
- I'll let go.
She can't do it at all.
Please watch the performance of only
the techniques Imoto can do.
You did it.
It's too early.
I practised a bit.
Here she is.
So slow.
This is impressive.
You only ran on the ground.
The reassuring spin.
This is impressive!
Amazing!
Impressive.
Gosh, the form...
I'm so embarrassed!
Embarrassed.
Lastly, a large spin
by Mr Takahashi.
This is tough in its own way.
The strength.
She has to endure it.
There's a bit of comedy added.
On the other hand,
it's the launching of fireworks.
We managed to get
the production cost
for the Special Fireworks Festival
of The Quest,
and secured an 800,000 yen budget.
Thank you.
They are the instructions
for each launch.
- So many are written.
- That's right.
To sum up,
- one square is one firework, right?
- Yes.
We'll launch a lot.
It's about 300 to 400 fireworks.
It's more than the number launched
at my hometown's fireworks festival!
This is the gunpowder for launching.
- We'll put it underneath?
- Yes.
Put it at the bottom,
and put the shell on top.
- That's all?
- Yes.
This amount of gunpowder will send
it up to 300 metres in the air.
In the past, a fire source was
placed in by hand to launch it.
Nowadays, we use an electric fuse.
When the current flows,
there will be a spark at the tip.
Finally, they'll launch
the fireworks.
The Special Fireworks Festival
of The Quest starts now.
One!
- Light it!
Beautiful!
Wow, nice!
Wow, impressive! What's this?
It's amazing, wow!
- This is a fireworks festival.
- Amazing!
Amazing!
How much did
the opening just now cost?
The amount?
- About 200,000 yen.
- Ask how many fireworks.
Instead of money.
It's ephemeral.
Well, then,
- let's launch the Imoto Smile
- Finally.
- we loaded the other day.
- Please.
Ignite Imoto Smile.
First, it's Imoto's face
loaded by Mr Saito.
"Imoto Smile by Mr Saito"
- Good! Good! Good!
- It's perfect!
You saw it?
It was great.
Its brows were connected.
They were. They were connected,
but it's well made!
What about the face Imoto made?
"Imoto Smile by Imoto"
That was so Imoto Smile!
Its brows were also connected.
Yes, they were.
- Anzue's.
- Mr Anzue's!
- Mr Anzue's Imoto Smile.
- Yes.
"Imoto Smile by Anzue"
It's the side?
It faced the side!
- They're different.
- Are you kidding me?
- Finally, the Shakudama.
- Here it is.
- The Shakudama I made.
- Yours. Okay.
The sound is different.
"Shakudama by Mr Saito"
Beautiful!
Beautiful.
It's huge!
"Imoto"
This is how big it is
compared to a person's size.
It's like the ground rumbled!
Is this okay?
Next, it's Anzue's.
- His first.
- His first Shakudama.
- Here we go, Mr Anzue.
- Okay.
Your first Shakudama.
"Shakudama by Anzue"
Wonderful! It changes colour!
How do you feel now?
I'll continue to do my best to load
fireworks even better than this.
It was beautiful.
To me, it looked the same
as Mr Saito's.
Mine was rounder.
Oh, was it?
Well...
Fireworks explode into a circle
no matter where you see it from.
That's where fireworks masters
show off their skills.
When we compare them,
it's as you can see.
"By Mr Saito, by Anzue"
Indeed.
Finally, they'll launch
Imoto's Shakudama.
Next, ignite...
the Silvery Purple Brocade Profusion
I made.
It was so beautiful.
It was great!
It was very round.
Maybe it was better than ours.
Yes, somehow, I feel that it was
as well.
I think it was the roundest.
Lastly, it's a Star Mine that costed
all the remaining budget.
Ignite!
It's coming.
Amazing.
Beautiful! Amazing!
Wow, beautiful!
It's so beautiful! Amazing!
Is this okay?
Is the budget okay?
Wait, is our budget okay?
- Wow, amazing!
- Don't ask about the budget.
They're drooping!
It's enough. Wow, amazing!
This is bad! Mr Saito!
That's the end.
Amazing!
The last one is your favourite,
Nishiki Kamuro, Ms Imoto.
The drooping one.
Didn't we launch too many?
- Is this okay?
- Yeah.
Is our budget sufficient?
I got scared at the end,
we kept launching, right?
What do you think this time,
Mr Anzue?
The number 10 firework shell I made
- looked small.
- What?
So you were happy,
but you weren't totally satisfied?
There's much room for improvement.
Maybe some people
will become Mr Anzue's fans.
If anyone asks Anzue
to make fireworks,
we'll launch his fireworks.
Really?
That's the 15th prefecture,
Akita Prefecture conquered.
I thought it was great and was
impressed across the screen,
but Ms Imoto
only talked about money.
"How much is this? Is it okay?
Is our budget sufficient?"
Just enjoy it quietly.
Mr Anzue also made his debut.
Yes, the gentleman was very pure.
Nice, Anzue!
- Anzue is nice.
- I like his name too.
- You want to say, "Anzue!"
- Anzue!
Anzue.
The next part is this.
"The Quest" Calendar Project!
This time, to take a photo with
a certain kind of rare animal,
I went to the sea in Izu.
Izu.
I exposed the secrets
of Izu's diving industry!
Secrets?
- We don't need that!
- But...
Don't expose them!
Members of The Quest go to various
places in the world every month
to take beautiful photos.
They aim to collect the photos
to complete the 2022 calendar.
This is
"The Quest" Calendar Project.
This time,
we'll go to a sea in Japan,
and try to take photos
of a kind of rare animal.
A rare animal?
It's sunfish.
Sunfish.
The maximum length of
the giant sunfish is 3 metres.
It is popular at aquariums because
of its lovely appearance,
but it is rare to see them
swimming in the ocean.
In the past, in The Quest,
Imoto had been to a sea
in Indonesia to look for them,
but couldn't find any.
In the end, she went to a place
in Chiba called Manbo Land,
- and swam with them.
- I see.
You recovered it that way...
It's a cringy way to end,
but well...
What The Quest left behind
will be recovered by
the sea traveller, Oceans Kaneko.
Ocean sunfish have been sighted at
a place from time to time recently,
that is the Izu Peninsula in winter.
So this time, we'll travel around
the sea in Izu
to look for sunfish.
Let's carry out the Izu
Ocean Sunfish Great Operation.
Oceans Kaneko has come
to the sea in Izu!
Chacha manbo, chacha manbo!
He has come to the southern tip
of Izu Peninsula, Minamiizu Town.
- Good morning!
- Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
His guide is an experienced diver,
Junji Suda.
He had sighted sunfish many times
in the past.
Nice.
But lately...
- Twice in three months.
- What?
That's so few.
Sunfish likes cold water,
so they appear in the area
of the sea in Izu during winter.
But in that time period,
they don't always stay
at the same place,
and it's said that they swim
around along the coast.
But there are places where you have
many reports of sighting, right?
There are several places.
Let's use our usual strategy.
We'll sail a boat,
and dive while we're moving.
I want to do that,
but we can't.
- What?
- Yes.
Why is that?
I heard music.
The thing that is in the way
of our search
is the secret hidden
in Izu's diving industry.
Here it goes.
As one of the best diving spots
in Japan,
there are many points
that surround the peninsula,
but shops that can dive at
each point are specified,
and other people aren't allowed
to step into the area.
This is their unspoken rule.
Like, this point is this shop's,
that point is that shop's.
Is there any point you want?
There are places I'd like to go to.
Do you hand them over
to other people?
We don't do that.
- You all have your territories.
- Yes.
This is like
the Warring States period,
- like battling over territories.
- Yes.
On the stage of Izu's sea where
invisible boundaries are put up,
a fierce battle has finally started.
The font.
That's enough.
"Project Q, Izu Sunfish Operation"
A unwritten agreement
in Izu's diving industry,
a non-aggression pact of points.
The territory of the shop
where Suda works
is 15 minutes away
from the port by boat,
at the sea of Mikomoto Island.
It's one of the best diving spots
in Izu.
If it's one of Izu's best,
that means it's one of Japan's best.
That's right, I shouldn't be
the one to say it, though.
It is the southernmost point
of Izu Peninsula.
The Kuroshio Current
relatively comes easily,
so small fishes gather there,
and big fishes go there
to hunt them.
Suda has Mikomoto Island,
so he is the winner
in Izu's diving industry.
The huge cruise that has a capacity
of 62 passengers is the proof.
- We're here.
- We're here?
Yes, this is Mikomoto Island.
No plant grows there.
On the sea
in the winner's territory,
they go scouting.
Amazing!
I see a large school of fish
right away. That's a lot.
The school of fish blocking his
sight is Japan's endemic species,
yellowstriped butterfish.
People call Mikomoto Island
the Paradise of School of Fish.
Various species of small fish
are shoaling everywhere.
A huge one is coming.
Oh, greater amberjack!
They're hunting these fish.
Usually, greater amberjack
is about 1 metre long,
but at Mikomoto Island,
individuals that are nearly
2 metres long have been sighted,
so it is obvious how abundant
this area of the sea is.
The sea is amazing.
Izu is huge.
With that momentum,
they go search for sunfish.
Come out, sunfish.
Oh, sunfish!
The chance of seeing sunfish
in Izu's mid-winter
will be several days
during spring tide.
Riding the rising current
from the deep sea,
the sunfish' favourite food,
squid and jellyfish, will surface.
It is said that sunfish come
to shallow waters to hunt them.
The chance will be the coming
four days starting today.
There's no sunfish.
There are small fish, though.
They did not find any sunfish
this day,
but Kaneko witnessed a phenomenon
that is rare in the world.
Wow, impressive!
That's a huge number
of hammerhead sharks!
They're very close. I'm impressed.
All divers long to see
the swarm of hammerhead sharks,
that is a Hammerhead River.
Impressive!
In the past,
Kaneko went to the sea of
Costa Rica in Central America
to try to film this,
but he couldn't see this sight.
Hurray!
The hammerhead sharks
are impressive!
Now, he will certainly get
many enquiries from customers.
Even if sunfish come after this,
I think it won't be as good as this.
Suda couldn't stop laughing.
It isn't about money. Stop it!
- Stop it.
- I'm sorry.
They did not encounter any sunfish
on the first day,
so they followed Izu's rule
and arranged another guide.
They'll go there by car tonight.
Along the way,
they talk about the happy things
that happened to Kaneko lately.
Last time in The Quest,
you introduced
Kaneko Takatoshi channel, right?
Hello, I am Takatoshi Kaneko.
At that time, I had 500 subscribers,
but Kaneko Takatoshi channel...
has over 10,000 subscribers now!
Thank you.
What videos have you been
uploading recently?
I live streamed when I cooked,
and my happy birthday the other day.
Daddy, happy birthday!
- Cheers!
Thank you!
How long is the video?
About less than an hour.
You show your viewers that
for an hour?
What do you mean?
Kaneko Family's home video
is left there to play.
The number of subscribers reduced
by 2,000 soon after that.
Reduced!
My father is very kind...
"Daddy Taka's 43rd birthday party"
Our family is proud of him.
Kaneko Takatoshi channel.
Day two of searching.
Our guide today is located in
the eastern part of Izu Peninsula,
Ito Diving Service's Yoshio Sawachi.
His website says this is a sea
where sunfish show up, but...
But...
Have you seen sunfish this year?
- I haven't seen any this year.
- What?
Are you kidding me?
It's still mid-February now, but...
Yes, maybe today will be
the first time we see them.
The boat's size also makes us worry.
It isn't about the size.
The search starts.
He's helping us.
There are a lot of small fish.
It's beautiful.
Here I am.
A swarming school of golden sweeper.
People call it Silver Flash.
The sight is beautiful,
but seeing this today isn't
worth being happy about.
Is that so?
The sunfish we are searching for
likes the temperature of water
to be under 15 degrees Celsius.
But in front of our eyes,
besides golden sweepers,
fish that aren't usually seen
in cold season are shoaling.
I see.
The temperature of water
is two degrees higher than usual.
Sawachi made a confession
of such important information
after they dived.
He says it in a nasty way.
The temperature of the water
is a bit high.
- It's high?
- That's nasty.
But I think they're
just around the corner.
Already...
Where is around the corner?
Really... Edit it again!
There are invisible boundaries
in the sea of Izu,
but there is a way to break them.
Hello, good evening.
I'm Oceans Kaneko.
Guides gather for a remote meeting
without crossing boundaries.
Has anyone been informed
of the sighting of sunfish lately?
Oh, Mr Kanazashi!
Kanazashi, who looks scary,
is a diver in Shobuzawa, East Izu.
- You saw them?
- Scary?
I didn't see them,
but there are fixed nets
at the coast of Shobuzawa,
they often get caught in the nets.
Also, in Futo, East Izu...
There are also fixed nets
off the coast of Futo,
and three were caught there
last week.
That means
there's a chance I will see
a sunfish?
- Just a chance, though.
- A chance.
What should I do?
I only have two days left.
Which one is the best point
to start?
In East Izu.
It's a huge responsibility.
Nobody... nobody is confident.
In fact,
the sea in East Izu is often rough,
so they can't even put out a ship.
Tago is in West Izu, right?
Yes, it's West Izu.
How will Tago be
in the next two days?
I think the condition will be good.
Is there a chance
I'll see a sunfish?
No.
"Project Q, Izu Sunfish Operation"
That's enough.
Day three of the search.
They came to the small port city
of Futo.
Is that the fixed net?
Yes, the fixed net I told you
about yesterday.
I see.
It's the fixed net that caught
three sunfish last week.
Today, around this area...
We'll dive and look for sunfish.
Search for them.
Sunfish is an animal
that is usually found alone,
if several appeared here,
maybe this is where they find food.
But contrary to our expectation,
no matter how long they dived,
their presence isn't felt.
Have you seen a sunfish?
"Japanese bullhead shark"
I'd like to see sunfish.
Diving in the freezing cold winter.
- Hot spring?
- Hot spring.
Hot spring!
The divers brought hot spring water
from near the port on board,
and make their bodies warm.
It makes me feel your kindness.
You pour warm water
on each other's backs.
The surrounding people tease him,
but there's already someone
in Odani's mind.
Mr Odani! Today is Valentine's Day.
Happy Valentine's Day.
How about Ms Hayashi?
Ms Hayashi!
When we filmed abroad,
you gave me a present
on my birthday.
What the heck?
Ms Hayashi!
He looks happy! He looks happy.
It's a heart shape
handmade chocolate
with his name written on it.
I don't remember the last time
I received chocolate.
What? Really?
Odani thought,
"Could she be serious about me?"
This is yours, Mr Kaneko.
Thank you as always.
Happy Valentine's Day.
What?
Okay, Happy Valentine's Day!
Gosh...
What the heck?
Day four of the search.
There has been an out-of-season
heavy rain since morning.
Oh, no.
To make things worse,
the strong wind makes the sea rough.
This is bad.
They put out a boat, but...
We'll stop here today.
- We'll end here today?
- It's dangerous.
That's right.
Their four-day challenge failed,
but there's no way
they can give up completely.
The next spring tide
will be in late February.
Late February?
I will be available.
We know.
Then, in late February.
The last guide we turned to was...
Sawachi and his little boat.
Compared to last time,
the temperature of the sea
in Ito dropped,
- and the condition improved.
- I see.
It's been a long time since we
last met. I'm looking forward to it.
Looking forward to it.
What?
Ms Ishihara, why are you here?
- I've come to help.
- You came to help.
The boundary of Izu's sea
has just been broken.
Has this happened before?
I don't think so.
Amazing!
Isn't it amazing?
Ishihara wasn't the only one
who showed us her passion.
Mr Kaneko.
I'll go sailing for the first time
in a while to look for sunfish.
I'll do my best!
I'll go to look for them too!
Off I go.
Divers at various places in Izu
go to their own area of the sea.
Ms Ishihara is also making
desperate effort to search.
Yamada in Atami
searches at the point
of a sunken ship.
In the past, sunfish have been seen
here many times.
At the same time in Osezaki,
Maki found wood like this at
the Torii gate at the sea's bottom.
If it's like this,
it doesn't matter who it is,
so if you see a sunfish,
please film it.
- Okay.
- Okay, understood.
Thank you.
In Shobuzawa,
Kanazashi with a scary face
arranged an underwater
photographer himself.
The chance will come
only for a second,
we cannot afford to miss it.
Please. Let a miracle happen.
There is only the slightest chance.
Even so, everyone continues to try.
A total of 11 people,
and a total of 100 diving sessions.
The effort finally pays off.
The lucky one is...
Okay, this time,
I will go to film the sunfish!
- Please!
- Amazing.
It's Kaneko, Sawachi and Ishihara
searching in Ito.
The water is very clear.
It was when they used a rope
to go to the bottom of the sea.
Oh, sunfish!
There's a sunfish!
Sunfish!
Oh, my gosh! A miracle!
Miracle! Miracle!
There's a sunfish.
A sunfish suddenly appeared
in front of his eyes.
It is about 1 metre long,
and it certainly isn't big,
but it has a presence.
It's cute, and its eyes are big.
It sways its fins vertically.
The sunfish uses its dorsal fin
and rear fin to swim leisurely.
How lovely it is.
So cute.
It does not move
even when a human is nearby,
and leisurely swims
together with him.
Thank you.
Thank you, the god of the sea.
Amazing!
Kaneko wasn't the only one
who had a happy moment.
This is filmed by Kanazashi
in Shobuzawa.
He caught a sunfish swimming
in the transparent blue sea.
Amazing!
In Jogasaki,
Yakita also saw a sunfish...
swimming together and successfully
filmed this rare sight.
Hurray! The Ocean Sunfish
Great Operation is successful!
Oh, it has gone far away.
The sunfish showed up in front
of us for only two minutes.
Even so, the time was like a dream.
Mr Sawachi!
What a surprise! I was surprised.
He uploaded so many photos
of the sunfish on his website,
but Sawachi was the one
who's the most surprised.
That's nasty.
We could do this because everyone
in Izu worked together.
We made it!
So the photo to be used
for the calendar
will be this one, which features
Kaneko and the sunfish.
Actually, the Hammerhead River
is more suitable to be put
into the calendar,
but we got too many shops involved,
so we're forced to choose this.
That's all for the Izu
Ocean Sunfish Great Operation.
Isn't the narration
even nastier than usual?
And they made Mr Tomorowo read it.
Exactly!
Mr Tomorowo,
you can turn down the job.
You can say,
"No, I can't do this narration."
Mr Tomorowo, it'll hurt you too.