Wow.. There are so many ingredient on it.
Yepp.. It is for Ramen soup..
Would not they make the best soup ever??
It is Dried foods that from all over Japan.
And he will make a soup of the proper taste.
What kind of Ramen will you make??
I will make Double soup that is consisted of  Chicken and  Fish.
The double soup that Amano says is that At first, make two different kinds of soup separately and then combine them into one.
In addition, Amano was preparing a "Nagoya Cochin", a high quality chicken, not just dried fish.
If you do not care properly .. Its Blood will make the soup dirty subtly..
Finally, he burned the gas.
This is a Best soup !! You guys!
And Hidden card 'Fish soup'
He strived to make a great soup by using Dried fishes.
That's incredible! Look at that soup!!
Amano who said Ramen is the universe used over 100 kinds of dried fish.
Wow.. Really??
Six hours after, the chicken soup was ready.
Look at that Chicken soup... and bone..
Then, Let's shake them.
He was shaking Chichen and fish soup.
Then.. How is its taste??
It has no smell that sting my nose.
He doesn't understand it..
Well.. How can I emote it??
Let's strive for it more and more.
Wow.. There are so many Dried fishes over there.
Amano started to taste all dried fish in the store.
And...
This flying fish ['Ago'] will be okay ..
May I try it?
Sure.. Why not??
Wow.. It tastes good.
The Frying fish..
(Emit)
I'll buy Flying fish.
Amano, who had this hidden card 'Flying Fish' in his hand, immediately returned to the kitchen.
This double soup that combines flying fish and chicken .. How is it taste?
Fantastic!!
Well.. I've never tried This  delicious Ramen before..
Look at his swordsmanship.
He is really Pro.
This is Amano Hiroyuki ..
Look at his 'Flying fish..'
The next thing he caught were boiled eggs.
Oh, He cut it very cleanly(Great!)
You know how to show it.
I hope you cut it with a knife..
Mr. Udo.. How about you..??
It is really really great.
Because he can do Japanese / Western / Chinese /Japanese food' ..
Why are you saying "Japanese food" twice?
Because He is great.
He opened the oven.
?? That's what I learned when I was at the restaurant.
It seemed delicious
And It smells Good..
No matter how much I take a sleep, I will be angry.
Yepp.. Angry..
You will mad, Huh??
Finally, he put noodles.
It's just that collagen comes out of the chicken feet. Then  I made a thick noodles to accompany it.
Oh Yeah??
Who will be?? Amano or Kimu??
What the.. ?? X2
He put the low salt soy sauce .. then several kelp etc.
It smells good (Komoto: Me, either.)
The soup is finally put into the bowl.
This is the chicken broth that he made for about 6 hours. (Miyasako: It's just sticky)
This is the 'Flying Fish' broth.
Here it comes.
Look at their applaud
It is used chicken feet that is full of collagen.
So ... He put it in the soup .
And He had topped the roast chicken and the Welsh onion before.
Besides, He put black sesame on it.
That's it.