The following program was produced with
the utmost consideration toward safety
and features dangerous activities which
were supervised by stunt professionals.
Do not attempt to reenact
any of the activities performed.
Angered by the fact that Chihara Junior
built a castle in Susono, near Mount Fuji,
Masatoshi Hamada, the pervert barbarian
from Osaka, has declared war against him.
Junior's Castle
Here they are, Junior's proud fleet
of eight foreign luxury battle cars.
Mercedes-Benz, Jaguar, BMW,
Volvo, Alfa Romeo, Lincoln, Audi.
Top-class cars that symbolize the various
western countries await their opponents.
As for Hamada's army,
they boast all Japanese battle cars.
Some of the foot soldiers have been duped
into competing with their own cars.
I feel sorry for them.
Hamada's army versus Junior's army.
It's a great car battle
with everyone's lives on the line.
The battle will commence shortly.
"Sentosha Laws" - Battle 1, Battle 2,
Battle 3: Scramble over battle cars
The battle will consist of four rounds.
For the first three rounds,
both armies will battle to win over
the opponent's car.
The winning team can select one car
from the losing team to join their army.
For the fourth and final round,
the remaining cars will battle each other.
The team with more cars left
at the start of the final round
will have a distinct advantage
in the battle.
Battle 4: Wipe out opposing army
with your remaining cars
You might die, battle number 1.
YOU MIGHT DIE
BATTLE NUMBER 1
Stop at the very last moment.
You might die?
What?
All foot soldiers from both teams
will participate in this battle.
This is a one-on-one battle to test
who has the most courage.
The first team to reach five wins
will win the round.
The losing team will need to hand over
one battle car to the winning team.
If you were wondering what's
on the other side of the wall...
We've reshaped the ground
into a steep cliff.
Cliff at a 60-degree angle
The cliff goes down at a 60-degree angle.
You may die if you fall.
Junior's Base - Hamada's Base
-What?
-Are you serious? A cliff?
You just need to stop in time.
You say it like it's easy!
-It's simple!
-You just need to be courageous.
That's right! You just need to go for it!
Does stopping at the last moment mean
when you're doing it with the ring girl?
Of course not!
Please stop it with the dirty jokes!
We need your car, not your sense of humor!
Okay.
Two cars will start accelerating
toward the wall at the same time.
They must reach a speed
of 40 kilometers per hour
before reaching the braking zone.
The speed of the cars will be measured
with a speed gun.
The cars that fail to reach 40 kilometers
per hour will be disqualified.
The cars are prohibited from braking
until they reach the tape
that marks the braking zone.
The judges will check the videos carefully
and if any driver violates this rule,
they will be disqualified.
The driver who stops closest
to the wall wins.
Cowards afraid to risk their lives
could never win this battle.
First team to reach five wins
will win the round
Both armies head to the scene
of the battle for an inspection.
Hey, Junior.
This is the first round!
With this much room,
there should be no problems!
No problems?
This is the braking line, right?
That's right! You need to reach that line
before you can brake.
If you crash into this wall,
it's going to break apart.
I see.
Look where you'll end up
if you crash through the wall!
Oh, wow!
-It's like a cliff face!
-This is great!
-It's like a cliff.
-It's fantastic!
It looks dangerous.
We really might die.
I really don't like this cliff.
It's at a great angle.
It looks great!
First Battle
Here we go!
Who's up first from your army?
First one up from my team is...
Seiji!
Yeah!
This is the worst!
Who are you sending?
Who is it?
It's a battle of the same generation...
It's you, Fujimoto!
Yeah!
He's the biggest coward
from our generation!
Say what?
I'll smash it!
It's gonna be smashing!
A real crash?
You'll lose if you smash into the wall!
Why are you trying to lose?
Are you dumb or something?
It's a figure of speech! I'm going to stop
before I smash into the wall!
Tell him, Fujimoto!
It's "Ugly First" for you, isn't it?
Not "America First"?
Volvo V70
New car price approx. 7.4 million yen
This is Toshifumi from Junior's army.
His battle car is a Volvo V70.
Engine 2.5L I5 DOHC IC Turbo / 209 hp / 4WD / AT / Weight 1620kg
When Fujimoto was offered a part in this
show, he insisted he wouldn't accept it
unless he was assigned a Volvo,
well-known for its safety.
Toyota Celsior
New car price 8 million yen
Seiji Chihara from Hamada's army.
His battle car is a Toyota Celsior.
This is Toyota's executive-class car
which evolved into the Lexus brand.
Engine 4.3L V8 DOHC / 280 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1800kg
It doesn't matter.
Go and die, if necessary!
-All right!
-Thank you for your work!
-Thank you for helping us over the years!
-Thank you!
-Thank you for your hard work, Seiji!
-Goodbye.
Please show them what you can do!
Give it your all!
-Come on!
-He'll get through it somehow.
It's a one-on-one battle of courage.
First army to reach five wins
will win this round.
Make sure you reach
40 kilometers per hour, okay?
I know!
I'll try my best to reach
40 kilometers per hour.
You can't just try,
you definitely need to do it.
-So, 40 kilometers?
-Yeah.
-You can hear the fear in his voice.
-His voice is shaking.
Suddenly, I'm really scared.
I'm getting more and more scared.
Just stomp on the accelerator
until you hit 40 kilometers per hour.
If I stomp on it, it will hit 40 easily.
No, no...
Not with that little distance.
Seiji, don't even bother
with the seat belt.
Of course I'm putting on my seat belt!
I'm putting it on!
Don't you lose to Fujimoto.
Show us some guts.
I'm not going to lose, no matter what.
Toshifumi Fujimoto (Volvo V70)
vs Seiji Chihara (Toyota Celsior)
The battle between
Hamada and Junior's armies
is set to commence at Susono,
near Mount Fuji.
The first head-to-head battle
to set the scene for the rest of the war.
Now, here we go!
Fujimoto is such a coward.
Seiji, go and die, if necessary!
Come on!
Let's go!
Who's going to win this battle?
Fujimoto from Junior's army
in the white battle car?
Or Seiji Chihara from Hamada's army
in the black?
Three... Two... One...
Go!
The first battle has started!
They both stomp on the accelerator!
They first need to reach
40 kilometers per hour,
the rest is up to their courage.
They're gathering more speed!
They're coming up to the wall!
It's very close now!
They brake! How did they do?
Wow, look how close Seiji is!
Winner, Hamada's army!
Seiji won!
Yeah!
Yeah! We won!
Seiji Chihara (Toyota Celsior)
45 km/h - WIN
Toshifumi Fujimoto (Volvo V70) - 46 km/h
Yes!
There is no doubt whatsoever.
It's a win for Seiji!
No!
What the hell are you doing, Fujimoto?
What happened?
Seiji's result is an amazing
80 centimeters!
SENTOSHA
Let's have a look at the replay.
At the start, even though Fujimoto
is a scaredy-cat comedian,
he finds his courage.
However, the one who had the courage
to wait
until the very last moment to brake
was Seiji!
Seiji, who went against his brother
to join Hamada's army,
has drawn first blood in this first round.
That was amazing!
Well done, Seiji!
You've done a great job
as the first competitor!
-Yeah!
-Thank you very much!
You went as close as 80 centimeters!
Our agency wants to make him
the elder brother.
But according to the family register,
I'm still the elder brother.
Of course you are.
You chickened out, didn't you?
That's not true. It's that...
A Volvo is a Volvo. Its brakes are great.
It's a four wheel drive, after all.
Yes.
You weren't going that fast anyway.
Volvo's are great!
Second Battle
Hey, Junior.
How do you feel about losing to us?
What?
Do you wanna keep going?
Why don't you just give up?
We'll...
Has Fujimoto gone home already?
I'm still here!
Dumb-ass!
Next up is Akina!
Yay!
-Let's go!
-It's Akina!
I'll try my best!
Then we'll send Nagisa!
Yes!
Nagisa's brought her own car.
She's got a lot on the line!
What? She brought her own car?
Why?
I'll make sure there are lots of dents
in it by the end of the day!
Mercedes-Benz SLK230 Kompressor
New car price approx. 4.8 million yen
Next up for Junior's army is
Akina Minami.
Her battle car is
a Mercedes-Benz SLK Kompressor.
Engine 2.3L I4 DOHC Super Charger / 197 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1380 kg
It's a two-seater sports car
that has a 2.3-liter DOHC engine
with a supercharger.
Nissan Fuga
New car price approx. 5.7 million yen
For Hamada's army, we have Nagisa
from Amako Inter.
Her battle car is a Nissan Fuga.
It is classified as an executive car,
but this model is a GT car
with a 3.5-liter DOHC engine.
Engine 3.5L V6 DOHC / 280 Horsepower / FR / AT / weight 1680kg
This battle car was forcibly
made to join Hamada's army
after Nagisa was fooled into
buying a car for a fake TV program.
It's a good car.
It's a nice car.
She just bought it, right?
She washed it as well.
Oh, no way. No way, no way.
She's laughing.
She must be happy to see you.
She's got a leopard print cover
on the steering wheel.
You've been duped, Nagisa. Dumb-ass.
Dumb-ass.
Do you want me to smack you?
This is Nagisa's first ever car.
-It's classified as an executive car.
-Wow.
How did you feel on your first drive?
Amazing.
I've never been so happy.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
She has only paid the deposit
of 100,000 yen
The loan on the car
has not been paid off at all.
She just bought it!
I feel so sorry for her.
-I feel sorry for her.
-We all feel sorry for her!
Hamada's army is so devious!
I'm so excited!
What?
I hope you fall down that cliff.
Why don't you drive through that wall
and down that cliff!
You don't know the meaning of having guts!
I've got guts, too.
You shouldn't underestimate me.
I'll show you.
Show me, then.
Two ladies will battle it out
in the second match.
The white battle car is the Nissan Fuga
that Nagisa is paying off.
Nagisa from Amako Inter joined
Hamada's army against her will.
The compact red Mercedes
will be driven by Akina
from Junior's army.
I'm getting nervous
now that I'm in the car.
I hear that Akina doesn't get nervous
in the car at all.
-Really?
-She's really quick in a go-kart.
She races go-karts? Really?
I'm so scared...
Go hard, Nagisa.
I can't go hard
or I'll go through the wall!
Try to stop just before the wall.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Go for it.
Akina Minami
(Mercedes-Benz SLK Kompressor)
vs Nagisa from Amako Inter (Nissan Fuga)
Akina becomes a speed demon
when she's behind a steering wheel.
Now she's smiling!
But Nagisa, is she okay?
She's not herself.
She must be worried about her car.
What is with that steering wheel?
The steering wheel's
got leopard print covers!
Don't mention it!
This is Nagisa's beloved car.
How gutsy can she be?
How hard can she stomp on the accelerator?
Three... Two...
One...
Go!
Here they go!
What's happening with Akina?
She runs straight into Nagisa!
Was that intentional?
She's being tricky right from the outset!
But this is a braking battle.
They need to reach
40 kilometers per hour first,
then hit the brakes!
Now, who won the battle?
Akina is well short!
Nagisa from Amako Inter (Nissan Fuga)
42 km/h - 4m 40cm - WIN
Wow, this is a surprise!
Nagisa is the winner.
The winner is Hamada's army!
Yeah!
Akina Minami (Mercedes-Benz
SLK 230 Kompressor) - 6m 10cm
What just happened?
A win is a win!
Akina, did you bump into her?
She totally bumped her.
Two wins in a row for Hamada's army!
Nagisa is the winner.
I won, so it's all good!
Oh, no!
It's all good!
But what is the damage to the Fuga?
She was rear-ended by Akina.
How does it look?
SENTOSHA
Here's the replay.
Akina intentionally drove
into Nagisa from the start.
Go!
Here we go again.
This is clear as day.
Akina has definitely steered into Nagisa.
She's clearly turning the steering wheel.
She's smiling!
What happened here?
Did we touch? Really?
You crashed into me!
Are you kidding me? What's wrong with you?
What were you thinking?
Did they crash into each other?
They bumped into each other.
I bumped into you? I'm so sorry!
Why, you little...
I'm sorry...
Are you for real?
My front bumped into you a little...
Come here! No way!
No!
What's so funny?
Hey!
Stop laughing!
This is so much fun!
Shit!
Run, run, run!
She crashed into me!
She crashed into my car!
I was so busy trying to crash into her
that I totally forgot to check
the speedometer.
I wonder where you bumped into
each other?
I don't know, but I think she bumped
me in the back at the start.
When I was driving,
I felt a bit of a bump like this.
-That was it, then.
-I think so.
Is that what it feels like?
Didn't you notice it?
I'm not sure
but when I was accelerating straight,
the steering went like this for a moment.
-That's it.
-That's when it happened.
That must be it.
So it happened right at the start.
Third Battle
Have you given up already?
You're not competitive at all!
That was a bit of an accident.
We just wanted to get the Fuga...
You come over here! I'll show you!
I'll get you!
No way!
Shit!
No way, your steering wheel
is leopard print.
It looks cool!
We're going for it now!
It's your turn, Matsuoka!
Yes!
Go for it!
For us, we have...
Katsumata!
Yeah!
I'll beat you to a pulp, Matsuoka!
I hear that you like cars!
I do love cars.
Then it will look bad if you lose, huh?
I'll never lose to you. Never.
Nissan Fairlady Z
New car price 3.5 million yen
The man who wears shorts all year round,
Kunikazu Katsumata.
Engine 3.5L V6 DOHC / 280 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1440kg
His battle car is a Japanese-made
sports car,
the Nissan Fairlady Z.
Jaguar XJ Executive
New car price approx. 8.1 million yen
The Rock 'n' Rolling speedster,
Mitsuru Matsuoka.
His battle car is the highest-class car
from Britain, the Jaguar XJ Executive.
Engine 4.0L V8 DOHC / 243 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1730kg
-The record is Seiji's 80 centimeters.
-Okay.
Let's do better than that in this race.
How about 15 centimeters?
I'll aim for 8.
I'll stop just before the wall!
Katsumata's trying to rev him up.
Yeah, he is.
It's a bit obvious, though.
He's trying to get him to crash
through to the other side.
He's trying to drive him off the cliff!
Looks like you really need to step on it.
No problem.
I'll stop really close to the wall.
I've really tried to egg him on a bit.
So I think he'll crash through
to the other side of the wall.
-Okay.
-So I'll go safety first.
You're revealing your plan?
After all that talk,
you're going safety first?
Safety first!
Mitsuru Matsuoka (Jaguar XJ Executive)
vs Kunikazu Katsumata (Nissan Fairlady Z)
Is Hamada going to take Junior's castle
right here, now?
So far, it's been two wins in a row for
Hamada, the Speedy Barbarian from Osaka.
Now, competing in the third round
are two silver battle cars.
Driving the Jaguar
is the Rock 'n' Rolling speedster
from Junior's army, Mitsuru Matsuoka.
And driving the Fairlady Z
for Hamada's army
is the man who wears shorts
all year round, Katsumata.
Come on!
My God, Katsumata's really fired up!
Let's go!
Go for it! Pedal to the metal!
By contrast, Matsuoka is very quiet.
Three... Two... One...
Go!
Now, Katsumata's really going for it,
full throttle.
The Fairlady Z is in front!
He is accelerating very fast!
Maybe he's going too fast?
They're up to the braking line.
They're stopping...
Matsuoka's doing well... No!
No, he's falling through
to the other side. Look out!
Matsuoka's doing well...
No, he's falling through
to the other side. Look out!
No, he fell down the cliff!
There's an explosion as well. Is he okay?
Kunikazu Katsumata (Nissan Fairlady Z)
45 km/h - 5m 30cm - WIN
Mitsuru Matsuoka (Jaguar XJ Executive)
49 km/h - DQ
No way! Shit!
Hamada's army wins!
Yes!
Just as planned!
Matsuoka! What happened?
He got overexcited.
I couldn't stop.
SENTOSHA
Who could have predicted Hamada would win
three in a row?
Let's have a look at Matsuoka's braking.
He brakes right here.
But it was all too late!
For the first time,
someone has gone through the wall
and fallen through to the other side.
This means Matsuoka is disqualified.
The winner is Katsumata.
They're playing it really safe!
-True.
-He chickened out.
What was that?
He stopped before the wall.
No problem at all.
He stopped well short of the wall. There!
Well short!
That's terrible. Is he even a man?
That's terrible.
Totally.
It went according to plan.
He got so annoyed at me.
He was so annoyed that he stepped
on the accelerator too much.
-Wow.
-He was behind you...
-Yes.
-So he was trying to catch up.
He was easy to fool.
You're so clever.
I got so fired up...
I thought I'd beat him up.
Fourth Battle
Hey, Junior's army!
What?
We are sending...
Juichi Wakisaka!
Then we'll counter with...
The other Wakisaka!
I'll beat you.
Tell him!
When people think of a race car driver
with the name Wakisaka, they think of me!
That's right!
This battle has nothing
to do with our past!
Yeah!
BMW 330i
New car price approx. 5.7 million yen
From Junior's army,
this is Shigekazu Wakisaka.
Although Shigekazu is less well-known
compared to his brother,
he's still one of Japan's top racers
competing in the Super GT class.
His battle car is the legendary car
from Germany, the BMW 330i.
Engine 3L I6 DOHC / 231 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1520kg
For Hamada's army,
we have Juichi Wakisaka.
His battle car is the Nissan Skyline.
In his 16 years of racing,
Wakisaka has only ever driven Toyotas.
Here, he has entered the competition
in a car from rival manufacturer, Nissan.
Modified to suit hooligans from Chiba
and Ibaraki,
it features giant over fenders
and a bamboo-spear muffler.
What does its exhaust sound like?
New car price 3.1 million yen
Engine 2.5L I6 DOHC / 200 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1400kg
If this weren't Mr. Hamada's program,
I'd never ever drive a Nissan.
Let me say that Toyota's CEO
will be watching this show
as I'll be driving in it.
The older brother Juichi
is known as Mr. GT,
and has been one of the best
race car drivers Japan has ever produced.
Currently, Juichi also manages
a Super GT race team.
Shigekazu Wakisaka (BMW 330i)
vs Juichi Wakisaka (Nissan Skyline)
His brother Shigekazu
is also a current race car driver.
Who will win this high level battle
between these two brothers?
Juichi's car sports a bamboo spear
reminiscent of the gangs
from Chiba and Ibaraki.
As a professional racer,
Shigekazu has always been called
Juichi's little brother.
Can Shigekazu beat his brother here?
How's the car?
As you can see...
The other car has bamboo spears
sticking out from the back.
If I lose to that...
-It'd be very embarrassing.
-Yep.
-It's a hooligan's car.
-Let's go, Juichi!
I'll do my best.
But Mr. Hamada, the view from here
is quite frightening.
The view?
The view from here is completely different
to what you see from up there.
It's quite scary.
But, no matter. I'll do my best.
You can't be beaten
by your little brother.
-I know. I'll do it for you, Mr. Hamada.
-Okay.
Can Shigekazu overcome his brother?
The battle is about to begin.
It's a battle between family members.
Listen to the exhaust!
Listen to the engine noise reverberate
in Susono near Mount Fuji.
Will it be the elder brother, Juichi?
Or the little brother, Shigekazu?
Three...
Two...
Please, we need to win this one!
One...
Come on!
Go!
Here we go! Look at Shigekazu accelerate!
Juichi has started very, very slowly!
If he doesn't reach 40 kilometers
per hour, he'll be disqualified!
Shigekazu has reached the speed
required, but how's his braking?
It seems Juichi has chickened out,
if he doesn't speed up,
he'll be disqualified.
Shigekazu has done an amazing job!
He stopped at one meter!
The winner is Junior's army.
This battle between two brothers has been
won by the younger brother, Shigekazu!
Juichi Wakisaka (Nissan Skyline)
35 km/h - DQ
Shigekazu Wakisaka (BMW 330i)
43 km/h - 1m - WIN
-Yes!
-That was bad...
What happened to Juichi?
Did he get scared?
He only reached 35 kilometers per hour.
Shigekazu has won very easily!
What the hell happened?
What happened?
-Shit!
-Shit.
-What was that?
-He was terrible.
SENTOSHA
Here's the replay.
The battle of the brothers.
Let's see where they both hit the brakes.
When did the tail lights light up?
Shigekazu hasn't braked yet.
He brakes right here!
How about Juichi?
He's already braking here!
Not only has Juichi failed to reach
the minimum speed required,
he also hit the brake
before the braking line.
This must be embarrassing
for the older brother.
He has clearly chickened out.
-He clearly chickened out.
-This is disappointing.
-He chickened out.
-He totally chickened out.
What the hell were you doing?
I'm sorry, I got really scared.
You're kidding!
He's supposed to be a pro!
So uncool.
The engine noise was also
really loud, so... It was really scary.
What do you mean, you were scared?
I'm sorry, I was scared.
That's your day job!
It's so embarrassing to brake so early
in a mod car!
So true! It's an epic fail.
Wow, look at the distance we won by!
Well done!
I ended up winning somehow.
Nice job!
How can you show your face after that?
You try doing it. It's really scary!
I did it!
Everyone did it. Even women!
We all did it.
They don't understand.
What do you mean?
We did the same thing you did!
We're all in the same team!
It's all for Hamada's army!
WIN Seiji Chihara vs Toshifumi Fujimoto
WIN Nagisa from Amako Inter vs Akina Minami
WIN Kunikazu Katsumata vs Mitsuru Matsuoka
Juichi Wakisaka vs Shigekazu Wakisaka WIN
In the fourth match,
Junior's army finally get their first win.
Now, on to the second half
of this round-one battle.
Fifth Battle
Next, we're sending Shoji!
Yeah, let's go!
And we're sending...
It's me! Iwahashi!
You're losing your voice already.
He's fired up!
I screamed too much when I found out that
I had to use my own car for this.
Now my voice is gone.
Honda Crossroad
New car price 2.9 million yen
Next up for Hamada's army
is Yoshimasa Iwahashi.
His battle car is Honda's small SUV,
the Crossroad.
Engine 1.8L SOHC / 140 hp / 4WD / AT / Weight 1480kg
What?
What's going on?
Iwahashi was lured over to Susono
near Mount Fuji
to film a TV segment
that didn't even exist.
Iwahashi was also forcibly made to provide
his own car as one of the battle cars.
Come on over here.
The muffler... What?
-What happened?
-What's wrong?
Shut up.
I don't know what's going on!
-Everyone, come over here.
-I still don't know what's going on.
Okay.
Alfa Romeo Alfa GT
New car price approx. 5.4 million yen
For Junior's army, Tomoharu Shoji.
His battle car is the Alfa Romeo Alfa GT.
It's an Italian sports car
with a two-liter DOHC engine.
Engine 2L I4 DOHC / 166 hp / FF / Semi Automatic / Weight 1480kg
I really love that car.
Shit.
It's my family car...
You can't drive into the wall, okay?
Can you stop saying that?
Don't do it, okay?
Stop it, will you?
Who's saying you can't crash
into the wall? Stop it?
Don't fall down the cliff, okay?
No, don't do that!
No, he can't say that!
Don't say that!
Iwahashi, make sure not to fall down
the hill, okay?
Please don't say that!
-Don't drive into the wall.
-I know that!
No, no, no!
Don't crash into the wall
with your own car.
It's really my car!
I worked so hard to buy this car!
Tomoharu Shoji (Alfa Romeo GT)
vs Yoshimasa Iwahashi (Honda Crossroad)
Iwahashi, who was deceived by the tyrant,
has been forced to participate
in this battle with his own car.
It's your own car. Do your best, okay?
Yes!
Bad luck for Iwahashi -
The camera that films his face is broken
I'm fine, but...
Can you stop them
from scaring me by saying
"Don't crash into the wall"
and things like that?
Hemingway.
You're saying random things again.
Ocean view.
Stop it!
Sorry.
Soy, soy, soy!
-What are you saying now?
-Soy beans.
Are you good to go?
Yes, I'm good. I'm up against Iwahashi,
so I think he's going to crash
like he usually does.
No problem at all.
For Junior's army,
we have the red Alfa Romeo
driven by the man
who often screams his wife's name, Shoji.
Will Iwahashi be able to deliver
his family car back home
without a scratch,
and also bring victory for Hamada?
Or will scream his wife's name in victory?
Three... Two... One...
Go!
There they go! Looks like a steady start.
No, they're both speeding up very quickly!
Iwahashi is in front!
Where will he hit the brakes?
He brakes here!
Can he stop? No, he can't stop!
Have a look on the far side.
Shoji's driven straight through!
He's driven straight through the wall
and went down the cliff!
Is Shoji okay?
What happened?
He just couldn't stop in time.
He managed to stop just before
falling down the cliff.
He did quite well.
He came so close!
-He showed a lot of courage.
-That's true.
He would've won
had there not been any wall.
Shoji, what were you doing?
Hey, Shoji!
That was really scary.
Yoshimasa Iwahashi (Nissan Crossroad)
45 km/h - DQ
Tomoharu Shoji (Alfa Romeo Alfa GT)
42 km/h - DQ
The Crossroad's crashed into the wall.
Has it sustained any damage?
I couldn't get enough speed at first.
It looks fine.
It looks okay!
Wow, there's a massive scratch
on the car!
No, there isn't!
-There's a big scratch there!
-That was already there!
It's not a scratch!
Wait a minute. Is it really okay?
SENTOSHA
Go!
For a guy worried about his car,
Iwahashi really stomped on
the accelerator.
He's going pretty fast,
then he brakes here!
The surprise is on the far side.
Did he actually hit the brakes?
Here's the view from his on-board camera.
The car that we can see to the side
is Iwahashi's car.
Was he too busy looking at Iwahashi?
He brakes way too late
and crashes through the wall.
Shoji goes down the cliff.
This means Junior's army cannot lose
any of the remaining matches!
Sixth Battle
The next driver is...
-Let's go, Itakura!
-Yes, sir.
They've got Itakura?
We're sending Sata!
-Go!
-Yeah!
-Who's this?
-Let's go!
You think raising your voice
like that is enough?
-Yeah!
-That's so old-fashioned.
You wanna fight me, do you?
I'll stop within 50 centimeters
of the wall!
How about you?
I'll make it 2 centimeters!
Nissan Laurel 2000SGX
New car price 1.03 million yen
For Hamada's army,
we have Masaki Sata.
He's participating in his beloved
Nissan Laurel,
first manufactured back in 1972.
It's a legendary car highly sought after
by vintage car enthusiasts.
Engine 2L I6 SOHC / 30 hp / FR / 5MT / Weight 1200kg
This car is 41 years old.
It was released in 1976.
I'd say there's only about
30 of these cars left in Japan.
If I take it to a dealer,
they'll offer me 7 million yen.
-Seriously?
-That's what kind of car this is.
Basic design is the same as Skyline,
can reach a maximum speed of 175 km/h.
But I brought this car today,
under strict orders from our agency.
"Mr. Hamada wants your car," they said.
Mercedes-Benz S320
New car price approx. 10 million yen
As for Junior's army,
we have Toshiyuki Itakura.
His battle car is a Mercedes-Benz S320.
The S class is Mercedes' flagship model,
a luxury car that anyone dreams of owning.
Engine 3.2L V6 SOHC / 224 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1800kg
If I win, it means your team has lost!
What?
You said you'll aim for 2 centimeters.
-Remember?
-I'll get 2 centimeters!
Can we say you'll lose
if you don't make 2 centimeters?
What do you mean?
You're the one who said it!
Can I say 2 millimeters instead?
Those aren't the rules!
The rule is you don't hit the wall.
No, it's like a promise between men.
What do you mean, a promise between men?
I wonder if he's also going to
go defensive?
I think so, too.
He was saying there were no more
parts available to repair the car.
He looks nervous.
How are you feeling, Itakura?
It's looking good. I think I can win.
It is your car.
How are you going to act under pressure?
Mr. Hamada, I can get quite stupid
at times like these and go all out.
Really?
Toshiyuki Itakura (Mercedes-Benz S320)
vs Masaki Sata (Nissan Laurel 2000SGX)
Junior's army,
with their backs against the wall,
has sent Itakura from the comedy group
Impulse in this silver Mercedes.
Up against him is Sata
from the comedy group Bad Boys,
who used to be the head of a gang
that dominated the Kyushu area.
Sata is competing in his beloved
Nissan Laurel!
Could you...
Sata looks cool, calm and collected.
It's a bit tight, yes.
Itakura is having some issues. Is he okay?
Itakura in his Mercedes cannot
afford to lose this match.
Three... Two...
Sata is relaxed enough to smile!
One...
Go!
Here we go again.
Itakura is gaining a lot of speed here.
On the other hand,
Sata's not accelerating at all.
He already hit the brakes
before the braking zone!
Sata is disqualified.
How about Itakura? He stopped!
He did very well!
His result is 1 meter 25 centimeters!
Winner is Junior's army!
Masaki Sata (Nissan Laurel) - 35 km/h - DQ
Toshiyuki Itakura (Mercedes-Benz S320)
42 km/h, 1m 25cm, WIN
-God, he sucked!
-He chickened out!
Yes!
And whatever happened to Sata?
Where is he?
What happened to Sata?
What?
Wow, who would have thought?
What happened with the former gang leader!
He chickened out!
Such a terrible attempt!
I know how he feels...
He got scared
because he's driving his own car.
That's so embarrassing.
So uncool.
That was terrible.
Sata is the second driver apart
from Juichi Wakisaka to be disqualified
by breaching both the minimum speed limit
and the braking zone rule.
He can't deny he chickened out.
SENTOSHA
Let's have a look at the replay.
Go!
Here, Sata's being very, very careful.
Too careful!
His beloved Laurel is said to be
worth 7 million yen.
He needs to take good care of it.
He brakes way too early!
A loss for Hamada's army means
they are at three wins and two losses.
Junior's army is catching up.
Here's Sata. He's not competing at all!
He's already braking here.
He must love his Laurel a lot.
What a disappointing performance.
What was that?
That really sucked.
-That was really bad.
-Yes.
You lost by 10 m.
My car is like a wife to me.
You can't let your wife
sleep with some guy you don't know!
What are you talking about?
-It's not your wife.
-It's your car!
-It's like my wife!
-It's a car!
-She's my wife!
You don't understand!
You guys can fix it when it gets damaged.
You can buy the same car if you want!
You should go buy the latest car
on the market!
There'll be lots of parts for those cars.
So true! Just buy a car
that you can easily buy parts for!
You didn't even bring your own car!
For Junior's army to win this round,
they must win both
of the remaining battles.
Seventh Battle
For this battle, I'm sending...
Keiji Muto!
Yeah!
In that case, we're sending...
The man with a face that could kill!
Face that could kill. What?
-Hey, Muto!
-Yes!
We're adults,
let's aim for 80 kilometers per hour.
What? Why?
He said 80 kilometers per hour.
If we win the next battle,
we win this round.
What?
We're going to win!
We're not going to lose!
Lincoln Navigator
New car price 10 million yen
Next man up for Junior's army
is Keiji Muto.
His battle car is an American car, popular
with VIPs, the Lincoln Navigator.
One of its strengths is that a 5.4-liter
engine pulls a 2.5-ton monster.
Engine 5.4L V8DOHC / 304 hp / AWD / AT / 2500kg
Your cars are just like pieces of paper!
The unbeatable Pro Wrestling Master,
Keiji Muto
I'll smash all of them to bits! Yeah!
Toyota Century
New car price 12 million yen
For Hamada's army,
we have Hitoshi Ozawa.
His battle car is the pinnacle
of Japanese cars,
the legendary Toyota Century.
Engine 5L V12 DOHC / 280 hp / FR / AT / Weight 2000kg
Ozawa, the man with a face
that could kill, will be driving the car
favored by government officials
and company executives.
The man with a face that could kill,
Hitoshi Ozawa
I'm famous for my audacious attack
and pulverizing my opponents.
You better be ready for an all out attack.
I feel like Mr. Ozawa's
not gonna brake at all.
We'll just see him disappear
down the hill.
We're already up to the seventh match
in this round.
Here's something troubling...
An urgent update.
Ozawa from Hamada's army has brought along
a multitude of weapons and destructive
materials onto the battlefield.
Here's Muto.
And where's... Here's Ozawa.
What is he up to?
He's walking toward Junior.
Hey, Junior.
He wants to talk to
the other army's warlord.
Why are you sitting on your high horse?
He's coming!
The man with a face that could kill!
Here you go!
What's this?
It's an audacious attack!
-It's my gift to you.
-Was that a grenade?
Is he nuts?
He's so dangerous!
-It's a gift!
-He's laughing!
It would have been really dangerous
if that exploded just a little later.
-He threw a grenade.
-A grenade!
That's dangerous!
That man is really dangerous.
Has Muto realized
what his opponent has done?
I smell danger already.
It exploded at a good moment.
He looks rather satisfied.
Even we can't control him!
The battle is about to commence.
I wonder if Muto has realized
what just occurred?
He is being taken to his car
in the back of a utility truck.
Muto's knee is like a bomb
that's about to explode.
That was a rather serene image.
Mr. Ozawa, you don't happen
to be hiding a dead body in the trunk?
I can't be sure that there isn't...
I remember once I packed napalm
in the back of a jeep
and drove straight down a cliff.
-This is bad.
-You'll be fine.
-It's hard!
-You can do it!
I'll try my best.
If you lose,
it means we've lost this round.
-I know. I'll push it as much as possible.
-Good.
Now, here is Ozawa.
I wonder what he's going to do
in the race.
Keiji Muto (Lincoln Navigator)
vs Hitoshi Ozawa (Toyota Century)
There's a sense of danger and a scent
of gunpowder in this battle.
Muto...
Versus...
Ozawa.
Three...
Two... One...
Go!
Here they go.
They've both intentionally
driven into each other!
Jostling for position.
Ozawa in the Century
and Muto in the Navigator!
Now, they just need to hit the brakes!
They both need to stop before the wall!
Muto's stopped.
Ozawa crashed into the wall!
Did he even touch the brakes?
Looks like crashed into it
without braking at all!
The winner is Junior's army.
Hitoshi Ozawa (Toyota Century)
60 km/h - DQ
Keiji Muto (Lincoln Navigator)
56 km/h - 3m 60cm - WIN
What?
I wonder if Ozawa is okay?
Muto's result is 3 meters, 60 centimeters.
I'm so glad that I won!
SENTOSHA
Here's the replay.
Here, they both turn
toward their opponent.
They both did it intentionally.
The 54-year-old Muto
and 55-year-old Ozawa.
Ozawa looks like he's having fun!
I wonder if got overexcited
in the beginning?
Let's have a look at how he went
for the rest of the race.
Did he brake at all?
He just drove straight into the wall!
Well, he is known for doing
his own stunts in movies.
Now, both teams are neck and neck,
at three wins and three losses each!
SENTOSHA
We never knew what he was trying to do.
-Well done!
-Yeah!
-Well done, Muto!
-You gave them hell.
A 54-year-old and a 55-year-old.
The warriors have completed their battle.
That's a nice scene.
Mr. Ozawa's not injured.
You should run, Mr. Ozawa!
He looks like he won or something!
Stop acting like you just won!
He looks so cool.
You just lost!
Mr. Ozawa!
Mr. Muto looks like he lost.
You didn't brake at all!
You didn't brake!
But, well...
I couldn't accelerate at all
in the Century.
Remember I told you
I'd reach 60 kilometers per hour?
I got there, but I fell down the cliff.
-You only needed 40 kilometers per hour.
-Why 60?
He reached 40 kilometers per hour easily.
I got there just in time.
You think the minimum speed
for you is 60 kilometers per hour?
That's right.
So you reached your minimum of 60.
I can't break my promise.
This means both teams
are at three wins and one draw.
This round will be decided by the result
of the last battle.
Last Battle
Here we go to the last battle!
We've got Ryuji Harada!
He's handsome.
We've got... Go ahead!
It's Yamamoto!
Let's go!
He's the guy that needs to be
censored on screen.
I don't need to be censored on Amazon!
Really?
You should apologize for disappearing
for ten years.
Ten years! Such a long time!
Everything will be decided
with this battle.
I won't waste what the others have done
for the team.
My target is...
Eight centimeters.
All right!
That's about the size of a rice ball!
That's about right.
My rice ball is about 15 centimeters.
What are you aiming for?
-2.5 centimeters!
-Yeah!
Audi Allroad Quattro 2.7t
New car price approx. 8.6 million yen
Ryuji Harada from Junior's army.
His battle car is an Audi Allroad Quattro.
This car is a crossover SUV that boasts
first class on-road performance,
as well as the ability to adapt
to rugged terrain and go off-road.
Engine 3.2L V6 DOHC Twin Turbo / 255 hp / 4WD / AT / Weight 1860kg
Toyota Corolla Van
New car price 1.5 million yen
From Hamada's army, Keiichi Yamamoto.
His battle car is the Toyota Corolla Van.
With a maximum capacity of 400 kilograms,
it can carry 33 mandarin orange boxes.
It is the king of delivery cars.
Engine 1.3L I4 DOHC / 82 hp / FF / 4MT / Weight 930kg
Resurrected after ten years of silence,
the Golden Boy, Keiichi Yamamoto
I just have to go for it.
The hero who makes your blood curdle
Ryuji Harada
Today is a great day to die.
I'll do my best.
Now, the team that wins this final battle
will win the first round.
I'm excited. I never imagined that
the battle would come down
to the very last competitors.
I can't lose this. I'll keep an eye out
for what the opponent is doing,
and I'll go for it!
Just go drive into the sunset!
That's not a good idea.
Let's go, Yamamoto!
Ryuji Harada (Audi Allroad Quattro)
vs Keiichi Yamamoto (Toyota Corolla Van)
Here's Yamamoto.
He's the Golden Boy,
resurrected after ten years of silence.
On the other hand...
He looks very serious.
This is Ryuji Harada.
Now, the destinies of the two armies fall
on the shoulders of these two men.
-Let's go!
-Come on!
They are both fired up!
Three... Two... One...
Go!
Here they go!
They both need to reach
40 kilometers per hour first.
Harada's really stepping on it.
I wonder if he can brake in time?
Is he going too fast?
This is Yamamoto in his delivery van.
They just have to hit the brakes!
The result of this round rides
on this battle. They both stop!
Yamamoto's done very well!
Wow, this has turned into
an amazing battle!
-Who won?
-How is it?
The last battle looks to be the greatest!
-We've won!
It's us, it's us!
-Who won?
Who is it?
This is so close!
For now, it's hard to tell.
SENTOSHA
Let's have a look at the replay.
Harada looked like he was
carrying way too much speed,
but he brakes really hard right here.
Harada's not touching the wall.
Yamamoto's done really well, too.
It's hard to see because of the dust.
SENTOSHA
Who is the winner?
I've got that 2.5 cm.
Who won? It's me, right?
This is quite amazing.
Is it Junior or Hamada.
It's so close!
Such a close battle!
We've won!
We must have!
The results are in!
Yamamoto is at 30 cm.
Harada, wow, 1 cm!
The winner is Junior's army!
Yes!
Junior's army wins.
He hasn't touched the wall.
Yes!
The distance from the wall
is 1 centimeter.
Keiichi Yamamoto (Toyota Corolla Van)
41 km/h - 30cm
Ryuji Harada (Audi Allroad Quattro)
46 km/h - 1cm
You're kidding!
He's touching the wall.
He's touching!
Ryuji hit the wall!
SENTOSHA
Hamada's army claims
that Harada has hit the wall.
Let's have a look at the replay.
He has... not touched it! The wall shook
from the wind pressure,
but the car has not touched the wall!
He really stopped
at one centimeter from the wall!
He truly stopped at the very last moment!
Even though Yamamoto has stopped
30 centimeters from the wall, he has lost.
Junior's army draws first blood!
That's amazing!
Yeah!
What...
Mr. Yamamoto's result is 30 centimeters.
I got as close as 30 centimeters
and I lost?
We've won!
Round One - Junior's army wins
Hey, Hamada. Give us one of your cars!
Hand it over.
Give us one of your cars!
Give us the Laurel.
No way!
We'll give you Katsumata's car.
Katsumata's?
It's my Fairlady Z!
I bought it a long time ago.
All right then.
We'll accept the Fairlady Z.
Thank you.
Junior's army won the first round.
After losing the first three battles,
they managed to turn the tide.
Junior Castle is safe for now.
Advance, kill them all!
Retreat! Retreat for now!
Through this defeat,
Hamada's army
has lost Katsumata's Fairlady Z
and are now clearly at a disadvantage.
We've got another battle car in the works.
The cruel warlord from Osaka
who will do anything to win.
Hamada's next strategy will horrify
enemies and friends alike.
I'll kill you all!
Junior! Junior!
You tiny little gorilla.
Come and get me!
Please stop!
-What's this?
-Just keep going.
I can't see anything.
What are you doing?
Die!
SENTOSHA: Battle Wheels