The following program was produced with
the utmost consideration toward safety
and features dangerous activities which
were supervised by stunt professionals.
Do not attempt to reenact
any of the activities performed.
The start of the battle
grows closer and closer.
Here, at the foot of sacred Mount Fuji,
Hamada's and Junior's armies
get ready for battle
to decide who will reign supreme.
Battle Royale
Battle of the Cars
Here they are,
both armies' battle cars
are running full throttle.
They are all heading
straight to the battlefield.
Now you can see the battlefield.
On this battlefield,
foot soldiers
willing to fight to the death
will battle each other
in their battle cars.
There's an eerie silence here now,
but soon,
it will turn into a scene of carnage.
Wow, that's a quick start.
No, that's so dangerous.
He drives straight into him.
He drove straight into
the side of that car.
Die!
He drives into the back of the car
and pushes and pushes.
Go!
Oh, he's going backwards.
He must be terrified.
Now, fly!
No, he's not backing down.
SENTOSHA: Battle Wheels
The year is 2017.
A new castle appears
at the foot of Mount Fuji,
seemingly built overnight.
Junior Castle
A castle that's gorgeously decorated,
beautiful and brilliant.
Protecting this fortress
is a collection of cars
bought with a large amount of cash.
Eight luxury battle cars from the West.
All top-of-the-line cars
that symbolize these Western countries.
Here's the man
leading the reigning champions.
Nobody can bring down this castle!
Warlord,
Chihara Junior
The young warlord and strategist,
Chihara Junior.
Forward!
Brave, highly intelligent,
and full of speed and aggressiveness.
Chihara Junior's army
with its original and creative strategy
recently had great success
expanding its territory.
Now I'll start assigning
the battle cars to you.
Firstly, the Volvo V70.
It's for you, Fujimoto.
Master. Thank you very much.
Master.
You're laughing already.
Wait a moment.
The Junior's Army's man of just words,
no action, Toshifumi Fujimoto
His battle car is a Volvo V70.
This is Volvo's first ever
four-wheel-drive model.
Volvo was the first to invent
the three-point seat belt,
and due to their toughness,
these cars were commonly referred to
as flying bricks.
Their safety is second to none
in the world.
New car price approx. 7.4 million yen
Engine 2.5L I5 DOHC IC Turbo / 209 hp / 4WD / AT / Weight 1620kg
-Next, Tomoharu Shoji.
-Yes.
You'll be driving the Alfa Romeo Alfa GT.
Yes. Thank you very much.
You should be happy.
Master, thank you very much.
The reckless man who often shouts out
his wife's name, Tomoharu Shoji
This battle car is an Alfa Romeo Alfa GT.
New car price approx. 5.4 million yen
Engine 2L I4 DOHC / 166 hp / FF / Semi Automatic / Weight 1480kg
This car uses its own unique
transmission system called Selespeed,
which makes it difficult to handle
for someone who hasn't driven it before.
This is a sports car
equipped with a two-liter DOHC engine.
Next is Itakura.
You'll be driving the Mercedes Benz S320.
Wow.
Master!
Thank you very much, Master!
What is this? What did you do that for?
You're our master, aren't you?
You're our master.
Shut up.
You can't resort to violence
just because you're embarrassed.
Riding the Reaper's Express,
Toshiyuki Itakura
This battle car is a Mercedes Benz S320.
New car price approx. 10 million yen
Engine 3.2L V6 SOHC / 224 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1800kg
The S class is Mercedes' flagship model,
a luxury car
that everyone dreams of owning.
-Akina Minami.
-Yes.
You'll be driving
the Mercedes Benz SLK Kompressor.
-Yes.
-Yay! Thank you so much, Master.
See, it's perfect for a girl like you.
Yay, it's an open-top car.
I chose it especially for you.
Thank you so much.
Just because it's red
doesn't mean it suits women.
The evil angel who never decelerates,
Akina Minami
Her battle car is
a Mercedes Benz SLK230 Kompressor.
New car price approx. 4.8 million yen
Engine 2.3L I4 DOHC Super Charger / 197 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1380 kg
This is a top-class car that evolved
from the legendary roadster 190SL.
It's a two-seater sports car
that allows you to enjoy open air driving.
Shigekazu Wakisaka.
Yes.
You'll be driving the BMW 330i.
Master, thank you very much.
It's such a snazzy car.
-Say something, Master.
-I'll just absentmindedly stand here.
The current top racing driver,
Shigekazu Wakisaka
New car price approx. 5.7 million yen
Engine 3L I6 DOHC / 231 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1520kg
The next battle car is a BMW 330i.
The 3 series is BMW's main model,
and it is ranked alongside
the Mercedes Benz C class
as one of the most popular models
on the European market.
Matsuoka.
Yes.
You'll be driving the Jaguar XJ Executive.
Thank you, Master.
The boots!
Did you make your choice
based on the outfit I'm wearing today?
Yeah, you look stylish...
-It suits a Jaguar, so...
-Jaguar material?
That's right.
-Thank you very much.
-Are you for real?
The Rock'n'Rolling speedster,
Mitsuru Matsuoka
This battle car is a Jaguar XJ Executive.
New car price approx. 8.1 million yen
Engine 4.0L V8 DOHC / 243 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1730kg
Jaguar is a luxury car manufacturer
favored by the British royal family,
and among its cars,
this XJ is a luxury saloon model
that belongs to the very top tier.
Next is Ryuji Harada.
Master!
It's an Audi.
Let's hear it!
-Thank you very much.
-Well done.
The hero who makes your blood curdle,
Ryuji Harada
This battle car
is an Audi Allroad Quattro.
New car price approx. 8.6 million yen
Engine 3.2L V6 DOHC Twin Turbo / 255 hp / 4WD / AT / Weight 1860kg
In the '80s, Audi developed Quattro,
a four-wheel drive system.
It's a five-door SUV
which combines
first-class on-road performance
with the ability to adapt
to rugged off-road tracks.
Finally, Keiji Muto.
You will be driving the Lincoln Navigator.
Yes, Master.
Thank you very much
for giving me such a strong-looking car.
It looks so resilient.
It's extremely strong.
It's a champion.
It's the best.
The unbeatable Pro Wrestling Master,
Keiji Muto
This battle car is a Lincoln Navigator.
New car price 10 million yen
Engine 5.4L V8DOHC / 304 hp / AWD / AT / 2500kg
In the early 2000s,
this model was so popular
that around 40% of all SUVs
sold in the North American market
were Navigators.
One of its strengths
is that its 5.4-liter engine
pulls a two-and-a-half-ton monster.
And there was an evil army
creeping closer and closer
to Junior's impregnable army.
He will be here soon.
That barbarian!
Speedy Barbarian from Osaka
Achoo!
Someone must be talking about me
behind my back.
Hamada Castle, Osaka
A change of scenery,
and we're at a creepy-looking castle
situated in the Shinsekai region of Osaka.
Here's its master...
Here you go.
Wait just a minute.
Warlord
Masatoshi Hamada
He looks like a man,
but has the heart of a monster
He's a beast wearing human skin.
You're wonderful.
Hamada's lover
Seiko from Amako Inter
He uses women as his playthings
in the castle.
Hamada is a pervert from Osaka.
God, he has bad taste in women.
He goes for anything that moves.
Hamada Army's Foot Soldier,
Seiji Chihara
It feels so good.
Master.
Oh...
Hamada's Army - Ninja
Masaki Sata
Say what?
That Chihara Junior has built a castle!
No way!
Seiji.
Did you hear
what your little brother has done?
Yes, sir.
We're going to go take his castle,
do you hear me?
Get ready.
Yes, Master.
No way!
It's war!
This was the way
Hamada's army fought its battles,
following a win-at-all-costs strategy.
He's sneaky and vulgar,
and a complete and utter sadist.
Hamada's fleet of battle cars
doesn't look flashy.
Highly functional cars,
all primarily manufactured in Japan.
Through Hamada's dictatorial leadership,
his men have been trained
never to disobey his orders.
They're a bunch of extremists willing
to risk their lives for their master.
Master Hamada.
Junior's army
has a total of eight battle cars.
We are at a bit of a disadvantage.
We're two cars short.
Yes.
I have no choice.
Let's go with that plan.
The day of the battle has arrived.
Hamada's plan
to add to his fleet of battle cars
has now begun in earnest.
Hamada is two battle cars short.
His plan to add to his fleet
was so devious,
it was hard to believe.
It's the first time that I bought a car.
First time.
It's only been a month
since I came to Tokyo.
I'm so jealous.
I haven't even told my mom.
Really?
I haven't told her that I bought a car.
Seiko of Amako Inter
Nagisa of Amako Inter - Kanako Kadowaki
Really?
Because she'll get worried.
I guess.
She'll go, "Why so soon?
"It's only been a month
since you've come to Tokyo."
I saw this car on the road and I liked it,
so I looked it up on the Internet.
I checked out all the specs
on the car info website.
Yoshimasa Iwasaki of Plus Minus
Nana Yamada
I'd been hemming and hawing for a while.
Then I finally found this car.
It's been customized the way I like it.
We're arriving at Ebina...
We're here at Ebina.
We're at Ebina.
Is this a brand-new car?
No, it's secondhand.
Really? It still looks so new.
The dealer gave me a really good deal.
Wow.
He was an amazing dealer.
It feels good
driving with the windows down.
Feeling the breeze.
If you saw this car on the road...
It's great, right?
It looks so cool.
-Yeah.
-Somewhere near the...
SUSONO
EXIT THRU TRAFFIC
What's going on?
Hamada Army's Foot Soldier
Kunikazu Katsumata
Everything is going well, Master.
-We're short of two cars.
-No problem. We're handling it.
It's all okay.
Currently, the first car
is heading this way.
We're going to use Amako Inter's car.
Battle Car Hunting Strategy 1 - Lure
Nagisa's car by filming a fake TV show
Amako Inter thinks they're filming
a TV segment called Driving around Tokyo.
They'll arrive here very soon.
So we're duping them, right?
That's right.
I feel sorry for them.
They know absolutely nothing.
It's the first time
they got their own show, right?
-Yes.
That's right.
So Nagisa's gone and bought a car
just for that show.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
-Really?
-She bought a car.
-She's really coming in her own car?
-In her own car.
She still has a loan on it, too.
She hasn't paid it off yet.
She only paid the deposit.
She was supposed to pay off the loan
bit by bit during that series.
Is that right?
She was going to use the money
she was getting paid to do the show.
Wow.
She will be so excited and happy
when she turns up here.
-Oh, well. We had no choice.
-Yes.
It's her darling little car.
Two months ago
The seeds of this plan
were sown two months ago.
Tokyo Drive!
The first filming is going to cover
Nagisa's first car purchase.
Yay!
It's amazing.
Fake Show Planning Sheet
"Amako Inter's Tokyo Drive"
Amako Inter's Tokyo Drive is a fake show
that Hamada's army made up.
Fake Show Planning Sheet
Show begins with Nagisa of Amako Inter
purchasing a new car in Tokyo.
(Nagisa will be liable
to pay off the car loan personally)
The conditions for appearing in this show
were for Nagisa to personally purchase
a car with her own money.
Plus...
What? I told all of my relatives.
Seiko of Amako Inter
Nagisa's going to have a meltdown
if she finds out.
Stabs partner in the back
to be part of Hamada's army
The army had drawn in
Nagisa's comedy partner Seiko
on the plan at an early stage.
It's a foolproof plan.
When you buy a car
-with your own money...
-Yes.
...you take really good care of it.
Yeah, you'll treasure it.
You'll want to keep it clean and tidy.
I'm going to buy my own car
for the first time in my life.
Wow, there are lots of different types.
Firstly, Nagisa will purchase a car
with her own money.
Blue Auto, Yokosuka City
Here, she falls in love
with a particular car.
We'll ask the dealer.
What's the model of this car?
That is a Nissan Fuga.
Fuga.
This car is considered
a Japanese luxury car.
Engine 3.5L V6 DOHC / 280 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1680kg
Wow.
Wow, it's amazing.
I like it a lot.
It's really great.
It's really similar to the car
that my ex-boyfriend had,
-so it feels really familiar.
-I see.
It feels natural and comfortable.
If you buy today, you get a discount.
It's yours for 350,000 yen
instead of 500,000.
-Really? 350,000?
-Yes.
-If I decide today?
Of course.
Whoa.
I'll take this one.
Thank you very much.
I really have to fill in the contract
and everything.
Nagisa purchases the Fuga
without a second thought,
drawn in by the discount.
BLUE AUTO CO. LTD.
I wanted to drive it home.
I don't want anyone else to touch it.
I understand.
It belongs to me now.
And two weeks later...
Have a look at this.
-What?
-See the wheel?
The Delivery of the Nissan Fuga
The wheel used to be silver,
but now it's black.
It's perfect for you, right?
The Fuga that used to ooze luxury
has been pimped
according to Nagisa's tastes.
Light covers and front grill,
and the wheels have been painted black.
Please note that this car
meets the safety standards
of the Road Trucking Vehicle Act (Japan).
The car has been customized to suit
Nagisa's rather questionable tastes.
Your first drive.
Whoa.
This is amazing.
It's really running!
How did you feel on your first drive?
Amazing.
I've never been so happy.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
-I really love it.
-That's good.
I'm so glad and...
-Happy?
-I wanted to...
I want to tell my mom I bought a car.
I want to let her know.
And the day of the battle arrives.
This meant the first episode
of Amako Inter's Tokyo Drive
was also going to be shot today.
Amako Inter's Tokyo Drive
The filming of the first episode
Hey, hey, hey!
Watch where you're driving.
Today's destination is Susono,
near Mount Fuji.
Seriously? Where the hell is that?
This is supposed to be a show about
going for a nice drive with a guest star
and talking about
the stylish lifestyle in Tokyo...
Hamada's Army - Ninja
Kanako Kadowaki
The guest star Kanako Kadowaki
is part of Hamada's army,
assigned to lure Nagisa.
What?
I'd like to see it.
You'd never want to scratch it, right?
No, I'd hate that.
I know.
I don't even want anyone to make a mess
by eating snacks in the car.
You love it that much?
2 Hours Later
Nagisa doesn't know yet that
she and the Fuga would end up like this.
No way. You can't do that to me.
Oh, my God, I'm so scared.
They're supposed to meet up
with a secret guest star
for the fake show
Nagisa thinks they're filming
at Susono near Mount Fuji.
Now we're meeting up
with the secret guest star.
Yeah, we're going to the meeting point?
That's right.
This is so exciting.
-I know.
-I really don't know who it is.
I wonder who it is.
Who do you think it is?
We have to turn onto this narrow road.
Okay.
Here we go.
There are so many people.
Okay.
Ready?
It looks really scary.
I'm so scared.
What's going on?
Sata, please guide them here.
Yes, sire.
It's such a lovely car.
It's a nice car.
She just bought it, right?
She washed it as well.
Oh, no way. No way, no way.
She's laughing.
She must be happy to see you.
She's got a leopard print cover
on the steering wheel.
This is so scary.
Let's get out.
What?
Come on out.
How are you, Nagisa?
Come over here.
Wow.
What are you up to?
We were filming a show called Tokyo Drive.
Uh-huh...
It's the first time
we've had our own show.
It's going to be shown on Amazon.
-Congratulations.
And the conditions were
that I buy my own car.
I see.
So I went and...
You bought the car?
How much did it cost?
Total was about 500,000 yen.
Wow.
The deposit...
500,000 yen in total?
I borrowed the deposit of 100,000 yen
from Yoshimoto Finance.
You borrowed the 100,000 yen?
It looks great.
You borrowed your deposit amount too?
Yes, all of it.
You borrowed 100,000 yen from your Agency.
Look here...
It's so shiny.
Look at your steering wheel.
Leopard print.
It's a leopard print
steering wheel cover.
They modified it just for me.
Looks so clean.
It's the perfect car for you, Nagisa.
I love leopard print, yes.
Looks so new.
-Look at the rear.
-Is it all leopard print?
There's a sticker of our show Tokyo Drive.
On the back?
Wow. A sticker for your own show.
Wow.
I need to work hard
to pay off the debt for this car.
I see.
You need to make Tokyo Drive
a popular show.
-Yes.
-Hey, Nagisa.
Do you know what we do here?
Do you know why we're here?
Well, we've been told
that we're welcoming
a special guest star for our show.
What, you knew?
That's the reason?
That's why you're not so surprised.
No, I'm scared to death.
Why?
You didn't expect us?
Why are you afraid?
You didn't expect
such a big star to be here?
I'm shaking at the knees.
-The three of you, come with me.
-Yes.
She's very lucky.
We can use that car.
-Yes, looks good.
-We should use it.
It's almost new.
I think it's just been serviced, too.
The tires and the rims look sturdy too.
Very strong.
Top class.
Why are there four special guests?
-Then it's decided.
-Yes.
-Decision made.
-Decided.
Let's go.
Well done.
-You've done a great job.
-You've passed.
What do you mean?
Well done.
I've decided to make you
one of my foot soldiers.
It's decided.
Foot soldier?
On to the next stage.
-Next stage?
-Yes.
-Congratulations.
-Congrats.
What's going on?
I'm really scared. Please don't touch me.
Did you think he'd snap your neck?
Please stand a safe distance away from me.
You're scheming something, aren't you?
Of course not.
Sorry we're late.
Really sorry.
What are you doing?
What is this?
You've been duped, Nagisa. Dumb-ass.
Dumb-ass.
Do you want me to smack you?
What are you saying?
We'd never get our own show
just like that.
Yes.
Why? I bought the car and everything.
That's right. That's right.
Of course.
The stories you told us in the car,
they weren't that funny.
I thought so too.
You didn't strike up a good conversation?
Not really.
Come on. You were enjoying yourself.
-Nagisa.
-Yes.
You never had your own show.
Why not?
You're going to become a Sentosha
in Hamada's army.
-That's right.
-What's a Sentosha?
If you didn't have this car, you wouldn't
be allowed into Hamada's army.
That's right.
Why can't I join if I didn't have a car?
That's the way it works.
It generally works that way.
I told you, it's called Sentosha.
Yes.
I've been wondering about that.
-I'm worried...
-You like battles, right?
Amagasaki's Reckless Magical Girl,
Nagisa of Amako Inter
Nissan Fuga
New car price approx. 5.7 million yen
Nagisa has entered this battle
with her own car.
This is an executive-class car
that was developed to take over
from the Nissan Cedric and Gloria.
This GT model is a sports car
that runs on a 3.5-liter engine
that generates 280 horsepower.
I was having so much fun
driving on the freeway.
Talking about lots of things.
So scary.
Where's the other car?
He'll explain.
-Yes.
-Master Hamada.
For this next car,
we've organized a TV program.
The contestants will go
from one Service Area to the next,
eating various gourmet foods at each stop.
It's called SA1 Grand Prix.
It's a fake show.
-Another fake show?
-Yes.
The driver will bring his beloved vehicle.
Currently, Iwahashi from the comedy duo
Plus Minus is heading this way.
He'll be here soon.
Sentosha hunting plan 2
Lure Iwahashi's car through a fake TV show
Looks like he's having
a lot of fun filming so far.
Of course he is.
He's been told both Seiji and I
will be doing the show with him.
I see.
He just thinks we're filming
in a different location.
We're supposed to be competing
with one another.
I understand.
The point of the show
is that you're using your own car.
-Today, we'll be going on a trip...
-Yes.
-...in Mr. Iwahashi's beloved car.
Hamada's Army - Ninja
Nana Yamada
Now Mr. Iwahashi,
what kind of car do you drive?
Yes, this is my car.
Wow, such a cool car.
It's a Honda Crossroad.
Engine 1.8L SOHC / 140 hp / 4WD / Weight 1480kg
It looks so cool.
Isn't it cute?
So cool.
It's both stylish and cute
at the same time.
It's the best car ever.
"Fake Show Planning Sheet"
"SA-1 Grand Prix"
SA-1 Grand Prix is also a fake show
that Hamada's army had made up
to secure another battle car.
I'll dig in.
The participants
will drive their own cars,
going from one Service Area to another
as a gourmet.
After they eat various items on the menu,
Great rice!
they must pick what belongs
on the top five most popular foods
at these Service Areas.
It's not the most fascinating show
you've ever seen.
Is it hot?
It's hot.
This car feels so smooth and comfortable.
I know, right?
Yes.
You know, as time passes,
these kinds of cars become rare.
It's not about the money,
it's worth so much more.
-It means a lot to you?
-That's right.
I want to keep it well maintained.
I really want to drive it
for a very long time.
A very long time?
Yeah, my wife loves this car as well.
Is that so?
Yeah.
2 Hours Later
It was his beloved car full of memories.
But two hours later,
this will happen to it.
Seiji, who is supposed to be appearing
on the same TV program,
tries contacting Iwahashi on the phone.
I go to golf in it...
There's a call coming through.
A call?
-Yes, a call.
-Okay.
It's Seiji. Can I answer?
Hello.
Good morning, this is Seiji.
Good morning, this is Iwahashi.
Thank you.
I look forward to filming today.
Yes, me too. You know...
Yes?
My guest star was Mr. Osamu,
our agency's veteran comedian.
Bonchi Osamu
Has similar characteristics to Iwahashi
Really?
You sound surprised.
-You're kidding.
-No, I'm not.
No, it was Mr. Osamu.
Wait...
So you're with Mr. Osamu now?
No, he just left.
So...
We're expecting another guest star
to join us soon?
Yeah.
Yeah, it will be similar to what we did.
So it's going to be Mr. Osamu
for me as well?
Well, it was him for my segment.
I think you should prepare something
to talk about with Mr. Osamu.
This is not good. Mr. Osamu
has the same characteristics as me.
We'll have frictions
and never get any work done.
I see... Where are you now?
We just passed Gotemba.
You're nearly there.
You're nearby?
Yeah, I'll wait for you
at the first meeting point.
Okay, thank you very much.
Sure thing.
Oh, no. Mr. Osamu is there.
Has Mr. Osamu joined Seiji's team?
Mr. Osamu jumps like this.
He can only ride in an open-top car.
Really?
Mr. Osamu never lets cameras
into his house.
That's right.
His wife doesn't want cameras
in the house ever again.
It's because Osamu
gets too tired afterwards.
Iwahashi's car draws closer and closer
to the location
where the Dark Army awaits.
He's here.
He is here.
He's here?
He's slow.
-He's coming now.
-It's such a nice car.
What?
What's going on?
Sata, bring him over here.
He parked his car there. Come on over.
Oh, no. This doesn't look good.
What the hell are you doing?
-Come on over.
-Don't let him escape.
Come over here.
This is so scary. What's going on?
What is this?
He knows that a special guest
is joining him, right?
What's going on?
He's coming.
What is this?
What's this? What's going on?
Here.
Here you go.
Oh, no. What?
-I want to open the back too.
-Stop.
Here.
Why do you want to open the back?
I don't get it. What is this?
Hurry up and get out.
Good morning.
Thanks for coming.
What are you doing?
-Come on, get out.
-Get out.
Stop the engine.
Get out.
I really don't get it.
-What's wrong with you?
-Why are you screaming?
We've been waiting for you.
What a great car you have.
What's going on?
How did you get this car?
I bought it.
I saved up.
How much was it?
1.3 million yen.
Wow!
I bought it two years ago.
These wheels have been modified?
They have.
No, these didn't come with the car.
That looks so cool. You've customized it.
I changed it to a special type.
What else?
What else did you change?
The over fender here...
Wow.
I changed the position
of the muffler as well.
You've changed that, too?
It looks more discreet?
That's right. Just the exhaust.
The muffler... What?
What's wrong?
-What happened?
-What's wrong?
Shut up.
I don't know what's going on!
Everyone, come over here.
I still don't know what's going on.
Okay.
I don't understand the situation!
It's a really good car.
This car is fantastic.
It's a great car.
-It's really stable.
-It'll work really well.
It's a four-wheel drive.
It would be suitable.
What are you talking about?
Lots of horsepower, too.
Tell me what you're talking about.
It's a really good find.
Yes.
Am I just talking to myself?
Agreed.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Done.
What's done?
You've passed.
Congratulations.
Congrats. Well done.
For what?
What was just decided?
Decision made.
You've passed.
What did I pass?
-We had a close look at your car.
-Okay.
You've passed.
Well done. Congrats.
Congratulations.
What did I pass?
-You've qualified to be my foot soldier.
-Foot soldier?
She's here.
She's gotten changed.
Come join us.
It's Yamada. She was just next to me.
Hey, Iwahashi.
What?
What happened?
You were enjoying yourself
driving along with me.
She was our spy.
Yeah.
You're so gullible, being duped so easily.
Damn, we were getting along so well
that I thought you might suck me off
at the end of the day.
You're such a lowlife.
Stop joking around.
Itchy.
You're the worst.
The worst.
What are you doing?
The uncontrollable hitman,
Yoshimasa Iwahashi
Honda Crossroad
New car price 2.9 million yen
Iwahashi is joining the battle
with his own car, the Honda Crossroad.
Its main characteristics
are high vehicle height
and the rectangular body.
This car has been customized
with a larger set of tires,
and an over fender.
It's Iwahashi's original model.
I don't understand
what Hamada's army means.
I know.
What does it mean?
It doesn't make any sense.
I was told I needed to buy a car
to shoot this series.
Since I saw Mr. Hamada there,
I realized it wasn't part of the show
I was shooting this morning.
I don't know.
I don't know...
I could crash into all of them.
Hamada's army
will soon arrive at this battlefield,
where Junior's army awaits.
Attack!
Here they are.
The lowlife barbarians from Osaka.
Look at those clunky-looking cars.
Yeah.
Here they are entering the battlefield,
led by the pervert barbarian from Osaka
who uses any means to win.
Hamada's army.
How could they show their faces?
Looks like a suburban car park.
Well said.
As opposed to Junior's army
that's full of foreign luxury cars,
Hamada will battle
with a fleet of Japanese cars.
Here's some breaking news.
Hamada has assembled his fleet
using somewhat dubious tactics.
Strategy that's barely legal.
There's a bamboo spear
taped to the muffler.
They are raring to go. And what's this?
That looks like someone's company car.
-Like, a regular car?
-A company car.
It's a company car.
Looks like a real estate agent's car.
Come on,
we don't use bamboo spears anymore.
The Honda Crossroad
and Nissan Fuga at the rear.
Yes, these are battle cars
forcibly made to join Hamada's army.
With this fleet of eight cars,
Hamada will attempt
to bring down Junior's castle.
Yeah. Are the battle cars ready?
Yes, they're as ready as they can be.
We're ready.
I still don't get it...
Could someone please explain to me
what is going on?
Yeah, all of it.
I really don't understand.
-Hey, Sata.
-Yes.
You brought along you own car too?
Yes, of course.
Here it is.
This is it.
It's a vintage vehicle.
Wow.
Well, well.
This car is 41 years old.
It was released in 1976.
I'd say there's only about
30 of these cars left in Japan.
Wow!
If I take it to a dealer,
they'll offer me seven million yen.
What?
-Seriously?
-That's what kind of car this is.
But I brought this car today,
under strict orders from our agency.
"Mr. Hamada wants your car," they said.
That's right.
The man who nearly united Kyushu,
Masaki Sata
Nissan Laurel 2000SGX
New car price 1.03 million yen
Engine 2L I6 SOHC / 130 hp / FR / 5MT / Weight 1200kg
Sata has courageously entered this battle
with his car, the Nissan Laurel.
This is a second-generation
Nissan Laurel C130 model,
first brought to the market in 1972.
Due to its two-door hardtop shape,
it's been nicknamed "pig's butt."
It's an extremely rare car that is
very popular with vintage car enthusiasts.
And this?
It's mine.
-The Z model is my car.
-Okay.
The man who wears shorts all year round,
Kunikazu Katsumata
His battle car is the Nissan Fairlady Z.
New car price 3.5 million yen
Engine 3.5L V6 DOHC / 280 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1440kg
It's Japan's true sports car.
Although it weighs only 1,500 kilograms,
it carries a 3.5-liter engine
and can output 280 horsepower.
-Whose is this?
-This is mine.
Wow.
The Chihara family's mad dog,
Seiji Chihara
His battle car is a Toyota Celsior.
New car price 8 million yen
Engine 4.3L V8 DOHC / 280 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1800kg
This is Toyota's executive-class car
which evolved into the Lexus brand.
This model continues to be popular
among hard-faced men like Seiji.
Who does this belong to?
This doesn't look good.
No way...
What's wrong with you?
I've driven a lot of cars,
but nothing like this.
I've never seen anything like this.
What are you talking about?
The only thing that matters
is the horsepower, not what it looks like.
If you say so...
The best driver in a thousand years
(according to himself), Juichi Wakisaka
The car assigned to a driver
who has only driven a Toyota for 16 years
is from a rival manufacturer,
a Nissan Skyline.
Modified to suit flashy drivers
from Chiba and Ibaraki,
it features a giant over fender,
and a muffler made out of bamboo spears.
It is destined to be very fast.
New car price 3.1 million yen
Engine 2.5L I6 DOHC / 200 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1400kg
So this car...
Awesome!
It's a perfect fit for you.
It really is.
This looks really strong.
Indeed.
We need you to perform well.
Yes, that's true.
We need you to be healthy
till the very end.
You don't need to worry about me.
The man with a face that could kill,
Hitoshi Ozawa
His battle car is a Toyota Century.
New car price 12 million yen
Engine 5L V12 DOHC / 280 hp / FR / AT / Weight 2000kg
This car was manufactured to celebrate
the 100th birthday of Sakichi Toyoda,
the founder of Toyota Industries.
It's a limited-edition car
that Japan can be proud of.
This is the only car that distinguishes
those who drive it as VIPs.
It is often used by Japanese government
officials and high-class executives.
Excuse me, Mr. Hamada.
What's up?
Having seen the cars up until now...
Hey, you're...
Are you allowed to be on-screen?
It's Mr. Mosaic.
Yes...
Apparently, it's okay on Amazon Prime.
Thank you very much, Amazon Prime.
-That's great.
-I still...
Is it a little early?
It's still early for regular TV.
Thank you to Amazon.
Wait just a second.
What is this?
Have a look at this entry and compare it
to the other cars in the team.
It kind of looks like a delivery car.
I see this type of car
around the Kabukicho area in Tokyo.
Delivery cars, right?
Cars delivering things to various shops.
It does look like a delivery car.
That's right, it's a delivery car.
Nonetheless...
I'm trying to make a mark here today.
Fair enough.
Resurrected after ten years of silence,
the Golden Boy, Keiichi Yamamoto
His battle car is the Toyota Corolla Van.
New car price 1.5 million yen
Engine 1.3L I4 DOHC / 82 hp / FF / 4MT / Weight 930kg
In the van bonnet class,
it has been
the number-one selling car for 26 years.
With a maximum weight capacity
of 400 kilograms,
it can carry 33 mandarin orange boxes.
This is the king of delivery cars.
-Here we go.
-Yes.
-Wait a minute.
-What's up?
I really love this car.
Can we take this off?
HAMADA 0511
HAMADA'S ARMY
Why do you want to take it off?
-You should be proud to have it on.
-It's a battle car now.
It's got "Hamada" written
on a black plate.
No, it's too dangerous. I can't have it.
It's a battle car.
It's the same for Nagisa.
I just can't...
You keep saying "battle car."
This is a guess, but...
It's not going to come back
in one piece, right?
-Right?
-It depends on how you decide to fight.
That's right.
It depends on how well you play.
I can only think of a terrible ending.
This is so much better than that boring,
fake TV show, right?
Which do you prefer?
This one?
It's all good then. It's all good.
Sentosha Battle Royale.
The battle is about to begin.
Take a look at that.
Who's that ugly woman?
Who?
Wow.
She's beyond ugly.
Hey.
What's with the ugly woman?
What?
I can tell that she's ugly
even from this distance.
I must admit
I'm a bit uncomfortable as well.
My team is just a bunch of weirdos.
There's also someone
who can't be on-screen.
Yeah.
It's okay to be on Amazon.
You can only see him on Amazon.
I can only appear on Amazon.
All right then.
Thank you, Amazon.
It's probably not the best time for this,
but it's very nice to meet you.
-What? First time?
-Is it the first time you met?
-Pretty much the first time.
-Really, the first time?
Seriously?
Yes, it really is the first time.
Pretty much the first time.
However, a very long time ago,
when we were doing
a comedy show in Nagoya,
we did catch a glimpse
of the Chihara Brothers
having a backstage fight.
But that's all.
They were having a fist fight
with another comedy duo.
Me and my partner tried to break it up.
You didn't actually do it.
Who were they fighting?
The Battle Begins
Look at this.
He's got a grenade in his hand.
One battle car pushes another one
right around.
Now we're coming along
to the slippery zone.
He can't stop.
Is he okay?
He's on his roof.
SENTOSHA