The following program was produced with
the utmost consideration toward safety
and features dangerous activities which
were supervised by stunt professionals.
Do not attempt to reenact any
of the activities performed.
Annihilate the opposition's battle cars.
That is the aim for both Hamada's
and Junior's armies,
to decide whose army reigns supreme.
Junior's army won the first round
after storming back from the brink.
However, the true hell of battle
will only now be unleashed.
YOU MIGHT DIE, ROUND 2
THE ROAD TO HELL
You might die, round two.
The Road to Hell.
Road to Hell?
-You might die?
-I don't wanna die.
DANGER - DANGER - DANGER
Overcome various obstacles
and reach the finish line first.
All foot soldiers from both teams
will participate in this round.
The team with the best total time
will win.
The losing team will need to hand over
one of their battle cars
to the winning team.
START - GOAL
The total distance of this course
is one kilometer.
Two cars will start at the same time.
The car that finishes first, wins.
Right at the start of the course
is the Hell Slope,
a steep, 60-degree downhill slope.
At the bottom of that slope
is a narrow hairpin curve,
only wide enough to fit one car.
After the curve,
there is a short climb
up to a 50 centimeter jump zone.
After landing,
you must navigate through
a hellish 30-degree bank area.
THE 30-DEGREE BANK FROM HELL
Beyond that area, there is a sharp curve
made hellishly slippery by laying
metal plates across the area.
THE SHARP CURB WITH METAL PLATES FROM HELL
Then we come across the bumpy zone
with a series of logs
lined across the course.
THE LOG ROAD FROM HELL
Then comes the explosion area.
This is a dangerous area
where drivers won't know
when, where
or how large an explosion there will be.
THE EXPLOSION AREA FROM HELL
Then, the drivers must navigate past
the giant swinging stone
to reach the finish line.
"The Road to Hell Laws"
The team that finishes the race first
will be awarded points
according to the time difference
with their opponents.
If they win by one second,
the winner will be awarded one point.
Any time difference over ten seconds
will be awarded with ten points.
We'd like to see someone
do a test drive first.
-Yeah.
-We wanna see what's so hellish about it.
We can't compete just like that
after being told "you might die."
-It's scary.
-Hey, Junior.
Can you show us?
-Please show us.
-Please.
It's an obvious course!
-No.
-Just look at the course!
We wanna get feedback from someone
who's actually driven the course.
-It's pretty clear!
-It's not clear to us, Junior.
Come on, please show us.
Let's go, sir.
Our master, Mr. Test Pilot,
is going to show us how it's done.
-What are you talking about?
-Don't take it too seriously.
-Just give us the data.
-Don't think too much about it.
No, no, no!
-No, no, no!
-Don't be so reluctant.
Junior and I, we're the warlords.
You're going to show us
because you're our leader.
That's right.
If I knew this was going to happen,
I wouldn't have had ramen for lunch!
We don't know what
we're facing at this stage.
Let's get in.
What? Why me?
Thank you, sire!
Thank you!
I don't need a ride! I really don't.
-Go check out what hell looks like.
-This sucks!
-You're coming too, Seiko?
-They made me!
I'm so scared!
Now, the warlords from both armies
are going to inspect
the course themselves.
I don't see the need for us to do this.
Three... Two...
I'm so scared...
One... Go!
Each car is being driven by
professional race car drivers
from Takahashi Pro Racing.
Right after the start, they encounter
a sudden 60-degree drop
that has been dubbed, the Hell Hill,
as it will scare the daylights
out of anyone.
Before they can take a breath,
they come across the hairpin curve
barely wide enough for them to turn.
The trailing car can hardly see
what's ahead of them,
because of the dust cloud created by
the leading car.
One can use this strategy to
their advantage in the race.
Then comes the 50 cm jumping pass,
and the 30-degree bank
made just for this show.
And here's the slippery curve lined
with metal plates.
We expect a lot of accidents
to occur right here.
Now this is the bumpy log area,
where four-wheel drive vehicles
will have a distinct advantage.
As expected, this car is slipping
and sliding across the slippery area.
No, no, no!
Now, they've entered the explosive area.
No one knows when and where it'll happen,
or how big the explosion is going to be.
This is the main street
of the "Road to Hell."
They've bumped into each other!
Of course, you are allowed to
run into your opponent.
You're also allowed to cut off
your opponent.
The rock! The rock!
They've now passed the explosives area
and these giant rocks
are blocking their way.
Those who can overcome the fear of death
and keep accelerating,
will win this battle.
That is the "Road to Hell"!
We finished first!
They've finished.
Are you okay, Mr. Hamada?
Mr. Hamada?
Are you okay?
-Mr. Hamada!
-Are you okay?
Are you okay, Junior?
Mr. Hamada, are you okay?
-Are you okay?
-He's dead!
It's so dusty!
He's dying!
-Are you okay?
-He's dying!
He's dying!
-What's wrong?
-Junior?
Princess? Master and Princess!
Junior!
They're so dusty!
Are you okay?
What happened to you?
He's going to throw up.
The ramen's going to come out!
How are you?
Is it frightening?
It's really scary...
The first slope downhill is like, boom!
Then you go careening around the corner,
and suddenly, you see nothing!
It's such a big drop!
-And you went down pretty fast, too.
-It's that scary right from the beginning?
Can we even race this course?
We're going to drive, right?
-We can...
-Can we sit in the passenger's seat?
-We can't.
-Impossible.
You can do it. Just try to
get in each other's way.
Yeah.
"Sentosha Laws" - Battle 1, Battle 2,
Battle 3: Scramble over battle cars
The battle will consist of four rounds.
For the first three rounds,
both armies will battle to win over
the opponent's car.
The winning team can select one car
from the losing team to join their army.
For the fourth and final round,
the remaining cars will battle each other
until one team has no cars remaining.
The team with more cars left
at the start of the final round
will have a distinct advantage
in the battle.
Battle 4: Wipe out opposing army
with your remaining cars
In the first round,
Junior's army drew first blood.
First Round - Junior's Victory
Harada's result, wow, one centimeter!
Yes!
Junior's army was able to gain
the Nissan Fairlady Z from Hamada's army.
9 versus 7
The current state of play is
Junior's army with nine battle cars,
versus Hamada's army with seven.
The next battle starts now.
First Battle
-Hey, Junior!
-Yes?
-Can I give you a suggestion?
You know, we lost the last battle.
Yeah.
-Hey!
-Show some respect!
He's suddenly very arrogant!
-What's wrong with you?
-You're too good for us now?
It's strange.
I want to suggest that we keep
the same match ups from the last round.
What?
We want the same match ups,
but we want to win this time.
-Yeah!
-We want revenge!
We want to avenge our loss.
Well...
All right, whatevs.
You're disrespecting us again!
Then you're up first, Akina!
Yay!
-Remember she crashed into you last time!
-Watch out for Akina!
You can't let her push you around!
She'll try to ram me again, won't she?
Then I'm going to run from her.
Mercedes-Benz SLK230 Kompressor
New car price approx. 4.8 million yen
The evil angel who never decelerates,
Akina Minami.
Her battle car is
a Mercedes-Benz SLK230 Kompressor.
Engine 2.3L I4 DOHC Super Charger /
197 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1380 kg
Nissan Fuga
New car price approx. 5.7 million yen
Amagasaki's reckless magical girl,
Nagisa from Amako Inter.
Her battle car is her own Nissan Fuga,
which she still hasn't paid off
the loan for yet.
Engine 3.5L V6 DOHC / 280 hp / FR / AT /
Weight 1680kg
Go!
In the first round,
THE FIRST ROUND
STOP RIGHT AT THE EDGE
Akina tried to damage the Fuga
rather than trying to win the match.
Wow, Akina seems to only
care about attacking the Fuga.
The winner is Nagisa!
The second round of the grudge match
is about to begin.
What will be the fate of the Nissan Fuga?
She crashed into me!
Next, in the fierce battle between
Hamada's and Junior's armies.
You Might Die, Round 2.
This round is a timed race through
the "Road to Hell" course.
Driving for Junior's army is Akina Minami
in the red Mercedes.
And in the white Nissan Fuga
that still hasn't been paid off yet
is Nagisa from Hamada's army.
Hey, Nagisa.
-Can you hear me?
-Yes, I can.
-You beat her to a pulp!
-Yes, sir!
She already attacked you once.
Make sure you pay her back, okay?
Yes. I'll get into the zone.
He's telling me to smash her car.
I told him I don't want to damage my car,
but Hamada's telling me to attack.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
-You're late!
-I'm sorry...
Don't touch my car!
-Don't touch my car.
-Why?
I don't want my car to get damaged!
It was only a scratch last time,
but I'll ensure I make
a big dent this time!
She's totally crazy.
Isn't this fun?
Akina, how are you feeling?
I'm so excited, I'm looking forward to it!
You go for it, okay?
I will. I'm going to make a dent
in her car this time.
Okay.
Akina Minami
(Mercedes-Benz SLK Kompressor)
vs Nagisa from Amako Inter (Nissan Fuga)
I think Akina's going to attack
right from the outset.
Yeah, I think so too.
-I'll beat you to a pulp!
-Me too!
Shut up!
They're already trash talking!
"I'll beat you to a pulp!"
"Me too!"
You can go ahead. Because it's dangerous.
You just want to rear-end me!
No, you can go in front.
What is wrong with her?
Three... Two... One...
Go!
The battle between the two women
starts now!
As expected, Akina's giving Nagisa
the front position.
Nagisa is the one that starts first.
Can she keep this front position
to the end?
She's attacked from the rear!
Just as expected!
Akina totally rear-ended her!
She's laughing!
Wow, that's so dangerous!
Now, through this smoke-like dust,
the small red Mercedes tries to catch up.
The back of the Fuga
is still under attack!
What is wrong with her!
Amazing!
Stop hitting me from behind! Seriously!
She's pushing her.
You can hardly see anything
on this dusty road
but the white Fuga...
And there's an explosion!
That's right, we don't know when
the explosions are going to come.
Akina's right behind her!
It's tail to nose!
They're actually touching!
Akina's pushing her!
They've gotten through
the slippery area unscathed.
Now they drive along
this bumpy path with logs.
Akina pushes Nagisa out of the way
and takes the lead!
Now, it's a straight line to the finish!
-She's reversing, she's reversing!
-No, no, no!
Wait, she stopped.
Akina has stopped her car.
She's reversing!
Nagisa crashes into her!
This is quite amazing.
Even though this is a timed race,
they're busy crashing into each other.
Akina's goggles have fallen off!
Is she okay?
That was a big impact.
It made a big crash noise!
Are you kidding?
Akina only seems to be interested in
damaging each other's cars.
Go, Nagisa!
I can't see.
Akina can't see anything
because of the smoke from the explosions.
Akina's coming up to the giant rock
swinging back and forth across the course.
How is she going?
She avoids the rock and accelerates!
She accelerates into the finish.
Akina wins!
Akina's time is 1 minute 55 seconds.
The winner is Junior's army.
Nagisa from Amako Inter
will follow her to the finish.
Wow, the front of the Fuga
is completely smashed!
WINNER
Akina Minami - 1m55s
Akina Minami - 1m55s - +10p
Nagisa from Amako Inter - 2m06s
She bumps into Akina at the finish!
Hey!
The battle is over!
Yeah!
Yes!
Well done!
Well...
That was so much fun!
Wow!
It's more damaged than I imagined!
That's how it ends up looking
when you crash like that.
She got reversed onto from the side.
Then crashed into Akina at the end.
Thank you very much!
Why, you!
Shit!
What the hell were you thinking?
Sorry, I didn't think it would be
this bad.
Are you kidding me?
I got overexcited.
I told you I wanted to go home!
That I didn't want the pay
for doing this show!
Let me go home!
I had a lot of fun. Thank you so much!
Akina fuels Nagisa's anger again.
Nagisa is furious.
Let's have a look at the replay.
SENTOSHA: Battle Wheels
Go!
Here's the start. As she declared earlier,
Akina lets Nagisa go ahead.
It seemed fine at first,
but Akina took aim here.
Akina keeps nudging from behind.
Nagisa becomes very flustered
at this stage.
With a wide grin on her face,
Akina pushes Nagisa from behind.
That's why they call Akina
the dangerous speed queen.
Behind the wheel, Akina's personality
completely changes.
She's nudging Nagisa here as well.
You can hear her laughing.
They somehow manage to maintain
control through this area.
And here it seemed
Akina made a great maneuver
and would head straight
to the finish line.
But she stopped.
She stopped and reversed!
Akina intentionally reverses into Nagisa.
This is where the damage
to the right front bumper happened.
It's a win for Akina.
Now, how is Nagisa's car?
Is the Fuga okay?
You were great.
Looks like you had fun.
-You looked confident out there.
-Thank you.
It was so much fun!
I had a lot of fun!
What were you thinking when you
reversed and crashed into her?
Well, since I had leeway, I thought
that one little bump wasn't enough!
I see.
Shall we let Nagisa go home now?
I guess so.
How did it go?
I didn't sign up for this.
Let me go home!
Are you sure?
Don't you think you should stay
until you get her back for this?
My car will stop working if I keep going.
Your car's beeping.
It sustained a lot of damage.
Second Battle
Let's go, Fujimoto!
-It's your turn, Seiji!
-This is a good match.
I'll batter your car to pieces!
Just like your face!
Volvo V70
New car price approx. 7.4 million yen
The Junior army's man of just words,
no action, Toshifumi Fujimoto.
His battle car is a Volvo V70.
Engine 2.5L I5 DOHC IC Turbo / 209 hp /
4WD / AT / Weight 1620kg
Toyota Celsior
New car price 8 million yen
The Chihara family's mad dog,
Seiji Chihara.
His battle car is a Toyota Celsior.
Engine 4.3L V8 DOHC / 280 hp / FR / AT /
Weight 1800kg
In the first round,
Seiji managed to stop the car
just 80 centimeters
from the wall,
to give Hamada's army a great start.
HAMADA ARMY'S MAD DOG
SEIJI CHIHARA
Fujimoto, on the other hand, is known
to be a scaredy-cat comedian.
The Junior's Army's Man of just words,
no action, Toshifumi Fujimoto
Can he bring a good result
for Junior's army in this second round?
Smash him, okay?
Leave it to me.
I have a perfect image
of what I'll do to him.
Fujimoto's a scaredy-cat.
Go beat him up, okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to beat up
your own brother.
No problem.
-Are you okay with that?
-Yup. No problem.
Good. Now I have permission
from the little brother.
Yeah.
Toshifumi Fujimoto (Volvo V70)
vs Seiji Chihara (Toyota Celsior)
Now, we're onto the second match up.
In the white Volvo
is just words, no action, Fujimoto.
And in the black Toyota Celsior
is the Chihara family's mad dog,
Seiji Chihara.
He betrayed his brother
to join Hamada's army.
Three... Two...
Let's go, Fujimoto!
Let's go, Seiji!
One...
Go!
Here's the start.
They bump each other from the start!
Seiji is already pushing! Can they get
through the gate? They managed somehow.
They go on the attack!
Seiji blows up a dust storm
and Fujimoto has no vision whatsoever!
He blocked Fujimoto's vision
with the dust!
Fujimoto can't see...
And he's attacked from behind!
Seiji has gone full attack mode
on Fujimoto.
Run, run!
That's why he's called the mad dog
of the family.
Seiji hits him at the top
of the hairpin curve.
He intentionally follows Fujimoto
and attacks him from behind!
Seiji seems out of control.
The Volvo V70 is Volvo's
first four-wheel drive model.
These rugged tracks
are causing no problems for this car.
What's happened to Seiji? He's stuck!
The wheels are spinning like crazy.
-You're doing well!
-You're in front!
Run!
In the meantime, Fujimoto opens up
a gap at the front.
Fujimoto has the lead,
but he's driving steadily.
Fujimoto's known for being
a bit of a chicken,
and he's not taking any chances here.
And here comes Seiji!
Wow, Seiji's catching up to him!
Fujimoto's driving steadily
here and there goes Seiji!
Seiji has caught up!
He's attacking relentlessly from behind!
The battle cars are ferociously jostling
for position.
Oh, the car has spun around!
The battle cars are ferociously jostling
for position.
Oh, the car has spun around!
The battle cars are ferociously jostling
for position.
Oh, the car has spun around!
Now Seiji is blocking his way.
Go, Fujimoto!
Let's go!
Now, Seiji is out to ruin Fujimoto's car.
You can hear the horn.
There's another impact!
Mad dog Seiji is going on
an all-out attack!
Fujimoto is through!
He managed to get away.
But he can't raise his speed.
There's another explosion!
And another one! Fujimoto is terrified!
This is an area where it's hard
to speed up. It's getting tight!
Seiji passes on the inside!
Now Seiji is in front!
Get him!
Fujimoto is coming up from behind.
There's a massive rock in their way.
They have managed to avoid...
No, it hit Fujimoto!
And here, Seiji completes the race.
Seiji from Hamada's army
has claimed victory!
WINNER
Seiji Chihara - 2m02s
The winner is Hamada's army.
Well done!
Fujimoto, while late, has also crossed
the finish line.
What are you doing?
The winner is Seiji!
You've lost two in a row to Seiji now.
Seiji Chihara - 2m02s - +3p
Toshifumi Fujimoto - 2m05s
Yeah.
Two in a row!
Shit!
SENTOSHA
Go!
Now Seiji has won two races
in a row against Fujimoto.
Right from the outset,
he shows us his mad dog qualities.
He was already attacking
even before the start.
Due to this dust storm created by Seiji,
Fujimoto is too scared
to put the pedal down.
And here, Seiji catches up
from behind and...
It looks like he's bullying Fujimoto.
A battle car is bullying
another battle car.
And here, Seiji nudges Fujimoto
from behind and spins him around.
Yeah!
You were great out there.
What happened to you?
What were you doing?
You were ahead in the beginning.
You're nearly in tears. What's up?
I apologize!
Third Battle
I'll go next.
-I have a plan.
-Okay.
If he tries to bump into me,
I'll run away from him.
-Right.
-Do your best!
-Good luck!
-Okay.
I'm off!
I'll go and shut him up.
-Yeah!
-Beat him up.
He chirps a lot
and it's getting annoying.
Wish me luck!
Good luck!
Jaguar XJ Executive
New car price approx. 8.1 million yen
The Rock 'n' Rolling speedster,
Mitsuru Matsuoka.
His battle car is a Jaguar XJ Executive.
Engine 4.0L V8 DOHC / 243 hp / FR / AT /
Weight 1730kg
He will drive Takahashi Racing's Toyota
Verossa, used for stunt car practice.
The man who wears shorts all year round,
Kunikazu Katsumata.
Since Hamada's army lost the first round,
his Fairlady Z was taken by Junior's army
at the end of the round.
He will compete in this round
using an alternative vehicle.
Go!
In the first round,
Katsumata won this by adopting
a superior strategy,
where he agitated Matsuoka
into making a mistake.
Maybe he's going too fast?
They're up to the braking line.
They're stopping...
Matsuoka's doing well...
No, he's falling through
to the other side. Look out!
No, he fell down the cliff!
Just as planned!
You're driving an alternative vehicle,
right?
Yeah, that's right.
I don't think I can accelerate too much
with this.
Is that okay? If you want to forfeit
the race, it's fine.
HAMADA'S ARMY 3P
JUNIOR'S ARMY 10P
In the last round, I got too angry
THE MAN WHO WEARS SHORTS ALL-YEAR-ROUND
KUNIKAZU KATSUMATA
and got drawn into Katsumata's strategy.
THE ROCK'N'ROLL SPEEDSTER
MITSURU MATSUOKA
This time, I'll use that anger
to my advantage.
All of Japan should be on board
with this kind of show.
A daily show with battle cars?
Yeah, we should have it daily.
Yeah, a daily show.
-You lost your match in the last round.
-I know.
You need to do better this time.
I'll pummel him this time.
He's also driving a replacement car, so...
I think he'll be lacking in power anyway.
Okay.
I think I'll get that car
ready for the junkyard.
All right!
I'm a car enthusiast rocker.
I won't let him disrespect me again.
I'll go full throttle from the beginning
and I won't let him catch me.
All right. Understood.
Mitsuru Matsuoka (Jaguar XJ Executive)
vs Kunikazu Katsumata (replacement car)
With his Fairlady Z in the hands
of Junior's army,
Katsumata has been forced to drive
a replacement car he hasn't driven before.
On the other hand,
Matsuoka is driving a Jaguar favored
by the British royal family.
The difference is clear to see.
Go!
Here's the start.
Katsumata has taken the lead
from the outset.
Katsumata is in front.
He got an amazing start!
He sprints through the explosion.
The race on the "Road to Hell" course
has started.
This uphill section leads
up to the hairpin curve.
Matsuoka hits him from behind!
Matsuoka's Jaguar is on the attack!
Katsumata has lost control here.
So too has Matsuoka!
Both cars have lost their balance
and are now stuck.
No!
No, no, no!
Get out of there.
He spun out. They've both spun.
Can they get back on track?
Matsuoka is...
Is he going off course?
Looks like Katsumata is going get back
on track first.
Matsuoka does a big U-turn
before he gets back on track.
And here
Katsumata takes the lead again.
He's driving a replacement car,
but showing very good control.
Now he's driving along the bank
at a steep angle.
He's at the slippery area.
Matsuoka's Jaguar is still nowhere
to be seen.
Look at that. The front of the Jaguar
is falling apart!
The front of Matsuoka's car is damaged.
No, he's getting away!
Why has he stopped?
What is that?
He stopped. Katsumata has stopped.
He reverses and hits Matsuoka!
But Matsuoka has used this
to his advantage and has taken the lead!
Matsuoka is in front.
Will Katsumata regret
stopping to hit Matsuoka earlier?
This is Matsuoka's big chance!
Matsuoka is in front,
but he's being pushed from behind.
He's pushing and pushing!
Someone has lost control there.
Coming out from the cloud of smoke is...
It's Katsumata!
Katsumata's car is in the lead.
He's controlling
the replacement car very well.
And we're up to the giant rock.
Can he avoid the rock?
He gets hit, but it doesn't affect him.
He gets the other rock out of his way.
The winner is Katsumata
from Hamada's army!
It was a great performance
in a replacement car.
Hamada's army wins.
WINNER
Kunikazu Katsumata - 1m31s
He was great!
Well done!
Matsuoka crosses the finish line now.
How is the Jaguar?
It has sustained a lot of damage.
Kunikazu Katsumata - 1m31s - +10p
Mitsuru Matsuoka - 1m41s
-The dust blocking your view...
-Right.
...is causing more problems
than we thought.
You can't see anything.
Yes!
-I can't open the door.
-The door won't open?
Did your window shatter?
Here are some parts from the Jaguar.
Wait a second.
The Jaguar looks nothing like
before the race.
It definitely won't take any
further part in this competition.
Let's have a look at the replay.
SENTOSHA
Here's the replay.
Katsumata went in front.
Then, from here,
Matsuoka started attacking
with the front of his Jaguar.
They both lose control right here.
We saw many instances like this.
This is what battle cars do.
Matsuoka in his Jaguar was well behind.
The Jaguar was already
falling apart at this stage.
Matsuoka somehow regains control
of the unstable Jaguar.
After this point, Katsumata is waiting
for Matsuoka
just so he can ram him.
This is where Katsumata hit Matsuoka.
But through this, Matsuoka was able to
take the lead in the Jaguar.
The Rock 'n' Rolling speedster
is in front,
however, the man who wears
shorts all year round is closing in.
Matsuoka loses control here again.
Katsumata is very aware of
what's happening around him.
Up against the world-famous Jaguar,
Katsumata was able to show some
wonderful skills in this race.
Hey!
Matsuoka!
Mr. Matsuoka from Sophia!
Sorry.
Mr. Matsuoka from the band SOPHIA!
I apologize!
What?
You like cars, don't you?
You can't lose to a man like Katsumata.
Didn't you go off course for a moment?
Yes!
It was a battle.
It was a big battle!
It went well.
-Well done!
-You were amazing.
I wanted to get as big a gap as possible,
but I couldn't help but smash him once.
That's right!
His car door won't open anymore.
I never felt like losing.
I never thought you would be
such an aggressive person!
Hamada's army - 13 points
Junior's army - 10 points
After three matches, Hamada's army is
leading by three points.
But they cannot rest easy
with their three-point lead,
as the "Road to Hell" is very challenging.
Fourth Battle
Nissan Skyline
New car price 3.1 million yen
The best driver in a thousand years
according to himself,
Juichi Wakisaka.
His battle car is a Nissan Skyline.
Modified to suit hooligans
from Chiba and Ibaraki,
it features a muffler
made out of bamboo spears.
Engine 2.5L I6 DOHC / 200 hp / FR / AT /
Weight 1400kg
BMW 330i
New car price approx. 5.7 million yen
The current top racing driver,
Shigekazu Wakisaka.
His battle car is the BMW 330i
from Germany.
Engine 3L I6 DOHC / 231 hp / FR / AT /
Weight 1520kg
In the first round,
the younger brother Shigekazu
claimed a clear-cut victory.
THE FIRST ROUND
STOP RIGHT AT THE EDGE
He was able to work off his long-standing
grudge as a race car driver.
How did they do?
Shigekazu has done really well!
Shigekazu has won by a clear margin.
What happened to Juichi?
Shigekazu's result is one meter.
In contrast, Juichi has only recorded
8 meters, 90 centimeters!
So scary.
On to the fourth battle.
Hamada's army currently leads
by three points.
Family warfare between two brothers,
race car drivers Juichi and Shigekazu
will battle each other once again.
Juichi is known as Mr. GT in Japan
with his unmatched record.
Now he also manages a Super GT team.
Although Shigekazu is less well-known
compared to his brother,
he's still one of Japan's top racers.
Thank you very much.
Hey, Mr. Wakisaka.
-Let's beat the other Wakisaka, okay?
-Yes.
I've been suffering in his shadow
for a long time,
since I started racing at 17.
Today, I'll get my revenge.
You're going to make him suffer?
-Let's go, Wakisaka!
-Yes.
Juichi Wakisaka (BMW 330i)
vs Shigekazu Wakisaka (Nissan Skyline)
Shigekazu has been trying to outdo
his older brother for a very long time.
He has often only been
referred to as Juichi's little brother.
Can he claim two victories in a row?
Three... Two... One...
Go!
Here they go!
They are side by side
passing the gate at the start.
The older brother takes the lead here.
Juichi currently in front.
They look calm and collected
at this stage.
In this cloud of dust,
the younger Wakisaka
is right behind his brother.
They have yet to crash
or bump into each other yet.
They're using their driving
techniques to outdo each other.
Here comes Shigekazu on the inside.
They are side by side.
They are side by side!
-It's like a proper race.
-Awesome.
They drive across the bank still
side by side.
Is Shigekazu in front?
No, still Juichi in front.
Now, Shigekazu takes the lead.
Shigekazu is half a car length in front.
-What's that?
-What's going on?
Is Juichi coming back at him?
Who are they? They're ninjas!
The Ninjas line up and throw paint balls
at them!
They are getting covered in paint balls!
The paint is blocking their view.
They can't see what's in front of them!
What the... I can't see!
They lose their vision
and here's an explosion!
Who will emerge from beyond all the smoke?
It's the BMW!
Shigekazu, the little brother,
is still in front!
Where is his brother? Where is Juichi?
There he is! They are side by side!
They are, again, driving side by side.
Juichi takes the lead in the left corner.
He made a pass!
-Such a good battle. Let's go!
-Come on!
Juichi is in front.
The giant rock swings by.
Is it Juichi or Shigekazu?
They are side by side.
They finish together!
Who crossed the line first?
It's too close to call!
Did I win?
Who won?
The winner is Hamada's army!
Juichi wins! The gap is just 0.1 seconds!
WINNER
Juichi Wakisaka - 1m05s
Yeah!
Juichi Wakisaka - 1m05s - +1p
Shigekazu Wakisaka - 1m05s
-Yes!
-Amazing!
-It's a matter of millimeters!
-He won by a nose!
-Who won?
-Did we lose?
We lost?
So close.
SENTOSHA
Let's go through the replay.
This was a wonderful match up.
This was a great race between
two professional race car drivers.
They drive side by side without touching.
They showed us what
top-class racing is all about.
Here they are side by side again.
Shigekazu is in the lead.
Juichi is right behind.
They encounter an unexpected
attack by the ninja paint brigade.
This paint ball attack
takes them by surprise.
Although their views get blocked
by the paint on their windscreens,
they were still able to give us
a close race
with less than one second between them.
First one to come out of
the smoke was Shigekazu,
but Juichi is also just on the other side.
Juichi takes the lead from his brother
and wins the race.
SENTOSHA
I won, didn't I?
I won?
You won one point.
You gained one point.
I won, right?
All right!
Yay!
Thank you very much.
You won like a pro.
I'm sorry.
It was a great race.
There are a lot of guys who you don't know
whether they're working with you
or against you.
Are they friends or foes?
They're a bit of both, really.
They got me right in the face
with a paintball.
They really did.
Fifth Battle
Mercedes-Benz S320
New car price approx. 10 million yen
Riding the Reaper's Express,
Toshiyuki Itakura.
His battle car is a Mercedes-Benz S320
from Germany.
Engine 3.2L V6 SOHC / 224 hp / FR / AT /
Weight 1800kg
Nissan Laurel 2000SGX
New car price 1.03 million yen
The man who nearly united Kyushu,
Masaki Sata.
His battle car is his beloved
Nissan Laurel 2000SGX.
Engine 2L I6
SOHC / 130 hp / FR / 5MT / Weight 1200kg
It's a legendary car highly sought after
by vintage car enthusiasts.
I know it's extremely uncool to do this...
But please excuse me from this race.
I'm sorry!
-What?
-Mr. Hamada!
This isn't like you.
My car is different to the others.
Other cars can be brought back
to their previous condition
if you have the money.
My car can't be repaired!
Go buy a brand new car!
Brand new ones have lots
of parts available.
I want this car!
I only want this car.
This car is extremely rare.
There's only a few left in Japan.
I drive cars for a living.
From my point of view,
if we lose this car to the scrap heap,
that means it will be a step towards
that car not existing anymore.
Produced between 1972 and 1977,
only 30 of these cars still exist
That's one thing you should think about.
You're speaking from a car professional's
point of view.
Please, Mr. Hamada,
it's a Japanese treasure!
That car is a priceless aspect
of Japan's car culture.
You think it's worth saving?
I think so.
If we damage that car,
you'll receive so many complaints
from vintage car enthusiasts!
Please, Mr. Hamada.
Of course, we were expecting this.
So we have another plan.
Is that right?
Please have a look at this video.
Hi, this is Koji Kato,
a ninja from Hamada's army.
A NINJA FROM THE HAMADA ARMY
KOJI KATO
I understand that you're short
on battle cars.
I was thinking what we could do.
On this occasion,
I hear that you were letting
my comedy partner,
Yamamoto, appear on the show.
It took Yamamoto ten years
to get back on screen.
We caused a lot of trouble for our agency,
Yoshimoto Creative Agency.
Of course, we caused a lot of trouble
for Mr. Hamada, too.
Since it's for Mr. Hamada,
we must lend a hand.
What?
We can provide you
with a Volkswagen Beetle.
-What?
-Yes.
Do what you like with it.
Wait a minute.
I don't care what happens to it.
It's Mr. Yamamoto's car, after all.
I hear that Yamamoto has less than
1 million yen in his savings account.
He had a lot of difficulty
while he was on extended leave.
But now, he's been cast on Amazon's
program, on Mr. Hamada's show, so...
Well done, Yamamoto!
I'm very happy for you!
I'm so happy for you!
But remember,
it's too early for regular TV.
-Seriously?
-Is he for real?
Now he has to provide his own car?
It's here!
Wow!
That's really mine.
That's it.
Mr. Yamamoto, thank you very much.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
It's coming.
Seriously, this is... I haven't...
KEIICHI YAMAMOTO'S BELOVED CAR
THE WOLKSWAGEN BEETLE
-When did you buy it?
-In November.
-How much was it?
-I bought it last November...
Its net price was
a little over 2.8 million yen,
but all in all cost over 3 million yen.
I've only paid the monthly
installments of 70,000 yen
for November, December, January, February,
March, April, May...
I've only paid seven months,
so I still owe 2.5 or 2.6 million yen.
-Wow.
-That must be hard for you.
-Thank you very much!
-Well.
You said if it was ten years ago,
you would've brought your own car
in a flash.
You said we weren't tough enough!
The times are different now!
A lot of things change in ten years!
You're not wrong.
I need to work hard
so I can appear on regular TV again!
Please, Sata.
I'm sorry. Thank you for your sacrifice!
I'm sorry for making fun of you earlier.
I'll apologize, so please!
No, no, no.
Mr. Hamada, please.
I'll do anything but this.
I'll bow down to you with Sata,
so please don't do this.
Sata, just go!
Did you know this was going to happen?
-Just go and take the car.
-You knew!
I'll do my best for Hamada's army!
You knew this was going to happen!
Sata, you must have known, too!
Did you know about this, Mr. Hamada?
Of course not!
I've got my electronic toll card
in the car!
Can you give the card back to me?
Burn the car down, card and all!
Can you take the card out?
You sound so desperate.
Volkswagen Beetle
New car price approx. 3 million yen
Yamamoto purchased this brand-new
Volkswagen Beetle last fall.
Although its weight is rather light
at 1300 kg,
it is equipped with an IC turbo engine.
It is very much
like a wolf in sheep's clothing.
Engine 1.2L I4 SOHC IC
Turbo / 105 hp / FF / AT / Weight 1300kg
I'm raring to go.
Then let's go, Itakura!
-Crush him!
-Yeah, crush them!
Mr. Yamamoto, don't worry.
He won't catch me.
Without a scratch!
He just has to lead all the way.
You don't look like a man
who is going to lead all the way!
I'll lead all the way.
I won't let him touch me.
He's the last one I want driving my car!
The one driving my car
is the craziest of them all!
Mr. Yamamoto, let's enjoy this more!
I finally understand how you feel, Nagisa.
After telling us off so much,
you're afraid to lose your own car?
Don't make that sad face!
Enjoy the game.
Mr. Yamamoto's been really good to me,
but this is a competition.
RIDING THE REAPER'S EXPRESS
TOSHIYUKI ITAKURA
I can't control what happens
on the battlefield.
I wonder what Itakura's killer instinct
is like.
What will become of Yamamoto's Beetle,
forced to take the place
of the precious Laurel?
Now, Sata gets strapped into the Beetle.
It still has that new car smell.
Are you close to Yamamoto?
Yes, Mr. Yamamoto's been
really good to me.
Is that right? That means nothing. Okay?
Mr. Sata?
-Mr. Sata?
-Yes.
I'd appreciate it
if you could treat my car well
I think that would be good
for both of us.
It's a very easy car to drive.
I understand.
Please don't stomp too hard.
Of course. I'm aware of that.
No problem, I will treat it very well.
The TV business has changed a lot
in ten years.
You're not supposed to do anything
too dangerous nowadays.
Is that right? I didn't know that.
That's true, right?
But this is for Amazon, not regular TV.
You don't have to show that kind of action
to Amazon members.
Amazon members only want to see nice,
tame programs.
Please, Sata.
He can't hear me anymore!
I'm glad he couldn't hear you this time.
He couldn't hear me...
Toshiyuki Itakura (Mercedes-Benz S320)
vs Masaki Sata (Volkswagen Beetle)
The Volkswagen Beetle
only weighs 1300 kg,
compared to Itakura's Mercedes
at 1800 kg.
If Itakura allows the lighter Beetle
to get away,
he may not be able to catch him again.
Three...
Two... One...
Don't let him get away!
Go!
The race starts now.
It's a very smooth start
by Yamamoto's Beetle.
Driving the Beetle is Sata
from Hamada's army.
It seems neither has been bothered
by the explosion.
Itakura seems to be a bit off pace.
He's getting away!
Just lead from start to finish!
The race has just begun.
No one knows what awaits them.
Run, run!
We can hardly see anything.
Sata is driving slowly, so is Itakura.
Looks like Itakura is catching up to him.
Slowly, slowly.
Keep going!
We still can't see the Mercedes.
There it is!
We go from this angled bank area
to the slippery zone.
No, he can't stop. He can't stop!
Is he okay? The car is on its roof!
We go from this angled bank area
on to the slippery zone.
No, he can't stop. He can't stop!
Is he okay? The car is on its roof!
We go from this angled bank area
on to the slippery zone.
No, he can't stop. He can't stop!
Is he okay? The car is on its roof!
Is Sata okay?
Itakura also comes up from behind.
He brakes.
That's so dangerous!
Is he okay?
There's some kind of gas spraying
from the car.
Wow, a massive accident has happened
on this "Road to Hell."
The Beetle has completely overturned.
Are you okay?
Is Sata okay?
Watch out!
Is he stupid?
It overturned!
But...
It's overturned.
It overturned.
What did he do?
That's terrible.
What the hell is he doing?
Sata!
What? It's making some whooshing noise!
Hey!
It's totally crushed!
Get out of the way!
We'll turn over the car.
They're turning over the car.
That's so scary.
The oil is leaking.
Won't it explode?
Stand back!
There's oil leaking from the car.
It's dangerous!
It's dangerous.
We should stand back.
Sata's still in the car.
SENTOSHA
Let's have a look.
It happened just after here.
The slippery area is coming up next.
He couldn't stop and went straight ahead
into the dirt wall.
After impact, the car overturns
completely onto its roof.
Wow, I wonder if Sata is okay.
Is Sata...
We're worried about how Sata is doing.
Now, this is the on-board camera.
This is the video of the moment of impact.
We are worried about both
the Beetle and Sata.
SENTOSHA
Can you hear from Sata?
Sata!
Get out, get out!
-Get out!
-There's an oil leak.
Be careful!
You better get out!
Get out, get out quickly!
Get out, get out.
Come on.
Just keep going!
Run!
I need my ETC tollway card...
It doesn't matter!
Yamamoto!
It's on this side!
It's dangerous, you need to get away!
ETC.
It's dangerous, though...
Just get it afterwards.
Forget about the ETC card!
It's dangerous!
I'll ask them to reissue it.
Get away, get away.
SENTOSHA
Here's the view of Sata's face.
We can have a look what happened
at the time of impact.
This is it!
The air bag pops out. That's so dangerous!
He's okay. He's alive.
He has somehow survived.
He has somehow survived hell.
SENTOSHA
Sata has now retired.
The Beetle is most likely
out of action as well.
Itakura from Junior's army
cruises to victory.
WINNER - Toshiyuki Itakura (Junior's army)
Earns 10p from Sata's retirement
-What were you doing?
-What happened?
The steering wheel wouldn't turn.
-What?
-I couldn't turn.
That's not possible!
That's never happened before...
I couldn't change direction.
You were worried about your ETC card
more than me!
I wanted to get it out of the car.
Did you get the ETC card out of the car?
No.
The car could have exploded.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm not injured.
This is Sentosha!
Sata has left the battlefield
for a medical assessment.
Hamada's army - 14 points
Junior's army - 20 points
Three more battles to go
in this second round.
Junior's army has now taken the lead.
Ozawa's got a grenade in his hand again.
He takes the lead right from the outset.
That's dangerous!
Wow, Ozawa!
He's taking aim!
Wow, he's riding up the side of that car!
SENTOSHA