Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
It's Viking's Kotouge!
Isn't it everyone's favorite Kotou-chan?
You are very kind
The whole of Japan's favorite Kotou-chan
-No no no
Old women still don't like me very much
What about Ani-chan?
You are the only one who would mention this person
Ani-chan?
My eardrums haven't heard that name in a long time
Very nostalgic
Since she got married
-After all, she's married
This time I've brought this theory:
The 5th Comedians' Funniest Moments
It's funny.
-It's great
The last time I presented something for this theory
Mouchu Gakusei performing on stage
Originally it was a segment that was supposed to be in front of an audience
But he ended up doing it in an empty room
The only sound in the room was his sneakers scraping on the floor
Squeaky
This kind of mental quality is also very rare in the world of comedians
So it was very interesting.
-Yes
But since that episode aired, it has become a hit again.
Thanks to your introduction
He has been able to increase his popularity again
Perhaps many staff members involved watched that episode
So maybe comedians can take advantage of this opportunity to become more popular
It's hard to say.
-We don't know yet
Straight away you're being difficult
It's not impossible
-Indeed
So maybe a comedian will have such an opportunity
It's hard to say, isn't it?
You don't know, so don't be so pessimistic!
The 5th Comedians' Funniest Moments
First is Shimofuri Myojo's Soshina
"Iroha ni Chidori" on Saitama TV last year
This is a program hosted by Chidori
Guests include 5GAP
At that time, there was a project called QUIZ 5GAP
Chidori watch half of 5GAP skit
Then Daigo and Nobu guess the rest of it
"What jokes will be made"
They guess and then the answer is revealed
QUIZ 5GAP Questions
Including this photo itself is already very funny
Next up is the Heavyweight Wrestling Championship
First, the challenger from the red side
The enigmatic masked wrestler Red Dragon
5GAP, what will be the next joke?
This is how it goes
The introduction says Red Dragon
But the guy who comes out is wearing blue clothes
It is indeed very much like the style of 5GAP
Said it was Red Dragon, but he's actually blue
In 5GAP's style it should be very funny
If he comes out in blue
If so then red should be emphasized more at the start
Say Super Red or something
Since he's talking about Red Dragon
So I think it wont go this way
In that case, the important point is the "enigmatic masked wrestler"
Both of them are very serious
This point
Although it is called "masked wrestler"
His face is actually showing
Not even masked
Both predictions are very serious
They have a mask, but the face is completely exposed
Thinking very hard
When seeing the correct answer I couldn't help but laugh
The correct answer to this QUIZ 5GAP is as follows
Next up is the Heavyweight Wrestling Championship
First, the challenger from the red side
The enigmatic masked wrestler Red Dragon
I think it's the face
Both right!
No creative secrets to speak of
We were both right
This is awesome!
Blue and not masked
Correct
Seen through their work too easily
I didn't expect both of them to be right
And this kind of thing
I laughed so hard, I laughed so hard
It's a miracle
It's also funny when he comes out with "Hey~"
By the way, when Nobu was recording this episode
He laughed too much, resulting in a lack of oxygen to the brain
After the recording he was taken to hospital
This is a legendary moment in the world of comedy
He collapsed because he was laughing too much
Next is Onigoe Tomahawk's Sakai
A program called "THE OUTSIDER" hosted by Maeda Nikkei
Gathering bad guys from all over Japan to fight
An amateur mixed martial arts competition
Is this comedy?
-Surely no comedy factor at all
Everyone was very serious, obviously not a laughing matter
But something funny happened surprisingly
The level of "THE OUTSIDER" is now very high
THE OUTSIDER" of more than 10 years ago
It was just street punks who thought they could fight well
It was a very rough
In such a rough competition
There was a contestant named Kuroishi Takahiro
He came from a gang in Yokohama
Seemed like a pretty bad guy
The kind of punk that'd appear in a manga
He had the vibe of "today we must fight to the death"
There was a murderous aura in his eyes
He had a match
The "dang" gong sounded and the match began
As soon as the gong sounded, Kuroishi rushed towards the other guy with all his strength
I'd like you to see that scene
Will this be funny?
Kuroishi from Yokohama's moment is this
Kuroishi
A murderous look
He has the momentum to rush forward with full force
Round 1 Fight
He's going to rush over
1 hit? Eh?
Out completely
A one-hit KO
As a result, members of their gang flew into the ring
You have to say it's funny, right? These people...
No one cares about Kuroishi
Why did they all run in?
-No one did anything wrong
They're all fighting each other now
Kuroishi is completely confused
No one cares about him
"What's going on?" This feeling
Doesn't get what's going on
No memory at all
Wasn't able to do anything
There's always next time
Kuroishi is crying.
-Must be very upset
I really did not do anything and lost in two seconds
Sakai, stop it.
-What a bad guy
This is Kuroishi
KO in the opening two seconds, this is something you can't do even if you want to
That's enough
And then his fellow gang members all rush in
Then he regains consciousness and gets up again
With this "Hey? What's going on?" look, its very interesting
I think this is a famous scene that will go down in history
This is Onigoe Tomahawk Sakai's funniest moment
Kuroishi of THE OUTSIDER
Next is Tokyo 03 Iizuka
I saw it on TV last year
Just after the M-1 Grand Prix
Nishkikoi, the champions attended "Wide na Show"
Hasegawa said he liked a certain joke of Matsumoto's
He began tearfully talking about his state of mind
I watched that too.
-Me too
A feeling of mixed feelings
When watching it I was also moved
But when Hasegawa was about to finish
Like a sudden awakening
The tears were stopped at once
Rather than stopping
It's more like entering a state of no-self
The feelings suddenly disappear
As something else is said, the topic is finished
Just this little bit
But his enigmatic slowdown is particularly interesting
I'm not sure what's interesting about this
Its difficult to describe
Please take a look
Sorry, he's crying
Matsumoto said...
Very touching
The phrase "the soul never grows old"
I too...
Like
No, that's too weird.
What's going on?
Why suddenly stopped crying
What really happened?
It's been a long time since I've seen it, but it's still fun to watch now
It's a mystery
Obviously so full of feelings, feelings are almost pouring out
So moved to cry
Suddenly becomes expressionless
It can't be performed
It's not something that can be acted out
This phrase I am too ...
Like
Scary
Suddenly, he stopped crying and said "like"
Another personality suddenly appears
Next is Magical Lovely's Noda Crystal
A fighting game tournament EVO2015
It's like the olympics for fighting games
This is for the game Guilty Gear Strive
There was a match between Woshige and Ogawa
It's a strong matchup
They are very passionate about the game
It's like a dream matchup
This was considered to be the pinnacle
But the ending of this game makes you think "Hey, really?"
This kind of world competition is of great interest to people all over the world
But everyone who saw this scene was dumbfounded
This is the moment
A very rare event
Ogawa uses the character with blonde hair and sunglasses
Woshige uses a female character with long blonde hair
By this time, Ogawa had already won one round
If Ogawa wins again in this round, he will win this match
Both sides do not give way to each other, the physical strength is also an even match
It seems he is going to be unable to hold out
But then Woshige makes a big move that is sure to kill
He got up and cheered, but the game wasn't over yet
There was still one more round after that
He suddenly remembers and rushes back to sit down
But it's too late
What is this?
Probably forgot
He's so happy
Overjoyed to have scored a point
Thought he had won
Probably just thought it was over
What is this?
Ogawa has no human feelings
What a vivid memory!
Ogawa showed no mercy
And regardless of that the opposite player hadn't started yet he just hammered away
A historic one-sided beat-down
This is too unreasonable, professional players should not make such cheap mistakes
They've been through so many competitions before
He ran 50 metres
Just posed like this
And was then reminded "you're not finished yet!"
The foreign live commentary says "oh my god"
So you can really say "oh my god" at this
OH MY GOD
This is Noda's funniest moment
A premature victory pose
Misunderstood
OH MY GOD
Next is Untouchable's Shibata
This must have been more than 30 years ago
ABC broadcast a show called
Wakabushigi Downtown
To say what sort of show it was...
Downtown hosted with Imada and Higashino
The Gottsu members
The show involved physical reactions
There was a time in this program when Honkon had mayonnaise squirted on his face
This is a simple scene
Balloons filled with mayonnaise
The balloon broke and then the mayonnaise in the balloon spilled onto the face
This scene was an earthquake level of amusement to me as a high school student at the time
Let's take a look
So young
Itao slipped on the mayonnaise in the background
The scene was chaos
Itao getting in the way
The spreading is also too perfect
That's him.
-Honkon at first glance
Even though the face is covered its so obvious its him
How'd it spread like that?
It's too perfect, right?
It was as if this project was made for him
Very impressive indeed
This is too perfect
There are all kinds of small accidents
And the actual result is an added bonus of hilarity
Next is Yahagi
I saw it on TV about five years ago
A program called "Tonight's Puzzle Training"
There was a question to guess who someone in a costume was
To guess
They'd use the speaker commonly used in quiz shows
Tell Ueda quietly, and he will then decide if the answer is correct
At this point, Sunshine Ikezaki seems to have guessed correctly
Usually you should speak very quietly through the speaker to say who it is
But he shouted "YEAH" especially loudly through the loudspeaker
While he was shouting "YEAH"
Ueda beat him up with lightning speed
Genuinely angry
Seeing people angry can be funny
The moment is this
Sunshine's answer is
YEAH
-What are you doing?
It's too dangerous
Idiot!
Really angry
Super quick to get angry
The first hit was a real hit
So fast!
Next time i'll punch you
His personal health is threatened
That's funny
Sunshine Ikezaki is also really good!
I don't think anyone but him would dare to make that much noise
Not in his right mind. Absolutely not
It's really dangerous
And Ueda is so quick to respond.
Took less than a second to hit it
If it was an ordinary "ah" it would not be so funny
YEAH
-What are you doing?
Idiot!
Both are great
No win or loss
This is Yahagi's funniest moment
Ikezaki, who was screaming in his ear, and Ueda, who was furious
Ikezaki is scary!
-Really scary
It was so close.
-Ueda felt the danger
Couldn't suppress his anger
-Indeed
Do you have a favorite moment?
Hasegawa of Nishkikoi
I can't believe his feelings changed so abruptly
You were there, weren't you? What happened then?
He wasn't really trying to be funny either
It was as if his battery had suddenly been pulled out
The line of emotion was broken with a click
-It was like that
It's funny how many times you watch it.
-What do you think, Kawashima?
If we're talking about moments, I think Shibata's
The combination of Mayonnaise and Honkon is great
-What can I say about this?
The shape is still obvious
Like the state of a carving before it is finished
What do you think, Michopa?
I think QUIZ 5GAP one is quite interesting
What kind of mindset do they have to answer this question?
Indeed, the answer is correct
They were so happy to hear the answer
There is no contrast between prediction and reality
There is no GAP
-0 GAP
Will this one become popular?
-It's possible
The guess was correct, that is to say, those two are stupid and too predictable
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's Koyabu
Shocked me
So sudden
I bring you a project that corrected the definition of a fan 6 years ago, please take a look
The 2nd Anyone Who Says "I'm Your Fan" Is Not a True Fan
Got it
We all encounter it often, right?
I met someone yesterday who told me, "I love Wednesday Downtown so much"
"I only watch Wednesday Downtown"
Aren't you going overboard?
Not a fan of me, but just Wednesday Downtown
I became a representative of the program
The 2nd Anyone Who Says "I'm Your Fan" Is Not a True Fan
So we prepared questions about comedians that all fans should know to ask passers-by
Shinjuku
So bad.
-Yes, its tough
The first participant is...
Yasuda Dai Circus' Kuro-chan
He has no fans
Behind him, a moderator is waiting with surprise questions
Working hard
So, soon
Here we go
I'm sorry
-Go ahead
Are you Kuro-chan?
Don't say it like Agnes-chan
Can we take a picture together?
-Yes.
A small group of young people come to ask for a photo
However
Are you fans?
Sort of... yeah
Wait, that's not right. The tone of voice is clearly not
It's not that we don't know you
Know but not very well
The truth
They reply fairly plain so they aren't really fans of him
It's all said and done.
-Yeah
Totally looking down on Kuro-chan
No fans!
However, at this time
Not anymore.
-Selfie again
The photo shoot is not finished
Are you Kuro-chan?
Don't say it like Agnes-chan
Save it. A frivolous sentence of nonsense
What's so funny?
I'm so happy to be able to meet you
I am your fan
-Really?
I especially like you on Wednesday Downtown
Here we go
Very fan-like
Thank you
So
Coming
-Here we go
As you claim to be a fan of Kuro-chan, please answer this question
-Ok
What is the iconic word that Kuro-chan often uses at the end of sentences
Da yo (heart)
You said you were a fan, right?
I am a fan of... well, how can I put it
What is it?
Not paying attention at all
Does Kuro-chan use it often?
Think back
- "desu" "Kuro-chan desu"
"Desu" is for everyone!
Wrong answer
Big problem
Are you really a fan?
Well...
Even if you are not a fan, you should know
Self-proclaimed fans can leave a good impression
You're just saying it straight out!
-Sorry, sorry, sorry
Not even a casual fan
No, no, cut this part out
Don't do this
It was just a coincidence
But afterwards the same
What is Kuro-chan's real name?
Akihito Kurokawa
Sorry, I don't know
Absolutely no idea.
-Why? Fans should know that
Only know his surname is Kurokawa
Yoshihito Kurokawa
What a face
Regretfully, that's incorrect
After that, the "I am a fan" photo scam continued
They just want a photo
2 hours have passed
Tough work
What is he pretending to do?
I am your fan
Really?
-Really. I like you a lot
Finally, a determined male fan
Kuro-chan's real name, what is his full name?
Akihito Kurokawa
Akihito?
-Yes
Congratulations! The answer is correct!
No need for the real name
Kuro-chan is the advisor of which five-member idol group
Mameshiba no Taigun
Congratulations! The answer is correct!
Finally someone that actually knows!
Then let's go for a more difficult one
What kind of fighting Kuro-chan is learning
Capoeira?
Congratulations. The answer is correct.
-There you go!
You must be a real fan!
Kuro-chan entered the entertainment industry originally not to be a funny artist, but what?
Idol
Congratulations, you answered correctly.
-Correct answer
Girlfriend looks so bored
My God, this is really
I'm so happy to finally meet a real fan
How did you get this information about me?
Probably through Twitter
Then you must be following me, right?
-Following?
Eh?
-I'm not following you
Why? Why not?
You stopped following me?
I used to
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Why did you stop?
I don't understand, I don't understand
Why did you stop following?
Its all pretty samey
Twitter content?
The things you post are all the same
The next participant is...
How'd he end up with this expression
Kikuchi Ami
Good choice
Ami is not even hidden
Hello
-How are you?
Just said hello to me
No photos?
Stop!
After being recognized she received a general greeting
Afraid to disturb her
Kikuchi Ami
-Hello
No one wants to stop for her
It's hard.
-Then don't talk to her!
They all peek at me, but no one stops
And then, an hour passed
This expression is bad
You're angry with Kikuchi, right?
At this time
What's going on?
-I'm shooting on location
Wait, are you a fan?
Fan?
Finally, original IDOLING member Rika Yokoyama appears
Are you a fan of Kikuchi?
Not a fan
We asked her a few questions anyway
Please listen
What is her nickname?
-Amimi
Congratulations. That's the right answer.
-We were in the same group!
Do not know is a big problem
No one stopped for the next 30 minutes
They're looking
Coming over?
May I ask if you are Kikuchi Ami? Can I take a picture with you?
-Of course
Thank you
You're cute
I am a fan
-Really?
Is it a fan?
So
If you call yourself a fan, please listen to the question
-Scared me a bit
What is Kikuchi Ami's nickname?
You should know that
Nickname
Amimi
There!
Congratulations. That's the right answer.
-Really?
What? What is this reaction?
Just saying?
-A guess.
Just now is the correct answer, right?
What is the meaning of "really?" after "correct"?
It's intuition
Say it like "a fan"
Very intuitive but not a true fan
Didn't she say she knew her?
And after this also
I don't know... Kikurin?
Don't know what the nickname is
For four hours, only 4 people claimed to be fans
No one knows "Amimi"
So tiring
So, the last person was
Diane's Tsuda
Can we take a picture together?
-Photo?
I'm a fan of yours.
-A fan? A fan? Really?
Come on, stand over here
So popular
For those of you who claim to be Diane Tsuda-san fans, please respond
What is Daian Tsuda's catchphrase
Goi goi su
That...
No, right?
I don't know
Unbelievably they fail to answer correctly
The two of them imitated Tsuda's pose and took a photo together for no apparent reason
So rough
Give it up
So hurt
At this time...
Hello.
-Are you Tsuda from Diane?
Yes
I like you very much.
-A fan? So happy
Thank you
Ready to go
This man has the most basic Tsuda knowledge base
So
Let's go
For those of you who claim to be fans of Diane's Tsuda, please listen to the question
What is Tsuda's real name?
Atsuhiro
Tsuda's... name
Takafumi Tsuda
Incorrect
Atsuhiro
Sorry, I'm a fan but I didn't know
What is the name of Tsuda's partner?
Yusuke
I know the face.
-Really?
No, right?
Suchi?
Incorrect
What is Tsuda's name?
Yasahiro
-Atsuhiro!
Not interested in remembering it at all
-Doesn't want to remember
Just wants to go home
Tsuda
-How are you?
I'm a fan
I've liked Shibuya for a long time
Ah, not my fan
Goi goi su
She's a fan of Shibuya
That's not it
Here we go
Are you working? I've been watching you on TV
Really? Thank you.
I'm a die-hard fan
A die-hard fan?
Here we go
Die-hard fan
So
What is Tsuda's name?
Masa Tsuda... Masamori
Masamori
Masa...mori
Aren't you die-hard fans?
As expected, there is not a single real fan
At this time
Another acquaintance?
Some juniors, who happened to be passing by after a theater performance, were asked to answer the questions as well
Small umbrella
Please listen
Naoki Tsuda
I know it
Atsuhi Tsuda
Not right at all
In summary
No one knows Tsuda's name
The end is not right, what is this conclusion
Such a sad conclusion
So sad, when they said his name wrong Tsuda tutted
What's his name?
Tsk
The worst is Amimi, right?
Not even a chance to play
Sugiyama looked like Stallone
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's ZAZY
-He's dressed up
Hello, I am ZAZY
-Nice legs
ZAZY be careful
-It's okay
So
Do you remember who the R-1 champion was this year?
Of course I remember.
-How can I put it? It's hard not to remember
It does ring a bell
It was Shinichi
We usually perform together
That's okay, right?
-I'm grateful for that
Every time Shinichi and I perform together
He will always carry the R-1 trophy
What does everyone think about this?
Don't think much of it
He likes to have his photo taken with it
Photo?
Says "hold the trophy like this"
Its a bit annoying
Tells you to hold trophy and asks "can we take a picture"
Please give it a hug" like your own child"
-Indeed
"Please see it one last time" like this
So, i've brought a theory about the trophy
Shinichi's R-1 trophy shtick doesn't amuse anyone
The trophy
He brings it every time
With it, the host will also mention the trophy, right?
The process is like this
But he's never ready to respond at all.
-Indeed
That's true
There's only ever this kind of dialogue: "why did you bring the trophy here" "why can't I?"
Instead, he's angry.
-It only makes people think what's going on?
So this time we have done a prank to destroy his trophy
Destroy it?
Does this qualify as a prank?
But it's not good to damage his real trophy anyway.
-It's not the real one
The one used is very similar to the real trophy
The real one still exists
Replica?
-It's a replica
We'll break the replica in front of him to see his reaction
Shinichi's R-1 trophy shtick doesn't amuse anyone
First, the replica is made
We received help from the Osaka art professionals in charge of making the real trophy
Rather than a replica, they just make another one
So it is
-Another real one
He was also in a scene where he cooked with the names of people he found on the street, which aired a few days ago
In between placing the trophy in the outside bus during his break
We took photos
On the basis of this photo
The old trophy scratches and dirt also were added to the new trophy
Later
Good morning
Bringing it with him
For this prank, we invited Shinichi to a fake interview
Doesn't even put it in a bag
Carries it every time
Let's move to another room first
We create a moment in which he is forced to leave the room
Hard to tell which one is which
The real thing is replaced
Shinichi is completely unaware
And takes the replica
The preparation work is done
The day before the trophy's destruction
What kind of caption is this?
Here is the prank
Understood, I'm really looking forward to it
About this operation
There's a bug in the trophy
That's right. In fact, when we made the replica
A bug was placed at the base of the replica
We have a fake program to verify whether "celebrities' homes are bugged"
For this, we visit Shinichi's home
Experts will find the wiretap
Bug Hunter
In order to take out the bug, the trophy must be destroyed
I'm so excited
I actually want to break it myself
Such an evil expression
So, the prank begins
Hello
-Nice to meet you
This is a special program to thoroughly investigate the homes of celebrities
We visited the homes of 50 celebrities
What lies are you telling?
Shinichi is the 16th.
-16th!?
Does Shinichi have any memories of being spyed on?
In front of the house
There was a person standing there, I wasn't sure if they were a fan or what
Feels like a stalker
Eh?
Thankfully, Shinichi is already weary of stalker-like fans
The closer the instrument is to the bug, the louder the sound
A check takes place for potential detection devices placed by fans
Thankfully there isn't one
Finally, the time arrives
I'm really looking forward to how he will react
Eh... scary!
-Wait
It's responding.
-What's the situation?
This TV is a bit suspicious
This expression is really quite worried
Nothing on this side
Eh? Scary
The instrument obviously reacts to the trophy
There is a response
Eh? Scary!
Is it really true?
After all, he's always with the trophy
Then
It's in the base
Do you want to try it?
-Wait a minute
It can't be
-Just now it made a sound
Ah this is so scary and disgusting
The sound coming from the headphones confirmed that there was indeed a bug in the trophy
Break it!
Finally it's time to break the trophy
What a badass
Take it out
A few weeks ago he was tricked into talking bad about Nagano
He said, "how long are you going to carry the trophy?"
It's so true
That part was genuine.
-Shinichi got super angry hearing that
Finally it's time to break the trophy
Take it out
Excuse me.
-What? What do you mean?
How do I get it out?
-Really messing with people
Can you disassemble it?
-Excuse me
No, wait, why?
So sudden?
Which line of business is this practitioner in?
Can you disassemble it?
-Excuse me
No, wait, why?
This will never work, right?
Looks like he's seen his son get beaten up
How can you demolish it like this?
This is it
There it is, the bug
What the hell is this? Was it spying on me for four months?
Indeed, this is a wiretap
More than the trophy being broken
His first thought is that he's been bugged for four months
Then
Ah, my trophy!
Despite the slow reaction, he's now angry at the trophy's destruction
Wait a minute, my trophy. What do I do now?
It's not okay to break the trophy, right?
I don't understand this dismantling method
Ah...
What do I do now?
This won't work!
It's a big fuss
This is something that changed my life
Seeing it at the point of no return is just too much
Shinichi, this can't be repaired
It's not possible
Already shattered
After all, it was smashed with a hammer
It's true.
-It's a hammer
No, no, this is messed up
This is a bit...
What do I do now?
Just as Zazy had hoped, Shinichi is in a very depressed mood
Go for it
The truth is revealed
Aren't you super angry?
What is it? What the hell is going on here?
This is a trophy-breaking prank
Eh? You guys have gone too far
This time, it went too far
It's really not good, seriously!
What's wrong with you?
Still thinks its the real thing
Do you know what this program is?
Wednesday Downtown？
You broke the trophy?
No, no, no, even a program shouldn't be able to break my trophy, right?
This is really not possible, right?
It has nothing to do with whether it's Downtown's program or not
This shouldn't be done, right?
If this was your idea then you should be the one to fix it for me
Go to the makers
Go to Kansai TV and beg them to make another one
Make the same one
Why would I do such a thing?
-You have to, this was all you!
Not surprisingly, there's a terrible atmosphere
Hey, #2? Newly made?
This is the real thing
Give it to me, wait, don't do this kind of thing!
Holding onto it
The child has returned home
The other one was just a replica
Even the marks?
Whoa
I panicked!
Ah, my brain is shutting down
I'm always holding it, when was it swapped?
Wait, is the wiretap real?
The wiretaps aren't real.
-Wait a minute
Wait a minute, wait a minute, i'm numb
You waited until now to destroy it?
The switch was made three days prior
But he misunderstood and thought he had been bugged the whole time and begins to panic
No, really, don't!
It won't go on air.
-What do you mean?
I don't think it's going to make it to air.
-What are you saying?
I can't do this!
Due to the interesting turn of events, we let him believe his misunderstanding a bit longer
Since a few days ago?
It's been a week or so.
-It can't be broadcast. It can't be broadcast
Why don't you explain what has been going on
For your own good, come clean
I XX'd
With a fan?
Wait a second, it's over
So was there anything that couldn't be broadcast yesterday?
Why do it in front of the trophy
NO
In summary
Shinichi's DM's are always open
What the hell?
Even brought out some other stuff
An unexpected twist
What is this?
-The last part is just too much
There was no wiretapping, was there?
-No wiretapping at all
He embraces his trophy and his fans
What happened in the end?
Hopefully he won't carry it around anymore
I worked with him yesterday too
He took the trophy to Hokkaido