WDT Project
Timers: ShiratoHaki, SilverDOA, Phantom, IngloriousBee, Gestalt Translators: Zebestt, Xueshi, Jump4r
Welcome to Wednesday Downtown everybody!
Welcome!
Okay let's start this. Here is our first presenter, please!
Oo, hello everyone!
It's Yoshimura from Heisei Nobushi Kobushi!!
Hi everybody!
Oh it's Yoshimura!
I am funny guy Yoshimura! I'll be in your care!
Ok let's get to...
Are you funny today as well?
What is it?
I'm funny today, as well as yesterday and tomorrow. I'm funny guy!
Sorry, I can't think of anything funny but THAT fact I can say.
Everybody,
By the way do you know the word "match fixing"?
Yes
It basically means that the winner and loser are known before the match...
and it just becomes a meaningless/show match.
Oh, it's like that hmm...
It's already known, yeah?
I have brought with me a theory about match fixing.
Here it is!
Theory: A fixed match where both parties are told to lose...
...will still be an exciting match to watch!
Ah that's evil!
That's what's going on...
Ahh...
Probably gonna be like "What you gonna do?"
That's evil!
We're trying to see what will happen if both parties are told to lose.
wouldn't it be okay if one of them cued the other.
Cue the other?
If one of them gave a cue to the other
Like "Let's stop this yeah?"
I'm sorry it's our first meeting but, what the hell are you saying?
After this, the forbidden double fixed match!
Will it truly become a battle you can't take your eyes away from?
After that, using raw eating power and cooking skills, who will be the one to consume the most wheat flour?
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
And then,
A theory about whether anyone other than herself can get Aya face paint correctly.*
*Aya is a female pro wrestler
Theory: A fixed match where both parties are told to lose will still be an exciting match to watch!
This time, the battle will unfold in the fake sports show Samurai 2018
Aah seems likely
Being the world cup this year, this is the catchphrase: "We also have battles you DEFINITELY have to WIN!"
Waah that's a big banner!
It really looks like a TBS special show right?
Celebrities confident in their physical abilities have been gathered
That's gonna be interesting
Wow that's gonna be hard...
Today, is a "qualification" setting, but just before the battle...
...the contestants will be informed by their managers that even if they win...
...their schedule is full on the day of the finals.
Resulting in a complete 180 to the show's theme:
We also have battles you DEFINITELY have to LOSE!
Getting us the complete fixed matches
The first battle is: Beach Flags
That'll put them on spot!
The first target...
What will they do?
Penalty's Wakkii, the person who won Beach Flags against the top of the entertainment industry.
Oh it's Wakkii
He'd hate being found out the most
Oh it's this kind of hardness..
That's right
First off, the explanation of the fake show...
...and getting him accustomed to the set.
So they check stuff like that...
Then, giving him plenty of practice time to not seem suspicious
Oh! He really got in there
That feels so good!
It'll be better to go barefoot
His bangs are awesome
It's fine if I go barefoot yeah?
No problem whatsoever.
It's time for the "losing meeting"
Waah, I'd hate that
Will he accept the fixed match?
This is a great moment
I'll go barefoot.
Does it seem okay?
It's better barefoot...
Wakkii's getting fired up for the big special show, but the manager
Wakkii probably wants to win too...
Feels real
Uhm, there's something that I have to apologize for...
The qualification will be done just after this right?
The finals will be next month if you can win...
Next month?
The finals
Unfortunately, your schedule doesn't really fit...
Whaaa...
The finals? If I can make it?
Uhm, yeah if that happens
Wakkii getting double booked unexpectedly
And now, to the fixing
I haven't said anything to the staff yet either..
About you not being able to be there.
So you'll kinda have to lose on purpose...
Hmm, I understand.
I need you to lose some way...
Really??
"I need you to lose some way" saying that in a sentence is weird...
Here Wakkii realizes the biggest point of the match fix
Without making the staff go...
"What's happening?"
That's what I have to do right?
Yes of course
Yeah right...
Yes, what is being looked for now is not to seem suspicious to the staff and the opponent
A real match fixing.
Makes me feel like hell
Meanwhile...
Wakkii's opponent,
Naitou Daisuke's warm-up is coming to an end
I wanna win
He looks like he'd suck at it
Naitou looks like he'd be bad
That's right
I was told by staff...
...that if you win, the finals will be March 24th
That day, you have a special show with NHK
And, it's hard saying this to the Champion but..
If you win, it'd be quite bad
It's like, what could we do?
The only way is to lose
Somehow, the match fixing idea came from the target himself
From himself
Were the staff not pissed?
Somehow the Champion...
I haven't really told the staff...
This means...
Both sides going for the loss at full force
It's started!
We have battles you DEFINITELY have to LOSE!
This is gonna be fun!
So entertaining!
It's the start!
What's gonna happen??
It's over if you get the flag,right?
You can't clearly throw yourself, right?
Now, the qualification matches for SAMURAI 2018 Beach Flag will take place
Celebrities will compete in different challenges, SAMURAI 2018
The Beach Flag qualifications will be under way
Wow he's really doing the serious face isn't he?
Only one of the competitors...
...will win and advance to the finals
That means that face is a lie, right?
If both sides go for the loss, will it still truly be an exciting match?
Wow this is interesting
From now on, we will have the announcer speak from the fixed match point of view
Now, a match you wouldn't believe both sides are trying to lose
It's better to go barefoot
Saying that but still putting on his shoes
Wow he really put them on
The only way is to lose
On the other side is the Champion Naitou who accepted the loss very quickly
Quickly accepted
Not quickly accepting, giving the idea himself
In what way will they try to lose?
A fixed match you can't take your eyes from will begin
This is amazing, I think I'm not gonna be able to watch
A high tension Beach Flag qualification battle
You really can't watch this
It has started! Wakkii falling straight away!
Naitou taking the lead after Wakkii's magnificent fall
He's in a real pinch!
How will he come through with a loss?
I can't even laugh
What are you gonna do Naitou-san?
What will you do Naitou?
Naitou-san was late as well though...
Wakkii falling straight away! What will Naitou do? He dives in the wrong direction!
He dives in the wrong direction!
Oh! He doesn't go for the flag!
Wahh I hate this! I can't watch it!
What will he do in this situation?
I don't want to watch this!
Naitou!
Don't take it Naitou!
He got the flag!
Wah he got it!
Naitou who has no time in his schedule for the finals has won the battle!
That kind of situation is hell
He isn't pleased at all
On the other hand we have Wakkii acting an expression of sadness
Wakkii was clever
Wakkii-san...Wakkii-san..
Why did you fall man?
I just fell down by accident
I shouldn't have worn shoes...
That wasn't his best, right?
It wasn't...It was okay if I won but...
Here we explain the prank to Naitou to ease his unrest
Naitou-san
Are you okay with winning?
Why is that?
He skipped a heart beat
In fact, this is not "SAMURAI 2018"
It's "Wednesday Downtown"
What the hell?
So THAT's what's going on!
Wait, what the hell?
We told you both to lose to set up a fixed match and to try and see what would be the result
REALLY??
What the hell is that theory man?
Falling down immediately like that, sorry but that really pissed me off
HE FELL DOOOWN!!
I thought "what am I gonna do??"
This is too funny
I thought "Let's not get it then"
He dove in where there was no flag!
Then I thought "Yay! He'll definitely get it!"
"He didn't take it!"
I was running behind...
He's not even close!
...so I saw you not get it when you jumped in!
Right?
I thought "He didn't take it!"...
"Let's not get it either then!" while going for it
It's because it's scary
What are we gonna do?
Why did you fall down man c'mon...
This is something I can't show my kids!
Really funny!
The next fixed match targets are
This is so good!
Eeeh~that's that's not sports...
(I hate this guy)
I can't do that as an athlete
You'd hate doing that
It's completely fine but, it's gonna be tough
Fixed Beach Flag Battle : Round Two
Are they that serious...
What will happen?
There aren't that many patterns
No, there aren't
A real fixed battle where both sides have to convincingly lose
I think there isn't much more than falling down
And the battle has started! It looks real! It looks real! They dove in! But can't seem to get the flag!
What will they do from now on?
They're acting dumb
Hold on a sec...
It's not here!
After a purposely missed flag, acting as though not seeing it!
It's right there!
They can definitely see it!
What's that? HG is hiding the flag!
It's not here!
Really?
This seems like it'll go on for a while!
I can't watch this
This is so embarrassing
It's impossible, I can't find it!
Ogata who absolutely saw the flag is acting as if there was nothing
It's so embarrassing
I'm sorry, I'm sorry it's right here
What?
Now is the reveal of the prank...
Did you get asked to do something?
Is it okay to say? The request?
They told me "The day of the finals...
...you have another thing on your schedule...
...so please lose"
That's a good face
So that's why!?
What the hell is this? Inside of the pit we were like "please get it" in hushed voices
We were telling each other
It got resurfaced during that
You pushed it here once didn't you!
Samurai 2018! The next battle is...
There are patterns other than just running
Fixed musical chairs!
A musical chairs battle of idols and gravure models,
Where sitting down is NOT an option
I probably can't watch this
Right?
The song stopped!
One of them sat down!
Sure it become like this
Did she feel the pressure and sit down?
This is weird
It is, because a chair is available and they're not sitting down
But...
The rest refuse to sit down
Two minutes pass
It became a forfeited match!
This can't happen
Are you feeling ill or something?!
With that, our last category, fixed arm wrestling!
The contestants are...
This is gonna be good!
My pride's on the line man!
There's nothing to do but push
The foreigner who hates to lose: Bobby Ologun
He doesn't like to lose Bobby
And his opponent
What'll happen if I go to the finals?
A bodybuilder as well as an entertainer : Nakayama Kinnikun
Both of them look like they're upset
Two entertainers who really hate to lose
It's hard to try and lose here
What kind of loss will they act out without the opponent noticing?
Now, the battle that you can't lose is starting
Oooh~ they're properly doing this part
First we have a seemingly real grip battle going on
You can't really tell that soon, a farce will play out from here on, amazing reality
You can't show this though
it has begun!
Double fixed match! The third battle will be arm wrestling
Sure enough...
It has begun!
Ah~ They're putting in force!
When you look at it, it seems a like a great battle, but is there really force put in there?
This can't be!
Only the face!
If you look closely you can see that both are trying to pull away from each other
Bobby is pulling at full force!
Kinnikun as well!
They're definitely found out
Their hands separated!
Now a short break
They're doubting something right?
They're thinking like "What?"
They're thinking to themselves "What in the world is going on?"
Both are in a panic state
What's wrong?
What is it?
What?
Bobby looking towards the camera with unease, they'll go at it again while thinking "I somehow have to lose"
He's like "why isn't he pushing?"
"Why is he pulling?"
They're pulling!
Two men going for the "win"
The other side is pulling
Is there nothing else to do?
Something that couldn't happen has happened
A new competition has emerged : Minus Arm Wrestling
Has a battle this amazing happened before? You can't take your eyes away from it!
Bobby sucks at this!
A reverse battle! The two are pulling with their full strength!
They're pulling!
And It's Kinnikun's victory with an amazing display of power!
Nakayama Kinnikun advances to the finals!
I'm really sad!
Now, we explain the prank to the duo that gave it their all
He really failed there
This is not Samurai 2018...
...it's Wednesday Downtown.
Are you kid- ARE YOU KIDDING ME!
When he said "Ready? Go!" we lost the grip instantly...
...and I thought "Wow this is really bad"
Since that can't happen...
That means, you can't have amazing battles even if they are fixed beforehand.
Now that was funny
How did you find that everyone?
An epic battle!
It was wasn't it, that arm wrestling one, a new type of battle got discovered
Where you pull together
Their faces got a bit flustered too didn't they..
Yeah
Uhm...
It's nothing
IT'S NOTHING?! When I ask you a question...
I'm sorry I'm sorry
But she cut me off and said "It's nothing"
I mean it was funny but, you can't really do a second one...
Ahh~ right.
Let's leave this for about a year...
To shoot a lot of them right?
Shoot a bunch?
Right
And then you put them on here
A year later? The people will have aged when you put it on air
Yeah they would have
Is that okay?
We can't even be sure that you will still be around...
You're right
With that said, we didn't go for a year but...
After the shooting, the second part of it is already complete
These losing battles will be aired soon
Let's move on, the next presenter is this person, please come on out!
It's Hamaguchi from Yoiko
I'm Hamaguchi!
I've already come with a lot of mixed rule eating battles on this show but do you remember them?
There were many of them
There were
For example, I was the presenter for the battle between a competitive eater and a pig
Yeah that was it
That was an interesting one
This time I have brought with me...
...a new rule. Here it is!
Mixed rule competitive eating! Consuming a huge amount of barley wheat flour!
It's a battle where you prepare the dishes and eat them
Oh that's what it is
It's not just about your eating, but also about...
...your cooking skills
Can't you just...drink the flour?
That would be a pretty boring video probably
Mixed rule competitive eating! Consuming a huge amount of barley wheat flour!
Sorry but...
I don't wanna do this
This battle's participant are...
With an amazing eating, but no cooking skills...
Oh so she can't cook
...the competitive eater, Angela Satou!
But she can eat
Next we have "the witch" Sugahara Hatsuyo...
She is really good too
Oh she can cook too
...with eating capabilities reaching Angela's...
...she is currently running a bakery and has cooking skills
Next is this duo where one is the cook and the other is the eater
And finally we have the comedian team of three
It's just flour? We can do it! I'm pumped as hell!
Both eating strength and cooking skill are unknown
Ah,a bit more
With the strength of numbers they faced the challenge
Wished he'd taken everything off
Currently, It's 5 minutes to 9 am.
With a time limit: 9am to 9pm
It's going to be 12 hours
That's quite long
Are you stupid?
Wished there was more to him than stripping
Between their different eating power and cooking abilities
Yeah,thought there was more
Exactly which team will consume the most amount of flour?
Our battlefield is set in this rented location
entirely for today's purpose
Flour Mansion
The 4 teams are given ingredients and cooking utensils
In the back,its filled with flour too
and then separated into their respective rooms
They are given enough flour to
carry back and use
5 minutes to 9:00 am
that much?
The showdown is about to begin
Starting with the comedian team
Lets confirm our food supplies
Food
So they share it?
Wow amazing
Ohhhh,There's a ton available
What's all this
Cabbage
Wow, there really is quite a bit
We can make okonomiyaki
Okonomiyaki's good
Let's go with the "Opening Food"
Let's go
Amazing
"Well done food"
The typical flour food
The process of making okonomiyaki
they sure are making a lot
Meanwhile, back at Sugawara's place
Baker? I wonder if she can eat so much bread
make different kinds of bread
I would like to show you that they are many different types and kinds of breads
With her main job being a baker,
She begins making bagels
On the other hand, Angela
That's going to make you bloat
Even if someone like me who can't cook, I can easily make this.
*Suiton is a hearty soup with dumplings,chicken and vegetables from Gunma Prefecture,Japan.
The cuisine she mentioned was: Suiton*
Using only flour and water
she kneads and then boils it
That might work really well
That's going to reduce quite a bit of the flour
Super easy and packed to the MAX with flour
A top dish made just for this challenge
With no time wasted, she embarks on her Suiton Strategy
On the other hand, confidence in his cooking skills, Modegi
If it doesn't taste good, you will not be able to eat large amounts of it
From breakfast
Hearty
Flour based cooking I would like showcase for all to see
kifuu~ Going all out~
Was he such a character before?
And what exactly is he planning to make?
When you speak of flour, you think of gratin
So I would like to make gratin
In terms of ingredients,chicken are the best
Chicken?
Therefore I would like to make chicken gratin
Then I leave it to you
Nakanishi decided that for breakfast
to make chicken macaroni gratin
Can you really use that much flour in gratin?
Shouldn't take much flour
Without delay,
Angela's self styled suiton has been completed
That looks a bit
Brothless and Bland
Rather than Sution it's
closer to lumps of flour
its good and fun to slurp
It feels the same as eating wanton skin
The amount she ate and the amount of flour consumed
has an almost 1:1 ratio
Around 15 Suiton
She has easily consumed 700g of flour
Won't she get tired?
Back here, with the focus on tasty
Modegi has also completed his gratin
Its finally ready. Thank you for waiting
What a great amount
What amazing gratins he made
Alright, diving in, Sensei
Looks really delicious
Filled to the brim with cheese
That does look scrumptious
Delicious
Chicken Macaroni Gratin made for 5 people
clocking in at 1600g calories replacing breakfast
Ah, its getting there
Thank you for the meal
I have finished the meal
However , how much flour was consumed in this dish?
It was a measly 30g
Roughly 3 spoons of flour
He should have made the macaroni out of flour
Due to Modegi's unwavering insistence on taste
The amount of flour spent was just 2%
What a horrendous flour consumption ratio
He ate quite a lot
However, Nakanishi without realizing anything
The others are in survival mode
while I'm the only one chilling in a restaurant feeling happy
In the meantime, Comedian team and Sugawara
Went to get tools which are missing
So that's viable too
They should've brought noodle making tools
Modegi, too heads out to his restaurant
and gets his secret ingredient
Replenishing his kitchen tools with this trip
He's aiming to make good food with his flour
to reduce the most amount of flour
Back to Kotoge which returned from shopping for the comedian team
Ah, you brought back a noodle machine
This is good
You told me to go buy this
They had a noodle machine?
I see
Amazing
It might be delicious
There it is, a hotplate
This is fantastic
Immediately, utilizing the hotplate, the production of okonomiyaki begins
By looks it seems quite crunchy
Delicious
That seems good
The expended flour amount should be reasonable
Between the three of them, two okonomiyakis were consumed
The amount of flour per 200g of okonomiyaki is
25 percent at 50g of the original weight
So its not that useful, losing to suiton
Don't you feel that..
our way of using flour is bad.
The efficiency is bad
This method isn't good enough
it has bad churn rate of flour
Not effective
There probably is a way of increasing the amount of flour used
Udon, they are going to make udon
using another method of eating
Why don't we try eating raw flour mixed with sugar?
Uwa,are you sure about that?
Too bothersome?
Why don't you try it just once?
That's probably for the best
Aiming for the 100% reduction rate of flour
The directly eating flour strategy
its going to be bad
How will it?
Impossible,it can't be
He took a decent mouthful in
Impossible?
Meanwhile, Sugawara who also returned from her shopping trip
Using the home-bakery she brought, she begins making pastries
So its bread
This is going to be useful
Cmon!
I wonder how it would turn out
Cmon!!
At this moment, her bagels were completed
looks delicious
The bagels have good efficiency as 81 percent of the bagel is flour
She consumes 7 of them
On the other hand, prioritizing efficiency over taste is Angela's Suiton Strategy
Back to Angela, and her tasteless suiton method
If there is no change in taste, I will get bored of it
Chicken Soup and...
In order to consume the highly efficient suiton,
That would work
That seems feasible
she forcefully injects flavour into the tasteless suiton
It has the aroma of ramen
This is damn good
She succeeds at her strategy, consuming the huge amount of 800g of flour
by giving it multiple tastes
On the other hand,
Nakanishi who is still waiting for Modegi
Now what should I...
He's wasting his eating capacity
If you eat like this, your stomach will surely fill
For some reason
Wasting his stomach space with something not made with flour
What a waste
Really
He should be training, to build up an appetite
Back to the comedian team who are showing new developments
If its Udon, we can do it
about a 4 person serving
4 persons worth? Lets do 4
4.. Couldn't we go for 6?
2,2,2
You said 4 didn't you?
6..6 I said
Can we finish 6 person?
You can down udon easily
No , lets go for 8
isn't he treating it as if its not his problem?
Placing 8 persons worth of flour into the noodle maker
If they normally don't eat that much, it might be impossible
So they really make noodles like this
They wait for 10 minutes
Make it like this?
Really
After waiting,soba will be produced
O..oh here it comes
Wahh
We can really make it like this
Can we?
Look
The result:
Impressive
a bit more
Is it coming out properly?
It's coming out
This will definitely have better efficiency, no matter how I think about it.
Yeah
What will they do with the leftover flour?
Its mostly made out of flour , isn't it?
Yeah,yeah,yeah
They can just add flavouring to it, or make kaki-udon
This is the way isn't it?
We have gotten our hands on an unbelievable item
The Udon are completed
Looks good
Good
It's Udon
Delicious
It's really like Udon
Its chewy and firm
The person who told us to make okonomiyaki was an idiot
At 71% consumption rate of flour, the 8 persons worth of udon
Look, they should have made noodles earlier like I suggested
has been consumed by the three of them
Collectively, they consumed 1kg of flour
There's no need to drink the stock
With their number advantage, will they be able to pull off a miracle?
On the other hand, Still the top choice
That's huge
While the bread is busy baking, I would like to eat okonomiyaki
Living up to her big eater status, she is able to
That's good pace
consume okonomiyaki made for 20 at 4kg.
That's really amazing
Witch Sugawara finally shows her true abilities
Finally Modegi has returned from his workplace
Modegi's so slow
With his tools gathered
There are so much tools
his next dish:
Using tomato sauce to make a Gnocchi styled flour pasta
It turned out really well
At the point where Nakanishi finished eating
It's 3pm, 6 hours since the beginning of the challenge
Therefore it's time for the half time point announcement
Here are the results for the 1st half:
I'm glad
2500g, Angela's amazing
What..
But
isn't it fine?
The comedian team seem to be trying
Huh!?
only 210g
That's the worst
He did too much extra stuff
Modegi sure is hopeless
The flour consumption challenge has finally reached the 2nd half
Sugawara gave Angela a big lead, but her strategy from now on will be...
I understand now that when you keep eating the same exact thing...
...you get really tired mentally
From now on, I will make small amounts of a variety of dishes
Sugawara, who can cook not only bread
But also various other dishes
Ooh it's suiton
Suiton
Ah so suiton is definitely good
Pizza
She can make pizza too?
Waaah
*Note: Chijimi is Korean dish, like a pancake filled with vegetables
Chijimi*
And other barley wheat flour dishes
This person is amazing
With various types and flavors, eaten at small amounts
She's really good
So as to not get too bored
Crepes, I get it
It's really tasty
Wow!
On the other hand, the three people comedian team
We can actually maybe win this
Both Sugawara-san and Angela-san are alone, right?
That sofa is really small isn't it
I think they'll start getting full from now on
Yeah they will
We are three people here
It's because there's three of'em
Taking noodles as their main dish
Oh ramen!
Even showing their ability to make cookies
Ah-
They continue to consume more flour
And then, Angela who's got the lead position
I need to expand the lead to feel safe
Yeah yeah! Go for it!
Will you continue with suiton?
Yes, with suiton
But no matter how you change the flavor, suiton is suiton
You'll get bored
That's right
It's hard
It's getting tougher
Ahh, you can do it Angela
Her lack of cooking skills has started to show
What the hell is this shot?
There's a limit to the suiton strategy
Scary- what's this shot?
Finally, the tag team who's in last place in convincing fashion
Modegi!
After the results get announced
Even a stupid man would notice the problem
Don't call him stupid!
If you try to make things that doesn't use stuff other than flour, like sugar
I think we can do this
We're putting in other stuff so
That might be the problem
The stupid one is talking
But we might also be overthinking the issue
Modegi who got criticized thoroughly
Ah- their teamwork
Prepares this dish next
Both of them are stupid right?
I made something that's creamy
Oh isn't this good! Gnocchi
Barley wheat flour gnocchi pasta with a white sauce
The appearance is good
Also...
...Adding some truffle
Waaah- Modegi
Two hours remain of the challenge
Oh!
How's Angela?
Here's the amount of flour used by each team
Waah she's getting closer!
At the top is Angela but,
Sugawara shows a great performance and the difference between them becomes about 100g
Yeah it's because Angela's getting tired
But unfortunately the other two teams have almost no hope of winning
And we can see the expressions of tiredness on not only Nakanishi's face, but also on the comedians as well
Oh so it's no good
With that said, we take an emergency measure
What is it?
We take the two bottom teams and put them together to give them a chance of winning
That's how...
Idiots + Comedians
Hey there
Hello
I want to share...
...the chef's prime creation
The comedians get their appetite back with the chef's real cooking
They get to eat really tasty stuff
It's tasty
Then I'll have some croquets as well
Nakanishi also
It's done!
On the other hand, Angela...
Go Angela!
Eating has gotten tougher so...
I'm going with a drinking strategy
Drinking??
She creates a shake that's mostly flour
For her last spurt
That's fricking amazing
You can taste the flour more like this...
She made a wonderful thing there
Sugawara is taking out the sweet bread she prepared first thing in the morning
After an 11 hour cooking time
11 hours!
Itadakimasu
She eats what is about 15 times the normal sized sweet bread
1.2 kg of bread completed
Of course she's putting nutella on it
It's 9 o'clock
This battle that lasted 12 hours has come to an end
He cooked so many of them
Modegi made so many of them!
Who has consumed the most barley wheat flour?
Modegi...
Uwah looks tough
Thank you for your 12 hour hard work everybody!
Surprisingly this time,
The difference between the first and third place is only 300g!
Wow
Whaat
What a good match
And the winner is...
With an amount of
4373g
Angela Satou!!
Waah!
YEEAAH!!
Yeaah
WAAAAH!! I DID IT!!
She drank flour
Are you really that happy?
I'm so happy
I get that you're happy but...
...this isn't a project where one would cry
I did it!
You still couldn't win five people
If we can't win like this there's nothing we could do...
As expected, competitive eaters are amazing
His belly is completely full
It's gonna tear apart!
It becomes like this, yeah
Your belly swells up
As a result, we can say that barley wheat flour makes your belly swell
that was amazing
Yeah that's right
In the end, five men couldn't beat a single lady
Yeah
Modegi is stupid though right?
Hey!
He only wanted to show off his cooking skills
He didn't use the flour at all!
Didn't use it
Nakanishi is also stupid but Modegi is even MORE stupid!
Hey!
When I saw his tan I thought "He's stupid"
Stupid people don't really eat barley wheat flour then right?
Even if you say "barley wheat coloured"
skin color
That was funny
Next, we have a corner where we show off some theories from the streets
Viewers' Theories!
Tonight's presenter is
It's Kendo Kobayashi!
Hello everyone!
Today we have some academic theories
Ooh
When this airs, the Pyeongchang Olympics will have already started
I think we all know the Olympic Logo right?
The five ring one...
The five ring logo
I think you all know it so...
Do you know remember the order of the colors on it?
You have seen it SO many times but...
The continents
Yes the five continents
The one on the end was black right?
This side?
Eehh
Mori-san do you know any of them?
I...
..feel like the one in the center was green
Oh green right, black and green
Shall I say them?
Yeah
From top left...
Top left okay
Blue
Hmm
Yellow
Hmm yellow
Black
Black was in the center!?
Yes the black is in the center
Green
And red
A logo that you have seen hundreds of time probably
That's right
I couldn't remember
So a human's vague memory
Regarding this...
...the theory I have brought is THIS!
Theory: Nobody but Aya herself can draw her face paint correctly!
Of course they won't!
They won't?
Don't even need to test this...
We're testing the theory that nobody but Aya herself...
...can draw her face paint correctly
Female pro-wrestler Aya Kong's trademark
There's green and blue and
Buru-chan!
Is her face paint, and when you look closely...
She's really grabbing her wow
...the colours are green, red and blue
How's it gonna be?
And the shape is pretty complex
She got it on these parts as well
Can anyone draw this...
Wah you can't get that
...from memory alone?
This is gonna be very hard
First at the pro-wrestling venue
We asked around in a place like this
Oh I get it
We got pro-wrestling fans to give it a shot
If you do it like that maybe some people will get it
Aya kong's face paint is like this!
Oh it's completely different
It's somehow similar
The general shape right
Eeeeh-
It's nothing like it
The shape is different here too
It looks nothing like it
Everyone knew who Aya Kong is but...
Ah very different
..not only were the shapes incorrect...
The colours were wrong too
It's getting mixed up with other wrestlers
That means, next we have
If no one could get it there...
A person who has...
...an active relationship with pro-wrestlers already
He's into this stuff
RG from LaserRamon (partner of Hard-Gay)
You can expect something from him but...
He was in a pro-wrestling club in college
He's even been in the ring himself after becoming a comedian
A very big pro-wrestling fan by all means
Amazing
This theory is about Aya Kong-san but...
Eh
Wha-What about Aya Kong-san is it?
It's about drawing the face paint
Aah...
of Aya Kong-san
...I get it
I get it.. okay
Ah he doesn't remember it does he?
Could you draw it please?
It's quite hard though right
I get it...It's a good question you've got here...
Good question, alright alright
Red- I think there was red- There was definitely red
But was it only that though?
So will RG...
...be able to draw Aya's face paint correctly?
I'm done
If he gets it it'd be awesome
This is Aya Kong-san's face paint!
Ah it becomes like that huh
That's a bit hmm...
Which means...
AAAH! Ouch ouch ouch!
But I knew there'd be green
Ah! There's green!
Hey! You're being pretty modest
That's pretty colorful
There's green...
Yeah there's hella green
And there's blue too...
True true
In total: Red - Blue - Green
Throw some blonde in there
and I could be a traffic light replacement
Very true
In the end, he couldn't draw...
Is it even possible?
...that traffic light face
And with that, our next contestant is
She's gonna get mad
Tokyo 03's Toyomoto
The Industry's No. 1 Pro-Wrestler Enthusiast
His wife is a pro-wrestler, right?
Right, because of his wife
I'm drawing on this right?
No way he can do this
Are you feeling confident?
I'm pretty sure I can do this
Oh really?
Your wife...
She's a pro-wrestler as well
Miss Mongol
In regards to this
I'm probably the best in the entertainment industry
Even if he couldn't...
He has to consider the appearance and genre
3 colors
Oooh spot on
Let's use 3 colors
The eyebrows are in the middle of the red section
All that's left is the pattern
A man who's wife is a pro-wrestler, the result is...
Aya Kong's facepaint looks...
...like this
Amazing!
While the use of colors was mostly accurate...
...unfortunately, he messed up the positioning of the blue stripe
but it's pretty close
Therefore
What a waste...
So close!
Suuuper close
Well, the fact you were able to get this close
is pretty amazing
I know right!
My neck... you took some skin off
The blue should be a little bit higher
Really, not lower?
No, higher.
Ah, it goes up to the eyelids
Mhmm
Despite being the entertainment world's #1 wrestling enthusiast, he's incorrect.
He was sooo close
Next, this active wrestler takes the challenge.
They both work together
woah, he's way off
Is that... Aya's face paint?
No way he just drew that
He drew that guy from Warriors
I was waaaaay off!
Despite being an active wrestler, he was incorrect.
Lastly, our next guest has fought countless times with Aya
Oh right! Bull-chan!
Shouldn't Bull-chan be able to draw him?
Former female pro-wrestler, Bull Nakano
She owns a restaurant now
We asked Buru about her former wrestling days
Nakano's
A store called "Nakano's Bull"
I wrestled with Aya everyday for about two and a half years
During that time I stuck pictures of her on the walls in my house
so I would never forget my hatred
They've been in my house ever since
This'll be perfect
I can do it
If Bull-chan can't do it, it's impossible
The final challenger, Bull!
The result is...
I'm in trouble if this is wrong
Aya Kong's facepaint looks like this
totally wrong
Hold on, Nakano-san
Gimme a break!
Eh?
Nakano-san
Excuse me
As expected of a junior
That didn't hurt at all
How nostalgic
There you have it, it turns out no one was able to correctly draw the facepaint
Only the real one could do it?
Subou-san, what did you think?
I'm happy there was a challenge like this, I can already remember the position of the colours.
You think could do it if we gave you the challenge?
Well we're not going to
Check out our Facebook and Website for more Wednesday Downtown! This video was subbed by a community run project called the Wednesday Downtown project. Thanks for watching!
Next week, Theory: "Finding another person in your bed...
...is the scariest thing that could happen."
w-what
And
I want to leave the group and go solo
If Jungle Pocket's Ace Saito leaves
will Oota and Ponkotsu Otake be able to continue on?
Solo...
Solo?
And then, with a height under 150cm
searching for the strongest 100kg bean-tank