Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Who's there?
It's Koyabu
The one with the good voice!
This time, I'm bringing the second part of a theory that was tested four years ago
It is, how to put it, a bold experiment
Please take a look
The 2nd Comparing sweet and harsh, the harsh will make people more desperate
What kind of theory is it?
Previously we did 'if you can hang a bar for one second longer than normal, you will be rewarded 5,000 yen'
With this sweet approach
A total of three people extended their records
The harsh was doing the hanging bar in the air, if they let go they'll automatically do a bungee jump
A harsh situation
As a result, not even one person beat their own record
Completely stunned by fear
-Because it was too scary
Forced to let go
The whole team fell beautifully
In a sense, it was a good experiment
The conclusion was that when you are under too much pressure, you won't perform as well as you normally would
-I see
Nice experiment!
This type of result disproves the perseverance theory
It's like a reflection of the current times.
-That's right
The corresponding data was obtained
What a great show
In summary, can the pressure of harshness be overcome
Will anyone extend their record?
Hold on a little longer
In addition, Showa, in retrospect, was a mess
Also, a new project will be started
The 2nd Comparing sweet and harsh, the harsh will make people more desperate
The participants in this validation are
Battle with Nature - Survival Camping
A fake program called these five people
Got a bunch of great people
I'm sure you've all heard that we're having a camping training session here
Actually, it's a fake show.
-Eh?
What's going on?
-What the hell is it?
What do you think this program is?
Progressing very fast
Looking at this collection of participants made me a bit concerned
There's Nishimura, there's Dancho, and a Mameshiba
It can only be that one, right?
With Mameshiba people in it
As soon as you said it was a fake show I immediately came to my senses
I've never seen Mameshiba on anything else
What are we doing in a place like this?
The other day, weren't you asked to do hanging bar?
Did it!
Eh
-Everyone?
The sweet part's done already
Did you hang?
Is it the one were we get paid?
If I don't get the money this month, I can't pay my water bill
Yes, in fact, two days ago
The members were called out separately under the name of other fake projects
In advance, we measured the time of hanging the bar in general
I see
Then
How long?
If you exceed this record by one second, you'll be awarded 5,000 yen per second
Oh~~
Ooh
Jimmy
Money is thus used as the motivating factor
To measure the time for the sweet motivator
This really makes people happy
I can make more money this way than any commercial performance
In summary, the usual data and the "sweet" data measured on that day are shown in the graph
What's wrong with Nishimura-kun?
Three of the five extended their records
Thus, a nice reward, to some extent, has the effect of allowing people to hold on a bit longer
This time it was also confirmed
Please do a follow-up on that one
Follow-up?
-There is no bar here
This time it's the other way around. We are testing how a penalty affects people
How much will it change in relation to the previous record
Ah, i'm scared, what do you mean by punishment?
The punishment is the bungee jump over there
Wait wait wait
-There's a bridge!
From there?
-Jump down?
Bungee jumping?
Hanging bar in the air with a bungee cord attached to the body
That's enough, that's enough
Bungee is a NG for me
I said that on this program, right?
Yes, it was said
Said bungee is a NG
But you can also not fall
No. That's only if you can set a new record, right?
NG?
-NG
It's also an NG for me
I feel like the world is ending
Yes, in fact, three of the members consider a bungee NG
What is the difference between this and SAW?
The kind of psychotic killing method
So, we took the members, whose faces were full of disgust, and went to the bungee jumping platform
Wow wow wow wow
Scary!
Just need to exceed the last record, right?
They can go back if they stay for longer
This is too scary, right?
57m
In addition, this time it is not a vertical drop bungee jump
Instead, we chose the swinging style to increase the fear factor
Is there such a thing?
This is not bungee jumping anymore, right?
I definitely will not jump
Is that the thing?
That is the bar
So first of all, the first person
Nishimura
-Eh?
Tough to go first
I don't want to be the first one
The first time he almost broke the 1 minute mark
Nishimura, who failed to extend the record with the promise of a reward, comes to challenge first
By the way, the backpack carried during the previous test
The weight of the harness and helmet was the same as when bungee jumping
It's really strict!
Is it pulling me? Why are you pulling me?
To get the rope...
A little bit shaky
This is scary
So scary!
Gotta hang there!?
One minute and five seconds is quite long
It's going out
Your palms will sweat, right?
Scary!
And the wind!
The eagle over there seems to have foreseen your death
The eagle's waiting for Nishimura to go down
Generally, if there are people it won't come anywhere close
I'm going to be fed to it
Will Nishimura be able to overcome the pressure?
Can he exceed the previous record of one minute and five seconds?
Ready, start!
Now you'd complain about why you stayed up for so long the first time
It's not good if you fall like this.
-It's not good, right?
Scary!
Wow, so scary!
This is the same as hanging on the edge of a cliff
Back to front
No, this is terrifying
It's really scary. It's like a shot from a movie
Very scary
This is bad this is bad
Just hold on for one minute and five seconds
Go for it!
Wow scary
Half a minute
Don't look down
Be calm
Whoa, seriously!
Thirty seconds left. Come on, come on
Not good...
No way, right?
It's okay, it's okay
20 seconds left
Not good!
Go for it!
It's okay. It's okay.
-Not good!
15 seconds left
A very typical fall
That's awful!
This is the fall
Scary!
This is too unbearable
Very, very scary!
It's like seeing the moment of a person's death
Nishimura, just ten seconds away, fell with regret
10 seconds is long
This is a big deal
Really?
The scariest bungee jump I've done so far
Wow, really? What's so scary about it?
First of all, not facing forward
Normally you're looking ahead when you fall
If you can't hold on and fall, it's really...
It's the same feeling as falling down because of an accident
It totally feels like the moment of death
So, the next to go to their death is
Morita
The survival time of Morita, whose record was extended by sixteen seconds because of the reward, is thirty-eight seconds
How?
No!
That guy is a bungee NG!
Please put your foot on the board
Give me a second, wait, I can't reach it
Give me a minute!
Give me a minute
Wait a little bit
I want to see Morita fall down!
What is he talking about?
Can you wait a little longer?
Can you let me go back first? Wait a second
This is very forceful
Same as the last time, when none of them could extend the record
Their entire bodies are filled with terror
So much so that Morita could not even reach the starting position
I guess so
Can't even stand up
The bungee NG people are faced with a lot of pressure
Let me wait a minute
Wait wait
Hurry up
As he couldn't make up his mind
He took 20 minutes to finally get ready
Not good enough
Go
Okay, here we go
It really took a lot of time
Can he or can he not overcome his fear and exceed the record of 38 seconds?
It should be okay. It's only 38 seconds
Prepare, Start!
It looks like he's about to fall
Morita
-You can do it!
Thirty-eight seconds
Not looking good
Survive!
Too nervous
Morita, you have to survive!
Ten seconds!
It's Kaiji!
Almost!
20 seconds to go
It's been 20 seconds
He can do it
More than usual
Twenty-five!
The fear is working
Yes, you can
Almost 30
30!
So close
Five seconds to go
This is accident footage
It is completely the expression before death
The picture is really clear
Well, he looks ok
What a pity!
Four seconds to go
Damn
Morita died with four seconds to spare
Goodbye Morita
The phrase "Goodbye, Morita" has found a new meaning
Can't let me fall, right? I said NG
What a pity, only four seconds away
My heart rate at that time was terrible, right?
Breathing was also bad
At that time it was really no longer possible
Even we could hear it
You can't broadcast this kind of expression on TV
This should be against the rules
Because I'm NG, really
You let me fall, how could you?
How to put it?
I feel the frustration of having been murdered by Wednesday Downtown
Its really heavy
There are really things in life that you can't do anything about, no matter what
Next up
Pretty good?
Because you can get paid
In light of a potential reward, Kaede held on for 9 more seconds
Is it doable?
You'd surely be scared
Already crying
Crying!
I want to go home
She's the last person who needs to do this kind of thing
After all, she's an idol
She's unlucky she became famous through this show
That's true
No, no, no, no
Stop giving Hamada close-ups!
Ethical Issues
Crying
How can someone who cries like that do it?
Morita is bad enough
Can she exceed the previous record?
Yes, you can!
Go, go, go!
Thirty seconds is still possible, right?
Start
Go for it!
-She can do it!
I want to cheer her on
Concentrating
7, 8
Nine.
Ah you counted wrong, Jimmy
Why do you need to rely on yourself to count
-There are timing boards over there
Why're you timing it yourself
Jimmy is pretty relaxed
Twenty seconds have passed.
-Twenty
Concentrating
Not bad, not bad
Go for it!
And no more crying.
-Amazing
Is it possible to pass?
-I'll be 30 soon
Thirty seconds. Hold on
Five seconds to go.
-Not good. A little shaky
Is she...
Great! Great!
This is really moving
Awesome!
She put her life on the line
Kaede finally managed to update her record in the face of fear
Great!
Finally, the first survivor
This list of participants is pretty impressive
Great!
Former participants
Impressive!
I really can't do high places
I even cry on the plane
She worked hard
Were you thinking "don't fall!" and stuff like that?
I was hanging there think "I don't want to die"
I feel like today is the most powerful day of my life
The type that is very strong under adversity
But Hamada isn't smiling at all
-A look of regret
No, no, no.
-Disappointment written all over your face
Next up
So short
Only hung for eight seconds originally?
Before the issue of rewards or punishments, Jimmy found hanging extremely difficult
I can't!
Yes, 20 seconds.
-Come on
Wait a sec!
Can he beat his own record of nineteen seconds?
Let me go
Prepare, Start!
You can do it
Go, go, go, Jimmy!
No!
Only 8 seconds!
He said "no"
Eight seconds
So fast
Scary!
You said "no", right?
Very, very scary
Terrible
Crying for this kind of thing is a first for me
Only eight seconds
Are you all right, Jimmy?
From the beginning, too much force was used
Couldn't even move
What he is saying, I don't understand at all
This is not a bungee jump
-It's even scarier than bungee jumping
Scarier than bungee jumping
It's like listening to some war story
So the final challenge is Dancho
Known for his great endurance
Especially in this program
He is the unbeatable candidate
Will he be able to surpass his own record of one minute and 29 seconds?
So long!
We start straight away
The expression is already very strange
Prepare, Start!
The face has become the same as Morita
A man of great perseverance
Not even 10 seconds yet
Saying only bad stuff
Go for it!
Its been a few seconds, Jimmy
Not even 20 seconds.
-How the hell is it below 20?
There's going to be a problem when it's over
Oh, its working
Reaching 30
Times three
That's a nasty way of putting it
This statement is not good
Times three something
Okay one minute one minute
Awesome
Passed the original one
30 seconds left
Great
-Not thinking anything
How do you feel now?
-Why are you asking him that?
So close
His hands are shaking
He was so close
Jimmy!
I blame Jimmy, he said a lot of useless things
Of course it will turn out like this
Did you hear Jimmy's voice?
Super annoying
In summary
Only some can extend due to fear
Kaede is awesome!
Only Kaede succeeded
Don't want to see her fall either, right?
Sure enough, we hoped she wouldn't fall and would come back safely
Everyone is happy
He said something very important
"What the hell? Why didn't she fall down?" and so on
Everyone clapped when Kaede succeeded
Only one person kept his head down like this
When Morita fell, he smiled as if someone asked him
"Should we go out for a steak?"
He had a big meal.
-As if there was a plate of steak in front of you
I'd like to ask if everyone here was born in the Showa period
Yes
We all experienced the turbulent Showa era
Thinking back, there was a lot of unethical behavior
There are a lot of those things, right?
The TV world is the same way
The theory I bring is this:
Showa, in retrospect, was a mess
It's true.
-It was a mess
Showa, in retrospect, was a mess
Compared to today, the Showa era had a lax system
The most liberal of these was the regulation of smoking
It's true.
-Everyone smoked
At that time, smoking on the road and at stations was a common behavior
There were no non-smoking cars on the Shinkansen
It was also fine on the plane
And even in the hospital consultation room
There were also many doctors who smoked in front of their patients
In the diet, politicians were covered in a haze
Thinking about it now, it was a mess
In a recent survey, the smoking rate among men was at 27.8%
But in Showa 41, it was as high as 83.7%
That's true.
-Everybody smoked
So at the time of the morning rush, the platform was like this
Incidentally, our Downtown also
So young
In the past, when I had no job and no money
I wanted to be on TV so much, I wanted to be on TV!
Didn't even have a regular program
This is just a special case
Even in Heisei, you could still smoke and record talk shows in the studio
There were also other messy things about the Showa era
Traffic
The current Tokyo morning rail congestion rate is 163%
For the full complement of trams in the 1960s
Surprisingly, it was over 300%
Not only was the number of runs low, but preparation for the ride was also impossible
Thus, it was a hell of a commute
We asked Mr. Hanashima, a former employee of the National Railroad, about the situation
Looking back on it now it really was like hell
We were overwhelmed by too many people
Broken windows were also a common occurrence
Especially when shattered by elbows, there were casualties
Peak season, summer, was the worst
Some people collapsed because of the heat and pressure
Heatstroke
What's more
It may not even be imaginable now
Sometimes when people squeezed on, their shoes fell off
When leaving the platform, they realized their shoes were missing
Larger stations had a shoe rental service
Incidentally, it was not only the train that was like this
Through the window?
The roads were also a mess
Wearing a seat belt while driving was not a requirement
Driving a motorcycle without a helmet was also the norm
Also, driving etiquette was not taken seriously
The lane lines at that time were also undefined
Looking back on it now, Showa was incredible
There are also other things
The pesticide DDT, which has now been detected as a carcinogen and banned from use
Spraying wildly!
Was sprayed directly onto human skin
Absorb the vibrations of this machine by putting your hand on it to improve performance
Your character will improve with this machine
Absolutely fraudulent
If you sleep on the pillow, you will become a genius
Products that blatantly advertised outrageous features were published in famous magazines
I had the x-ray glasses
In retrospect it was quite a lawless zone
But even more excessive is
Privacy of celebrities
We heard from a journalist
It was common to simply reveal the address of a celebrity
In a lot of magazines
They were subtly included in there
And written next to the person's name
Yes, next to the name of Japanese celebrities at the time
The artist's real name and home address were clearly stated
In this all-star address book, published as a supplement to the magazine
A total of 1,857 celebrities' residences were revealed
What's more
The addresses were also thoughtfully organized into a map of the "streets where the stars live"
Also
They'd go through actresses' bins
The magazines would report on it
That's a crime
At that time, there were many reporters who went through the trash cans of celebrities to collect information
One magazine had a "Trash Hunt Series"
Which revealed a big starlet's cigarette butts
Toothbrushes and other household waste
In addition
From scripts for TV shows to things that can't be shown on TV
All kinds of garbage were posted like a house raid
Clearly, there was no privacy for celebrities at that time
What's more
Now I think about it, it's unbelievable
The tax bureau revealed how much certain people paid
Published in a serious manner
With the tax money
Annual income can be generally guessed
A ranking of the rich issued from 1950 onwards
Featured annual publication of high tax payers in the arts and energy sectors
Thus, their annual income was known
Among the most popular people in all walks of life
In 1993, the 30-year-old Downtown made the list
After two years
The difference with Yoshiko Mita, who won four consecutive championships, was huge
At the young age of 32, they'd literally reached the top of the entertainment industry
Still smoking
This isn't good
Until the system was abandoned in 2004
Neither of them ever dropped out of the top 10
In summary
Showa era and Downtown were a mess
Why do we have to be involved?
I did see the rich ranking a lot when we were kids
I've seen it.
-It's true
They made it into a book
And someone even tried to sell it to me
Rich ranking?
After ringing the doorbell, he said that this year's rich ranking is out
Do you want to buy one?
"Matsumoto, you're in there!"
What a mess.
-I don't get it
Compiling other people's income into a book is already too much
Not to mention that, you come directly to my house
Why do I have to pay for it?
Cigarette smoking while filming was very normal
What shows would you do it on?
How to say, they were in the late-night slot
-Late night
But I think smoking on prime time was also common?
Like throwing cigarette butts at other people
Indeed
Thrown
-Yes it happened
He was a professional at smoking and throwing it at others
Competitive?
-Yes
Cigarette butt flicking
And walking like this
Like a monster in Space Invaders
Shoulders like that
-Little by little rubbing forward
The Nagoya method
※The Nagoya method of play is a basic technique that allows players to use the loopholes in the game Space Invaders to get high points from their turrets by attacking without damage.
Let's welcome the next presenter please
Who?
Nanamagari!
We are Nanamagari
I thought your were the car rental clerk at the airport
No, we're Nanamagari
Okinawa, right?
-Okinawa or something like that
The one standing there with a board
At Naha Airport
I get it
We are here regarding that Nanamagari project
The legendary one.
-Do you remember?
The guessing one
We'd never been on TV before
It even won the Galaxy Award.
-Yeah!
It was an honor to receive the Galaxy Award
This time we bring a follow-up project
A new escape
The content is as follows
If you are locked up, if you can get the "lucky item of the day", you will be able to escape with luck
Aah!
-An escape room
A group of comedians will be locked up in a building
Somewhere they cant get out of
These two people will receive the "lucky item of the day" announced in the fortune telling segment of the TV program every day
I see
And we will see if they can successfully escape with these items
Will items useful for escape be given to them?
They are lucky items
So even if they are locked up, they'll surely be able to escape, right?
Sorry to interrupt, but Hagi hasn't said a word
Sorry
If you are locked up, if you can get the "lucky item of the day", you will be able to escape with luck
It's Yoshimoto again!
This time, the challengers are...
It depends on who comes out of the building first
24 years in the business but with an empty schedule
Too harsh
It's not too late
It's a lie, right?
Eh?
Scary scary scary
Please come with us to another place
Eh?
Now? No way
The two immediately understood the situation
The only program that would do this is this one
Please put your hands out
Okay, thank you
Still seriously disinfected
How to say...
In view of the current situation, no infection prevention measures should be left behind
It's a bit too much, isn't it?
Eh? This way?
Super scary
Please get on
Please note the steps
So kind
After obtaining their consent they are gently guided to the car
Has to be done this way
Just the two of us?
I appreciate the opportunity but it's scary
You know, after being on the show last year
We haven't been on any other show
Well, it's certainly good that someone wants to use us
It's just being locked for this show...
As they said, a year ago
The duo were also locked up for work
Happy New Year! Congratulations on the New Year!
These 43 and 48-year-old professional confinement entertainers
Travel for 5 hours
It's quite far
It's been a long time, where are you taking me to?
Why is it always 5 hours?
They eventually reach a certain building in a certain place
Ah, ah, it's indoors
So warm
Warm at least
All clothes and personal belongings will be confiscated at this time
And they change into plain clothes
Still haven't figured out whats happening
Then
Can this be taken off? Eye patch
Won't answer us?
Yes
Take it off
Okay, take it off.
-Blinding!
Oh, oh, oh.
-What is this place?
Quite spacious
What is this place?
-What's the room for?
What?
Can't start without reading this first, right?
From now on, you will use the "Today's lucky item" horoscope published in the morning horoscope broadcast by each TV station to escape from this secret room and return to Yoshimoto headquarters
Have to go back there?
Yoshimoto headquarters? By ourselves?
More than just escaping from the room!
Eh? How far have we travelled?
The earliest broadcast of horoscopes is 4:25 a.m. on TBS HAYADOKI,
Good luck!
Too early
Horoscope program, right?
So cruel? This program
It's cruel
So, this time, the two were challenged to escape from the secret life via the use of lucky items
In the horoscope segment of various programs
The lucky items stated in each will be provided
They will try to use these items to escape from this secret room
Its closed...
You see, this is a lock or something here, a padlock
Ah there is
Here's also locked
Two locks.
-This is the second lock
Yes, this door has two locks
So, the location of the key is...
Ah, I found it
Wow, what is this thing?
There's a key
The key? The one hanging
It's so high!
If the lucky item isn't high pruning shears we're done for
A ladder or something will definitely not be in the lucky item list
A ceiling height of 4.5 meters
Too high!
A serious escape room
Also, another key is hidden elsewhere
I feel like I can hear something
Is there something in there?
Eh? Eh? Eh?
What's down there?
Scary. Scary.
-Is there a living thing?
What's this?
This is a rat, right?
A rat?
So big, so big, so big, so scared, so scared, so scared
What?
Look. Side. Side. Side of the neck
There's a key!
The key is on it!
The key to the other lock
The key to the padlock
Ah so it is so it is
What a joke
The key to this lock is hanging around the neck of the mouse, right?
I can't believe its on a rat
The mouse inside has the second key hanging around his neck
Hmm? Where did it go?
Too tough to catch, super fast
So far inside
Did it go in?
Come here
It ran to the farthest point
Not coming out?
We can't wait for it to come out
Rats can go anywhere they want
If it goes in a crack somewhere its over
It'll go outside?
We'll never get out for the rest of our lives.
-Yeah
Can the two men get the two keys and escape from the room?
Also
How do we get back?
We don't even know where we are
There was no sound outside
This is interesting. More interesting than I thought
But it's warmer than last time.
-It's warm
Isn't this a daily conversation in the sauna?
There is another reason for setting to be purposely warm
Because
Where is this!?
They are in a small, isolated house in a snowy field somewhere in Nagano Prefecture
Wont they be uncomfortable when they get out?
Please return to Yoshimoto Headquarters
With the luck of the lucky items, can they return to distant Tokyo from this snowy land?
So hot
Looks hot
At this point, late at night, 1:30 am
Nothing to do
To prepare for tomorrow morning's divination session, they go to sleep
Lying down I can still see the key
I'm aiming for that key
I want to smoke.
-I want to have a puff
Said he wanted to smoke
Understandable
Lucky item escape room life - Day 1
Quit smoking!
Wow the snow is flying!
Here we go
Turn on the TV
Watch TV
Okay, 4:20
Get it in one
This early in the morning there are horoscope programs...
First of all, they watched "HAYADOKI!", the first TBS show with a horoscope segment
And this time, the content of the broadcast was sent to the room
The two people's zodiac signs are Aquarius and Virgo, respectively, what are the results?
Originally it was going to be you two
So close!
There was a slight overlap with their schedules
Great, thank god for the theatre
Ah, here we go.
-Ok
Who looks forward to this so much?
Opening animation
Horoscopes, right?
Not so quick
What is this?
How long will it take for the horoscope part to begin
In the second part, right?
Later on, right?
-Yeah
True
They waited 15 minutes for the horoscope session
Here it comes
So cute
Horoscope horoscope!
The best fortune today is
Ah, this?
It starts at 4:40
Let's record it
Gemini
Today you can play to your strengths
Language skills and communication skills become stronger, your evaluation will also improve
Wait, this one
The lucky item is a glow stick
Lucky color is yellow-green
So that's it. Lucky items are coming
Ah, look at your own look at your own
-Aquarius
Sweater
The sweater is good to get
Useful for the snow
These two people on the TV are also Virgo
History books, do not need this
History books
-History books?
The following lucky item "priority seat" is also something
That's the end of it?
What does "priority seat" mean?
Eh, wait, I want to see the other star signs
Check it out!
There is also a "flower painting"
This is too much
What can we do with this sort of thing?
This part is unexpectedly fast
-It's so short!
Couldn't see what the others were
Next is the weather forecast
Lazy egg horoscope? My first time
Glow Stick
Badges
Sweater
History book
Fashion Magazine
Belt
Video App
Coaster
Forks
History Books
Priority Seats
Flower Painting
The lucky items stated on "HAYADOKI!" on this day are as follows
Not great
Yes, the useful ones seem to be...
Although there are no items useful for obtaining the two keys
The two tentatively obtained a sweater and history book first
History book is useless
History books are really not needed, right?
The most useless
They then looked to other station broadcasts
So
See if it's on Asahi Channel?
Oh, here we go, here we go
Oh, "Gogo Horoscope"
-"Gogo Horoscope"
Ship models
Novel
Reference Books
Home Theater
Poetry Collection
One Stroke Paper
Bulbous Root
Musical Greeting Card
Glow Stick
Sound Mix
Gogo Star Horoscope on Asahi TV's "good! morning"
Oh here comes Aquarius
Folded leaflets
What are "folded leaflets"?
10th is the same as just now
Rose Fragrance
What? What the hell is "rose fragrance"?
It's not even an item anymore
What? The smell?
Smells aren't needed
Not at all!
After that
Will these things work?
Oh, it's airing quickly, this is dangerous
Oh wow, wait, that was close, that was close
Nervous this time
French Bread
Stacked Rings
Tomb
Honey Beverages
Winter Delicacies
Bargains
Soy Milk Latte
Alleyway Shop
Chocolate Board
T-junction
Fuji Channel's "Alarm TV" started almost simultaneously with Asahi Channel
In today's ranking
Aquarius is fifth place
-Aquarius fifth place, its different
Latest Hot App
Latest Hot App, what?
Ah! I came in last!
Virgo is new products page
New Products Page
What does that mean?
To increase your luck: a sip of water
What about "a sip of water"? We drink it every day!
So far there are no items that can be used at all
Can they do it?
Okay, next is Nihon Television
The items are awful
After that, they looked around for other stations to watch
But no other lucky items were found
Oh wow, no horoscope?
Exactly. The only programs with lucky items are these three
It's too hard. Even after watching there's nothing they can do
Not only that, these divination sessions are all concentrated in the morning before 5:00
4 o'clock is the most important time in our lives now
What to do the rest of the time?
The bored two decided to have lunch
Too difficult
At least they've got food
That's good
Sleeping
Its probably better than yours
Temporary Forced Sleep
After 1:00 p.m
We didn't get food
Bathroom
Toilet
What's arrived?
They have a bathroom too
Ah so, the delivery is coming
Can I have some toilet paper?
Say something
Ah, they won't give it?
Why?
-Completely ignored
Today's lucky item delivery
It's finally here. It's finally here
History Books
Sweater
Good subdued color
Rose Fragrance
Folded leaflets
What? What about that?
What about the APP and the web thing?
What about the stuff from Fuji Channel and the stuff from Asashi TV?
Ones that aren't physical objects wont be delivered?
Non-physical items Won't be provided
Ah, it smells good!
The scent of roses
Life has become leisurely with this
But it's not necessary
This is completely useless for escaping
However, such useless items this time can
Be sold
I see
Unwanted items can be sold at market price
Paper towels
Cups
Hand towel
Underwear
Sweatshirt (set)
Potato Chips
Tea
Cigarette (one)
Lucky Chance Small
Wipes
Toothbrush set
Bath Towel
Socks
Chocolate
Peanut Rice Fruit (sachet)
Coke
Cigarettes (one box)
Lucky Chance Medium
Toilet paper
Bath Set
Blanket
Slippers
Dried Squid
Cheese
Beer (350ml)
Lighter
Lucky Chance Large
They can buy the items from the following material table
It can also be used for transportation to Tokyo for the upcoming days
Cigarette (one)
Cigarettes (one box)
Cigarettes are expensive
What? Cigarettes are more expensive than in our time
※At that time, a cigarette was 50 yen, and a box of cigarettes was 800 yen
Really expensive
It's too expensive, really
300 yen per stick
Toothbrush set
-Wow, that's expensive!
Its like Kaiji!
If we don't buy this underwear, is there no change of clothes?
If the underwear isn't used
Toothbrush set also
At least one.
-I want it
One for two people is good
Lucky Chance is also available here
It's a bit expensive, isn't it?
And so begins the life of the lucky item escape room
Will the two of them be able to use the power of luck?
What about escaping safely from a lonely little house in the middle of a vast snowfield?
Ah~
What a cruel project!
Indeed
Isn't it just snow everywhere?
Yes
Didn't they realize when going in?
The snow was removed when the two were brought in
The snow was shoveled out of the way for them to walk through
Then the snow was piled back in again
It was smooth when they went in
Why put so much effort into this part?
Incidentally, in the old days, cigarettes were 50 yen each
The price has really gone up
The cigarette exchange rate has gone up
It's desperate. This cigarette smoking
You haven't quit smoking yet?
From that time onwards, I liked smoking more
Its really the best taste in the world
Really the best! Cigarettes!
The feeling of being able to smoke freely
Every day, I thank God for letting me smoke freely
Getting back to the point, we are now looking forward to the sequel
It can't be helped
Surprisingly...
That's it for this week
Eh?
There's more?
Next week, we will present the final chapter to you in its entirety
Please look forward to
Next week is the finale
Eh? What's the deal?
What the hell do we have to do to get it right!
Will the two of them be able to use the power of luck
From a lonely little house in the middle of a vast snowfield
What about escaping to the distant Tokyo?
Going this far to be on TV
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03