Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
It's Kawashima!
Thank you
Solo artist
I'm not a solo artist, my partner is still alive
He's just a little bit out of the TV business
Today is the 3rd edition of a super popular project
Does this program have a super popular project?
I think it has given birth to many masterpieces
Do you have a project in mind?
Akatsu system
Akatsu appears every now and then
Is today something that hasn't been seen for a while?
Yes, it hasn't been done for two years
Let's take a look
What i'm talking about it this
3rd Early Bento Sensei
Two years have passed
-Two years already?
Was it that long ago?
Do you all remember the first one?
Slightly
The project was how many bento can be eating during class without the teacher noticing
It was quite well received
Because of the good response, a 2nd edition came out almost immediately
Do you remember, Matsumoto?
Remember, I remember
Too many elements were added into it
It was a big jump from the school setting
Eating crabs in psychic attractions, it lost the original intention
-It was inexplicable
Too fast perhaps?
Too much going on
Just like mom's dinner
Give her a little bit of praise and then the next day's meal is awful
So, because of all of this, we have returned to the morning classroom setting
Also,
Will an athlete's plan to prank someone be more interesting because of their lame acting skills?
If you are a person who can supposedly sense when someone is behind you, can you evade an attack?
This time, we used a fake project to find three teachers
Students compete to see how much food they can eat in class without being caught
The resurrection of Early Bento Sensei
The challengers are
Unique
These candidates are
All fatties
Did you ever eat lunch early when you were a student?
Yes, I did, I ate it during class time.
And then again, the class is still...
I did sneak a little bit of food in class.
I had one of old-fashioned lunchboxes for Dad.
-Those huge ones?
They'd see that, right?
Not suitable for sneaky eating
It can keep miso soup warm.
The first hour involves eating cream puffs
Should be okay
They get 1 point for eating 1 in a 10-minute course
But if discovered the points go back to 0
The results of the seat lottery are shown above
Sitting in front is dangerous
The teacher for the first class was
It also depends on the teacher
Madame Devi
She'll be angry
Stand up
The topic of the class that Madame will be teaching is about the society
Bow
Sit down
The tension is amazing!
The student over there, why are you grinning?
Scary
Not just you but but the one behind you also
I'm sorry
You have to be more serious
As the teacher sends a warning almost instantly
The air in the classroom suddenly becomes heavy
Good morning
Please introduce yourselves
I am Hollywood Zakoshi
A very serious introduction
I'm Maple Leaf Super Alloy's Ando Natsu
Maple leaf super alloy?
Yes, that's the name of our group
Piqued her interest
Which part?
What is the origin of the name
Not interested in Zakoshi
For the name, I like sweet maple sugar sauce...
He's eating
A sprint!
Covered by Ando's huge body
Nishimura gets one point
Nishimura is super lucky!
Nishimura has a good spot
Superb wall!
I'm Tom Brown's Razor Ramon, please tell me more.
Hello, my name is Hikomoru
I'm Viking's Nishimura
Your name is like the name of that program
People often say this
I'm Trendy Angel's Takashi
I'm not sure I understand, honyuu Angel?
It's Trendy Angel
Trendy Angel
Not at all trendy
I'm the Angel
-Oh I see
Then let me introduce myself
Turning around is an opportunity
My name is
Now!
Quick!
The cheeks are protruding too much, right?
Go for another!
While the teacher is writing on the board
The students stuff the puffs into their mouths one after another
Ate a lot!
This will end soon surely
Ratna means gemstone
Go again?
This time
What's going on?
Choking on your food?
Oh no, Nishimura is in trouble!
Yes, in fact, one of the ten small puffs is filled with mustard
Is this necessary?
The students who don't know anything
Must deal with the surprise accordingly
What are you up to over there?
Gemstones yes
My name is the jewel of...
Luckily they've got water
Despite Nishimura's strange behavior
He's SAFE
After this, Nishimura's abnormal state goes unnoticed
And the other students continue to sneakily eat their food
So
Gradually, the mustard begins to rear it's ugly head
It is called Pearl of Orient...
What do you have in your mouth?
Eh...
Sorry... that's...
I'm just bleeding a bit
So I stuffed some tissue paper in my mouth
You put tissues in your mouth?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry if I hurt you a little bit.
-In the mouth, right?
Sorry
SAFE, right?
Despite using a messy excuse
He isn't exposed and the class continues
They're getting by
However,
A sudden streak of mustard attacks the class
What's wrong with you?
I'm moved to tears, I can't stop it
Because it's a good story
Another far-fetched reason, but nonetheless SAFE
Next
This is the end of 1st lesson
It's finally over
The results so far are revealed
Good work everyone
Everyone is exhausted, right?
No one said there'd be mustard
What the hell is going on?
-It's too much!
It halted the rhythm of eating completely
Did everyone eat everything?
No, I have some left
I ate them all
So the results of the 1st lesson are shown above
The next morning meal challenge in lesson 2 is
Please look over here
What, what?
A rice bucket
-Rice bucket?
※Still widely used for measuring sake and rice. 1 bucket is equal to 150 grams of raw rice, which expands 2.2 times when cooked.
This time, the whole team will work together to finish a meal
If they finish eating in the 10-minute course, they will all get points
This rice bucket will be placed in the cabinet behind everyone
This will be exposed ah
-Definitely!
The seats after a lottery are shown
The teacher of the 2nd class is
Akira Yamane, former president of the Japan Boxing Federation
That's bad
I'm not good at writing, so please bear with me.
Despite surely having been seen
It is ignored
Contrary to his scary appearance, he is a teacher with many flaws
This is also time consuming
Takashi is responsible for serving the rice and then passing it in relay to the other participants
Then, they eat the chosen ingredients
I am Yamane
15 years-old?
Is that it?
-This is it
So handsome!
-Awesome photos!
Don't praise him
Be sure to look at all of them
Please write the release date and name of your book
Why are you telling him what to do
Thank you
What the hell is going on?
Close the cabinet!
After that, the teacher's vulnerability is taken advantage of as everyone eats
This will surely be exposed
The cabinet never closes
2 minutes left on the clock
I told you to close the cabinet!
There's now just a little bit of rice left in the bucket
State 5 points that you like most about your wife
Or if you were to say 3 points, what would they be?
Please write it on the blackboard
I'll say it with my mouth
Write it on the board so that we can take notes
-We want to write down
Don't use words
Ando's brilliant trick forces the teacher's attention toward the blackboard
And with that, the final dash
The sound of clacking chopsticks
I told you to close it!
There's only a little left
Can't close it
Not a bit of garbage is left, she cleans several times a day
His wife's strengths are really narrow
Not much time left
So...
But it feels like it will work
Lawlessness
How do you feel after all your hard work?
"Rikido" is written on the blackboard
It was possible
What was this class about?
How about the barrel? Is it all gone?
Impressive, its all gone!
So everyone scores an extra 10 points each
After a strange class
It's finally time for the final battle
Let's have a scarier teacher
Lesson 3 is buffet mode
Here there are 20 types of dishes to choose from
However much they eat will determine their points
What the hell is this?
You can make pancakes.
-With that?
You want us to cook?
Yes, that's right
In class?
This time, there is an expanded range of cuisine
And the score is determined by the difficulty level of cooking
Who is the teacher?
The lowest scoring students so far choose the most difficult dishes
And fight to get to the top scores
Depends on how dumb the teacher is
The teacher of the 3rd class is also from the world of boxing
When he's angry he's surprisingly scary
I'm Yoko Gushiken
Its serious
Today
First, let me briefly introduce myself
I used to be a boxer
I am using my real name, not a stage name
Where is it hidden?
A name with high ambition
Today's topic
It's like a normal meal
The proverbial broken teacher
And the students who are bolder in front of him
Too bold, right?
Then
Where do you go to work out?
Starting to cook
Sendagaya's...
Takashi is hard at work on his pancake
No noise?
How can I put it? It's hard just to make ends meet...
And so
Ready to eat
What's that?
Watermelon! Watermelon!
Gushiken!
The smell must be strong
Teacher, pay attention!
The WBA is now based in Panama
At this time, the three people in the back row all decide to make the loudest dish with the highest score
This will make a sound
But
If you win, you get a shot at the title
An unimaginable volume of spicy fried chicken with cheese heats up
Why are you so oblivious?
There's a sound!
But even with this, everone is surprisingly SAFE
So
The juice is coming out
The back of the classroom is as noisy and roaring as an industrial plant
But the teacher ignores this and continues the lesson
However, suddenly...
Oh, you're not eating watermelon are you?
Eh?
A mysterious claim
Is it okay to bring watermelon?
And so, the watermelon is exposed
And so, the lesson ends
I can't believe such idiots really exist
With both sound and fragrance
CHUUUUU, the sound of it
The final score is shown in the chart
Hollywood Zakoshi takes the top spot
Impressive
What does everyone think of this 3rd edition
I guess it's best to go back to square one
The class setting is best
But the teachers should make it more tense
Yes, Gushiken didn't even notice ice being ground
Maybe Gushiken can only hear the sound of the gong for the start of a match
Yes, the sound would definitely catch his attention
And the little puff is unnecessary
The ones filled with mustard?
It's like a punishment
But Hamada was smiling like a baby when they ate it
That man loves to see people in pain
I also enjoyed it to be honest
It really was interesting
Let's welcome the next presenter
Hello everyone
It's Sanshiro Komiya!
This time I'm bringing you the 2nd edition of a theory from 4 years ago
4 years ago?
-The 2nd one?
Do you know what it is?
-There have been many theories before
Even if I know, I won't say it
Just say it, please say it
So, what is it?
-I don't have a clue!
What type is it?
It's a prank series
A series of pranks?
-There were many.
For example, Matsuno once appeared in it
Ah!
-Remember?
Is it some kind of project about a lame actor?
Yes yes
-Athlete
Athletes
-Yes, yes, yes
So the theory I have brought this time is...
Will an athlete's plan to prank someone be more interesting because of their lame acting skills?
This fact was very interesting indeed
The first edition was a long time ago, you still remember it?
With Yu Sawabe?
-Yes, yes, yes.
Last time Sawabe laughed because of the lame performance of Akemi Matsuno
Isn't your tie pin too close to the top
What are you saying?
Your tie pin is too close to the top
Ah, sorry
So strict!
This has nothing to do with the program
I planned thoroughly in advance, please don't disrupt my rhythm
Is it going the way you envisioned?
Not at all
Will an athlete's plan to prank someone be more interesting because of their lame acting skills?
The first participant is Karina Maruyama, formerly of the Japanese women's national soccer team
She may not be very good at acting
It's the first time I've been able to prank someone
Although I am often pranked by others
But it's the first time I've done someone else
The target for this time is...
Do you know Hashimoto?
Yes, I know. I've heard a lot about him
Have you ever worked with him?
Experience of working with him...
About 5 times or so
5 times, may be a little less than 10 times, maybe
This time, Maruyama's plan is "she actually has psychic powers"
For the setup, she will perform a séance
But because the purpose of this project is actually to see her acting skills
One hour before
Hashimoto is made aware of the plan
She'll be talking about your deceased grandfather".
-OK, I see
Hashimoto doesn't look ok with it
So, the plan is put into motion
Hello
What exactly will Maruyama show us?
I'm really nervous today
-I'm nervous too
Psychic ability prank plan (1) Desperately emphasize  psychic ability
Hashimoto, do you feel something strange in this room?
Starting so soon
Strange?
Well, it's just the two of us
I have always felt that something is very wrong
Really?
I'm just gonna say it
You mustn't tell anyone else
-What is it?
I have better psychic ability than humans
Humans?
Better than humans, really?
-Yes, a little bit
What you mean by better than humans?
That is, strongest among humans
Among humans?
-Yes
Ugh? I'm really not good at this kind of topic, its pretty scary!
Really?
-What do you feel? Was it in this room?
Psychic ability prank plan (2) Able to talk to spirit in the room
I can really feel it
It's clear now because it's already behind you, Hashimoto
-Eh?
Imagine the situation over here. You do it yourself
Try it yourself first
Yourself?
Ah, not that you can see it yourself, but I can see it
What the hell are you talking about?
-She's not really saying it right
What, what?  You can see something can't you?
Yes, it's your late grandfather, Hashimoto
Eh, can you see him now?
I can really see him
She's laughing out loud
Now listen to what he is saying
You seem to be worried about whether to buy a sofa lately, right?
How did you get this information?
That's because I can actually see it.
-I didn't tell anyone
Yes, I heard about it from your grandfather, and he's here.
Of course, the info about couch has not come from the grandfather
Recently i'm debating whether to buy a sofa
I want a leather one
I see
So, actually, the information is from Hashimoto
And Maruyama was informed in advance
Did my grandfather tell you about my worries about buying a sofa?
Yes, he also said something about leather
Genuine leather? Yes, I do want to change to leather
Yes, yes, he knows you're thinking about leather
So he's here. He's always been here
So far, Maruyama has done a surprisingly good job
Next is the final step
Psychic ability prank plan (3)  Possession via séance
Today, your grandfather is here right now, isn't he?
Hashimoto, do you want to talk to Grandpa?
Well, if it's possible, of course
Right...no I thought you would say the same thing
So much work
No. If I can, I have to
She laughed out loud
Totally laughing
Give it a go
How do we do it?
I'll do it. I'll do it. I'm sorry
She's laughing instead
I'll do it. Right now
Okay, are you ready?
Sorry, I mean the spirit will come to me
I throw the soul onto me
Throw?
You can throw souls?
What kind of talk is that?
This is really unbearable
-Way too much
Anyone else would have to laugh out loud
Is she throwing it?
What is she going to do next?
It's down
Naohiro, how are you doing?
My name is just "Nao", that character
Oh, excuse me
You're sorry? What the hell are you saying sorry for, that's bad
Nao
Yes, is that Grandpa?
Yes, it's grandpa
Do you have something you want to tell me?
Nothing to say to me?
Do...do you?
Which of my grandfathers are you?
Grandfather..
-They've both passed away
I see
It's... actually half and half
-What half and half?
Unbeknownst to him, it was a twin soul
No, no, I can't take anymore
This should have ended long ago
Maruyama, what the hell is all this
Hashimoto is also uncomfortable, right?
Are you okay?
You're back to Maruyama now, aren't you?
It seems to be quite physically demanding.
-Yes, it's very strenuous...
When your grandfather was coming through me... in the séance
When he abandoned me, I was unconcious
-Abandoned you?
I left my body
-Oh so its like that
Next, after Grandpa, comes...
Do you have anyone you want to communicate with, Hashimoto?
The next séance begins
Is a professional wrestler ok?
Professional wrestler?
I really like professional wrestlers
I see
I like Giant Baba
※Formerly known as Masahira Macha, a Japanese professional wrestler, died in 1999.
Can you talk to him? After all, he's a legend
No problem, let's begin
Who is it again?
Giant Baba
She asked who it was, she doesn't know him
Ok, got it
It's a bit too much for you
That's too fast.
-Way too fast
Ah…
I think she said "ah"
I'm Baba
How dare you say "I am Baba"
I am Baba
I am Hashimoto
Ah, I know you.
-You know me?
Yes, I know you.
-I'm very honored
In addition
Can a historical figure like Ieyasu Tokugawa be connected with?
Yes, yes.
-Thank you
Too fast!
I am Tokugawa
Which Tokugawa?
I am Naoki Tokugawa
Naoki? Aren't you Ieyasu?
I am a friend of Ieyasu
Friend...
So you're not Ieyasu Tokugawa, but Naoki Tokugawa
I am Ieyasu's cousin
Just said they were friends
Nao...Naoki
Where did Naoki come from?
This is awful
Poor Hashimoto
It's hard, isn't it?
You're a moonwalker!
Awesome
You'd better not tell anyone
Please don't tell anyone
Otherwise people will say "bring this person out, bring that person out."
That's true
So, grandpa, I think so too...think...no, think...
Is Grandpa's spirit still there?
There are still remnants
Now the truth is revealed
The prank is disclosed
That was a prank.
-Give me a break
Hashimoto is still
cooperating
That was all a prank
-Wait, that was really scary
Success!
I could not have imagined this was a prank
How do you feel? Your first time pranking someone
Great!
Pranking someone is so cool
I'm really sorry that I lied to you. I apologize
The prank was a great success!
In the same way, the next athlete to be set up is
So that's it?
Just move on straight away
Hello everyone
Mr. SASUKE Yamada Katsumi
The program team really likes Yamada
Mr. Yamada, what happened to your face?
I suffered an injury
What happened
While practicing, when you're older its easier to fall over
I fell down and hit my face
Are you ok now?
It doesn't matter, it's just the face
Why?
This time Yamada is going to prank someone regarding memory loss
The target is the current top SASUKE participants who also have a personal relationship with Yamada
So, the prank begins
With injuries like this...
Are you OK?
Hello
-Hello
Are you OK?
He's really hurt. Looks like the real thing
Are you all right?
-Good morning
Are you OK?
How are you feeling?
What's going on?
Ow ow ow ow
Are you not feeling well?
Well, it's pretty tough
I'm sorry, what's your name again?
-Eh?
I am Hioki
-I am Kawaguchi
Hioki? Kawaguchi?
What's my name again?
He's going through a tough time
Amnesia plan (1) Can't remember his name
Aren't you Yamada Katsumi?
Yamada?
That's right, Yamada
-Ha...
Ah, I got hit by a bike on the way here
Yes
Perhaps because I hit my back and head hard when I fell
No way!
Someone brought me here and I don't remember anything
Putting aside the quality of Yamada's acting
The script regarding the accident is moving forward in a very serious way
What is my relationship with you guys?
Didn't we meet through SASUKE?
SASUKE？
Ow ow ow ow
Headache
Amnesia plan (2)  Hearing "SASUKE" gives him a headache
It hurts
What did you just say?
I just said SASUKE
Ow ow
Ow ow ow ow
What the hell do you mean by that? What the hell is SASUKE?
Did you say SASUKE?
SASUKE？
Ow ow ow ow
What does that mean exactly?
What does SASUKE mean?
-The meaning!
That's a tough question
I get a headache when I hear it
I don't think we can say SASUKE
Can't say SASUKE?
SASU...I told you to stop talking about it
What exactly is SASUKE?
SASUKE involves climbing walls, jumping, catching ropes
Are you talking about some kind of athletic competition?
Adults do this sort of thing?
You're saying that?
You have done it the most
No, no, I don't remember
This competition thing doesn't sound even the least bit interesting
But you are Mr. SASUKE
No, no, no, no
Little by little, Yamada forgets the "headache when hearing SASUKE"
Next
Amnesia plan (3)  Use SASUKE actions to awaken his memories
Is there anything that can make me recollect it?
What is he doing?
It's dangerous. It's dangerous.
-Very dangerous
What? What is he doing?
What? What's he going to do? Scary
What?
Something like SASUKE?
Have I done similar exercises like this?
That is SASUKE's "Pipe Slider", it is the last part of the third stage
Pipe Slider...
Holding a pipe with both forehand and backhand
This is the method for the pipe slider that Yamada came up with when he was young
Yamada, you have reached this level many times
What the hell is he doing?
Dangerous
What is all this
Is this the way to do it?
Like moving forward, swinging forward
Ow ow ow ow ow ow ow
Are you OK?
Hand slipped
An unexpected reenactment of a SASUKE performance
Next is the final step
Amnesia plan (4)  Repeatedly shouting SASUKE to awaken his memories
Repeat what you just said
I seem to be remembering something
SASUKE？
Yes, SASUKE
Maybe I can think of something. Think of something
SASUKE SASUKE
-Yes, yes, that's it
Mr. SASUKE Mr. SASUKE
-Yes yes
SASUKE SASUKE
Only like SASUKE, most like SASUKE
SASUKE Black Tiger
Mr. SASUKE Mr. SASUKE
SASUKE SASUKE
Next the prank is revealed
He snickered, feeling successful
What is this?
What cha la la la, what the hell is going on?
Great success~
What is all this?
My first prank was greatly successful
Give me a break!
Next is the last person to be set up
Former professional wrestler Animal Hamaguchi
He definitely can't do it
Can't do it can't do it
In fact, this is the second time that Beast Hamaguchi has appeared in this project
He was there last time too
Yes
I am a person who is actually very spiritual
Really?
Last time he acted as the pranker for the paranormal program
And gave a perfect demonstration of lame acting skills
This time you're going trying to trick Kyoko, your daughter
He can't, can he?
Leave it all to the old man, no problem
The trap to be set for Kyoko this time is
We invited Kyoko to our hotel on the grounds of a magazine interview
You will be the journalist of the magazine
We want you to disguise yourself
Kyoko must not see through your disguise
This time, Animal Hamaguchi disguises himself as a magazine reporter
And so
Feels good
If I put on a beard and glasses, I'll be...
-Totally unrecognizable
That's awful
It's bad. It's really bad
Although I do want to see him make a fool of himself
What is your favorite type of man?
Can you make your voice a little higher?
Kyoko, what is your favorite type of man?
At this level, Kyoko will not be able to hear who you are
That's not good, is it?
-No, it's not
Not bad
You can hit such a high tone
The staff are full of malice
Of course
Just like before, Kyoko is told all the details of the plan beforehand
The prank begins
Isn't it still him?
-That's Hamaguchi!
Please come in
Did he really think Kyoko wouldn't recognize him?
Excuse me
She is already laughing out loud
What a mess
Really, both sides are like this
Definitely not. No, no, no
I said no!
Hello
I am Ohara from the editorial team
Also, this is Ohtani from our company
It's bad, Ohtani!
The incredible disguise
Kyoko couldn't help but laugh out loud
On the other hand, Animal Hamaguchi clearly saw Kyoko laughing out loud
But is somehow completely unmoved
He must have thought he hasn't been exposed.
-He must have thought so.
By the way, the final task for Animal Hamaguchi this time is
Get Kyoko's personal information
And so
Disguise prank plan (1) The female reporter leaves the two alone
So hard at the beginning
Excuse me, I have an emergency call to take
Excuse me, can I leave for a moment?
Yeah, it's okay
I'll leave you with Ohtani
Ohtani, please.
Ohtani, is it okay?
So~
Ohtani will ask a few questions
What are we watching?
Your tie clip...
Yes, I'm sorry, i'll be careful not to let it slide up again
This is a very interesting section
I'm impressed!
It's better down a bit
-Enough! Stop focusing on it
So~
Ohtani will ask a few questions
No way.
-This is too strange
Kyoko, please take care of yourself
What is this?
So how do you spend your days off, Kyoko?
Well
Well that, drink a little wine, play a little bit, eat a meal or something
Although Animal Hamaguchi's skills are quite clear
Kyoko's acting is also quite lame
Thus, a horrible parent-child lame rivalry battle ensues
What the hell is all this?
So, what is your favorite type of man?
Please
When it comes to the type of men I like...
I can't accept one like my father
Hearing this, Hamaguchi is clearly depressed
Next, there is one more thing I want to ask
Are you currently seeing a man?
What follows is a counter prank
In response to Hamaguchi's questions
Kyoko suddenly announces that she is getting married
I see
Hearing this news, can Animal still hide his inner turmoil and continue to finish his job as a journalist?
About the man i'm dating
Now there is one
I'm actually dating someone now
And I want to use this interview to make it public
Completely frozen!
Today, I told the guy I'm dating to come here too
I think he's probably on his way
No watch
Kyoko's lines are fragmented and don't make any sense at all
To sum up, "Her boyfriend will appear shortly"
I've called him over
Excuse me.
-Just in time
Ah, really?
What the hell?
It's such a mess. Is it okay?
This is the person I started dating this year on the premise of marriage
Professional wrestler Hollywood Stalker Ichikawa
Although this person dresses very sloppily
He is indeed a genuine professional wrestler
And upholds his exaggerated performance to appear as the boyfriend
Can Animal Hamaguchi continue to play journalist?
Ah, why are you not the same as usual? Are you nervous?
Well, a little bit
At such times
Only by kissing me, will you cure this kind of tension
Seriously, kissing must be - saved - for - the future
Ah, left until later
What is all this?
Animal Hamaguchi did not expect to see such explicit affectionate behavior
After temporarily tolerating for a period of time, Hamaguchi finally...
YOU BASTARD!
HEY, YOU BASTARD!
I'm talking to you, you bastard!
What did you just say, you son of a bitch, you little brat?
What's wrong?
What are you, you bastard?
Hey, why did you bring him here?
Hey, when did I ever teach you to do this?
We brought our marriage registration today
You bastard!
Look at this!
What's the "prank big success"?
This is a prank?
Initially, he failed to understand the situation
So, the staff took the time to explain the situation to him
And then...
Come on, let's have a successful ten in a row
Ready? Go!
Big success, big success, big success, big success, big success, big success, big success, big success, big success, big success!
So tough
Big success!
In summary
Yamada wasn't needed, and Stalker Ichikawa was even less needed
What is all this?
The end was indeed a little, well, how can I put it?
A little too convoluted
What was that last situation? Was he really angry?
His eyes looked really angry
It's true that he really was angry.
-Really angry?
Yes, I know the feeling
The last time I pranked Animal Hamaguchi
He literally chased and beat me
Chased and beaten?
Yes, not only chased and beaten
He also threw potatoes and pans at me
His eyes then were the same as just now
So he is indeed angry
I'm impressed.
-Yes
To sum up, Animal Hamaguchi is a lousy actor
Kyoko too, and what's more, even Hollywood Stalker was lame
It feels like this theory has played itself out already
This has the feeling of a finale
Next is everybody's theories
The presenters is...
Kenji Tamura
Thank you everyone
Let me ask you, have you ever had such an experience?
When walking on the road
You suddenly feel something behind you
Have you ever had such an experience?
Being watched or something like that?
I guess so
I suppose I can't say I absolutely haven't
Occasionally something like that happens
Have you experienced it, Maggy?
I have, forcing me to suddenly turn around and look
Also, sometimes there's no one there
No one there?
No one
At home, for example.
-At home?
Have you never expereinced such a thing?
-I get it, I guess
When you open the door, you feel as if there is someone at home
Yes, yes, that feeling is super scary
So it seems everyone has experienced this to some extent
So, the theory that I bring you this time is
Please take a look
If you are a person who can supposedly sense when someone is behind you, can you evade an attack?
Oh, like this?
Yes yes
It's not often that people can feel an aura or someone's breath or something like that behind them
For example, if you feel a murderous aura
It would be pretty much impossible to encounter this in real life
And yet there is the impression that one could feel it
But after all, you can't feel it at all, right?
Wait a minute, I don't understand what you're talking about...
Shortly, we will verify if an attack from behind can really be sensed and dodged
If you are a person who can supposedly sense when someone is behind you, can you evade an attack?
This time there are 3 people who have signed up to participate
The first one is
The director of a comprehensive karate martial arts school with over 200 students
Kazuya Koike 35 years old
Students in this dojo are instructed on how to sense and avoid attacks from behind
If you just rely on the eyes to see it is easy to be fooled by fake actions
So do not rely on the eyes to feel the sense of air from behind and so on
We practice the habit of being able to decipher in different situations and so on
If it's something like detecting an attack
I feel I can do it, more or less
Can he really defend against an attack from behind?
We will verify it in this shopping street
Mixed in with the real members of the public are 10 assassins sent by the show
If they can defend against all attacks from behind, the challenge is successful
If they feel the breath behind them, they will cross their arms over their head for defense
But the number of defense must equal the number of enemy attacks and not exceed 10 times
In order to prevent spamming of defensive moves to muddle through
Can they all defend against the attacks of 10 people or not?
Start!
The attacks were communicated in advance
It is understood that someone will attack
Indeed, it is
Can you tell by the sound of footsteps?
Its normal to not realise
One's coming
Ah, like this should be obvious
Can hear the footsteps
Eh?
What is this?
No way!
This is completely different from the time of practice...
Couldn't even hear the footsteps?
It's completely different
Well, in the dojo, the rules are pre-determined
It doesn't feel the same at all
Hit him with a "bang!"
A nice sound
The next person is
A martial artist who explains "how to detect an attack with your heart" on YouTube
Shinsen Akira 30 years old
Seriously?
Obviously, he will attempt it without the mask...
The mask isn't needed
I heard that you can sense things behind you
-Yes
Is this true?
Well, if you know how to detect it, you can do it
Detect what?
Well, the human body emits energy and so on, aura and so on
Probably everybody has something like this
So it can be perceived
Start!
Seems interesting
He already knows, right?
Yes he knows
Oh, one's coming
What's is this?
What the hell?
Looked to the right
Can't do it at all
Sorry about that...
Sorry?
You were hit
Ah, sorry... was hit...
Why are you smiling?
I couldn't help it...
Maybe because the conditions were not clearly understood
Don't you understand the conditions?
Conditions?
Can I look back? Probably...
Can I look back?
Turning back to block? Something like that
It should be blocked like this
That has to be done in advance...
Go on the defensive, right?
What is happening now?
But you didn't do anything just now...
-Yeah
Didn't move at all
You didn't even look back
Indeed
Why is this?
Yeah, why?
Wanna see him get hit again
Because the feeling was not detected
Why?
And so, the final participant is...
Aikido 8-dan
Ando 62 years old
This person seems to be really good at it
In his 44 years of Aikido, the number of students he has instructed exceeds 200,000
To be honest, he should be in a different class from the two people just now
Don't say that
The others are also good
Is it true that you can detect presence from behind?
Yes, I can detect it
The qi is the "opponent's mindset", right?
You can feel it with your back
I want to believe
I've had training to sharpen my senses
I guess the first two people are actually different
Oh, using qi
No need to attack
No, no, no.
-What is this?
What are you doing?
When they're behind they're going "goo" and pushing their qi out
Pushing it out
Check it out
Did he really push it out?
Hamada, look!
Hey, don't laugh!
Can't touch him at all
No, no, no, no
Hamada, look, they're completely unable to touch him
I'll get 'em all!
Is this not a performance?
This is an opponent-oriented hold
No, he's a master
Well, in other words, "charm" something like that?
It's all about "charm"
More than just detecting presence
You can also "charm" to control your opponent
This is "Wife"
Eh?
His wife?
Correct
Using the power of qi, he has been able to charm a foreign women
Can he detect all 10 enemies?
Do you need glasses?
Start!
Why do you need glasses?
It's by qi, right?
Go for it!
Walking pretty fast
Very fast indeed
Go go go!
I hope he blocks them all perefectly
It's over.
In summary
It might be impossible
What the hell
I'm tired of it
Very unsatisfying
Why did he put on glasses at the end
Can he not see in front of him?
Perhaps to focus completely behind him he has to be able to see in front with ease
So he put his glasses on
Perfectly done
The second one seemed to be under a lot of pressure
Probably forced to do it
The director seemed pretty impatient too
That guy looks like he enjoys being bullied though
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03