Eternal Rivals
Their rivalry began with Moriman humiliating Yamasaki and stealing his underwear
And same thing happened again in the second match
Even by the third match, Yamasaki was not able to taste victory
He got his ass kicked by Moriman in every match
He became looked down by society
Now once again Yamasaki will meet Moriman on the batleground
The sanctioned match begins again
The participants held a pre-match conference
Could you sum up your feelings towards this match?
Ah, let's start with Yamsaki-san
From the dawn of time, the woman takes care of the house, and the husband does the hunting
That's my belief
That's your belief?
The male is strong
That's what I want to spray all over society
Spray?
Since this is your 4th match,
Don't you feel like it's been enough? Isn't Yamasaki a real pain in your ass?
It is a pain
We all know how this ends and I still have to come out here
Wasting my time for this piece of shit is-
Shut up! Be more nervous!
What?!
Be more nervous!
But she's not nervous
Since you already know you're gonna lose,
I don't know I'm gonna lose! Victory is a matter of timing!
Finally, time for the match
Within the walls of Korakuen Hall, people gather to watch Yamasaki vs. Moriman's final revenge match
Many bad memories have been built here
So before the match, let's see how they're doing
Lets look into their dressing rooms
Who is in here?  Oh it's Moriman.
Ah, a bento?
She's just having lunch before the match
She's taking it easy, eating lunch, looking at the horoscope
The horoscope!
What a champion, I wonder what her sign is
But more than anything, she's very relaxed
Meanwhile, Yamasaki-san
This is Yamasaki's trainer
Well done, genius comedian!
He has a strong resolve (?)
Well he is preparing
Looking forward to this
Indeed, I'm looking forward to it. The gong will ring any moment.
Everyone, you've been waiting for you
Starting now,
Yamasaki vs. Moriman - Final Revenge Match will begin!
First, the commissioners of this match, the duo DownTown!
Just to see Yamasaki and Moriman,
Why are there so many people here?
That really is a mystery to me as well honestly
There's nothing interesting at all
First off I want to answer something,
These are my everyday clothes
You didn't just go and change into these right?
These used to be my dad's white clothes that I got dyed black
Eh? Dyed?
I thought it could become fashionable this summer
So today,
This TOTALLY is,
This is amazing
The final match
They'll fight till we are satisfied it seems
And I don't know who the audience is rooting for
I have no idea what they're looking forward to
That's what I don't get
Probably fresh blood or something
They might want to see their blood on this floor
Let's call them out shall we?
Everyone, pay attention to that corner;
The Challenger Yamasaki will make his entrance
What was with that entrance?
Actually, honestly, when he came out
I felt kind of inspired
Or rather
I was inspired too
He looked cool
Yeah, I'm here to look impressive today!
You can't show them your lame side
Yeah, there's so many girls here too right?
TODAY, I REFUSE TO SHOW MY GOOD SIDE!
You refuse to show your bad side, right?
I won't show my bad side
"I WON'T SHOW MY GOOD SIDE"
Are you,
nervous?
So now, Yamasaki's closest friends,
Will present flowers to him
First is his best friend from Elementary School,
Nadai Yoshihiro-Sama
His former comedian comrade, Fujita Seiji-sama
You're very happy, aren't you Yamasaki-san?
I'm very very happy!
The audience doesn't know them at all though
Next, the champion Moriman's entrance
COME ON!
THAT'S RIGHT!
You always get your ass kicked first huh?
Next is their introductions
In the red corner, at 210 pounds....
The Invincible Champion, the Assassin Angel
Moriiiiiiiiiiiiiman!
In the blue corner, forever the challenger, The fighter from Nishinomiya
Yamsasakiiii HOOOOSEIIIIIIIII
Before the match everyone,
We have Endo Shozo
Endo Shozo will perform, everyone stand up please
With that, Endo!
Do you know the rhythm of the Samba? HOI HOI HOI
Well...
I'm sure the audience is thinking why they had to stand up for that...
Well well
It was to commemorate this
So now Yamasaki vs Moriman,
Final Revenge Match will be held
What battle shall we start with?
Right, lets have Yamasaki choose first
Let's have him decide
The challenger's choice?
Indeed
So Yamasaki-san, choose the first battle please
There's 18 here
There's 18. Alright I've decided
FRENCH BREAD SMACKING BATTLE
Let's begin!
Round 1...
What kind of advice could this be
Yamasaki-san?
The french bread... the french bread... hit my crotch
"The french bread hit my crotch"
Well whatever
You just got your ass whooped
All the footage of you was like this
I don't think that's true
We saw with these eyes
I got it, I got it
The bread is no good,
Boiling Hot Ankake Battle!
Yamasaki-san!  Yamasaki-san!  Yamasaki-san!
That was hilarious
You just can't write a script like this
This is just real life
Yamasaki-san?
You lost again
Hell yeah!
No not "hell yeah"
You can't say "hell yeah"
You can't say "hell yeah" to that
Hamada-san I got it
Yamasaki-san sucks at using tools
So now, right away,
Let's go with the Slapping Battle
Yamsaki-san!  Yamasaki-san!
Why cry?
Are you a sparrow?
That's the first time I've seen someone's back on the rope
What shall we do?
Please allow me to fight properly
We have!
K-1 Battle!
Is it alright doing this battle so soon?
I think this is 2 battles two early,
But it seems Yamasaki-san wants to get this over with
Hamada will be the referee
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Fight!
Sweep!
I can't go on
You can't go on?
Fight!
OK!
C'mon push through!
Down!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
You can do it!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
AUDIENCE: Stand up! Stand up!
Nine!
Fight!  Fight!
It's already over
Fight!
Yamasaki-san!  Yamasaki-san!
Our stomachs hurt!
Yamasaki-san!
What should the next battle be?
How should we continue?
Moriman!
This is the end for today,
Next time, fight me in a field!
Where the hell is that?
Get outta here asshole!
Audience: Get lost!
Can we end like this?
Go get him
There's so many people here, it can't end like this
Last battle!
HOT TOWEL SMACKING BATTLE!
Your face looks like you just came back from a swimming pool (?)
Yamsaki-san...
Why would you wrap the towel around the rope?
I thought he was gonna bring the rope with him
Everybody... thank y*cough*...
Hey, you guys
They might be able to convince him again, I think so
Maybe if they give him a soft drink or something
Just that?
Maybe a Big Cool
What happened?
What do you mean?
In short, what he repeated over and over again,
"Please spare me"
He said it over, over and over again
And there's something that confused me. Dripping out of his nose...
It wasn't boogers,
It wasn't snot,
But something was dripping out
Yeah
What he wanted to say, to all these people who came here today
Next year, this match can be continued
Tanaka! Tanaka! Tanaka!  Tanaka!
Hold on, wait a minute!
There's two of us, why cheer for me?
Yamasaki vs. Moriman Revenge Match! Settled next year!