- Today, we're having a dodgeball match.
- How many years has it been since you played?
- I wonder how many its been...
- But isn't it harder to play dodgeball after grade school? You're not as good once you grow.
- I dunno.
- He wouldn't even say "Probably." or "It seems like it would be." for you.
- That's why his solo show in Nagoya only sold twenty tickets.
- It was twenty-five!
In Tokyo, it was around 100.
- What was the capacity? - It could fit 300 people.
- That's horrible.
* Yamazaki's Solo Show "Like Yamazaki" August 9, 1999 7PM Aoyama Circular Theatre *
- Even though it's a circular theatre with room for 300 people...
you couldn't make a circle with the 100 people.
- Hurry. - Let's go, so we can play dodgeball.
- What's wrong with that car?
- Why won't it go?
The car in front of us is saying like "Come here!".
- What happened? *Reluctantly, the group goes to help.*
- Fujiwara... - ... go out there for us...
We can bring a rope if they need it.
* Manager Fujiwara goes to listen to their needs *
- It... ita... It's Itao. - Itao-san?!
- Isn't that Itao? - It is.
- What's wrong? Who is that with him? * Itao tells Fujiwara what happened *
- They're wearing the same clothes. - That must be his wife.
- They say we dented their car.
- They're saying we hit them in this car?!
- There wasn't any time where that happened.
- He's looking at us.
He's looking hard.... - He even got up close.
- He's not going to go away. Let's just hurry up.
- What's going on out here? - Ah, good morning.
- What's up? - Well, you seem to have hit me.
- Eh?! We did all this?! - Yep.
- Umm... and she is? - Um, this is my wife!
- This one's different than the one we went to your wedding party for.
- No, that's not it at all.
It's not it at all, right?! - Of course.
- Anyway... Itao, we don't have any mark on our van.
- I bet you probably do have one.
- To do this, they must have hit you hard.
Maybe someone hit you before and you didn't notice?
- Looks like it was from something round. - No, no. It wasn't like that when we left.
Even so, come look over here.
You guys knocked over my stew over!
- Why did you guys make stew? - I thought "Let's go see my parents."
So we made some and put it in our car to take to them.
This thing won't even close anymore.
The insides are all scrambled now!
- Were they like that before? - No, they weren't.
It was from the impact. It had to from the impact, didn't it?
- Of course.
- Well, I'm sorry, but... - This seems odd.
I still think you're wrong, Itao.
I think you didn't notice it before you got in.
- Either way, we still have a location shoot to do.
- We don't really have much time, and it might rain.
- I think I can feel my neck starting to hurt.
- Were you geing serious?
- There's nothing wrong with your wife, right? - Is your neck okay?
I think she's fine, but... oh man, your neck is really hot here.
* Itao checks on his beloved wife *
- We have to go have our match, and then we've got a talk to do.
- We still have a talk to do. What time is it? We should try to hurry.
- And it looks like rain.
- Since we can't do our location shoot if it either of those happen...
- But first, can I get something from Nihon TV?
Even if it's just for the damage to the car...
- We can talk about whether we hit him or not later. * Itao requests money to fix the car *
- For now, just take that.
- Okay, we'll leave it like that for now.
I understand.
* After being held up in an unexpected place, the team finally heads to the location shoot *
- Gaki No Tsukai's first ever: "Hit 'em, Hit 'em, Hit 'em hard!" 100000 yen Summer Dodgeball Match!
Matsumoto Team: Hitoshi Matsumoto and Naoki Tanaka Hamada Team: Masatoshi Hamada and Shouzo Endou
* Out!!! *
* Yamazaki notices something *
- Matsumoto... - What?
- Itao's here.
- What's going on?
- They said there's something wrong with our necks.
- You went to the hospital? - Yep.
- As you can see, my skull's got cracks in it.
- This here? - Yes. - That's not your neck, right? - Yes.
- This here's my woman.
- When you say your "woman", you mean your wife?
- What are we going to do?
* Itao is asking for medical compensation in addition to the car maintenance money *
- When you say "What should we do"....
- Well, right now we're doing a location shoot. - Yes, we're actually shooting.
- I understand that us playing dodgeball doesn't really matter to you, since you've been injured...
but this is our job, and we have to get this done.
- Well, I've been on the show before. My wife was too.
Like when you hit my car.
- But we won't be showing that on-air.
- But just in case I do show up...
I think I should get an appearance fee for that as well.
- I don't think so, since that isn't part of the show. * This time, Itao is requesting an appearance fee *
- The cameras were spinning and acting like it would be on air, so I believed it.
I thought I'd be appearing as a talent.
It isn't normal circumstances.
Thinking I was a guest, I did things for the camera...
So, I should get paid.
- I'll talk with Mr. Tokuoka about getting you money for your car and for your appearance fee.
I'll talk to them, so please let them do this opening.
- What are you guys doing? - Dodgeball.
- Well, since I'm going to be on the show anyway, I should earn my appearance fee, right?
- If we did that, we'd have 3 teams. - And we can't do that, so no need to help.
- And you guys are injured.
- I'll do it anyway.
- If you did, we would ask some staff to play.
- The staff is no good.
Let my wife play with us!
- We can't do it with her. - Don't you want to do this together with my wife?!
To make the time pass quickly.
- Uh, Wife, will you do it?
- Of course.
- Suga-san, what are we going to do?
- Let's put the wife in and make this 3-on-3.
- You serious? - Yes.
- Does the game have prize money?
- Yes, it does. - How much?
- 100000 yen. - 100000 yen? Let's take it to 1 million yen.
- A million's a little much, isn't it?
- Even if you win, it's hard to just accept that much.
- A million will be fine.
- Okay, we'll do a million. Since we're paying, let's do this again quickly.
It looks like it's going to rain, but we have to finish the shoot.
- What are we going to do? - As far as teams.
- Well, right now, what are the teams like?
- Right now, it's red team vs blue team.
- Then I'll go on Hamada's team. Wife, you can go on Matsumoto's team.
- You okay to play? - You can, can't you? * Itao divides the teams to get money, whoever wins *
- Of course.
- Ready?!
GO!
* OUT!!! *
- You okay?!
- Wife, he hit you. You've been hit.
- I only hit her a little on the leg.
- What's wrong? - She's dead!
- Dead?! I only hit her lightly on the leg.
- That's no reason to die.
- Hey!
Even if she didn't die, you would have put her in an ambulance.
- I guess it couldn't be helped.
I can't really be helped that getting all excited and then getting hit on the leg killed her, can it?
- All the stuff from before just mixed and added to it.
- Ah, from before...
- But as far as a decision goes... Our team won, right?
- There's no winner and no loser.
- Well, I mean, we still have the prize money...
- Is your wife going to be okay?
- More important than the money...
Is she okay and do we have to call an ambulance?
- Right now the prize money doesn't matter.
What is it? - That just leaves things unsettled.
What?! I don't even get a little bit of the money?
- What's wrong with you? Money?
Do you only want the money?
- Hell yeah, I want my money!
- Even so, maybe we should call an ambulance.
- No, let's deal with the prize money first, before we go calling ambulances.
- What the hell? You're wife's down, shouldn't it be the ambulance first?
- I know you think it's odd, but look at it from my point of view.
Think about why the money comes first.
- If I were you, I'd call an ambulance.
- You just don't understand my point of view!
I knew you would say something like that.
But try stepping over here.
First comes the money. Money, then ambulance.
Ambulance then money would just be odd.
- I guess it's just that type of thing.
- For now, I'll be fine with the money you have here.
* Itao frankly asks for the money *
- We brought the 100000 yen for the original prize.
So as a start, please, take this.
- As a start. - As a start?
- We'll send the remainder to you. It will be coming at a later date.
The appearance fee will come too. - Good.
If it was just 100000 yen, this would be it.
But since it was a million, you'll be sending 900000 yen later, right?
- That was the money, so now for an ambulance...
- Since I've got the money... Okay, now you understand.
- Itao-san... your wife...
- What the hell?! - The wife... Ah!
- Get up, you liar!
Don't make up lies like that.
- You're his wife, aren't you?
Of course.
- Hey! Hey! Where are you going?
- Where are you going?! - Itao went over there!
- We'll get even next time.