Subbed by: Mickstar813 & YamasakiGIFs
Gaki no Tsukai- Backstage
Damn, my body hurts...
What the hell are you doing!
Matsumoto Hitoshi         Hamada Masatoshi
Downtown
My body really hurts...
Piss off you idiot.
Don't touch me
Oh don't be like that
What the hell , you always...
Cocorico
Endo Shozo        Tanaka Naoki
It's like always...
Good morning.
Pardon me.
Can... Can you listen for a minute?..
My body hurts so bad...
Yamasaki Housei
What?
Well... I kind of need to discuss something...
Um...
Lately, I've been struggling financially...
Damn, he's really...
He's so direct...
I know it's sad
But seriously, last week, when we finished recording and I jokingly looked in his wallet...
He only had thirty something yen...
For real.
Oh, was it three hundred and something?...
You're kidding!
Yeah it was
No way...
No, really.
I was surprised.
Really?
I just bought a house, you know?
Ah right, yeah.
And the loan re-payments are tough
And I have 2 kids right now
That's right
And to be honest, I want to put them in a private school...
you get me?
That costs a lot..
It does.
You have two girls right?
Yeah...
So why don't you just work really hard?
No, I mean... I am working hard...
But it never changes...
Since I was 28, it's not gone up once!
My worth!
That can't be!
Honest!
But it's not something to say here, it's something to say at the offices...
Right, yeah.
No, no, that's--
Just tell your wife
Just say it to '******* *******"
OI YOU!!
What was wrong, he should say it to his wife...
To his family, right?..
He shouted 'KORE ME-N' at me... (Note: He meant to say "Kora Omae- OI YOU"
But anyway... Seriously...
I want money...
So I heard that you can get a lot of royalties selling music...
Yeah I've heard that.
I mean yeah, I guess it is true...
Yeah, I heard that you can so...
Wait, are you a rakugouka?.. Why are you taking your jacket off whilst talking...
I was a bit hot
As if he's getting to the good part.
What the hell...
After shouting, I got a bit hot...
Right? So I heard that you can get a lot of royalties when you do stuff...
And you know I have so much talent when it comes to music?
And so...
I actually went and made some music. Seriously.
What? Four songs for us?
Just from your images...
one song each?
And so you guys sing it and burn it onto a CD...
And then.. I would get the royalties from it...
So you composed and wrote the lyrics?..
Right, yeah.
Just for this day, 4 completely original songs
Narrator: Noda Keiichi
were genuinely created from scratch by Yamazaki.
And on top of that, he only had
4 hours to create them, showing his genius.
He was not a comedian whilst working but just a creator
Whilst imagining the singers, he was serious when checking over the melodies and lyrics.
All for the mortgage and the future of his family
Will Yamazaki be able to realise his potential as a music producer
and live his life off royalties like he dreamt?
So singers royaltieswill start at 200,000 yen each
So singers royalties will start at 200,000 yen each
However many we sell, that is set.
That's the contract
I don't know, this is something I've thought from a while back...
But Yamazaki uses Gaki no Tsukai for the privatization of things...
Yeah, he does it a lot
He really does!
Just for money too...
He really does.
Honestly, he just keeps doing it time after time...
Hamada-san, let's go.
Let's go.
Right now?
Right now.
M-me!?
Wait, right now?
Listen to it, rehearse it and then shoot the real thing
Eh, seriously!?
Really?
For real.
There's no way someone wearing this kind of shirt can pull this off...
Dun-dun!
Seriously!?
You're kidding!
Really.
What the hell...
Damn, this is tough
This is really tough
4 hours later
Thanks for your work!
Alright!
This is a horrible kind of tiredness...
Was it?
It's not like a nice 'tired' feeling...
You might feel like that now...
But you're going to watch what you did now and think "I'm glad I took part in that"...
Really?
You sure?
This is new ground for everyone...
There are loads of things I want to protest about...
Right anyway...
Let's start with Hamada-san's...
Oh me?
Wait, am I actually going to sing?
Hamada's Rehearsal
Yes, you are...
Wait... Why?...
Well.. That's so...
So we make sales...
To sell CD's, you can't muck around...
Please play it then
Why does the song have such a fast tempo?
You could have made it slower...
Sung by
Yamasaki Hōsei
♫ Machi no man'naka de haretsusuru ♫-
It explodes in the middle of the town
♫ Osae kirenai yokubō to ♫
The desire that cannot be supressed
But seriously, the person who made the whole thing is really amazing, huh?
Well, I did the whole thing by myself...
Right here...
Yes...
This part is really tough, even I struggled to sing it
Right.
♫ Tobira o akeru shinku no kagi to ♫
The crimson key that opens the door
OK.
Yeah?
You ready?
I mean, I don't really know...
Okay, let's try it for real.
No, no, no, wait up!
This is impossible
Just sing it once, seriously.
You can't just say  "Sing it"...
I don't remember the words so how am I meant to sing it?..
Okay, let's go.
♫ Machi no man'naka de haretsusuru ♫
It explodes in the middle of the town
♫ Osae kirenai yokubou to ♫
The desire that cannot be supressed.
♫ Tsukurare sugita genjitsu o ♫
The reality which had been dictated by man too much
Yeah?
You really weren't paying attention at all, were you...
I'm very sorry...
You were literally so bad right from the start...
I'm sorry..
Eh, hold on,
Wait, this is going to take some time...
I mean...
I know I was singing it casually like
♫ Machi no man'naka de ♫
Right.
But sing it like
♫ MACHI no man'naka de ♫
Right?
MACHIno...
♫ Machi no ♫
♫ MACHI no man'naka de ♫
Like a bit faster.
OK, I get it.
And just the last part
OK.
Just at the last part, it's a bit hard because of the lack of characters
Then add some on...
No but, er,
♫ Daremo shiranai sono sekai e ♫
'To that world that no one knows about...'
That's how you want it?
Yes.
Oh wait, the dancing...
The dance?
Well you can't be like this...
Oh you mean pose?
Yes
So start like this...
Like this...
Hold on now,
Are you sure this is okay?
Isn't it really lame?..
No way...
OK.
♫ MACHI no man'naka ♫
MACHI...
In the middle of the town...
No way, this is going to be so lame...
It's never going to be lame...
Sorry.
Yamasaki Produce!
#1 Hamada Masatoshi
Yamazaki produce... Hamada's song...
Weirdo alert...
Lyrics & Composition by Yamasaki Housei
Sung by Hamada Masatoshi
What the hell is this?..
Eh, what was it called?
"Beach Paddy."
Woah, this is...
Like a really old idol...
♫ Machi no man'naka de haretsusuru ♫
It explodes in the middle of the town
♫ Osae kirenai yokubou to ♫
This desire that cannot be surpressed
♫ Tsukura re sugita genjitsu o ♫
I balance this reality which has been dictated by man too much
I now know what image he's going for
For real?
♫ Hakari ni kakete ikite iru ♫
and continue to live my life
♫ Doko made iku no dousureba ii no ♫
How far will we go, what should I do
Like...
It's really old, huh?
♫ Kotae ga aru no dare ga kimeru no ♫
Is there an answer, who will decide
It really is...
Like the 80's, maybe 70's?..
♫ Fumouna tochi ni ♫
Shine the light on
♫ Hikari o ataeru ♫
this barren land
And it's been done so badly...
♫ Meshia no iru sekai e ♫
And on to the world where there is a Messiah
What the fuck is 'The world where there is a Messiah'?
♫ Hageshiku uchi narasu ♫
It violently rings
Literally...
♫ Toki o kizamitsukeru ban'nin yo ♫
O keeper who controls time
I have no idea what the lyrics mean either...
♫ Erabareta monotachi to ♫
along with the chosen people
♫ Tobira o akeru shinku no kagi to ♫
and the crimson key that opens the door
♫ Hageshiku uchi narasu ♫
O keeper who
The lyrics...
The lyrics are amazing
♫ Toki o kizamitsukeru ban'nin yo ♫
violently writes time
Do you get what this is about at all?..
♫ Ima koso tobidasou ♫
Let's jump out right now
Umm..
The lyrics are just...
♫ Daremoshiranai sono sekai e ♫
To that world which no one knows.
Aww, you laughed a bit at the end...
Sorry about that.
Like it's a best 10 hit or something...
This is great
You get it right? Like who this is meant to be and all...
It's him right? I might be mistaken...
* Popular music artist Takanori Nishikawa (1989 - Present)
TM Revolution.
Without doubt...
No, no...
It's not?
Totally wrong
I've never of this 'TM'...
Oh really? I was sure it was TM...
It's got to be...
However you look at it, that was TM...
Wait, is it similar?..
TM's Nishikawa-san is very much like that.
Very similar.
Even the outfit.
No no, that's just...
Even the movements.
Actually, Hamada-san was even more
pumped to do it than I thought...
Well he might not be as bad as you but
he is someone who loves royalties...
Oh, so he was thinking about that?
Yeah, he thought about that and got into it...
To try and sell it, huh?
As if that shit will sell...
Of course it will sell!
Really?
Yes!
An by the way, this song is called「BEACH PADDY」。
Right, why?
It's Hamada (in english)
Hamada
Oh really?
That's why
What kind of a title is that?..
But he's like
not said beach paddy once...
It has nothing to do with the song...
I can get if that musician is called it...
But the title of the song shouldn't be that...
No, because Hamada-san sung it...
Did you sing it, Matsumoto-san?
No, I didn't...
You didn't, right?
That's why it's「BEACH PADDY」
Well, I guess I can smack you anytime I want to so it's okay...
Let's go to the next one!
Next is Tanaka...
What was Tanaka's like?
Was the song style different?
Yes, it was
Can we proceed?
Yep.
Right, here is Tanaka's..
This is, uh...
Tanaka's Rehearsal
This is the stage.
This is the stage for my song?
Right, so do it the way
Right.
that you want to.
Okay
Do it like that..
Ok...
he doesn't look at me when he speaks to me at all, huh?
Right, cue music!
♫ Itsumo omou no ♫
I always think...
Can you sing through your nose a little bit more?
Through my nose?..
♫ Itsumo ♫
I always
When you do the V sign, look at Camera 3...
Right by your face...
Like this?..
V sign like this?
Basically as long as it's cute, you can do whatever you want
Yamasaki Produce!
#2 Tanaka Naoki
Yamasaki produce: Tanaka's song...
Lyrics & Composition by Yamasaki Housei
Sung by Tanaka Naoki
♫ Itsumo omou no ♫
I always think
Hang on, this is Noppo-san!
♫ Anata o soba de kanjita toki ♫
When I feel you next to me
I know, right?
He's gay?..
♫ Sou kono kanji ♫
That's right, this feeling
I thought that would be the best...
This is horrible..
♫ Osanai toki no mama yo ♫
I felt it when I was a child...
I have a lot of things to say about this too...
♫ Hareta hi wa mukae ni kite ♫
I will come to pick you up on sunny days
He does sing it like...
♫ Mae de matteru wa ♫
and wait at the entrance
It's intentional, I was singing through my nose a bit
♫ Futari no aizu ♫
Our special sign
♫ Ryoute de buisain ♫
The V sign with both our hands
Ah, that's awesome.
I was doing as I was told
And the movements, right?
Yes
♫ Kodomo no koro ni ♫
When I was a kid
♫ Kiita ohanashi ♫
I heard this story
♫ Itsumo wa happii end ♫
It always has a happy ending
♫ Anata wa watashi ni ♫
So what kind of ending
♫ Don'na ketsumatsu no ♫
will you give me
♫ Ohanashi o tsukuru no ♫
for my story
This is just..
This is a song for a woman to sing, surely?
♫ Sutekina sou rabu sutoorii ♫
For our lovely, that's right, love story...
This is some lyrics...
Wow, that was just...
This was really difficult
It was hard to sing it I bet too...
It was.
I was meant to be a 15 year old girl singing
Right.
My one, I was meant to be 21...
Right? I was 15...
Oh I see...
A 15 year old girl!
Right now, there are 6 billion people on this planet...
Who benefits from this episode?..
What you mean, some people might listen to the song and it might cheer them up!
What was the title called?
This one is「Riziere Centre」
What does it mean?
It means Tanaka...
In french though...
That's Tanaka in french?
Yes, it is
Is that what it means?
* Shoumurasaki Hiroshisan (Gaki Director)
It's so obvious you made Komu or someone go and search that...
Definitely...
Shall we go with the next one?
Ok
OK!
Right, next up is Endo-kun...
Right, my one was a real problem
This one in itself...
This was really difficult...
Right, shall we proceed then?
Shall we...
Endo's Rehearsal
Er...
It's all in English isn't it?
But I don't get why...
This isn't about remembering the words...
Ok
It's just your soul shouting
That's too bad
Pardon?
When you say That's too bad, say it like...
"That's too bad!"
Yeah, that's so much better...
Okay...
The interlude is like really long...
Yeah it was..
You're like free to what you want there...
Free?
Sorry producer, can you not like tell me what to do there and stuff?..
So we'll do this like once
Like we have no time
So we're going straight to the real thing...
Yamasaki Produce!
#3 Endo Shozo
Yamasaki produce: Endo's song...
Lyrics & Composition by Yamasaki Housei
Sung by Endo Shozo
Everything is done by Hosei-san, huh?
What's that about!?
Holy shit...
This is...
Oh damn, this would be tough to do...
Woah, this is...
This is something else...
This is...
I actually think Endo's amazing for doing this..
Yeah, this was really...
You really performed for your seniors...
Your seniors would never do this...
Yeah, Matsumoto and I would never be able to do this
Yeah, we wouldn't...
Yamasaki-san chose like everything with this, including the clothes
This was really tough...
Wow...
Honestly, I applaud you Endo for doing that...
Well to put it simply, that was heavy metal...
No Death Metal, it's Death Metal.
Damn but...
Death metal?..
If you put this into one of those hexagonal graphs...
You know, measuring applause from the crowd and all
It would definitely be close to like a dot in the centre...
Seriously, it wouldn't spread out at all...
Was there a reason for mine being all english?
Well because it's death metal
Oh, so because it's death metal...
You've been like preaching 'death metal, death metal' from before
but what the hell is it?..
It's a song
It's a song from hell
I sang that?..
Then don't make your juniors sing that kind of song...
Right, lastly...
Right.
Let's check out Matsumoto-sans...
Oh man...
Right, have a look..
Matsumoto's Rehearsal
♫ Mou ♫
It seems
♫ Modorenai ♫
that we've come to a point
♫ Tokoro made kita mitaida ♫
where we can't return anymore
This is literally
the manliest
of men kind of song
I see...
So I really want you to put your heart into it and sing it...
Uh-huh, yeah.
It's fine if you cry...
Without being embarassed
That's it.
Can we try then?
♫ Mou ♫
It seems
♫ Modorenai ♫
that we've come
♫ Tokoro made kita mitaida ♫
to a point where we cannot return anymore
That's great. This is really...
♫ Mou ♫
It seems
That's fantastic, Matsumoto-san
♫ Modorenai ♫
that we've come to a point
I'm sorry, I don't feel like I'm going to cry
but I'm going to laugh instead
No, you definitely cannot laugh
Really?
Yeah.
♫ Shinjitsu o ♫
that you have
♫ Tsukamu made ♫
nothing to lose
OK! OK, OK, OK!
We can shoot the real thing
Okay, let's do the real thing
Can I
drink something quickly?
Sure.
About the change of clothes...
Please go get changed, we've prepared something for you
I have to get changed?!
Yes.
We've got everything prepared
Seriously?
Yes.
Aren't we going a bit too quick?..
Alright, if you could please.
After this, Matsumoto records his real take..
Yamasaki Produce!
#4 Matsumoto Hitoshi
Yamasaki Produce: Matsumoto's song..
Lyrics & Composition by Yamasaki Housei
Sung by Matsumoto Hitoshi
This makes you look so lame already...
♫ Mou ♫
It seems
♫ Modorenai ♫
that we've come
♫ Tokoro made kita mitaida ♫
to a point where we can't return anymore
The theme of this song makes you look so lame...
♫ Furikaeru ♫
Every time
♫ Toki wa itsumo ♫
I look back
He should let you like run around a bit more...
♫ Jibun no ♫
I see
♫ Kage o miru ♫
my own shadow
Right?
♫ Sou ♫
And
♫ Sorenaraba ♫
if that's the case
♫ Iku tokoro made ikou ♫
let's go to the place where we must go
♫ Sou sureba ♫
and if we do that
You know like
They literally forced me to wear the jumper and jacket...
♫ Kitto ♫
we'll probably
Ah, right.
So I look like so serious...
♫ Furikaeru ♫
not look
♫ Koto mo nai ♫
back anymore
This feels like I've gone to welcome drinks or something...
♫ Zutto ♫
These precious
♫ Shinji teta ♫
thoughts that
I just come to Tokyo, and need to work hard.
♫ Taisetsuna ♫
I believed
Be friendly with the people I have to work with...
♫ Omoi o ♫
in
♫ Darenimo ♫
and my heart
♫ Jama sa rezu ♫
which I've brought up
♫ Sodatte kita ♫
without letting anyone
♫ Kono kokoro o ♫
get in my way
Oh damn, this is tough!
This is SO tough!
♫ Kitto yareru sa ♫
You can probably do it
This is so bad
♫ Itsu demo sou sa ♫
It's always like that
So old!
No, please no english!
♫ Nani ni mo makenai ♫
Until you grasp
♫ Shinjitsu o ♫
the truth that you
♫ Tsukamu made ♫
have nothing to lose
He's really gone and...
This is so bad...
It really leaves its mark for sure...
Right?
This is tough...
So bad right?
That was awful
That was amazing
Like I sweat the kind of sweat that comes out only when you've broken a bone...
You could have let me muck around a bit more
That's true
I wish you'd done something for me like Endo's...
I mean, these 3 got to muck around!
I mean yeah, we didn't have to dress up like you...
You guys are like doing it as part of the joke...
Yours was so serious...
It was so serious...
No, everyones was serious!
I'm so embarassed...
Everyone's was serious
* Popular music artist Shōgo Hamada (1975 - Present)
That was definitely Hama-shou...
I don't know who Hama-shou is..
I mean Hamada Shogo...
I don't know Hamada Shogo, that much...
You used to listen to him every day...
Yeah, but like... I forgot who he is
Even though you listened to him so often?..
I don't get it...
That reply was hilarious
You just forgot him?
Yeah...
So that was original.
All music producers watching this on TV
What is with him being like this?
Out of the 4 songs, I don't care which one, I want to make them into a CD.
We're all like totally serious
Wait, what?
"We're all serious?" You mean you're serious?
Yeah...
Right!
You are
Wait, what, what?
Everyone, bow your heads.
Please!
No, what do you mean?
All 4 of them?
Yeah, that would be fine
So for example
1 song is fine, right?
Yeah, 1 song is fine
Even just Matsumoto's...
Yeah, that would be fine
After watching them, I think only Matsumoto's has a chance...
Ours are like...
Ours were a joke...
Seriously,that was the first time in my life
the words 'Let it be' came out of my mouth
My mouth is shocked
So everyone in the music industry
We will be waiting
So please consider us!
Info Text
He's serious
There it is!
And we would like to end the show this week with this song...
Whilst listening to this?
I mean, this is the only way...
Geez...
This really leaves its mark...
What is with this feeling?
♫ Hageshiku uchi narasu ♫