Subbed by: ShadiHD & Zurui
Color coding:
Matsumoto
Yamasaki
Endo
Tanaka
Hamada
Fujiwara
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi     Hamada Masatoshi
Welcome to Gaki no tsukai Batsu game Special episode!
Cocorico
Yamazaki Hosei
Endo Shozo     Tanaka Naoki
We have a time issue, so this special won't include all of the material
This was a 2 hour special but it still wasn't enough time for all of our punishments
--Yeah
Downtown
Gaki no Tsukai
ya Arahende!!
Never-seen before scenes!!
Don't laugh
in
High school
Slippers Scene
We're entering!
Here we go!
They start the Batsu game where they must not laugh or get punished
We already seen this scene
So, whatcha ya think? you're going to be studying
here, It's not bad, huh?
but then when they were heading to Morning Assembly...
Hey!
Why were you late?
My bicycle had a flat tire.
and you?
I overslept.
Gekidan Hitori
(comedian)
Come closer
Why are YOU late?
My little sister got sick, so I took her to the hospital.
Why are you late?
My sister got sick a---
My sister--
You little... come with me!
Principal's greeting
They were greeted by the Principal and the teachers
Teacher scolding students for not wearing slippers inside the school
Why aren't you wearing your slippers ?
Don't do that again, now get out of here!
You come closer
Why aren't you wearing your slippers?
Someone is playing a prank on me and took the slippers from my locker.
Someone took them from---
You moron!, come with me.
That's enough!
Reading Haiku?
Fujikumi sensei
Fujiwara Hiroshi
(former downtown manager)
Open your books to page 57.
Fujikumi sensei requested to open page 57 to study the modern 31 syllabled verse and the haiku.
This textbook has a trap
Along with Ishikawa Takuboku and other famous poets, there's a section for the works of Suga Kenji--the chief producer of the show.
what will his haiku talk about?
Next is Suga Kenji.
They fell easily for the trap
You are going to need imagination
There will be questions that they have to create a story from.
The 4 of them will use this blank textbook
to create a story from the title
This is the title
3 Matsuzaka cows
Title
Matsumoto, you start
What is this feeling of "freedom"
that's what the Matsuzaka were thinking...
Why are you looking at me like that?
Matsuzaka can't keep still, so suddenly he went outside...
Hana Masa arrived
Because the teacher's laughing!
Next, Yamazaki
Matsuzaka and Hana Masa are 3 calves
How...
how do we care for them then eat them?
Lunch scene
They all eat their various box lunches, and take a much needed rest.
however this will never last long!
(Tsuruko) Let's answer questions!
Tsuruko will answer any question from the Kuchibiru West High school
Grade 3 Class C
Broadcasting from school
Let's hear the question that can't be answered
Nice to meet you
Your high pitched voice sounds nice
Thank you
Please introduce yourself
Grade2, class C, Koumoto Junko
Jun-chan
Koumoto
Junichi
Everyone calls me Jun-chan
So, what problem, can I help you with?
I fell in love with someone
You fell in love.. what's your age? 10?
I'm 17
17... Is this your first love?
Yes, it's the first time, and I have weird feelings
I know it's hard, but can you say his name?
If not, how about just the initials?
Uh.. ah.. Hitoshi
What?  What?
H-kun.. with H-kun...
H-kun?
Because it's Hitoshi
With H-kun... when I do it with H-kun... he feels good.. then it's done
Usually you do (censored)
Hitoshi-kun... H-kun, doesn't have anything
What are they saying?
Yeah, really
End of broadcast
The real Jun-chan appears
I caught you!
Jun-chan, was that OK to say that over the air?
Sure, no problem
Because I didn't say any names...
I didn't say Matsumoto-kun's name so it should be OK
You should have said his name
I can't do something like that, if I did...
If I said his name, he would be angry
But you did "it" with Matsumoto-kun, right?
I did
In the pool
we did "it"
Give me a break
Science Class scene
Hosshan Sensei (Comedian)
For today's class, I'd like to study about
Science Teacher
the science of breathing.
Udon Noodle
Hosshan Sensei was explaining to the four how breathing works
Hosshan Sensei is a professional at passing things through his nose. (Do not try this at home)
That's...who wouldn't laugh at that?
Sensei, that's just wrong.
This is freeze frame of breathing
We already get that
This is no good. this is the type of tube for going down the throat.
Later on...
So you now understand how we inhale oxygen and then exhale carbon dioxide
Hosshan sensei, you have a phone call, please report to the teacher's lounge.
Ok I have to go.
Hosshan Sensei had to leave, but there's no relief to our four since the wolf came in to ensure they laugh again.
Hosshan Sensei went out because he has a meeting, so I brought a Video with me.
I really have a bad feeling about this
Yea me too
The Balance of Life
In the Neutral world there's a Balance & Order
there are animals that eat grass and bugs and there are animals who pray on other animals.
It's called the Cycle of life, and it creates the balance in the neutral world to make everything in order
it starts here from the very grains of sand where millions of Microorganism live
and then we take the sample of sand and study the Microorganism that lives in it.
we found Heipo
Heipo (Director)
Heipo multiply & duplicate itself and creating hundreds of similar Microorganism resulting in what we call the Heipo multiplier
How can you control yourself?
Then Heipo emerges from the ground and grows, but he get prayed on by small Animals, and then bigger Animals pray on them.
Seriously, How can you not laugh at that!
--It's not easy
and the snake get prayed on by an eagle, and then the greatest Animal prays on both.
Then Heipo returns to the sand once again
thus creating the balanced cycle of life
That's too much
Matsumoto explodes by himself!
It's been 5hrs and 30 minutes since starting
Matsumoto has a break down all by himself
I've been thinking...
You guys...
When I'm... I'm...
ready to laugh, like just now...
right?
What?
Like now, right?
Yeah
It's not our fault
We're just listening to you
If I were in a Batsu game with my senior
if he...
was having a hard time...
I would take the punishment for him by laughing first
So you're saying if we see
that you are ready to laugh, we should laugh
and take the punishment for you?
I'm not saying that in so many words
But, yes
Again we were just listening seriously, we didn't do anything
For example if I were with my senior Shinsuke
Yeah
Right?
If he was in trouble and I...
saw that Shinsuke might be hurt
I wouldn't want him to take more punishment...
Club Activity
Everyone lets go and see the clubs
They are going to see the club activites with Fujikumi sensei
What's waiting for them?
Doomo Tsuyoshi    Doomo Koichi
Totally different
Because they are totally different
And then someone appears
Matsumoto pinches his butt
to stop from laughing
Tsunsuku
And then...
Rapper
(Tajima Manager)
"My name is Tajima Yuichi" "I'm the number 1 bad boy in Yoshimoto"
"I want you to hear my rapping skills"
"Listen now, to my rapping skills"
Matsumoto fell for all 3 tricks
Extended dance scene
While eating in the Gym, Itao's wife appears with Madonna's song
Itao's wife
Itao's Wife
Her famous style of dancing is 100% effective in making them laugh
Actually she has a super version of this dance
That's excellent
Very good
What's with that sad face
--I can't stand it
Don't make that sad face
Stop making that face
What the hell?
I understand already
Yes we get it already
Don't get excited
What the hell?
She's amazing
Hamada Silent Library Game
We're entering the Library keep quite!
Hamada takes the four into a library where he'll make them play a batsu game within a Batsu game, the Silent Library!
These are four cards, and uh...I think you know the rules already
The one who draws the card which has the "lip" on it receives a punishment
Ok, Ready...set
Tanaka got the Lip card
Ok, here's Tanaka's punishment
Thai Kick
You gotta be kidding me!
This is so wrong!
Tanaka stand over here
This is wrong, this is the worst punishment yet!
Tanaka come over here
Are you for real?
Quiet!
Tanaka be quiet!
Ok again
Ready...set
Matsumoto-san punishment is...
Tickling army
Come in
Ok that's enough
Why are you laughing?
Yama-chan you're taking it gracefully
Shocking remark!!
A student should sleep early
Go to sleep
After the lights went out there was a shocking remark from Matsumoto!
It's annoying that we can't tell what time is since there's no clock in this class
Our four can't tell what time it is since there's no clock in the classroom
Can I say something?
If it's pass 12 o'clock
then it's my birthday
Current time
1:13 AM
Did I have my birthday? I don't know...
Happy Birthday
(Fujiwara):- Matsumoto Happy Birthday, now go to sleep!
What the...
This is wrong!
Matsumoto has reached his Birthday
Matsumoto Happy Birthday
Now go to sleep!
Matsumoto Out
That's incredible
You should let me know which scenes you want aired
At the end...
when we finished the graduation, and the Diamond group appeared
Oh, yeah
Why were they mad?
Yeah, Diamond was really mad
Chief Producer
Suga Kenji
I wondered why Diamond was so mad
I asked the staff and they said that he was supposed to have a rifle, but it wasn't ready
Diamond Kesuke is supposed to carry a gun
Chief producer Suga
Oh, that's why he was mad!
He wasn't carrying anything.. that's why his hands were lonely
He took out his anger on us
Diamond Scene
Graduation students, you may leave
During the graduation
a group of men were waiting in the silent forest
The 4 had no idea
The group is...
The Angry Diamond Group
Police woman  Diamond     Hatomura   Police woman
(Old lady #1)  (Suga Kenji)  (Nakamura)   (Old lady #2)
Why are you so mad?
Punisher from Hell
And finally
Super Sadist Hamada unleashes his final beating
Who the hell are you?!
We already left!
We have come to the end
By the way
Super Sadist Hamada
Couldn't stop...
Number one comedian, Super sadist Hamada is going to follow them to hell!
Stop!  Stop!