Subbed by: Mickstar813 & HouseiGIFs
Episode Aired: 2004.12.05
You know how I am really talented with music?
2 years ago, he made original
songs for the Gaki members
Narrator:
Noda Keiichi
I made you all songs...
to try and live off royalties
for the rest of his life.
Am I actually going to sing?
Yeah.
We were all shocked by his talent.
Why?
To sell...
♫ Machi no man'naka de haretsusuru ♫
It explodes in the middle of the town
♫ Osae kirenai yokubō to ♫
The desire that I cannot suppress anymore
♫ Mou ♫
It seems
♫ Modorenai ♫
That we've come
♫ Tokoro made kita mitaida ♫
To a point where we can't return anymore
The theme of this song makes you look so lame...
However, no one from
the music industry called...
So tonight, in order to save
his reputation, Yamasaki will try again.
Yamasaki Produce
It's been 2 years since the last one,
this is the 2nd installment of Yamasaki Produce.
Yamasaki Housei
Downtown
Matsumoto
Hitoshi
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
I totally forgot about it.
It's been that long?
We've all done the filming
this time already, right?
Yes we have.
I am just done...
But seriously,
we've actually done three songs
Downtown
Hamada
Masatoshi
this time.
Right.
A solo for Endo-san.
Yeah.
Then a duet for
Matsumoto-san and Tanaka-san.
Yeah, what the hell was that about?
Wow awesome, that'll be incredible.
Tanaka Naoki
Cocorico
And lastly, all 5 of us,
with Hamada-san being the main lead.
Well, we did it together...
Yamasaki made the song and lyrics
And they're all really good songs this time.
Last time, unfortunately...
none of them became CDs
You say unfortunately but we had no plans to make it into a CD anyway.
No, but seriously Matsumoto-san,
your song last time...
was good--
♫ Mou ♫
It seems...
♫ Modorenai ♫
That we've come
♫ Tokoro made-- ♫
To a point--
You're going to continue singing!?
There was a bit of a laugh
from the staff so just leave it.
Man, that's lame.
It really is...
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todokanai ♫
The music this time is also awesome.
Oh?
First up, Endo.
It's a solo, right?
Endo up first.
Oh this one, I've not
got a clue about it.
Me neither.
This will be the first time we see it.
So I'm looking forward to seeing it.
During Rehearsal
When I think of your song,
my creativity just goes crazy.
Oh, well I'm very thankful to hear that.
Yeah, right?
So, can you listen to this once?
Um... wait, just before that,
last time...
it was death metal right?
Right.
Wow...
This is...
Last time, you were awful.
Yeah, honestly...
You were like the Endo who I hate the most...
I hate that kind of Endo...
So this time,
it's totally different, seriously.
Really?
I want you to sing this seriously
and to hear your beautiful voice.
Ah, OK.
So let's take a listen first.
♫ Wasurerarenai Summer ♫
That unforgettable Summer
It's actually Japanese this time.
Like properly...
Yeah.
Huh?
♫ Enoshima no umi ja wakareta onna ga hitori ♫
There was a girl who had just split up,
alone at Enoshima, by the sea
♫ Namida misezu ni ♫
Without showing tears
So listen and make sure you understand
it's about summer--
Wait a second...
It's a medley?
Yep.
But I've only just listened to
this song for the first time ever...
and I have to do a medley suddenly?
Yeah, so...
In my head
you've already released loads of hit songs.
Wait a minute...
I don't get the meaning of this.
Seriously, in my head I just
started imagining loads of things
and I got loads of good ideas for songs.
So I got the best part of each song,
so instead of one song
I combined all of them together.
Look at it like this,
I'm betting all this on you
Seriously...?
Yamasaki Produce
Endo's Solo Medley
Endo will sing: The Summer Medley.
Summer Man 2006 Medley
Lyrics & Composition by
Yamasaki Housei
Sung by Endo Shozo
That outfit...
That Unforgettable Summer
I have definitely listened to something similar to this...
♫ Wasurerarenai Summer ♫
That unforgettable Summer
What the hell is with that?
I was just doing as I was told.
That Girl of Enoshima
♫ Enoshima no umi ja wakareta onna ga hitori  ♫
There was a girl who had just split up,
alone at Enoshima, by the sea
♫ Namida misezu ni ♫
Without showing tears
This is...
♫ Yokohama no machi ja furareta onna ga hitori ♫
At the Yokohama district,
there was a girl who had just been dumped
You've definitely heard similar,right?
♫ Kasa mo sasazu ni ♫
She didn't have her umbrella up
♫ Aruiteru ♫
And she kept walking
Oh, so he sings a number of songs.
Awesome, right?
Truly.
It's going to change here again?
What's going on?
The Sea '06
How do you do a medley when it's new to you?
♫ Aoi umi ga yonde iru ♫
The blue sea is calling out to me
Like, no one knows these songs in the first place!
♫ Koyoi nami no you ni tsuredasu ♫
Tonight, it moves me like the waves
♫ Yaketa suhada mabushiku ♫
My burnt skin shines bright
♫ Ore no mune o kogasu ♫
It starts a fire in my heart
♫ Summer day ♫
Summer day
To You Who I Love
♫ Ameagari ni minareta michi o ♫
The road which I was
used to seeing after rainfall
The way he sings is hilarious.
This is so screwed up!
♫ Oh yeah ♫
Oh yeah
You're just impersonating that person...
♫ Nanimo kawaranai ♫
With you who has not
No, this is Endo.
Really?
Yeah.
This is something you do like 10 years down the line!
♫ Kimi to ♫
Changed at all
♫ Sutekina omoi o mune ni ♫
I can say finally for
the first time with all my heart
♫ Oh yeah ♫
Oh yeah
♫ Hajimete ieru ♫
With all my heart
♫ Sukidayo ♫
That I love you
That Unforgettable Summer
♫ Ichido kagiri no Summer ♫
That once in a lifetime Summer
Once in a lifetime Summer...
This is hilarious
Just this part, I like...
4 songs...
That Unforgettable Summer,
The Girl of Enoshima,
What's this? Sea '06
Sea '06.
To You Who I Love,
And lastly--
The very last thing he said...
the, "Once in a lifetime summer,"
that's a bit depressing...
No, not at all, it's to encourage people to
enjoy their summer and Endo
got his message across.
And, as everyone was saying before
I was just suddenly given a medley.
The lyrics are fine, right?
You didn't rip it off from someone, right?
No, of course not.
I'm sure I've listened to something similar.
Yeah, me too.
Well yeah,
you've heard of Enoshima right?
You've heard of the place
Enoshima, that's all.
That's what you're confusing...
Really?
Even the way he sang...
Um--
Half way through, it became
a bit like Sen Masao...
Right, shall we go to the next one?
Tanaka and Matsumoto's duet.
We did...
This is something
you wouldn't normally see too.
That's true.
Yeah.
During Rehearsal
This is really pop-like.
Pop?
It's really pop, watch, from here...
This is pop?
The prelude is really long.
So as a present,
I'm allowing you to do what you want.
I don't want a present like that...
Not yet, not yet, see?
Oh, really?
Damn, this is gonna be difficult.
It really is long.
It's so long...
♫ Kare ni wa saikou ♫
It's great for him
♫ Dakedo oreni wa kodoku dake ♫
But I feel lonely
♫ Imanara zekkou ♫
Now is the time
♫ Kore ga saigo no chansu da ze ♫
This is the last chance
Umm....
* Popular pop music duo (1997 - Present)
Maybe you should ask Kinki Kids to do this...
I think...
I don't think we can do this...
No, no.
You can.
This is awful.
Is it?
My face is gonna go so red.
This is a song for someone in their teens.
That's right, young...
Like someone young.
He's in his 30's, I'm in my 40's...
But it's great that you understand this song
is meant to be sung by someone in their teens.
That's exactly how I made it.
Tanaka, when you sang last time
Yeah.
that was a 16 year old girl.
♫ Itsumo omou no ♫
I always think
It's Noppo-san.
♫ Anata o soba de kanjita toki ♫
When I feel you next to me
I know...
He's gay?
But this time, you get to sing as a boy.
I guess you're right.
So even that, he's closer to being himself.
Yeah, you are.
I guess so.
Oh man, this is tough.
Honestly,
I want to see a Matsumoto-san
we've never seen before.
Like really pop.
♫ Kare ni wa sai... ♫
It's great for hi....
I do want to see that too.
It's so funny.
Damn, this is tough.
I really do.
This is hard...
Just do it like facing forward.
OK.
No seriously,
I will just make you do it all day...
No we are trying our best.
Seriously, we are.
More like this!
Wait, how?
Like this.
This looks awful.
Stop trying to make it sound like this is cool...
And then what?
Like this, you know...
Youngsters do this all the time.
There, yeah, yeah.
Oh like this?
Right, right.
That's it, yeah, yeah!
It's so different to what you said before...
Is it really like this...?
Just do it like that.
After this
Matsumoto & Tanaka's song!!
Matsumoto and Tanaka perform their duet,
Yamasaki Produce
Matstumoto & Tanaka's Duet
a hot tune to reach your heart.
Lyrics & Composition by
Yamasaki Housei
Sung by
Matsumoto Hitoshi
& Tanaka Naoki
Woah, incredible...
This was really hard.
This is something else.
It was so hard.
This is awful.
This is something else.
There was 30 seconds of this.
30 seconds!
Just the prelude?
♫  Kare ni wa saikou ♫
It's great for him
♫ Dakedo oreni wa kodoku dake ♫
But I just feel lonely
♫ Imanara zekkou ♫
Now is the time
♫ Kore ga saigo no chansu da ze ♫
This is the last chance
♫ Kurueru youna dancing de ♫
With my dancing that will make you tremble
♫ Otosu ze konya wa ♫
I'm going to drop it tonight
♫ Itetsuku youna hitomi de ♫
And with my steely gaze
♫ Kimeru ze konya wa ♫
I'm going to score tonight
♫ Kitto kiminara ♫
You can do it
♫ Tobou ze futari de fly away ♫
Let's fly away together
♫ Megasameru made ♫
Until our eyes open
♫ Touku ♫
Far away
♫ Ikouze futari de run away ♫
Let's go, the two of us, just run away
Wow, this is something else.
I know.
♫ Wasureru made ♫
Until we forget
This is so lame.
It really is...
♫ Motto motto♫
More and more
♫ Tobou ze futari de fly away ♫
Let's fly away together
♫ Megasameru made ♫
Until our eyes open
♫ Touku ♫
Far away
♫ Ikouze futari de run away ♫
Let's go, the two of us, just run away
♫ Yume ♫
Until we make
♫ Kanau made ♫
Our dreams come true
Holy shit...
This is so lame.
This really is.
Incredible!
Sure is.
You moved a lot...
Actually, we did it 3 times because
we screwed up a couple of times...
Ah, I get it.
Right.
My body is so tired...
The prelude was 30 seconds...?
Yes.
And you had to do that dance the whole time?
Right.
I thought whilst doing it,
"Someone has done this kind of dance before."
* Comedian Sakata Toshio (1967 - Present)
Sakata Toshio, right?
No, I don't think so.
It looked similar.
I saw him doing it backstage.
The reason why the song
is written is ridiculous too.
So, if we like have an example...
For example, if we have
Endo and Chiaki, married
and then,
Matsumoto falls in love with Chiaki.
Yeah.
So he falls in love, and this isn't a song
between Endo and Matsumoto as rivals
it's a song about me and Matsumoto-san
where I am supporting him to win...
That's so complicated.
It is complicated, there's 4 people in this story.
What the hell is that...?
And when you include
Sakata Toshio, there's 5 of us.
Yeah, and it becomes complicated.
There's no reason to
include him anyway, but...
"I'm going to score tonight,"
and you reply, "You can do it."
Yeah.
Until our eyes open,
Away and away, More and more.
That's the point.
We tried our best.
And I can't believe that
the producer of that song watches it and
says, "Damn, that's lame."
I can't believe that either.
No...
I couldn't tell when I was watching it live--
I feel so betrayed.
Yeah...
That shouldn't be aired on TV...
I'm really sorry about that.
Yeah...
That was shit!
You're going to admit it?
I mean, that will happen,
but the last one...
This is the one you really like, right?
I do, this song
Yeah, he loves it.
really got good reviews...
From who?
I listen to it in my car,
my daughter remembered
this song and she sings it.
I genuinely cried...
listening to her singing it
Well,
I'm sure your wife was
crying about you crying...
I was really touched.
For a different reason...
The final one
has Hamada in it.
Well, we did it all together
and Yama-chan was part of it too.
I wonder how this one turned out.
Anyway, let's watch it.
OK.
If you would.
During Rehearsal
Seriously, I want us to go on Kouhaku.
No, before that,
it's not even going to be made into a CD.
Wait, does it have to be sold as a CD
for Kouhaku to consider us...?
Well, yeah...
It's about the sales.
But anyway, sing it
and they might really love it.
This song is really awesome.
The song?
Yup.
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todokanai ♫
Oh stars that shine so brightly
So embarassing...
♫ Hikari kagayaku hoshi-tachi yo ♫
That our hands cannot reach
It is...
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
Somehow, always, please envelop
♫ Yowa sugiru bokutachi o ♫
Us who are too weak
Damn, we are really weak, huh?
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
Somehow, always, please envelop
This is tough.
Re~~~
♫ Kujike souna bokutachi o ♫
Us who are discouraged
You go into the next line so quick.
Yeah...
I think that will be impossible.
The last part, right?
So Hamada-san will go...
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
Somehow, always, envelop
Oh, so it goes up.
♫ Kujike souna ♫
Us who are
♫ Bokutachi ♫
Discouraged
♫ o ♫
What was that?
Oi, oi!
You go up again?
* Popular music artist Hamada Shogo (1975 – present)
It's Hamasho...
It goes up?
That was a bit...
Hamada-san does
♫ Bokutachi o ♫
♫ Bokutachi o, bokutachi o ♫
So they go...
Right, right.
Yup.
But seriously,
how weak are we...?
Yeah, we seem so weak...
We are though, when we are alone,
we are a 5 and we are good.
And then this is the first part.
So, "masen," that one
that Tanaka cannot forget
And then...
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todokanai ♫
Oh stars that shine so brightly
♫ Hikari kagayaku hoshi-tachi yo ♫
That our hands cannot reach
We're like drifting
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
Somehow, always, envelop
I know right?
Don't raise your hands.
♫ Yowa sugiru bokutachi o ♫
Us who are too weak
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todo... ♫
Oh stars that shine so bright--
I'm in the center?
This is weird!
That can't be right.
This is seriously messed up!
My position changes so much.
I can't be in the middle surely?
So Tanaka finishes in the middle?
Can we change it?
And this last part,
before, I was singing it with everyone
but it then suddenly
becomes a Hamada solo...
That's really annoying to remember.
OK then here, if all of us sing
then it should be fine, right?
And then Hamada says
the, "Somehow, always..."
Exactly, let's just sing this altogether.
Then why do we have to do this here?
So, just the part it goes slow
at the end, I will sing by myself.
Oh, the final part?
Shall we do that then?
That way...
it might be better...
Well, if that's the case,
the "somehow" part--
Stop complaining!
No, seriously, it's disgusting.
Let's just make the "somehow, always"
part just Hamada's thing here...
Oh, from the start?
Then the "Oh stars..." we sing altogether.
Shall we do that?
Well, put bluntly...
I don't give a shit how we do it...
Umm... he just told you straight out.
No, this is great.
You can't say that.
It's fine.
I just realised, I am getting
so into singing this song!
Yeah, I know!
I was thinking,
"Damn, he's getting into this."
Damn, I just realised, you guys
must be thinking I'm so up for this...
That's good!
No, it's just the planning is crap.
After this
The ultimate song is born!?
Yamasaki Produce
"Not an Errand Boy" Theme Song
Gaki no Tsukai
Lyrics & Composition by
Yamasaki Housei
Sung by
Gaki no Tsukai All Stars
Please watch Tanaka at the end, by the way.
♫ Ah Yamazaki-san ♫
Ah, Yamazaki-san
♫ Futari miageta hoshizora ga ♫
The star filled sky that we gazed upon
That's the kind of face you were making...?
♫ Kinou no you ni kono mune ni ♫
Still rings in my heart as if
That's funny.
♫ Utsushidasa rete imasu ♫
It were yesterday
That's a hilarious face.
♫ Ah Matsumoto-san ♫
Ah, Matsumoto-san
♫ Ano hi chikatta yakusoku wa ♫
That promise we made that day
You are as well!
This is funny
You are so into this!!
♫ Kokoro no hikidashi ni ♫
Has been shut in the
He looks so happy
Right?
I thought I would
do this part properly
Look at you,
you're so into it!
♫ Shimatte imasu ♫
Drawer of my heart
Of course...
♫ Taisetsu dakara ♫
Because it's important to me
♫ Sabishi sugite ♫
I am so sad
♫ Hitori ja arukenai ♫
I cannot walk alone
♫ Kodoku ni obieru boku o ♫
I shake all lonely
♫ Hanasanaide ♫
Please do not let me go
♫ Dakishimete ite ♫
Please hold me tight
♫ Ah Tanaka-san ♫
Ah, Tanaka-san
♫ Sagashi mono wa arimashitaka ♫
Did you find the thing you were looking for?
Me too...
You just don't know what kind of face to make there, right?
♫ Kokoro no sukima umeru no wa ♫
You probably know the way to
♫ Kitto wakatte iru hazu ♫
Make your heart whole
Look at him, only guy wearing a hat.
♫ Ah Endo-san ♫
Ah,Endo-san
Here comes Endo...
♫ Kimi no heya de katatta yume ♫
That dream that you told me in your room
♫ Hohoemi nagara unazuite ita ♫
You smiled whilst you nodded
♫ Sono yasashi sa o ♫
That kindness
♫ Wasure raremasen ♫
I cannot forget
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todokanai ♫
Oh stars that shine so brightly
♫ Hikari kagayaku hoshi-tachi yo ♫
That our hands cannot reach
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
Somehow, always, please envelop
♫ Yowa sugiru bokutachi o ♫
Us, who are too weak
♫ Ah Hamada-san ♫
Ah, Hamada-san
♫ Karada ni wa ki o tsukete ♫
Please take care of your body
That's hilarious.
♫ Itsumo tsuyo gatte bakari iru kedo ♫
Even though you always try to act tough
It is.
♫ Wakatte imasu wakatte imasu ♫
We know, we know
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todokanai ♫
Oh stars that shine so brightly
♫ Hikari kagayaku hoshi-tachi yo ♫
That our hands cannot reach
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
Somehow, always, please envelop
♫ Yowa sugiru bokutachi o ♫
Us, who are too weak
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todokanai ♫
Oh stars that shine so brightly,
♫ Hikari kagayaku hoshi-tachi yo ♫
That our hands cannot reach
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
Somehow, always, please envelop
♫ Yowa sugiru bokutachi o ♫
Us, who are too weak
He's so into it...
He is.
♫ Dou ka zutto ♫
Somehow, always
♫ Tsutsunde kure ♫
Please envelop
♫ Kujike souna bokutachi o ♫
Us who are feeling discouraged
Watch Tanaka...
Does he do something?
Yeah, he does.
Eh...?
Woah...
What are you doing...?
What the hell were you doing?
We said "hands up."
What were you doing?
What happened?
Well, um...
I got a bit carried away...
You do get touched really easily
by these kind of things...
Yeah...
In Yoshimoto, you get touched the most.
How is this, you all sang your feelings and...
isn't it great?
We don't usually sing and have to move about.
Yeah
I don't know...
It was great, it's a fantastic song.
This was your favourite song, right?
Yeah, I want to get onto,
I want to get onto Kouhaku.
You all went on?
Right!
Yeah, we did.
Except you.
We've all been on it...
Right.
Right?
I can't accept that.
But even if we get
onto Kouhaku as a 5...
Uh-huh, yeah.
It will be like, "Ah, Ezure-san..."
What?
Assistant Director
Ezure
He's got nothing to do with this though!
He's not wearing a belt today...
Oh yeah...
That's right.. He looks like a Kagamimochi.
* Mochi placed one on top of another
Amazing...
We can do it.
They won't be interested...
Music producers who are watching this,
we WILL release a CD!
We WILL?
No we won't.
Anyone who really wants us to release it with you,
we will await your call.
Everyone, bow your heads.
Please consider us!
What if Tanaka and my song gathers interest?
The duet?
Yeah.
Yours and Tanaka's one?
Well yeah, let's just release it.
Release it and see how lame it is...
Producer...
Let's watch it once more.