TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai: World Famous Heipo's - Comedian's House Sleepover!!
Yay!
So, today is about our Heipo
Known as World Famous Heipo,
30 years of experience as a producer
Yamazaki Hosei
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Heipo
Hamada Masatoshi
He's not producing jack though
Well, that's true
- 30 years already?
Even the others told me it feels odd to have the producer here
Really?
I think he's been odd from the very beginning!
And I think we have to fix this oddness somehow
I see...
We'll have him stay for a night in a comedian's house
PLAN GOAL
Heipo will stay for a night in a comedian's house
so he can learn how today's comedians are thinking
Are you kidding? We've done that?
It's true
I'm not kidding, that's true
- You know what? I want him to appeal more to our audience
Oh, I see
Makes sense
Do we really want to see him die a midget?
I'm not a midget!
- We don't
World Famous Heipo
Sleepover in a comedian's house!!
A 56-yo single man is going to have
a sleepover in a comedian's house!
(Release date)
Yoshimoto Kogyo
Today's host...
Mr. Yamada Yoshi
And today, Yamada Yoshi from the duo "COWCOW" is going to make this Heipo plan happen
A certain place in Tokyo
Heipo, dressed in a tuxedo, heads towards Yoshi's house
staff) it's here
This one
- Again?
Is he inside this messy house?
Don't say that
We arrived at Yoshi's apartment
No it's fine, it's ok
You're always complaining
That's true, he complains a lot
Should I ring it?
- Please
Why shouldn't you?
Excuse me?
Aaaah! Sorry!!
You had a dog?!
Nice to meet you--
Yamada Yoshi (36 yo)
I'm-- going to stay here for a night, but...
- Oh, sure
I hate dogs...
I'm Yamada from CowCow
I'm Heipo, the World Famous
- My pleasure
Thanks for having me for today
Is that his surname?
Excuse me
From this moment on, we'll film with the cameras set inside the house
From now on, we'll monitor Heipo with the cameras we set in Yoshi's house
Excuse me...
- Please, come in
Living room
Such a nice house
Nah, it's really small
- Whoa, two dogs?!
Is someone else there? Like, your wife?
Right now she's...
- Groceries?
She went out to pick up our son
Ah, you have children?
- Yes
daughter
son
wife
COWCOW Yamada Yoshi's family
Yoshi's family is made of four people, with his wife and two kids
Yoshi's house - layout
daughter
son
wife
Front door
bedroom
kids' room
Living room
And Heipo will live with them all, until tomorrow morning
That's incredible
It's just a normal house, is it ok for you?
- No it's fine, I'm sorry for disturbing you
Aaaaah!! Dog! Don't get close to me!
- What's wrong with you?
Oh my, I don't like them
Do they know that?
- They did
You sure it's ok for you to stay here?
Yes, I want to see the stuff you comedians are hiding
- Sure...
The stuff? What?
What was that? A dirty joke?
That's not it
- That sounded suspicious
Woof
Ah!
Oh, good morning
- 'Morning, oh
Thanks for having me here
- It's a pleasure
Thanks, so pretty!
I'm Heipo, nice to meet you
- Nice to meet you too
Wife
Miss. Mayo (29 yo)
She's Mayo, my wife
And you little miss... boy? Miss or boy?
I'm a boy
I thought he was a girl!
His name is Sakuharu
Sakuharu (4 yo)
Nice to meet you, Sakuharu!
He's so cute
I'm glad he doesn't look like you
That's rude
You're such a dick...
He looks like his mom
What was that for?
Sorry for the disturb
- Don't mind
Off to a bad start
Your wife is so young
She turns 29 this year
- In her 20s, huh...
Kids' room
I'm single so... she looks so fresh to me
Do you like kids?
That's a tricky question
- Oh, is that so?
A tricky question?!
To put it simply, he hates kids
Don't say that!
They get really mischievous as they grow up
That's true
Aah, seems like he's having fun... ooh, so much fun...
The hell are you sayin'?
That's what a kid does
- In kansai dialect, too
He really likes soccer
A lot of kids do, actually
Wanna play soccer with him?
Soccer? How do I play it?
Saku-chan, let's play soccer
- How do we play it?
Go there, Saku-chan
Kick it over here
Like this?
Oh shi-- it flew!
Amazing! What a nice kick!
Come on man, it's from a 4-years old...
- I'm ready here
Eh? What's this?
This is our cat's...
It's our cat's toilet
- You have a cat too?!
It rarely shows up
Do you like having pets? I'm no good at all
I used to be a pet groomer
I see... a pet groomer... and what is that?
Come on...
It's like a barber for dogs
Ah, a barber for pets, I see
- For dogs, cats and such
This whole day ain't gonna be easy!
So hot!
What?
And I jumped over it...
Woof
I'm home
Welcome back
- Hi
Right, his daughter
Nikori (6 yo)
She's Nikori
Miss Nikori?
I'm Heipo, nice to meet you
Nikori-chan? Eh? she's not nikori-ng that much!
*nikori = smile
- That's her
What the hell, man?
Haha, she's just tired
- She's nervous
I bet she hates him
The entire family is now together
And now, CowCow Yoshi's family is all together
He made such a bad first impression
- I had no doubts
Can he spend a whole day with his children and dog!?
But can Heipo spend a whole day, surrounded by things he dislikes?
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION        shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
FOLLOW: FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI ~ TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
WANT TO SUPPORT? YOU CAN:
- DONATE ON KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
- BECOME A PATRON ON PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
,.,AND GET EARLY ACCESS TO RAWS, SOFTSUBS & UPDATES!
Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
World Famous Heipo:
A major accident while taking a bath with the kid!
And that you do this...
Now that the whole family is reunited, Heipo starts to communicate with the kids
Heipo establishes a contact with the children
What's this?
I must say, it's a wholesome view
You use it like this
Like this?
Yes, true
- Mh
Mayo appears holding a cat
He's irritating
Oh, here's the cat
- Here it is
Ooh!
That scared the hell out of me
Are you kidding me?
It's just a cat!
No way, it's just a cat
What's wrong with this house?
There's nothing wrong with it
stickers
Wait for me
Aaah!! That scared me
Eh?! What-- what's that?
Is there something? What? Eh? Wha-?
It's just a sticker
Ah, a sticker...
I thought it was a bug or something...
She likes stickers
I see, she likes to place stickers around
It's fine
You two should get closer, don't you think?
He's so cute!
You really think so?
You're lying, aren't you?
She's so cute too! They're both so cute!
Did Heipo overcome his dislike for kids?
A victory over his dislike for kids?
Excuse me...
Can I smoke a cigarette inside here?
- Actually here...
We don't smoke inside
It's dangerous
Should I just go outside then?
Of course, you dumbass
Alright then, I'm going for a quick smoke
stickers
He's full of stickers!
I'll be back soon
Just a few minutes
He ran away
I wanna go to Heipo's house!
- Whaaat?
He's interested in Heipo
Heipo's house...
- What a turn of events
Heipo is having a smoke break in the waiting room for the staff, in the same building
Cigarette break in the staff room
Oh man
- He looks tired
Man, I'm beat up, this is gonna be long
Always complaining...
Can you stop filming for a bit?
Over and over
- As always
Sure
hidden camera footage
I'm gonna be fed up with it if it's gonna last for that long
We're talking about someone's kids here
I'm already thinking I want to go home
staff) for now just stay for a night
A night!? That's so long!!
As expected, he doesn't like kids
Heipo's dislike for kids won't be cured so easily
(staying since 3 hours)
And it's barely been few hours
- Right
Do you guys play games more than you watch TV?
Well, we play a lot
So that's how it is when you have kids...
Hey, you want me to help?
What's wrong?
- It's fine, I'm almost done
It's time for dinner
Come sit here
Dinner menù
stir-fried meat and veggies, sweet & sour burdock root, meat & potato stew
salad, boiled black soybeans, miso soup, white rice
Looks delicious
The table is full of hand-made delicacies made by Mayo
Looks really good
Why are you holding a Mitsuya Cider?
- It's 'cause I like to drink it when I eat
But why a cider?
No one drinks it when eating
- I do
- It's time to eat!
Did you all eat already?
Not yet, we're about to
We're all eating together
Let's dig in
I'm so hungry
Take as much as you want
- Sure
This is handmade, right?
- It is
Doesn't seem to be enjoying it...
- He's so irritating
I'm sorry to say this but...
If there's an animal nearby I can't eat at all!
I'm afraid their hair is going to fly around...
- Don't worry about it
Will you-- p-please, I'm-- I'm going--
I'm going for a quick smoke
- Sure, but, the food...
He barely eat anything and leaves
Are you kidding me?
You can't do that!!
I wonder why, huh?
What?
I wonder why
I dunno...
The staff goes to see Heipo
You ruined the atmosphere
- He's right
I can't eat in a place with so many pets around!!
Let's go back to Yoshi's house real quick
- No way, I'm done
He's heading to the staff room,
shaking off the staff's orders
He goes back to the smoking room, ignoring everyone
hidden camera footage
This is unbelievable!
Let's go eat at a ramen place or anywhere else,
I'm not eating anything in that house!
Heipo refuses to eat inside Yoshi's house...
Heipo firmly refuses to eat in Yoshi's house
because of his pets
hidden camera footage
He stuffs his stomach with some cup-noodles
- Really?
No way...
This is unbelievable
The kids are so lively too, how can I sleep in there?
Cup noodles and onigiri?
(staying since 4 hours)
It's 7:30 PM
And she made all of that...
- I like those
Heipo returns to the room, full thanks to the cup noodles
Back home with a full stomach
He won't let go of his Cider
He's making me so angry
He joins them without eating anything
Are you ok? You sure?
- Poor family...
It's so pitiful...
- Really
He didn't even help putting stuff in order
Niko-chan does her homework
Time for homework, huh
Heipo, if you want you can go take a bath first
- Oh, sure
Can I go first..?
- I've prepared a change of clothes for you
Heipo is the first one to take a bath
So disrespectful...
- He should have refused
Why before the others?
Hot!
I don't think it is
Don't cool it down
- But it was hot!
Really?
- Yeah
That mark is so small!
Guess it does the job
- So small
He gets inside the bathtub
without washing himself first
- Take a shower first!!
- So filthy!
Why did you get in like that?!
That's not how it works
I hate him!!
Careful--
I live alone,
that's how I do it
- It's not the same here!
So hot...
Come on, give me a break...
Look how much it's overflowing
Stop it already!
Oh!
- What's going on?
Saku-chan joins the bath
It's hot here, you're ok with it?
- Let him in
Hot, isn't it?
It's hot...
Right?
You want me to cool it down a bit?
Oh! What's wrong?
- What now?
Whining
Everything ok? Saku-chan?
- Too hot?
Is it hot?
It's too hot for him
Mama? He says it's too hot
Is he ok? Ohh no way...
- It's fine, don't worry
Take it easy over there
Too hot for him, huh?
A 56-yo man at his wits' end
What was that for?
Are you ok, Saku-chan?
Wanna put some ice in? Sure
Saku-chan comes back again
- I see what he's doing
Makes sense, right? Since it's so hot
Let's pour some cold water in
It's a bit slow
Can you wash Saku-chan for me?
Sure thing
- I'm counting on you then!
They choose to censor Saku-chan too
Saku-chan's mark is bigger than Heipo's
See?
- You're right
Is it good now? Do you usually do this with your dad?
How is it? Are you ok?
He said it's good now, it's fine
Is that a toy gun?
- It's a toy
Gimme that
Doesn't that camera break if it gets wet?
It does, don't get it wet please
- Like this one here
As a producer, he's
concerned about the cameras
I'll shoot it over there, ok?
- What is he talking about?
Over there
- I'll aim there
Ah! You wet that other camera!
Oh shi-- swipe it up, please! It's a camera!
- You're an idiot!
What the hell are you doing...
I didn't see that
What are you doing?
It wasn't on purpose
I'm sorry, but we can't wet that
But you're the one who did it!
- Well... right
Trying to blame someone 50 years younger
Sorry for that
Feels nice, huh?
- What now?
Now I wash it, like this
- That's right
Good boy, well done
- What am I watching?
Now we do the shamboom
What now?
I don't know anymore
- This is fun
No, on my head
On your head?
- He's saying he wants a shampoo
You want me to use the water gun?
No!
- No?
Of course not that
- He's dumb
Use this one
Really...
A 56-yo man making a
4-yo kid angry
Hurry up and wash his face!
- It's not hard
I'll do the head now
Here comes the shampoo! Close your eyes
Not inside his nose!
- That hurts
You made him cry again
- What are you doing...
Crying out loud, again
You can't just do that
Something's wrong!
- It's so obvious
How many times are you making him cry?!
- It wasn't on purpose!
- You're the worst
I'm sorry
The same scene again
Sorry for that
- He hasn't cleaned up the camera yet
- Heipo made him cry again
You're right
But that brought a change inside Heipo's heart...
What now?
(staying since 5 hours)
Changed into home clothes borrowed from Yoshi
Let go of that, Saku
I didn't wash his head properly
'Cause that was a shower
I wanted to splash it from above, but...
You didn't even try
Excuses...
- All inside his nose
Wife and husband go out for a while
Yoshi and Mayo go out, leaving the three at home
I'd be worried
- Me too
The size of this is so big...
- Mom and dad...
Heipo and the kids
Said they went out to get a futon
- A futon?
Yes
But you were taking a bath before
Juice, please
This?
This one
- You want it cold?
Be careful, ok?
- I'm coming
Is it good?
Is this yours?
- Probably
You can have it, it's ok
- Hey
What's your futon, Heipo?
She said mama and papa went out to get it
Do you know AKB?
I know them!
I wanted to meet you, I wanted to ♪
No time to rest here, huh
- I love you, I want you ♪
I need you ♪
- Incredible
They're getting along, though
- Yeah
I wanna drink the chilly one
- Sure
Here's the chilly one
That can't be good for him
♪ Heavy Rotation
Here comes
Wanna dance? Come on, show me!
- She's not dancing
The pounding love in my heart is a heavy rotation!!
Haha, cute, very cute
Quick intimacy with the kids
Heipo is slowly shortening his distance with the kids
- Doesn't look bad now
- He's doing great
Scary
Eh? Is it?
Woof
Oh! Ah!! What--
Husband and wife came back
Oh it's you, sorry
I'm going to bed...
- Goodnight
It's bedtime for the kids
It's time for the children to go to sleep
I'm going out for a bit, ok?
Heipo goes for a cigarette break
Again?
What's his deal...
hidden camera footage
Oh boy, I've grown attached
to them in many ways
It happened
It's such a nice family!
His human side is showing
- It happened
Heipo's statements have changed
That's nice of him
(staying since 7 hours, 30 minutes)
It's now 11:00 PM
Heipo came back in the room without complaining, and not only that...
What's wrong? Aren't you sleepy? Come on, sleep
Oh! He's touching it
- I got used to it
He overcame his dislike for pets
He doesn't hate pets anymore
- Amazing
Now I'm completely fine
- And while Mayo arranges his futon...
While Mayo arranges his futon...
He checks Niko-chan's homework
This should be fine, but raise the
bar a bit and I have no clue
Are they sleeping with me? Oh, so cute
It's fine, I'm used to them by now
- Are you sure?
- He's really fine by now
Sorry for that, and thanks for everything
It's our pleasure
Goodnight!
- 'Night
Do you wanna come here in my futon?
Can they come here?   - Of course!
I see
- With you?
Look, they want to
- You're right, incredible
Take care of them, ok?
Ok but--
They took my place now
Really?
- Yes
- Didn't you hate that?
- It was fine
I guess I'll sleep here
They're following him
What? Now you're coming up?
They love him
Do you wanna be with me?
Here it comes, how lively
You're so friggin' clingy~ so cute~
Pick one!!
That's so un-cute!
- The hell?
coming up
A sudden change in Heipo!!
It's just disgusting!
(staying since 15 hours)
After sleeping surrounded by dogs,
it's time for Heipo to wake up
Saku-chan woke up early
Huh? Oh
Everything ok, Saku-chan? You woke up?
So early!
When is kindergarten time?
- Do you know?
I dunno
Ah, you don't...
Oopsie daisy
- Oh my
Pure love
The two spend some quality time
together before saying goodbye
I haven't taken a bath
- But you did yesterday
I did not
You did, with Heipo! Remember?
- And you said "it's so hot!"
Right?
The look of a father
His smile is the same smile a dad would have
(staying since 16 hours)
Only a few minutes left until it's time to go
Sorry for not eating with you yesterday
It's fine
And why you're ok with it today?
I'm ok now
Eating just fine
How does he eat?!
You're ok now?
- I am, yes
Heipo is going home after breakfast
Are you ok with it?
If so, come back tomorrow too
Maybe tomorrow I can't
What? Unexpected
And when it's time to go
an unexpected turn of events...
And now it's finally time
Time to say goodbye...
Goodbye kids!
- It's time for him to go
Saku-chan, you're going to school?
- Not yet
Nico-chan, a squeeze and smooch?
Sure
Let her hug you
Squeeze and smooch?
- It's getting wholesome
- Oh my
Squeeze'n'smooch
It's Saku-chan's turn now
- Incredible...
- These kids are so nice
Here goes
Oh my god
Thanks so much for having me
Come back anytime you want
Thanks, I'm kinda moved to tears
Thank you for coming
- Thanks to you
Bye bye!
Oh boy
Bye bye!! They're all there--
Heipo!!
- Bye! Be nice!
This feels good
It's incredible
It's heart-breaking
I had no idea I would feel like this about it
What is it? Those kids were so... adorable
How should I say it...
I really want to have kids now!!
- At first I didn't really like kids that much...
Now I want someone to make kids for me!!
All the love and happiness you gave me ♪
At first he didn't like kids...
Are overflowing inside me ♪
Huh? What are you doing? Oh my
How will I ever be able to give you back ♪
But Niko-chan and Saku-chan changed him a bit...
All this time you spent on me? ♪
Mom and dad kindly watched the whole thing
Let's head back home now, let's go home ♪
Errands
What's this?
I went out to buy groceries
And now a stroll
- Whose dog is that?!
On this purple-colored street ♪
Strolls
Did you steal it?
Whose dog is that?
Hold my hand and let's go back home ♪
After a single night...
You went for a stroll with them?
- Ohh, nice
He said "I want kids now"
You're my only sweet love in the entire world ♪
That was so unexpected
- Yeah
And I'll always, forever, everyday ♪
Be thankful for that ♪
Thanks for everything, Yamada family
Such a nice family you meddled in, huh?
- Really
Yoshi's family is great
You even got your own smooch at the end
I was surprised
- So, what do you think about it?
I had no idea I'd get that
It made my heart go thump-thump
I wonder why
Who are you, Ikko?!
So in the end was it really hard to say goodbye?
It really was
I'd love to meet them again
That's so nice, right?
- Yes
They're adorable, really
- Well...
- Make up your mind!
Are you crying or not? I can't tell
I don't know either!!
Are you IKKO's stand-in?!
Go ahead and just cry, it's fine
- I get it
Nice! Go on, cry it all out!
They're so cute!!
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS TRANSLATION BY SHION MORE EPISODES ON SHIONNOTSU
KAI.WORDPRESS.COM | LIKE MY FB PAGE FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI OR FOLLOW ME ON T
WITTER FOR UPDATES TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | YOU CAN SUPPORT THIS NO-P
ROFIT FANSUB PROJECT BY MAKING A DONATION ON KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI OR B
Y SUBSCRIBING TO MY PATREON PAGE AT PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI, TO GAIN EA
RLY ACCESS TO RAW + SUBS FILES AND EPISODES SCHEDULE BEFORE EVERYBODY ELSE!!
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FANSUB PROJECT, MADE BY FANS FOR OTHER FANS.
Really now?
What's going on?!