\fnBebas Neue
Gaki no Tsukai presents Walk until you meet a Celebrity!!
Shut up
Jiyugaoka!!
Hamada Masatoshi
Tsuketitei Housei
Endo
Tanaka
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Shut up!
Your voice is so loud
Whoa! A thief!
An old thief!
An amazing mask huh?
That's right!
It's scary
Ok, I'll take it off
Ah, Its really cold huh?
Yea
It's cold huh..
Where are we today?
Jiyougaoka
Jiyougaoka huh...
A lot of people come here
Yes
Last time we found people right?
Yea, Last Time
In Naka-Meguro
We found 3..4 people right?
Yep, Yep
We found quite a bit
Walk until you meet Celebrities
Naka-Meguro Prefecture
Last October, The series was in the Naka-Meguro Prefecture
Oh thats it!
Yea, What is it?
FOUND YOU!
Akiko Hinagata
They found 4 celebrities in an hour and a half!
Masaya Nakamura
Sekiguchi Mandy
Last episode produced the best results!
Search Area
Today's area is...
Meguro Ward's Jiyugaoka!
Street's with the looks of other countries
In the heart of a Top-class residential area
If you walk around Tokyo you will meet celebrities
It's time to investigate if that's true!
When I say "Jiyugaoka", What do you think of Tanaka?
Tanaka, Those clothes!
Amazing huh?
It's amazing!
So wide!
The end continues to get wider
I don't understand!
What's funny about it?
You dont understand?
It's just so wide!
Yea, I get that but
What's funny about it?
It's something a girl would wear
It's amazing. Seriously Tanaka
It's like a mini-skirt
They can't stop the walk until they meet a Celebrity
Search Rules
If they can't say their name it's    NOT CLEAR
If they get the no good from the producers   NOT CLEAR
There is no time limit!
Now, The curtain for the Challenge rises!
There's a lot of pretty people here
Madame-like feeling
Pretty huh?
There's no one here that doesn't stand out you know..
There's no one here with rice on their sleeve
The Symbol of Jiyugaoka procceding through the Green Road
Jiyugaoka
I want to find someone already
Seem's like Model's come through here
It seem's like there's Clothes and Accessory Shop's this way
Oh, That's what it is
Why did you buy these clothes?
What's so weird about it?
These part and the sleeve's
It doesn't reach
Seriously?
Really?
Honestly?
Your
unfashionable
WHAT!?
What do you mean!?
What does he mean?
Please, Wait a second
Imagine if a Gaki no Tsukai Regular was called Unfashionable!
Right now...
Do you think there could be
people getting a hair cut?
In Jiyugaoka huh?
Yama-san, Do you mind checking?
A haircut huh?
Alright I'll go!!
There's probably someone in there
It'll be amazing if we find one here!
The way he went up the stair's
was really light huh?
Amazing right?
Yamazaki has entered the hair salon
I'm looking for celebrities but
There's not one having a haircut right now is there?
Anything would be good
What if we run into a 5 celebrity group?
A group like Ayaman JAPAN would be good huh?
You have to say their
names though
What are their name's again...
5 min's later
Huh, This is unexpected
It's been a while huh
Isn't it good if its been a while?
Yea, I think so
It seem's like he found someone huh
Seriously
Wait, we have to try and call the Producer's as well
HUH!?
Wait wait, Is someone there?
Is it over!?
Is this the end already!?
This quickly?
Yea, but this is normally difficult
If nothing was there He would of be coming back already
That's right
Subbed+Timed by : DatCheesus
Visit
www.gaki-no-tsukai.com
/r/GakiNoTsukai
for more Gaki No Tsukai Content
Continue Walking until you meet Celebrities
In the Hair Salon
The rest of them are waiting on Housei who's in the Salon
Why is he taking this long
If he's getting a frizzly perm
I'll Laugh
And Then Finally....
No way
No one is there
No one is there BUT
Alright, Let's go
Wait a minute!
No one is there but?
No one is there BUT
"A lot come"
Men and Women
Celebrities come a lot
Ah, So That's it
Wrong time huh
It's a timing problem huh?
Search Time 14 mins
It's a timing problem
Will they be able to meet a celebrity? Only God knows
I don't know...
Strange huh...
|I wonder if Anmika is here
Said they shop at Jiyugaoka
Oh, is that so?
But do you know their names?
Definitely not
But It seem's like Jiyugaoka has things like General Stores
Yea your right
But Here...
There's not that many people here huh?
Because of that
It's easier for celebrities to come through the crowd
Headed to the North Entrance Shopping Area
There's no street that a car can't go through huh..
When I met Iyo Matsumoto, It was like that as well
How long has it been since then?
Hmm.. It's still been
32...
Because im 40~♪ right?
That was a long time ago
About 15 years ago
Iyo is 57!!?
According to the Staff's information
Before the walk started
Masakiyo Maezono was here
Seriously?
So it's that sort of place huh
A place where Maezono would be..
Maezono is good huh...
Eh, Where are we going
Arriving at the Shopping Area
It's been 30 min's since the start
They arrive at a shopping area of General Stores and Boutiques
Isn't it strange
Search Time 30 Min's
This look's like a place celebrities would go
Do Celebrities come here?
No one's there
Yes they do
They come?
Who come's here?
Nene Ohtsuka
Didn't I say it was a sure thing!!
Nehe Ohtsuka is good huh...
This street
The smell?
smell's amazing
Ah, It's good huh
The 5 get excited knowing that someone they know was spotted
Expectation's rise from the eyewitness report
There's not that many people Yama-chan
Your sure we can meet someone at this place?
Probably not
Didn't you say to go this way?
Supposing If it's a miracle
Amazing Sunglasses and
mask
Really?
She seemed full of Rikaco but I was wrong
I dont think she would ride a bike
Searching Time: 52 Min's
Detemined, The walk continues
There's no way they would come to pray at a Shrine
Were there Celebrities in there?
None
None huh?
No one
There's absolutely No one
He completely
lost all motiviation
What?
This is bad huh
It's something like
The atmosphere
is completely gone
Seem's that way huh
Time continues to pass
With the circumstances turning bad
The 5 are running out of reluctance
Over there, There's shops like
Uniqlo and Gindaco
Ah, I wanna eat at Gindaco
Wanna go eat at Gindaco?
Somewhere like Gindaco
I don't think Celebrities would eat there
Can I drink Hot Whiskey with my Gindaco?
Headed toward's Gindaco Peacock Shop
With that, They head towards the Gindaco Peacock Shop
Kobe Croquette
seem's delicious
Buy!
The surroundings are filled with delicious things
All around
Having a Meal at the Croquette Store
First before Gindaco, They go to the Croquette Store
Ready to eat?
Yes
At last, they go to Gindaco
Excuse me
One of these and
Negidaco as well
Delicious!
There's no celebrities?
They continue to search while waiting for their Takoyaki
Honestly, I'm getting excited if were going to find someone
If we can't find anyone
Can Endo look for them by himself?
*Because Endo is the youngest*
Wait, I don't understand
In the beginning
it was supposed to be Your Program
Originally there was a talk between Yoshimoto and Japan TV
"What program should we do with endo?"
At that time I was a shitty amateur
Takoyaki ready
Thank you very much
Your eating from here huh?
Gimmie one
Now that they have Takoyoaki
Headed Toward's the South Entrance again
Once again, They head towards the south entrance
Endo Still has
Crust from the Croquette stuck to him
So where are we going
OGO
Pteranodon Endo
At that time
I really wanted you
to say OGO
He won't ever say it
Your aiming to make it a popular phrase
You definitely have to use it everyday
Like what?
Is your zipper open?
OGO
Good, Good...
Can I speak frankly?
I hate OGO
Did someone drop their wallet?
OGO
They've arrived at the Green road for the second time today
Searching Time: 1hr 18 min's
Temporarily taking a break
The five enjoy some good Takoyaki
Spread the Mayonnaise equally already
I'm spreading it!
It's not a delicacy anymore
Your doing it completely wrong
This place is too upscale for this crudeness
Ah, I thought that was Muji-san
Muji-san huh
Looked a lot like him
At the place we bought this earlier
They said that
Sekai no Owari Fukase came
Yea but you wouldn't have been able to say his name
Yea
(Celebrities) Will they come or not
Bang
Eat one already!!
Im looking
for Celebrities
Endo is your fly open?
OGO
No, My fly is good
Your voice on that OGO was tiny
What time is it?
OGO
I don't understand OGO
What do I do?
But your OGO  was interesting
When you checked your fly it was the worst but
This OGO  was good
Matsumoto
On your shirt
Takoyaki
flew from
Housei's mouth
OGO
When we did this in Daikanyamacho
I got bird shit on my hat~
Searching Time: 1hr 31min's
After taking a break, A fresh start
Once again they approach the fashion area
This is bad huh
Really bad
No sign's appearing
Now, There are no sign's of celebrities
Have you been on TV?
No I haven't
Have you welcomed any Celebrities?
Yesterday
It seem's there were some
The Search Continues
In order to break-down the situation
Were already at the station huh?
This place isn't showing any sign's of celebrities huh
The Situation isn't changing
Searching Time: 1hr 52 min's
It's been 1 hour and 52 min's since the start
After Walking around, The green road once again
Look we came around in a circle
This is the main street huh?
Yes, The main street
I call it the Celebrity Street
I see
This is the Celebrity Street?
Celebrity Street
Yet There isn't a single Celebrity
To sum it up for everyone
This time
It is the end of the program
Until Next Week!!
See ya~!!
Were ending the program like that huh?
Resuming the Search
Mustering all their willpower
The resume the search
Determined to Find a celebrity
They continue to search
In store's as well, They search every nook and cranny
No one
Searching Time: 1hr 52 min's
There's no one
Well, This is impossible
In front of the station there's people coming and going
You want to go there?
Yea
Gravure Idol groups and other's
Ah, I see
Actor's that go back and forth as well, Use the trains
Because there's a lot of cars
I see...
Jiyougaoka is probably filled with people like that
Aiming for Celebrities that use the train for commuting
With this, They squeeze down on the Celebrities that commute from train's
Ambushing at the Ticket Gate
They play to Ambush them before the Ticket Gate
We've come to the station
Searching Time: 2hr 27 min's
How is it, Is anyone here?
How many are here?
None...
Squeeze out one!!
They'll begin to come out
It's gonna be a big haul
"A Big Haul"
They won't escape
Definitely!
They definetely won't escape!!
Believing in a Possibility
They believe in a small possibility
Determined, they continue to wait
The man who vote's to quit is....
In the group
There is one man who is cutting the mood
There's no one
Even at this place
Express Train at 39 Min's
The local at 41 min's
They'll come on the Express
They won't come
The people that come on the next express
will be Exposed!
Yea!
They're gonna be found out!
Were gonna expose them huh?
They won't come
Ah, The train's here
Alright!
It's gonna bring some fresh celebrities
The long awaited Express Train
The express train they placed their thought's on
Squinting their eye's
The result!?
They stare at the passengers!
No Celebrities Found
It's strange
No, It's not strange
The next one,
If there's no one on it, Let's Quit
Yea, But well...
I guess we have no choice but
to wait till the last train
No Way, No way, No way
Honestly,
After the next train
We quit
The next Train is also empty as well
Now what?
Can we go back for the last time to the "Celebrity Street"?
I think we should go to the Train "Rotary"
If we do that, Can we wait for the Express at 7:49?
I think we should go to the Rotary
I said the Rotary is no good!
But the Express at 7:49
At the rotary
Can we wait for the Express?
The rotary is no good!
Let's wait for the Express at the Rotary
Let's try it once
Because there's another exit from the station right?
Alright let's try it once
Let's wait for the Express at the Rotary
Going to the Rotary at the North Entrance
Cocorico
Downtown and Housei
Separate and Search
With this, Cocorico and Downtown and Housei split again
Yea but you know..
Searching Time: 2hr 50 min's
I guess we have no other option but to trust the atmosphere
Meanwhile, Downtown and Housei
Is that person
a celebrity?
Which one?
The woman in the white
Excuse me, Are you a celebrity?
Is that person
a celebrity?
Which one?
The woman in the white
This one?
Yea
Excuse me, Are you a celebrity?
I'm trying to be
Oh, Your trying to be?
Can you just come over here for a bit?
We found one!
Eh?
They're Celebrities
Seriously?
I'm only trying to be...
She's trying to be
Ah!
So that's it!
This is OK right?
It's not OK
It's not OK?
Please work hard at it!
Sorry about the inconvenience, Good Luck!
Thank you!
Understand
Something
Hopefully one day we can perform together!
They must find a Celebrity Otherwise
If all 5 of them don't find a celebrity they know
The Walk wont end
The walk wont end!
What the hell are Cocorico doing?
Their Job's!!
Enough Already!
Searching Time: 3hr 04 min's
3 hour's have already passed since the start
I told you it was impossible
In 3 minute's an Express Train come's one time
The Railway Schedule was detailed
We understood Jiyugaoka's Train's
I see
Don't you understand? This atmosphere
On Ougon Densetsu
Ougon Densetsu is Cocorico`s show
We only do these kind of thing`s
From now on
we'll do this program
Alright I know
Let's Try going back to the "Celebrity Street"
Over there you said there was no one so we came here
Then we went to the station and no one was there
The station was useless so we went to the rotary
Ahh, It's difficult
Then Now....
And now he want's to go back to the Celebrity Street
YOUR NOISY!!
Headed toward's the shopping mall Fullel Uizu in Jiyugaoka
Come on let's shoot the ending
Downstair's!!
Up!
Upstairs huh
Downstairs
It seem's like
people are going up huh
Yea
Even though it's the second floor there's still people
Continuing to search for Celebrities
Hamada's Spirit is running out
The Search within the store continues
And then!
Now what?
Of course until the end
The rule until we find one
I as well
want to push through and find someone
And you Yamazaki?
Well, I sorta...
Say it clearly!
It's impossible
I want you to lend me that
There's no other option but to decide by majority
The people that say it's impossible?
Yes!
And you Cocorico?
Of course we want to continue!
I
want to try going to the Rotary
Stop with that!
It's impossible!
You like the Rotary huh!?
You only want to go to the Rotary!
There's just something about the rotary
Is this the last time?
This is the last
Really the last time?
The Last Rotary
Don't say it's the last one!
Do you want to quit?
For the time being
I want to do something about this
It's extremely cold
And If we got you a scarf?
Please Let me think about it
Think about it?
You can't do it?
Let's get a scarf
Let's go
Buying clothes to prevent the cold
With the end not in sight, to prepare for the battle
They buy clothes to protect them from the cold
I gotta take a piss
Where's the toilet
Hamada goes to the toilet
With this, Hamada goes to the toilet
During this time the rest prepare for battle
Preparing for Battle
Until then...
There's seriously no one
Excuse me,
Staff
Hamada
went home
Seriously?
Hamda did?
Hamada gave the mic to the staff and ran away
What now?
Should we continue?
The four at a loss for word's
The 4 are at a loss for word's at
Hamada running away
The remaining 4 continue to search!!
Ran
Away
After Hamada ran away from the others
The 4 continue to walk until they meet a celebrity
Once again they go to the rotary
The four of them after obtaining protection
They Once again, Go to the Rotary Entrance
Searching Time: 3hr 38min's
Finally, 3 hour's and 38 min's have passsed since the start
Will the remaining 4 be able to find a celebrity?
There really is no one huh
♪One more time, One more Chance - Masayoshi Yamazaki
If we dont find someone in an hour let's go somewhere
As I thought,
Celebrities are rare huh?
Right?
It seem's that way huh
♪If I lose any more than this, will my heart be forgiven
♪How much pain before I can see you again
Its really cold
♪One more time, please don't change the season
Are you a celebrity?
No
♪One more chance we cannot choose our next place
Wait, Check this place
♪I am always searching somewhere for you
No one
No one?
Theres really nobody
♪Opposite of the house, the other side of the alley's window
Oh, Here?
Oh, This place
It was fun during that time huh?
♪Even though I know you won't be here
Eating the Crockett's and thing's
Yea
♪If my wish is to be granted, please bring me to you right now
♪Betting and embracing everything
♪To show you there's nothing else I can do
Time Elapsed
4hr's 47min's
4 hours has passed in the Big Search
The decision
The four have decided
The Decision is!?
Since it can't be helped, Let's call Hamada
Calling Hamada
They report the situation to the deserter Hamada
Hello, Hamada?
Right Now,
Umm...
We're at the Rotary
He said "Haah?"
Ah, Hello?
I was just thinking but...
There's no one we know at the rotary can we quit?
We couldn't find anyone
And We're not happy
He hung up!
He's in a good mood eating sushi
No way
"Hahahahahaha"
So he was laughing?
He was laughing
Then it cut off
Subbed+Timed by : DatCheesus