Tonight's Gaki No Tsukai: Ikinari Steak Part 2
Eating by yourself is OK too
Is that so?
Right now, I suddenly -
Shit I said suddenly
They must cooperate to finish 200g of steak at each location
They aim to eat at all 37 stores along the Yamanote line
There's a prize of 100,000 yen if they finish
But if anyone gives up, the challenge ends
Whoever gave up must pay for all food eaten thus far
In the last episode, they made it past the 7th store
Will they be able to finish?!
They arrive at the 8th location, the Kamiyacho store
Here we are
This way, let's go
This poster here,
It's from that game
This store appears in Yakuza 6 (on PS4)
This store shows up in the city
Sorry for the wait!
Excuse me,
This is tenderloin
Yay!
They enjoy the exquisite steak
They've all eaten 280g of steak so far
They aim to keep eating
You guys said you like the Tenderloin right?
Man, you keep on eating that corn
You really do like it
The corn lover Endo is in charge of the side dish
Let's do something with this corn
A corn episode for Endo
A corn episode?
You do love it
Isn't that nice?
They quickly finish, and head to the next store
I'm so full!
It's alright to say that
It just matters if I keep eating
That's true, just keep eating
Yeah it's alright
Exactly
I was hoping someone would say they aren't full though
The 9th store,
They choose the steak for the 9th store
Endo-san, here you go.
Tenderloin, get the tenderlong
You said tenderlong
It's "top rib."
Top Rib steak
Side?
Green beans
I can't hear you
It's alright actually, no need to shovel corn down Endo
It's not that kind of episode
I like corn, but...
In order to eat as soon as they arrive, the staff order over the phone
How would you rate your fullness?
For real
Around 5
5 or 6, I can still eat
Hosei-san?
I'm not sure honestly,
The burps just won't stop
Then you're at 10!
It really feels like we're at the end
In past eating marathons, Hosei has given up twice
Hosei's perserverence will be necessary to finish
At the 9th store at Daimon, they enjoy a rare Top Rib
The most delicious part of a rib roast, the top rib is seared
The flavourful fat is now a burden on the 5
I want something from the side menu
You want to order?
I want something to wash this down
You always order tea right?
Yeah I do
They can order anything from the side menu,
But they must finish what they order
How many ml is it?
I can't see
350ml
They enjoy the steak here as well
Endo wait Endo hold on- Stop please
Endo Endo Endo!
Look at this, look!
What's wrong?
It's so different!
It's the same amount of meat
Don't compare with him
Yeah I have to eat the green beans
Rare is delicious
Rare!
Is it becoming difficult?
Not really
Hosei you should drink some of this tea
Yeah you can drink it if you want
Nah, I'm gonna finish this
Oh he did it
Hosei-san, congrats
Finished!
Let's head to the 10th store
However, the unfair portions have defintely affected the members
Next Hosei chooses for the 10th store
Tenderloin, please! Shit!
What is it?
Top rib!
Hosei-san, how should they cook it?
Cook it....
I want corn for the side though
Decide on corn first
Making Endo eat all this corn,
Trying to get him to give up, is a problem I think
I see, it's not right
I get to serve it, right?
You get to serve it
Hosei-san, please,
Yeah, don't do that
Do you think I tried to purposely give you the fatty parts last time?
I will never forget that
The 10th store, Sanda location
This is the medium steak
Please enjoy this with the corn
Was there always that much corn?
Small pieces
Are you doing it?
My piece is so big!
I can see that massive piece for me
Mine's is big too
Hosei-san, c'mon this is wrong
Now you've started a war!
Yeah
I did it, sorry, I did
I'm only eating this, this time
At least eat the onions
Endo,
From the next store I'll eat a lot
Sorry, but just now,
Are you being serious
I couldn't even walk!
I couldn't walk!!
I promise!
I'll eat SO MUCH at the next store
Of course Endo has not just the steak, but the corn too
How many grams?
It's not the same for sure
Was the string always that tight on you?
It wasn't like that before
He's like the Michelin man
Finished!
Brilliant
The atmosphere is dampened by the weight of their stomachs
They shall have Tenderloin at the 11th store
Side?
Corn
He's a demon
Demons actually exist after all
Hosei promised to eat a lot at this store
The biggest hurdle awaits them
Ikinari Steak marathon: The 11th store, in Gotanda
Yama-chan, go ahead
You gotta catch up with us
Eat a lot, quickly
It'll be impressive to see what you can do
You gotta do this
Hold on that's not-
It really is like that
You 4 will split that?
Eh? Are you serious?
Thank you!
The 4 eat a literal bite
Hosei must finish most of the steak
A tenderloin at this point is great
You gotta show the people watching TV your eating skills
This is important
Honestly, the people watching this are thinking: "Ah, this is the ending"
Exactly
Right?
I see
They don't believe me
I'm gonna betray them
Yeah show em!
Oh I forgot about the corn, my bad
THAT'S HOT!!!
What an intricate performance
He was sticking his face forward
I'm gonna take care of this
This really makes Endo look impressive
Exactly, you gotta show off too
He went for it
There it is, the Double Corn!
Hosei shows never before seen perseverance
Endo challenges him with Double Corn
Endo is amazing
Just the tenderloin now
Today's Yamasaki is different
This is the time to persevere
Let's get past this, this is the first obstacle
I can tell his senses have sharpened
The focus is off the charts
He's crying while eating
Like a little kid
That's what babies do, yeah
He did it!
He kept his word
He's a man of his word
Unexpectdly! Hosei surpasses everyone, and is at 520g
You finished cause it was tenderloin?
If it was sirloin it would be impossible?
Yeah. Rib would've been impossible too
Time to choose the next steak
Top Rib!
Ah, top rib?
What about the side?
Can you?
stop
"Can you?" - Of course he can't!
Why would he say he can
Are you feeling really full?
Matsumoto-san, are you feeling tired?
Who?
Matsumoto-san
Not at all. Does it look like I'm tired?
It totally does
His stomach's been making noises the whole time
It seems like I'm tired?
You've got your face stuck to that seat
Tanaka-san, is your stomach fine?
Yeah, I'm fine
Right before leaving,
They were waiting for Tanaka to get back from the bathroom
What was that?
I was feeling a little sick in the car
Car sickness
Car sickness?
Why the hell do you work here then
You feel better getting off?
Yeah I feel better after I get off
What about now?
I'm feeling really sick right now
Cause we're driving?
Please don't give up cause of that
That pathetic reason
So on the No Laughing Bus?
Sick, I'm very sick
So you've kept quiet about it all these years?
I thought I would ruin the mood on set
So nice!
What a nice guy
The 12th store, Meguro Kamiosaki location
We've arrived
Let's go
Are you ok, Hosei-san?
Are you alright Hosei-san?
That was no good, Hosei-san!
It seems everyone has an obstacle in this challenge
Corn
Can't walk
Car sick
Full stomach
Drunk
They enjoy the Top Rib steak, which is exceptionally fatty
Thanks for waiting,
Where's the green beans on top?
Green beans coming up!
No no no no! That's ok!
No thanks!  We're ok!
Store person!
Even though you asked not to
We genuinely didn't do this
We wouldn't do this
They made a mistake, for real
They made a mistake?
You have to make sure to tell them, or you'll get corn
The base is corn?
Corn is the base
I totally asked for green beans though
Hosei-san finished
Just the corn left
Endo is actually so slow with that Corn
He did it
Finished!
Next, with heavy steps, they enter the Ebisu store
Here they enjoy a medium tenderloin
Sorry for the wait
A 200g tenderloin, medium
Where's the green beans?
Ah well, what can you do
I truly want some green beans!
Just take it already
They side is once again the standard corn
Now I actually don't like tenderloin
They struggle to swallow the steak
I want more!!
Finished!
The excitement from the start has disappeared
These 5 are different people than they were
And then
It sucks being the last person
Jus one bite
He's done
Just Endo's corn
It's just this footage over and over again
Is there any scene of me eating meat?
Finished!
Let's head to the next store
Let's go
C'mon let's go
I'm feeling it
5 hours since the start
They've all eaten over 500g
They've long since lost the will to speak
14th store; Shibuya's Sakuragoka location
They enjoy a well done tenderloin
The side is of course CORN!
I'm gonna die at this rate
Making me eat this much corn for 37 stores
The 5 split the steak, aiming to finish
Would you be able to eat, if it was you?
He got mad at us
Can I have the onions?
The onions are pretty good acutally
Well done is a lot
It's well done, right
(complaining about well done)
It just won't go in
Oh, amazing, Endo-san!
Is there footage of me eating meat?
Not at this store
But there's plenty of footage of you asking "Is there footage of me eating meat?"
Brilliant
What is it?
This would be a good time to finish
DownTown are at the same amount
They were classmates after all
I think this steak wasn't that bad actually this time
The vibe changed a bit
The vibe changed
This is a good time to finish
There's a lot huh?
That's what everyone is thinking looking at your plate
3 minutes have passed since he touched his food
Is there a time limit?
A time limit for each store
No, there isn't
10 minutes could pass by like this
From my POV, that's just a straight up cow!
A total cow
So, how about 1 more minute?
Is 1 minute alright?
Okay, start!
If he can't do it, we'll take that as a give up
The cow is back
Just a cow
A battle to finish the challenge
Hamada's fork has totally stopped
We're done here
No good!
That was close!
We didn't make it to 37 stores
This one mouthful is impossible
You couldn't get that last bite?
Hamada has to pay the 27,416 yen cost from his own pocket
The total is amazing
That's a lot of meat
That's not the point of this challenge!