The 1st Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende! chiki chiki
Let's all sing as Nagabuchi Tsuyoshi~!!
This is, you know...
an ill-advised project, I believe.
I feel like the staff forced this onto us.
Well at last year's "No Laughing"...
Endo started singing "Tonbo" (Dragonfly).
And then Matsumoto sang it.
- I did adlib and join.
I also joined in a little and this is based off that.
A moment in last year's "No Laughing".
Endo, sing us a lil' somethin.
♪ Clop-clop on the asphalt, as I walk...
♪ I can hear my footsteps every time.
♪ For me, I wish...
♪ I could have stayed...
♪ so I had hoped for~.
♪ But I see people say one thing and do the other...
♪ and now I find myself counting the nights.
♪ As I pretend to sleep in the darkness...
♪ of which, I cannot escape.
♪ Would've given my life...
Matsumoto
Endo
Tanaka
Hamada
OUT
At the time, did Yamasaki or Tanaka think of joining in?
We did!
"But what if I sing over!?"
I was debating that.
That's what we're gonna be doing today, without singing over, with 10 people.
Tanaka, this is gonna take a lot of effort.
Can we do this?
Here it is.
When are you going is the question.
The last one, we all sing!
The last one we all sing and the real singer will probably come out.
Extravagant!
We all know he's not showing up.
So in addition to us, we invited these members. Come in!
Since this is a challenge of 10, we invited these 5 to participate.
(Junichi Komoto, Shoji Tomoharu, Nozomu Iwao, Kazuhiro Fujiwara, Takafumi Inomoto)
There's no order here.
There's no, "Who's top?". It's with us 10.
So let's get this challenge started!
A review of tonight's rules.
"Tonbo" is split up into 10 parts.
The 10, will sing a verse when they think it's their time.
If they can sing it without singing over anyone, they clear!
Can't stop until you finish the song!
We attempt an unexplored challenge!
How's this gonna work?
Endo was saying he'll be top, tho, huh?
Yea, yea, that'll eliminate one verse.
That's true.
Alright, let's do this in one-shot!!
We're already starting?
♪ Clop-clop...
Oy!
I wanted to go.
Why you guys so eager?
Isn't this my part?
You don't have dibs!
Yea, I thought this would be Endo-san.
You did, right?
It sounded like everyone was singing.
I wanted to sing, too! I held back.
Let's just go! Let's just go!
So no Endo-san then, right?
That's irrelevant!
For real, there's no Sr./Jr. or if you're a Nagabuchi fan or anything like that.
Let's go!
♪ Clop-clop on the asphalt, as I walk...
♪ I can hear my footsteps every time.
♪ For me, I wish I could have stayed...
♪ so I had hoped for.
♪ But I see people say one thing and do the other...
♪ and now I find myself counting the nights.
♪ As I pretend to sleep in the darkness...
♪ of which, I cannot escape.
♪ Would've given my life...
Wait, wait, wait...
Don't you wanna sing this part!?
I wanna sing this part!!
No, you should wait a little longer!
You don't need this part.
- Matsumoto-san, if you could...
No, no, this is Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende so...
That's what you're thinking?
I wish you could've sensed that.
Read his mind!
Wait a minute. Lemme clear my head, one time.
Yeah, let's do that.
Let's reset.
Reset.
No! No! No!
Are you kidding?
I said, "Let's reset!", didn't I?
I said, "Let's reset!"
I thought you were fooling around, Hamada-san.
- Sorry. Sorry. For real.
I really meant to reset so I thought I should hold back.
Meaning starting from zero?
Zero! Starting from scratch!
No eye-contact, ok?
Still, after that...
♪ For me, I wish...
♪ But I see people say one thing...
Who was it?
It wasn't that easy to clear.
Failures continue to mount.
Let's get the first half.
Yea, let's do that.
Wait a minute!
You're not going at all!
- At all!
Yea, this guy ain't going at all!
What are you aiming for?
Where do you want to sing?
No, I'm thinking of going, but...
I can't find the right time.
You have a keen eye!
Cus you're not going at all!
C'mon, man.
We gotta keep this moving.
We're gonna move it!!
For sure!
♪ Clop-clop on the asphalt, as I walk...
♪ I can hear my footsteps every time.
♪ For me, I wish I could have stayed...
♪ so I had hoped for.
♪ But I see people say one thing and do the other...
♪ and now I find myself counting the nights.
♪ As I pretend to sleep ...
Who was it!?
No, it was me and...
You two sing over a lot, Endo and Shoji.
SINGING OVER IS FINE!! YOU JUST SING!!
You can sing over?
- You can't sing over!
You can't but...
NOT EVEN ONCE! NO, "WHAT ARE YOU DOING!"
Do you not know this song?
For now...
wanna try get to #5?
For now, k?
I'd like to clear, "Big Tokyo".
- Exactly!
Let's try and clear that, at least.
For now, they challenge to clear #5!
♪ Clop-clop...
Figured I'd give it a shot.
Did I give off that vibe?
I had a feelin you were gonna go!
I thought it was about time.
I know it's not gonna get that big a laugh.
This I know!!
We just need one of those!
Let's continue! Let's continue!
Let's get to 5! First, let's get to 5!!
Up to 5, right?
♪ Clop-clop on the asphalt, as I walk...
♪ I can hear my footsteps every time.
♪ For me, I wish I could have stayed...
♪ so I had hoped for.
♪ But I see people say one thing and do the other...
♪ and now I find myself counting the nights.
♪ As I pretend to sleep in the darkness...
♪ of which, I cannot escape.
♪ Would've given my life...
GOOOO!!!
GOOOO!!
DIDN'T YOU WANNA GO!? SERIOUSLY!?
Seriously!?
No, no, I thought this was Non-chan's.
Non-chan already went!
I didn't know that!
But you were the one, who wanted to sing this part, so there's no excuse.
No excuse.
Honestly, I don't wanna sing this part.
You said this was, "Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai".
But I thought someone from here was gonna go.
Raise your hand if you want, "Big Tokyo"!
Actually, I do.
This many!?
But Non-chan, you sang already.
Yea, I did go earlier.
I didn't even know Non-chan went.
There's no distinction, so I can't tell.
I want you to make it so I know it's you.
Express your individuality.
- OK, I understand.
Let's get to, "Big Tokyo".
- Let's get to, "Big Tokyo"!
Yea, up to there...
That's a lot of pressure.
That's why I said this is gonna be harsh.
♪ Clop-clop on the asphalt, as I walk...
♪ I can hear my footsteps every time.
♪ For me, I wish I could have stayed...
♪ so I had hoped for.
♪ But I see people say one thing and do the other...
♪ and now I find myself counting the nights.
♪ As I pretend to sleep in the darkness...
♪ of which, I cannot escape.
♪ Would've given my life, for that place...
♪ that booming city, Big Tokyo.
♪ With my worn out boston bag...
What happened!?
These two.
Sense it.
You're neighbors, you should sense each other.
I wanted to sense him, but I couldn't see him while turning.
Shoji could see.
Right?
Was it on purpose?
It wasn't on purpose. I just wanna sing soon.
We all wanna sing soon.
You haven't sung yet.
For real!
I do wanna sing!
Dishonest. That's dishonest.
Not dishonest. So I can sing for real, right?
There's this sense of, "Maybe it's okay if he doesn't sing" so...
I'm so nervous now.
It's fine, right? I can sing, right?
If that's the case, then that would be bad.
Also Non-chan. The way you sang...
Isn't that a little too expressive?
You said you couldn't hear me.
Which are you? #3?
Right now, I'm #3. I mean I've been recently singing.
Recently?
I dunno. It's not like it belongs to me.
That's not the case!
It sounds like it's yours.
I just meant #3 is my most common.
But we did clear, "that booming city, Big Tokyo."
- We did! We did!
So the question is #6.
Alright, let's get the next one!
Let's get it!!
♪ Clop-clop on the asphalt, as I walk...
♪ I can hear my footsteps every time.
♪ For me, I wish I could have stayed...
♪ so I had hoped for.
♪ But I see people say one thing and do the other...
♪ and now I find myself counting the nights.
♪ As I pretend to sleep in the darkness...
♪ of which, I cannot escape.
♪ Would've given my life, for that place...
♪ that booming city, Big Tokyo.
♪ With my worn out boston bag...
♪ up North, up North, I go.
♪ When I'm knocked to the ground and eating dirt...
♪ that's when my memories come to light.
♪ And that's when the truth...
Who sang #8?
No, you've been waiting for so long, I thought you were going for the hook.
That's what I thought.
That's why I went here.
Yeah, there's no hook here.
I was offering it to you.
This is what you were waiting for?
Who waits for the line before the hook?
- What'd you say?
You'd think he'd want the hook.
Don't make it seem like I can't read the situation!
That's not what I'm saying, but...
Can we take a break?
Let's take a break, one time.
This ganging up, ain't right!!
The group takes a break.
Wanna mix it up, one time?
Really mix it up?
Really mix it up. I mean...look at Hamada-san's.
Hamada is singing "Clop-clop" a lot, huh?
It's totally fine. It's totally fine.
But I think we can clear it on the next go with what he have.
Eh? Me being the hook, right?
You're gonna say it!!
And all that time waiting and it wasn't even that funny, huh?
Finally unveils, and it's flat chested.
Completely different from what I expected.
Let's mix it up, one time.
They decide to mix up the natural occurring order.
A new challenge!
(Next: A miracle for the 10!?)
Clean slate again.
Though, I would like to see one where we're ALL out, at least once.
Alright, let's go!
You all heard, right?
Well, someone has to start things off.
- Exactly.
♪ Clop-clop on the asphalt...
That's not what we meant.
Is that not good?
What the hell!
Don't you want stuff like this?
They'll think, "Wow, comedians are so intuitive."
We can read between the lines.
If we were 100, they'd keel over.
Alright, let's really mix it up.
Let's mix it up then.
Blank slate, right?
Really mix it up, yes.
♪ Clop-clop on the asphalt, as I walk...
♪ I can hear my footsteps every time.
♪ For me, I wish...
Yup, that'll happen. That's expected!
I dunno if Shoji was hesitating or what...
but his voice was super weak.
Was it?
You didn't think you'd be singing alone.
I realized, "I'm singing alone."
It tightened up!
I could totally tell!
They continue on with the challenge, but...
♪ Clop-clop on the asphalt...
♪ For me, I wish...
Consecutive failures.
Here, Komoto suggests something.
Do we have to stand in this order?
Ah, okay, okay!
I'd like to change places.
Komoto, where do you wanna go? Pick.
The only issue is the level of the mics.
- We can adjust them.
Carry our mics?
We can just take it, like this.
We're talking about the height.
- Oh, height.
You don't even know what we're talking about!
We can all do that!
We're not talking about the audio level.
We have no time!
Let's move on. Move on!
Alright, Komoto. I'll pick too.
- Anywhere is fine. Anywhere.
The 10 try a fresh new start.
They revise their configuration.
On to their 24th attempt.
This reconfiguration leads to an unexpected result.
♪ Clop-clop on the asphalt, as I walk...
With a fresh new start, they revise their configuration and attempt their 24th time!
♪ I can hear my footsteps every time.
♪ For me, I wish I could have stayed...
♪ so I had hoped for.
♪ But I see people say one thing and do the other...
♪ and now I find myself counting the nights.
♪ As I pretend to sleep in the darkness...
♪ of which, I cannot escape.
♪ Would've given my life, for that place...
♪ that booming city, Big Tokyo.
♪ With my worn out boston bag...
♪ up North, up North, I go.
♪ When I'm knocked to the ground and eating dirt...
♪ that's when my memories come to light.
♪ And that's when the truth...
No one sang!!
NO ONE SANG!!!
- Who was left?
We were doing so good!
I was about to cry!
I can understand!
That was close.
This doesn't happen twice.
8 and 9 and we woulda been done.
Back to square one.
Z-Zero?
That was a good one.
I was surprised when I was singing by myself.
Everybody.
No good!
We used up all our luck earlier.
I don't think this "Tonbo" is possible.
As Matsumoto predicted...
did they run out of luck?
They continue numerous attempts, but...
they find themselves stuck on part 1!
♪ Clop-clop on...
Let's go.
Aren't you singing over everybody!?
Now you're singing all of a sudden.
Alright, let's go!
♪ Clop-clop on the asphalt, as I walk...
♪ I can hear my footsteps every time.
♪ For me, I...
Nobody went with him.
But you'll go for the "Clop-clop"!!
I was thinking about goin, tho.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Natural. Go natural.
We can do this!
(Next: A shocking conclusion for the 10!?)
Natural. Go natural.
We can do this!
♪ Clop-clop on the asphalt, as I walk...
♪ I can hear my footsteps every time.
♪ For me, I wish I could have stayed...
♪ so I had hoped for.
♪ But I see people say one thing and do the other...
♪ and now I find myself counting the nights.
♪ As I pretend to sleep in the darkness...
♪ of which, I cannot escape.
♪ Would've given my life, for that place...
♪ that booming city, Big Tokyo.
♪ With my worn out boston bag...
♪ up North, up North, I go.
♪ When I'm knocked to the ground and eating dirt...
♪ that's when my memories come to light.
♪ And that's when the truth...
♪ hits me right down to the bones.
♪ Ahhh~
♪ the happy...
♪ dragonfly~, oh, where...
♪ oh, where...
♪ are you...
♪ flying off to~?
♪ Ahhh~
♪ the happy...
♪ dragonfly~ Look!
♪ Sticking out his tongue~
♪ and laughing.
We did it!
(10-Man "Tonbo" achieved!!)
(Time: 1 hr 24 min, 38 attempts)
How come!?
How come?
How many times?
38!
38 times, 1 hour 20 minutes!
We did well, didn't we!
How? How? How?
We just got better at it.
- We sure did!
Man, we're gooood!
Job well done!
Thank you!