[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
Hot!
Damn it!
That was hot!
My god!
It hurts so much!
Shake! Shake! Shake! Shake!
Ouch!
Let's go!
You bastard!
Let go.
Thank you for being here today.
Thank you for having me.
The beginning of this season was like the debut of a porn actress, wasn't it?
Like, "Did you have a good sleep after?".
Isn't that amazing?
If you think about it, porn actresses would have sex after those scenes.
I realized how hard they must work.
And today we're talking about that, right?
-I mean, we're not talking about porn...
-Right.
We've been building up our audience during these past three seasons.
And the response has been huge this time around.
That's right.
Did you ever anticipate this reaction from the public?
Well, whenever I start something new I'm not really as conscious of it as people may think.
I never thought I was doing anything that incredible.
I only thought of getting some laughs.
So I was never worried about the show at all.
Since it's a new show, you could do some new and bold things, right?
Well... But you know, I...
I don't really know about that.
But whenever we do comedy in places like this (Streaming Services),
we end up thinking of stuff we're not allowed to do on TV.
But you end up being too conscious of TV.
And you also get fettered by it.
Instead, we should just focus on making a funny product.
And even on TV, all we need is good comedy.
Documental, start!
It started.
Oh, it's finally started.
Let's play nice.
But I feel like the world has changed their opinion on shows in streaming services.
Right...
I didn't really know how Amazon Prime Video would turn out either.
But it has clearly changed, hasn't it?
The atmosphere, I mean.
Yeah.
I think it has.
Right...
Season 1
Began Streaming on November 2016
What is the hardest thing about doing Documental?
The hardest thing is going on the offense.
Ready, go!
Maybe it's just the nature of our work...
But whenever you try something new, you always get questions.
And at times you can't help but to laugh at that.
Nice to meet you, I'm Yuriko Koike. (EN: 1)
Nice to meet you.
You're going to Toyosu, right? (EN: 2)
No, I changed my mind.
What?!
Really?
Yes.
Where, then?
Jakuzure. (EN: 3)
What's wrong?
You're better off going on the offensive.
But it's also much more risky.
This is so embarrassing.
You're already laughing!
Is this really a documentary, or is it a TV show?
Could you talk about that?
Well...
I do read the reviews, you know?
But there's some people that take it way too seriously.
Ehm...
And I always think to myself, "You guys are taking this too far"
But in a sense it's also a TV show.
It's entertainment.
What's wrong with Kinoshita?
Yamamoto is laughing.
He's still fine.
He won't laugh.
But all these comedians are really smart.
They are all working hard and going all in.
But you have to look at that place objectively.
The rules of the game will keep changing.
Who did you think was the worst of all the members?
I guess that would be Jimmy.
It's gotta be Jimmy.
I actually hadn't met him.
It's Jimmy.
I haven't properly introduced myself to Jimmy yet.
Oh...
Really?
I'm Tokyo Dynamite's Jiro Hachimitsu.
-I'm always watching you on TV.
-Thank you.
Have you met him?
It's also my first time meeting him.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kyojin, from "All Hanshin Kyojin".
That ain't right.
That's not right.
What is?
Come on.
Huh? Which is it?
I-I'm Kyojin.
Jimmy...
Are you Kyojin?
Yes.
You're not Hanshin?
It's super small.
Jimmy is about to go.
But you said "Kyojin".
Ehm... Jimmy?
Jimmy?
Excuse me, I'm gonna get up.
Sorry.
H-Hold on!
Hold it!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
No way!
Jimmy is a bit twisted, isn't he?
Jimmy, huh?
That guy might be a different species.
According to Jimmy...
He thinks he's like an air purifier, cleansing all the bad air out.
That's how he keeps the comedy in the room alive.
And the moment he's gone...
-Everyone's dazed and a bit confused.
-I see.
What is that power?
Instead of forcing a laugh,
I think it's important to first create an atmosphere where the comedians have no choice but to laugh.
And to make that happen, you have to do some crazy stuff.
That's how I think about it.
Everyone, pay attention.
Everyone.
Did you quit priesthood?
I'm quitting.
Hmm?
Everyone, look.
Yes.
Alright.
Stop being a priest.
You're already laughing.
I'm not.
Look, look.
Wha-?!
What is this?
What the heck?
I can't deal with this.
I didn't use any of my old jokes for this show.
I had to come up with all new stuff.
Even now, I still laugh at the thought of this...
When Jimmy's balls were getting sucked into the vacuum cleaner.
Let's go.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
That was hilarious.
I've never seen anything like that before.
You know, that guy is almost the same age as me.
Actually, he's way older.
But he's always been like that.
He's so funny.
But he's lost all respect from the younger generation.
He's not holding anything back, that's why he's so funny.
Hot!
That's so hot!
That was super hot!
Whenever we ask who is the worst to have, Jimmy's name always comes up.
But when they think about it carefully, it's always Cookie.
I see.
Personally, I think Kukky is really crazy.
For me it's Kawashima. (Kunihiro Kawashima, aka Cookie)
Cookie is also crazy.
So funny.
You never know what he's gonna do.
Alright, Daisuke!
Kubota.
It's a real photo of a ghost, take a good look.
Really?
A ghost?
That's just a tiny head.
That's scary.
It's super small.
It's the tiny head Master.
Isn't he just far away?
No, no, he's in front.
If it was far away, his body would also be small.
Forced perspective.
Only the head is far away.
Master Daisuke is scary.
Is this forced perspective?
Cookie is really... You know...
I'm always amazed by his existence.
Here.
Hold on, stop, stop.
They put in white ones now.
Look here, look.
It's full of silver-capped teeth.
What's going on?
Look at them, look.
He's got a bit of a different approach than the other comedians.
He does.
It's a very strange way to approach it though.
Well, he's also doing other stuff with Amazon.
I also watch it all.
But he sure is funny.
What's wrong with him?
But many people think he's nonsensical, but that's not the case at all.
He's just very good at acting like that.
He's amazing.
But you have to be amazing to be here.
You can really feel the comedic talent in the room.
All the guys that were told "you're hilarious, you're funny" in middle and high school are all here.
That's why I love this kind of environment.
I want everyone to know me better.
So I brought some old photos of me.
When were these taken?
Like, in primary and middle school.
This is my primary school entrance ceremony.
Oh, these are your memories?
Yes.
I wanted to show everyone...
My primary school graduation ceremony.
Oh my.
This is my American father.
Fujimon, please take a look.
Victor.
Professor Victor?
His name is Victor.
Please look at Victor's photo.
That's where the direction of the comedy falls to pieces.
That's right.
-It's those moments.
-Right, right.
Those moments when they're not sure of what's funny anymore.
Cause they have no input.
That's right.
You really don't know.
For real.
You prepare some jokes...
But then you figure, "This'll fall flat if I do it now".
And that's constantly in your mind.
And I think this happens to everyone.
Like...
"Oh no... This is bad, it's bad... Hold on..."
"I'm bombing!"
"If I say it now, I'll totally bomb!"
Yeah.
But you know, most of it will flop.
Doesn't matter what you do.
And coming up with new stuff after everything else is gone, is what's interesting.
You don't know what's gonna come out of it, but you just have to try.
That seriously hurt!
And being in there, you don't even know if Matsumoto is laughing, right?
That's right.
You must be feeling a lot of uneasiness while you're there.
That's right, and that goes on for 6 hours.
Those 6 hours are hell.
But you know, at the moment I don't find it difficult at all.
I mean, in terms of mental exhaustion.
Doing it is extremely enjoyable.
All of these hilarious people are gathered into one room.
So having some self-control is obviously essential.
It's like holding in your pee until the very last minute.
And getting that laugh is such a relief after holding it in for so long.
It feels really good.
Even if it isn't something funny at all.
Who was the worst of them all?
It's gotta be Daisuke for me.
We've known each other for ages so it's only natural.
Daisuke Miyagawa's eyes go like this...
Like that.
He's cross-eyed!
Looking at him just cracks me up.
Play a round of 'Acchi Muite Hoi' (EN: 4)
Sure.
That's weird.
Let's play some Acchi Muite Hoi.
That's strange.
You don't need that.
It calms me down.
I don't care.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
He's cracking up!
He's totally laughing.
He's so busted!
Daisuke...
That's another monster for you.
Ready, go!
There's still some tissue stuck in there!
Why do you have tissue paper there?
You know, the other day we were drinking...
Anyway...
He just told me to thrust at him.
Thrust?
He put his hands on the table, like so.
And told me to thrust into him from behind.
What an idiot, what's he doing?
He just started moving back and forth...
Of course, he was wearing pants.
But he was laughing out loud!
I couldn't keep up with him.
That's amazing.
You know, he's twisted!
That's crazy.
He's crazy!
What's funny about that?
Right! What's so funny about that?!
He's a monster.
But I'm always amazed at how good he is on ItteQ. (EN: 5)
Right, right.
He's completely sane.
He acts like a totally normal human.
And he's super popular with the kids.
That's right!
But on the opposite side, he's such a maniac.
I think it was Tamuken.
Tamuken!
He's also said the same "thrust me" to Tamuken (Kenji Tamura).
-And Tamuken was also cracking up
-Just like that?
It's not funny at all.
I don't really get it.
Me neither!
But it is so funny whenever Daisuke does it.
What's up with that?
I remember what it was.
We were talking about something...
And he really loves Sukeroku Sushi. (EN: 6)
So he had gone home, to his hometown...
And his mom apparently told him they were having some Sukeroku sushi.
He was so happy that his mom did this to him.
From behind.
I see... I see...
He was like "For real?!" and his mom did this to him from behind.
That's scary!
He's totally out of his mind!
All of those crazy people are gathered in one room!
It's crazy.
What was that sound?!
It's fine.
Don't worry.
Please forgive me.
They end up laughing when there's nothing going on.
That's right.
And that's also funny.
It's not funny.
Not funny.
Did you make this yourself?
I didn't.
I didn't make it.
I really didn't.
Huh?
What was that just now?!
What was that?
I think so...
One of the older people...
Don't want it.
You have to wipe-
After looking at that I also end up laughing.
And then the audience also laughs.
It's all about objectivity.
So at the end, when Cookie was pretty out of it, Kubota did an impression of Pikotaro. (EN: 7)
It wasn't funny at all.
But they still ended up laughing.
Should I do that thing? The one trending right now...
What?
Pikotaro.
Hmm?
Pikotaro... Pikotaro.
Pikotaro.
He's really popular.
I have a pen!
But I'm gonna do a boring version of that song.
Huh?
That sounds interesting.
Right?
Ba-
Nana!
Banana!
It's really bad...
That's so bad.
That's how you make it popular.
You make it boring.
Just like that.
Oh!
E!
Boobs!
Right...
That also happened...
I mean...
These days it's normal to laugh at something because of the fact that it's so boring.
Really?
Season 1's best moment must be...
It must be Jiro Hachimitsu's collection of masks.
This is the most orthodox mask.
I know that one.
I've seen it.
Me too.
Now it has hair.
Did you add that later?
Something like that...
No, no, just salt and pepper.
And some Soy sauce.
Oh no, this is dangerous.
You give up?
Oh, it's got hair now.
This one's a bit cute.
It's like a Pierrot. (EN: 8)
Right?
It's like a Pierrot.
It's quite interesting.
Watch out!
Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch!
Are you okay?
You ruined the chair!
Season 2
A Point System is Introduced
It turned into a point system, right?
I think this point system made the aggressive people even more successful.
There's quite a few people that just go on the defense.
So I had to make something to increase proactivity.
And who's gonna benefit from this?
Yoshimoto is the only one, isn't he?
Rumors of Documental's season 1 spread like wildfire throughout the comedy world.
And you hear all these stories.
Right?
I mean, comedians are super excited once things like this come along.
Simultaneously, you don't want to get invited... But if they don't invite you, it's like you're not good enough...
It's a weird feeling.
I mean, I was very honored by the invitation.
There was no way I was gonna miss it.
I'm really glad that Matsumoto called me over.
It's Koji!
See!
There's people outside Yoshimoto! (Yoshimoto Kogyo)
What's going on this time? This is crazy!
Kotoge!
It's so stacked!
It is super stacked!
This season is super stacked!
All these funny people from all over the place started coming out...
And I thought, "It's gonna get crazy".
This person's already got something shady there.
Who is it?
I was already expecting it to be a wild ride...
But when Jimmy showed up with that weird outfit, I was like, "Why's this old man here again?".
Like, "Don't come again!".
I'm glad we got some people outside of Yoshimoto to change the air in the room.
I didn't care for Kojima though...
Call me 'Oshima', just as an example.
Just as an example.
-Oshima.
-It's Kojima!
Get it?
I don't...
Just for that?
That's just a waste of space.
I'm gonna do this multiple times!
Documental is all about the 'boke' (funny) man.
You either go to 0 or to 100.
You have to go all in.
You have come crashing into the room like an asteroid.
The jokes wont' land otherwise.
Because it's a room full of pro comedians that won't laugh at just anything.
This show is not about cheap comedy, it's about impactfull comedy.
Say you have something you're sure it's gonna kill...
But then it bombs... That's so embarrassing.
Okay, alright!
-You said it yourself.
-Sorry.
Jimmy, are you going next?
Here comes Kotoge.
Jimmy, what's this?
What just happened?
-This isn't it.
-That's not it.
No way.
It's super erotic.
Taking the picture with a Polaroid is so erotic.
It's really embarrassing.
Because I have completely turned myself into the 'funny' man.
That's really hard for me.
You have to breathe through that barrier and see if you're any good.
That's where you have to go hard.
Saito did get zero points.
The things I was planning to do and had prepared for that environment,
were so much different from the reality of the situation.
That might have been the hardest and most intense time in my life as a comedian.
Yeah...
What skills do you need to appear at Documental?
Right...
Well...
You've got to be creative when everything has been taken from you.
At first everyone is a bit flustered and they waddle through most of it.
But most of their material doesn't go the way they planned.
Most of them have probably used all their weapons by the first hour or so.
The challenge comes after that.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Right!
Huh?
What's he doing?
I might have my favorites...
But I think Fujimon is always funny.
He really is.
But he's always getting bashed in the comments.
Poor guy!
And everyone's always saying I'm too lenient on him.
But I'm really not.
Yes, there's no way.
Cookie said Fujimon was amazing.
He is.
It's frightening.
Right.
Everyone else is just pretending to hear the jokes.
They're not trying to listen.
They're just looking but aren't actively trying to process the jokes in their minds.
But Fujimon is always listening carefully.
And he adds a joke here and there.
Oh, hold on.
You've got a beard...
And sunglasses...
A beard and sunglasses... Who?
You must be Kazuyuki Izutsu. (EN: 9)
You're wrong, you're wrong!
What?
Are you telling me I'm wrong?
My memories!
You just flipped it.
Today at Shibuya:
5 o'clock!
See? It must be him.
Right?
That must be it.
Today at Yoyogi:
5 o'clock!
There you go!
Everyone else is just letting him do his thing.
But he is a true comedian.
He keeps saying the right stuff at the right moment.
I think so too.
But it doesn't seem to be reaching our audience.
I also hear Goto is amazing.
And our audience seems to think so as well.
But no one likes Fujimon.
I really do hope they start looking at him more.
He's doing so much work, right?
He really is!
He's actually working so hard.
But remember when he missed one season due to another commitment?
He really is!
In our post-recording review, we found out that Fujimon added a lot to the room.
By not being there?
But I bet they're still gonna bash him in the comments next time.
I'm sure of it.
Everyone thinks the judge is too lenient on me.
How would I know?!
I mean, I hear it from time to time.
There's nothing I can do about that!
Right?
Kotoge was also incredible.
His body got all banged up.
He was full of injuries.
He went a bit too far.
Akira! Akira! (EN: 10)
Let's go!
Here we go!
Ready?
Shake! Shake! Shake! Shake!
Ouch!
Are you okay?
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
More! More!
They are super stretchy!
Fujimoto! My nipples won't go back now!
What am I gonna do?!
Well, yeah...
In the end it had to be Kotoge.
I had to laugh when Kotoge was doing absolutely nothing.
But you had an amazing look on your face. I saw you from the back.
Hold on.
Hold on!
Everyone just turned around and looked directly at Kotoge.
We were waiting for something.
But he didn't do anything.
He wasn't aiming for anything with that stunt.
That guy's beyond help.
There's no other place as funny as that.
Ouch!
It's a place where fun and tension coexist.
You don't find that very often.
But I always wonder why everyone just keeps wandering in circles.
They just can't sit still.
The ones that do actually sit down are Fujimon or Goto.
But everyone else is always walking around.
What is going on there? Why are they moving so much?
I think it's that...
I'm sorry for bringing up the 'porn' example again.
But at times, they all look like those porn doubles they use just for the semen.
They are just walking around, waiting to ejaculate.
They're just jerking each other off.
I see.
That's why they wander around.
They're just walking and jerking each other off.
I see.
This is a jerking house.
Comedian jerking house.
"I just wanted to stay in the room as long as possible."
That's what I was thinking.
The whole time...
Right.
But I was so shocked when Fujimoto was eliminated.
I thought, "What am I gonna do now?".
Kotoge vs Saito
Sudden Death with 10 minutes 57 seconds on the clock
-Hey!
-You bastard!
-You wanna go?!
I was very lucky to get Kotoge as my final opponent.
I have always admired him.
I've been in this business for about 21 years now.
But this was the most exhausting thing I've had to do.
The whole thing was hard.
Re-start.
Alright!
I just wanted it to end.
There really wasn't anything left to do.
You had to squeeze every last drop.
It felt like there wasn't even a trace of fluid inside my body.
The end was amazing, we didn't really expect that conclusion.
That end was amazing.
Kotoge said he doesn't remember what happened at the end.
Is he in trouble?
I also felt like our time in there...
It was...
It was like we were transported to another world.
The whole time I was thinking, "What am I doing right now?".
"Is this right? Or wrong?".
I didn't know if we were making comedy or not.
It was just a frantic frenzy.
What?!
Look at me!
Good! Good! That's good!
I don't care!!
Comedians might recognize how much of a feat this is.
But I wonder how normal people see this?
He was having sex.
You're right.
He thought the teddy bear had gotten pregnant.
Did he come inside?
He did come inside.
The chicken is crying.
It was the Joyman showdown. (EN: 11)
I was like, "Can I win with this?".
I was about to laugh when we did that.
What the heck?! This is so funny!
Hilarious!
That was amazing.
I was really moved by that.
That's why there's a lot of people that think season 2 was the best.
I guess it leans harder on the documentary side.
Are you serious?!
Season 3
Zombie System is Introduced
I was finally here.
I felt like I was finally here.
I had watched season 1 and 2.
After watching season 1 I thought they'd invite me, but I was wrong.
You were actually invited...
Yes, I was supposed to be there.
But that's all in the past, so let's sweep that under the rug.
I don't really know why I didn't get invited to seasons 1 or 2.
So I went out to Tokyu Hands in preparation for this battle. (EN: 12)
I went out looking for a weapon.
And what came out ahead was that funny looking pencil eraser.
I'm seriously giving back your Frisk.
Sorry, I have to go piss in between.
In the fridge.
Sure, sure, sure, sure...
Whoa, that's crazy.
Amazing!
He laughed!
-What?!
-Huh?!
It's a tiny curry-rice.
Goto is amazing.
He's a mighty opponent.
From all the comedians in Japan, he's probably my biggest weakness.
Wait, wait! Hey!
He's playing with electricity.
In Goto's case, he plays both the 'straight' and 'funny' man.
He's a competent guy.
This thing spurts out a ton of water!
Does Goto even need to say that?
He's commentating on the amount of water.
I really discovered something new.
I've never seen that kind of footage.
How far does the tip stretch?
The tip?
The skin.
The skin?...
The foreskin...
Amazing!
This should fit in there.
Oh, I think it does.
It went in.
Let go.
That pencil eraser, was that one of Goto's?
Yes, the ones he brought.
He asked me if it would fit in there.
It all happened at an unbelievable speed.
I knew it would come back out, since I had put it in myself.
But the exit velocity was something else.
And the way it came out...
It was unexpected.
And so funny.
You can't be laughing at that! You'll break it off!
I just really wanna say one thing.
People have the opinion that there's too many dirty jokes on Documental.
But you know, I really believe there never has been a dirty joke on Documental.
Those are not dirty jokes.
They think were all laughing at some 'porn'.
But we wouldn't laugh at that, would we?
Because there would be nothing to laugh about there.
Then why are we laughing at the stuff they do?
We're not solely using our nakedness to make people laugh.
Please don't judge a book by its cover.
Those are not dirty jokes.
What's this?
A racket?
So you introduced the Zombie System in season 3.
This was one of my inventions.
Well that's all up to the comedian itself.
We were all up to the task.
If you make everyone laugh, was it a draw? Or something like that?
-All the money goes back to its owner.
-That's right, no-contest.
Right...
You can also make teams with this new system.
So I think it blew a breath of fresh air into the game.
Zombie Time!
Hello!
I'm Terance Lee. (EN: 13)
You see, today I brought a teddy bear along with me.
A teddy bear.
Teddy bear, come!
Daddy...
Come!
Come, come!
Teddy bear, over here.
You're cute.
So cute!
They seem to be having a blast in the Zombie room.
The Zombie room sounds so fun!
I hope that's what's really going on beneath all the tombstones.
Zombie Time!
Here it comes!
Let's go!
Scary!
I'm fine.
Get comfortable on the back couch.
Yes.
Mister, you're gonna take a shower, right?
Oh, yes.
I prepared the Chinese dress and the massage oil.
I was thinking of performing some kind of massage if I lasted long enough.
Then, Akiyama and I were talking...
And I told him I had prepared something for "that" kind of massage.
Akiyama already knew what I wanted to do at the middle of my explanation.
He put on the Chinese dress right away.
So we just did all the "that happened to me too" jokes we could think of.
(Speaking in fake Chinese)
This will feel really good, Mister.
I thought of just ejaculating there.
But... I just ended up with a semi-boner.
Even after Akiyama's real handjob.
Can you do this?
Of course Mister, this is a freebie.
Okay.
Okay!
Alright!
Are you allowed to do this?
I really wanted to just cum there.
I figured it would be so funny if his hands were all sticky afterwards.
I've never wanted to get a boner so bad in my whole life.
I also thought it would be a bit funnier if he actually got a boner.
Akiyama didn't know he was trying to get a boner.
He was really desperate.
And Koba was well aware of that.
So he was like, "Get up! Get up!".
But he couldn't get a boner!
Both of them thought it would be hilarious if he got a boner, but it didn't happen in the end.
There might be some people using Viagra in the future.
Right?
For real.
(Speaking in fake Chinese)
Season 3
The Second Winner of 10 Million Yen.
Did you cut it?
Did you tear it up?
This is the worst.
Let's leave it at that.
It's always the same...
So you went to the finals with Kinoshita.
Yes, right.
And you had already gone toe to toe for the past 6 hours.
Did you already know who would win at that point?
I didn't know.
It might be a lie.
He's mad.
You know, I thought Kinoshita had an advantage over me.
And to tell you the truth, Kinoshita's picture was insane for me.
The moment that came out I knew he had a point.
What are you licking?
The ones from before.
That was also an accidental by-product.
I really couldn't do much.
So you didn't know who was the winner until Matsumoto announced it, right?
Yes.
We didn't know.
The winner is...
Yes!
Yamamoto!
Me?!
I see...
Yamamoto wins!
Congratulations!
I was destroyed by Oshima's panties.
It was nothing crazy.
But just looking at them, they were dirty.
More than dirty, they were super old.
And then someone went, "What is this? It's so dirty!".
"Did you play baseball in these?".
Jimmy, let's take a good look at them.
Let's take a good look.
What is it?
I don't know, just some panties.
Those are huge.
Are those Oshima's?
Yeah.
Aren't they big?
What's with this color?
But the back is clean.
D-Did you play baseball in these?
They're so dirty.
A ball of hair!
Did you put these on and play some ball?
What the hell was that question?
Baseball?
It's hilarious.
Too many things made me laugh...
But I think the best one was when he was wearing those weird glasses and started cracking up.
I see, I see...
Whoa!
That's a lot.
Stopping there was a lifesaver for me.
If they hadn't pressed the stop button, I would have laughed to eternity at his appearance.
For me it was RG's impression of Konjakuan's Master. (EN: 14)
You know, I was just there this morning.
And the Master was there.
He greeted me with an, "It's been a while!"
And I just went on my merry way.
Then we started the show.
And I never expected that to happen at Zombie Time.
I went like this the moment he came out.
I cut all eye contact.
It's Konjakuan.
It's been a while.
Hayashi... Rice...
And RG even talks like him.
You'll never know how similar it is until you go there.
But that was crazy.
Himura tried to do some acting with his belly.
And that fell a bit flat, didn't it?
But then he was trying to do it again.
He was gonna do it after the first start signal...
Then we went like, "Let's do it".
And then the signal came!
I played that part so many times.
That was the scene for me.
But there's still time, what should we do?
Start after the signal?
Sure, let's go after the signal.
In what sentence, how would you describe comedy?
For me it's when the joke develops into something I'd never think of myself.
With that much time and all those comedians,
there's bound to be some miraculous moments.
The most memorable one though...
Well, I was there...
And Iwahashi was next to me.
In front of me was Goto.
And Goto joked about my pubic area, since I don't have any hair.
You're all smooth ('tsuru tsuru' in Japanese) down there.
That's right, he made a joke about my lack of pubes.
And by pure chance, Iwahashi was folding an origami 'Tsuru' (crane) next to me.
How was it?
Oh, like this, and that.
You're all smooth.
Oh, right, like back in the day.
Not like that.
You're doing it wrong.
That moment was so inspirational to me.
I just joked about how smooth ('tsuru tsuru') he is...
And he was folding a 'Tsuru' over there!
Matsumoto, can you think of one scene that was amazing for you?
Amazing? I wonder...
I don't really remember.
Sometimes, even I tune out a little.
You do?
That room is like an abyss of electronics.
Though I know I shouldn't tune out.
But I like that one.
The little window?
That's right.
I like the sketches that use the little window.
I think those are funny.
Like Himura's.
Himura's... Right...
Yes, that was super funny.
Jimmy's act was also funny.
Yes.
That guy is crazy.
This one was really good.
It would have been crazy if it was that thing.
-It was so funny.
-And he tried so hard.
-It was a very strong trump card.
-Yes.
-It's similar.
-Were you aware of that?
You're not laughing.
We already watched you do it, you know?
Kotoge.
It's not doing it for me.
It's the same thing.
That's just Jimmy.
I'm not him.
Jimmy, right?
That's Jimmy.
Poor Himura.
Jimmy?
Yes?
You look the exact same.
The only thing is your golden tooth.
Right, right.
This Himura is hilarious.
This is so funny.
I'm not him.
Himura, thanks.
Thank you.
Scary, scary, scary.
Hold on, I can't close it.
He can't close it.
Sorry.
What was that?
What's wrong with him? Really...
He must have made that at home, right?
He apparently cooked it in parts.
The middle part has been boiled.
Only the middle has been boiled.
He told us the Konnyaku gets firmer if you boil it.
Right.
It's gotta have some integrity.
And it has to hold everything with the string.
He's 54.
Actually, this time around...
We will talk about what we call the legendary season 0, which we couldn't talk about or even mention its existence.
I mean, it was just a big experiment.
Right, an experiment.
But we did it for 14 hours.
That was amazing.
We started to see different things.
We had some horrible people.
They wouldn't do anything!
I couldn't believe there were people like that.