What kind of comedian suits Documental?
Well, for example, comedians like Shirai, who can strike the fatal blow on his own
Contrarily, comedians that are never suitable for Documental would be those like Uchima*
*Uchima is a contestant of the experimental Documental Season 0
No way!
How come?
No way, why is Nobu here?
That being said, Uchima actually turned out to be interesting, you know what I mean?
I'm not talking bad about Uchima
Uchima appears interesting if we think about it again now
So we can see that Owarai is really
a profound matter with many layers
This can't be true
Your beard will be stained with milk
No it won't be stained
Try to drink it then
Chug it
That's fast
It's stained dude
You are the one who asked him to do it
Daigo, yellow!
Yes, I understand
Kurosawa, what happened?
What happened?
How come?
Seriously, what happened?
It's truly a male‐dominated society
A male‐dominated society...
It's fine, don't worry
Don't worry, everything will be fine
Here it starts
-It started?
-Yes, it started
He's being so nice to her
-Yeah, you've gone too far
-I bet they did it
Why don't you just leave her alone?
No, I did nothing
But you were being nice to her right?
You did it?
No I didn't, I'm not being nice to her because we did it
Did it? What do you mean did it?
You mean they had sex?
Because he started saying we did it. Of course we didn't
Say something Kurosawa
We did it
With Fujimon?
Wait, Kurosawa...
You did it?
We didn't dude, why are you lying
She's a bit moody now, please excuse her
Who did you do it with?
Fujimon-san
-He did it?
-Yes
Come on, Fujimon-san, that's unacceptable
How dare you put your hands on your juniors
That's incest
When did he do it?
In 1998
That was long time ago
-Right after you made your debut?
-Yes
No I didn't, why are you lying about this? You're being weird
-Where did he do it?
-Drink some tea
Where?
The basement of Tameike-sanno
*Kurosawa and Fujimon are both employed by Yoshimoto, which was located in Tameike-sanno back in 1998
Minato-ku?
Where Yoshimoto was located previously
Before he got married?
At the basement?
That's where Yoshimoto was based right?
Yes, the former Yoshimoto base
So he did it after work right?
Yes
Did he do it because of love, or did he abuse his power as a senior? This is a crucial difference.
I didn't do it dude, why are you saying it like I did it?
What was the sex position?
What's that called again...
His face is over here, and his sex organ is on my face
So it didn't go in then
It can be conveyed by numbers right?
An even number and an odd number?
Even number and odd number right?
-Show us how it looks like
-Yeah, try it out
So I'm going to do 69 with Kurosawa now?
-Because we don't know what kind of position is that
-Just reproduce the situation and show us how it looks like
Who was on the top?
Kurosawa do you remember who was on the top?
He was at the side
At the side?
That's innovative
Is that even possible?
-So Kurosawa you're in this position?
-Yes
Oh, I see what you mean
What do you mean?
So you did it from behind right...?
He put his face in my butt
(It's lacking a decisive moment)
That's not a 69 then
-Just try it out
-But that's not a 69
What is this called? 69?
Put your face here
You didn't touch me though
-He didn't touch you?
-Yes, he didn't
His nose is in my butt
-It went in?
-Yes
-Fujimon said he wants to do it in this position?
That's not how you have sex
-His nose went in?
-Yes
-His nose went in smoothly?
Not like that, your nose went further
It went further?
Ah, just like that
It went in?
Yes, just like that
Why are you speaking like Henna Oji-san?
*Henna Oji-san is a famed original character by Ken Shimura
Ah, just like that
-Ah, just like that
-That's Shimura-san
Why are you speaking like Henna Oji-san?
-Did he ask you to act Shimura-san during the play?
-Ah, yes he did
-Kurosawa you're fine with this right?
-Yes
I'll do it then...
Ah, just like that
Sometimes you say it, and sometimes you don't right?
Why is that?
You missed the spot isn't it?
Can I try it again?
I'll do it again now
No, that's wrong
That's too strong
That's still too strong
You didn't use too much force before
-Do it smoothly
-Yeah, do it tenderly
-Be tender
-Put it in smoothly
Are you using greasepaint?
Yes, I am
Come on, her pants will be stained
That's no good, Fujimon-san
Don't stain female's pants with greasepaint
So in the end, they didn't have sex right?
Yes
-Yes, we didn't
-Only the nose
Only the nose went in, so that doesn't count
Can you stop checking your pants here?
We can see your underwear
But I'm wearing two underwear
Stop, girls shouldn't do that
What's under your pants?
Double underwear
One is a normal underwear, and the other one is a boxer short
-Your underwear looks like concrete
-Yeah
Like granite
Yeah, the gray one
Kitagi island has a lot of granite too
That's irrelevant dude
-That's the island where I lived
-That's irrelevant
We don't need that info
And your dad collects round stones right?
My dad goes to the seaside, and collect perfectly round stones without any corners at the beach
And show it to the boss of the island
What is the boss of the island?
The island's boss
You call him the island's boss?
My dad calls him the boss
Yeah, but he's not being employed
Like the don of the island
So like the authorities
And show them the stones like
"Boss, here is the perfectly round stone"
Will the boss pay for it?
Yes, a little bit
How much?
5000 yen
So this is how you were raised
By round stones...
Is it 5000 yen per stone?
If it's not perfectly rounded, it won't get paid
-So the more rounded it is, the more expensive it is
-Yeah, of course
The more rounded it is, the more expensive it is
So is the boss collecting round stones?
The island's boss is the owner of a stone company
You need say that first, otherwise we won't understand
What are they using the round stones for?
Well, probably just to look at it
Look at it?
So the women boss is collecting stones just to look at it?
Not a women boss though
Oh, it's not? Sorry, I thought the boss is female
-90 percent of bosses are males right?
-Is it?
No way, that's gender discrimination
Not discrimination, but did you ever heard of a women boss?
Yes, sometimes
Yeah, think about Wonder Woman
Wonder Woman is not relevant to this at all
This is really impressive
*Impressive and souvenir have the same pronunciation
Yeah, it's interesting
-Who you buying those souvenirs for?
-Shinagawa-ku
Where my home is
Souvenirs
No one else buy souvenirs?
Well, I do buy souvenirs though
Are you guys good at buying souvenirs?
Like when you're filming outdoors?
-What does good at buying souvenir means?
-Like the sense of buying souvenirs
I see, well...
I'm the type of person who buys a lot of delicacies and end up throwing them out
-I see, so they went stale
-Yes
-It's hard to hold back
-Exactly, I love it
And there's a lot of these edible chili oil nowadays
I threw out 2 or 3 of them already
Because it's spicy, so I always thought it will never go stale
-Yeah, exactly
-You're right
-There's edible chili oil?
-Yeah, there is
It's really popular now
You can buy it at Pengin Shokudo
What the heck is Pengin Shokudo nara?
*Nara is a pun from the previous episode
Pengin Shokudo
There's throwable Shumai too
What are you doing?
That's terrible
You asked for it
Are you joking?
-I tried to hold back
-Are you serious?
-Dude, stop messing with me?
-What did I do?
It's cunning to pinpoint me
That's because you were asking me
What just happened?
We were talking about edible chili oil, and he said there's throwable Shumai as well
I just imagined how you throw a Shumai like this
-I can't help but imagine that
-Yeah, you made him imagine that
I understand your feelings, but that was terrible
You went like "ge-hey-hey-hey"
Come on, I'm so weak
-There's edible chili oil?
-Yeah, there is
It's really popular now
Oh, really?
-You can buy it at Pengin Shokudo
-Yeah
What the heck is Pengin Shokudo nara?
*Nara is a pun from the previous episode
(He actually tried to attack here)
There's throwable Shumai too
He tried to muddle through by smoking
But he couldn't make it
But I didn't laugh out loud right?
Well, umm...
Well, yeah but still...
Sorry
This is fast
-This is fast
-Yeah, this is fast
Just in 30 minutes...
-There's still 5 and a half hours left
-Oh god, seriously?
Are we even going to make it through guys?
-He'll always come out if he becomes a zombie
-Yes, exactly
Yeah, it's fearful to make him a zombie
The earlier he loses, the more he'll come out, and that's frightening
Don't make him a zombie please
Yeah, I should have been more considerate
Let's start
Even if I play it cool, it's meaningless if I'm out
There's this chicken that screams like "quack" right?
-Let's play with that
-That sounds interesting
What's a chicken that screams?
You squeeze it and it goes "quack"
-Ah, the one that looks like a wild turkey
-Yes
Kurochan put back the milk bottle slowly just now
You don't need to talk about that
No, I don't remember that
Ah, I saw that before
This comes out in the United States Navy's enlistment test
Eh? What kind of test is that?
To not laugh at this
You need to hold back your laughter while it screams in your ear
No one will laugh at this though
What if I squeeze it while standing up
What the heck was that
Fujimon, can you give me a shout?
Can everyone come over here?
Yeah, we should watch this together
Ask me to turn around and see if you guys can hold back
-Of course we can hold back
-Yeah
We watched this many times already
-Are you ready?
-Yes
Miyasako-san
What's up?
-Let it scream dude
-It's not screaming
Nah, this is not going to work
Anyone want to try this?
Nishizawa
Nishizawa can you do this?
Nishizawa do it at the front
Nishizawa-kun's face looks hilarious
Don't let Nishizawa do it dude
I never did this before though
Hey, look at him
Damn it, damn it
Should I give you a shout?
Should I kill him, dude
Can you give me a shout please?
-Do it after he gives you a shout
-Sorry
Hey, no dude
No, Nishizawa, turn around after I give you a shout
I got it
No, no dude
There's a lot more
-A lot?
-Yeah I brought a lot
-Why though?
-A lot?
Wait a moment
-And can you...
-Yes?
They all sound a bit different
That's a lot
-That's too much
-Are they all the same?
-What happens if you squeeze them all at a time?
-Let's try
-That's amazing
-Yeah, that's amazing
Daigo laughed right?
-What happened?
-Who laughed?
-Who is it?
-Is it you Daigo?
-It's Daigo
No, no way
No way, that shouldn't count
That shouldn't count as laughing
-You're yellow carded already right?
-Eh, really?
Yeah, Daigo is yellow carded
Eh, wait a second, did I even laughed just now?
No, I didn't laugh, no
-Who laughed?
-Who is it?
Eh, at this time?
-That's too fast
-That's really fast
Daigo...
Let's have a look
Eh...
Let's have a look first
I'm not really sure about this too
It's so sad if Daigo is out
-Does that count?
-That's absolutely laughing
I have to give you an orange card for this
-You actually should be out
-Yes
You should be red carded after a yellow card
-That's how it works right?
-Get ready
-Okay
Stop it, it's sticking in my mind
Please let me calm down first
Please don't play with that for now
What's going on with him?
Daigo is so weak
He's so weak right?
Come on
Let's start
Here it starts again
-Let's calm down first
-Yeah
The pace is too fast
Is this fast?
Yeah, it's really fast
Daigo will already be out next time
-Yeah, I'll be out next...
-You'll be out even if you just laugh a little bit
That's alarming
-Let me squeeze this first
-Stop that
Listen, they scream differently
Come on, stop that
Are you the hero who saved them?
Why are you holding so many of them
And look at his biceps
It becomes brawny when he squeezes them
He looks like a frightened kangaroo right?
I told you not to hold too many
Hey dude
-Are you cosplaying?
-What?
Aren't you cosplaying?
You changed your clothes?
No, I didn't
Who is he cosplaying?
The staffs at Kariyushi Urban Resort
The hotel at Okinawa, Kariyushi Urban Resort
You're cosplaying them right?
-No, I'm not
-Oh, you're not
-You stayed in that hotel before?
-Yes
It's a good hotel
That scared me
That scared me, I thought it's a buzzer
Do I look like them?
Exactly the same, check out how they look
You look exactly the same
This is fast
Yeah, it is
Because it's a Shinkansen
And Shikansen is...?
FAST
-You're annoying
-That scared me
Who will even laugh at that?
Well, Shinkansen is fast though
Fujimon, Fujimon, Fujimon
-Kurochan dance to the music
-Yes?
It's not interesting at all
-Yeah, seriously
-Eh?
Not at all
Why didn't you do something?
-Do something?
-Add something to your dance
Like something with your own style
My style?
Did you even try to make him laugh just now?
You just muddled through right?
No, you asked me to dance, so I just danced to the music
No one will laugh if you just dance to the music
Next station is Shin-Osaka
Eh, it's speaking
It was speaking all the time
Yeah, it's just this kind of toy
Eh, did it speak before...
Ah, it's speaking
You never saw something like this when you're a kid?
-No, never
-Then what toys did you play with as a child?
-What kind of toys?
-Eh, Famicom
What's that answer
Other than Famicom?
Others?
All that you played is Famicom?
-No, no
-Then tell us
Eh, flints
Flints?
-Your parents bought it for you?
-Yes
Is that even a toy?
That's not a toy dude
Next station is Shin-Osaka
Ah, it's speaking again
We told you because it's just this kind of toy
-Were there these kind of toys?
-Of course
Eh, who's voice is this?
Prominent people?
He said prominent people...
Are you really Kurochan?
Eh?
Yes, I'm the real Kurochan
Shiro-chan?
*Kuro means black and Shiro means white
That's a wrong color, an opposite one
That was so fast
I have hair?
*"So fast" and "have hair" sound similar
No, I mean fast
Ao-chan?
*Ao means blue
No, I'm not a healing color like blue
Aka-chan?
-We are always chil...children in our parents’ eyes
-You just bite*
*Aka-chan means baby
*"Bite" means tripping over your own tongue
No I didn't, I only bite my lips when I'm frustrated
You bite a chewing gum too
Never
Kiiro-chan?
*Kiiro means yellow color
No I'm not an expansive color
Amazing
Aka-chan?
We are always children in our parents’ eyes
No, you said that before
Wait, wait a second...don't do this to your partner dude
I'm feeling distant
Looks like good friends though
It's fine to do this right?
It looks like the photo of young actors
Do young actors take this kind of photos?
Young actors be like "How are you doing buddy"
Between you two?
We looked like that just now
You mean Fujimon-san?
Who do you mean?
You mean me?
Who?
What happened?
Wait a second...
What are you doing?
What's going on Nobu?
Wait a second, no, no, no
You're the only one laughing
Wait a second, it's you...
What? No, I did nothing wrong
I did nothing wrong right?
Why is everyone staring at me all of a sudden?
Of course we will
Because you started Tsukommi
Please don't...I didn't laugh...
Matsumoto-san, I really didn't laugh
That wasn't even funny
Chidori seems to be really weak
Yeah, we're both easily amused
Chidori is so weak
Nothing even happened
Yeah, nothing happened
Even the audiences are not laughing at all
-You're the only one laughing
-Yeah, exactly
You're the only one laughing in Japan
I don't want to lose like that
It looks like the photo of young actors
Do young actors take this kind of photos?
Young actors be like "How are you doing buddy"
Between you two?
We looked like that just now
You mean Fujimon-san?
Who do you mean?
(He's already laughing at this point)
You mean me?
What's funny about this?
What's so funny about this?
Conversely, how did you hold back all these times?
If you're laughing at that
-With such a weak defense
-No, seriously...
Oh no
-Well, you're yellow carded
-Yes
But this really raises my guard
Everyone says that, but no one is really guarded up
It's possible that Chidori will both be out first
That's the worst, I really don't want that to happen
So maybe it's better if I just stay still and don't move
That's none of our business
Yeah, that's none of our business
-Decide it yourself
-None of our business
What is this most easily amused person trying to say?
None of our business
That was a superficial strategy
Today is seriously gonna end early,
only less than an hour has passed
This is awful
-Good luck
-Thank you
If you try to attack, you may end up laughing
-Yeah, that happens
-End up laughing instead
I'll think about this again
I paid one million for this and Matsumoto is watching as well, I need to keep this in mind
-We need to stay calm
-Yeah
Let's start
She's rubbing the cucumbers
Eh?
Girls are amazing
What are you making?
It's some pickled cucumbers
-Eh? It started right?
-Yes, it started
-Oh really?
-It's delicious
What is that?
It's some pickled cucumbers
Thank you
Eat it up
Maybe we'll laugh if she feeds him in a strange way
That's enough
Can you eat it all?
-No, that's too much
-There's two more cucumbers though
Thanks, I'm good
It's leaking
Can you eat it all?
-You can spit it out
-Are you ok?
He's gonna puke
Why are you covering your mouth like that?
Ah, a lot came out
Is Kurosawa-san laughing?
She's laughing
What was that?
She laughed out loud
You didn't even try to hold back
She said "a lot came out"
She said it while laughing foolishly
Like a newly married couple
She screwed it up right, Matsumoto-san?
She definitely screwed it up
What was that?
Because a lot more came out than she expected
-And because it was crunched when it came out
-That's just because he chewed it
Of course it's crunched if he chewed it
Ah, a lot came out
Don't say something like an escort
What do you mean "a lot came out"
-Well, Kurosawa you're yellow carded
-Yes, I'm sorry
-Counter-attacks are fearful
-Yeah it is
-We need to be careful
-Yeah
Hey guys, I actually have strong and powerful arms
I want to life up a guy
Can someone just wear this above your pants?
Who seems to be the skinniest...
No, it's not me
-It's Nobu right?
-Then Nobu-san...
Kurosawa
Kurosawa wait a second, ask Jun-san to do it
-No, you got nominated
-I'm not, no, I'm not nominated
You said it's good to let Nobu do it right?
No, it's not good if I do it
Let Jun-san do it
No, Nobu you've been mentioned by name
Just do it Nobu
Kurosawa, you're terrible
Can I take it off?
-The belt?
-Yes
Wait a second Kurosawa, you are...
You are...
But you can do it with your own underwear too
-Just with your own underwear...
-Everyone can see my underwear now
Wear this please
Wear this above...aww it's disgusting
It's the same underwear as Tsurutaro-san
*Tsurutaro-san is a famed Yogis
No, I don't wear it for yoga
Never mind, it's too gross
So you're not doing it?
What?
-I want to use this to show my power
-But how?
-Your power?
-Yes, my power
Because Kurosawa said she's powerful
What do you want me to do?
You're just embarrassing me for wearing the same underwear as Tsurutaro-san
-Is this the one for Nobu?
-Yes
Can you wear this above your pants?
Let's see who is the real Tsurutaro
Thank you very much
-Are you Tsurutaro too?
-He's not Tsurutaro at all
No, I'm not Tsurutaro-san at all
So what should I do now?
Let's say you come home drunk
And you fell asleep in front of the door
So I'll move you to the bedroom on my own as a strong woman
That must be really tough
That's good
She must be a good wife right?
-It's amazing if she can make it right?
-Yeah, it is
Is there any techniques?
Can you come home drunk please?
That's quite a distance though
-It started?
-Yes
I'm back
I'm so drunk
Oh, come on, you're so drunk again
Oh, don't fall asleep here
Did anyone laughed?
Who laughed?
Probably one of you two laughed during the performance
You laughed while you're acting
No, no way, I didn't laugh
Kurosawa probably laughed
Yeah, Kurosawa laughed
So it's Kurosawa
You can't laugh even if you're performing
That counts as out too
Yeah
Kurosawa just laughed normally
Yeah, we were told not to laugh in performances right?
I'm back
I'm so drunk
Oh, come on, you're so drunk again
Oh, don't fall asleep here
Well, that was...
Excuse me
Wow, orange
-Kurosawa you're close
-You'll be out next time
You're out next time
-Kurosawa you're in danger okay?
-Yes, I got it
That's scary
-It's fine for now right?
-Yeah, it's fine
So you can't even smile
It's awful to leave without finishing any performance
That happens
That always happens
-Shall we continue?
-Yes
Let's do this again
-Sorry for asking you to start again
-No worries
-Be careful
-Even if you're performing
Hold back your laughter
It is a tough day
So tie it up like this
And then...excuse me...
-So I'll then grab here
-What's going on?
It's such a tough day
Huh?
He's heavy
-Is it possible to lift him up like that?
-That's amazing
That's amazing
How can she move forward though?
Did you do something wrong?
No, but he was heavier than I expected
-Oh, I see
-Yeah, I'm quite heavy
-Kurosawa, what are you doing?
-I'm sorry
I just wanted to show off that I'm strong
That was impossible
You should pick someone skinnier
How far did she move him though?
Huh?
How far did she move?
Well, just from there...
One banana, two bananas
Can you bring me some more bananas?
Anymore bananas?
It's not necessary to count it with bananas
Iio-san that's enough, no one will
understand if you count with bananas
We usually say it's how many meters
No one will understand even if you say it's how many bananas
-That's no good, Iio-san
-What do you mean?
Fruits Samurai
What the heck is that?
Mother of Fruits
That's from Ultraman
-I see, so it's from Ultraman
-Fruits Taro
That's from Ultraman again
Can you stop saying fruits though?
That's banana
-Banana is a fruit right?
-Yes it is, but...
He's the only true son of Mother of Ultra
-Yeah
-Oh, he's the only one?
What about the others?
Yes?
The others are relatives
-Ryotsu Kankichi
-Here it comes
*Ryotsu Kankichi is a manga character with super thick eyebrows
It should be Fruits Kankichi
Oh yeah, Fruits Kankichi
How could you say Ryotsu?
How could you not notice it?
That's terrible
Eh?
-What did I do?
-All this time
-Bananas...
-I mean since you become a comedian
That was just a careless mistake
I'm so sad, Tobojite Tobojite, Fruits Tobojite
*"Tobojite Tobojite" is a phrase said when feeling sad, invented by the manga character Inakappe Taishou
Hit your eyes like "don"
-That's scary
-That's dangerous, don't do that
-More, more, show us more
-What?
-Show us more
-More?
Just do it, more characters will pop up
The nipples beam cross section is in heart shape
What's wrong with you?
Come on
Why did you laugh at that?
I have no idea what he's talking about
-What the heck was that?
What?
What the heck did you do?
-Nipples beam
-And the cross section?
Cross section is in heart shape
What the heck is that
You're the one who pushed him hard to perform
Why did you laugh at something so basic at this stage?
That's such a basic failure
-Eh?
-Come on
-It's dangerous to push Kurochan too hard
-Yeah, exactly
(Fujimoto-san is already trying hard to hold back)
The nipples beam cross section is in heart shape
Don't try to play hardball with Kurochan
You have to dodge his attack
His attack hit you right in the face
He attacked right in front of me
You're infinitely close to this...
But a yellow card, you're very close
You're very close to a red card
So Kurochan scores a lot of points now
-Thank you
-Oh yeah
-He scored points for this
-Yes
Let's start
Don't attack Kurochan anymore
Iio-san is the one who started the banana
Please stop this Iio-san
I just tried to attack
Hey guys, can we gather up please?
-Yes?
-So here it comes
I have some horror photos
-Here it comes
-Horror photos?
-No way, stop that
-Seriously?
Stop this series dude
Don't do it, we're definitely going laugh
Don't do it, don't do it this time
No, it's really some horror photos this time
No way, how could that be true
Seriously
We'll laugh if it's really scary too
Stop it please
Is that face fine?
What? Did I look weird?
Kukky really like this
Stop that Kawashima-san
*Kawashima is the real name of Kukky
That's no good
That's really no good
That is just...absolutely no good
Who's denture is that? You're always wearing it
Who's teeth are those?
It's my grandpa's teeth
-He used to wear it?
-Yes
Grandpa?
Don't use a real one dude
-He's still alive though
-So he's still alive
Let's have a look at these horror photos guys
No, let's watch it when everyone is here
Put it away first
-Put it away dude
-Okay, sorry
-Please put it away
-Yes, okay
This is seriously killing me
That's not horror photos
Yes it is, look at it, it's terrifying
-Look over here
-Let's wait until everyone is here
These photos are coming out too early
Yeah, that's too early, it's awful
I hope you can show it later
Shisho is coming
*Hamburger Shisho is the original character that Jun-san is acting
We won't laugh at Shisho
Hey, come over here
-It's not about Shisho now
-Not now
And we won't laugh at Shisho anyway
Oh, really?
Your buckle is a hamburger?
Yeah it is
Please let me do this again
He's living near Roppongi
And we were having a drink there, so we asked him out
-And he came in that costume
-That's amazing
And then...
No one laughed
No one laughed at all
How did that even happen?
-This town doesn't change at all
-Here it starts
What happened?
Why are you looking at me as if I'm the dispensable mixed veggies
No, we didn't
Did you guys forget about me?
It's me
HAMBURGER
What I've prepared for all you starving people,
is the 100 gram Teppan joke
When me, Hamburger, was dawdling at home, my mom said this
Hey Hamburger, why are you always dawdling?
Why don't you find a stable job, you're Hamburger right?
Yep
*Set meal and stable job have the same pronunciation
Here comes the set meal
HAMBURGER
You are so noisy
-That's so loud
-Didn't know it's so loud
Here comes the section that you've all been waiting for, The Challenge Hamburger
Challenge Hamburger?
Is this an interactive performance?
This is the dinner menu of the hamburger restaurant "Gold Rush"
And there's 14 items in total
Fourteen
*Fourteen and juicy have the same pronunciation
Juicy
HAMBURGER
Here starts the Hamburger Challenge
This is so long
-He's so strong
-He's not laughing at these photos
-The photos were translucent, and I almost laughed
-Yeah
So now...
Miyasako-san can you please hold this for me?
What's going on?
I'll be reading these 14 dishes from Gold Rush as fast as possible
Can you count the time please?
Please look forward to how many
seconds it takes for me to read them all
So let's get started
Challenge Hamburger
Ready, set, start!
Gold Rush Hamburger
Teriyaki Hamburger
Grated daikon radish Hamburger
Teriyaki and cheddar cheese Hamburger
West and east Hamburger
Japanese style Hamburger
Cowboy Hamburger
Half and half Hamburger
Double cheese Hamburger, Garlic Hamburger
Garlic and cheese Hamburger
Fried tomato Hamburger
Triple rush Hamburger
Garlic diced steak
What's the time?
Two seconds
Fourteen seconds
Juicy
HAMBURGER
No, he said it's two seconds
It's two seconds
That's not in your script?
You don't usually see me in this costume right?
-No, you're in this costume every time I see you
-Yeah, we always see this costume
But you don't usually see me in this cosutme right?
-No, we do
-You always wear like this in Nichima Channel right?
In Osaka?
Like this?
No
-Like this?
-Yes
With both hands?
Like this?
That's a nice one
That's a nice swing
Can you imitate the swing of famous people?
Yeah
Just shout out their name
-How about Ichiro-san?
-Nice choice
He's left-handed
But I'm right-handed
Well, just imitate his movement
That's completely different
He does this first right?
But Ichiro is left-handed, so...
-Well, yeah
-Someone right-handed please
-Who's right-handed?
-Someone who swings with right hand
-What about Ogasawara?
-That's a nice choice
He have some unique movements
But Ogasawara is left-handed too
Ah, he's left-handed
But he's easy to imitate
However, I'm right-handed
Then try to do it on the right side
That's the same dude
Swing it as Ogasawara
What about Matsui?
But Matsui is left-handed too
Just imitate his movement
So like this...
It's Kazuo*
*Fujimon means it should be Matsui Kazuo, instead of Matsui Hideki, who are both famed baseball players
Kazuyo?
*Matsui Kazuyo is a female actor, well-known for uploading videos to YouTube that criticizes his husband Funakoshi for having affairs
O?
Kazu...yo
Yo?
Kazuyo?
The swing of Matsui Kazuyo?
Just imitate how she looks like in those videos
Like a "if someone swings" series right?
If Matsui Kazuyo swings?
On YouTube right?
If she swings on YouTube?
Remember to imitate how she critisizes his husband
-I am...
-Put your hands here
Nice
-I am...
-Nice
Really...
Suffering...
And this is how I swing when I'm suffereing
Please have a look
Nice one
Kazuyo did a nice swing
That's a really nice one
I didn't know Kazuyo can swing so nice
Do Kazuyo swing like that?
She was more emotional in the video
Yeah, you're right
More like how Sarah Connor speaks to his son in Terminator
I don't really watch videos though
Like how Sarah Connor speaks to John Connor
"John, if you're watching this, it means that..."
"You are..."
You're wearing the same tank top as she said this
Completely the same?
Not completely
"You are..."
Are we ready for some horror photos?
-No, not yet
-Kurosawa is still changing clothes
Then let's wait for a while
-I can see her over there
-And her costumes
Hello, hello, hello everybody
I am Daichi Mao
Wait...
Evil spirits, there's evil spirits
Evil spirits, evil spirits here
Let's exorcise evil spirits
Evil spirits here
There's evil spirits here
There's a lot of evil spirits here
There's evil spirits
Evil spirits, there's evil spirits
Evil spirits, evil spirits, evil spirits
There's a lot of evil spirits
Wait a second...
Wait, wait, wait...
You're scary
Evil spirits, there's evil spirits
This...
This..
Can you hold that end for me please?
This end as well
Thank you very much
Dong, dong, dong
Here comes the straddle
Ah, ah, straddle, straddle
Ah, ah, straddle
Here comes the straddle...hold it up
Ah, ah, straddle, straddle
Ah, ah, straddle
Here comes the straddle
-What is she doing?
-Oh, it's over there
Wait a second...
Ah, ah, straddle
This is awful
This is just...
Did Kurosawa laughed again?
Kurosawa laughed inside there?
Is it me?
Did you laugh again?
Ah, maybe I did laugh
By the way, what's going on with that wig
Kurosawa is out if she laughed though
Eh, who is it?
Kurosawa was orange carded already?
He almost laughed all this time
And finally, he wasn't able to hold it
Iio
-It's Iio-san?
-Yeah, he laughed in the end
Oh, I'm sorry
I wasn't able to hold back when she was straddling, I can even feel the rope shaking
That shake is killing me
Ah, ah, straddle, straddle
Wait a second...
This is awful
Yeah, he was definitely laughing
Well, yeah
I'm sorry
Well, yellow umm...yeah, maybe yellow
Yes, thank you
-Many of us are just one step away
-That's scary
Yeah you're right, many of you are almost out
Are we still going to look at the horror photos?
-You guys wanna watch it?
-Shall we?
Sure, I haven't shown all of them yet
Kurosawa-chan, can you sprinkle some salts?
Ah, excuse me
Because it's horror photos, maybe you can exorcise it with salt
-These were on the floor, is that fine?
-That's completely fine
Excuse me, excuse me
Oh yeah, just like that
Horror photos?
-Yes
-Is it exorcised?
She tried to exorcise it
So it should be the normal Shisho now
It's a photo of Shisho?
He's looking normal now
His face is so small
He has no neck
-The evil spirits did this?
-Yes
-It didn't return to normal
-His face is so small
-Is it exorcised?
-It didn't return to normal at all
What kind of horror photo is this?
Which person is possessed by an evil spirit? Daisuke...?
*Hanako Shisho is the women, and Daisuke Shisho is the man
It should be Hanako right?
-You must be joking
-It's Daisuke Shisho
-No way, Hanako-san looks normal
-No, it must be Hanako-san, just look at her face
-So Hanako Shisho is being possessed?
-Yes
But he looks so small somehow
-Please look at it
-Yes I am
-Miyasako is not looking at it right?
-Yes, I am
Miyasako-san is just looking at somewhere over here
No, I am looking at it
This is the vertical version
-Vertical?
-Vertical version?
I am looking at it
I am, I am
That's so stupid
I've prepared photos for everyone too, please pass it around
For everyone?
Not for everyone, please
So you mean individually?
Yes, I'll pass it to you individually
Come on, not for everyone, please
Wait...can you start with people who are not carded first?
That's our only request, please
Give it to the carded group afterwards
I'm really sorry, but please
Please
I'm carded
-I'm carded
-I got one card too
-I'm yellow carded
-Yellow too
Seriously, please
Well, I understand this
I'm sorry, please excuse us for this
Hey dude, why are you showing it to us?
-Are you an idiot?
-You heard what we said right?
Show it to them! To them!
To those who didn't get any cards
Have a look at it yourself
-This...
-Ku-chan
Seriously, don't do this Kukky-san
We'll be out
We will all be out
We'll be out Kukky-san
Choose one representative then
No, please don't do that
Come on, please
Don't put it here smoothly
*(CARD) When I saw a girl vomiting, I had an erection
Please, don't put it smoothly
These things actually really happened to him
-You mean to Shisho
-Yes
Wait a second, wait a second
Ku, please
Read it out loud
Is that a true story?
Yes, that's a true story
Look at it, come on
Look at it
*(CARD) When I was humping, and my wife saw it, I was dead
Are you looking at it?
You're not looking at it, Fujimon, you're not looking at it
Look at it
Nobu is not looking at it too
Come on, look at it
I'm looking at it
Well, I think this one should be fine
*(CARD) This shit is worth ¥100,000? Please let me eat it
Look at it, Nobu, look at it
What's that face?
Please don't say Nobu
This face should be out
Come on, have a look
That's cheating
Nobu, look at it
*(CARD) I think I had it when I was 40 years old, I had a vasectomy
Nobu
Come on, Nobu, look at it
-You're not looking at all
-Yes, I am
Yeah I looked at it, he had a vasectomy right?
Yep, I see
Are these words...Ka-ha
*(CARD) I'm going to buy some Yomeishu (medicinal alcohol)
Ka-ha?
Wait a second, wait a second...
Wait a second please, come on...
-You guys are too much
-What was that just now?
That was a tough one
Yeah, that was a tough one
Come on, this can't be true
Matsumoto-san...
-There's nothing we can do about it
-He definitely laughed
What was that ka-ha?
-This is the first time this has happened
-He said Ka-ha right?
He went like Ka-ha right?
Wait a second, Matsumoto-san, no one can hold back on this
Yomeishu...
*(CARD) I'm going to buy some Yomeishu (medicinal alcohol)
He really seems to say this
Yeah, this is hilarious, it's hard to hold back
Yes, I'm looking
Look at it Nobu
Yeah I looked at it, he had a vasectomy right?
Nobu
Are these words...Ka-ha
*(CARD) I'm going to buy some Yomeishu (medicinal alcohol)
Matsumoto-san
No, that was just a dialogue
That's the highest level of laughing
What is that Ka-ha dude?
-You're orange carded
-Thank you
You're very close now
You'll be out next time