This time we dont have tough opponents like Kukki
So we have some new players
But slowly, the numbers of Documental veterans
is increasing isnt it?
How do you want the ideal
evolution of Documental to be?
I definitely think variation
is very important
Like if it ended within
5 minutes
So if everyone laughed within just
If it just ended that fast
I think if something like that happened
that would be interesting
I have similar thoughts in my head
[Recap]
Here we go
-Is there a Magic Marker here? For the water...
-To write names?
-Its not that but wouldnt this work too?
- Yeah thats fine too
It would be good so we know who's bottle is which
We dont want to be
unhygienic
Why did you write Hayashi Maya?
You can write whatever
-As long as you know
-Yeah like I am the one who wrote Hayashi Maya
I see
Passion Yaura?
Passion Yaura: A comedian
That guy?
This guy?
Choge Choge Passion
You have to look at him
He said Choge Choge Passion
Choge Choge Passion
Dont look away
Takahashi and Junior cant hold it in eh
-Choge Choge Passion was..
-Let him write it
Hes really good
Kobayashi is really good
-You can tell who wrote what right?
-Yeah
-Wankoso Bataro? Who is that?
-Wankoso Bataro?
Its a funny name I came up with
for making people laugh
Wanko Sobataro?
-Isnt it Wankoso Bataro?
-Wankoso Bataro
Eh? Wan Kosobataro?
Wankosoba Taro, right?
Wait a minute...
Its Wankosoba Taro
Its not Wankoso Bataro?
-Its Wankoso Bataro?
-Bataro?
-Yeah thats it
-Who is Wankoso Bataro?
Its just a funny name I came up with
-Wanko F. Bataro?
-No thats not it
Its Wanko Sobataro
Do you guys not have a name...
that you use for making people laugh?
Usually I use
"Makise Riho"
I see
That changes with time right?
Depending on the era
Should we do something?
Lets finish writing the names
I can write anything right?
Yeah
[inaudible]
The bad thing about
Jinnai is....
I mean what worries me about Jinnai is
he is an all-rounder but
his Oogiri is really not funny
A new Kamen Rider is still
made like Kamen rider, right?
It doesnt make any sense right?
Wankoso Bajiro
Oh little brother?
He had a brother?
Wankoso Bajiro?
Wan Kosobajiro
So its Wan Kosobajiro?
-Bajiro
-Wan Kosobataro?
Wankoso
Figure it out already!
How long are you gonna
take?
As long as you know what you wrote
anything is fine
Ichiro
Thats the full name?
Jimmy, Jimmy
-Didnt you say anything is fine
-Anything is fine but..
Then literally anything
should be ok right?
Just one..
This is the best one
I could come up with
Jimmy-san?
-Jimmy-san?
-Yes?
What made you laugh?
The ichiro bit got me
The ichiro bit almost got me too
I dont understand how that was
funny
I thought is he gonna say
eat an egg to fix that?
-Thats really a stretch
-Yeah but then he looked at me
Ichiro
Jimmy-san..
-Jimmy-san
-Yes
Junior and Takashi were almost laughing too
Yeah really, they were very
close
You almost laughed during the Passion
bit didnt you?
-Werent you laughing?
-No I wasnt laughing
Since the beginning, you have
been laughing
No, I havent
-Even while talking, you were laughing
but seriously, there was nothing
funny about ichiro
But It made him laugh
-That was really a stretch
-There is no penalty for that is there?
-Juionr-san werent you laughing too at that?
-You did, right?
-LIke that!
-Ah, you cant smile while talking either , right?
Thats not allowed either right?
Thats not acceptable either, eh?
-Looks like Jimmy-san is being left out
-No, thats not true
No, thats not true
Really
What did you write?
I should read it right?
Purin Hime(Pudding Princess)
-Whos that?
-Someone you know?
Its about when Zakusho
failed to lose his virginity
-You held hands till the morning right?
-You liked her?
The name sounds like
Goth Loli Fashion
She had a tasty lookin face
-She had a tasty lookin face
-And since he couldnt lose his virginity
I challenged him
to hit on girls
I told him to come with me
We picked up girls together
Then we sang some songs and said
"lets go to the Love Hotel"
"Tell me what to do" he said to the girl
and lost his virginity
Jimmy?
The girl he was with was called Bayashi
Lets go
and he said "Bayashi, what should we do?"
"Take it out" , she said.
So at that time when you
lost your virginity
and he asked "How did it go?"
Did you say that "something gummy
just came out of me?"
Wait it was me?
Was it me? Was it really me?
-Was it me?
-Werent you just laughing?
You were really laughing!
When your turned your head away
you were laughing
-Yeah thats how it looked
-Wait a minute, wait
Wait, he will tell us who was laughing
You really were laughing
The Judge will decide
What do you mean The Judge
-It cant be me can it?
-Its Junior!
That was quick!
-Junior-san got one earlier too
-That was fast
-I was laughing?
-Yeah, lets have a look
and he asked "How did it go?"
Did you say that "something gummy
just came out of me?"
No, I was holding it in
It wasnt full on laughing
Thats why I didnt give you red
This is not acceptable either
But seriously, you have to be
careful now
-It hasnt even been 30 minutes
-We want you here, Junior-san
Junior-san if you laugh once more,
you are done, son.
-You just have one chance left
-So early
Even though I do want to see
Junior as a zombie
Try not to laugh
for as long as you can
Wait, who placed the egg here
-Is that what you were..
Somethings gonna happen with that?
What are you gonna do if
you know the culprit?
-But when its there-
-Who would laugh at that?
It just makes me curious
Are you writing Jimmy-san?
Are you farsighted?
No, nearsighted
How old are you now?
Ah, your eyesight must be starting to get bad now
Kanou Hospital
-Kanou Hospital?
-You have been there?
-Oh the place where you work?
-No, I was hospitalized there
-Why were you hospitalized?
-Why?
Ah thats um..
I cant talk about the reason
Eh?
Was it something really bad?
-Its ok, Itsj ust a disease right?
-Its up to you
Yeah
What happened?
The diagnosis was that , I got electric shock
-You got shocked?
-Where?
In my head
How long ago was that?
When someone told me to go
to the hospital
Who told you that?
-The police
-The police?
Why?Did something happen?
-Nothing happened but
-Out of nowhere?
-You were just shocked?
-And they told you to go to the hospital?
It really hurt
You were hospitalised?
No, at first It was just
Regular treatment
I was hospitalised for 3 days, however
Wait, so were you or were
you not?
-At first I wasnt hospitalised, but later I was
-Later you were?
-At Kanou Hospital?
-Kanou Memorial Hospital
Memorial?
Where is it located?
Near Ichiro
Ichiro?
Takahashi...
-The ichiro bit reminded you of it eh?
-Yeah, the ichiro bit
You really like Ichiro dont you?
He must really like it
Have you always liked it?
Lets stop with that
Everyones drinking now
They probably thought
"Lets stop this"
Theres alot of beef sausages in the
refrigerator
-Jimmy-san you should lay down here
-Thats alot of sausages
-I saw this in a Korean show
Someone was able to fit about
30 sausages in their mouth
Lets see who can fit the most
in their mouth
-These orange things?
-Yeah these
Lets see who can fit the most
in their mouth
-One by one?
-Wouldnt that many make you gag?
One person was able to
fit 30 on the show
Which Korean show is that?
-Jimmy san you..
-You should do it
-That would be good
-Ok, Jimmy-san and I will do it
-Takashi and Jimmy-san right?
-Alright
Lets do 3 at a time
Oh thats how you have to do it?
-Yeah just like that
-Someone did 30?
-Theres no way thats possible
-I think my mouth is just small
-Wouldnt it be easier if someone helped you with it?
-Yeah please that would be better
-Helping each other...
-You can still fit more right?
-Yeah, do 3 at a time
-I think 3 at a time would be difficult
You can fit 3 more?
3 at a time
-Its gonna fall , hold it in
-I dont think this is possible
Theres only 6 in and it already
looks full
Go ahead Kobayashi-san
-His mouth is so small
-Its not gonna fit anymore
-Even 10 seems impossible
-Hes got 7 now
Jimmy-san still has plenty of
room in there
-You can only do 7 right?
-Or can you do 8?
You are 8 sausages man
-8
-8 here too
Jimmy-san 's mouth is really flexible
-He can only do 8 I think
-Its not gonna fit
-Thats too many already isnt it?
-Is he gonna be able to do 9?
-Jimmy-san's mouth opens really wide
Alright, hes gonna do 9
-It fit
-Ok
-10 sausages now
-It looks so easy for Jimmy-san
-Thats awesome
-Alright the 10th now
He looks like hes struggling
Waah
Oooh!
-This is an intense battle
-But 30?No way
-Jimmy can probably fit 50
-His mouth is so flexible
You are starting to drool, Jimmy-san
Oh , cant fit any more?
Lets do three people at once?
-Yeah, that would be good
You are gonna do it yourself?
Ah! That was really hard
-But didnt you laugh?
-No seriously I didnt laugh
-Tamura was...
-I didnt laugh, I was just surprised
Tamuken!
-Almost everyone was about to laugh but Tamuken
seemed like he did
No way!
Ok after looking at it
I did laugh, even that is unacceptable eh?
-Wasnt Takahashi laughing too?
-Takahashi laughed harder than me
-No , I was just surprised
-Cut him some slack , his mouth was full
-He was just surprised
Honestly, I was just surprised
He put so many in, so easily
and quickly, I was shocked
Now that I saw that
I gotta really hold it in now
Oh and if you get hungry ,
feel free to use the phone
to order pizza or sushi, heres the numbers
Ahh that spells danger
-This is gonna be tough
-I gotta be more self-conscious y'all
Only after watching myself
I realized I was laughing
Here we go
-Are you gonna do it Akiyama?
- You can do atleast 10 right?
-How many?
-What if you do 10 at once?
Instead of doing it one by one
Just put alot at once
You wanna do 13 at once?
-Lets do 10
-10?
So thats how he wants to do it
He had that under his shirt
Beautiful
Umemiya-san please open your mouth
a bit more
Wouldnt it be harder with the
tongue sticking out?
Its one of your favorites
Beef sausage
You like that, dont you?
-Ah really?
-You like beef sausages?
Where do you get your sausages from?
You like all kind of meat right?
Not all meat is the same
I prefer steak
This is really difficult
Jinnai-san you do it
Alright I will do one at a time
Thats a really small mouth
Not just on the picture
Ok hes got it
-How many should I do?
-5 or 6 should be fine
-I'll do 3
The meat smells good right?
-If it didnt smell good, I wouldnt eat it
-How much meat do you usually eat?
When I eat, I eat like
400-500 of them
-Wait , hold on
-Its only 4 so far
Should I keep going?
No more
Did he say..
-Umemiya san?
-Ah , I cant really fit more
How many were in ?
Ah only 4
-Ah it came out
- Cant see through that right?
I couldnt fit anymore
It was too much
I was starting to gag
-Oh we got something else
-What is it?
I have this um
Duck Eye Light game
If you take these and the eyes light up
then you made the correct choice
Among these 4, 2 don't light up.
choosing the ones that light up gets you the win
-When you hold them they light up?
-Hold and press the button
Let me show you
-Right choice!
-But isnt that the mouth?
-So Duck Mouth Light
-Yeah the mouth lights up
-And thats the correct choice?
-Yeah since these light up
-So who wants to give it a shot?
-You get 2 at a time?
-Yeah so you choose 2 at a time
-And you just chose the right ones?
Alright, please pay attention
-Does someone want to do this challenge?
-I'll do it
Is it really difficult?
Its difficult when you have to choose
the correct pairs
Then that was impressive
that you did it
What happened?
It..uh
It shocked me
Really?
I was suprised
Try doing it
I dont know..
-Did it really shock you?
-Maybe it was just me
Watch out behind you
-Watch out, its Golgo
-Whats he doing
-Whats he doing?
-Looks dangerous
-Hes aiming at Jimmy-san
-Why are you aiming at me?
Isnt it really hot?
You want to...
isnt it hot?
Its really hot
Its so hot
Whats this?
If both of the ducks that you choose,
light up, then you win
-You choose two? which ones
-Whichever your want
2 of them light up
and the other two dont
Hold them and press them
from both sides
-The metal part is fine?
-Yeah, if it lights up, then you win
-It hurts
It hurts, it hurts....
Eh?
-What happened?
-Huh?
Huh?
-They all light up, dont they?
-Thats weird
You were just pretending
you werent feeling it right?
They all lit up
Wait, why is this not shocking you?
-Whats happening?
-Shigeo, check it out
If you do just one,
its fine?
Just drop it in
my hand
-I am scared
-Once you know it its scary
That really shocked me
Eh?how?
Thats unbelievable, how can
he just bear it
Are you not feeling it?
-Its fine
-If hes holding it like that, it must be fine
Yeah
I can do 4 at once too
Eh? No dont do that
-Thats really something, I dont get it
-Arent you just pulling a poker face?
-Are you actually feeling it?
-Yeah, I can feel the electricity flowing
That much at once gotta
be really powerful
It must be very painful
-You gotta do 2 at the same time?
-Yeah
-So you hold it and press it?
We did tell you, it does that
What happened?
Whats making that sound?
-Eh? what is that?
-What ? what?
-It sounds like something vibrating
--Something down there
-It happened because of the electricity?
Ah its a vibrator
Isnt that dangerous?
The electricity from this turned it on
-Thats crazy
-Turn it off, and do it again
-Who are you?
Who is it?
Are you asking about me?
Me?
Sato Mascar Yojiro
I am Sato Mascar Yojiro
Hafu usually refers to half-japanese
-I am a Hafu
-Eh?
I am a Hafu
-Sato?
-Yeah, Mascar Yojiro
What are your two halves?
England and.....
Canada
What an uncommon mix!
Yeah but it happens
What is this?
It turned on, because of these
Try doing two
Yeah press it while holding it
-Like this?
-Yeah
-Both sides?
That hurts
I am sorry
-Eh? what? Blue eyes?
-Blue eyes?
Yeah, since I am a Hafu
I see.
Werent there any bluer
contacts?
-Eh? This is supposed to be funny?
-Who would laugh at this
Because you look like
a hafu?
-So you put the contacts?
-Whats your mix?
-England and Canada
-Didnt you say that earlier?
I will be going back
Oh you are going back?
-That was it?
-What do you do?
My profession?
Um..
I live in Tokyo
and have a gift-shop
What do you sell there?
-Chicks (young birds)
-Like this too?
-Yeah, different kinds of things
-You sell these too?
-These too?
-Yeah these are the new ones,
we do Chick Manjuu too
-Thats all you sell?
-We sell Electric Chick, Chick Manjuu
Chick Magnets, Chick Pasta
-How do you make that?
-Using chicks
-You use meat of the chicks?
I have to be leaving soon
What do you need to do?
Take the Bullet Train
The train
-Ill be leaving then
-Alrigh then
-Thank you
-Take care
-Hes got a strong heart
-The eyes were too dark
-Should we play cards?
-Yeah lets do it
Lets play cards
But what are we playing?
-How about Poker?
-With so many people?
-Then should we play Daifugo?
-Yeah thats fine
-You know how to play Daifugo, right?
-Yeah
It slides so easily
-Hes like a dealer
-Jimmy-san do you know Daifugo?
-Yeah I am familiar with that
Joker is the strongest and 3 is the weakest card
and if a pair comes out
You have to beat it with a higher pair
The objective is to get rid
of your cards?
-Yeah
-You gotta get rid of your cards
Eh?
-The 3 of-
-Which ones did you just put?
-Eh I got good cards
What just happened?
-Eh what?
-Why were you laughing?
-Was it something I said?
No, Junior-san wrote something on
these cups
Ichiro
-You really like that bit dont you?
-Wait what was it?
I couldnt tell what made you laugh
That.....Ichiro
Whats funny about that?!
From that earlier Ichiro bit, it was..
I thought oh not that again
Yellow!
Wait, I mean its supposed to
be orange
But I am still..
-You wanna check?
-But it really was funny
Alright, lets have a look then
-It really was funny
- If it turns out to be
the source of laughter
I mean names can be
really funny too
What is causing you to laugh?
Surely, there must be a reason
-Eh I got some good cards
Hes not even trying to hold it in
He was full on laughing
but there was a reason for laughing
Resisting laughing actually
becomes very
funny too, everyone
Who put it here right?
Kobayashi
He did?
But this sucks
I havent even done anything so far
This is no good
-You had a bad start this time, Jimmy.
-Seriously, dont tell me you set me up
Seriously, I didnt
-You forgot to take that one
-Yeah , I know
-Jimmy is in trouble
-Theres one there, look
-Uh oh, Jimmys gonna..
-Which is the stronger card? I have no idea
-What is this?
Jimmy-san can you look at the
egg ?
-Just once
-Alright I will
-Who put it there?
-Kobayashi did
What about Ichiro?
That..
I already looked at it once
I looked at it already
-Just one more time
-I looked at it already
-Just ONE more time?
-I already did
-Please just once more?
Do it once more please
Ok, then just
-Just once more right?
-Isnt it just a normal egg?
-Its just a normal egg right?
-I know..
Wait a minute, wait wait
Hold on, I was just starting to get used to it
-You cant be serious
-Why did you even laugh?
You were laughing so easily
-You kept talking about the egg
-Whats funny about that? Its just an egg
-Theres nothing funny about this
-Its just an egg nothing more
The scale usually is lower where the weight is
I thought when is it gonna go down
Its not a scale
-This is just a candle holder
-Oh really? thats what it is?
Was that really it?
-You thought it was a scale?
-Yeah I thought it was strange that its not tilting
-I thought its so weird
-Why would the egg stay like that on a scale?
I thought it was just a really light egg
-Thats what made you laugh?
-Ah this cant be
Wait , wait  I didnt even...
You really laughed a lot
At the end, he laughed so easily
-Lets see it
-He couldnt stop laughing
-One more time
-I already did
-Just once more?
-Alright just once
I should just look at it right?
Isnt it just a normal egg?
-Why did you laugh?
-What was even funny?
-Why couldnt you hold it in?
-Its ok, we still have Zombie Time
-Yeah thats still
-During Zombie Time you can make them laugh
-Zombie is allowed to laugh too
-This Zombie is gonna be a tough one
Its gonna be a very tough Zombie
-You guys better prepare yourselves for the Zombie
-I didnt even get to do much
-Everyone crushed him together but
the crushed one will be back
What do you mean
the crushed one
You brought all that
Alright then
He will back as a Zombie
-Because of a white egg
-That was quick
I didnt get to do ANYTHING
Junior-san..
is really talented
Everyone was on the offensive and I got caught in that
and during that time
I couldnt endure it
and ended up losing
I am disappointed in myself
because I coudnt persevere
Its a bit..