Documental is like a mental game right?
I have yet to be in a situation where I am
driven into a corner like an animal
in a life and death situation, trying to figure out how to escape
Basically its a very uncertain thing whether someone
will laugh at something that you think is funny or not...
One can laugh at anything
When its something funny
and even when its not
[Recap}
To make someone laugh you have to
be creative
and you try to think outside the box
Its gets really difficult when you keep thinking
about which thing will make them laugh and which wont
[Recap]
Alright
Is the meat done?
-Its done but..
-Thank you
-Are you gonna eat?
-Yes
Kurosawa-chan you dont have a mirror by any chance?
-Ah I just have this
-Oh thats fine too, thank you
-Mirror?Theres a mirror in there too
Oh I just thought it was way over there
You are using that to wipe it off?
Yeah
Thats just one sheet
-You cant take it all off with one
-I dont need to take all of it off
-Eh?
-Eh?really?
It sucks but thats all I have
Most of it comes off with one wipe
Its really bright
If you do it fast it doesnt come off, so you have to
slowly do it
Oh it all comes off you do that?
-You have to keep doing it like this
-The face looks so small now
-The face seems tiny
-Oh wow! Thank you so much
-That looks amazing
-Meats ready!
Thank you Miyasako-san
-Wow
-That looks delicious!
-As if from a Restaurant
-Yummy
-Wow
-That looks delicious!
-As if from a Restaurant
-Yummy
-It looks amazing!
-Delicious looking
Seriously, looks amazing
Oh you cant eat it
-Huh?
-Eh?
Since I cooked it
Eh?
-Eh?
I just only said that its done
Eh?
But you didn't bring this meat, did you?
Anyone can eat it if they cook it, and since I am the chef
But earlier you said it was for everyone right?
No, I meant I will show everyone how its cooked
-Eh?
-Huh?
Eh?
-Eh?
Hmm?
-We really cant eat it?
-No, its only for me
-One person cant finish it
- Theres  alot of meat
-There will be leftovers
-Eh?
huh?
You know you are not supposed to eat the leftover food
at a restaurant
It looks really good
I am gonna take some
With the Okinawan Sauce
A-1 Sauce
Adds a little kick to it
Delicious!
-I'll try it too
- Lets try it
-Ah, ah
-Ah
-eh?
Alright I am full, I am gonna put it away
-No dont do that
-No
Alright , then
Ok, If you do a gag then you can eat it
-Why cant we eat it without doing that?
-Do you want to eat or not?
You cant get it for nothing
So what should we do?
Some kind of gag or impression
Thats a little weird
Can you show us an example? I dont know what thing to do
Anything really, something original
Like something like this?
Yeah?
-That kind of gag?
-Like that?
-Do like an introductory gag
-Oh so "Hello" and then
-Is it something like that?
-That would be an introductory gag
-Hows that?
-Alright you can eat it
-Ah, thank you
-Eh?
-Huh?
-Its because I did the gag
-Really?
-Thats how it should be
-Yeah
This looks really good
What are you doing?
Why not just eat it right away?
-I was just practicing, like golf
-Practicing how to eat?
-You need to practice that?
-Yeah
-Heres Chopstick Man
-Alright, you can eat
-Thank you
Wait, you can do anything?
-That was perfect
-Right?
Its so good!
Seriously, wow
Really delicious
How about that?
I am a nosey person
[Laughter]
Hes a snotty kid
Ku-chan just laughed,right?
-I wasnt laughing
-It wasnt you?
-Who was it?
-I just did that, is that not allowed?
-Eh
-Then..
-Matsumoto-san
-I didnt make a sound or anything
-This time theres two people
-Eh?really?
-And Daigo gets a point
-Yeah
-Ku-chan was a little..
-Ah, no
Aaah
-Ok lets see whether Ku-chan laughed or not
It did seem like he was
-Ah I see, but its not certain right?
-Yeah so lets watch it
-Hows that?
I am a nosey person
-Thank you
It was really quick, I wasnt laughing right?
Right, it wasnt a laugh right?
-Ah so what should we do? Is Ku-chan in the clear?
Ok hes clear
-But there was another one, Itoda
-So it was me?
-Yeah
-Hows that?
I am a nosey person
-How about that?
-Is that considered laughing?
That was a bit too much
-Really?
-Yeah
-Seriously?
-Ok I accept that
-Kuro's got nothing right?
-Kuro chans clear
-I havent gotten any card yet
Are you even real? You dont laugh at all
-Is something wrong with you or what?
-No thats not it at all
-Thats weird, he doesnt laugh at all
-Thats not true
-Yeah but he doesnt have any points either
-Yeah hes at zero right?
-Yeah nothing so far
But what about when I drank milk?
-I wonder what he will do
-We gotta make him laugh
Right?
We gotta make it even
[Clock Beep]
Here we go again
Its really juicy inside
Its really good
I think everyone forgot about Zombie Time
-So good
-Its delicious, right?
Its the first time that
one zombie is against 9 people
Zombie time
Oh! I forgot about that
Isnt it just Nobu?
-Just him?
-Just one person?
I dont think anyones gonna be laughing
I agree
Oi! Oi
Eh?
Madness! Its crazy out there
Zombie room is flooded this high
Eh?
Inside the Zombie Room, this high
All the way here
-But his back is completely dry
-It really is
Just the front?
-Were you floating like this?
-This high
Eh?
I was like this
Really?
Prepare yourselves, Zombie Room is really scary
-Theres water in the hallway too?
-As soon as you enter?
They throw you in there like that
So hallway too?
They throw you in there yet your back is dry?
You were in there all this time?
Yeah all this time
-Thats not a way to treat people
and under the water too
What was under the water?
-A Spear-wielding knight doing this
-A knight?
-The Knight, what was he like?
-This tall
-like a Ninja?
-It wasnt just a statue?
-From all sides he was doing this
-A spear-wielding knight?
-Please be careful
-Ok
- Later then.
Later
Daichi Mao-san sent this and
wished you luck , Miyasako-san
-Really?
-Eh?
You know her?
Yeah Since I am a fan
You saw her today?
Not really
-Then how did you get that?
-Who gave it to you?
-Shes sitting behind Matsumoto-san
-Shes the special guest this time?
-Really?
Seriously?
Right next to Matsumoto Daichi
So theres two MC's?
Yeah theres two MC's this time
Really?
From the flower side,  batter number 4
Is it a good idea to do this
in front of Daichi-san?
They are watching right now
Thats not gonna look good
-I think hes just doing whatever
-Really?
-Alright lets just do our thing then
-I wanna eat
Its delicious
-Its the best steak I have ever had
-Its really good
The sauce is really good too
Yeah its not too bad
Its a bit like Steak-don
(don=rice bowl)
-Right?
-Yeah
-It would be great with lettuce right?
I'll be back again
I'll be right back
I'll be back later
It goes really well with it
If that zombie had kept going
-He would have started crying
-He has a very strong spirit, however
-He really does
Maybe when he goes home today
hes gonna cry
-It got a bit quiet
-huh?
It got a little quiet right?
-Yeah a little bit
Lets roll over
If you roll over, you might break your fingers
-Who is it?
-Who is that?
You can't see, you bastards?
Bakufu Slump
Whos that?
I am Barbecue Wasada
-Theres no one like that
-Right?
You said Barbecue Wasada?
-Its Pappara.
-It changed?
Pappara-san looks like this?
-Not at all
-No
-Is that the hat?
-Yeah, the hat
-Isnt that just tape?
-No its a hat
-Its a hat
-What did you come here for?
-Thats a good move
Is  that Yamamoto Shinya?
Hes impersonating him
Its a game
You shouldnt let your feelings out in a game
Huh?
Controlling your emotions is a strong point
Ah if you want to play a good match
you should hide your weaknesses?
Yeah, exactly
He is Barbecue Suikichi-san?
-He changed it a few times and now..
-Funky
-Funky,. isnt that just your normal voice?
-Why?
Are you Pappara-san?
Oh, me?
Nishioka... Sumiko
Nishioka Sumiko?
No way! You came here?
Can I go back to normal now?
Eh?
You werent forced to do it
It became a little complicated right?
Became too complicated
Doing Bakufu Slump's impression is pretty difficult
-You were changing it too much tho right?
-Yeah
-I didnt know what you were trying to do
I was trying to do multiple impressions
Oh so thats what you were trying to do?
Here he comes
He took so long just for this?
Wow
You were in there for so long, for this?
-Oh it was a little hot so I went and changed
-But earlier...
What made you think
thats funny?
Huh?
What is that?
-They are overalls, Its really hot so..
-I know they are overalls
Thats the reason?
Yeah
Whats funny about that?
Funny?
Eh?
But if you wanted to make us laugh
How is wearing those overalls any funny?
Funny?
-Its not supposed to make us laugh?
-Not at all
I just changed because its hot
-We are not children you know
-You are not children?
We are adults so we wouldnt laugh at that
Because you are trying hard not to?
Not just because of that
-Its open from the side
-huh?
-Its open there
-on the side
-We can see it
-You can see it
-Right here
Why? it fits well
Whats this?
-Whos that?
I am called Kishi Daisuke
I am on my break during a photoshoot
(one of his famous gags)
and I was a bit restless
Cant you take the wig off for now?
I will be going back anyways so its ok
How long is your break?
-84 hours
-Thats a long time
Usually its not that long
-You should take it off
-yeah you should
I cant take it off now
Did you bring something?
Ah this is..
Fish Hamburger
Eh?
-Fish Hamburger
-Unbelievable
-Theres three of them
-Three?
-You only eat that?
-Eat atleast one with meat
Isnt the shirt too big?
Its XS
-XS?
-Yeah XS
-Isnt it XL?
-No this is XS, since its from Africa
-Ah thats why its so big huh
Its a shirt from Africa, thats why
What are you workin on at the moment?
What I am working on right now?
-Yeah your current project
What I am working on right now is called
"Kishi Daisuke's Male Ninja"
-"Male ninja"
-Is that why the hair?
-His fighting skills must be really good
-Oh thats right
Are you gonna show us?
Its definitely gonna be good
-Whoever can hit you?
-Yeah thats fine
Ok, stop it
-His head must be hurting
-That wig is really tight too
-His head must be hurting alot
Kichi-san is pretty weak
Ok wait stop
What was that?
-People who are in those shows are usually
good at fighting right?
-You can start yourself if you want.
-That was sudden
-Thats dangerous
Adults shouldnt act like that you know
Two handed style
-That was awesome
-Hes really strong
Thank you very much
-Kuro-chan is that really..
-Huh?
You changed because it was hot?
Yes
-Is it not hot?
-Sorry, I shouldnt have said those things earlier
Its that hot to you?
Not really
Who would laugh at that?
Huh?
-Why?what happened?
-You know why
Oh you guys saw it?
Well whatever
Oh whats that?
Eh?
Its the Ice Bucket Challenge
People still do it?
Who challenged you to do it?
Umm.. I dont know
You dont know that?
Thank you for waiting
Sorry for making you guys wait so long
Ah I made you guys wait huh?
Alright, go ahead
Ah thank you for waiting
-Can we ask you questions?
-Yeah go ahead
Ask me anything
-Ask me about any problem you have
-Anything?
My..
Shoulder when I move it
Its been hurting recently, so what
should I do?
Eat some chanko
Chanko is a type of stew
Chanko
-That was pretty fast
-Eating chanko will fix it
-With vegetables too
-Ah? just eat alot of chanko?
-I live in an apartment but
-You live in an apartment
-the neighbors dog is really noisy
Eat Chanko every wednesday, alright?
Really?
Eating chanko will help
Whenever you are hungry, just have some chanko
right away
-Chanko works for everything?
-Yeah for everything
Pro-wrestlers eat it too.
With fish, meat, vegetables
everything.
-My tooth hurts
-Toothache?
Eat some chanko
with the left side of your mouth
Right side hurts right?
With left side, eat some chanko
It works pretty good
Its good for you
-Chanko for everything?
-Yeah Chanko works for everything
Thats how I was able to become like this
-You do Sumo?
-No, I do Wrestling
-Arm wrestling
-Arm wrestling?
Hows your performance?
6 wins, 27 losses and 937 draws
Thats alot of draws
Wow
-Even if you try hard you cant win?
-Its really tough
-Isnt it crazy?
-Do you eat Chanko?
Yeah ofcourse
You eat it and still so weak?
-No thats what makes me strong
-If I didnt eat it I would be weak
-What do you like about Chanko?
What do I like about Chanko? Thats a good question
Whats your name?
-Terryman
-Terryman? thats a good name
I love the flavors of Chanko, when my mom makes it
-You like the Chanko that your mom makes?
-Ah thats enough
-Whats all this?
-That,  I wanna know too
-Really?
I wanna eat Chanko right now
That would be great
Alright lets all eat Chanko together
Whats he doing?
Its the Ice Bucket challenge
Thats admirable
Here I go
[Weird Kuro Chan Noises]
Eat some Chanko! It helps when its cold
-Chanko
Is he gonna be ok?
-Are you cold?
-Yeah
He must be cold
Are you looking for your t-shirt?
-Since you are cold, I'll give you this
Its so cold
The wind is so cold
-You are drinking that?
-Yeah
Just stop that ok?
Its full of minerals
Cant believe he drank it
Its ok
-Is that lotion?
I thought it would be good to have
for when I work out
Is that so?
-Yes
You should have eaten Chanko instead
-Cant believe he drank that lotion
-Eat some Chanko
-Will this not help?
-Eat Chanko
-I cant even watch
-Ugh
What are you doing man?
-Are you serious?
-What are you doing?
I am trying to swallow it
You are not supposed to drink that
-Do you have a headache?
-Its been hurting since earlier right?
-Its alright
Let me see
You are such an idiot
What was that?Someone hit me?
He forgot
Did something happen?
You were just feeling hot
We still have that right?
-Zombie Time is not gonna be invoked right?
-Because theres only one zombie
Since theres only 1, He cant do much either
And there hasnt been much movement either
-Alright alright
Its tough
Things are starting to move
Its sudden but I was wondering
if you could try something on for me
-Who are they for?
-Will they fit anyone?
Daigo-kun
These
Thats uh..
-Daigo?
-Or maybe Iio-san
Me?
-Its a leotard
-Just that?
So just try it on?
Daigo-san or Iio san can try it
Cant refuse since she went to
the trouble, right?
-Ah then Fujimoto-san
-Why me?
-Thats weird why me?
-Since its not very modest
-Didnt you say it should be Daigo or Iio-san?
Since you are so nice
What even is this?
Its golden too
If it was silver I would wear it but its golden
-This?
What happened?
-Hes looking at something
-Jun-san?
-Its his mom
He must really love his mom
-Homemade video?
-Shes amazing for 60 yrs old right?
-Shes pretty sexy
-Thats amazing
Oh!
Amazing!
-Thats really something
-I am happy that you wore it
-What kind of look is that?
-The naval looks weird doesnt it
-Is that the naval?
-Its really big
-
Is that your navel?
-Isnt that kinda big?
Yeah right there
-Theres something inside there right?
-It looks kind of big and round
-Is that the belly button?
-Really?
Hows that the belly button?
Its just a big belly button
Belly button?
-Its really portruding, the belly button
-Right?
Thats the wrong one
-She recorded it
-Wow
In the voice recorder
-Why did she record it?
She really recorded it
It feels weird, what did you
want me to do?
You should dance to the beat
[Kurosawa's Magical Singing]
.
~Whether the darkness prevails or the day breaks
I live life to its fullest~
I did not know
What it was like to get hurt before
meeting you
It feels like the world has stopped turning
and time has stopped moving
and you are oblivious to it
That the time has stopped moving~
What does it mean to be free?
Oh tell me what it means to be free
Tell me do you know
What that means
Please help me
I beg you
Please for the love of god
Help me please
Someone please
Please save me from this
Theres no getting out of this
So forget about trying to get out of this
I beg you
Please save me
-Did anyone see a Puma wallet?
-From earlier
-I really cant find it
-you lost it?
Did anyone take the Puma wallet?
-Its not here
-It really was here
-You do Judo?
Yeah
Even when I dont do Judo, I wear this
-You wear these as your normal clothes?
-Yeah these are my plain clothes too
Please dont take the Puma wallet
But there was no Puma wallet here
-Dont know anything about that
I actually lost it somewhere here
Its Puma?
-Yes
What color is it?
Its a checkered pattern
You are looking for it?
Yeah
How did you lose the wallet?
Eh?
"You come on"
"You you come on"
"you you"
"you you you come on"
What ..
What kind of person are you usually?
Usually, usually
what kind of person are you?~
Usually I am a happy person
Usually, what kind of feelings do you have?Oh Oh
--
Hes looking cute today too~
He is always careful
He is always humble
Teddy bear-chan, Cute bear-chan
[Laugh]
That was something else
-So tired , so
That took so long
That took really long
-Sorry
That just went on and on
-Daigo!
-Eh?
-Really? it was him?
He had been slightly smiling for a really long time
-"Teddy Bear -chan" is the one that got me
--
Teddy Bear-chan, Cute Bear-chan
[Laughing]
-This is definitely
-Yeah, that was a smile
I already had an orange didnt it?
-Yeah
-Really?
-Yeah so he will be eliminated and become a zombie
Now we will have a tough zombie
We were all thinking he probably cant
do much as a zombie
-Alright lets go, Daigo
-Daigo will be a zombie now
It should go faster from now on
But you know Kuro-chan
still hasnt gotten anything
-Thats true
-Seriously
Kuro-chan doesnt laugh at all
Kuro-chan what can we do to make you laugh?
-No idea
Ah why did this happen
I am not really sure myself
It was difficult to maintain a "straight" face, because
my normal face seems like a smile
So I had to really force it
It was a learning experience but
You cant help but laugh at those 4
Especially when the "animal" entered
That bit was really good
Teddy Bear-chan
Here we go
-Kuro chan has no cards so far
Lets all try to make him laugh
-I agree
Its like nothing makes him laugh
-Can he even laugh?
Its hard to know what to do
Ah- can you do it slowly please?
Sorry, It hurts if you do it fast
That kind of..
-Doesnt she look like Oshima there?
-She really does
Since shes part of the trio
-Whats that dog for?
-I just thought it was cute
Its a bit weird but yes
Murakami-san?
Appearance of Oshima,
Actions of Kurosawa
-Shes like 3 in 1
-right?
Thats amazing
- Thats a full package
What was that?
It was Janet Jackson
-Janet Jackson?
-Ah The Superbowl halftime-show incident
That controversial incident right?
[Janet Jackson Singing]
Janet Jackson
-Ah I see
-The super bowl incident right?
-Ah thats what it was
[Singing]
--
Whats "nogera"?
-It doesnt mean anything really
-Ah it was just made up
-I see
That was great
Hes back with the same thing
I thought it would be good to wear this again
You are feeling hot?
Are you guys fine with it?
-Its not that hot
Eh?
When did this happen?
What is this?
Eh?
What is this rubber? Can you take it off?
-Take it off
Alright
Take it, take it
Yeah just pull it off of me I dont want it
It didnt come off
-You want us to pull it off?
-Yeah pull it hard
Are you sure?
Ah
It didnt come off, You should have pulled it all the way
I am taking it off of you, isnt that what you wanted?
You can take it off from here too
-Take it off of me!
-Thats what we are doing
-It hurts
There you go
-Isnt that what you wanted?
-You could have taken it off yourself
-Pulling it wont work
-Isnt it a little hot?
--
Eh?
Its still here
Pull it off of me
You just want us to hit you with it?
You are gonna do the same thing again?
Stop with the "huh?"
Just stop that ok
Do some capoeira
-Capoeria?
-Yeah
-Ah you can do that right?
Ok thats enough alright?
Dont do the capoeira anymore
Dont stand so close to me
-Do it Kuro-chan
-This is your chance
This is your chance
You can make him laugh,
Get closer
Why?
-It smells rotten
No Its your mind that is rotten
Miyasako-san
-That hurt! What strength!
"What strength!"
Miyasako-san
You want another one?
-No way
-Miyasako-san, Miyasako-san, Why?
Look at me
-What a great punch by The Great GenIchiro
(A famous wrestler)
Whats funny about that?
-I think hes done with you
-Miyasako-San
-Thats how it is
-Eh? what are we doing now?
Are you depressed or something?
-No thats not-
-Theres a porno mag here
Who brought this porno mag here?
Do you think its appropriate?
To bring it to a place like this?
What were you thinking?
Who was it?
Is it me?
I almost laughed too
That was a hard one
( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)
How can you get hard in this situation?
Are you serious?
but Miyazawa-san actually got you erect
Howc can you even get hard in this situation?
Its Iio
It would be really hard to get erect in this kind of situation
Who is it?
Who is it? Its you!
Its Iio
Who brought this porno mag here?
Do you think its appropriate?
Bringing it to a place like this
What were you thinking?
Who was it?
Since you already had an orange, you will be eliminated
-I wonder what made him crack
-Definitely the penis
-This really is a first isnt it?
-So it seems
To get hard in this kind of situation
it really is unprecedented
Well done, Iio-san
It was a pleasure
Thank you very  much
Ah thats it then
-Theres fewer now eh
-Its getting lonelier
I really didnt expect that
he would do something like that
It made me laugh
When Matsumoto-san entered
he didnt have any doubt who it was
When he entered he was laughing so
It definitely was a funny thing
and that was  bit of a relief
that he found it funny too
otherwise I would have been disappointed
--
-Kuro-chan you still dont have anything right?
-What makes you laugh?
-Like in general, what do you find funny?
Axel Hopper-san
-No way!
-Are you serious?
I really like his act
Other than that I am not really sure
So Axel Hopper makes you laugh?
Yeah
Oh you know how to do it Fujimoto
Alright sit down and watch him
Fujimoto is gonna do it
Poin Poin Supa Poin Poin
Baka Tempo
He didnt laugh at all
-It was a little different
What do you mean it was different?
Thats what he does
Why are you getting mad?
-We dont know how to make you laugh
Give us a hint or something
Ok Normally, what do you laugh at?
-I really like dirty humor
But you didnt laugh at Miyasakos bit
That just seemed too serious so I was surprised
But isnt that better?
Ok what kind of dirty humor?
Like um.....someones testicles getting touched
-What do you mean? hows that
-If you see that happening you will know what I mean
-Hows touching testicles funny?
-So if  you see that you will laugh?
-Yeah lets do that
-Someone will get their balls out and then you have to laugh
-Whos balls do you wanna see?
-Yeah whos do you wanna see
Who's balls?
Go ahead and choose the person
Alright, Choose the balls
Me?
Yeah I wanna see what yours are like
-Jun-chan's balls?
My balls are really nice looking
"i wanna see what your balls are like"
Why does he wanna see Itoda's balls
Hes doing it so slowly
--
They are really cute testicles
How do you want me to touch them?
-Miyasako-san are you gonna touch them?
Yeah
How do you want me to touch them?
Between you and the sky~
A cold wind blows today too~
For the sake of making you laugh~
I would even turn into a devil~
Between you and the sky~
Thats really nice
A cold wind blows today too
For the sake of making you laugh~
I would even turn into a demon
-You are looking right?
-Yeah I am
That seriously stinks
-No way!
-Jun, thats really nasty
-Seriously
-What the hell man
-Jun-chan you really did that?
-Jun..
I was really surprised
Wipe that off the floor
Jun...
This is...
-Kuro-chan, wipe the floor
-Ok
-It just came out
-How can that happen
-What are you doing Jun?
-Seriously
This guy is such an idiot
-What did you do that for?
-Sorry, because of the touching I couldnt hold it in
-Hold this too
-Yeah sorry
Uh why is it so hard to wipe off the piss
Its not even coming out
It was only a little bit
Wait wait, let me clean you
-What were you thinking, pissing here
-Sorry
That much came out?
-Dont give me so little
This much is not enough
-Hes laughing now
He laughed!
Yeah he just laughed
-Dirty humor is my weak point
-Thats what you laugh at?
Ah is that really what made you laugh?
-"Dont give me so little"
-Ah thats what really made you laugh?
That was really embarrassing
Matsumoto-san, Please come here
-What was that?
- I dont know what just happened
You cant just apologize
Back there everyone was
laughing their asses off
His urethra just went like this
For the sake of making you laugh
I would even become a demon
You are looking right?
-Yea I am
-What did you do that for?
-Sorry, because of the touching I couldnt hold it in
Uh why is it so hard to wipe off the piss
-Hold it yourself
-sorry
-Dont give me so little
This much is not enough
-Hes laughing now
-He laughed!
-Alright Kuro-chan Yellow card
-Alright
Still hes only gotten Yellow
-But finally, someone made him laugh
-I was able to hold it in during Jun-san's bit but
-When I was passing him the paper towel
and he said "dont give me so little"
I was thinking maybe he got some on his hand
So thats what you were laughing at?
[Sub End] Thank you for watching.
By Delicious_Course632