Librarian's Note: Not Subbed until 00:30
Last week's broadcasting
Subtitles starts at 10 seconds. (this part is a recap. Kinda pointless and hard to understand)
Cocorico Endo's Shichi-Henge
It's hard to think that Tanaka won't succeed, there are no doubts
Rules of Shichi-henge (seven transformations): During the planning meeting, the performer must make one "trasformation" after another. For each time someone is seen laughing, he's prized with 1milion yen!
Because he can perfom 7 characters, right?
That's right
So... let's call Tanaka here, ok?
Ok!
Cocorico's Tanaka, please!
Thanks, good morning!
So, now are you ready to perform perfectly?
Cocorico Tanaka Naoki
I think that the chance of failing is far away, by now
Where do you think you're going to end up in the ranking?
Of course, the top!
That's great!
Because I'm a comedian!
Though, those people were very funny
*Matsumoto is mocking Tanaka by pointing his partner, Endo, which scored the bronze medal.
Yeah yeah, funny...
If I end up getting lower than Yamazaki, than that's a total fail for me.
I'd say that everywhere is fine, as long as you can impress this guy (Hamada)
That's absolutely right!
I don't how can I impress him, though
That's because he's a strange sadist.
Translation, Subtitles, Encoding, Timing etc. etc. by Shion (youtube.com/user/ForegroundNoises)
So everyone, what should we do?
Planning meeting
Our number kinda increased since the other day...
Uhm... Let's see.
"Gaki no Tsukai staff family's athletic meet opposition"?
Producer - Suga Kenji
Isn't this good?
I'm dead serious, let's do this.
What about "Yanawana (?) hits the budokan?"
Budokan: an indoor arena in central Tokyo, where famous artists perform music live showsYanawana(?): That's gotta be something Hawaii-related
Shichi-Henge begins!
That's going to be good right? A hawaiian is totally random there
Though, I really want to see the "Family's Athletic Meet"!
Speaking of which, that's why we need Endo as a team member
And even a recovery place
No, that's just a little of a bad thought.
Right, uh?
Right.
Penalty
*Each time you spot 罰金 the meaning "penalty" is repeated
What's the meaning of this?
The oxygen that runs off by farting...
Running out oxygen with farts...
The pitch of the farts had me.
Agreed
Man, he's totally going to hit the podium.
*Tanaka is wearing the outfit of a Tengu (天狗), a mythical japanese creature with a long nose.
The funny thing is that he's smelling his armpits with it.
Cocorico Endo Shozo
That's so unfair...
That was dangerous!
What do you propose, Yamazaki?
I wonder what can we do...
Should we do a Goodbye Party Consolation?
A Goodbye Party Consolation? No good.
Is that so?
Yes.
Do I look good?
Where aren't they pointy?
That was unexpected!
Hamada laughs way too easily!
That's Right!
I always laugh 'cause he's laughing.
In the previous skit, when he was laughing
"Damn, he's already laughing!" I thought.
Maybe we should perform stand-alone entering next time, right?
Right
With your right, your right.
Raise your elbow, raise it-
All right, let's go to the court
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm really sorry
"I'm sorry for touching your butt"
That was unfair
Really!
Wow! That's a nice amount!
If it keeps like that, Tanaka's estimation will start to escalate, that's bad.
Who knows...
I'm sorry
Everyone is saying "Kitana!" meaning "How Dirty!"
That's against good manners!
That was filthy, wasn't it?!
It totally was.
Enough of fart-gags, geez.
You're right, geez!
Here
I probably won't have enough money to come back (home).
Here we go again, Hamada's laugh that makes me laugh!
That was impossible..
That was great!
Thanks!
How many money he gathered?
40,000 Yen!
Did he reach the top?
He reached the top.
Highest Money Amount: 40,000 Yen!
Congratulations on reaching the top!
Thank you!
1st: Cocorico Tanaka - 40,000 Yen
2nd: Director Ootomo - 29,000 Yen
3rd: Manager  Isomata - 25,000 Yen
Maaaaaaaaan!
Now get the hell back home.
Why?!
At this point, please let me say a thing:
*The money gathered in this project will be devoted in beneficence
Tanaka, you did well
You were funny
Even this last white-thingy
Subscribe for more clips! Read the description for infos / contacts / etc. ~Shion
uh-uh..
But that wig is not funny at all.
You mean those?
I think if it was completely smooth it would have been funnier.
He's right...
Completely smooth?
In that sense...
Wouldn't have been better to shave off your hair?
I'm not even able to make a comment about your last sentence!