Subbed by Mickstar813 & HouseiGIFs
On tonight's Gaki no Tsukai
a new challenge begins
5 men who aim for the summit of the comedian world
It's this... Breath Holding Challenge!
The name:
Breath Holding Challenge
Right, Matsumoto-san...
Yeah?
What are we doing today?
We've decided we need to form a new club
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Right!
And there are loads of clubs in this world
But the thing we are the best at...
has got to be "holding our breath"
Like hell we are
The 5 sleeping lions of Yoshimoto
I'm talking about us by the way
We were sleeping..?
Indeed...
So we're waking up now, correct?
We're going to form our "Breath Holding" club
Right!
Right here, today
Alright!
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
To see how long you can hold your breath for underwater...
Right
And we're going to have our first match today.
I see
And our leader for today
is Yamasaki Hosei-san
Alright!!
Zaki-san!
We're counting on you, boss
We are counting on you!
Yamazaki Hosei
Leader
I'm the leader?
Right.
Why's Yama-chan the leader?
Simply put, he's good at it
He's our secret weapon
Yeah.
Really?
He has a huge lung capacity
When you hold your breath, it's all about lung capacity
So
That's exactly what he just said
I just said that
You did, Endo-san did indeed say that
So basically, my lung capacity is awesome
No jokes here
What you mean by that?
No but like
I'm not just saying that and it turns out I do the worst
Oh right, I get you
So there's no anticlimax?
No.
We will definitely win
But you know, since it's the first ever match,
the staff haven't brought just any ol' regular opponents
I see
They've brought some serious opponents
They were told to come here at 3 o'clock apparently
Man, that's early
Well anyway, let's get the opponents of our first ever match in here
Please enter
What the hell is that?
Damn!
Amazing
They are totally 100% stupid
Damn
They are absolute idiots
Watch out!
That's dangerous...
Are you okay?
Alright!!
Here we are!
There's the father of all those idiots
Why was the father hiding below?
Office Kitano Team
I was a bit embarrassed, that's why...
Office Kitano Team...
Damn, they're going to be tough opponents
Yeah they are
You know...
Here they come
I'm sorry but
You've chosen the wrong opponents
Wait, why is that?
However you look at it,
when it comes to anything with water,
we are Number 1
Well, maybe that is the case
But don't underestimate our Yamasaki
Right?
We're going to do it
You have more lung capacity than any bug out there, right?
Yeah...
Are we really going to win..?
That's awful
What?
We will definitely win
Saying that,
I've actually played Darumasan ga Koronda (tag game) underwater.
Amazing
We're in trouble here...
You're working too hard, man
But we definitely won't lose though
and you guys, as well...
I don't think there's any point being that serious...
Don't say that!
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai
ya Arahende!!
We're going to win
This is a battle
This program is sponsored by the companies as seen onscreen
Anyway, it's a team competition
They time how long they can stay underwater
and add the times up to decide the winner at the end
So everyone has a go
back and forth
and then add all the times up at the end,
so please decide your team order
OK.
Right then, let's go ahead with it
And talking about orders, Kitano Team,
do you know who's going first?
I think we'll start with our weakest guy...
Me? Right then, I'm going first
We will then
Endo!
Right!
Endo Shozo
Round one
Mimata Matazou
I'll do my best
We're counting on you
I will, I'm going to really get stuck in
We can get a good few seconds more here
I will try my best
I'm going to win
I'm not going to lose, man.
Look at you, with your shit body
First up
Jordan's Mimata Matazou
First up, Office Kitano Team choose Mimata.
With his fat belly, will he be able to hold his breath for long?
Right then
First up for Office Kitano
Starting with Mimata
Why did I not get to decide which team went first?
You're being way too serious
Yeah, you really are
No, because it's easier to see how long the other person stayed under so you have something to aim for...
Well yeah, I get you
So maybe later on, we can make it so that you go first out of the two teams
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, sure we can do that
Yeah, that's fine
Then it's fair
Let's be fair
By the way, right now, the world record
World Record: 8 minutes 6 seconds
Martin Stepanek (Czech Republic)
Holding breath
is held by some bloke from Czech Republic
8 minutes, 6 seconds...
8 minutes?!
So yeah, try your best
I don't have to think about being funny, I just concentrate on this, right?
Of course
Have you ever even been funny before?
Oh yeah, sorry...
Like not at all...
As soon as your face goes past here, it starts
I understand
Right then, are you ready?
Yes!
Do your best!
Let's go then
Ready
Start
He's in
Do your best
Why is he playing with his hair..?
Wow
Can you hear us?
Oh my God, he's already struggling
He must be able to see us
Uh oh
He's struggling
He's struggling now
He's finished
We don't know what you're saying
I wonder why he's trying to talk to us...
Alright!!
Damn...
Result: 36 seconds
That's great for us!
It is
36 seconds!
Wait, what were you saying under the water?
I was saying "how long have I been under"
But obviously we can't hear you!
But 36 seconds isn't bad
Right?
I wonder...
Wait, you guys made this "club"... haven't you done it before?
Umm, no... This is our first time ever
First up
Endo Shozo
Gaki team, first up is Endo
He has plenty of energy from playing high school baseball, even with his belly.
We're counting on you, man
Honestly, when you get here, you get really nervous
Relax, man...
They're not used to this at all...
Right then
Endo, ready...
Start
Man he's got a serious face on
That's good
His concentration is good...
It really is
When little bubbles come up, that's a good sign
I see
He's quite good...
That's good
Right? Keep calm, man...
Exactly, keep calm...
Great stuff, Endo...
Hold on, it's getting a bit...
Keep calm
Uh oh!
Keep calm, you've still got a long way to go
Wasn't that bubble a bit big just now..?
This is bad
He's fine
He got over that hard part
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
You're fine still
He's done
That was good
Result: 47 seconds
47 seconds!
Next us is Taka-san and me
Hamada Masatoshi
Next up
Gatarukanaru Taka
We're counting on you
Let's widen the gap here
There's only a 11-second difference, right?
That's right
I'm sorry
but we're going to push you right to the limit
Next up
Gatarukanaru Taka
Kitano Team, next up is Gatarukanaru Taka, 45 years old
He's one of the elite comedians as well...
Oh man, it's really nice being in here
Oh really?
That feeling of returning home...
Oh man, when you get in, it's nice
Right then
Ready
Start
Look at that smile
He's really happy
Amazing
He's looking good
Compared to the wash basin, there's water pressure in this
Ah, I see.
So it gets harder
But is it okay for him to have his mouth open?
No, this is really bad
Why are you like sounding like a guide book for this..?
Uh-oh...
His face
Something's come out of his mouth!
You're kidding me!
He's finished soon!
No way, stay in longer!
Do your best!
His legs...
He's staying in there...
He's gotten over 50 seconds
Will he get 1 minute?
Amazing!
Result: 53 seconds
I wanted to get to 1 minute
Something weird came out of your mouth halfway through...
Damn, that's tough
Right then, leave it to me
What a guy...
We're counting on you
By the way, out of all of us, he's probably the worst...
He's probably the worst out of all of us
Next up
Hamada Masatoshi
Gaki Team, next up is Hamada
He's basically just a guy who sucks holding his breath; how well can he do?
How many seconds do I need?
Well we'd really like you to get at least 45 seconds
He got 53 seconds...
Yeah, there's a 42-second difference right now
Office Kitano Team: 42 second lead
So if you get 45 seconds...
You can see the timer from inside
Could you?
No, not at all
Oh, can't you?
You need goggles
Someone get me some goggles then
No, because if you do that, we can't laugh at your face
That's true
You can't put goggles on in here
Yeah, otherwise we can't get a good reaction from your face
It's all about the time
Right then Hamada-san, we're counting on you
Ready
Start!
We're counting on you!
There he goes, 45 seconds...
He looks like he's struggling already
That's hilarious
That's funny
WHAT?!
Result: 9 seconds
NO WAY!
YOU'RE KIDDING ME!
Awesome!
HAMADA-SAN!
That's fucked up, that's so fucked up.
What is?
No, I'm just pissed off now
No, I heard a noise in my ear
This is such a joke
I'm begging you, man, seriously
I can't stay underwater because of my ear
Well yeah, I know but still...
Right?
They've lost
I'm really sorry, but we've got this in the bag now...
Fantastic work, sir
Seriously...
Well done
This is worse than a child
You know, you can't see underwater
No, you can't
Of course you can't if you stay under for that short a time...
But you were really trying to see the timer?
Exactly, exactly
And then suddenly I heard this noise in my ear
and thought "Fuck it, that's it" before my ear got worse
What the hell, man? 9 seconds...
Halfway point
Tanaka Naoki
Next up is Tanaka
He has scuba experience, but can he pull it off when it matters?
We're seriously counting on you here, man
Yep, I will seriously
Seriously, I want to continue with this "team"
Yeah, seriously
Right.
"Team"?!
So just think you're here alone
Don't listen to anyone around you
That's right
Just go for it
Okay
Ready?
Let's get to it then
You going to be okay?
Yeah.
Ready
You might find some insects in there by the way...
Start
Right then
This is scary
It's good
He's doing well
He's really concentrating
He going to be okay?
He's doing fine
Hold on
He's trying to come up
No no, get down
Stay under
He's got to
He's fine
You still got plenty in you
Go down, go down
Okay, good
That's fine, keep calm
Come out, come out...
Go down
Down, down... That's right
Good
41 seconds...
No way
Result: 41 seconds
What the hell, man?
I drank some water...
I don't give a shit, man...
That's the worst
Halfway point
Yamasaki Masaya
Kitano Team, next up is Jordan's Yamasaki
He's got a good body, being 180cm tall; will he be able to perform?
I'm going to try my best
Go for it
Wait, what was that?
Huh?
Your part will just be briefly summarised
Sorry about that, doesn't matter how well you perform
It'll be like "And he got this many seconds" and that's it
Just your part...
Seriously...
Right then, let's get to it
If you don't get to 1 minute, you're out...
Ready
Okay...
Start
I wonder what kind of face he'll show
He just hit his face on the glass...
You can't see well under there after all
You don't realise how far away you are inside...
Man his face is annoying
Isn't he in trouble..?
Yeah he is
Wait a minute...
He's in trouble
Hold on a minute
Stay under
Do your best
OI!
Result: 37 seconds
Are you serious?
We can still win, we can still win
You were doing your best, right?
You can just summarise my part...
You know, you can just go home now, man...
Office Kitano: 29 seconds ahead
Wait a second...
If we get 30 seconds on them in the next one, we can win; what shall we do?
You're talking about the order?
I think the most confident person should go last to be honest...
I honestly think now is better
I agree
Really?
Seriously, I think so too
Okay
and let's put our hopes on Matsumoto-san at the end
Excuse me
We're going to change our order here
Eh?
This is part of our plan
Yamasaki is actually amazing at this
I'm going next
With a bang!
Next up
Yamasaki Hosei
For the Gaki Team, next up is Yamasaki
The Daddy who has a lot of confidence in holding his breath will try to rid his name of being a weakling.
I think it's time to reveal my record...
Recently, I mean it was in a wash basin
but Yamasaki tried it then
and got close to 3 minutes, when doing it...
Eh!?
But you know, when he gets in, the water volume and water pressure will shock him
That's true
So he might get so shocked and come up sooner than 9 seconds...
Yamasaki, we're seriously counting on you here
Let's do this
Oh wow, the temperature is perfect
Who cares...
No one cares about that; it's just about the time...
Like he's getting into the bath...
Are you okay?
He just went under and came out...
That's it...
Wait, wait...
We don't need like this kind of "betrayal"...
Seriously
We don't, it won't be funny at all...
"Betrayal"...
Right then, let's get going, Yama-chan
Ready
Start
He just floated in
His breathing technique is suspicious
Wait a minute, he's struggling already
Hold on!
No, he's fine
This is where it starts
He's fine
I told you, the wash basin and this are different
Yeah, this is genuinely painful for the whole body
That's right
Look at him
Come on, Hosei-san, come up already
This is really bad
He's crying...
He's crying underwater..?
Hold on, this is it
Zaki-san, seriously, we're counting on you
Don't push yourself too hard!
You'll actually die if you try too hard!
Don't come up...
Hit the thing for him
See, his eyes are opening up...
He's doing well though!
Here it comes
This is going to be awesome, he's going to get a good time
He's actually amazing, he's gone past a minute
Damn...
He's doing well
Here it is!!
Zaki-san!
Oh my God!
Come up now, come up
He's struggling so much
You can do it!
Zaki-san, you're doing well!
It all hit him at once!
He looks ridiculous!
This is hilarious, this is hilarious!
Wow!!!
Result: 1 minute 33 seconds
Yamasaki, that was awesome!
YEAH!!!
Are you OK?
Amazing!
That was amazing!
Well done!
That was amazing
YEAH!
You really are amazing
Right?!
They've completely flipped the tables...
They're like more than 1 minute ahead now
1 minute 4 seconds?
1 minute 4 seconds...
We need at least a minute here...
We can win...
Yamasaki, that was awesome!
Yeah, Zaki-san!
That was fantastic
Amazing
Amazing, that was awesome
Fantastic
Damn, the Gaki team had an ace in their team...
I know, right?
But his face just suddenly changed
I know, all of a sudden
Yeah, I died once in there...
You died once?
I really did
Your face went mental suddenly...
Well he was amazing, but
we have the man who once became 2nd in the world...
That's right
This is the part I have no idea about...
Kitano Team, next up is the man who became 2nd in the world in bench press lifting once, Nabeyakan
Next up
Nabeyakan
His awesome muscles which he's trained so much will help him greatly
Here we go then
You going to be okay?
Ready
start
Here he goes, damn he went low
He went so low
This is really bad though; there's more pressure down there
He's really tough on himself, huh?
He's fine
I wonder how long he will stay in there
He looks totally fine still
He really does
He can still go, oh hold on...
Uh oh
Great, great!
He's struggling!
His face looks like a father's one now...
This is bad
Just a bit more...
What is this even?
What is this?
Not yet, not yet!
Not yet!
No, no, no!
A bit more
He's still hanging on though
You can do it
You can
Amazing, stay in a bit longer
He's doing well
I will hit the thing when you get to 1 minute so keep going!
He's done a minute!
You're close to a minute!
Amazing, amazing!
You're close to 1 minute now!
Amazing, holy shit!
This is bad, this is bad!
This is awful!
Oh man, oh man!
He's amazing
This is awesome!
Wow!
Result: 1 minute 18 seconds
As expected of him
That's awesome, you did fantastic.
You did well
That was amazing
Office Kitano Team: 14 second lead
The second half has been awesome
I know, he got close to Yamasaki...
Yakan, that was amazing
Let's go first here...
Yeah
Then Matsumoto won't know what the hell to do last...
There will be loads of pressure on him and everything
Damn you, you veteran!
Last up
Great Gidayu
Finally to the last person
Kitano Team has the man who has risen up the ranks doing a number of jobs, Great Gidayu!
Right then, here we go!
Ready
Start!
Oh man, why would you do that!?
Why would you do that?!
That's a no-no!
We spoke about not doing this too!
Wow, his hair is...
God damn it...
And he hasn't moved an inch...
This is bad...
What is he doing?
Oh damn
Result: 31 seconds
Alright!
You can do this!
Couldn't you hold your breath for longer?
....I'm sorry, I really am
You've done so much to get here!
Matsumoto-san's face has gone so white...
I don't know what to do...
This is a tough one...
I think I can do 46 seconds...
Over 46 seconds and Gaki Team wins
You can do it
Let's win our first ever match
But it's different once you get in
Yeah, it really is
Wait, do you have any advice for me...?
Umm, no, not really...
After the break - Will Matsimoto be able to win it?!
Last up
Matsumoto Hitoshi
For Gaki team, last up is Matsumoto
Will he be able to reverse the deficit under this pressure?
Over 46 seconds and Gaki team wins!
We need you to do this!
But you know
You can do this
But you know...
When you did that 25-metre race against the other 4, you couldn't even swim the whole length...
Your eyes might bulge out even more now since you're not wearing goggles...
The pressure...
Yeah it must be bad
You can do this, don't worry
You can do this
46 seconds
Oh man, there are a lot of spectators too
I'm so nervous...
Relax, relax.
46 seconds...
We're counting on you
46 seconds is a long time, you know...
At 30 seconds, we'll hit on the glass
No way he can do this...
At 30 seconds...
Shall I hit it?
Yeah, please..
You can do this
The pressure is intense!
I know
Good stuff
That's not a good thing to do I don't think...
Right then
Right then, here we go
Please do!
To decide everything
We're counting on you!
Ready
Start!
He's under pressure
Right
Oh man, he's got a bad face on
What kind of a face is that?
He looks like a wax model...
He does...
What a face...
There's a fair few bubbles coming out...
He looks fine though
Why does he look so calm?
No, it all comes in one go
Yama-chan just suddenly...
Uh oh, hang on... This is bad
Hold on, his feet...
No no! We're counting on you!
Stay down!
Not yet! Not yet!
Come on!!!
See, he looks fine.
Why does he looks so calm?
No, it all comes in one go
Yama-chan just suddenly...
Uh-oh, hang on... This is bad
Hold on, his feet...
No no! We're counting on you!
Stay down!
Not yet! Not yet!!
Come on!!
YES!!!!!
So close!!!!!
Result: 41 seconds
Damn it!
So close!
We were so close!
They're a loser of a club, it's decided.
Matsumoto-san, thank you so much
Wait, I'm so gutted!!
I'm so gutted right now!
Gaki Team
Office Kitano team
3 min 51 sec
3 min 55 sec
3 minutes 51 seconds against 3 minutes 55 seconds
Office Kitano wins!!!
Office Kitano Team wins!
Yeah!!!!!!
We need to get revenge!
Yeah, we do
Yeah, we need to
Let's do it again
Yeah, we accept your challenge
Yeah, we can do it again
Let's do it
But you know, we were really serious this time
but next time, they might come all serious and stuff too...
Yeah we will be...
We're going to train and stuff...
Yeah, let's train!
All he needed was 13 seconds...
Yeah that's true
15 seconds and we'd have won
That's right
Yeah, I was like dying in there trying my best and
thinking "why do I have to work this hard?"