2nd Time on Gaki no Tsukai - Nostalgic Song Drive!!
This is the second time
It's the second time, and actually,
The first time, there was a proper ending actually
There was one, but because of the weather it couldn't happen
It was raining like crazy
And there is one person here who absolutlely must do that punchline
That's why he was smirking all this time
If anything that was a build up for this
oh really?
So there's a brilliant ending waiting for us
Something innovative
NTV might even pay him a fee for this
We can just do this like always right
Of course, you have all brought your nostalgic songs
You gotta hype it up
Innovation, innovation
I understand, there will be a nice ending right?
If we can hype it up eno-
Enough please! Enough already
Timed & Typeset by: Kedomas
Translation by: senor_wristband
What is Yamasaki's innovative punchline?!
2nd Nostalgic Song Drive!
A blue sky, for real
Yes, no rain for sure
Yeah it's not gonna rain
Did everyone remeber to bring their songs?
The CDs
Of course
Of course, my nostalgic songs
Hmm, Yama-chan, that?
Hamada-san just laughed so hard!
Hard? I did not laugh hard
I just thought "Oh it's like that again"
You really are loved.
By the staff right? They only gave me this
Why do they do that? Do you tell them to?
I really don't tell them to,
Before starting today the staff called me over. In fact there were 5 other ones beside this one!
"Choose from these ones"?
Yes they said "Please choose from these"
Wow
That's totally favoritism
Shall we decide who goes first
Alright, then Tanaka you go?
Really?
Yeah we can start with Tanaka
Shall I start?
Tanaka you've been nominated
The first song on here please
Tanaka's first song
Yes
What? What?
This is...
This is Murashita Kouzou-san's "First Love:
Murashita Kouzou - First Love
It's a bit unfortunate that this had to be the first one, as it's so special,
Yeah
Back in the 2nd year of middle school, I liked this girl from the class next door
And I liked her so much I had to do something,
I confessed to someone that I like them for the first time in 2nd year
And in the end she did reject me
How did she reply?
"Tanaka-kun the way you walk is gross!!" she said
This is uh,
I was shocked, by the reason too
I talked to her a bit too
Endo was in the class next door
She was in my class
So I talked to Endo about it, and he told me it doesn't seem like she likes anyone,
She doesn't have a boyfriend
Right, and then I confessed to her, and she used that reason to reject me
It was my first confession, and I bawled my eyes out
You cried?
I cried and cried and cried my heart out
It took me so many days to get over it
Damn, that's not cool
I was so shocked
And when I turned the radio on after that happened this song was playing
This song is "First Love"
Yes it was linked to my first love, my first confession
If someone tells you the way you walk is gross,
It's gotta pretty difficult to walk after that
Someone telling you you're walking is gross...
I couldn't walk
It's your natural gait after all ... It's an insult to your life!!
Exactly
So right after that, I think this follows that obe
This one, everyone knows it I'm sure
O-NyanKo Club - Don't Strip Me of My Sailor Suit
EVERYONE knows it
When you were in middle school?
This is from when we went from 1st to 2nd year of middle school,
During 1st year, Tanaka was actually shorter than us
In fact you could even say he was shorter than average
And then went Tanaka entered 2nd year, and he fell in love right?
After that,
Tanaka's height suddenly grew by 10-19cm
Oh yeah there were kids like that
And then, that girl that was his first love,
And what all the girls in my class were saying was
"Isn't Tanaka from next door getting bigger every day?"
They said something like, "Isn't it super creepy?"
That's just how suddenly he grew super tall
Oh wow
You grew a lot right?
Like "Isn't he even bigger today?"
Exactly, after his confession he still kept growing
Yeah
Did you ever ask her out again?
I didn't
After that- After that Endo started dating that girl that rejected me
Oi asshole!
You didn't mention it did you?!
Endo! You can't do that!
Yeah I know
After that, that girl confessed to me she likes me
When I asked her "What do you like about me?"
She replied "Endo, you're proper"
After that Tanaka bawled his eyes out again
All I do is cry
All you do is cry
getting taller and crying, getting treated like a monster
I feel bad for Tanaka
Alright let's go with Hamada-san
Oh me?
The first song on here please
The first song
What is this?
Ah! It's Candies
Yes yes
Candies!
Candies - Gentle Devil
This was a hit
It was
Gentle Devil
This is super famous
Oh yeah this
Up until this song, Candies dressed rather conservatively,
After this song, they wore black fishnet tights and amazing outfits like that
I remember very well
Like "God damn what is this"
It was so arousing!
Black fishnets
How old was DownTown back then?
Like 14
Oh the perfect age
They went ALL the way up
It was shocking at the time
It was impactful
I see it was something totally different
Pink Lady came after this y'know. Nobody else came out in outfits like this.
Yeah
If it wasn't for this Pink Lady might not have been a thing
Yeah perhaps
This certainly was super arousing
The song, but also the outfits
Wasn't there like frilly thing here too
There was, like paper lanterns
Like some lace thing
Yes yes yes
Paper lanterns?
It was like puffy up here
I remember that very well actually,
They would shake their hips when dancing
Yes yes
Can I continue on this?
Yes go ahead
This
It would've been better if we weren't in a tunnel. Bad timing.
You're right
So, Hamada was aroused by "Gentle Devil" just earlier right?
For me it was Iyo-chan's "TV no Kuni Kara Kira Kira"
Mastumoto Iyo - Sparkling in the Land of TV
I was in year 2 of middle school,
Was this that kind of song?
The start,
The "Ne~" part
That part right?
"Ne~ konna no kanji te ii no?"
TS: "Hey, Is it alright to feel this way?
"Konna no..." I forgot the lyrics though
What?! Enough
Why did you even bring it up then
Wasn't that the important part
I don't know anything after "Kanji te ii no"
But the bit that goes "Ne~ something something"
The "Ne~" part,
I repeated and listened to that so many times
Why the hell
Oh that part aroused you?
Yeah it aroused me
I recorded that part and listened to it so many times
"Ne~?"  "Ne~!"
"Ahn Ahn~?"  "Ahn Ahn~!"
It is a good song
What the hell man
This one, I think Hamada and Endo might relate to it
Some people might find it an odd choice for me
What is this?
Ahh, yes yes yes
No idea
Endo you don't know it?
Not yet
Eh? Endo can't tell huh
Oh I got it!
So nostalgic
It's the Chunichi Dragon's song
Yes, "Burn Dragons!"
Bandou Eiji - Burn Dragons!
This one,
Is this Bandou-san?
Yes it's Bandou-san
"Fight Dragons! Burn Dragons!"
People in Osaka from a young age, they wear either a Giant's cap, even in Osaka,
Or a Hanshin's cap
Nobody wears caps from any other team
This guy was the only person wearing a Chunichi hat
Why? Why?
Wow really?
Did you like Chunichi at the time?
No, I'm not really sure why,
The only time I went to a shopping street with my dad,
My dad for some reason bought it for me
There were 12 other hats,
And just going by the colours, I said "this one" and got him to buy me a Chunichi hat
I have no memories about Chunichi at all!!
Everyone supported Kyojin
Yeah at the time
And some Hankyu fans
And I wasn't interested in baseball in the first place
So I decided to become a Chunichi fan after that
And everyone else were fans of other teams, mostly Kyojin
So I forcefully became a fan
I was probably hoping that they might win someday
And after I forcefully became a fan they went and won
So there was nothing to hope for anymore...
And they're from Nagoya after all,
I still can't get excited about them
But now that I think about that was when I was most passionate about pro baseball
I knew all the players at the time
There was a time when they were popular
Tanaka?
Yesss
Since we're driving, I think this one might be perfect
Excuse me, the first song on here please
Yes, since we're driving, it's main theme of 007
007 Main Theme
This is, back in 5th year of elementary school,
I decided to go watch a movie by myself
Wow that's amazing
A 5th year going to the movies using his own money,
And my older cousin gave me some Levis,
500 series or something I'm not sure,
But I wore my Levis, and went to all the way to Umeda
And I was going to watch a 007 movie
I thought in 5th grade, wearing Levis and going to watch a 007 movie by myself was so mature
After the movie, on the way back, in Umeda I was mugged by some highschool students!
I was super scared!
Tanaka man... your stories are so depressing. Every time.
I ran all the way to the Takarazu line
And I bet the way you ran was gross too
I was thinking  "I'm such a grown up",
Yeah you completed the mission,
I completed the mission, but...
I got mugged a lot back then
Yeah
Yeah it happened so often
I was mugged a lot in Amagasaki
TN: Amagasaki is DownTown's home town
Once you cross that side, you enter Ama right?
As soon as I crossed over I was terrified
Ama was scary?
Yeah for real. You can only buy bad clothes in Amagasaki
That's not true
It's all in Ama?
There was a place called Akadama (clothes shop)
I also went to Akadama during high school
There were some weird unknown brands there
Yankees liked to gather there
Did you ever go to 100 Yen City?
100 Yen City too
Then I'll go too, this song is also from then. The first song please
Let's go with the school theme
What's this?
Between Earth and Sky
I really like this song
Matsuyama Chiharu - Between Earth and Sky
In 3rd year of highschool I went to a boarding school,
It was a very strict school
Whenever ANYTHING happened they made us all sing this song
Is this really a song for group singing?
Exactly!
Eh what's wiuth that?
Whenever ANY incident happened they made us all sing this song
Isn't this supposed to be a moving song?
Yeah
If someone got in a fight or caused an incident
Or if they told us "You guys have bad attitudes"
Whenever ANYTHING happened in the end we all had to sing this song
It's not that kind of song!
Maybe to teach you something-
Like maybe to encourage you
Like "Do better!"
So basically just "Do better"
Yes yes yes
I really got into these lyrics
It was a super strict dorm right?
I don't think places like that can exist anymore
There was 1 day where you could go home but had to come back right away. And instead of doing that,
I called Matsumoto, I told him "bring some money"
He got money the moeny and met me at Tsuruhashi
And we ran away together, not going back to school
Matsumoto-san, you ran away too?
I got the money, and met him at the gate
Matsumoto was the assistant
I got him to buy me Udon
It was just us 2, slurping like madmen,
There was one guy just staring at us the entire time
"How hard can they slurp?!"
"Humans can slurp like this?!"
Eat until you drop
Yeah, when it's some food you like
That's an amazing memory
Amazing
Then I'll go with the second song here
What is this?
Oh right, this is Missing right?
Yes, as Hosei-san just said
Kubota Toshinobu - Missing
When we were kids, and we would go to karaoke after school
And we called over the girls we knew
This is my, "lulling a woman" song
Oh you'd sing this
Oh, to lull them?
You really are an idiot aren't you?
No no no
When my turn would come up,
It's not like this would be the first song, we would sing other stuff to get excited,
After they're warmed up
And after they're all warmed up,
And right before it was time to leave, I would put this song in,
I'd sing this song, and take them home...basically
This guy is an idiot!
An idiot!
I wonder what kind of girl you can bring home by singing this song
Wow
I listened to this song so much
I did. All the women just like swooned
Idiot
Nice and smooth
And even my seniors wouldn't mind, some of them liked this song and they would swoon too
Can you sing just the hook for us?
I LOVE YOU even if it's not possible
Even though you forgot about me
I'd sing this, and you guys are swooing right?
But, yeah - No I'm not swooning
Let's go with this!
Ahhh this is nostalgic
I think only Hamada will know this one
I don't know this
It was a huge hit in Kansai though
Ah! This is "Kawachi no Ossan no Uta"
I think I've heard this before
Who's singing this?
Miss Hanako
Miss Hanako - A Kawachi old man's song
Oh right
This,
This one
This was super hilarious, basically
Basically, like that story earlier,
I was dozing off, listening to the radio with headphones,
When this song came on for the first time,
It was so funny, I couldn't sleep!
"What the hell is a Kawachi old man's song?!"
I couldn't hold it in
It was just so funny,
And our house was super small too,
And my older brother and my dad were sleeping nearby,
I couldn't laugh, I was trying so hard to hold it in,
It was just too much! Like this "My wife, that bitch" bit
This part
TN: The singer is using "ware" which is a rude way of referring to someone. I think, please correct this translation in the comments if it is incorrect
His wife
"He said bitch?!"
He called his wife a bitch! Even though the song is nice
Trying to hold my laughter in...
It was super difficult
1 hour since the drive has started
Yamasaki finally makes his move!
Then can I go, excuse me. The build up took too long you guys
Oh it's finally time?
We took too long?
Too damn long
Let's stick this landing,
Right, you weren't able to do it last time right?
You wanted to do this last time right?
Yes yes indeed
Now is just right
Counting on you!
Here I go
After this, we finally see Yamasaki's killer ending!
It's been a while since Yamasaki-san got off,
Yes it has
According to Yamasaki-san,
"This is the actual nostalgic song I want to present"
He wants to present it in a different way
So it's not simply putting the song on?
A more grandiose presentation
That's what I've heard
Oh?
Ishi Akemi - Cha-Cha-Cha
BEEP
They're getting angry
Oh really?
They're angry
Man...
Even though he was smiling, he looked so somber at the end
I just couldn't laugh
When it gets that bad
I saw his panicked face. Absolutely hopeless.
Timed & Typeset by: Kedomas
Translation by: senor_wristband