First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
"Let's ask the best 5 of a town we've never been to"!!
So Matsumoto, This time we will be
Today's plan
The 5 members will go to a town they've never been to
and they will ask the locals for info
to determine that town's best 5
Going to a town we don't know and ask
Its best 5 to the people living there
That's the plan
Matsumoto Hitoshi, Hamada Masatoshi, Tsukitei Hosei, Endo Shozo, Tanaka Naoki
Ok, now Hosei takes the lead
Counting on you
That's a first one
Do I have to explain it?
Honestly, I'd love to listen instead
Look, this is the Kanto region
This is the map
First off we pick a prefecture
Rules - they'll choose one prefecture from the Kanto region, then they randomly pick a paper containing the name of a train station from inside it
Can we decide which one to pick?
Sure, but when we pick a paper next
If there's even a single person who have been there before
We just scrap that away and pick another one
Rules - If even a single one of them has been to the town they get, it's not valid
We can pick one of these, right?
- Yes
I think we all know Tokyo very well
Yeah, we can't do Tokyo
We would end up walking around somewhere we know
You're right
- Those are names of stations, right?
I know those of Tokyo
For example, let's see what happens
This is Tokyo's
Oh man, I don't think I've ever been to...
For example, I could be wrong, but...
We're gonna scrap this one later
See?
Senju-Ohashi
Where the hell is this?!
I've never heard it before
Never been there
It's in Adachi
Tokyo's prefecture, Adachi ward // Keisei Electric Railway - Senju-Ohashi station
I have no clue
I've heard "Senjuu" alone, like in North Senjuu's station
But this-- alright, let's scrap it
That can happen
Now I see
Let's choose who gets to choose
Ah, like this?
Shozo, then
Eh? Can I?
Sure, whatever
It's an important task
Well, if I have to choose...
It's fine
What about Kanagawa?
There's not many inside, but I haven't been there that much
Yeah, same here
Right, huh?
This should do it
- Kanagawa
We're doing Kanagawa!!
Remember, if you've been there already just say it
Let's go
My feet already hurt
- This one
Please, reveal it
No tricks or gimmicks here
I've only been in Yokohama
I wonder if I can read it...
That's an issue too
No way!!
No way we got this one!!
I wonder how...
It's Yokohama
I've been there before
Getting Yokohama... out of all of these?!
Not Yokohama, everybody has been there before right?
I have
If we were to choose its best 5
we would just loiter around its Chinatown
We can't do this one
- Right
What should we do? We can pick another one too
Oh, I see
We can move to Chiba too, or a different one
Let's stick to this
Alright then, let's see
This should be new
Yeah, I wonder...
Where?
- It's Shonan
Shounan-Fukasawa
That's famous too
Kanagawa's prefecture, Kamakura city // Shounan Monorail - Shounan-Fukasawa station
I mean, it's Shounan
I'm sure I've been there
Definitely
No doubts about it, you see
We also filmed Gaki in Shounan, once
You're right
Yeah, it's a famous spot
Whatever man, let's do this
It's here
I see
Are we doing this? Oh, look
We're mixing everything up?
Yeah, let's just do this
I think that's the best solution
It's best like this, we don't want this to look staged
Alright, let's do this
Now all the prefectures are mixed together
You go now, Hamada
Yes, it's Hamada's turn
Please
We're counting on you
Here's one from the center...
I wonder which prefecture it's gonna be
Right
Probably we wouldn't even know
Eh? Where is this?
"Shizu"
Is it in Chiba?
Is it read as "Shizu"?
staff) It's in Sakura town in Chiba
Sakura...
Sakura town in Chiba?
Never been there before
Me too, never
Which railway is it?
It's above Yuukari-ga-Oka station
Yuukari-ga-oka...?
I have no clue!
Alright, we're going here?
We have it
Let's go to Shizu!
Let's go and ask the best 5!
What are we supposed to do now?
1 week later
Alright guys
This is nice
We're in Shizu, Keisei line
Which is close to Sakura town in Chiba
That's where it is
This is nice
Keisei Electric Railway - Shizu Station (Chiba Prefecture, Sakura Town, North Shizu)
It's around 1 hour from Tokyo, and there's a lot of people who commute from here for work or school
I didn't want to say this, but...
You all have this dumb half-smile
No way
You're the one saying "this is nice" all the time, dude
But I mean it as "This town is nice, I like it" in a good way
But it feels like you're looking down on it
That's not true, it's 'cause it's sunny
At least try
It's not about trying
Today we're gonna ask the locals about this town
We're going to find out the best 5 of this place
Let's see what they'll recommend
We don't know anything
In order to know the 5th best recommendation, they're gonna start an interview before the station
It's time to ask the locals what Shizu has to offer
Let's see what's is on the 5th place
We can just ask anyone, right?
Oh, excuse me!
No, that's--- it's our staff
General manager - Suga Kenji
He's not a local
My mistake
He got embarrassed
his face was red all over!!
I wanted to see more
Are you a local?
He's not used to TV
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TYPESET BY MATTEE53
MORE EPISODES: SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
SOCIAL MEDIA: FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI - TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
DONATIONS:
- PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI (get early access to softsubs & raws!!)
- KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
YOU CAN SUPPORT MATTEE53'S TYPESET WORK
BY SUBRSCIBING TO HIS OWN PATREON: PATREON.COM/MATTEE53
Today our members are headed to Shizu in Chiba prefecture
To ask around the locals about the best 5 things in this city
First off, let's see what the locals
Suggest as the 5th best thing of Shizu
Should we ask those kids?
Definitely
Oh, here they are! Hi!
Can we ask you something?
Are you from the New York Yankees?
Are you locals?
Which base are you protecting?
Shut your trap
Are you students?
We are
What were you doing here?
We heard a rumor...
Mh?
Which rumor?
Like, someone was filming here
Oh? They all already knew it?
I wanted to meet you guys
So you came here to meet us?
My, thank you~
I see your nipples wanted to meet us too, they're standing for us
That's nice of them
Let's ask them first
So, we wanted to ask you recommendations about this town
We wanted to know what you think
We're looking for the 5th best thing
It's number 5
We want you to let us know the 5th best thing about this town
Number 5 is pretty hard
Yeah, 'cause there's a lot on top of it
You gotta calculate it
Just get a general idea of it
He was so quick to write, are you sure?
Yeah, I think so
Do we have our five?
Alright, let us see it
It's the curry shop
The curry shop is this town's 5th!
Why this generic answer---
I mean, there are surely loads of those
Like, the shop's name?
It's called Sathi
It's close, over there
It's run by a foreigner
So it's the real deal
He makes a naan
Like, this huge
Which curry is the best one?
Chicken curry
What about you?
My favorite is the shrimp curry
Shrimp curry
Very nice, don't you think guys?
Well, we just have to go
Are we going?
It's worth trying, isn't it?
Can you please lower that thing a bit?
Oh hey, it's the nipples...
Enough already!
That's enough
Thanks
We're going, then
Thanks a bunch
And so they're heading to the recommended curry shop
There it is
Already?
- Yep, that's "Sathi"
Go ahead, Tanaka
- Sure
I'm gonna ask if it's ok to film
Cocorico goes inside to ask about the filming permission
First off, cocorico gets in to ask the owner for the shooting permission
Rules - if they won't get the filming permission, they'll have to ask someone else"
In case they won't be able to get it
They'll have to change their plans back from scratch
It's ok, yes
- Why are you saying it like that?
We can get in, it's fine
'Cause I was shocked
He said OK in a flash
Permission granted: time to get inside
Filming permission granted, it's time to get inside
Thanks for having us
They speak japanese just fine
Before making an order, they'll ask about the shop
Can I ask your name, sir?
My name is Gimire Ganesh
Such an easy name to remember!!
Not at all
It's difficult
What's the meaning of this restaurant's name...?
The word "sathi" means "friend"
"Friend", huh...
I see, so it's "friends"...
Must have been hard currying  on the shop, yes?
It's not curry, it's carry
We're in a curry shop, you know
Ohh, is that so...
He has no idea what you're talking about
Have you ever been on TV before?
It's my first time
For how long have you been here in Japan?
I've been here for 7 years
And this shop is 5 years old
Oh, I see
So you've worked hard for 2 years to arrange this shop?
That's right
That's impressive
So, what are we taking?
Chicken curry
Yes
What did they tell us?
- It was...
Shrimp?
Shrimp curry, chicken curry...
One of each please
Check this out, isn't this amazing?
That's made of spinach
That's why it's green
Yeah but those guys said shrimp curry, so...
Why don't you wanna eat the recommended one?
He's right, stick to the plan
Those two for now
I agree with that
Right?
That's right
What can I say, I'm really enjoying this fuss we're making
You're having fun, aren't you?
That's not it
We gotta stick to our recommendations
Alright, shrimp curry was it?
And a chicken curry
We all wanna eat the chicken one, right?
Alright, thanks so much
Thanks
While they wait for the curry, Matsumoto talks about something...
As they wait for their order, Matsumoto tells us something...
If I'd be walking around Amagasaki (birthplace)...
And suddenly a TV celebrity would come
And ask me what's the 5th best thing here it'd be hard
What about the beef shop?
Ah, you mean Yamazato Hormon?
A shop run by a Downtown's former classmate - "YAMAZATO HORMON"
I think that's... 12th in rank
Make it fifth at least!
I don't know about that
There's a lot of exhaust gas in that shop
You even said its name
Just make it fifth and we're good
It uses gas to grill meat, it's dangerous
That's why
Thanks for waiting, here's the shrimp curry
That's so big
That's a huge naan!
They said it was
Look at that naan
Shrimp Curry - 700 yen (plus tax)
It looks really tasty...
That's incredible
This is...?
- The shrimp one
You go first, Hamada
What the-
Why me?
It's fine, just go
He's right
That's hot!!
Of course it is
Why shouldn't it be?
I can't eat this now!
I think it's not as hot on this side
You sure?
Well, it's not as crispy here
Shoot, it's hot, it's hot all over
How about this part?
You mean here?
It's hot!!
Everywhere I touch it's hot
I think this one's cold though
No way this is cold--
Hot!!
He completely fell for it
Thanks for the show
Thanks
It's freshly made
Of course it is
Let's eat
Let's slip the naan
It's sweet
Sweet?
I can feel it
It's so good
You're right, it's really good
second suggestion
Shrimp Curry - 700 yen (plus tax)
And here's their second suggestion
The chicken curry
I like this
Do you want one more wet towel?
Which one is better?
It's really good!
It's not even that spicy
It's good, isn't it?
I think it's delicious
Yeah, just barely spicy
It's not one of those which make you sweat
I think this one is way better
That's what that kid told us, go for the chicken
He was right
- So good!
That was really good
It's unfair to put this only at 5th place
You're right
I agree
This could have been higher to me
But yeah, we were looking for the 5th place...
Right, we can't only rely on food
That's the problem, yeah
We should think about who to ask next
Right
Isn't there, like... a sort of spot for tourists?
Like, a place someone would say "you have to go there"?
I mean...
- Something like that
1st place should be a hot spring or such
Sounds nice
Is there a hot spring in here?
I bet there is
We're in Japan, they're everywhere
Everywhere?
Are you sure?
We'd be screwed if they would be everywhere!!
That's not normal
It's fine, trust me
I wonder if there is one
They were all satisfied about the curry's taste
Thanks for the meal, mr. Sathi!
And so, the 5th best recommended place of Shizu is confirmed to be Sathi
And now they're back at asking the locals to find out the 4th place
Excuse me, good morning
Good morning
Are you from Shizu?
I'm from the next town!
Ah, is that so?
It's fine
What were you doing here?
There's a market beyond the station
There?
Yes, it's mostly for handmade stuff
It's held once every month
Is that fried tofu?
Fried tofu?
On your mouth...
It's a mask
Sorry about him
Sorry, I didn't get it at first!
It kinda looks like it
I see
Tanaka, please
Alright, so...
We're currently looking for
The best 5 things in Shizu, by asking the locals
We were wondering if you could tell us the 4th best one
Not the 5th, 3rd, 2nd or 1st...
Like, some place you would enjoy going to or such
Leaving aside the rest of them...
Not the others?
Like, if you came to Shizu there would be this, this and this...
If you came to Shizu...
One thing, let's try not to include restaurants or such
Something like a park or such...
A park?
Yeah, like a place you can go to
A giraffe...
There's a park with a lion in it, right?
Sounds nice
Really?
Where is it?
Not a real one, right?
No, it's not real
Alright, let's go then
Where is it?
Where can we find it?
It's called Southern Shizu Park? Maybe?
Can we reach it by walk?
It's really close by car
It's on the other side
Of Dotonbori, the okonomiyaki shop
I remembered, it's Southern Yukari Park
But that's part of Yukari-ga-Oka...
Oh no, it's fine
Eh? In Shizu?
But it's fine
Do you have any idea?
Oh, it's fine, don't worry
It's good
Thanks so much
And so, they get in the car
To reach their 4th best place: Yukari Southern Park
They said there's a giraffe here
I wonder how it is...
So, it's a park in Yukari-ga-Oka
It's incredible we got away from its station only at number 4
How about we go back and do the same thing again?
One more time?
That's not the plan
broadcast of 10/23/2016
Can we shoot the same footage 3 times!?
That's another episode
That's impossible
No thanks
That was exhausting
But that was hella fun, wasn't it?
It was
No one ever told me it was, though
Really? It was fun...
I think so too, but no one seems to agree
Not even a single soul
Told me they had fun watching it
Really?
Well, yeah, sadly...
It didn't work out, I guess
broadcast of 10/03/2016
Hot Blooded! Hamada's Cram School 4
Can't say the same for Tanaka's performance on Hamada's cram school
Look at that new building
Looks so out of place
- Yeah...
It's all empty around it!!
Is it?
Oh, he's right
There's nothing around
- Told you
Maybe this town is gonna prosper more in the future
It's called Yukari-ga-Oka, huh?
Places named Something-ga-Oka are always like this
Can you name another place with that name?
Huh?
Shut the fuck up, Endo!!
He's in such a bad mood
He got so angry in a blink of an eye
He totally snapped
Yeah but
I only wanted to know more, that's it
This guy is crazy
I always wanted to do the "shut up" thing
It's pretty far
Yeah, I thought it'd be closer
I think we're close
Are we sure the giraffe and lion are worth all of this?
I was wondering what the giraffe and lion actually are
What do you mean?
I mean, they could be an animal-shaped slide...
Or? What else?
Enough of those---
There are also jungle gyms, aren't they?
Giraffe-shaped jungle gyms
A giraffe jungle gym?
What do you think, Tanaka?
I don't think that's the case
I'm asking for your opinion
He's getting hard to approach
Okonomiyaki shop
"Dotonbori"
She said it was outside Dotonbori
The okonomiyaki shop
It's way bigger...
...Than expected
Oh! I see the lion!
Coming next - they just found the recommended lion?!
It's already here?
I can see the giraffe and lion!
They start moving to the next place
The suggested 4th position
The park with the lion and giraffe!
Is it going to be worth of place number 4?
Okonomiyaki shop
"Dotonbori"
She said it was outside Dotonbori
The okonomiyaki shop
It's way bigger...
...Than expected
Oh! I see the lion!
It's already here?
The giraffe too!
And here we are
It's just as they said
They quickly head towards the lion object
Here it is
This is impressive
It's a female
A lioness, huh
Isn't it great?
It's a female, right Tanaka?
Yes, and it's well done
They also take a look at the giraffe
And they're having more fun than expected
And so, the fourth best place of Shizu
Is confirmed to be Yuukari-ga-Oka's animal park
Here in Yuukari-ga-Oka's southern park
There are roughly 2.1 hectares of field
And there are lots of games and lawns inside it
It's a popular park between the locals
And now, they venture again inside the park
To ask about the third best place
Maybe we should ask a young woman? Like the one we asked before
How about a dad?
How about asking a kid?
Nice
How about them?
I think we should try to
Grade schoolers?
Hey, hello!
Hi! Can we ask something?
We can...
- Can we?
We can have Tanaka
Deal with them
Countin' on ya
How old are you?
10 years old
10? So you're a fourth grader?
Ohh
Where do you leave?
Over there
There?
Say, can I borrow this helmet for a while?
What were you doing--
What are you doing?
You took it already!
That's not good
Alright, we're currently asking the locals
About the best places of this town, Shizu
And now we've already asked the 5th and 4th best place
What's the next place if we go higher?
We're looking for the third best place
Even a thing kids love is fine
But first, can I borrow this thermos for a while?
This guy is an hassle, isn't him?
His face says "piss off"
Well, he deserves it
Now they hate you
You made two enemies
They're like "what's his deal?"
Alright, I admit my defeat
Anything's fine, really
Like, places you visited with your parents...
That's right
With your mom and dad
How about you tell me the code number for this?
Nope, right?
That's a key, it's important
Ignore him
They hate you
Are we gonna--
Oh, what is it?
Aqua
What is this "aqua"?
It's a place with a pool, and a public bath...
that's it
A place with a pool and a public bath?
Aqua, right?
Is that so? Is it close?
Is it near the bowling alley we just passed?
Yes, it is
Is it here?
That means it's close
We should try to go there
Sorry for this, thank you!
Keep your eyes open
They move back to the car
So they can head to the third place
A place with a bath and a pool as suggested by the kids
As soon as we got in the car, they followed us
They must be scared of you, Hamada
No way
I think if I was a grade schooler
And I'd saw your face I'd be traumatized
Why the hell?!
I didn't do anything
That's the scary part
The fact you say "I didn't do anything"
TRANSLATION & EDITING BY SHION TYPESET & QC BY MATTEE53 VISIT SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.
COM FOR MORE EPISODES, LIKE MY FACEBOOK PAGE FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI  OR FOLLOW ME ON TW
ITTER AT @SHIONNOTSUKAI SO YOU WON'T MISS ANY UPDATE! IF YOU WANT TO SUPPORT MY TRANSL
ATION PROJECT, PLEASE CONSIDER DONATING, IT HELPS ME MOTIVATING INTO DOING MORE AND MOR
E! YOU CAN DONATE ON KO-FI AT KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI OR YOU CAN BECOME A PATRON ON MY
PATREON, PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI - IF YOU SUBSCRIBE TO MY PATREON, YOU WILL ALSO GET
EARLY ACCESS TO RAW / SOFTSUBS AND YOU'LL BE CONSTANTLY UPDATED ON MY UPLOAD SCHEDULE!
ALSO, DON'T FORGET TO CONSIDER DONATING TO MATTEE53'S PATREON: PATREON.COM/MATTEE53
!!! ATTENTION !!! THIS EPISODE IS PART 1 OF A 2-PARTS EPISODE. PART 2 IS CURRENTLY SCHEDULED T
O BE RELEASED IN THE FUTURE (HOPEFULLY SOON). AS OF 12/12/2020 WE HAVE NO UPDATES ABOUT IT
S UPLOAD DATE / TL PROGRESS. STAY UPDATED BY FOLLOWING ME ON SOCIAL MEDIA AND SUBSCRIBE
TO PATREON IF YOU WANT TO SEE PART 2 EARLIER THAN ANYONE ELSE!
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT TRANSLATION MADE BY FANS FOR OTHER FANS TO ENJOY. NO COPYRIGHT INFRIN
GMENT INTENDED. HEY YOSHIMOTO. DO YOU NEED A TRANSLATOR? LIKE, AN OFFICIAL ONE? HERE I AM
TAKE ME. I'M YA BOY. I'LL SEND YOU MY RESUMEE ANYTIME. 吉本興業の皆様へ、もしこの字幕動
画を見つけたら、字幕家・翻訳家として会社に雇っても構いませんｗｗ　雇ってくれえええええ