translation: Shion
typesetting: RIDDELL
First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
Let's become the prince! Burning hot tennis classroom!
What's this about, Matsumoto?
Yes
Today we're all going to actually play tennis for real
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Can we actually do it?
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Of course we can
You have experience, don't you?
No, not at all
Yamasaki Hosei
We also have this guy with us
I don't know why we need him, though
Heipo
What are you hiding under that, huh?
I'm not hiding anything
He's just chubby
Must be that
We're beginners, so there's not much we can do by ourselves
Right
So let's introduce the coach who will teach us
Please come in, coach Hiranuma!
Nice to meet you guys, it's a pleasure
H-Hey, my name is Endo...
They say that love strikes like lightning, but...
I never thought this would be the place
Looks like I'm the coach's target for his smash of love
Thanks for coming
We can't do much, so...
Don't worry, you'll learn step by step
Are you sure?
What a risqué outfit he's wearing!
If you wear such short pants...
People might think you're tempting them!
Could it be that, maybe, coach... you too are...?
You know coach, between us Endo used to play baseball
Is that so?
Yeah I think that could be relevant
Can I just... may I?
You're right, you can tell he has a nice build, nice muscles
Hey, hey, are you serious?
This is what they call...
"Petting", isn't it?
What about me? I play golf, I think I'm in good shape too
May I?
Please
You have a nice build too, Hamada
Really?
I knew this man would get in between us
After all...
Hamada has been trying to violate me for ages
He quickly noticed my feelings and tried to get in my way
Translation & editing by: Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Typeset & quality check by: RIDDELL (springmanRIDDELL)
like my page: facebook.com/shionnotsukai
find more at: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
support my content on:
・ ko-fi:  ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
・ patreon:  patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Warming up
Alright, let's warm up so we won't get hurt
That's important
Move your wrists and ankles around
Next up, let's all bend forward
I'm doing it first, so take a look please
Raise both your arms up and stretch them as far as you can
Yes
Be sure to stretch this part
Looks hard
Feel the tension
Crap! I wanna touch it... I'd love to do it!
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven, eight...
Hey, what are you looking at?
That ass is mine, you bastards!
Two, two, three, four
Even this old dude is looking at my coach...
Gaki no Tsukai is nothing but a den of crazy lustful men!
Two, three, four, five, six, seven and eight
Alright, next up...
Let's form pairs and do some stretches
Do it with me, Endo
Oh-- I'm good
I'll do it with Tanaka
What the hell? Look at our position
We got paired up dude
This guy... he suddenly started touching me
How long has he been holding back?
Come on, let's do this
Here goes
Ow ow ow
You're so stiff
"Stiff"?
Don't joke around
Do you think I'd be turned on by this shit?
Spread up your legs more, dude
Spread my legs? Is he going to do it here...?
Someone, help me! Tanaka...!
It's pointless, he's pretending not to see me...
Maybe Tanaka is under Hamada's control?
Does this mean... Hamada grabbed his... you know?
What's going on with this show?!
Alright guys, we're done; Now please stand up
Alright stand up, next up...
Next up we're gonna stretch our backbone, let's do it in pairs again
You can put all your weight on your partner
Let your entire weight push on your partner's back
And make sure to sway a little, like this
What a lewd view! I can't hold it anymore
His thing is right in front of me... The coach's thing is right in front of me!
Coach! Coach!
You're Endo Shozo, right?
Coach... you're so close...
Now...
Can't you be more honest with yourself?
Coach... I...
Endo Shozo... will give my everything to you
Coach... Hah!
Oh, it's the same coach as usual...
What was that just before...?
How to hold a racket
First, place your racket on the floor
Leaving the racket on the floor...
Does it mean we're gonna use our mouth..?!
I'm doing it first, so make sure to watch closely
Grab it gently
And hold it up
Let's all try, shall we?
Alright
So, I shouldn't grab it hard but softly, gently...
I see, so the coach is the type who
doesn't forget to be gentle in bed as well...
Crap, just by thinking about it I can feel Mr. Willy's
head coming out from my underpants
With this, you have your basic grip; now,
place your left hand over the racket
And lower your balance like this
Now, you have to point your racket upwards,
but you shouldn't have it too erected
Too erected? What's wrong with that?
Doesn't everyone prefer it harder?
That's really good!
Yamazaki, point it higher, like that
Your stance is great too, Matsumoto
But make it stand more
Got it
Coach... how about the way I'm making it stand?
Hurry up and come and touch it!
Let's try making it stand higher
Hold it firmly, even more
Very firmly, and place your hand here
Endo! Erected position!
Make it stand firmly like this!
But... making it stand above this point...
Does it mean it's time to let Mr. Willy out of my pants?
Such a malicious guy...
But even so, I still...!!
Endo Shozo, it's fine
It'll be fine
Coach...
Ah!!
Again? What's going on with me?
Swing
There are two types of swing in tennis
This one's called "forehand", and this is "backhand"
Huh? There's a "back" too?
How about we all try it? Let's start with forehand
Raise your shoulder and strike, just like this
Next up is backhand
Isn't this spanking?
As expected from my coach
I'm glad he immediately realized I'm a masochist!
Sorry coach, can you check how I'm doing it?
Sure
Let me help
See, you have to lift the racket higher...
Wasn't this guy into Matsumoto...?
Ah, I see!
He wants to make Matsumoto jealous by making his move with the coach
But is Matsumoto going to be affected by such a cheap strategy?
I see, that's how I should move my elbow
He's 100% jealous!
They say a bit of jealousy is a great
incentive for couples dating for a long time
I guess it's true
Coach, what about me?
Can you try it for a second?
Ready?
Get your racket up here and swing
Coach's hand is twisted around me...
Coach, your crotch...!
Shit! At this rate Mr. Willy's face is gonna poke out again
Coach, this is bad! Your crotch is touching me!
Coach!!
Endo Shozo... we meet again
How do you like my racket?
Wanna touch it?
Shozo, wait
Now, touch me
Coach!
Ah! Again...
Something's wrong with my body...
Okay, your swing is good enough, now let's try hitting some balls
Returning a ball
Here goes
Hosei is doing great
Yeah
That's good
Nice one
Pretty good
A weak blow
Not a single one went over the net
Here goes
How about Hamada?
I wonder if playing baseball could help
Farsightedness​ is kicking in
That's why he can't hit 'em
Let out more strength
More strength, let it out
More! Nice one
Put more power in it
Relax and let it all out
Let it all out? You think it's okay if I do it here, coach?
I actually already busted one out this morning
But I can do it so many more times if it's for you, coach!
Try to scrape the ball from below
Scrape it
Endo, scrub it
Let it out and make it rub against it
Coach... is it also okay if I rub against it?
Does it mean that... it's the same for you..?
Alright, let's change
Next one
Here I am
Can you check how I do my back?
And here he goes again...
Do you think I can do your back in this place?
This guy... his salary is high but everything else is so low
Alright guys, let's take a small break
Alright
Let's have a break on the benches
I survived... right when things were getting bad
Good work everyone
Bananas are perfect after doing sports, they're very nutritious
Oh, no need
Thank you
Can I have the biggest one?
Is there one? I guess it's this one
The biggest one...?
You can tell this is fresh
First you peel it nice and clean...
Then you gently stuff it all down your mouth
But wha-- what am I looking at?!
This looks like the stuff you see in that kind of video
I suddenly feel thirsty
Can I just...?
He came here just to deliver an indirect kiss?
Why make such a platonic move so late?
What does it mean?
He's going for a bukkake!
Has everything else been done to lead to this?
I'm done, I can't see anything else but you, coach!
How is it? Warm, isn't it?
I'm ready for it
Look at me
Come to me
Let's have a proper match
The other coaches will back you up, so let's practice a double match
You'll enter one by one, first up is Hamada
Here?
Yes, Endo too
Get in from this side
Me?
Alright, let's practice while having this double
Seems hard
This is bad... this is so bad...
I'm way too close to the Kansai's Lustful Demon
My body is in danger
It's going over them
Damn
Come on
Be brave
Your back is good, use it
Be brave, man
Come on...
I can't hit it
Here comes
He did a feint to his own partner
What the hell!
Come on...
Play as if you're playing the Australian all-open!
Australian all-open... all-open...
All-opened butthole?!
What the heck?
Nice!
Hit it!
He made it
Good
Fifteen - love
Endo, that smash felt like Kei Nishikori's!
Kei Nishikori...? Kei Nishikori...
Gay Nishikori?!
The hell is he talking about?
Ball boy! Please take the balls away
Taking the balls away?!
Does it mean Yamazaki is ready to undergo a sex change for Matsumoto?!
Let's go guys
Nice one
Go go go
What are you doing man?
Ouch
I got hurt a bit
Are you okay?
Yeah, just a small cramp
Can you take my place?
Sure
Alright! Now there's no one between my coach and me
And he's right in front of me! Time to play to my heart's content
Endo!
Come on Endo, you can do better than this
Hit that ball
Be quick, you can do it
Endo!
It's fine, just hit it that way
Why is he rooting for me so much?
He was so cold to me just before
I'm supposed to become one with the coach...
But Hamada's getting in my head...
What's happening...? What's this feeling...?
Oh, Hamada...
After all, I think that I...
I think that I...!!
Alright!!
Yeah!!
Hamada!
That's right... I have no doubts now...
Endo Shozo is the number one person in this world
Who can clearly say
"I love you."
Enough of this
Stop this shit, man
You have any idea how many times we had to cut because of you?
Say, Tanaka...
Woah
What is it? What's going on?
Sorry, but...
You have so many eye boogers right now
Oh crap, no way
That's horrible
You still do
It feels like I have garbage on my face
There's a load of 'em
Do I still have them?
This is the worst start ever
Yeah, you took 'em away
Sorry for that
You know, about eye boogers
I have this eye boogers compulsive disorder
What is that?
I'm always worried about having them on my eyes
And if there's a mirror near me I can
see it and it's fine, but if there's not any
I wonder if I have any and start to feel worried
So I start to do this
And I see there's nothing on my finger
I mean, with that alone you should be sure you don't have any
Yeah
But after I see there's nothing on my finger
I start feeling like I simply couldn't get out the ones I still have in my eye
Yeah, I totally understand
Right?
It happens
By the time you reach this point, it's over
You can do it a hundred times
And you're like "am I carrying it around on my face?"
And you start doing it compulsively
Yeah you can't stop wondering where it is
And you can't stop scraping your face
So I did it like four or five times in a row, and after my fifth attempt
I told this same thing to my wife
And she said "you have some now"
For real, man
I think that could be a disease
I mean, you can never take 'em off
Well, it's also my age I guess
Really, let me ask you something Tanaka
What is it?
Your sexual desire is zero, right?
Well, you see...
I mean, our age...
I see, yeah
I mean, when we were young...
Actually Matsumoto, I still do have sexual desires
Come on man, you make me look bad
No wait, that's not what I meant
Just say you don't!
That's not it, listen
I am interested in lewd stuff, but I'm quiet about it
I mean, let me explain
I never been told such things
While being stared at like that
I mean...
Are you for real?
Yes, I am
But you can't say it aloud
I mean, I can't just say dirty jokes and such so lightly
Is that so?
To me, it became harder to say 'em as I got older
I mean, if you'd tell me a sudden dirty joke I'd probably freeze up
Right, that's what I meant
But I do have that side
So, yeah, I mean...
You know, Yamazaki went through abstinence for like 6 months or so
And said he felt the urge to jump towards
some old ladies' butts at the bank
He felt like jumping towards some filthy old granny's butt
I see that but... it's hard
So you like, watch erotic DVDs?
Erotic DVDs? Let's see...
I've been married since seven years
And I secretly rented some only three times
Come on, be a man and just buy them!
Rent? Seriously?
So, I rented them three times
And I've been found out all three times
So I just stopped doing it
I mean, my rates of being found out were 100%
Yeah, three out of three times
That's scary
It is
So I just kind of took distances from this stuff
But I mean, what's wrong with wives nowadays?
Yeah, I mean, it's crazy
It was completely fine before, but not now
Before marriage, your girlfriend
gets home and sees you're watching one
It was normal, yeah
But as soon as they become wives, it gets harder
I remember some time ago Rin got home, and told me she didn't mean to
Subtitles & editing by  Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
But she hit the DVD player while cleaning home
Typesetting & QC by  RIDDELL (springmanRIDDELL))
And a DVD came out from it
And you know, some DVDs today have pictures printed on their surface
Find more episodes  @  shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Oh yeah, true
Not only its pack, but also the CD itself, and there was this girl
Like my FB page:  facebook.com/shionnotsukai
You just couldn't hide it
Yeah she just told me "sorry, I saw it"
Want to support? make a donation on ko-fi: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
And I didn't feel like getting angry or laughing about it
I was just like...
Like this, that's all I do now
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SPECIAL THANKS TO RIDDELL FOR TYPESETTING THIS EPISODE!!
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FAN-TRANSLATION MADE BY A FAN FOR OTHER FANS. ALL COPYRIGHT ARE RESERVED TO THEIR RESPECTIVE OWNERS.