First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
Yamazaki Housei
Yamazaki Housei's seven transformations!
To be honest we already did this, I did
Hamada Masatoshi
I did it and it was quite a success
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Then I thought about
How will it turn out if you did it too yourself
Thanks a lot
I've observed you
And studied a lot
And I've been thinking a lot
To come up with hilarious skits
The problem is I don't think everyone will laugh
Nah, you can't say that for sure
Is that so?   - By now...
Everyone thinks of me as a bull's-eye
'Cause they're kinda aiming at me, you know
I'm fun--
I have no idea what the hell "aiming at me" could mean
'Cause its grammar is weird
You know I'm like a bull's-eye for them
Like, the core essence of comedy
Are you saying you are usually
the one who laughs at other's jokes the most?
No, that's not it
I'm saying I hit their spots with what I do
But it could happen that no one laughs
Yeah
I'd say more like they won't be able to laugh
Unable to laugh
No way they won't laugh!
They just have to resist, right?
In case someone laughs
RULES EXPLANATION:
THE COLLECTED MONEY WILL BE DONATED TO THE KOBATO FOUNDATION
EACH TIME ONE PERSON LAUGHS, THEY'LL PAY 1000 YEN
Yes, what about them?
In the worst case    - Yes?
They'll have to pay a penalty
How many years have been since you know us?
Well, It's been 7 years since I've met you two
7 years    - Right
In this time span I've never laughed at your jokes
Of course you did!
You've laughed few times!
He said "few times"    - "few"
Translation & subtitles by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
FOR OTHER CLIPS VISIT WWW.SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
LIKE MY FB PAGE: FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FANSUB, MADE BY A FAN FOR OTHER FANS
NO COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT INTENDED
PLANNING MEETING
Let's just try to figure this out
I wonder why it's always so hard
to decide when it comes to Yamazaki
I wonder why
In the end I think
We should find a partner for Yamazaki
Maybe something like
Yamazaki-Jimmy or Yamazaki-Degawa
Who?
I see
But not them
We had enough
The question is: who?
I think Suga-chan suits Yamazaki well
I mean Suga-chan is...
producer
SUGA
KENJI
I'd be fine with it
Is that so?    - Yeah
You know, when paired up with Yamazaki
Everyone ends up going home in low spirits
Most of them end up calling Noriyasu on the telephone
YAMAZAKI'S FORMER PARTNER
NORIYASU HIROMITSU
And they ask him "what should I do now?"
Someone will give in
That's not for sure
Or maybe just some cougar
I mean, as his partner
I wonder if a woman would fit in it
Nah, it would be hard
Maybe we're overthinking it
Are we?
If we don't have nothing let it be
So?
You shouldn't look behind
Matsumoto got away with it
He tilted his head in a flash
I averted my eyes because I mean
That was just the first one
You're right, I see what you mean
I mean, I think I've doubted his skills
Yeah me too
But really, what should we do now?
What could it be?
If we have to find a partner,
maybe we can try to do a one-on-one
How many people do we need?
I think 5 would do the job    - Right?
And switch them in case
All at once, right?
So, stick him with 5 guys?   - Yeah
Let's start
PENALTY
That's the plan, right?
There aren't much actors for this
That's right
You just shouted, didn't you?
This one was merciless
By this time
I think we have nothing left but doing as we thought
What should we do?
PENALTY
It was hard to endure his face when he entered
You're doing great today
Actually I'm like
How about a second episode of the
popularity contest including Yamazaki?
With Yamazaki alone?    - Yeah
I wonder if it'll make him popular
A copy, please
A popularity contest...
Hello?
Oh...
Was it George?
Ok
Michael?
Bye bye
PENALTY
You know, a looong time ago
There were tons of tv shows with office lady-like girls
Each of them?
No but, like, lots of them
Starting from "Ohayo Asaten"
You're right
How about we all get a tattoo?
Not the tattoos, please
Why is that?
Don't say that, I have one myself
Oh, I'm sorry
I have no idea what to do...
PENALTY
We don't want to do lame stuff
Any suggestion?
I really have no idea
I don't even know what can be funny
No idea
What should we do?
That was so unfair
Why one by one?
I have no idea
I lost it at Suga-chan's beating
That was the best part
PENALTY
Maybe something fun could
happen if we all put Yamazaki in a bag
Sounds weird but alright
Even more than one
More?
PENALTY
Can we come up with something?
Nothing yet?
Translation & subtitles by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
That was the end
FOR OTHER CLIPS VISIT WWW.SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
It was
LIKE MY FB PAGE: FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
Here I am
So irritating...
If anything, you got Matsumoto 5 times
Did I laugh 5 times!?
I've paid only 3 times
Oh
You owe me 2000 yen, then