The first ever Gaki no Tsukai
"Tsukitei Housei's 46th Birthday Celebration
24 Hour Long Interview!"
This is unheard of, huh?
Matsumoto
Hitoshi
Hamada
Masatoshi
Endo
Shozo
Tsukitei
Housei
Tanaka
Naoki
It's amazing, I've never heard of this before!
The title is so long.
Yea, the title is long!
So why are you doing this, Yama-chan?
Why you ask?
Well, this time I turn 46 years old.
You're turning 46 huh?
Yes, my 46th birthday has come.
I think it's bad if you don't try to look back on your life
Eh? 46 years old is your halfway mark?
Isn't it usually 50?
Shouldn't you have done it last year?
You're right, when you're 45!
Is there gonna be questions like that?
I think so, it was 24 hours!
I'm sure you've all been interviewed before.
Isn't 30 minutes kind of long?
Yea...
There's nothing more to ask in 30 minutes.
Completely?
Completely.
I see...
We'll know the real Tsuki... tei Housei.
Remember it already! Seriously!
Translated by: DCSubs
Timed by: YamasakiGIFs
www.gaki-no-tsukai.com        www.reddit.com/r/GakiNoTsukai
For more GnT Discussion and Videos:
Narrator:
Yamada
Shinichi
Taito, Asakusa
The setting for the challenge is
Downtown Tokyo Asakusa's
The Gate Hotel!
Good morning!
Morning!
Housei-san, we will shortly begin the long interview
but how do you feel?
Well... All of it...
I want to summon up all of my 46 years of living.
When you look from behind he looks like Hidetoshi Hoshida.
Good morning!
This is gonna
be long huh~
Isn't this
amazing!
I was extremely
tired.
In this hotel room
a great challenge in TV history is about to start.
Once the interviewer comes
the 24 Hour interview will start.
OK.
Good luck!
Alright, thank you.
This time for this challenge,
there are 3 interviewers on standby.
They will switch out with each other for the sake of the interview.
Excuse me!
Freelance Writer Kojima Kenichi
Published the subculture
book "Tamori Douhon"
with various other writers
Don't worry about it.
I will be asking for your stories, I'm Kojima.
24 Hour Long Interview
Start
It's 9 AM.
Finally, a performer's willpower will be put to the test
as the 24 hour interview starts.
As we begin with this
so called 24 hour interview,
Mhm.
Tsukitei Housei, I plan to
ask about everything in your 46 years.
Let's start with your kindergarten years.
Kindergarten years huh?
From the time you were born.
Alright, let's start with from when I was born.
I was brought outside a lot.
When I was brought out things like
"cute, handsome," I was always called.
My father would get really happy.
And because he was happy,
that's why I was brought out a lot.
I've already given up on this.
So quickly!
But it's the first question!
No, no, there's more!
It was when I was about 3 or 4,
they couldn't take their eyes off me.
For example I was waiting for the train
and I thought we were getting on the next one.
When they looked inside,
I was in the train waving.
They screamed and then
they quickly searched
the next station for me.
Now that you're aware of it,
surprising people and making people laugh,
Well, you know...
looking back on it, how do you feel?
Well, this is
what they call
an interview...
Yea, you're right.
It's not that I'm looking back on it
but rather what I think now but
when I think about what a performer is
I think it's the feeling of trying to make people happy.
I think getting pleased by people is a small part of it.
The feeling of trying
to make people happy
Would you say you were
always livening up your surroundings?
I'd say so.
Was it 3rd year or 4th year
of elementary school...
What the hell!
3rd year or 4th year of elementary school...
When class was over
there was about 10 minutes left extra on purpose.
And then
I said, "There's time left over today too~"
"Then do something Yamazaki."
I left ahead and did an imitation of our teacher.
And then one time I... It was my
3rd grade teacher, was it Mr. Oda?
When we talked about, "What I did like always"
I did a dirty joke.
From that teacher,
because I did that dirty joke...
I remember being told
"You shouldn't make people laugh with a dirty joke."
What the hell!
So this is the tone of the interview huh?
This atmosphere.
For you, is there a boundary line for dirty jokes?
A boundary line for dirty jokes?
For example, your penis...
If you put it out plainly, it's not amusing huh?
Don't you think it's not amusing to a greater extent?
But...
if you stick it over here, isn't it amusing?
It's not amusing if you flauntingly put it out?
Isn't it the opposite?
Of course it is.
The penis is like a spice, don't you think
if you line up penises around it's no good?
Poop is interesting as well.
He changed it!
If you have a bit here, it's funny but
if you had it all around, it's no good.
What the hell is this?
A boundary line for dirty jokes.
2 hours and 50 minutes have passed since the start.
2 hours and
50 minutes!
You were the funny guy
in elementary school
but did a change happen in middle school?
But there's still
so much more!
I guess it was around 2nd year~
Puberty came~
Did you ever get into fights?
Oh yea, I fought a lot
Oh, in primary school too?
I fought 'till 3rd year in middle school.
Tell me about a tale of your heroism.
Well I wouldn't call it heroism.
In primary school as well,
people would gather and fight.
It seemed like you'd go to attack the school.
What happened after your raids?
Honestly...
When I think about it...
It seems like when someone said
"It's getting dark," we'd quit.
What the hell...
Were you a Yankee?
Hmmmm...
Well...
In middle school
I wore one of those long biker jackets.
The ones biker gangs wear, huh?
Those jackets have a lot of kanji on them.
What was on yours?
Well, if I can remember correctly...
"Battle"
Are you sure
that's not a lie?
Is this a real story?
Are you joking
with us?
I can't really remember it...
I'm serious...
It's because it's
a long interview.
No this is
really real!
You just left
it like that!
And drank
some water!
When was your chance to quit?
You had a chance right?
The chance to quit huh?
It was the "Period."
Period?
The period.
It became the period where
I had to choose between what was cooler, that or surfing.
At that time I chose surfing.
Coincidentally,
did you surf long or short style?
Are you serious?
Yes??
I did both.
But isn't there a difference
between the two? Long is....
Yea...
Look you
skipped over it!
Housei! Housei!
My throat
was dry!
Are you sure
it's not because
you're lying?
No! Not at all!
It's been 4 hours and 5 minutes since the start!
Food has been prepared for the battle.
And with this the interviewers change!
Film Writer Kyouko Kunigawa
Writer for Yoshimoto News
Center, experienced in
interviewing celebrities.
A woman!
Thank you for going for such a long time!
Excuse me. Have a seat.
Were you popular in middle school?
Hmm.. Well, if you're
gonna say popular, I was but...
I was
You can see his
worn-out face has
come already....
popular since the low grades of primary school.
Actually, I'd say since kindergarten.
In my classes
I was always chosen as the cutest.
You were well liked huh?
It's been 5 hours and 40 minutes since the start.
The interview continues as they change venues.
Thank you for having me!
I want to continue to ask you
a story from your middle school days.
They're gonna do it here?
In middle school did you
have something you were addicted to?
Well, at least the
weather is good.
I know you did kendo in middle school but...
Well~
When I think about it, in middle school...
The thing I was addicted to
the most was kendo of course...
But that's just one axis of it.
Music.
Music huh?
Honestly, I was addicted to music.
At that time,
I was really into guitar.
Well, it was a lot of heavy metal.
Because I couldn't make a lot of noise, I bought an amp and with that amp...
It sounded a lot more louder.
What was your dream in middle school?
Man, that face
pisses me off~
Because I was playing the guitar,
my dream was to make a living off of it.
It's my
listening face.
When I think about it now....
"When was the happiest time of my life,"
if you asked me that,
it was 2nd year of middle school.
This without a doubt.
On my first date
I went to go see the movie "High Teen Boogie."
In your
2nd year right?
3rd year.
What year was it!
It wasn't in your
second year!?
Which one is
it you idiot!
He's pretty
off, huh?
We met at Koshien Station then
went to Umeta Station and from there
Housei continues to talk about his 3rd year story.
we went to the movie theater then had a break...
Then we rode the train back to Koshien Station,
and said, "Bye bye."
We didn't say a single word.
It was so embarrassing.
When we exchanged diaries at school,
she wrote, "It was fun," but
I thought "LIAR!"
Housei, what did
you think about it?
Me?
It was fun.
Then both of you...
No...
That was a good first date huh?
Well... I guess...
What the hell
is this!?
That's a once in a lifetime date.
7 hours have passed since the start.
Continuing, they go to a cafe.
Were you in any clubs in high school?
Well I joined the kendo club but I quit really quickly.
Why was that?
That's because
I was too busy with the guitar and surfing.
You really surfed?
Is this the truth?
I know after that you had a band but...
when was the band formed?
We formed in the
first year of high school.
Were you a genuine band?
Yea...
I thought of making a living off my guitar.
Oh, is that so?
Where did you perform?
We did it in a studio.
In front of
an audience?
Well, we didn't perform in front of an audience.
Well, I wouldn't say we didn't...
We did some film concert type thing.
What the hell!
What's that?
Well, we did various things.
Look, he's trying
to continue the lie.
Like what?
No, it's not a lie!
Look! This is the
face he makes
when he's lying.
Please go ahead and eat.
OK.
Speaking of the film concert, what is that?
Look she's
asking what it is!
What the hell's
a film concert!?
He's pretending
not to hear it.
Answer it
already!
The film concert?
Huh?
Are you joking?
No, he's serious!
What about it?
Well, I don't exactly understand
what a film concert is...
Hm...
Well...
Isn't it what the name implies?
There's loud noises
and there are performances... And then
because there were cameras
during our time in high school...
Yea...
I think that was
around the first year of high school,
cameras and videos...
Housei begins a story about recording equipment.
They were all over the place.
He didn't say
what it was.
Did you show your band in the film concert?
Hmm... Well...
Our band,
Micheal Schenker Group.
To what percent did you show
your band compared to others?
I don't know if I'd say percent.
It was the fusion of our dream.
The dream of appearing together.
To appear together.
So I don't know if I'd say that...
Well that, I don't really remember.
Did you do it alot...?
Yea, we did it quite frequently.
We weren't there you know, during the film concert...
What the hell
are you going
on about!?
What were you doing then?
No, I was uhh...
Working backstage I guess.
Backstage?
Backstage??
What do
you mean!?
Backstage?
So you didn't perform?
He's finally
gonna lie.
Well because we were doing the film concert.
So it was a film concert where
you showed videos of artists?
Yes.
Housei, so you didn't
show your band performing?
Yea.
So it was something everyone got together for
to watch videos of their favourite bands?
Am I right?
Yes, yea.
Thank you very much!
It's been 8 hours and
38 minutes since the start.
Freelance Writer Koji Aoki
As an editor for "TV Pia" he's
interviewed a lot of actresses.
Current chosen "Monthly Sukapa-"
Returning to the hotel, the interview continues.
What was your impression
when you first saw Downtown?
Well the first time...
It was late at night on a manzai program,
they came out as newcomers.
Um~
They did a comical skit about a doctor.
When I saw that
I thought "Eh?"
It surpassed my expectations.
I thought,
"These guy's are gonna take over the world."
Thank you very much!
What is comedy for you?
In this world comedy is on the highest culture.
Do you have pride in your ad-lib?
Well isn't it obvious?
It's my strength.
Honestly, I have a lot of strength in that.
Why did you have this hairstyle?
I don't know why I thought that was good.
That image pisses me off!
How do you feel being called "Good for nothing?"
Honestly...
Somewhere it killed my soul.
What's your favourite word?
It's "Soul"
"Soul"!?
Your favourite motto?
If you give luck to someone you'll receive it as well.
I think it was...
What does a "married couple" mean to you?
To be inseparable.
When you were picking out your kids' names
did you judge it with character strokes?
I only did it with Tenma.
Looks cold!
Because if Rara and Momo get
married they change their surname.
Uwa~ It looks so cold!
Well this is the coldest
time of the year after all.
15 hours and 32 minutes have passed.
More and more they break into the late night hours.
Housei.. For now...
It seems like there's a massage service.
If you want you can call them.
Ah, I guess I will.
He's calling it
in the interview
room?
What? What?
You're requesting
a massage?
One massage please, room 1205.
The interview switches to asking about rakugo.
The interview continues while waiting for the masseuse to arrive.
The topic; the story of the change to rakugo.
Why did you think of switching to rakugo?
For a while...
I was definitely looking for something
and I thought, "Did I find it?"
Ah, the masseuse has come.
The massage Housei requested has arrived.
The massage has arrived to the room.
Thank you for requesting me today.
The interview continues while she prepares.
It was during the time
I started a regular Osaka program with Higashino.
I think we did it for about a year.
"Yamachan, have you heard of rakugo?"
"Have you ever listened to Shijaku Katsura?"
"Sorry, I've never listened to it."
"If you listen to it once, you'll find it interesting."
Sorry for interrupting your story,
I need you to get changed so I can use the oil.
Is that ok? Yep.
Is that ok? Yep
The boxers he got from Tanaka
Those boxers.
Ahh!
Those boxers!
In an instant, he changes and gets ready for the massage.
Let's continue the interview where we left off.
You talked about how Higashino
recommended listening to rakugo but
what did you listen to?
No, because Higashino recommended it to me
I went to "ＴＳＵＴＡＹＡ"...
"Shijaku's Complete Works"
I rented a volume of it.
I said, "Rakugo is this interesting!?"
"Eh! This is what rakugo feels like?"
Because of this characteristic,
I began wanting to do it.
I thought, "Huh, now you mention it,
Tsukitei
Hachimitsu
"I think Hachimitsu said he had an interest in rakugo."
I called him and said, "Honestly, your rakugo...
"How do you do it?"
"Housei, I'm a professional storyteller (rakugo)."
Tsukitei
Happo
He said to his father,
"Housei wants to do rakugo."
And every month there was a study group thing and
I was finally able to participate in the study group.
What did you learn from your teacher, Happo?
As a teacher, it was about 2 years,
at that time...
"I'll try to get you into the Kyoto Rakugo Association."
"Ah! Sorry, thank you very much!"
After I became a member
the surrounding families changed their discerning eye too.
After I heard about it
I realized the huge battle my teacher did.
A certain group were definitely opposed to it.
A guy that wasn't studying fair and square.
But... my teacher fought a huge battle for me.
Lastly he said,
"If Housei does something wrong, I'll quit."
Your teacher himself said that?
Well...
Until then this world...
Um...
Huh?
He's overcome
with emotions...
What the hell,
you're crying!
This is emotional,
huh?
No, entering the rakugo world and this comedian world,
up until then....
What a dirty
tear!
He's looking this
way while getting
an oil massage!
What the hell!
Enough already!
This is a
disgusting
picture!
Even though you say
it's an emotional thing,
this is definitely
not emotional!
He's talking about
his teacher with
half of his ass out.
He's already
sleeping.
Housei falls asleep in the middle of his memory of his teacher.
You're lying!
You're lying.
You've gotta
be lying.
Uwa, uwa....
Housei~
He fell asleep while
crying about his
teacher's story!
Housei?
Are you kidding?
As I thought, the memory of your teacher, Happo...
What a dirty
picture!
Housei, more and more...
Housei~
Scary...
Scary.
Uwa, uwa!
This is
too scary!
Housei-san, are you alright?
It's like he's
a ghost.
The massage finishes and he goes to the bathroom.
With this the massage is finished.
Like this, he goes to the bathroom.
How's your throat?
My throat hurts a lot.
What time is it?
2 AM.
2 AM?
I've been talking for 17 hours already.
17 hours huh.
NEXT WEEK
There's nothing more to ask?
The 24 hour long interview sequel!
What did I say?
Housei, can you please wake up?
Challenging an unprecedented record, the fate of Housei is!?
We come close to knowing all of Tsukitei Housei!
Challenging an unprecedented record,
the fate of Housei is!?
Oi, it's the morning.
Uwa, uwa...!
This is too scary!
It's like he's a ghost.
Gaki no Tsukai #1198 (2014.03.30) - Heipo Review