Missing parts translation [japan to french]: Hotarubi
Missing parts translation [french to english] & edit / styling: aymeric000 (Thimble)
Original subtitles from: Sutekidayo & Mr_Orange, Gojinki & Alex, and Shadi
Autumn 2005
A legendary batsu game was going to happen...
A school where you shouldn't laugh.
The 4 men who will participate in this batsu game are...
Yamasaki Hosei
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Matsumoto Hitoshi
And the man who will abuse them in the dark.
Hamada Masatoshi
School life,
it was laughter and hope in everyday life,
memories that you keep forever in your heart.
But this school was a place where laughter is punished...
A school where a small smile is enough to be beaten...
In addition, this school has many traps...
This place is hell on earth.
It all started with this event...
"Gaki no tsukai ya arahende!!" Introduce you
"Electrical outlets Russian roulette" challenge!!
Out of 100 electrical outlets, there are 4 in which the current flows.
The game will be held until the elimination of one of the Downtown member.
They can only count on their luck!
The first man to receive his ticket for the batsu game is...
This one should be fine...
Will it be okay?
This one is very height.
The light has changed, right?
Yes, the light has changed!
With that, we can have suspicions!
You can see how lousy
the electrical installation is in this studio!
It's not good!
You're saying nonsense, It's not that !
I'm going for it!
I don't feel it! I don't feel it!
Come on!
It comes!
Endo Shozo participates in the batsu game!
The second man after Endo is...
I'm going!
(Show time!)
Yamasaki Hosei participates in the batsu game!
Who will be the third victim?
I'm going!
Wow! Fast!
Tanaka Naoki participates in the batsu game!
And finally, the last man...
I choose number 64!
Wow, I never thought it would be like this!
Are you OK?
Watanabe! Are you all right?
Keep yourself together, Watanabe!
I'm going!
What? What?
Stop that! It hurts too much!
The last one is Matsumoto Hitoshi!
Here are the 4 participants in the batsu game!
Electric Shock Showdown Winner
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Hello Everyone! Today, I would like to show you the Batsu Game you've been waiting for!
Alright, well lets get started. Ok guys, please come out!
Downtown
Electric Shock Showdown Losers
Matsumoto Hitoshi ・ Yamasaki Hosei ・ Endo Shozo ・ Tanaka Naoki
Cocorico
I really think we should stop doing these types of Batsu Games.
Oh really?
and it probably makes you angry when I say that but...
but we haven't been able to sleep!
After you went home did you go to sleep?
Its like we are so wound up we can't sleep!
after we received all those punishments
and everytime I'm about to doze off I hear - "Matsumoto- OUT!!"
Tochigi Prefecture, Nasu Shiobara
This time the stage for the Batsu Game is in a place famous for it's Hot Springs
Nasu Shiobara in Tochigi prefecture.
Surrounded by nature, this green paradise is to 4 people...
Hell on earth.
Day of the Batsu Game
7:00 a.m.
On the day of the Batsu Game
because of an incoming typhoon there was heavy rain in the morning.
Wow, the weather's horrible.
Yeah, it even affects how you feel..
affects tension too.
8:45 a.m.
Then at 8:45 am, the rain got lighter
The bus carrying the 4 losers arrives at the school.
The person waiting for them there is, of course, this guy
You're wearing the same clothing as then!
(Hey! Guys!)
Fujikumi Sensei
*parody of a teacher in a j-drama "Gokusen"
Fujiwara Hiroshi
(Downtown's Former Manager)
He's So ugly!
This way! Over Here!
Welcome to Kuchiburu... I mean, West Kuchibiru High School,
It's a funny name right, Matsumoto?
The school name is in honor of Hamada
Kuchibiru = 'Lips'
West Kuchibiru Private High School
When it (the batsu game) starts, can you take your wedding ring off?
We'll start with you, get going.
That way I think I won't laugh as much.
That's mean..
Look at it!
More importantly, you guys are entering school now, whats with those clothes?
I have your uniforms in the car.
So change right away.
Changing Clothes
<Yamasaki> (laughs)
<Matsumoto> Whats so funny?
<Yamasaki> I've already found the first trap
<Matsumoto> Wha...
<Matsumoto:That's not fair. You'll have an advantage.
<Yamasaki> Yeah, I guess I will
Are you guys about done?
Yeah
When you... (cough) are ready, could you come out here?
He sounded like he had
something stuck in his throat
When Fujiwara sees Yamasaki's uniform, he can't stop laughing
Other stu-(laughs) students are..(laughs)
Yamasaki, the school rules...(laughs) you're almost breaking them.
That's unfair right?
I know, right!
Its not my fault...it was in the--
Shut up!
Let's go.
Announcment of School Rules
I'm going to tell you the school rules
First Rule: You four are going to..(cough)
Why don't you cough it out?
Did he have a cold?
You are going to enter West Kuchibiru High School.
Until the graduation ceremony tomorrow is over, you are high school students.
Second Rule: Once you get through the gate you cannot laugh under any circumstances.
The gate?
Its right here.
Rule Number 3: If you laugh, a horrifying punishment will be executed right away.
Starting Line
That is all.
It starts from here?
This white line.
It's gonna be a long day!
Lets go.
Fujiwara should stop laughing for no reason
I'm coming in!
Here we go!
9:00 a.m.
I didn't see the first half of the show.
So, whatcha ya think? you're going to be studying here.
It's not bad, huh?
Not bad all it,
Its big too.
I think I'll have you guys tell me what you think.
Yamasaki, you first.
It's not shabby at all.  With a gym and...
Cut the crap.
Endo, go.
I think it's...
Ah!
A middle-aged school girl arrives at the school
Good morning!
Good morning~♥
She's too much!
She's really something
That's Kuchibiru West High's Madonna
Don't even think... about asking her out.
He always stumbles
(laughs)..Shall we go?
He just laughed!
You!
It was a nice first laugh.
Was it Yamasaki?
If you laugh, other school students smack you with a bamboo sword (Shinai)
This the punishment?! Are you serious!
That's definitely gonna hurt.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Yeah!, It really hurts!
Much more than that whip from last time
Ouch!
Sensei Please,
Seriously, no more studdering. Please.
We're going.
Ahh, this is going to hurt.
It will seriously damage my behind if I get lots of them.
Come on, hurry up!
Monsieur Kamayatsu
(musician)
Something like that...
Kamayatsu, you aren't giving your all these days.
Wait a minute!
You may not know this, but his father was struck by illness.
So he's working as a paper boy in the morning.
Is that true, Kamayatsu?
Yeah..
Do you want to?
It's funny because I can't hear anything they're saying because of the wind.
It's blowing too hard.
Oooooouch!
That's gotta hurt
It hurts!
Kamayatsu, we've gotta practice for the next competition.
Its wrong for him to be on the team.
What are you doing Kamayatsu! Catch it!
(The ball hit him right in the in the face)
It was right in the face.
No wonder we all laughed.
That's not fair.
Catch the F'ing Ball Kamayatsu!
They did it again and again.
Stop this. Please!
Don't do it again.
Kamayatsu, we run next.
Go fast Kamayatsu!
Run!
Kamayatsu-kun
Faster, Kamayatsu. Kamayatsu--!!
Ah, The bloom of youth.
Aren't sports great?
Don't do that again, please
He dropped the ball so many times
There has to be no more of that
My thigh really hurts!
Yeah, mine too.
The one you got looked painful.
Man there's a lot, of these skits
How bad is he?
Is he okay!?
Nu..Nukumizu
Ace of the team who is cooling his shoulder
Nukumizu (actor)
Nukumizu, how's your shoulder?
I can't really say right now
You pitch too much!
I'm sorry, I'll do the best I can
All right.  We continue practicing for the national tournament.
Yeah!
Look at him
Look at the way he walks
There ya go,  that's a good throw huh?
What?!
That was safe!
Ahh! My back!
That one really hurt!
Nukumizu is in no shape to play any sport
This is impossible when you see that.
He will never make it to the national tournament
It has just started, But we're already...
It's very fast paced, its intense!
Yeah it is
Here's the shoe lockers
There's a locker with your names on it for each of you.
So open it and change..uh.. your shoes.
this is kind of scary,
Ah, its OK.
Tanaka's indoor shoes
I don't like this...
Ah, mine are perfectly fine too
Endo's indoor shoes
Oh, Good.
Matsumoto's indoor shoes
Its fine, There's no problem.
Didn't you laugh just now?
They're filthy
Yamasaki's shoes
Those are filthy
Yeah really dirty.
Matsumoto notices something and starts laughing
And they're a little too small
No no no! I didn't laugh at your shoes
Look
(Gum)
I couldn't keep the chewing gum to myself
Ow!  My thigh hurts.
I thought this was the only trap
Yeah, kind of a decoy
At this school, "the pen and the sword" is our motto.
"BunBuRyouDou" is a saying meaning = Both Literary and Military Arts--Smart and Athletic
even the sports teams are very successful.
These are the Baseball club's...
They are runner-up in the national tournament.
Wow, that's amazing!
The softball team also came 2nd. The soccer, 3rd.
Who wouldn't laugh at that
He's too good
And these are the amateur wrestling team's...
They're the national champion.
Here's a picture of the team.
Chief Producer Suga
Suga-san is my weakness!
It's hopeless, Suga-san gets me every time.
Yeah, me too.
Here's the article from when they won.
(He's Strong, Too Strong! Super High School Kid Wrestler Suga-kun)
did you see that picture?
(Endo hid his face and luckily escaped the punishment.)
There are way too many traps.
Suga-kun is the hero of our school.
He's face is intense! This pictures incredible.
This isn't good.
Wait! I didn't laugh!
This way.
I can't lower my guard, this is rough.
Here
This is our class?
Their Classroom   3 nen(year) B gumi(class)
This is your classroom. Your desk has your name written on it, so please find it.
(West Kuchibiru High School <Motto> Moisture, Thickness, Glow)
(Blue Sky MC Blue Sky)
They thought we'd find this funny?
Wait here.
(Blue Sky My Sweet Helen Blue Sky)
I don't know what they were thinking
The four of them finally arrived at the classroom
The fact that recieved so many punishments in so little time makes them uneasy.
I understand why you laughed at that, Endo.
The wind completely drowned out their voices
Football Star
Monsieur Kamaytsu
That was really hard, honestly.
That wasn't right.
The guy with the tuque...
Yamasaki pulls stale bread from his desk
Isn't my belt too short?
Just barely
He laughed.
He did.
Tanaka was out too.
You didn't have to tell us
Why did you tell us?
Here comes the boss
He remembered you, Tanaka
Okay?
*Kakushinhan - Is the japanese noun for the type of crime that somebody commits believes that their actions are right based on religous or political beliefs. In a legal terms its a "crime of conscience"
Really, I am
Hear that Smack?
I'm no good, this punishment doesn't suit me
don't say it "doesn't suit me"
This happens a lot doesn't it.
It's just Friendly Fire right
Yeah, like a stray 'one word' bullet
Right right right.
There's no such thing as a punishment that "doesn't suit you" or "suits you"
9:30 a.m. Morning Assembly
Only 30 minutes?
9:30 a.m. It's time for the morning assembly
(It felt so long.)
They go to attend the morning assembly
Hey!
Why were you late?
My bicycle had a flat tire.
and you?
I overslept.
Gekidan Hitori (comedian)
Go to the morning assembly right now.
Come closer.
Why are YOU late?
My little sister got sick, so I took her to the hospital.
slap
Why are you late?
My sister got sick a---
My sister--
You'll laugh at that for sure
You little... come with me!
He was so cruel to such a kind boy
There's no way we couldn't laugh,
Such a kind boy.
He was ripping into him
He was beating the crap out of him.
Anybody would laugh at that!
Had enough of Suga too
I would still laugh at that even if it meant I'd die tomorrow.
You guys are late. Quick, get in line.
There's a teacher with an Afro
We now begin the morning assembly of West Kuchibiru High School
First off, greetings from the principal.
Principal's greeting
Good morning everyone
Good morning
*He keeps using 'lip' instead of 'mouth'
The other day, triggered by a bad 'lip'...
some students in this school got into a fight with students from another school.
It has even become trouble for the police.
I've told you all..
"Before resorting to violence let your 'lips' do the talking" many times before.
I've 'lipped' this to you over and over. As the saying goes:
"Don't let your 'lip' get you into trouble".
Take that to heart, and act responsibly
Thank you very much
Next, let me introduce the newly appointed teachers.
New Teacher Introduction
From Shogun High School...
Mr. Topknot
Mr. Topknot from Shogun High
From Bird's Nest High School...
Mr. Big Afro
Mr. Big Afro from Birds Nest High
What kind of name is that?!
Lastly, from Metropolitan Strip House High School...
Mr. Omame (a bean)
4'10" Mr. Omame (Director Heipo)
That wasn't bad. He usually sucks, but this time...
I wasn't ready for that. Omame
On behalf of the new teachers, greetings from Mr. Omame.
(Greetings on behalf of the new teachers)
(For some reason the mic feeds back)
Some one broke their bamboo sword.
Eh.. I'm going to teach at West 'Lip' High starting this semester,
Eh..
I'm 'a bean'!
I admire the extras for keeping a traight face
Eh.. I'm going to teach at West 'Lip' High starting this semester,
I'm 'a bean'!
I... eh... before becoming a teacher,
i was in charge of lighting in a strip club.
Note: Heipo really worked as a lighting designer in a strip club when he was in his twenties.
Thank you, Mr. Omame
(A Black student starts to wobble.)
Are you all right?
Watanabe, are you OK?
Watanabe
Are you ok?
(He's speaking a local dialect)
My he...head is spinning...
Keep yourself together, Watanabe!
I advise everyone to be careful of anemia (not enough blood making it to the brain because of poor circulation)
Next, we sing the school song together.
(Everbody Safe)
West Kuchibiru High School's school song
(They even made a school song?)
That girl has the things that make me fall in love
What kind of lyrics are those?!
They rise from her mouth like Mt. Fuji
Plump, soft, and glossy
Two nutured red shells
Aaa 'Lips', 'Lips' West High School
(You were laughing hard)
Wha---?
(This time, tons of hard bread)
(that was definitely out, Tanaka)
That's a lot (of bread)
(They always set up traps on Yamasaki)
(They do)
(Its not fair.)
(Like an inside man?)
Hou-san (Yamasaki), Do you mind, from my angle...
..the bread (in the desk) is...
I can see it!
Come on, its in sight
Its not my fault
oh Jeez !
30 a.m, the first class is Japanese.
(Classmates attend Class)
Good Morning
All rise.
Bow, sit down.
I'll take attendance
Aikawa Kengo
Here!
Kakizaki Shinya
Sudou Michisuke
Here!
Watanabe Saburou
3rd Year, Class B
Matsumoto Hitoshi
(Didn't he just collaspe recently?)
Eh! You again!?
(We saw him when he came in. Still, it was funny.)
Matsumoto hid his face and luckily escaped
the punishment.
I was lucky that time
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Here
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Here
All present.
Umm.. Teacher?
Well..
(You made us laugh)
(And you were out too!)
My butt is numb.
(Sometimes it really hurt!)
Yamasaki, don't talk like you're in a comedy skit please
Take your textbook out of your desk.
Open your books to page 57.
We're going to be studying the mordern 31 syllabled verse and the haiku.
Along with Ishikawa Takuboku and other famous poets, there's a section for the works of Suga Kenji--the chief producer of the show.
This textbook has a trap
Let's turn to the next page
Next is Suga Kenji.
Those cameras nailed us
You couldn't hide from them
This time they were right in front us
No! The Big Guy!
Which one of us?! Which?
Why me!?
It was impossible to get away with
anything with those cameras
I'm going to read his Haiku, so repeat after me
If ramen doesn't get you high ratings... bring out dogs
Dirty Jokes while I'm around...are unforgiveable
TV people, All the good ones are dark (skin tone)
(That's not true. Just because he's dark...)
Yama-chan, you stay serious.
The following exercise aims to use their imagination.
They will have to write in a blank book,
a story that matches with the title.
And the subject is...
The title of the book you will write is...
"Three Matsuzaka's cows"
Matsumoto, read the first part.
"What is this feeling of freedom?"
Thought Matsuzaka...
Why does it sounds like a conclusion?
Matsuzaka couldn't remains quiet, so he went outside.
And suddenly...
...Hanamasa arrived.
I can ear the teacher's laughing !
"I'm going to go to Kobe."
Next, Yamasaki.
Matsuzaka and Hanamasa were heading towards Maesawa.
With the three little calves.
How far...
...did they take care of them...
...by eating them?
Now, its kind of sudden, but we're going to do a quick pop quiz
You may begin now.
(Pop quiz starts)
They take the quiz very seriously
(We were very serious)
(The student that came in late)
(Nandenkanden's (Ramen restaurant Chain) President/ Owner: Kawahara
The president...
What is he doing here?
Producer Nakamura
*parody of a detective in a drama played by Tachi Hiroshi
Isn't that Tachi Hiroshi? Everyone, look!
He was walking in the heavy rain.
And he started walking from so far away
Yeah, it was pretty far huh.
Man the punishment hurts
11:30 a.m. The second class is English
They have this guy as their teacher
You were laughing
Science Teacher
Murakami Shoji (comedian)
Stand Up
Good morning everyone
Sit down please
Before learning English, it's important to study American history, isn't it?
The first President of the United States, Washington.
Ah! Or was it Lincoln?
Yes that's right, the first president was Lincoln.
And the second president was Killer Khan (former wrestler).
What!?
Huh!? Me too?
Professor, you are despicable.
Let's study
This is my mother
At work, I've been asked lots of times to bring pictures of me from when I was little but...
This is the only one I have.
Actually, this isn't even me, its my little brother
He was telling us sad stories the whole time
I don't know why, but it just got funnier and funnier
Why did he do that?
He was changing his glasses a lot
George
Trainee George
Cabbage
George
Tomato
(snorts)...Tomato
again?
He did it over and over
I never understood why
For some reason, Mr. Murakami changes his glasses
Manhatan is a incredibly scary place.
It's late
Since its so late my mom is probably worrying about me
I better go home now
Myhattan is scary!
Who's there?
Is it just in my head?
Maybe I'm mistaken
'cause I do that alot
Who the hell are you!? Freak!
I know you've been following me since "Akabane Bridge"
"Akabane bridge" cracked me up
(Murakami and George left the room due to some urgent business)
What was with the glasses?
I don't know, he changed them alot huh
Mr. Shouji still isn't able to come back so
we're going to study using an english educational video
Okay, playing the video
Let's read about Marco Polo in English
Reader: Jimmy Onishi
(comedian/ former member of Gaki no Tsukai)
Its definetly not "es"
He really got me there
This is bad
Yeah this is going to be rough
That was a completely different word!
Why on earth did he say "lotion"?
Hou-san did very well here.
He doesn't give up
It's definitely not "Victor"
definitely not "victor"!
'victor'...
He couldn't figure it out so he changed
it to 'victor'.
Let's count to 100 in English.
oh please we had enough already.
What an idiot
This is so not right! Something like this!
This must be beyond any stretch of
their imagination
How long is he going to keep this up?
Pinching your face is cheating Matsumoto!
This is impossible
How much longer?
He's too much
who wouldn't laugh?
Ahh, that is impossible, good thing its finally over
No more. No.
No, we've had enough.
Let's Say days of the week in English
Can I just say the ones I know?
That's not how it works
go easy on me please! OuCH!
I'm done..I can't
I can't take this anymore, Teacher.
What days are his fingers? Is he saying them order?
I couldn't help it
What's the point if it isn't in the right order?
Yeah, He's screwing up the order.
What else...
Kayoubi(Tuesday)-
Kayoubi?
Kaviar...I never learned that.
no way... why didn't he ?!
gees
(Recess)
That was tough
I was already laughing every time he was about to push the start button.
Really? Ehehe-- Uh oh!
(Matsumoto forgets he's in the middle
of the batsu game and laughs)
(Luckily he is safe because they missed it)
You next class is P.E. so
change into the P.E. clothes in the lockers and come to the gym.
Where'd that voice come from?
(Endo Notices something is wrong with his gym clothes.)
(Chiaki (his wife) Love <3)
It was mean
We could take it though
it's just...
It was mean to Endo
Get moving, go to the gym
I did feel sorry for him
It did hurt a little
12:30 p.m.
3 period - P.E.
In the third hour, their next class is P.E.
The person who is going to teach them is...
Nandenkanden is the only student who also participates in the course
Oh yes it's true. But why ?
Ride On!!!!
Hard Gay P.E. Teacher
Razor Ramon HG sensei
Okaaaaay!!
Hard Gay is here!!
*Hard Gay is the performing name of Masaki Sumitani, who is a famous Japanese wrestler, comedian, and talent.
Okaaay!!
Don't be shy, Stare all you like!
Here we go, check this out
The smell of a gym
FooooooooO!!
Okaaaay.
right, line up.
First we will warm up with some excercises
I'll call it the Hard Gay work out.
Here I go
1..
2..
3..
4..
you do it.
There's a sudden downpour outside
Imagine you're having sex
That's some intense rain!
Incredible
That was some loud rain.
Waaa! it hurts so much in these pants!!!
Yeah, they will
They're thin huh...
This is how you thrust your pelvis.
Its going to get faster
much faster, watch!
Faster! Faster!!
Do you think this looks slow?
You're wrong.
I'm moving at such a fast speed that it looks like I'm moving slow.
This is uber fast.
It took me three years to master this.
Today's class is...
Hardle's Foooooo!! (Hurdles)
In hurdles, it doesn't matter how fast go
If you wanna be Hard Gay
you gotta go jump hurdle's the Hard Gay way
Got it? Watch closely
It's how erotically can you get over the hurdles.
You can rub against it
You can improvise
He's Crazy
This is how you do it.
That's not "jumping", he went under it!
Matsumoto you first, Go
How erocitally can you jump them
that is the Hard Gay way.
I was going to say "Ride On"
This is really... Can we skip this?
Let's do something else.
This was really hard.
You can go back Matsumoto.
Hmmm?
Hard Gay Fooooo!
Razor Ramon NP  enters
(Nakamura - Producer)
Ohh, you're here
Nakamura Producer - NP himself
Okaaay
Okaay
We're buddies, pals!
Did you see that unsure look on his face?
This is too.. This is Dirty!
Your boxers, (I can see) your boxers
Do you know what kind of relationship I have with him?
Oookaay
Its this kind of relationship, yeaah
Boxers
Okaaaay!
Isn't this fun!?
Look at the camera
We'll have them look at our faces
We'll make them stare at them
Its funnier watching the video
Yeah
They're really, really trying too hard
What's this?
Placed Note
Put on this wig!!
Look, see you had another advantage
A blonde perm wig
I had a lot of those didn't I?
Hey, Guys. Its time for the long awaited lunch break
There is a packed lunch in your bags. Eat up!
Really?
Sweet
Let's eat!
I'm so happy
All right...
This time its stale bread from his bag
Look at mine...
A box lunch of just beans
Tanaka's Super
Deluxe Box Lunch
That's luxurious
Yeah it is
What is this unfairness?
I thought I could get one
They only gave the big box
lunch to Tanaka
Yamasaki's Box Lunch
Mine's pretty normal
What's yours (Matsumoto)?
Why am I laughing?!
that was a big box.
It was pretty heavy, I think it was about 5 kg
They all eat their various box lunches, and take a much needed rest
However, that won't last for long
For the assaults are going to begin again
(Tsuruko) "Discussion on heartaches with Tsuruko"
Grade 3 Class C
Shôfukutei Tsuroko's radio
I answer all the questions that the students of
Kuchibiru West High school could ask themselves
(Tsuruko) I receive a student who seems to have a little problem
(Student) Nice to meet you
(Tsuruko) What a beautiful voice, she is so cute!
(Student) Thank you
(Tsuruko) Could you introduce yourself?
(Student) Grade 2, class C, my name is Kômoto Junko.
Jun-chan
Komoto Junichi
(comedian, actor)
(Jun) But everyone calls me Jun-chan
(Tsuuruko) So, what is your problem?
(Jun) Well, I'm currently in love with someone
(Tsuruko) And how old are you now? ten...
(Jun) I'm 17
(Tsuroko) 17 years old... And is it the first time that you are in love?
(Jun) Yes it’s the first time I’m feeling that, the first time
(Tsuruko) It doesn't have to be easy to say his name on air, does it?
(Tsuruko) Can you tell me the initial of his first name?
(Jun) Aaah... Uhh... Hitoshi...
(Tsuruko) Huh, what what?
(Jun) H-kun. With H-kun...
(Tsuruko) H-kun?
(Jun) Because it's Hitoshi
(Jun) When I do it with H-kun... It always ends... as soon as he finishes
(Tsuruko) Ah yes, normally he must also ***
(Jun) But Hitoshi-kun... H-kun... never does it
What are they talking about?
What is this discussion?
Right.
End of broadcast
Jun chan appears
I caught you!
Jun chan, was that ok to say that on air?
Sure, no problem !
Because i didn't say any names...
I didn't say Matsumoto-kun's name so it should be ok
You should have said his name
I couldn't do something like that, if i had done that...
Matsumoto-kun would be angry
But you "did it" with Matsumoto-kun, right?
I did!
In the pool...
...we did it
Give me a break...
This isn't really... ah someone's here
Please, make it stop
He's so dark
Vrrroooom
Itao Itsuji makes a magnificent entrace
*Itao Itsuji is a famous Comedian, he is part of the comedy duo 130R.
This is too much
What is he doing?!
What is this
Ahh, this is gonna suck
Whose the jerk called Nandenkanden?
Those glares where pretty fierce
He's leaving with that?
His leg got caught!
It was a natural Itao exit!
That was typical Itao
His leg got caught?
He got it caught really good on the seat!
That last part was pretty cruel wasn't it!?
Yeah it was
He was supposed to look cool on the bike
but when he went to get on--BANG, he smacked his leg on the second seat in the rear.
And that's why everybody laughed
Who wouldn't laugh at that?!
How long was that company president with you?
The president...I don't remember
2:30 pm
5 hours and 30 minutes passed
4th hour class  Science
2:30 p.m. 5 and a half hours have passed since the game started.
Their next class is Science
The teacher in charge is?!
I feel nervous...
If Nomo's pitching we're okay.
For today's class, I'd like to study about
the science of breathing.
When we breath we take in oxygen and put out CO2
Science Teacher
Hosshan Sensei
*Hosshan (Hoshida Hidetoshi) is a comedian who is famous for his ability to put things up his nose.
But its kind of hard to see air.
So I will teach you about breathing in a very easy to understand way.
This is what we commonly use for this demonstration.
Udon
(Japanese Fat Noodle)
I knew it.
Watch closely
Breathing, suck in, push out. You guys are even doing it right now.
That's...who wouldn't laugh at that?
Sensei, that's just wrong.
Hosshan Sensei is a professional at passing things through his nose. (Do not try this at home)
I'm gonna definitly laugh
Is this really science?
Is that going into your lung?
Ok, we'll try a longer one.
It's easier to see.
stop it, We get it already
We're good
This is freeze frame of breathing
Ahhh, I wonder where the air went
We already get that
We don't need to see it
Give us a break, lets stop this
Its still a pretty hard to see, isn't it
This here is rubber
Rubber
As in a rubber jump rope?
Yes
Ahhhhhh
Sensei, you don't have to...
We're good
You don't understand what oxygen isssaaaaaah
We got it
I think he doesn't get what it is
Cough*
Why did udon come out?
Its Carbon Dioxide
you breathed in oxygen, and then that's the CO2
What is that
I have some fun experiments too.
Will someone drink this juice through this tube?
Tube
Its okay, this is juice
I'm okay, No thanks
When this tube comes out, will someone drink through it?
We're good
Sensei. That's pretty disgusting
This is no good. this is the type of tube for going down the throat.
Aww, come on lets stop this arleady
If we're going to keep doing this, we can just keep the bambo sword guys here
How can I get you to understand?
We understand it
We get it
Alright, well tell me what is breathing then
You inhale oxygen and exhale carbons dioxide.
Yeah, but your forgetting about it going through the lungs.
It goes through the lungs before you exhale it out.
But the udon wasn't going through your lungs was it?
It did!
No it wasn't
It wasn't going through your lungs though right?
It did!
No, you're lungs are...
IT DID! I'M TELLING YOU IT DID!
It didn't pass through!
IT DID!
It was just going through your nose a mouth
We've got no choice but to accept it, he's the science teacher.
Ahhh-- My bum is getting swollen already.
It's intense ---Owwww that hurts
We understand it! We get it
Should we do it with Bracken next?
*Bracken (warabi) is a wild plant with large leaves that grows thickly on hills and in woods and turns brown in the fall.
Say whaa!?
Whaaa!?
Don't whine so much when I say a Japanese food like Warabi.
Warabi (Bracken)
What type of class is this?
This is the "just right" pattern
It's just right.
I've never heard of that pattern
There's no such thing
There is one. Even in respiration, when you inhale the just right amount of breath!
It hit my balls.
Going in is hell, but coming out is hell too!
This is the first time I've been stuck in the middle of the "just right" pattern
Endo, will you try it? The 'just right' pattern
I'll pass. I'd mess it up for sure
Endo, just try it for me!
That really is "just right", I can see it you know.
If you can see it then its not "just right"
I just see the end in your nostril
It didn't make it around into your throat did it.
So it's the right distance, right?
Breathing therefore means breathing in oxygen and exhaling CO2.
Hosshan sensei, someone asks you on the phone.
Please go immediately to the teacher's lounge.
I hope you have learned the lesson.
We will never forget it.
And at the end...
The science teacher was awful!
You should watch him.
Hosshan sensei cannot return at this time.
You will still learn through a video.
I hate this kind of video!
What is the food chain?
In the countryside, each living being eats and is eaten by another living being.
This is called a food chain.
The ecological balance is managed from this chain.
The first link of the food chain is a microorganism found in the earth.
And this microorganism is...
...the "Heipo".
While it formed only one Heipo at the start, it multiplies thanks to the sunlight.
This is called the Heipo multiplier.
How can you hold it !?
What is this video...
I'am afraid about the next...
This is not good...
After having multiplied, it moves to the surface of the earth.
And suddenly, it is devoured by herbivores or insects.
The herbivore that ate the Heipo is...
You guys are seriously strong!
In addition, these primary carnivores are themselves devoured by secondary carnivores.
As long as the animals are alive, they evacuate their fecal matter, and thus the Heipo returns to the earth.
It plays an important role in the ecological balance...
This video is horrible!
It's because of his laugh!
This video is filled of bad things!
That's true, they wanted it unnoticed.
A really bad video...
And the laugh at the end...
Science is terrifying.
Terrifying !
Terrifying.
Tired of laughing so much in science class, they are now taking a break.
This is where Matsumoto's concentration weakens.
I'm thinking that... guys, really...
When you see I'm about to laugh, you might...
You see ?
What ?
It's not our fault.
We have nothing to do with it at all!
We listened seriously to what you had to say.
Exactly.
Ah, did it touch your balls?
I pity you !
For example, if one of my senpai
would be in this kind of batsu game,
and from the moment I see that he begins to laugh...
I will laugh before him, in order to take his punishment...
Before ? So, if you are going to laugh, I have to laugh before to take the hit for you, right?
I didn't mean to say it so directly but...
But, yes...
Yes.
We listened carefully, we didn't do anything wrong !
It's totaly your fault!
For example, if Shinusukeniyan...
You see...
If ever, both of us had participated in this batsu game...
As soon as I thought:
"Aah ! Shinsukeniyan can't take it anymore!"
As he reached his limit, well...
He is scary! He is scary!
The ground shakes when the guy is coming!
It's a little scary.
The next class is a sociology field trip.
So now we're going to get on a bus, and go study society.
3:30 p.m.
(6 hours and 30 minutes since it started)
5th hour class -Sociology field trip
3:30 p.m. the 5th hour class is a field trip for sociology.
Riding the school bus for a sociology field trip!
The quickly board the bus and depart for their destination
However...
These four students of sociology are about to discover the terrifying reality of society.
Even here an ingenious trap is...
Now, the thing waiting for them is?
Huh? What is that?
It looks like that car is having engine trouble
Wha-! Isn't that Mori Shinichi?
*(Mori Shinichi, born November 18, 1947 in Kofu, Yamanashi) is a Japanese male enka singer and composer, who also sings folk and pop music. His total sales of gramophone records and CDs has reportedly been over 90 million copies.
Mori Shinichi in a pickle
because his car broke down.
Really? I wouldn't know Shinichi even if I saw his face...
Everybody Safe
I never thought I'd see Mori Shinichi in a place like this
The first place they come to is one of the longest suspension bridges in Japan.
Momijidani Suspension Bridge
About this time all four of them forget they are in a batsu game
and go on an innocent stroll through the air
This bridge's total length is 320 meters! (1,050 ft)
Wow, that's something
Woah, its really shaking.
I still don't know why they took us all the way over there.
The four of them head back towards the bus
A new trap catches the four
but there is an unexpected trap waiting for them...
Ah! We're getting a parking ticket!
Whaa!? A ticket?
WHERE do you think you're parking?
Police Grandmas Appear on the Scene
A parking lot...
Tanaka wasn't the one driving so...
Where do you think you're parking?
Where are you parking?
For some reason the police grandma kisses Tanaka.
Don't ever park there again.
How many times does she do this?
She just wants to do THAT doesn't she.
And you're even called out on top of that
What just happened?
Her face was HUGE!
you got kissed!?
Yes.
She's really stepping on the gas
That's dangerous
They're flying!
Haha that's kinda funny
Tanaka are you ok?
No no no..I'm not okay...
Shall we go to the next stop?
After having been slowed down
Hurrying to the next stop
the party heads towards their next stop
However...
Uh oh
What the...Mori Shinichi is getting a parking ticket!
Mori Shinichi recieving a parking ticket
How did you not laugh at that?
Seeing them the second time was just too much
Scary
I bet that's why they were driving so fast
Ah it all makes sense now
The party makes a pit stop
Because their destination is so far away, they stop for a bathroom break.
However even here...
Wha!? We're getting another parking ticket!
Not again
The school bus gets parking ticket again
WHERE d'ya think you're parking?
Come with me
Ah no, spare me!
I'm begging you!
PLEASE, spare me!
I'm sorry...
WHERE d'ya think you're parking!?
There she goes again... That's long
That's pretty scary
It was terrifying
The Mini Patrol Car speeds off to the next scene
Were they really that fast?
Shall we go to the next place
That was funny
The next stop is an old lady who is popular for her traditional handiwork
After picking themselves back up they head towards the next destination.
Studying Traditional Weaving
I've done this since I was kid so I've gotten pretty used to it...
They admire her handiwork, and the field trip comes to an end...
or was supposed to...
Ahhh, Again?!
Police Grandmas on a stake out
Again?
hey hey Hey HEY!
You never learn!
Our teacher (Fujiwara) said he'd take responsibilty.
But if we don't deal with the younger generation...
please no
Matsumoto trying to escape
Ah! It wasn't you
You, you're perfect. I'm going to teach you a lesson.
I've said it over and over but you never learn
WHERE do you think you're parking?
Look!
Where do you think you're parking?
Isn't that abuse?
That's gross
Think about the rules of the world a little!
You mean you guys?
They had you for a long time didn't they.
Yeah it was pretty long
What are they staring at?
I wonder what they found...
5:30 p.m.
(8 and hours and 30 minutes has past since it started)
5:30 p.m. After returning from the field trip from hell,
the four of them relax in the classroom.
Meanwhile, Endo goes to the bathroom by himself.
Endo going to the bathroom alone.
Atou Kai using the john next to Endo.
Atou Kai (realname Atou Kouichi) is a Japanese Actor who has been in over 45 films, and over 50 telivision shows. He has also written 3 books and been in commercials.
I never thought I'd run into him in a bathroom.
Excuse me,(I'll be leaving first)
Couldn't see that at all.
What happened?
Yeah, what was that all about?
just a little happening.
Something you weren't expecting?
Nope, NOT expecting that
Definitely was NOT what I thought would happen
6:00 p.m.
(9 hours since it started)
6 hour period - Music
6:00 p.m. 9 hours have past since the start of the game.
The next class is music.
During the October 9th, (Sun.) "Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai" broadcast, this scene from the batsu game was not aired. Enjoy!!
Here a VERY famous teacher is about to make his appearance!
This is getting old..
Umm.. Today we're having err a special umm music ummmm
teach-- um professor coming.
Teach--!
"Okuru Kotoba"
"Okuru Kotoba" is like the Japanese version of Good Riddance by Green Day or "Pomp and Circumstances", a standard graduation song.
Hori is a famous comedian known for his impersonations, there is even a type of impersonation named after him called "Horineta" because of his "things they would never say" impersonation skits.
Right now he is impersonating Kinpachi sensei, who was portrayed by the singer and actor Tesuya Takeda, who also wrote and performed the song "Okuru Kotoba" when he was in the band Kai'en-tai.
Kinpachi Sensei
(Hori)
"The words I send to you"
"As you go away into the light and shadows"
"of the town in the gloaming"
Oh! Wrong show?
Well, Good morning!
Hey
Hello
Today I would like to do some impersonations.
Umm. Let's start with Terakado Jimon,
*Terakado Jimon is a famous comedian, also known as Nature Jimon
So Terakado Jimon is surrounded by a bunch of other celebrity judges,
and the Terakado Jimon that hardly ever gets called on...gets called on.
Ooo Ooo Pick me! Pick me!
Yes, Terakado Jimon
Oh. That's nice. Yup yup, umhmm.
Okay let's move on...
Ooo Ooo Pick me! Over Here!
Yes, Terakado Jimon
Oh, very good, that's great, yup yup, umhmm.
Okay, let's go to the next one
Ooo Ooo Pick me! Pick me!
Yes, Terakado Jimon
I also think so, yeah its good. umhmm.
Okay lets try another one
The thing that I ate was pudding...
Cocorico's Tanaka
The thing that I ate was pudding!
Yamasaki Hosei
That really sounded like Yamachan
That didn't sound like me...is this Music Class?
Yeah, this isn't a music class at all!
It's 'cause rythm is very important
Are you ready?
Here I go...
(As Yamasaki) As for me---!
Ah man
Sorry, sorry, lets move on
Okay how about Katsura Koeda from the Tantei Knight Scoop show.
What is this, (I'd like to know)
Okay, what I really want to do today is
"Things they would NEVER say"
So let's do a little bit of those
Okay something I would never say (As Kinpachi Sensei)
Kinpachi-sensei is the story of an 3rd year junior high school class in Japan; its teacher is Kinpachi Sakamoto, played by Tetsuya Takeda.
Okay firstly:
You know what...In this world, if you have money
you can buy anything! Oh yeah!
Secondly:
I never thought that when I got to this age that...
I would be F*#@ing this often.
Definetly wouldn't say that
Tanaka was laughing too
Okay, Thank you.
Let's do another one
Something Enari Kazuki would never say...
*Enari Kazuki is a young actor Born Nov. 9th, 1984.
Take a shower first, then get back to me.
Yeah, he probably wouldn't say that...
What was that (kind of blow) just now?
Did you understand ?
So, thank you.
Thank you, hum.
Bye thank you, bye thank you.
It would be nice if you die, bye bye.
My butt still hurts.
When he says "Ouch, I'm in pain"... well it's normal, but...
But...
HOY ! MATSUMOTO !
Suddenly, a Bosozoku gang burst into the classroom
Seems that you dared to touch my girlfriend.
We will not forgive you for touching Tecchan's girlfriend! We're going to slaughter you!
Wait!
I beg you to not touch them! My precious students!
Who are you!?
I am the head teacher of these students!
What are you saying, shut the fuck up !
I will not forgive those who raise their hands on my students!
And uh...
It really was not the time!
Apologize for your mistake!
This is what a real man should do.
Excuse us!
Why is he laughing!?
I'm tired of this.
Please, be serious a moment!
Don't laugh anymore!
6:30 p.m.
9 Hours and 30 minutes
The long class ends
and the four of them are starting to look tired.
However, behind the scenes...
Hamada arrives on the scene
Hamada finally arrives at the school.
I came to inflict pain
I'll show 'em no mercy
First, he will check out the Operation Headquarters and start directing the action from behind the scenes.
Operation HQ
Naturally, his arrival means that this Batsu game is only going to become more intense!
PuPu-
Didn't that sound like 'Yossha~! (Yes!!)?
Haha, what the hell was I saying?
I just recieved a sort of pep-talk just now
He was telling me, 'hey, don't laugh at stupid things'
Like a "pull it together"?
Yeah, like that.
This one really hurt..
Yeah I said that it had to of
It still hurts, my butt feels like its on fire
Huh? Does this mean...
That 'Downtown's Hamada' arrived?
Isn't just "Hamada" okay?
Do you have to add the "Downtown"?
That was safe!
I bet he's here!
That was even called out,
He's definitely here.
I saw right through it
And his way of beating is here!
He's definitely already here
He must of told them to hit harder
He's started giving directions concerning everything now.
At times like this, he directs like he has more than two hands.
So that means he's on top of everything
Yeah its incredible!
So he's here, finally...
Downtown's Hamada Enters
So he is here!
So he was here
I figured that out right away
So how is it? This time's Batsu game?
Its pretty intense
Yeah, amazing
Its pretty rough, its hard.
What part is rough?
Huh?
That was mean
Sensei, that face looks like a chimpanzee
please stop making it
Endo, You laughed didn't you, just now!
so strict, You're too strict!
Ouch, That one had to hurt
So-- What's rough about it? What parts
Well it started early in the morning and...
Huh?
Come on... I told you
Whaaat?! are you serious?
Strict isn't it
just a second!
I'm going to die if we keep going like this
I said wait
just wait a little...
Sadistic Hamada laughing uncontrollably
Alright, lets change the mood and play a game!
I've had enough games...
I'm good, seriously
No more..
Its a really simple game. Look!
Super Ball
You've done it before, like this...remember?
yeah
Okay come over here
So we just do what you did?
Well, if you don't catch it there is a punishment.
Whaat!?
Only if we don't catch it there's a punishment?
Yes, if you don't catch it there's a punishment.
This is horrible
Try your best!
Lets start with Endo
Right here right?
So that line, got it
What was that?
Ahh this sucks
I couldn't stop laughing even though I was being hit
Isn't there a punishment?
Endo, your punishment, hurry up
That wasn't the punishment?!
No it wasn't.
That was the punishment for laughing
Ehh?! What is this? Why...
Because I said so
where?
Right here
Stand like this, right here
From here on it was hell
The start of a massacre
What's going on
Why are you guys here?
The punishment squad were overwhelmed by Hamada's awe inspiring-ness and came out.
What we didn't laugh
Nobody has laughed
Did you laugh?
I didn't laugh, I didn't laugh
He didn't laugh
This is messed up
Why?!
Even though he's been hit already, Tanaka getting grabbed again
What is that?
They should do their job right
It was all messed up
I wonder who's fault it was
What is this, Jungle Rules?
Yamachan
Yes?
your turn
Okay lets go Yamachan
Ball Catching-FAIL
The slap, after he failed, is fast
It was so sudden...
Endo's Laughing
Yes its too quick
We need some time to prepare ourselves for it
What was that?!
That's strange
He acted like twice was normal
Tanaka, you're up
Tanaka clearly aiming for Hamada
You little.. catch it!
You meant to do that didn't you
He was completely aiming for you just then
were you?
No
Well, if you weren't able to catch it, there's a punishment
You had such a scared look on your face after you didn't catch it
Okey, Matsumoto
Ok
Ball Catching-FAIL
Alright, go to your seats
The 4 of them hurrying to their seats
It seems like Takeda Sensei has something he forgot to do last period so...
Good morning, Hi, How are ya
Hori (Takeda) Sensei appears again
Sorry about this
No no, I'm sorry about making you put up with me over and over
I forgot about something I was supposed to teach you
Yeah, that's right
I had some excercises I was going to have them do
Right right right...
This is what your teacher forgot
I just taught it, "Things they would NEVER say"
And I'll give you another example
Something Beat Takeshi would never say...
Beat Takeshi (Kitano Takeshi) is a famous comedian (also known as one of the comedy Big 3).
Dankan, Thank you!
Dankan is a Japanese stand-up comedian, actor, writer, and filmmaker. He is a member of Office Kitano--which was founded by Beat Takeshi.
I was thinking, "he might say that..."
I thought well he might say that but...
If he did he'd be a fresh new Takeshi
Endo
Huh?
I wonder if it's okay? I think so...Jerk
Okay, Yamasaki
something he wouldn't say?
he would never say...
Dankan, you dirty rat
What was that? He would definitly say that
That hurt, definitely hurt
Okay, Yamasaki
What?!
Yamasaki
Dankan, Good Night
Oh, this is hopeless
"Dankan" gets me everytime
Yeah, Takeshi probably wouldn't of said that...
Ahhouch, Please stop saying Dankan
Okay, Yamasaki
Wha-?!
Me? Shouldn't it be Endo next?
Yamasaki
Dankan, have a croquette
Please stop saying Dankan...
I'm hopeless when it comes to "Dankan"
I can handle anything except "Dankan"
Did you even know what you were going to say?
Have a Croquette
That one hurt didn't it Tanaka
Thank you very much, sensei.
The teacher looks like the original, right?
Did you like this class?
It needs to be fun, right?
"It's time for the library to open."
"Students are free to come and borrow books."
So everyone? How about borrowing books before you go home?
Okay? There are surely books that will interest you.
Let's go.
Do we have to borrow books?
Let's go quickly to the library!
Isn't that thing?
Stay silent in the library.
No speaking
It's a silent library, so don't talk too loud.
Do you understood?
Only one of these cards is a bad card.
Well, take a random one.
Whoever draws the card with the lips receives the punishment
Ready? Go!
Tanaka takes the punishment
Bad luck Tanaka, you drew the card with the lips.
Here is Tanaka's punishment!
THAI KICK
It's getting worse!
It's getting worse! Is that possible?
Tanaka, come over here.
It must be a nightmare!
Shhhhh don't speak!
Tanaka, don't say anything!
Let's go.
Ready? Go!
Matsumoto takes the punishment
For Matsumoto san, it will be...
This !
Tickling Man
They are there!
Please!
It's over~!
What are you laughing at ?
A moth on Tanaka's face...
Good Yama-chan, you accept it like a man!
After the devil like Hamadas time is over, finally a breath of relief..
But then Matsumoto notices something.
Aren't they being soft on Yamasaki? That was so clear.
If it had been me it'd definitely been ~babaan (out).
They are probably in the middle of planning and not watching the monitor.
Ah I see
Hamada probably has them all gathered up
"What should we do?" Kinda planning
Try laughing and you'll see
It's definitely safe
Try laughing
No no it's no use if I do it
If you get ~babaan (called out) I'll look at the situation and laugh
Ah then it can be called even
It's definitely safe
Definitely safe
It's safe it's safe it's safe...Now's your only chance (to laugh freely).
No idea
Why aren't you laughing?   Weren't you going to laugh if someone gets called out?
That was meant for Saki(Yamasaki) only
I meant Yamasakis try only
I thought the same
Maybe Yamasakis CCD is broken or they are being soft on him
Endo try it out
No way
But it's probably the CCD (that's broken).. Maybe
Endo try it.. It's definitely safe, definitely.. I'm confident it's safe.
If it's safe, would you mind switching places with me for the time being?
Ah! Kinda as a reward for taking the risk
That's ok
If it's not safe they are being too soft on Yamasaki
That's right
That's definitely wrong
If this is safe, please switch with me
Sure
They are watching
Getting punished more than ever following Hamadas arrival, finally a break for the four of them
Washing away their exhaustion
But after this, laughter triggering assasins will be appearing one after one. The punishment game is far from over.
You guys noticed directly, "oh he's here"
After your arrival it got a lot stricter and we got beaten harder
After watching this I've realized, we aren't equal at all... As if I'm 4 years younger.. 5 years older sempai.
5 years older sempai
21:00, the five of them start talking about their school years.
The 4 students seem to be in great shape.
You know it's only the female mosquito that bites?
Yes.
I think so.
Our school has many enthusiastic students.
Even this late, they take care of their club.
Huh?
How about see what they do?
Even this late!?
This way.
It smells like curry.
It smells good!
"A sneaky woman"
Sharam Q
Matsumoto pinches his
butt to stop from laughing
Who can resist that!?
Tsuntsuku
It was dangerous!
It's totally him!
This imitation still had an impact on us!
I'm the only one who thinks it's funny!?
It was perfect, he is like him!
And finally, here is the last show.
Come !
Tajima Rapper
(Tajima Yuichi Manager)
"My name is Tajima Yuichi, number one bad boy in Yoshimoto"
"I want you hear my rapping skills which I'm so proud of, LISTEN!"
"Hamada is awesome, he's a great man.
He's the number one handsome guy in this business."
"Even if sometimes it can be ha... harsh."
"His lips are in great shape!"
What does that means?
I don't understand anything!
The robot dance had nothing to do there!
Scary!
So he did it... His Tajima's rap...
This is where the real game starts, isn't it?
This is the first time I've ever been at school this late
That's true
Would you like to return to high school?
High school? Well.. High school was quite fun
High school was really funny
During the 34 years I've lived, 2nd year of high school was the most fun or 2nd most fun year.
Same here
2nd year was fun
Everyone thinks so too?
Yup 2nd
Yea 2nd was fun
You're laughing like normal
I was laughing?
He was laughing normally
Definitely out
You'll get slapped for sure
Recalling nostalgic fun times
A normal overflowing affectionate smile
Amazing
How many friends did you have?
I still meet up with 3 of them
Isn't that too few?
I had a lot
You mean very close?
Aah I understand
Yup close friends. Other than them I had like 20 people around.
20 I can't really believe
I was in the Kendo club, there where a lot of people
That's club members, I mean real friends
But..
Who?
Mochan. Mochan and Sasagish and..
Huh?
Sasagish
Sasagish..
Because you don't know them it somehow becomes funny
That slap hurt
My ass is really starting to hurt
Sasagish and?
Mochan and Sasagish and.. Kuroyanagi
About 8 people
You haven't mentioned all 8 yet
What was your nickname?
Matsun
The whole time?
During high school they used to call me potato
Why the hell?
That's unfair
For real
Why'd they call you that?
My head is uneven
Whoa it really is
My head is really strange
Once during high school there was a time they called me rice cracker
Eh? Because of your skin color?
22:00 A pleasant announcement for the 4 who haven't eaten anything since lunch
You guys are really pathetic. Dinner is ready so get moving to the gym
Dinner
you guys really are pathetic.. Let's go
Smells good
Aaah as expected
You guys line up too
Work hard, you can do it
Ishihara Yujiro and Actors from
Ishihara Agency are serving curried rice for Dinner
So that's how it is
Nakamura   Suga   Yutaro
(Hatomura)   (Daimon)  (Kogure)
"from a Detective Drama"
Captain Kogure and his men
GNT Producers
Seems like he's going to call out to us
Curry suits you, good luck
Next. Good of you for coming.
Why is he talking so arrogantly?
Do you like curry?
Want me to add some of this?
Eat up eat up. You seem to be really energetic. Anyone want some more?
They're staring at us
Daimon is amazing
Peaceful isn't it chief?
Dan-Cho! we have a situation !
What's happened?
What's wrong? A case?... Dan-Cho(Daimon), Hato!
Let's go!
Kogure and his men
rush to the Crime Scene with Haste!!
all right! I'll leave this up to you.
What the hell?
That one seemed to have hurt
Itaos Wife
she's not his wife actually.
She gives off a smell of money
She really does
I wonder why
Like (casino) chips
Smell of (casino) chips right?
She really knows lots of dance styles
What kind of dance is this!? Enough already!
What was that?
That was amazing
Please let it be over
Next time she comes I won't laugh any more for sure
What's up with her repertoire of styles?
They switched the damn song
It hurts too much with these pants!
She is really good at it.
Well done!
What is this sad expression!?
You won.
Stop making that sad face!
Stop making that face!
It's boring...
We understood, you can stop!
Do not suddenly become happy!
It was impressive.
Wait, I can't take it anymore.
Give me a break, I'm in pain!
This woman is incredible.
23:00 14hours into the batsu game. Finally the time for some rest has arrived.
Futons have been prepared so you can get some sleep
Whoa futons
Argh it's hot
It's hot
Finally peace for the four
But, someone is plotting to ruin it
In the planning headquarters sits the Demon leader Hamada ready to torment the four with further traps
I want to torture them with some silly trick
Tonight is crucial
Konya ga Yamada
it showed up
It did
Tonight is crucial
Tonight is crucia~l
he was singing off sync.
they told me that they repeated it like forever.
Tonight is crucia~l
What the hell!?
You don't intend to let us sleep!
Who and who?
Hamada Joins the Bamboo sword Army
Ok, I'll get Endo
way to persistent!
Damn it!
and I thought that I could really sleep...
Anyone would be surprised at that!
what was that?
He Kicked me! seriously. It hurts
Sadistic Hamada couldn't help
but be amused
you went to sleep right after that, Endo
--Yea you did!
I couldn't pick my self up.
you didn't move at all.
you like a dead fish!
Tonight is crucia~l
this was a real torture.
Endo looks nearly dead
--oh yes I was!
Chiaki!(Endo's Wife) I love you!
Chiaki! I love you!
Was it Hamada-san again ?
I think It was me again, I kicked you in the butt
It was...I think...
Sadistic Hamada Again.
it was me
This is so wrong!
They noticed that it was me?
There is no one else around who'd do that
There is no way we can sleep like this!
0:30 15hours have passed
After finally having escaped the evil Hamada and fallen asleep, the four receive a new trial.
Wake up!
Everyone get up!
Actually, in the schools gym, it's said a scary ghost appears
Can you guys check if it's true?
If you do meet the ghost, ask what you as comedians should do from now on
First up is Matsumoto
Alone?
Alone
Yamada Hanako in the toilet
They told me to stay here for a while and I've been here all the time, need anything?
What are you doing here?
It's like they told me to stay here and like stuff. Saying people will be coming for like advise like and stuff like so you should like stay here.. So?
Note: Yes she's really talking in an annoyingly messed up way. Ex. Adding 'um' or 'hm' between every word.
Like wine is good and like Hamada came and like said drink this drink this and like yeh
Like I was told like french wine is good and like ihihihihi
Who are you? Wait a bit
What's this? Then like there aren't enough drinks like
You drink too much
I don't drink too much it's just red wine
Like listen... Like a point or something like that is unimportant
I don't get the point of this
Waah wait someone that big!
Listen!
Aaah no I don't want to hear anymore!
Like red like french wine and like they let me drink it like
Hell has arrived
It'd be better if you slept and drank some water
Like it's not about water it's like having fun with Downtown and like Hamada came
I heard I heard you've already told me about Hamada!
It's enough already spare me!
Ah no more!
Hamada like was here and like.. Listen to me
It's pure hell! The worst! The worst! The worst!
You really better prepare yourself mentally or... Anyway just go
Endo
What? Yes Yes
Oh my, we~lcome
Good morning
Good morning. Like I don't get it either but like I got to drink and some guys would be coming and like
Well for now let's sit down
I like don't really get it but like french wine is good and stuff
You really reek of alcohol
Reek of alcohol like I like think so too ihihihihi
What the hell is this?
I like don't really like get it either but like
Ah Endo has quite an 'ah' atmosphere going on
Excuse me, I'd like to go to the bathroom
Is there a bathroom around here?
The bathroom is right there
Could you call the staff?
Thank you
Thank you. Staff people, I'd like to go to the bathroom
That is.. A ghost, a real ghost
A real ghost
A real ghost?
Scary for real
Endo, Matsumoto! You've said too much. Don't you understand the situation?
Listen, sit! Like french wine is good and stuff like ihihihihi
Something like, something like being here the whole time is like, wrong and like
Big sister, big sister
I'm not big sister
We don't have that kind of relationship
Where?  Excuse me!
Like I was told to be here and like
This is the wrong place
Like this is the right place. Want some wine?
Eh? I don't really need any
Like french wine is good and stuff and like they said they'll bring some but like I think I'm being tricked
This conversations is totally..
It's like not wrong or something. Like french wine is good
Eh stop that
Ouch! I just like hit my head
She's pulling on my leg
That kind of reaction is good
Ah! Wait! Ouch!
Don't need the same reaction twice
That was scary
Yamasaki's face expression is creepy.
This is wrong
Completely wrong
Scary right?
I was really scared
It's time for High Schoolers to sleep
Could you go to sleep?
For how long are you going to stay awake?!
I have no idea what time it is.
We don't even know how many hours have passed since the start.
The 4 do not know what time it is because there is no clock in the class
Can I say something?
If it is past midnight...
... this is my birthday
1:13 am
But I don't even know... If it's my birthday or not.
This is hard.
Happy Birthday.
"Happy Birthday, Matsumoto."
"Hurry to sleep."
This is...
This is crazy!
It was a long time ago that Matsumoto was 42
No, no, no !
"Happy Birthday, Matsumoto."
"Hurry to sleep."
"Matsumoto OUT"
Awesome.
This should not happen often.
07:00 For the tired four the special time is drawing near
Good morning
High Schoolers mornings are early
Endo, get up! Today is your graduation
Your fun school life ends today
Eat breakfast for now
The refreshing air relieves the four from their tension, but at the same time
At headquarters Hamada moves towards the climax. What kind of traps await the four?
The sleeves are a bit short too
like you're supposed to be from a poor family.
That's the kind of look they went for
Ah such a setting
this is second hand.
08:00 Only one event left of the batsu game
Fujiwara dressed as Lum-Chan (an Anime character)
for no reason
It's time for your graduation, let's gather at the gym
Let's go
Even his ass is flabby
His ass is amazing
his ass is huge.
what's up with him?
Let's go
Yes, just graduation left.
look at his ass, I can't tell the ass from the back.
It's hot today!
come on darling! (imitating the Character)
come on darling!
faster darling!
Line up here
Yamasaki, Endo, Tanaka, Matsumoto
I'd like to begin the Hesei 17th(2005) West Kuchibiru High School graduation
the Hesei 17th(2005) West Kuchibiru
Hight School
Graduation ceremony
First of a graduation speech by representative Shoji Tomoharu
Shoji Tomoharu
Comedian, part of the duo ShinagawaShoji
In the world there are, different kinds of pi-po-pa
Pi-po-pa, Pa-pip, Po-pa-pip
He's like Endo when he was young
Ta-ten-pa-pip-pe-pop
Enough already
Sadist Hamada
Whoa it's Hamada again!
You are tottering again.
You look like a radish
I feel like I was smacked with a
thick rope or something?
And now, let's sing the school song together.
How to say... this is...
She is small!
Where is she looking at!?
She doesn't even look at us.
Pull oneself together and let's sing the school song.
Can we stop that ?
She sings playback!
Her hand gestures
were hilarious!
Don't look at her face!
She adds too many emotions on it!
She is incredible !
She is so good!
Yamasaki tries to resist
You are doing great !
Pull oneself together and let's sing the school song.
Proof of having completed necessary studies. Congratulations
Graduation proof, Endo Shozo. Congratulations
Graduation proof, Tanaka Naoki. Congratulations
3rd year, B group, Matsumoto Hitoshi step forward
Graduation proof, Matsumoto Hitoshi. Congratulations
With this the graduation ceremony is over.
Graduates dismissed.
*Music: "Sotsugyou Shashin"
24 hours of reliving their High School days
But they have no good memories to remember...
Only the pain of being smacked by the bamboo sword guys
Tanaka Naoki
Smacked
95 times
Endo Shozo
Smacked
103 times
Yamazaki Hosei
Smacked
103 times
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Smacked
162 times
Your student life ends here.
Be careful when you get home.
Yes.
Thank you so much.
You didn't see it coming, right?
How many times has she danced this time?
She's got us 100%
Yep 100%
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU!?
We are outside!
We already left!
Itao's wife,
it's not even his real wife !
She is not !
For only 5000yen she really works hard
That's not true, how could you know that?
Really 5000!?
She is the MVP!
She was awesome.
In the end did you understand that it was me?
Yes.
During the night Endo getting kicked...
At the end with "the end" title,
we actually ran like 200m
We really ran as fast as possible.
Yes... For Hamada, the batsu game was not finished yet!
Ouch, I'm in pain! It really hurts me!
Hamada chases the 4 runners at full speed until exhaustion.
How much of a super sadist is he?
Because we didn't know what would happen if Hamada caught us.
We ran so far!
We ran so far.
Too bad...
...nothing of it will be on air though.
Huh !?