In tonight's Gaki no Tsukai,
The members will make their ideal robot out of cardboard
using cardboard,
the 5 will make their ideal robot.
License will be the moderators
License will be the moderators.
And Inomoto was meant to start off the program with the 'Title call.'
Inomoto was meant to start with the 'Title Call...'
Okay, we are going to start now.
Ok, let's go.
Let's go.
5 seconds... 4... 3...
That right there,
with that "Stop talking, people" type of tone.
The first annual Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende
Shit, he said it before me!!
Oh shit, I wasn't meant to say it.
I'm meant to...
He said it before me.
And there it is!! God this is annoying!
I'm done, I'm done
See ya later!!
It's because he didn't say anything!!
For some reason, Hamada started off with the Title Call
He didn't say anything!
I can't do this
Because he didn't say anything!
His words are useless
No no...
What the hell do you mean 'his words are useless'
So you're going to hog all the attention, huh?
No no...
It's not like that at all
We don't get any of the good parts...
I always do it,
so it's like a habit, I'm sorry...
You're so happy that we all find this funny, huh?
Why would I??
Just with this, he can afford to eat a lot
My Robot is Number one!
Ultimate Space Robot Fight!
Make your own ideal robot
Using Cardboard
Time available: 1 hour
So
Let us explain the rules
This time, the 5 will use cardboard and have 1 hour
to make their own ideal robot.
They will do everything by themselves
Using various cardboard sizes and other equipment,
they will build and decorate the robot all by themselves.
And at the end, have a Space Robot Fight
Who's Space Robot will be the best!?
Who's robot will be crowned the ultimate robot?
You know, we drew a picture of a robot?
Before building, each drew the robot they planned to build
So we have to create the robot as we drew it?
Well yeah
That's why we drew it...
Can we really make it?
All you did was draw what you wanted to create
I don't get how the drawing is getting you down...
What's wrong?
He's really looking confused...
He was in such a good mood before
No no no, I wasn't in a good mood...
Downtown's
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
DTR-Subs:
Typesetter: Ducktoaster
Proofreader: typesoshee
http://dtr-subs.tumblr.com/
TeamGaki:
Translator: Mickstar
http://www.teamgaki.com/
Make your own ideal robot
In tonight's show, using cardboard
they will create their own ideal robot
and at the end, they will battle their robots
Which Space Robot is the ultimate one!?
Whose robot is the ultimate one?
Building begins!
They go into their own rooms and begin building
4:29 PM - Start
Right then
I'm going to do this!
We haven't got much time!
You're right, time will be tough.
That's true
We only have 1 hour
Did I really draw this illustration?
I haven't a clue where to start...
From the start, Hamada seems confused
From the start
Hamada seems confused
We don't have as much time as I thought
Tanaka is worried about the lack of time
How's it going?
We're coming in...
No, umm...
I've got the image in my head
Ok...
Uhuh..
like really well
But I'm also thinking we don't have much time
I see, only 1 hour...
How to say it...
I don't want to feel it's incomplete
Yeah...
like no matter what
So you're worried about it being incomplete
Yeah...
I really want to avoid that but
At this rate, it will definitely be incomplete
Wait, already?
You already know? It's been 5 minutes...
I know it after 5 minutes...
But it's fine, I'll make it
4:39PM - 10 minutes in
With the limited time they have
Will they be able to make their ideal robot?
Out of the 5, Hosei is the best at creating
Out of the 5, Hosei is the most dextrous.
How confident is he...
Probably, compared to the other guys
I can make a different robot
I see
You're right, he's building really quickly
He's doing it as he speaks to us too
Hang on, what's he doing, what you doing here?
Wow wow...
You do this
make it soft and break the fibres
breaking it in...
Do you have to break it in?
I guess he's thinking about the strength of the materials he's using...
It didn't really do much...
It didn't do much at all...
You did that and put it there?..
But it's getting there...
Yeah, it is getting there...
What kind of robot is he trying to make!?
And Matsumoto...
What kind of robot is he trying to make...
Huh?
Damn, that's big.
It's huge!!
Don't say "it's huge" so loud man...
I haven't got time!!
But if this...
is just the arm, you're in serious trouble
It's not just the arm though, right?
No but seriously... I need an assistant or something...
If things didn't go to plan, I would've probably lived in something like this, huh?
How is Hamada doing?
Now the one we are most curious about, how is Hamada doing?..
We're coming in...
Don't look at him...
We're sorry...
What a psychotic-looking scene.
Shit, shit, shit...
That's a dangerous person...
There's a serious psycho here.
Hamada-san, so how is it all going?
I've done this and not progressed at all since...
You don't know what to do?
It's like a newcomers break time...
I was wondering how I would look in it...
So I got in...
So you've got in and just completely stopped
Yep, exactly...
Like literally, he cannot do anything right now...
This is..
Hamada is stuck
Hamada is already stuck
what will happen now!?
What will happen now?
20 minutes since the start
Unusually, they all have serious faces on...
they are absorbed with their projects
You stop talking... Like you can't keep talking whilst you're doing this...
30 minutes since the start
Everyone...
Yep...
30 minutes has passed
What?
What,
already 30 minutes
We are at the half-way point.
Please do your best
To make their ideal cardboard robots...
they just carry on building...
Will they be able to make their ideal robots?
Will they
be able to
make their ideal robots?
I think it's going well
Oh really?
Amazing
That's awesome
You've only got 20 minutes though, you know?
Yeah, I'm not going to make it, seriously...
I really don't think I will have enough time...
And then...
I wanted a bigger one but...
do it like this and...
Damn that's scary!
Scary!
The face is so scary!
Why? It's not that scary...
10 minutes remain
Only 10 minutes remain
The final push to make their ideal robots...
It's completely different to my idea...
I guess it isn't as easy as I thought it would be.
I think it looks good.
Okay...
Okay okay...
It's good..
Did they make the ultimate robot!?
Some of them are confident, others a bit concerned...
Were they able to make the ultimate robot?
Okay, it's done
Damn, that was hard work though
Time is up!
Great job, guys!
Right then, let's get you all to come out one by one.
Tanaka's robot
step forward
Let's get them now to show us their finished robots!
First up, Tanaka's robot
Tanaka-san's robot: Vehicle Warfare Trans T.
Vehicle Warfare Trans T
What was that?
Trans T?
It's a pretty rubbish name...
The emblem fell off...
The most important part..
Stick it on for me...
It's just hanging on...
It's like a clock on a wall.
Of course it'll fall off then...
But that's an important part of your robot, right?
Yes
I am a Transformer kind of robot, it's in style now. I know, and you probably know this already.
I have four tires so I usually move around as a vehicle
Can transform into a car
and then I transform and become this robot
The biggest thing to note is this steering wheel on my chest...
Oh, so that's a steering wheel huh...
This can rotate
Oh wow
Yeah...
And out of this...
It releases an amazing ultrasonic sound
It's a really nasty ultrasonic sound
Oh, for people?
So it will stop the enemy from being able to move
The ultrasonic sound stops the movements of the enemy
And that's when I get this...
when I've transformed...
And this is...
Oh he didn't accidentally rip it, they break apart.
Yes
This is what you do
Ohh, it becomes your sword?
The steering wheel on the chest becomes a weapon
Yes
Oh but seriously
surely...
Wouldn't it be better to use the ultrasonic thing the whole time?
Yeah...
Because it can get everyone, there's no reason to make it into a sword...
There's no reason for it
It's for close range combat
I'm a close range combat robot
But before you have to go close range...
Why don't you use that radio wave thing...
The radio wave is only used to stop the enemy from moving
And can you see the V on my forehead?
This is a wiper
Oh I see...
No it's not V for victory...
It releases another ultrasonic sound...
Damn you release a lot of ultrasonic sounds...
Right?
The wiper also releases an ultrasonic sound
This is quite an aggressive ultrasonic sound so will just...
and the belt...
can you see the black circle?
This is the horn
and so
when you push this, it will just shoot at the enemy.
The horn stops the enemy's movements
Damn, he loves stopping the enemy's movements.
If he could actually become a car from this, that would be amazing
Yeah, if he actually did it now...
If you started as a car and then transformed into that then it would be amazing
Oh yeah, that would be amazing
Haha, look at him... Won't say a word.
Maybe you can do it if you bend down and stuff...
Yeah, try doing it
I thought you could do it...
Go on, try doing it
I thought you would be able to
I can't see it as a car otherwise
You should be able to transform like...
*pop*
Give us a minute...
The belt made a huge sound
It just suddenly broke
Give us a second...
I think a poo came out...
I honestly thought a poo came out...
Vehicle warfare
Trans T
Can transform into a car
Steering wheel on chest becomes a weapon
Stops movement with ultrasonic sound
Wiper also produces ultrasonic sound
The horn stops the enemy's movements
Vehicle Warfare: Trans T
It stops and defeats the enemy with its ultrasonic sound, a transformer robot!
Hosei's robot
Step forward
Next up is the very confident Hosei's cardboard robot.
And its name is...
Julia, step forward!
Julia
Julia...
Here comes Julia..
Out comes Julia...
This is amazing...
It's a tank robot...
There's a dog behind it as well...
He's brought a dog?
Wait, that's a dog?
I think it is...
It was lying on its face...
Oh I see, it fell over...
I see, it's a dog robot, like in Casshan*.
*Casshan is an anime series created by Tatsunoko Productions in 1973.
Yeah...
That's right.
So this
Julia is REALLY heavy...
Very heavy
It has so much weight
that it loses its energy really quickly.
and if you can all go behind me, there is a SOS...
Oh yeah, it says SOS here...
SOS, yep...
So this
So when it's out of fuel, that starts to flicker
The SOS?
Yes, it flickers a lot and the dog understands that
and the dog will come and help me
And when the dog comes to help me...
The dog robot helps Julia when it runs out of fuel
It gives Julia a hell of a lot of energy
And when it gives me that energy
This is my final secret weapon... You can see it says 'Danger'
From here...
It can give a mega punch
The punch goes downwards...
A mega punch comes out of the chest
That's quite cool...
It's fine it came out but it won't go back in...
Julia's
weapon are these...
The attack?..
Yes...
This is a missile
Oh, it's a missile is it?
It's covered in deadly poisonous lacquer.
lacquer??
It's got lacquer on it?
Has missiles covered in poisonous lacquer
It has lacquer all over it?..
That's not something
A robot...
Please do not kick it, please do not kick his robot.
It's his loving dog after all.
It's my loving dog.
It doesn't look like it's got no stability. What's this thing called by the way?
This is Roberts
So we are Julia Roberts...
If you hadn't told me just now I would have NEVER known
It's a girl, my robot itself is a girl
It's a girl
I don't get why it's a girl...
Yeah, it's a girl
So this is the boob...
Oh that's the boob?
But...
I didn't think this part was so thin...
Oh really?
So my neck right now is just...
Oh this?
I'm actually looking this way...
Oh, are you?
The body is narrow so he can't move very well
So when the robot faces forward, your head faces us?
It's like that magic trick
His body faces one way and his face faces another..
Damn, Julia has it tough
Julia
and Roberts
Has a dog robot come with it
Mega punch from the chest
Has missiles covered in poisonous lacquer
The body is so narrow it can't move very well
Julia Roberts!
Comes with a dog robot who helps the robot out
It defeats the enemies with its missiles covered in poisonous lacquer
Endo's robot
Step forward
Next up is Endo's cardboard robot
He has emphasised one part of the robot
It's a defence robot, Bariaan, step foward!
A defence robot?
Defence robot: Bariaan
So it just defends?..
Maybe so...
What is this...
This is...
Bariaan...
No way it could just be this, surely...
No, I think he is going to break apart and...
Yeah this is where it really starts...
Wow, that's AWESOME!!
Isn't it?!
Hosei-san couldn't hold it back
It just came out!
Is it awesome?
He accidentally blurted 'It's so awesome'...
Is it really?..
Thank you so much
It's just a stalker...
No no, not at all
However you look at it, it's just a normal stalker
No, this is the defence robot, Bariaan.
So you just defend really?
Well I mean I can attack as well obviously
But I focus on the defence more...
Specializes in defence
So really this is all
harder than diamond
so whatever missile comes I can just
The barrier can protect him for any attacks.
The barrier can just do this...
Oh, just defend...
And then I can walk on like this...
And when you think it's okay...
I just pop out
and the attack...
Well obviously you need an attack as well...
Yeah
Man I can totally see inside your barrier
You can totally tell what kind of lifestyle you live...
Like a one room flat...
Your lifestyle is awful
It's literally a one room...
It feels a bit like the entrance to a one-room apartment, but...
What is that, your weapons?
So these are the missiles
Slipper Missiles can be launched
So can I do it once, it's a bit dangerous..
Really?
So when I want to attack
Yeah...
So I am now in defence...
And when I go on offense,
I open up and go BAM!
Your leg...
Endo-san, your leg...
The protection of your leg came flying out...
The protector...
I guess his leg protection can come off...
Yeah, it's like that
Is it okay for it to come off?
Oh wait, what?
So this can't come off?
No, this shouldn't have come off
The protection
for the weakest part of your body, the shin...
You'll get defeated...
You don't want to lose the shin guards...
Defence Robot
Bariaan
Emphasis on defence
Can protect from any attacks
Has Slipper missiles
The robot that focuses on defence, Bariaan
It's got armour harder than diamond and can protect itself from any attacks
Hamada's robot
Step forward
Hamada, who was struggling to make his robot
How did he do in the end?
Hamada-san's robot, Hamajinga Z, step forward!
Hamajinga Z
You're kidding me...
You got to be kidding me
Just from the name, I have no expectations of it..
Something on his right arm keeps moving
Hang on, he's so small!
That's a drill on his arm...
It's a drill?
I think that's the hand
Wait, it's so small
It's so slow!
Hamajinga Z is so slow!
Damn...
It's disgusting!!
What's with the strange balance?
His legs are so stiff that he's so slow!
It's disgusting!
He can't move at all
And he is so small
It looks like Ohyoi-san (NOTE: Ohyoi-san is a nickname for Shunji Fujimura)
It literally is
I'm a very attack-minded robot
An attacking robot.
Yes, this is my drill
Super Attack-focused Robot
Yeah I got that...
What is that horn thing on your head?
This is a rocket
A rocket?
But it will just shoot upwards...
What kind of rocket?
No so anything that comes right above me, I will just shoot it like this...
Equipped with missiles that will shoot enemies that are right above
So he just guesses...
A rough estimate.
He's going to miss a lot...
What is the left hand?
Oh this, is also attack-minded, so it's like
a sword
A sword?!
Isn't that a trowel?
It's very sharp
It can cut anything
Isn't it a cinnamon cookie?
And my legs are
hammers...
He can attack with his legs which are hammers
Oh I see
Oh it's a hammer
Yeah
And that's why he's so slow
And drop kick...
Please do it then, so an enemy has come
Damn, it must be a small enemy
I'm guessing your opponent was someone you could beat up from the start...
And we also have his illustration...
right here and this is how he actually wanted to design it...
Well the illustration itself is awful...
His illustration is worse than the real thing...
What the hell is this, the colours he's chosen really piss me off...
Why does he have white trousers?..
You're right
It shouldn't be white...
I see
It's off balance
The precious missile
If this happens, I can take any enemy diagonally upwards out
You'd adjust the timing
Yeah yeah
It depends on the situation...
But you know, I can't see like any joints...
No joints so hard to move
Yeah, that's true, his arms and everything...
Oh dear...
I may have got it a bit wrong...
This robot is SO weak!
Definitely
Hamajinga Z
Super Attack-focused Robot
Can shoot missiles at enemies directly above it
Legs can be used as hammers
Has no joints so can't move very well
Hamajinga Z!
It's a Super Attack-focused Robot
It has no joints though, so it can't move very well which is its weakness.
After this
Matsumoto's robot steps forward!
Matsumoto's robot is shown!
Matsumoto's robot
step forward
Who's robot is the ultimate robot?
Last up is Matsumoto's cardboard robot
Matsumoto-san's robot, NTV Robot, Holdings... Step forward
NTV Robot: Holdings
If it's a NTV robot, maybe it's huge in size.
Holy crap!
It's huge!
How is it moving?
What is this?!
The movement is so smooth!
Those things aren't straight
The arms...
Oh, those are the arms?
It's amazing right?
Wait, we're not eating cold noodles from that?
The ones that come flowing out?..
Hang on a minute...
Can you tell us a bit about it...
This is absolutely huge, Matsumoto-san
2.5 metres tall
In terms of its size, it's a lot more impressive than the other robots.
It's huge
It has loads of weapons too
I see
For example...
Bowling balls?..
Wow wow wow, that's dangerous
It's so dangerous
So many come out...
Bowling ball bombs as a weapon
It can
really make people feel like they're in danger
It is really dangerous
It's so dangerous...
It will really annoy you too
And also...
I can do this...
What's this
What's that
Something has come out
Some weird thing has come out
These are my kids
They're still infants...
Infants?
They're infants?
He just kicked your infant
So lots
of infants come out
and
and eat into you
The small robots eat into the enemy
So these things are the main robot's kids?
Yes, so even whilst this is all happening
inside...
they're copulating...
Inside?..
They're copulating right now, inside?
Is there a female in there?
Damn, so many are coming out
How many?
How many are there?
And seriously...
So many of its kids coming out...
They'll come out at random times.
They're so many of them
It's amazing
So they're going to eat away at the enemy.
So there's loads of things like that...
Wow wow!
Damn, that was dangerous!
That was so dangerous!
Damn, so fast as well
I also have a lethal weapon...
Oh, this isn't all?
Oh shit, I twisted my ankle...
You twisted your ankle?
His final attack is eyeball bombs
So, does he lose his eyes then?
His eyes...
He had eye balls inside too...
But I can't reach the eye sockets to put them back in...
Oh, that's why you twisted your ankle before...
Because of that...
He jumped...
So you're looking through the hands part?
Yeah...
I can't really see through this V part...
This is meant to be a robot, right?
But you know, it's fine.
NTV Robot
Holdings
2.5 metres tall
Has bowling bombs
Has mini robots who eat into the enemy
His final attack is the eye ball bomb
NTV Robot Holdings.
A giant robot 2.5 meters tall.
He will defeat his enemies with a variety of attacks.
Finally, the time for the battle
Now the time for the battle - Who's robot is the ultimate robot?!
Who's robot is the ultimate robot?
Finally, the time for battle - Who's robot is the ultimate robot?!
And that person will sing the theme song to the fight...
Right then, the robot war, START!
Special Guest
Mizuki Ichiro
We are robots, the ultimate robot
To protect peace, stand up now!
Steering wheel rotating ultra sonic sound - Sonic Crush!
The sad fate of the defence robot... BARIAAN!
His unknown strength is still asleep, the all weather growth robot!
The huge robot that shakes the earth, it's just so big
He wants to protect the smiles of the people, justice flows through his body
He doesn't look good but he is strong, he will hit the crap out of you ZE-!!
Cardboard robot! Cardboard Robot! Start the fight!
Cardboard robot! Cardboard robot! It's a fight
Go!!!!!
Cardboard robot, Cardboard robot, start the fight!
Cardboard robot, cardboard robot, it's a fight!
Go!!!!!
OW!!!