What are we doing today?
Well...
I have some sad news
You see, today...
We have Murakami Shoji's... Not again...
We already had enough of him
We must go outside
It's always on the outside
What are we doing? Today is a...
Geisha (Maiko) Class
Our ratings will slump again!
Tanaka, don't you have a car?
Yes, a Volvo
Can you take us away?
No wonder the Five don't like it
A series of six Murakami Shoji's classrooms has been held so far
Shoji himself divides the schedule on his own
And calls up members to do whatever he wants
And when you have low raitings on top of that
It's just too much
FROM WHICH ANGLE DOES IT LOOK LIKE A WASHING MACHINE!?
I'M ASKING YOU, FROM WHICH ANGLE?
We do it too often
I think we really need to go to Shochiku (Video distribution company)
Taki Akira (Shoji's mentor) wouldn't be pleased
We have no other choice, but to do it
But before that
we have a guest
That's quite rare
We rarely have any guests
That's really seldom
"Toshiaki Karasawa"
That's so dirty...
I'm here to boost the ratings!
He has it, no way
Why do they always have to do it
Why can't he just come in empty-handed?
One has to do it in a midst of our show
Well, I'm sorry to interrupt, but I have to advertise
20th Century Boys from 30 August
The film is being screened to great acclaim!
This is the masterpiece
Please, dear Gaki viewers
Make sure you'll watch it!
See you in theaters!
The budget is 6 billion yen
My character performance alone costs 5,3 billion
Are you for real?
We had no idea
Alright, Karasawa, shall we go?
We're going to meet big brother Shoji
Everyone has to wear it. What's that?
We're doing Maiko
It seems to be a Maiko class
Although, we hate doing it each time, he still calls us
You've come all that way here, so let's go with us
Once you're hooked, this guy will never leave you
And so, Karasawa Toshiaki
was decided to take part in Maiko class!!
You look great
Doesn't he?
He's more determined than I thought
At all...I knew that after all
Our master isn't here yet
A shrine
Look, there's something written
"Gather here for the Maiko class!!"
It's like he wants us to come over
That's true
Shouldn't we have a tatami room?
He can't even organize it!
There's someone on the bike
Greetings!
He's so scary...
I'm scared...
The landlady just asked me to buy some dried tofu
What a coincidence to meet you here!
Good morning!
Good morning
Despite the members' feelings, the one
who dashingly appeared on stage was
Murakami Shoji
Big brother
I don't think Maiko training should be done outside?
You're, this time
your brother
WHO'S A BIG BROTHER HERE!?
I AM YOUR OLDER SISTER!
We see
Because you're Maiko san
You're just incessantly whining
I guess because you're always too much physically in pain?
This time
We're doing Maiko class
We're sorry, sister
This time we have one more student
Is that so?
Karasawa?
Your sister didn't know about this
Thank you so much
Take it
Thank you very much
"Soyo Kaze" (gentle breeze)
Sister's name?
Soyo Kaze?
In order to sell well
I have them named
And in the back
That's great!
That's right
What's that?
Well, that's
"what the hell is this?" That was my chief's advice
You see?
I guess so
Sister, let's work hard today!
Yes. Listen, you
Karasawa works in theaters, right?
That will be quite special
What if a person don't want to do it?
Go home!
GET THE HELL OUT OF PONTOCHO!(geisha district)
"GET OUT OF PONTOCHO!"
Excuse me
I am sorry that Yamasaki san told me to say it
Right? Yama chan
Wait...
Your father was permanently banned from Gion (geisha district)
And you haven't heard anything about it?
He's so incoherent
He pulled maiko's hair
And ran away with Kyoto vegetables
I wonder if his dirty behavior led to him being reported
Usually, maiko have fans with them
We see
A special tool
to make one look sexy
Thank you
You'll be Hamayako
Thank you very much!
You're Enyako
You're Matsuyako
And
And you'll be...
Tayan
No, let's go with Tayako
And also...
Because you're a newcomer
I didn't expect you coming today, so this is the only one left
But that should do well
I really didn't know
Fine? Excuse me, sister?
I don't have anything
What?
I have nothing
Do you want one?
Yes
Follow me
Follow me, I'll give you something
Don't you want it? He wants it!
He gave him a drawer instead of a fan? He definitely made a mistake (sensu tansu sound similar)
He definitely messed it up
It's quite heavy
I think it's a wardrobe
What's that?
Where are the tanks and the drawers like this?
All sorts of things can be stored here
Like this, you see, there's this drawer with two tiers
It's a wardrobe indeed
Maiko's basic skill are precise measurements
Finally, the practice begins in the tatami room
Right now
Don't you think it's a bit to early for a tatami room practice for you?
Matsuyako
What kind of maiko do you want to be?
Well, I want to be a maiko who is loved by everyone
You're wrong!
You want to be a skilled maiko!
I'm sorry
Actually I (washi sounds like I, but means paper)...
Why did you say washi?
I'll act like a head of the company
Okay? Endo
Why Endo? You really need him? Didn't you need Matsuyako?
What is your name? My name is Enyako
Could you fill it up? One moment
Watch carefully!
That's impressive! That's how one shall open a bottle!
This is not a pub
You're really good
The fact that it's done without teaching
Is awesome!
Thank you very much!
Hamada!
Your turn
Do your best!
You're quite a nice girl
Will you fill up my glass?
What the hell is that faltering way of pouring?
But that's such a tiny cup
Chief wants to have a full cup
How can you do it with such faltering before a chief?
What the?
That's
Don't say things like "what the?"
It's a rule
Yamasaki! Yes!
Can you do it? Absolutely!
Alrighty
That's yours
Stand up for a minute
Stand up
There are people who love this kind of thing
Wait a moment...
Do you have more beer?
Come here
Yes
I'm sorry
I'm back
Look
I can't do it. It's way different from others
Today's girl is full of excuses...
If it's hot, it's hot
If it's cold, it's cold
It's hot for African children each year
How many seasonal words
do Japanese people have?
Let's move on
He's done
These days, there are calls for cost reductions
Transporting food is also
maiko's important job
These are food smaples
Here
That's every chief's favorite full-course meal
It's quite simple
It looks like breakfast... Simple?
Can you say that to a dead soldier?
He wouldn't be able to eat it
The distance to the tatami room where the food is served is 20 meters
The first step is to finish off the dish with a deftly arranged salad
Quickly cross the plank
And have a quick bite to eat before getting to the tatami room
Sliding down the slide at the end
And deliver it to the tatami room
The boss is tired from overwork and is hungry
If don't bring it to him soon
He'll look like a demon
Hamayako tries first
Sister and other members are waiting by the table
Ready!
Steady!
Go!
Go for it!
Hamayako, go for it! So fast!
Hurry up!
Bite that bun
Hamayako, you've lost your head...
Should be fine
50 seconds left...
Hamayako!
Hamayako, are you alright?
That's too fucking slippery!
Thank God, I was a spectator
Let's move on
Karayako!
Do your best! Be careful!
You don't do such things in the films
Go over the Shijo Bridge (in Kyoto)!
That's good
Do it carefully!
Karayako, are you fine?
That was awesome!
That was perfect!
You really flew...
My ass hurts...
Sorry for the wait
You passed!
Karayako, you're great!
Compared to you, Hamayako
I'm sorry
Look at you...
With the way you did it, you'll never be invited to the tatami room!
I'm sorry
I will do my best!
Don't bullshit me!
You're punished!
I'll be wearing these
No, no, no
If no one does anything properly, everyone will be held responsible for that
Yes
Next up is
Maiko's evening practice
which only happens if the baggage is hard
We're maiko, which means we are virgins
I'll be the chief
and you guys
will be called from the next room
And you should be able to turn me down
The chief played in many places
Undercover snack bars
Cabaret clubs
The final place is this one
This is the last one
Most certainly if you
answer in a weird way
he'll hold you the other way round
Alright, Matsumoto
Turn me down
Alright
Do your best!
You came, Matsuyako?
Looks like you're used to it
Yes!
Just recently... I see
Yes
Come on, be my woman!
I am very delighted to her that, but
Today...
Fine
That doesn't matter
Yes, but that's too embarrassing
What are talking about?
I'll draw you a towel
Please, stop that!
You can't do that!
I don't want bath towels or anything extra
You're so shit!
I'm sorry!
What was that?
You're doing it in a such usual way...
Sister, what kind of refusal is the best one?
If the president did that, you'd feel sorry for him
Try being a boss
I'll show how it's done
Please!
Excuse me
Sorry for the interruption
Thank you very much
I waited for you
What did you want?
Well, listen
Let's sleep together
Please, stop this!
Wait
I jumped and my ribs came off
You jumped and your ribs?
I have a scratch on my back!
What's with that?
You're lying!
I have a dirty butt
I have a dirty butt!
I don't care
It's true!
My spine is oddly rigid
Please, stop!
The class is coming to an end
With a little break
I heard you don't have to take out this watermelon's seeds
Practice some pouring
Try this one
That's the revenge for what happened earlier
Please, watch out
That was awful
Do you even know how to operate it?
That's my first time
I always poured into the cup like this
It's not always can be like that
Understand?
Not really
Tanaka
Tell him what I want to say
I'm not really sure
You should be flexible, right?
That's right
What was that?
It looked like a cross chop
He made it like a cross chop
Maiko san, what was that?
That was a cross chop
Do you want to leave?
Let's get going
Maiko must get into the tatami room
under all circumstances
How shall I say... In Kyoto
It's quite cold
And summers are hot
Seasons are quite varying there
There are also storms
That's how it is
No matter what happens
You must get to the chief's room
Today, I've set up a storm
Anyone wants to go first?
Ah, right!
Karasawa!
You're a newcomer
Come here
Karayako, good luck
Karayako, do your best!
Karayako newcomer
Why don't two of us have a showdown?
We'll do it together
Let's do it
MAN CATCHING SHOWDOWN!
Okay
Man catching showdown
You can choose one
out of five regulars
Not as girls
But as men
As a man
A girl won't fit for that role
The one with the most applause wins
The one with least loses
The loser has to do this
Starting with
Who thinks that Karayako is handsome?
That's enough
That was okay
Thank you
I don't know how much will applaud
Now
Who think Soyo Kaze is awesome?
I lost
Completely
I really hoped I could go to Thailand after all this blabbing
At least
I was like, can I leave already?
Shall we start the storm?
Yes
You can do it
You know how I risk my life every time I go up to the tatami room?
I will show that
Don't stand in front of that storm
And you won't get hurt
I will show you
the real Maiko Spirit!
Alright!
Start!
He's calling for me!
He's finally here
Give him some more
A bit more
Mum, that's too much shower
Landlord
Is there a roof?
That was really great
I haven't been so wet in ages...
Let's go?
Wait
Wait, there's
the final part
Do be done by our sister
Chief...
Are bonito (fish)
already caught in Tosa Bay?
What was that?