Matsumoto Gets Angry
You know, there are times when I get angry.
A lot.
- Like what?
I was driving. There was this narrow road.
Of course I didn't even want
to go that way, but I had to
An older lady and a kid were walking there.
The kid was dragging a toy behind.
The lady looked at it as if
it was cute or something.
In the middle of the road!
What were they thinking!
- Well, maybe they just didn't notice you.
They didn't notice me at
all! So here's the question.
What would you do, as the
person behind the wheel?
Honk the horn.
- Precisely.
Not too loud.
- That was a good answer!
I did so. I did it as soft as I could.
But you know, horns are always loud.
It's not about how soft you press it.
It's about the length of the honk!
So the lady was eyeing me.
I don't think she had a face like that.
I was like "Give me a break,
this isn't a walkway".
But I'm an adult, I don't get mad over
that like I would have in the past.
I rolled down the window and asked "What?".
The lady screamed "You startled the kid!".
So what happened next?
I was still talking to the lady.
Then, I don't know where the hell he came from, an old man with a huge dog.
"Just because you're a TV personality, you think you can get away with anything?"
As if I did it just because I'm on TV!
Maybe you were following
them and did it on purpose.
So she was saying "You startled the kid!".
But the kid and the big dog were like this.
Not startled in the least.
So, suppose they were, even though
that was so totally not the case.
What is so bad about startling a kid?
Is it wrong to startle a kid?
To raise a kid in this world
without startling is impossible.
To reach adulthood without the sound
of a honking horn is impossible.
Right?
"What am I going to do? What's a horn?"
"What's a horn?"
What if I'm driving, and the driver in front
of me doesn't notice the green light.
"Damn I want to honk the
horn, damn I want to!"
"But what if there's a kid in
that car. I can't startle him!"
I'm picking up a friend.
But he doesn't notice me.
"I should sound the horn. But
wait, maybe there's a kid here!"
"I can't startle a kid, you know!"
It's impossible to live like that!