TEAM Gaki + DTR Subs
presents:
Timing/Typesetting:
Sacro
(TeamGaki)
Translation:
Michael
(TeamGaki)
Oolong
(DTR Subs)
Final checker:
James
(TeamGaki)
Gaki no Tsukai presents
Risk everything on this mouthful for 100,000 Yen
Kiki Mizu Youkan (soft sweet bean jelly)!!
No one has got it in ages...
The prize?
The money, right?
Yamasaki
Matsumoto
Hamada
Endo
Tanaka
Last episode
Miso Soup
Yakiniku sauce
Canned Tuna
Oolong tea
Apple juice
No. No one has got it...
No we haven't won...
Yamasaki
Miso Soup
Matsumoto
Yakiniku sauce
Hamada
Last episode
Canned tuna
Endo
Oolong Tea
Tanaka
Apple juice
Today is the 31st Kiki episode...
Actually, you won once recently, didn't you?
Recently?
Yeah, you got canned tuna!
I remember now
Yeah you did...
Do you feel better?  Getting it all out before going on set?
Do you feel better? Getting it all out before going on set?
There were some rumours, that in the toilet...
Yeah, in the toilet...
Some explosions were heard...
He was properly going at it...
For real..?
If I were an idol (Japanese model), I would have killed myself by now...
Just as we start the episode, you guys to tell everyone about me pooping, something that has nothing to do with the show...
Kiki Mizu Youkan
To pick the correct one whilst eating out of 12 samples
Correct answer - 100,000 YEN Wrong answer - Punishment
You know, to just be bullied...
Kiki Series episode 31
Mizu Youkan
Kiki series, episode 31 will be...
a typical summer delight, mizu youkan
The first to go will be...
Shozo you go.
Eh, we're starting with Shozo again?
I am the youngest, after all...
I want to get to go first for once...
You're the youngest?
Well out of us Gaki guys...
How old are you, youngest one?
The youngest one here is 41 years old...
You're so young!
Here we go, the power of youth!
When was the last time you ate Mizu Youkan?
About year 6? (Aged 11-12) I think...
For real?
You know I am kind of more of a...
SHUT UP!
Answer for Endo
Nodogoshi Raw Mizu Youkan
Taneya
Endo's answer will be the "famous for being easy to swallow"
Taneya's Mizu Youkan
Here I go...
Mizu Youkan...
I know right?
Mizu Youkan and...
Mizu Youkan huh?
Youkan (sweet bean paste) are two different things after all...
Man that's sweet!
Wow, so it's like this?
Are you serious?
It melts so quickly in your mouth
Are you "taming it"?
How is it? Are you "taming it"?
Correct answer is
Nodogoshi Raw
Mizu Youkan
Taneya
I'm going to go for this one...
Currently tasting
Water from bamboo
Mizu Youkan
Wakamatseun Yoshimasa
Famous water from bamboo pipes
Oh no... look at him squinting...
He can't see for shit...
The last time he ate this, I bet he could see clearly then...
Created by Meisu Hyakusen
That's the so called "youngest one"?
As it doesn't smell at all...
and nor did the one before... Here I go...
Oh is that so...
No, this is wrong!
Everyone says that...
You going to do that cliched reaction?
The Mizu Youkan
that I ate is NOT Wakamatsuen Yoshimasa
Everyone usually knows the difference on the first one...
Correct answer is
Nodogoshi Raw
Mizu Youkan
Taneya
Currently tasting
Mizu Youkan
Kapou Shisada
It's NOT the Kappo Shisada Mizu Youkan
We recycle all containers thrown away
Currently tasting
Canned Mizu Youkan
Imuraya
3 cleared out of 12
I'm going to try this Shifukuno Mouth melting Mizu Youkan
Currently tasting
Melt in mouth
Mizu Youkan
Nakajima Taishoudou-san
Melt in mouth Mizu Youkan... Nakajima Taishoudousan
It's the same...
His ability to distinguish is starting to..
It's the first time he's...
He's stuck, isn't he?
The ones I have tasted before were a bit harder in the mouth...
This just melted as soon as it went into my mouth
Maybe he's chosen this one too quickly?
Hang on a second, but you know, this one is...
Is it that similar?
Did you find it?
I think I have met it...
But he did say that when he met Chiaki as well
We did break up after saying that...
He said the same thing about melting in the mouth too...
I remember well he said, "I've found her"
I'm going to go for it
Ugh but this one is just...
If I'm completely wrong, it'll suck so hard...
Here we go
I'm going with this one
Okay
Here we go
The one I ate IS "Shifuku Kuchidoke" toro mizu youkan
Please, come on...
Pathetic...
Just pathetic.
Not even close
Sucks so bad...
Wow, scary...
He's scary...
He's really scary...
This looks bad...
I ought to tame your sense of taste!
Yeah, let him do that...
Yeah you should
Get tamed!
This was the correct one
Can I just try?
Try it...
and if it melts as easily...
What do you think?
I have no idea...
Answer for Hamada
Shifuku Mouth-melting Toro Mizu Youkan
Nakajima Taishoujou
The one chosen for Hamada is the Nakashima Taishoujou...
Shifuku mouth-melting Toro Mizu Youkan
Have I scooped any?
Yes you have...
There's not much weight to the azuki (red bean) after all...
He's put it into his mouth
What an annoying mouth...
This isn't that sweet...
It's very slippy...
Have I scooped any?
Yes you have.
He can't even distinguish weight anymore...
You would think it's easy enough to distinguish...
It's so soft!
It doesn't smell at all, does it?
Have I scooped any?
Yes, for crying out loud!!
Tell him, Endo...
Good going, Endo, youngest one.
Idiot
Correct answer is
Shifuku
Nakashima
They all do taste and feel the same in the mouth...
Oh man I don't know...
Well that's because you haven't tasted any...
If you knew already...
If you already knew, it would be weird...
It would be...
How many times have we done Kiki now?
This is our 31st time...
31 times now...
I can't work with you guys if you're going to be so harsh on me...
Oh man, what should I do..?
Okay, let's go with this one... Kogetsu
Currently tasting
Gokujou Honmizu
Kogetsu
Okay, he took it...
No, this is wrong
It's tough
That was quick...
That was different, huh?
He said it like "This weren't the one"
It wasn't as swe-...
It wasn't this sweet either, the one I tasted...
What did he say?
It didn't have the sweetness...
Like "This weren't the one I had"... (Nagoya dialect)
Are you from Nagoya, sir?
He said, "This weren't the one!"
He's from the mountains of Nagoya...
Oh will you just shut up already!!
The one I ate was NOT Kogetsu Gokujou Honmizu!
The one I had wasn't that sweet...
Oh so that one was too sweet?
It was...
Sweet huh?
and it was harder too
sweet huh...
The one before just slipped down my throat...
He did say it was really slippery...
He did say that
This looks like if you put it in your mouth...
That's good information...
It would melt away...
He said it was too hard too...
Currently tasting
Shifuku
Nakajima
Currently tasting
Shifuku
Nakajima
Yeah
He's picked it up...
The taste is similar, but the sweetness is different
but the one I tried wasn't this sweet
The sweetness... The one over here...
Oh really...
Yes
WHAT THE HELL?!
Tanaka... Tanaka, right?
Look, he's talking to you...
Wait, wait wait...
Tanaka, it's you, I've got nothing to do with it...
Me.... Me?!
Was there such a strong taste of azuki in the one I tried?
He sometimes just locks on people...
yup...
And then comes close...
I'm sure it was more slippery...
and then just went down my throat...
Yeah, see... This one is still here...
See...
So... What are we meant to say..?
I have no idea...
It doesn't affect us...
Oh, so it melts..?
It's still in my mouth...
See, and then at the end, this sweetness comes through, it's definitely not this!
The one I ate was NOT Nakajima Taishoudou's Shifuku!
Not even close...
It was this one...
Hamada-san...
No no no no no no!
Come on!
He said it was definitely different.
He said it totally differently...
Oh man...
It wasn't like this at all!
That was so pathetic...
It was this one!
Unfortunately, it was...
The second one...
The second one you tried!
I thought you would get it since it was the second one you tried...
It's always like this, the one I try tastes different to the original one...
That was really pathetic...
Lame...
He's really angry...
That's good...
Bring the Youkan and come apologize!
Do we need that?
Oh man, this is going to...
Oh my God, are you okay!? Are you okay!?
His asshole came off...
His asshole came off for sure...
For real?!
Yes it was...
It was this one...
This one melts in your mouth instantly, right?
Yeah it does...
Yes...
It didn't melt before...
Let me eat the one I had first...
No seriously, this one melts quicker...
What the hell..?
They're the same...
What THE hell..?
Correct answer for Tanaka
Mizu Youkan
Surugaya
The one chosen for Tanaka is Surugaya's Mizu Youkan
The azuki taste is really strong
The taste of azuki is strong...
You know how everyone has said it melts instantly?
This one doesn't melt instantly...
Oh I see...
You didn't scoop any...
He can't even see and because he didn't scoop any mizu youkan, he just got hit...
Like really hard too...
Correct answer is
Mizu youkan
Surugaya
You all said how it melted instantly...
Yep yep...
It wasn't really like that though...
It was a little tougher and remained in my mouth for a bit longer...
So we chose onethat didn't just melt...
So we chose one that didn't just melt...
That's right, mine was...
a bit tougher and was one
no one has tried yet
I'm going to go for Bunmeido
Go for it...
I want to see the difference...
Currently tasting
Mizu youkan
Bunmeido Tokyo
That's what I want to look at first...
It's so slippery...
Well if you use your common sense, they're all slippery.
That's what mizu youkan is...
I can totally tell!
He can "totally tell"...
You ALWAYS say you can tell...
It's different?
I can tell
The way he said, "I can tell"...
My one didn't melt anywhere near this quickly...
Yes!
The one I ate was NOT Bunmeido's Mizu youkan.
Correct answer is
Mizu youkan
Surugaya
Currently tasting
Mizu youkan
Kihira Main Shop
The one I tasted
He deduces by the "strong taste" and gets the next one right as well...
2 out of 12 Done
Well well well...
It starts here...
The wrong ones will be wrong...
From here onwards...
Souhonke Surugaya mizu youkan...
Currently tasting
Mizu youkan
Surugaya
Currently tasting
Mizu youkan
Surugaya
Surugaya...
Say the name...
He didn't say the name...
It's in his mouth...
Yes...
You can't choose another one now...
Ahhh yeah, I want it (Hoshi= want it) (Oshii= It's close)
You want it?
You mean "it's close" right?
It's close...
What the hell, man?
What do you "want"..?
You're eating it, for crying out loud!!
There wasn't enough sweetness and the azuki taste wasn't...
The one I ate had a stronger taste...
Out of the ones I've tried so far, it was the closest one...
That's not the one you take is it now...
Why are you taking the plate?
It was the closest one so far...
There are still people who did, huh?
31st time we've done this...
31 times...
The one I ate was NOT Souhonke Surugaya's mizu youkan
He didn't have a clue!
You couldn't tell the difference at all!
Pathetic!
It all happened way too quickly!
It was so quick...
Damn, it was that one...
It really hurts by the way...
It does hurt...
It hurts... and it's scary
Poke poke...
That's why gloomy perverts are no good!
That's true
Oh right, he's a gloomy pervert...
He is...
It's really heavy right?
Okay Tanaka-san, take a look at the answer...
It was so quick...
It was this one...
This was the one
You ate the correct one...
I'm sorry...
You ate the correct one, after all...
You know what, I haven't a clue.
He gave up...
He totally gave up...
Let's choose one.
Right...
Let's choose one
Let's go for something...
that's like...
OW OW
Just wait a second, I can't stand here anymore...
I'm so scared I can't stand here anymore...
Correct answer for Yamasaki
Canned Mizu youkan
Imuraya
The one chosen for Yamasaki is one that is famous for its azuki flavour and toughness
What's he doing..?
He's eaten it...
Just look at him...
Do you even want to get it correct?
Give me a second...
What are you doing..?
If this was your first appearance, I would back away...
What is wrong with this guy..?
Seriously...
It's totally different!!
What is different?!
The slipperiness of this spoon and...
Well obviously!!
You can't be comparing them to each other...
Correct answer is
Canned mizu youkan
Imuraya
Like everyone else said, mine doesn't melt in my mouth.
You mean when you put it in your mouth?
When I put it in my mouth, I can tell.
Can I just try this one, one of the ones that melt?
Currently tasting
Shifuku
Nakajima
Can I just try this one, one of the ones that melt?
It's totally different, seriously.
Everyone says that...
No, seriously!
That's what everyone says when they try the first one.
That's true...
It's totally different, I mean...
Hoi hoi hoi hoi...
Jeez... So sad...
If this was your first time, I would back off so far...
You would if it was the first time for sure...
What's wrong with him?
You would...
Even if it wasn't our first time, you would back off...
The one I ate wasNOT Nakajima Taishou's mizu youkan.
The one I ate was NOT Nakajima Taishou's mizu youkan.
Now that's out of the way,  we can narrow it down...
Now that's out of the way, we can narrow it down...
How!?
We still have 11 to go!
You have 11 to go...
You've just started!
Right!!
Oh shut up, will you?!
I'm pretty sure it's Imurayasan
Oh man I'm scared
What are you scared of?
Right, let's go with this one
Shall I try Imurayasan..?
Super...
Super..?
Mizu youkan!
Currently tasting
Mizu youkan
Ryouguchi
I went for the one beside it...
So he tried to trick us into thinking he was going for Imuraya...
I guess there was a reason...
But we aren't bothered if he picks Imuraya or not...
It's not like surprising or anything for us...
It's totally different...
Totally different
The one I ate was NOT Ryouguchi Mizu youkan
It looks like he can clearly distinguish between one another...
I think I will go for Imuraya...
Shall I just go for it...
No no no, we don't care about your preferences...
We don't care...
Just go for whatever makes you happiest...
I'm going to go for it
Okay, YEP!!
Currently tasting
Canned mizu youkan
Imuraya
Currently tasting
Canned mizu youkan
Imuraya
He took it...
He did...
What will Yamasaki's fate be!?
Currently tasting
Canned mizu youkan
Imuraya
Okay, YEP!
Currently tasting
Canned mizu youkan
Imuraya
Currently tasting
Canned mizu youkan
Imuraya
He's touched it...
He did...
That's a scary face he's making...
I wonder what's wrong...
What's with that scary face..?
It's totallydifferent
It's totally different
It's wrong!
The one I ate was NOT Imuraya's mizu youkan.
Are you kidding me..?
This is just...
impossible...
Seriously guys...
You got to be kidding me...
I thought you would...
The sweetness was totally different though...
I'm telling you, it's different to when you eat it at the front..
Here he comes...
That was not it
Here comes the Buddha...
For now, quit being a comedian!
For now...
It hurts...
It really hurts...
I've seen all four of you get hit, what the hell do I do?
But probability-wise, you should get it!
That's right
You know what, I'm going to be a law breaker here...
Seriously, I am...
A law breaker?
I'm going to down all of it in one go...
I don't really get it but fine...
I'm going to leap over this by daringly ignoring the taste
In the name of my gramps!!
Correct answer for Matsumoto
Mizu youkan
Surugaya
The one chosen for Matsumoto was the strong tasting Surugaya's mizu youkan.
So I'm going to just...
What you going to do? What you going to do?
Of course I'm going to eat it, but...
but I'm not going to actually taste it
I'm going with a delinquent approach
He went for it!
He ate it all!
Man that was quick!
I went with a delinquent approach
A delinquent approach...
What the hell does he mean by delinquent?
What does delinquent mean?
We have no idea...
*Nofuuzou is an uncommon term for "rascal"
We have no idea at all...
Correct answer is
Mizu youkan
Surumeya
It was like proper "youkan", I thought I was quite picky with mizu youkans but...
You do eat it the most out of us.
He does indeed.
Out of all of us anyway.
Yeah he probably does...
I think it will be one of the darker ones...
The ones that are closer to youkans, these light ones are definitely wrong.
Right, I'm just going to go for it!!
Of course, please go for it
Please go for it.
By all means
I'm feeling wild!!
The me today is  feeling wild
The me today is feeling wild
Oh just shut up
I don't care about  being nice at all
I don't care about being nice at all
Here I go!
Currently tasting
Canned mizu youkan
Imuraya
That crazy?...
So wild...
It's totally different!
Amazing!
He's different to us...
It's completely different
You're just shouting, that's it!
Just shut up man!
The one I ate was NOT Imuraya's mizu youkan
See?
Amazing, amazing...
That was amazing
Let's just keep going like this
The next dark one is, this one is dark...
Tokyo youkan
Tokyo youkan...
Currently tasting
Mizu youkan
Tokyo
Here I go guys...
I'm going for it
Again!
TOTALLY WRONG
Scary...
He's threatening us
He is...
Why is he threatening us..?
What the hell is this?
You're so bloody loud...
The one I ate was NOT Tokyo youkan
Amazing
But seriously
You're doing well
You're getting it right
He's done two
Right, this one
Currently tasting
Mizu youkan
Ryouguchiya
There he goes
He's gone for it
THIS ONE!!!
You already got it?!
He shouted, "THIS ONE!"
IT'S THIS ONE
This one?
You can't taste any more!
You can't taste it anymore...
Have you got it?
Did you actually get it?
It's this one, this one!
It's this one?
I ate it all...
You did...
Who cares, if that's the one?
It can only be this one...
It can only be this one!
He's so bloody loud...
He's so excited...
You know, I could not go for this one though
Like actually
I think I might not go for this one
I think I will leave it to when we do it as a team..
We won't be doing that...
Will Matsumoto get the 100,000 yen!?
Correct answer is
Mizu youkan
Surugaya
Currently tasting
Mizu youkan
Ryouguchiya
You know what, I'm not going to go for this one...
I'm going to be mature here...
and I'm going to back down here.
I'm actually going to back down and not go for this one.
The one I ate was NOT Ryoguchiya's mizu youkan.
Just a hunch, he got it on a hunch
You got it right on a hunch...
Correct answer is
Mizu youkan
Surugaya
Currently tasting
Mizu youkan
Wakamatsu
He nearly got it wrong, but from there on, went onto get 4 in a row correct.
Currently tasting
Kuda Mizu youkan
Kihira Mizu youkan
The 7-year wait motivates him to get that 100,000 yen!
Currently tasting
Miyakohon
Mizu Youkan
7 out of 12 clear
5 more to go...
Currently tasting
Mizu youkan
Surugaya
Currently tasting
Mizu youkan
Surugaya
Surugaya-san's...
I'm going for Surugaya's...
It's really close...
But no...
It is really close
But you know, I'm not going to
ever get tricked by your poker faces...
I've seen them so many times up until now
Your tricks are just old
Your tricks are old
The one I ate was NOT Surugaya's mizu youkan!
It was this one...
I don't want to get casually just hit...
Here he comes...
Here he is...
It really hurts...
Bite your wife's boob really well!
He is really giving it to him...
Bite it well...
That sounded like it his bone...
And also the back of his thigh...
Right on the back of his thigh...
The really painful part...
That would hurt...
That's a really painful area...
The answer was...
Yeah, let's show him the answer
Yes, let's...
The answer was this one...
You also got caught out by this one...
In the past, I was sure they didn't do this, you know
something so cliche, I really didn't want to believe it...
But it's really starting to make me think that it's true...
They change the products in the back...