1st Time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende
"Which Looks Most Like Hamada!? Hamada Photo Contest!!"
When I entered the studio, without Hamada here it felt so peaceful.
From the moment you enter, you're surrounded by such a gentle atmosphere.
All of the staff are smiling.
I thought it was really nice.
Thank you for mentioning the nice atmosphere during the opening.
This time, we went to a shopping district...
...and anything that looked like Hamada-san, we took a photo of it.
Well everyone, this is Fuzashikōyama Shopping District.
Find Hamada-san and take a photo.
Well then everyone, let's go.
Hamada has taken over the city.
More than you think.
It's a little off.
I'm sure there's one here somewhere.
It's subtle.
I thought I had it there.
Pretty much everything looks like Hamada-san.
Like I thought, looking underfoot is the way to go.
...for Hamada-san.
Ah, a bread shop!
There'll definitely be something here.
It's a little harder than I thought.
I see.
Surely one in there.
Right.
Everyone seems so into this segment.
Ah, how about this?
Eye, eye and nose.
Maybe it looks too much like a monkey?
Ah, you're that drone guy, right?
Drone guy, huh.
The drone comedian, right?
I'm not a drone comedian.
Give it your best, I'll be watching.
What's with the weird behaviour?
I've kinda got this feeling there's something here.
How about this?
The mouth's a little rough.
How about that person over there?
I think it looks more like Hōsei-san.
Staff
You think?
It's all about the lips.
I think getting the mouth is more important than the rest.
If you can clearly see the lips, you'll be able to see Hamada-san.
I think this is...
When he's in Guam, he probably looks something like this.
See the lips here.
This over here.
It's Hamada-san!
The eyebrows, eyes, lips.
Thanks, it's Hamada-san!
Probably, rather than here...
...Hamada-san is more likely to appear in the back alleys.
See, look at this.
Look, look, look
It looks just like him
Look, look, look.
Hamada-san always makes this face.
I bet there's more around here.
It's amazing how many Hamadas there are.
So many Hamadas.
Coming up, we'll see what the six members found, the hidden Hamadas.
Timed & Typeset by elliebeano
Translated by Inepped & Oolong
QC by GakiDave
We're back from the location shoot. What did you think Matsumoto-san?
"There's so many Hamadas in this town."
They were everywhere.
Of course Hamada-san isn't in the studio.
Yeah, he's not here...
But the company has no idea where he is.
No way.
Stop it already.
You're making it sound like a weird situation.
At that time, Hamada...
Good morning.
Can I have a moment?
Today, I'd like to see a bunch of Hamada-san's emotions.
Staff
I want to take pictures of your various emotions.
What?
Hamada-san's spectrum of emotions.
It'll be a location shoot.
Eh, just me?
Yes, let's go right now.
I want to see all of Hamada-san's emotions.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
So everyone...
...we've got a bunch of photos of Hamada-san.
Who wants to start us off?
There's no losing here.
So if you don't mind, have a look at this one.
I think this one looks like Hamada.
Oh, it's Hamada-san!
He looks kind of surprised.
Sort of...
Happy, but also a little bashful Hamada.
Like when he's been complemented.
When a B-class Gravure idol complements him.
I had to be told what Hamada-san's kind face looks like.
He looked like that after the Deluxe episode.
Hamada-san in a bit of a daze.
This is a little tough to see at first, so I also zoomed in.
Ah, I see.
Eyebrow
Eye
Mouth
Is that the mouth?
There's the mouth, the eyes and eyebrows.
He looks a bit like that when he's just woken up.
Can I show something sort of plain?
There's nothing that special about this.
But it's purely Hamada-san.
You see that face all the time.
That is just plain Hamada.
Isn't it super plain?
When he's calling out "Oi, Oi"!
Let's show off the other plain ones.
Ah, plain, plain.
So plain.
There's just so many plain ones.
Here's a plain drain cover.
I've also got another plain one.
I've also got this one.
That's amazing.
There's so many plain things that look like him.
Does this count as plain?
Is this plain?
This is quite good.
It's pretty good.
The plain series has been pretty good.
At that time, Hamada...
After this, you can just take it easy.
Where are we heading right now?
Staff
I've prepared several locations.
Several?!
We'll be going to different places...
...and having fun.
Ah, that's good.
Recently, he's been using an e-cig.
Ah, that's it there?
That's the e-cig.
A bag, huh?
You haven't shown anything yet.
I've got a sort of travel series.
Can I show a vacation pic of Hamada-san?
You've got so many.
Not really.
It's a volleyball, isn't it?
Along with a volleyball...
Playing on the beach.
It's Hamada-san.
There's loads of 'em.
A family of Hamadas!
A family of Hamadas huh?
On vacation in Hawaii.
That's all my travel ones.
Speaking of holidays...
...I've got this.
Hamada-ya (Hamada's Shop)
I just happened to see it.
It's this kind of thing, right?
Yes, well, yes.
Is it time to show off the angry side?
The angry side of Hamada-san.
Oh, he's pretty angry there.
"WHO ARE YOU!!"
"DON'T TAKE A PHOTO!!"
I've seen that so many times.
So, I've got one.
Hamada-san often looks like he doesn't quite understand what you just said.
"Eh?" like that.
This is that Hamada-san.
I see "Eh?"
This is another angry Hamada.
It's Hamada when the unit price hasn't gone up.
When the price is lower than expected.
Continuing with the angry series.
I think this one is pretty angry.
What is that? A crab?
A crab, yeah.
That's pretty scary.
It's taken from the front.
He's like that just before we start filming.
He looks like he's about ready to shout.
I think it's hard to top that one.
Impossible to beat that.
We could go with animals next.
Sometimes he wears that bobbed wig right?
At that time, he looks like this.
I saw someone carrying one of these.
It looks exactly the same.
"Can I take a picture?"
New Year's Eve.
The New Year's Eve Hamada-san.
This is one of the staff but...
Program Director
Fukuda Ryu
There are even Hamadas
among the staff.
Is he sneaking around in here?
He's even found himself...
...as a Japanese national rugby star.
Rugby Japan Representative
Inagaki Keita
That's a good find.
An in-shape Hamada.
"Time to get in shape."
Alright if I go next?
Where is Hamada-san in this photo?
Where is he?
This is pretty hard.
There he is!
There it is.
Ah, I see it now.
That's Hamada-san for sure!
Cute!
Well found.
I was pretty happy finding this.
Hamada, when he's just arrived on set.
Ah, he does look like that.
That's the character for "Tani".
It's Tani, but also Hamada.
Yes, he looks sleepy.
That's odd, it's supposed to be Tani-san.
Yes.
Late at night.
He was being chewed out by Natsumi (Hamada's wife).
Hamada-san on a good day.
That's a good one.
That's so Hamada.
I think this is one when we're greeting each other.
That's good.
Yeah, that's Hamada.
Definitely Hamada-san.
Here's a "surprised" one.
Yeah, there are times when he's like that!
I've got another surprised one.
This one looks super surprised.
That's good.
So surprised.
I've also got a surprised one.
Even if it's a broken item, it can become Hamada.
How's this one?
Ahh, this one is pretty interesting.
It definitely looks like Hamada-san.
At that time, Hamada...
Here we go.
Ow!
Should I play 1-bingo?
Yes, to start with.
7 next.
Eh? I hit it!
Hamada-san when he was young.
This kinda feeling.
I see.
When he was young?
His lips were the main focus.
With that in mind, how about this Hamada?
A young Hamada.
From, "Yojidesuyo~Da"! (An old variety show Downtown hosted in the 80's)
He was super popular back then.
A worn out Hamada-san, like when he's drunk.
That's gross.
What is that?
Gum stuck on the ground.
After that Hamada-san, we have a hungover one.
This is that Hamada-san.
The face, there's the eyes and mouth.
Hamada-san's sleeping and snoring face
A Tree
Speaking of trees...
..."Kekka Happyō no toki" Hamada-san.
"Kekka Happyō no toki" = "It's time for the results"
Hamada shouts this often and has become sort of a catchphrase of his.
There's the mouth...
...and the hair.
I also have a "Kekka Happyō no toki"
What is that!
To begin with, WHAT IS THAT!
Oh, that's funny.
Well, this is sorta like "Kekka Happyō!"
I think I've got some other "Kekka Happyō!"
How about this one
"Kekka Happyō!"
Then, how about this one?
Me too, "Kekka Happyō!"
There's way too many!
This one too,"Kekka Happyō!"
"Kekka Happyō!"
Zaki-san's "Kekka Happyō!"
Zaki-san = Hōsei
What is that! It's GROSS!
That's not a "Kekka Happyō!"
Ugh. Go with the flow!
It's pigeon droppings.
He's gonna be truly mad at you.
He's gonna wanna hit you.
When he watches this, he's gonna come for you!
I've got a couple's photo.
Look at the Hamadas.
They're close, aren't they?
I can see the eyes and nose.
That's amazing.
This one's a part of his body.
Hamada-san's calf.
It's okay to do calf?
Oh, that was his calf!
Calf, do I have something...
Nope.
Could go either way.
He did have something like this.
I think this looks like Hamada close up.
Ah, that's Hamada-san.
What is that?
A chestnut?
A cross section of a chestnut.
At that time, Hamada...
Nice shot!
I wonder if it's alright just doing this.
I see him quite a lot in his private time.
This is Hamada-san playing golf early in the morning.
He looks like that?
What is that?
It's a plug outlet covered up with putty.
Hamada really appears everywhere.
Here's another Hamada.
Oh, you're right.
That's so Hamada.
Is that the backside of a shoe?
If you squish your shoes, it's Hamada.
The face looks similar.
It's scary close to Hamada, right?
He's in a good mood.
If it's a good mood, here's another one.
This is a rare one, you might see it once a year or not.
He's winking.
He had to have two good days in a row or else you wouldn't see this.
This is a truly happy Hamada.
So happy.
He's having a great time.
This is a dead Hamada.
Just the mouth.
He looks this featureless?
This is... Yes, this.
What sort of death causes that?
He passed away peacefully.
Yes, you're right.
I don't get any sense of suffering.
Yes, very peaceful.
The future Hamada.
He's become a robot.
What the future holds.
The future.
There's someone I'd like to introduce you to.
He's a junior but...
...he seems to be imitating Hamada-san a lot
Who is that?
Wes-P.
The one who does the tablecloth skit.
Hamada just shows up everywhere.
He's even appearing among the juniors.
He's infiltrated the juniors.
Hamada seems to have aged a lot recently.
This is the worn out Hamada.
Totally worn out.
He's looked like this since the start of the year.
This one definitely isn't Hamada-san...
...but I found Matsumoto-san.
Maybe a few years ago.
A few years ago.
Before the blonde hair.
We've come to the end.
One more thing?
Should we make this the last one?
This is definitely the most unbelievable one.
*Not Abashiri Prison
Hamada-san was at Abashiri Prison Museum
The real one.
It may have been.
I'm sure this is the real one.
Isn't this close!
He did look like that when he was younger.
Truly young.
The ones that are left aren't that bad.
How about this one?
Me too.
Vegetables? Vegetable series.
I can't decide which one of these is him.
I just couldn't decide.
There's just so many.
This one is him when he's super angry.
This one?
This one's great.
There's also this one...
...and this one.
Those three are great.
At that time, Hamada...
Is that a caffè latte?
That's right.
Are you adding sugar to it?
Of course!
You add it?
It's bitter!
Is it bitter?
Then why have you got ice cream in yours?
That's true, but does a caffè latte really need it?
It does!
We've come to a close.
I would've gone with this one.
Imabari City, Ehime Prefecture mascot
Barii-san
You've left the best 'til last.
I thought it'd be lame to put this down.
This ain't it.
I had a lot that weren't quite right.
I'd like to have another go at this.
If you looked all over Japan, you'd probably find some crazy stuff, right?
With that said, have a look around your town and find the hiding Hamadas.
Whatever it may be, people, things, animals, plants...
...If it looks like Hamada, anything is OK!
Please visit the show's homepage!
That was a good one.
This one is so good.
Couldn't you use this in your home somehow?
If your family was okay with it.
It's like a funeral portrait.