The First Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende Chiki-Chiki
Yamasaki Hosei's Ass Open Sparring
Long time no see, Matsumoto san
Ass Open Sparring
That's correct
To simply put, that's Yamasaki's last chance
Already the last one?
Why's that, let's hear that from the man himself
I see
Right behind us, Yamasaki is standing by
So, why don't we enter
What a cool face
How are you feeling?
You see, I'm very angry today
Angry? Yes, I worked hard
You're a real performer once you do something serious
When you're in an entertainment world, you either win or lose your butt
And in the end, the only way to get to the top is by getting your opponent's butt
Is that so?
Yes. Once I'll get my opponents' butts, I'll win
Sparkling Yamazaki fights to protect his ass, saying that the entertainment industry is an ass whooping contest.
Yamasaki shall take the pants from two sets of five opponents each and keep an eye out for his own ass for as long as he can
So, after all the most important for me so far is to protect my butt
Who's saying that
And win by that
And to fight your best? Yes
Once you'll get opponent's butts, you'll win?
That is so
I see
As a 35 year old
A thir... a twenty nine year old
What was the for?
Matsumoto san, let's start with the first group in this Sparring
You shall keep your pants for as long as possible
And you shall not lose your own
During this time
At any circumstances you should not lose them
Yamasaki, shall we begin?
So, let's start. The first Sparring Group please
Matsumoto san, that's quite a tough-looking group
Will Yamasaki come out alive from this powerful American Football team?
Yamasaki, shall we commence?
Yes, bring it on!
9 seconds and 51
He was outnumbered
So, that's how it went
You should have been more active a bit
They grabbed him so fast in the air
I've been outnumbered and didn't have anywhere to run
You didn't run at all
Thank goodness. Thank goodness?
What was good about that?
So, let's continue. The next Sparring Group, please
What's up with these elderly ladies?
It's getting heated
That's amazing
In this one he may have some chances
In this one he has a considerable advantage
Will he be able to protect himself from these demon women? The Grannies
Hang on!
That was too ferocious
What's with him?
Is he an idiot?
Alright, Yamasaki san
You did it in 19 seconds
So, better than the last one? Thank goodness
But it didn't make to 30 seconds yet
But again you didn't run at all
He can make a gag with these pants
There's something in this
Ah, he did it
What about this time's opponent?
That's quite scary, but it's the last one
A strong champion
Top profile champion
No one decided that person to be a champion
Let's start
Champion's arrival
"Moriman"
Hilarious, that's going to end fast
That's quite an opponent
Will Yamasaki san be able to do it?
This time, being not a sparring, that would be an achievement for Yamasaki to keep his pants this time, so let's look forward to it
He shouldn't be careless
Will he be able to fight back?
Absolute winner of all title matches, Champion Moriman
Let's start
They're kicking
That's bad!
Yamasaki san, do your best now! Yamasaki san!
Yamasaki kun, stand up!
Yamsaki san, stand up!
"Champion Moriman Victory!!"
You were so weak
"Yamasaki lost when he really meant to win"
Yamasaki san, couldn't you have tried more?
Give me one more chance, please
I can't be done like this
This looks really bad, all jokes aside, he'll never be able to win
Maybe he needed some more time? I see
He really has a not so good looking face
Let's start!
At this point you can't tell
Throw him, throw him
Looks good
He's getting captured
"Champion Moriman Victory!!"
Yamasaki san
What's up with you?
No way
Moriman, you're so dimwitted
You're not even funny, you're just so weak!
You're today's opening idiot
The hell you're saying, look at yourself
That wasn't fun at all
I don't understand what you mean by being fun
When Moriman came I always thought how cool she is
She always showed us his bare ass
Your little green pea looks through