TYPESETS & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
Big bro
Oi, Hamada, ya punk
Oh my, Imada! What brings you here?
Why are ya asking, ya know it
- Oh, hello there
I'm here to get my money!
- But I don't have any, you know it
You're always asking me--
- The hell are ya sayin'?!
Quit it
Hands down
Sorry
- Use your mouth to talk
Big bro...
- Have a seat, please
Sorry for that, please take a seat
I know it's hard to say the same thing everytime...
But I don't have the money you want, I'm sorry
Are ya sure about that?
- Yes, I swear
We recently heard that you're
kind of a big deal, huh
What are you talking about, that's stupid
Ahh, you're really getting in trouble, ya know
- Why?
Mr. Hamada...
Japan surely is flourishing, don't ya think?
Answer
- Yes, that's true
Ever rode a shinkansen before?
Yes I did
It's incredible how fast a bunch
of metal scraps can run
That's true...
It can go from Tokyo to Osaka in 2 hours
I took it recently
Ya know it has the
announcement speakers, right?
Right?
- Yes
It said "this train has just passed Shizuoka"
Think of me when I'm being told this...
WHAT SHOULD I DO ABOUT IT?!
THE HELL AM I SUPPOSED OT DO?!
MORE!
- WHAT IS HE SUPPOSED TO DO?!
MORE!!
- WHAT IS HE SUPPOSED TO DO!?!
MORE!!!
-WHAT IS HE SUPPOSED TO DO?!?!
NOW JUST IN YOUR HEAD!!
Answer the phone, please
- Yes
Ah-- yes, please wait a second
Boss, we have a call from Osaka
Yes? Oh, hi, yes, so what's the estimation?
Yeah
15 million? Each? For Hawaii?
That's cheap, but it's still a lot!
Alright, that's it then
Oh, is that so?
Can I take my employees with me?
Yeah I mean...
once a year it's not a big deal, right?
Alright got it, let's stick with that,
thanks for calling
We're going to Hawaii!
Let's go to Hawaii!
We're gonna have a blast!
What should I bring with me?
Hey
You... seem to be enjoying yourself a lot
Yes...
Do you know Sakata the dumb?
Do you know him?
Oh, mr. Sakata? I do...
Looks like he had a little accident, lately
- Oh, I heard that
Gotta be careful, huh?
- True, true
You know, everybody called him dumb for that
They really did
But he said,
"if you're dumb, you can't be a comedian"
Is that so?
"I can act dumb because I'm smart"
I see...
- It's the same in a circus
The clown, you know... the clown
is actually the most skilled member
Ah, is that so...
- He's so good he can act that way
I see, makes sense...
It may be like this...
But THAT GUY IS A REAL IDIOT!
- A REAL IDIOT!
A REAL IDIOT!
A REAL IDIOT!!
- A REAL IDIOT!!
MORE!
- A REAL IDIOT!
MORE!!
- A REAL IDIOT!!
IN DARK DUCKS STYLE!!
- A re～al idiot ♪
I... huh... my head is aching a bit
Can you bring me some medicine?
Sorry, let me take that first
Ouch, it hurts
Of course it happened...
- Maybe this...?
How many pills?
- Two of them
Alright
- Just two
As expected from my big bro
Serves you right!
Let's bounce!
- Yeah!
Welcome back to reality, gramps
TYPESETS & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION