Sho-ta
Sho-ta! Sho-ta.
- Hey, you have to get it together.
(What?)
(What are you doing?)
What are you doing?
A funeral.
You are doing a funeral?
Dead?
Am I dead?
Yes, you are dead. - Really?
It's so boring.
What? - I'm so bored.
Tired? - Bored.
That's the way it has to be.
My condolences.
What are you doing?!
What... - I'm so sorry.
Hey!
Hey! - My mouth was kind of...
I apologize for this.
I spit it... - Hey. - Sorry.
I just felt something was
wrong with my mouth.
Don't do that again! Please excuse him.
Just sit there.
Don't misbehave. I'm very sorry.
Ouch!
Hey!
Hey! - I'm terribly sorry.
What's the matter with you?
I thought I heard you saying
something about snapping...
What? What the hell is that?
Are you nuts? - I'm sorry.
Hey! knock it off!
Obviously, I was wrong.
I apologize. Please continue.
- obviously someone doesn't want me here.
Please. For my son.
That's enough! - Sorry.
Please. - OK.
(what's the matter with you?!)
(Cut it out!)
Look! Baldie!
Baldie!
(OK, OK.)
Say "Baldie!"
(What?) - Say "Baldie!"
Say it.
(No way.)
Just say it.
"Baldie!" - (No!)
Baldie! - (Never!)
Baldie... - Baldie!! - Hey!!
Hey! - You are a baldie.
You baldy priest!
Hey! - Don't you see you are bald?
Hey! This is it! - Sorry.
What are you thinking?
I'm out. - Please stop. - He's bald!
I am sorry. I am.
This is way out of line. - Sorry.
Do you really understand?
- I am terribly sorry.
Please continue. - Please.
Stinking priest! - You stinking priest!!
Hey!
Just knock it off. - Shut up.
I've had it. I'm out. - Please wait!
I'm very sorry.