http://zurui.blogspot.com
Subtitles: Zurui
That's hurts!
Masao-kun
Masao-kun is in trouble, he will soon
be hurt. Hurry "Miracle Ace!"
It's "Miracle Ace", you're bothersome!
Go away!
Just go.
Thank you Mister.
You helped me again
Helped you? It was a coincidence
I usually walk home the other way
Something told me to walk this way
You're always getting bullied huh?
Yes, but I don't know why
There must be something about you that gets you bullied
You think so?
Yeah
Mister?
- What?
I have a favor to ask
Don't get angry, just listen
You're giving off a weird vibe
Promise you won't be mad?
You promise?
Actually, I really wanted you to take off
that paper mask so I can see your face
So what about it?
Thank you
I got something good... something sweet
It's sweet
This here
Choose one
Which do you want?
You can drink that one Mister
Sorry about that
It's Ok
That was mine right?
Yes
Open this
I just cut my nails yesterday
Yeah, this taste better
Ahh, this is good
Mister the last time
I want to be strong like you
It's cold! What are you doing?
I'm sorry
I'm a mess
I wanted to be strong like you
That fine, but I'll get scolded when I get home
I'm sorry
You should be more careful
It could be you are getting bullied because of stuff like this
Really?
- Yeah
I have to dry this
Maybe when you wear this, it makes you stronger
Hmm... maybe
This is what gives you power!
Come at me
Right?
I'll put this back on
I have it on right?
Do you remember just now?
Yes
You remember right?
Come at me again
Somehow something is wrong
I can't really say what's wrong but
It's something... I got to go
What?
Oh, I have to go
Where are you going?
I have to go and get my insurance card
Sorry
OK
Well, see you again
Thanks for everything!
So that's "Miracle Ace", he still has a lot of secrets