Translation/Timing: Dith
Spot Translation: Zurui
www.zurui.blogspot.com
Sensei, this is your line for later.
Sensei, it's "Daigorou".
Please!
And later Daigorou...
Nishikawa-kun listen.
Nishikawa-kun!
Listen Nishikawa-kun, your line is "Chan".
Look at this!
Nishikawa-kun!
Here, read it... Nishikawa-kun!
You're noisy!
I'm so...
Nishikawa-kun knows it, stop being persistent.
OK, let's try it.
You guys, make it look real.
OK let's start!
Thank you for waiting!
OK let's do it!
Scene 32, 1st cut!
Ready?
Start!
Lone Wolf and Cub
Kenichirou~!
Aga so ga!
Ashite ma!
Omae sa!
Cut.
Cut!
Your line...
It's not "Kenichirou".
It's "Daigorou".
That's strange.
Daigorou!
I'm counting on you!
Marry me.
Nishikawa-kun!
What did you say?
"Chan!"
Your line is only "Chan".
It isn't a long line.
"Chan"!
When you hear "Daigoro" you say "Chan!"
Nishikawa-kun.
Chan...
Yes, Chan!
Say it loudly!
It's okay!
Let's be serious now!
Thank you for waiting!
Do it with enthusiasm please!
Scene 32...
Scene 32, 1st cut!
Lone Wolf and Cub
Junpei~!
NABA
AAAA
Naaha
Cut!
Sensei!
Sensei it's "Daigorou!"
It's "Daigorou!"
Can you memorize the line!?
It's not "Junpei".
Congratulations on your marriage.
Never mind her, your line!
Sensei!
It's "Daigorou".
Please!
Please.
Nishikawa-kun!
It's "CHAN!"
You see...
You're overacting!
Don't be a demon!
He spit...
He's just acting!
He spit on the set!
He's trying his best!
Let's start!
OK, Nishikawa-kun...
You have to...
I'm counting on you!
"Chan".
I said it earlier already.
Say it loudly.
Chaaan.
Yes!
See, you can do it.
OK!
Let's continue!
Daigorou it's "Chan!"
You guys are OK!
Get ready!
Let's start!
Scene 32, 1st cut!
Ready?
Start!
Lone Wolf and Cub
Eat
Daigoro's curry!
Get
Chan's
T-shirt!
Cut!
What the hell was that?
Soon after "Daigorou" you say "Chan!"
You say "Daigorou" and then it's "Chan!"
Didn't you listen Nishikawa-kun!?
It's part of his act!
Don't mess up my clothes!
I'm sorry.
That's it for today!
Tomorrow be here at 6am!
Finished for today!
Done for today!
I'm done!
Forget it!