Downtown no
Gottsu ee kanji
Translated by eChie
Song: Kirai Dayo
Performed by: Fairchild
Sung by: YOU
Chotto yakisugita bekon wo
We ate a little overdone bacon
sukoshi karai ne tte tabeta asa
saying it's a bit salty in the morning
Hajimete kenka shita yoru ni
At night we had our first fight
Yabure naka tta ano shashin
The photo I couldn't tear
Dea tta koro no chikoku ha 10 pun
10 minutes late when we first met
Saki ni matteru houga sukida tta
I used to prefer to wait for you
Zenbu oboeteru yo
I remember everything
Omoidaseru
I can recall
Tatta hitotsu no story
The one and only story
Dakedo zenzen kirai daikirai
But I don't like you, I hate you
Wasurenai kedo
Even though I won't forget
Mou kirai daikirai
Yet I don't like you, I hate you
Imaha iranai
I don't need you now
Dakara zenzen kirai daikirai
That's why I don't like you, I hate you
Nakuse nai kedo
Even though I can't lose
Mou kirai daikirai
Yet I don't like you, I hate you
Dare mo iranai
I don't need anyone
Kitto zenzen kirai daikirai
I'm sure I don't like you, I hate you
Mou ikanakucha
I gotta go