The Future Century
Squadron: The Five Rangai!
The manager, He said he'll divorce
his wife and marry me.
Realy? He can?
I didn't much love him at first,
but what he said moved me.
You really need to think this
thing through.
Yes?
Ryoko-chan! Why didn't you come
to the Tokyo Dome?
I was waiting for you all day.
- I did, but when I see you outfit...
Oh, what's wrong with this?
- You guys had a date?
I paid much money for the tickets.
- Hey, this is my apartment!
Shut up!
How about movies then?
- Yes.
If you don't wear this outfit...
- Oh, let's do it now!
Ouch. What?
- He's calling for you.
Please stop!
I said he's calling for you!
Ok, maybe next week.
No! Heeelp!
Stop!
Red Rangai!
Pink Rangai!
Blue Rangai!
Yellow Rangai!
Green Rangai!
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
Ladies got out of here, now!
- Thank you.
Stay right there!
On our spot!
You creeps me out!
You are gruesome!
Ok. Red, Pink, Yellow, Green and Blue.
The colors are good.
No problem with the color this time.
- Thank you very much
You guys are beginning to get it
aren't you?
We're sure you'll be satisfied today.
Well... let's check out you guys
one by one.
You're... able to fight?
Yes.
- You have a hell of a body!
A hell of a body... but, still not right.
You need sleeves.
Oh, do I need those? This isn't right?
- No.
I wonder my being gay got
something to do with this.
Pink, you aren't bad. But  your knickers.
- This is mobile.
But that's not for a hero.
I can climb high.
- I know that.
Hey! Dame.
- What is it?
Can you go around like that ?
How do you fight?
I'm a lady, so if there's a bad guy
I'll pay someone to take  necessary...
Cut the crap.
You are the one who have to fight.
- I'm very sorry.
You! You got  too much attached.
Which are your real name?
What's are you doing with these?
You can't even punch me with this.
- No.
You don't need these.
You know, when I was doing this move
I felt ridiculous myself.
And what's this?
Why suckers?
This is a... Taizo made this... ad lib.
So Taizo make your costumes.
I can't even come up with the words...
You have no intention to fight.
- I was on track team in high school.
I run very fast.
- So?
I thought may be this will make
me run even faster.
Please fight with us.
No I can't.
- Let's fight.
Stop! You idiot!
Wait! Just wait a minute.
Is he capable of fighting?
How about him?
I admit this costume isn't
cut out  for fighting.
My costume lift up my spirit.
- Me too.
Why you are on all fours?
At least I won' get caught up if I run.
You're not making any sense.
That's means no fighting?
- No. You've only got the colors right.
I see you understand about
the colors finally.
You are suppose to be a heroes!
But you were stealing glance at me
for quite a while, Dokuro-san.
That mean I'm OK, right?
I can attract viewers too, right?
I was looking because
your nuts are sticking out!
I can't help it!
It bothers me.
Keep it inside!
No, this is... a kind of
smoke signal... for me.
I think he also have a problem
with his lower body.
I don't see anything wrong with me.
Doesn't the fact you're talking to
me in that posture makes you realize?
If you want to ride me just say it.
You just have too much attached.
But, I mean we are...
- Why are you giving me this?
You don't need that much!
What? You've got something?
No use provoking me.
I'm not gonna fight.
Pink is the closest,
- Really?
You only need to change the knickers
and throw away the lunch box.
So pink is the closest, right?
- Yes, I can tell you that!
You got it?
- Yes.
Thank you very much.
You! You better think really hard
about what a hero is this time.
You are standing now!
I'll excuse myself.
Don't forget what I said.
- I won't. Goodbye.
Thanks. Don't forget it, ok?
- I won't.
Does this still continue?
The Future Century Squadron: The Five Rangai!   To be con't.