My first errand. Summer adventure special.
In the Seto Inland Sea we find the second biggest island next to Awaji island
the first errand will take place on Shōdo island.
The film "Twenty-four eyes" takes place here.
Since they made the film there they've opened up the filmset for tourists to visit.
This will be the goal for the first errand.
It's about a young female teacher and 12 first-year students
and how she reaches the hearts of those students.
The teacher would ride her bicycle all the way round the sea shore and through the town to school on the opposite side.
That the errand would follow a similar objective was conceived by the father.
Kairi
3 years old
With the 3 year old Kairi who can greet people with a confident voice.
He can also hand customers their voucher.
"He can do the errand if it's in the movie set" is what his dad said.
But as expected he can't go by bicycle.
He still can't ride one.
Since it takes 30 minutes with the bus how would he get there is what the father worried about.
But they found a clue in the movie.
When the teacher hurt herself she returned to the town by boat.
The exact same route as the teacher sailed is open every spring holiday.
The sailing time is merely 10 minutes.
Kairi's first errand will fall on the second week of April on a Thursday.
Wonder if he can do it by himself.
And now finally it's that morning. Kairi's mother will ask him to help out with an errand.
Can you help me with cleaning?
Open the sliding doors.
Before putting him to the task his mother wants to put him a "helping mode" first.
It's not going too well.
Oh, it nice.
Next up wipe the table. Yes, that's it.
You are really helpful.
Is he really helpful? It seems like there is no chance of him going on an errand.
No motivation.
At that time a phone call from the father.
Hello.
I forgot the sales vouchers.
What?
He uses these vouchers to hand out to people.
Kairi, come over here.
Kairi often goes with his father on deliveries so he knows about the blue voucher book.
It was in a very easy place to find.
Where is it?
- Kairi?
- Yup? Yup?
- I have to use it for a delivery.
- Yup.
I will need this when I go to the film set village.
This voucher book is needed for when he goes to the film set village.
- What will you do?
- I will bring it?
Even if he says that his finger is still inside his mouth.
Remember that I made an apron for you.
An apron?
Yeah, I made an apron for you.
When his father makes deliveries he also wears an apron.
I made it for when Kairi goes on deliveries.
He made this apron so that Kairi could look up to his father.
Come here.
Benten Circle. The shop's name is written on it.
- Kairi, can you wear it and drop by?
- Yup.
Okay then. Do your best.
Even though he's supposed to be stoked about the task.
- I will be waiting for you.
- Yup.
Okay.
Not a strong response from him.
I wonder if he will be okay.
It's 700 m. from the house to the boat boarding dock.
He will then deliver the vouchers to his father waiting in the village.
High five!
Is he excited about going now?
High five.
Amazing.
Maybe not after all.
He stopped.
His sister cheered with her support.
She said "do your best!"
Wonder if the feeling reached to him.
He started moving faster.
Remember that the shop is called Benten.
Blue Line!!!
Blue Line?
- Mom, there is a blue line.
- Really?
What?
See! Blue Line has come.
Blue line is the ferry that connects Shōdo island with Takamatsu.
Rather than being excited about helping his father he's excited about seeing the jumbo ferry.
Okay.
Be safe.
Blue Line. Bye bye and I will ride you once again, okay?
He suddenly changed into the usual big brother with a loud voice.
Kairi loves huge things.
Bus.
And of course he also loves busses.
Carp streamers.
They are big. Just like that dog.
What?
Ah, a real one is there.
But it's in a cage.
It's fine. It's fine.
Even if it's that far away.
Ah, he sat down.
He's in trouble.
He can't move.
But at that moment...
An old lady came out and started talking to him.
What's wrong?
A dog.
I hate them.
Do you like dogs?
You don't like them? Want me to walk down the street with you?
Want to go? Okay then, let's go.
Phew, what a help.
Are you okay with dogs?
I hate them.
Oh, so you like cats?
Cats. If only it was a cat.
Bye bye.
Even if it scares him he makes sure to greet it properly.
His mother has made a flag that says: "I will cross".
The boat boarding station is on the other side of the road.
It takes about 10 minutes to the film set village.
The boarding stop is located at
olive beach which is 700 meters broad.
Marine sports in the Seto Inland Sea take place here.
Going left here and he will be at the boarding stop. Seems like he knows the location.
Wait, what's up with his facial expression?
It has departed.
It's departing.
- No way.
- Why?
The boat is leaving.
It was requested to go the film set village.
While it takes 10 minutes each way it takes time for the tourists to board.
So it won't be heading back until after 15 minutes.
I see.
It has departed.
The harshness of the ocean as well as its kindness the 3 year old man who knows this well...
Kairi!
- So cool.
- Cool.
Blue Line!
Just like his father wanted. A confident boy who loves the ocean and its ships.
Shōdo island where both the ocean and the mountains are near
and where the temperature is closer to that of Spain or Italy.
In this island famed for its handmade soy sauce and sōmen noodles
it also produces the most amount of olives in Japan.
This is what charms the tourists who visit the island.
Anpan...
No matter how loud his singing is
it bothers no one.
Is it coming?
It's coming. It's coming.
The boat is coming back.
Welcome back.
Yahoo!
It came, it came!
- What an energetic kid.
- He's great.
Hello.
Amazing kid.
Yes, just as he has been asked to.
Greeting people with a confident voice.
The usual fare is 500 yen.
But if he tells them he wants to go to Benten Circle only for today it will be free to ride.
I wish to go to Benten Circle.
Ah, he said it.
What?
Yes, I understand.
To Benten Circle, please.
I understand.
I came to deliver something.
He was able to say it.
Since there are no other customers he was allowed to sit in the special seats.
How lucky.
Bye bye.
The weather is so fine today and there's no wind.
The small boat is floating on top of the ocean that is clear as a mirror and heads towards the coast.
What an amazing view.
- What a nice expression.
- That's the best.
Within 10 minutes and they can finally see the film set village.
Carry me please.
He is able to properly ask for help.
His height is only 91 cm.
He noticed that he forgot something.
Old man. Thank you very much.
That's right. He forgot to thank him.
Such a good boy.
Thank you.
I crossed.
This is the film set village for "Twenty-Four Eyes".
I came to deliver something.
Hello.
Since he came to deliver something
there won't be any entrance fee.
This is the set that director of the color remake: Asama Yoshitaka used for the film.
I wonder where dad is.
The place that the father is always at is at a restaurant in a gallery called Kinema cuisine.
The father delivers rice and vegetables to this place.
The father is supposedly in
the warehouse furthest away.
The cameraman went on ahead.
Ah, found him.
He knows that Kairi has arrived on the address.
Put his father plans on not coming out until his son calls him in a confident voice.
He's just pretending to be doing something.
He has to say: "This is a delivery".
But he says nothing.
Erika and Minami who always give
him candy are right there.
Not here. He's not here.
Isn't he going to go in?
He wasn't there. I will go over there and see.
- He could've just called for him.
- Yup.
He will look for him elsewhere.
Seems like he knows where else to look.
But this place is instead where the gallery is.
He's looking for his father there.
But his father is always back at that kitchen.
What's that sound?
He's totally not looking for him.
Hey you, what did you come here to do?
Huh? I came here to play.
Oh really?
He forgot.
I will go and see if there are any fish.
He just passed the restaurant again and went straight to check up on his friends.
Ah, he went to look at the fish.
Kobuchan.
Kobuchan?
He calls Asian sheepshead wrasse for kobuchan.
The endearing nickname he uses while feeding them.
What? Kobuchan aren't coming at all. Oh!
What's up?
Kobuchan.
Meanwhile his father who has
nothing better to do but to wait.
Like he is looking for something.
Kobuchan. Oh, it went over there.
The fish just doesn't let him approach them today.
I will also check if dad is there.
He finally remembered.
He has played enough for today.
But he came here because of the errand.
He returned to the restaurant his father is in.
I came to deliver something.
It's for Benten Circle.
He can finally hear Kairi's voice.
Finally.
I came here for a delivery.
Kairi, did you come by yourself?
Yup.
Thank you.
You forgot this thing.
The crucial voucher book.
He's so well raised.
Thank you.
You really helped me out.
Since you did so well.
Why don't you feed the fish?
Feed for the fish.
Hey, the sheepshead wrasse are coming.
How amazing.
It gulped it down.
If you don't feed them then they won't come to you, huh?
Kobuchan.
The unchanging blue-green ocean
and at the foot of the mountain.
There are still 3 years until
Kairi begins elementary school.
I feel so proud.
Yeah, the world of movies.
That's why I felt proud.
- Amazing that a 3 year old kid is riding a boat by himself.
- Yes it is.
And the way he thanked the old man in sunglasses.
And when he was sitting there he expressed such satisfaction.
And somebody in the studio even cried during that scene.
Remembering when I was that age
and trying my best
and when he clearly answered "I came here to play".
When going outside by yourself
for the first time it can be quite scary
and there all these excitements and unknowns.
It made me think of when I was a child.
And this time Sugiyama has also
put her child out on their first errand.
Yes, I did indeed.
How do you feel right now?
I feel nervous and all kinds of weird feelings are mixed in while watching this.
There are worries such as whether they can succeed or not.
Indeed, it's very exciting to watch.
We look forward to see your kids first errand later on.
Sugiyama family's first errand.
Tomiura is located in Chiba prefecture (Town of Minamibōsō).
It's where we can find the father-daughter couple.
The cool daughter who loves her father.
Koiki who is 3 years and 9 months old.
So cute.
Jinsei
The day her little brother - Doushi - was born she turned into a big sister overnight.
"I love my father" is what she's been saying a lot lately.
She will go on an errand for her father.
Those are dad's legs and his hands.
What about a kiss?
Eh?
Won't do it, ha!
What are they doing?
They have a great relationship.
Will you do it?
As the mother told us.
The two of them are always like this.
Rather than father and daughter
they behave like a couple.
How nice.
The house her father grew up in is nearby.
It's a guest house.
Every morning the grandfather gets the fresh fish and prepares them for his customers.
Mom, what can I help you with?
What a good kid.
I will.
Won't you help out with this?
The truth is that since a couple of days they've been training Koiki to help out.
Today she will do whatever they tell her to do.
Alright. I will go now.
Father will go with grandpa to collect the recent catches.
- Take care.
- Off I go.
He always enjoys the bento that his wife makes for lunch.
But this time he has forgotten it on purpose.
Whose this?
An onigiri bento.
Is it dad's?
Koiki immediately noticed it.
That was quick.
Is he still there?
Father, hurry. Hurry.
Hurry out.
Daddy.
Close call.
He barely managed to escape.
He left.
This will be the errand.
He left, Koiki.
What will we do?
She's so dejected.
I can't leave the house because of the electrician coming.
What will they do?
She's spinning.
Where did dad go?
To work.
She knows that he left for the harbor.
Grandfathers boat is waiting 2 km away from their house.
It returns here for lunch.
Can I ask you for help?
For my first errand?
Did she figure out it's for the show?
No no no, that's not it.
Can you go?
Last month everyone in the neighborhood was praising her big brother saying: "Wow, you were able to go on your first errand".
Next up, I (Koiki) will go.
It's a true "first errand" fad.
But there's one puzzling thing
in regards to Koiki's first errand.
Her mother has given her a good luck charm with words of love.
Pipi? (sounds of weeping)
It's because Koiki tends to cry very easily.
As soon as things don't go her way she will start weeping.
That's why her dad and her made their own word.
Koiki, pipi.
I will not cry.
Are you a baby?
I'm not.
I won't cry.
Pipi.
She doesn't want to be called a baby.
She wants to be seen as a big sister.
Yes.
You're a big sister.
What does it say here?
It's the word we use every time you cry.
Pipi, I will not cry.
If you cry just look at this good luck charm, okay?
Just look at this and give it all you got. Can you do it?
All right, stand up. I will put it on you.
She will be fine if she's got this charm.
Can you do it?
I wonder...
Aiming for the coast
her father will return to the harbor around noon for lunch.
I'm off.
Take care.
Today she departed the house without crying all pipi-like.
How remarkable.
Just as she promised her dad who she loves
I won't cry anymore.
Song lyrics: She has started walking with a charm in her chest that her mother put on her...
She uses all her strength to head for the harbor.
She's so strong.
- You are so cute.
- Hello there.
There's no time for the abundance of greetings.
Even though it's a street without a crossing
since she's a big sister she knows how to properly cross a street.
How great.
It's almost lunch. I wonder if the boat is about to return.
Yes, it's over there.
The boat is returning to the harbor.
Thankfully.
Original song:
By Keiko Utoku · Shingo Maekawa
The loving words from the jet of a voice
They've already caught lots of shellfish and have returned to the harbor to deliver them.
I wonder if they can hear her
if she shouts in a loud voice.
A sigh instead.
I wonder if they will come back.
What? She will not shout for them?
What's wrong?
Daddy.
Since her father is completely focused on getting the seashells out he has not noticed the Koiki is there.
I see.
No matter how long she's been standing there she's not shouting out to her dad.
Oh no, is she leaving?
Who are those people out there?
Dad and grandpa.
The cameraman couldn't help himself and spoke to her.
If you shout to them don't you think they will hear you?
She's careful since it's a first.
And she often says "can't do it" and then gives up.
I wonder how it will be today.
Must be a bit embarrassing for her.
Indeed. Indeed.
Nothing came out.
Daddy. Grandpa.
There it is.
Yes, she shouted out to them.
But they can't hear her.
Her voice didn't reach them but she won't quit.
One, two and... Father.
Grandpa.
At 3 years and 9 months
this is the loudest she has ever been in her life.
Koiki.
Her voice reached her father.
Daddy.
Koiki.
They are like lovers.
The affectionate bond between Koiki and her dad.
You forgot your lunch.
I came here to bring it to you.
The voices of the two is flying across the harbor.
O-Onigiri. You forgot it.
Koiki.
Daddy.
Koiki.. the harbor...
What?
Please wait at the harbor.
Understood.
Oh no, tears are starting.
I get it. Of course they would.
Because of how long they spent touchingly shouting at each other she had to wait an extra 12 minutes for them.
- Yup.
- Did you come by yourself? How great.
I came alone.
There's also grandpas lunch.
You also brought mine? Thank you.
Sorry for making you wait grandpa.
Remembering the word pipi she didn't cry even once.
Dad, I love you.
I also love you very much.
There's no room for grandpa in this equation.
- Hey grandpa.
- He looks so lonely.
Because she excelled at this errand the father has thought up the next one.
The filefish and turban shell that we just caught
can you bring them to Genbei?
Koiki responds immediately.
She will have to bring them to the guesthouse at her fathers childhood home called Genbei.
It's true.
See? They are right here.
The filefish that they caught this morning are still alive.
Koiki look.
Looks heavy.
Even turban shell.
It's peeking out.
They caught 3 of each type.
That's quite a heavy load.
I wonder if it will be fine.
- That's heavy.
- Yeah, it will be.
First she will go to the marketplace
and get them to add ice.
The guesthouse Genbei is further away.
What?
Yeah.
Koiki will you use this one?
A secret weapon.
What is a secret weapon?
Father got it from a hardware store just this morning.
For 2950 yen.
With this she can carry anything.
I'm begging you.
I'm heading off.
The father has been planning for this day for a month.
Do your best until you reach Genbei.
Just hoping that this will be a good memory for Koiki.
You two love each other a lot.
I still hold back on my emotions.
Father.
And about the expression of love that cost 2950 yen.
Koiki has taken it to her.
Since it is past noon calm has fallen over the marketplace.
Her fathers senior at his middle school -
Masayoshi - works there.
They've arranged that if she shouts
"Masayoshi" then he will come out.
But she's a bit scared by her fathers senior.
Even though he's a kind person.
Too scary looking.
It might be due to him always talking in a loud voice.
Wonder if Koiki will be alright.
Let's see if she will manage to
call him in a confident voice.
Masayoshi.
She did.
I came on an errand by myself.
An errand? To do what?
Did you come by yourself?
How remarkable you are.
What? He's a very kind person.
Just like her father. Men of the sea
are both strong and kind.
Masayoshi has worked at the fish market for 26 years.
He's working there as a general worker.
There's some tape inside.
Oh, so they prepared some tape for it.
What will you do with it?
This?
To put some ice in it.
Put ice in it. Alright, I will put some in for you.
Since it's after hours for the market
he's been waiting all this time.
Thank you.
This will be enough, right?
Be careful.
He's known her since she was born.
He's so kind.
From just being thought of as a baby
she is now regarded as a big sister.
Thanks to daddy's secret weapon carrying it would be easy-peasy is what they thought but...
it's not that easy either.
Koiki who usually quits right away won't quit today.
She pulls with all her power.
She could've just used the road.
Thanks to pipi she won't cry or give up
cause she is carrying her fathers catch of the day.
She has arrived at the guesthouse Genbei.
The house her father grew up in.
Her dad told her that when she's at the entrance she should yell out: "Mom, please come and help."
Ah, did she arrive?
She noticed her but she has decided not to come out until she is being called.
She's not calling for her mom.
Is she carrying it alone?
She intends to bring it in all by herself.
That's quite impressive.
She has made sure to open the doors wide open
but it's still heavy from all the ice.
She can't get it over the last 10 cm of the last step.
Even though she could've gotten her mother to help.
She's great.
But she wants to do it by herself until the last step.
How remarkable.
She can't quit now that she brought it all by herself.
Properly closing the screen doors.
She's excellent.
And with this the errand is done.
Splendid.
I brought it.
Yes.
I brought it with me mommy.
Thank you very much.
Turns out she's actually a really strong-willed kid.
This is the first time her mother has seen Koiki's face so full of confidence.
Welcome home.
I'm back.
Thanks to the ice they managed to create an extremely fresh dish.
Daddy, I'm home.
She's enjoying it with such a prideful face.
It's delicious.
How is it?
Is it delicious?
Koiki, who will you marry?
Daddy.
That's what she always says.
How wonderful.
This was truly a wonderful errand.
It was truly an adorable dad and daughter couple and you seemed really touched when they called each other.
It was like a trendy drama.
They went "Koiki" and "daddy".
There's no room for grandpa in this duo.
He seemed so dejected.
He just wants to eat with the other two.
His face told the entire tale.
- Imagine that dad on her wedding day.
- Yeah, he will be crying big time.
- He will watch this video on that day.
- No doubt.
- And you have a huge family, right?
- Yes, I have 6 children.
The youngest one is 4 years old.
But I've never put anyone out on an errand. So I'm amazed by how well raised the kids here are.
Yeah, the parents must train them well for this.
With Koiki I thought it was amazing how she brought the luggage in herself.
Her parents have clearly told her
"if you open something then close it."
and she did close it but there
was still a small crack left, right?
I think that was so cute.
In the vicinity of Sumida river we find high-rise buildings erected in the heart of Tokyo.
And as you enter the shopping street it starts smelling of Monjayaki like a true Edo part of town.
The father brought a house in this desirable building before marrying.
Then he fulfilled his dream.
The one who was born here is Ryuta.
A stylish kid who will only wear the fanciest shoes.
Looking good is a recent interest of his.
He does look stylish
Today at Ryu's house a friend has come to play.
Soichiro who lives in a similar apartment.
His favorite food is fatty tuna, herring roe and mitarashi rice balls.
His mother is born in Tsukijima (the famous fish market).
Ryu who gets things done and Sou who is more prudent.
They are like axel and break so their mothers thought of an errand they could both go on.
But they live right next to the famous monjayaki street of Tsukushima.
Everything can be found here.
So they will be requested by Sou's grandma in Tsukiji.
- It's a-chan so please sit here.
- Who is a-chan?
My grandmother.
That's nice. Is her house near?
Tsukiji.
Is that so?
Crossing the Tsukuda bridge they will go to grandmas house to get some fish.
Back over the bridge to get diapers for little brother.
And then getting yoghurt from the supermarket.
So difficult.
Ryu is the one wearing the strong yellow and the other one is Sou.
Which way?
The one who knows the way to Tsukiji is Sou.
and the one who knows the way to the drug store is Ryu.
Since they are going together they share the responsibility.
To keep them from fighting the mothers made sure to only give them one bag that they have to share.
Ah, I found a camera.
The one who noticed is Sou.
Please don't look at them.
- This is bad.
- Don't say a thing.
I found yet another camera.
This is bad. We can't film like this.
But it's fine. In those situations...
Good day.
What's this?
This is for measuring electricity.
They immediately lost interest.
Look at our matching rubber boots.
Proud of being stylish.
Since I lent them to Ryuta.
Even if they have noticed the cameras they aren't aware that they are being filmed.
They are only focused on one thing.
Prior experiments with this filming style has taught us that it's possible to get away with until they are about 5 years and 3 months old.
Errand. Errand. It's fun.
Since it's fun then it's fun.
Ah, another camera.
God day.
Even if they see it no worries.
Also measuring the electricity.
Ah, there too. An there too!
For real.
No matter how well hidden the boys spot them easily.
Many over there.
Are you counting them?
Getting peckish.
Finally something new.
Let's have a drink.
Nice idea.
Since they are good friends they share water bottle.
They are thirsty from all the talking.
You drink so gracefully.
Let's see a point from the cameramens guide.
"If they are asked then they should ask a new question."
What are you doing?
Work.
What kind of work?
What are you two up to?
We are...
Errand.
The topic changed.
Going on an errand by ourselves.
The two of us.
Because we were asked to do it.
I see.
Bye bye.
It smells good here.
Doesn't it?
They've reached this far without fighting.
They have neared Kachidoki bridge which is near their grandmothers house.
Both are born between January and April 1st.
They often fight about who is in the wrong and pass the blame to each other.
But when they turned 4 they suddenly stopped fighting.
They have found a way to reconcile and become good friends.
That's a good thing.
Grandmas house is just around the corner.
Does this happen in real life?
Who is at fault?
Are they okay?
Let's watch it again.
Does this happen in real life?
Oh no, will they fight?
Equally to blame.
I have to apologize.
I'm sorry.
It's alright.
Let's go?
Hurt, didn't it?
So this is how they've avoided fighting.
Here? Is it much further?
Stop!
Here?
Arrival at grandmas house.
She lives on the first floor so they need to hit the doorbell.
Grandma, I came all by myself.
But they both came.
I see, So.
I came with my friend.
He let his friend go first.
"Please go first."
And he heads straight for the house altar.
Ryu is well-brought up. When visiting a house he prays at their altar. I'm sure his friends' ancestors will be pleased.
The sounds are a bit odd.
The other way.
Ah, he's using the wrong end.
The grandmother starts to pack
the best parts of the fish that she has.
This fish is definitely delicious.
Lend me this.
It's Ryu's camera.
Go ahead.
They need a picture to prove that they did the errand.
Ryu took it for them.
This picture will prove it.
He's making a face.
We've walked so much already.
That's right.
I'm getting kind of tired.
Tired? There's still more to go.
Both the drug store and supermarket are waiting.
I see.
Let's buy some juice.
Ryu who acts on his impulses.
We'll use up all our money.
That's no good. Let's go.
Exactly.
Let's go play in the park.
Ryu again.
Let's go to the park.
No thanks.
We can't.
Aw, shucks.
Yes we can.
We can't.
We will be scolded by our mothers.
You will be scolded.
The prudent Sou puts a stop to it.
Let's go next time.
Will they fight each other?
Will they?
Let's go to the park.
No thanks. We can't.
Aw, shucks.
We can't.
Yes we can.
We will be scolded by our mothers.
The prudent Sou puts a stop to it.
Let's go next time.
Will they fight each other?
Will they?
Swing swing goes the swing
This is what they've started doing to avoid fights.
This is Kachidoki bridge.
Ka●chi●do●ki bridge is what it says.
So he can read?
This isn't the route their mothers suggested but it's even faster.
They just have to cross the bridge and head for Tsukishima.
Let's take a commemorative photograph.
Now they can remember walking back on Kachidoki bridge.
What an amazing scenery.
Will they remember the trip by this?
Crossing the bridge is a first for both of them
and yet they didn't take a picture of the bridge.
We've crossed it.
Let's take another picture.
Exactly. Take a picture of the plaque. However...
They can't read kanji yet.
I don't understand it.
Then it's better not to take a picture.
They won't take a picture since they can't read the sign.
They don't understand it.
They've returned to the monjayaki street of Tsukishima.
It might be sold out.
They are heading for the drugs store a block from Ryu's house.
Ryuta?
Yes?
Is our house this way?
See? We've reached our house.
We have.
But which direction should they go from here?
Where is Papasu?
Let's find someone so ask.
They asked the cameraman who has been stationed in front of their apartment.
This shop has been here in 60 years.
Papasu.
Papasu on the other hand is a new shop.
It's the other way.
The old lady knew.
Over there.
We are on an errand.
It's this way.
The old lady knows both the old and new shops.
Ah, Papasu is this way.
It's over there so you have to cross at the crossing.
We can do it.
Papasu.
You can? It's just over there.
Take care.
We can do it.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Helpful instructions.
She swiftly went back.
Let's hurry.
This way.
They are bying diapers for their little brothers.
Medium for Sou and Big size for Ryu.
We want M, right?
I want M.
Let's go with M.
He's following Ryu's lead.
Where are there more diapers?
He's never had to purchase diapers before.
M? L?
Which one was it?
The big ones?
I was told to get the big ones.
That would be Big.
Big?
Ah! It's Big.
It's Big. That was a bit hard.
Errand                        errand                        how jolly
They didn't fight even once so far.
Only yoghurt is remaining.
What are we getting?
The yoghurt they want is placed on a high shelf.
Can we grab it?
Ryu is 105 cm tall.
Go.
Be careful.
Can't reach it.
I will grab it.
Sou is 5 cm shorter at a mere 100 cm.
Can't reach.
Ryu steps up to the challenge. The two have learned to help each other out.
This is amazing!
What an amazing feeling.
We better hurry. Our mothers are waiting for us.
Mother.
Yep.
We walked a lot.
I'm exhausted.
Crossing both Tsukuda and Kachidoki bridge.
They've really made the rounds.
See. We've come to my house.
We really have.
Welcome back.
Ah, there's a camera over there.
Oh no.
Ryu immediately finds the cameras.
Why are there cameras?
The electricity company.
Electricity? Are they getting any reception?
That's right. Radio waves.
8 years later...
The two are walking down Kachidoki bridge again.
They are first year students in middle school.
They go to different schools so even if they live close they don't have many opportunities to meet.
Let's take a picture.
Take a picture.
Taking a picture this time?
Wonder if they can read the sign this time.
Which side should I stand on?
Ryuta has grown the most.
He has grown to 172 cm.
Souichirou might start growing from here on.
They've become like a comedic duo.
I can't get your face in frame.
Again? You can't tell where they are in this picture.
Since they are in Tsukishima they might as well eat some monjyayaki.
Can you make it?
I can do it.
Since this is the home town of Ryuta.
He prefers to do it himself.
Ooops, I spilled it.
Spilled it.
He can't do it.
You gotta use oil first.
Yep, oil first.
You have no clue how to do it.
Eh? He's pouring it from above?
And then chop up the ingredients.
This is how it should be done.
Create a ring and pour the soup in.
Pour it all in.
This is how we always do it.
How annoying.
We need to reinforce the ring first.
I see. Have to wait for the ring to absorb the liquid.
It needs more time. It's still too soft.
Starting to look good.
What school club are you in?
Art.
The club with the least amount of days.
While it's with fewer days here is Ryuta painting.
He loves mountains and sceneries.
What about Souichiro?
From the age of 4 he's been going with his family every season. He's been excelling through even the harder trails.
Little brother.
The ski club has even fewer days.
They've both selected the club with the least amount of days.
How is the taste of Tsukishima, Souichiro from Tsukiji?
Hot.
Nice. Well said.
Cameraman: Are you giving it to me?
Thank you for everything you have done.
As a thanks to the cameraman for taking a picture of the two on Kachidoki bridge.
In this one it is clear where they are.
What a nice errand.
Right?
They've grown so fast.
At that age I thought the two would fight. But they didn't.
It was a nice relationship.
I got so nervous when they found the cameras.
Since they are kids they directly point it out.
If it was an adult they would behave since it's for TV.
And the lie about measuring electricity.
And the cameraman just ignored them.
Can't believe such a simple trick worked.
Simply crossing a bridge can be a huge adventure for a child. Do any of you have experience with that?
My fathers parents live in Miyagi so in elementary school I would go there every summer.
I would go on adventure in the mountains by myself.
And they would tell me to only go exactly this far in.
Every year I would go further across the boundary.
That's what it made me think of.
It's like Stand By Me taking place in Miyagi prefecture.
Next errand, a girl who like her father is a bit ditzy and forgetful.
Seto Inland Sea is a town called Niochou.
Beautiful.
Here they still make salt in the traditional way.
Especially the fairytale-like scenery of Chichibuga seashore.
Ah, beautiful.
This place is currently very popular among young people.
It's very popular for snapping Instagram photos.
Take a look at this.
Amazing.
At that place a father and daughter are taking pictures.
Her posture is like a model.
Actually, her father is a pro cameraman.
Say cheese.
This is An who will go on an errand. She is 4 years and 1 month old and has a younger brother who is 2.
Her father is bringing her up in his own home town.
This old part of town remains like a time capsule.
They purchased an old Japanese home 3 years ago and turned it into an office.
They hope to establish a business of long standing.
This neighborhood used to be sprawling as a shopping district.
While the times have changed what remains the same is the shrine that stands strong.
It goes back to the Edo period and has continued throughout Meiji until now.
This is a pamphlet with pictures the father has taken.
The handmade bread of the old baker lady or a diner. It's full of great information.
He is now gathering information for a new edition.
He's the type who becomes oblivious of their surroundings when focused.
He also forgets a lot.
An watches her father and his hard labor.
As the gets home that day she immediately...
Father is at work.
Again with this.
She found something.
He forgot this.
It's his water bottle.
For real.
Father is such a forgetful guy.
He is.
And then...
The phone. It's dad.
Hello.
I forgot my water bottle.
An, can't you bring it?
Okay.
Yes.
Can you do it?
And furthermore...
I also need a cream puff for work reasons.
I will purchase a cream puff for you.
Could you?
It's located next to the town shrine.
It's mainly a place for traditional Japanese confectionary.
The third generation owner has started selling cream puffs with a luxury sugar called Sanuki sanbon.
It's a very popular item.
Amazing. Amazing.
Also at Nori's place buy a trash bag
since I have to clean up around here.
Yep.
Along with her small good luck charm.
She first has to walk 20 meters.
This is the soy sauce makers house.
In old times they used to make soy sauce here but now they just sell it.
They also sell trash bags.
The cream puffs are sold next to the shrine.
All in all 450 meters.
It's a neighorhood errand.
Take care.
I will head off.
In her hands is her dads free pamphlet along with an empty box to put purchased items in.
Hard to carry.
Instead of a shopping bag.
The mother is wondering if she will
be fine since An takes after her father.
Oh, she's looking at the pahmplet.
Cream puffs for dad.
Cream puffs.
That's right. But before that she has to purchase the trash bags.
However, she just passed it.
I will be late if I don't hurry.
For the cream puffs, right?
Wait. Why did she turn?
A building has popped up on this otherwise plain parking lot.
This is a brand new specialty show for handmade cakes.
Two cream puffs, please.
One cream puff?
They usually make round birthday cakes upon request.
They don't even have a display counter.
Two cream puffs? One?
They also make cream puffs here?
They will take her order since she's come all the way.
It will take a little while. Is that okay?
Yep, that's fine.
Okay.
Please come again.
She has made an order.
But she wasn't asked to purchase cream puffs from here.
After ordering the cream puffs she suddenly remembers to trash bags.
He even mentioned the day before
that he intends to clean up his office.
The shop owners are way back in the home part of the building.
Can she say "trash bags, please" in a loud voice?
Cardboard box, please.
She wasn't asked to get a cardboard box at all.
What are you looking for?
A cardboard box.
A cardboard box? Is that what you are looking for?
Not vinegar? Did they really ask you to get a cardboard box?
Really? A cardboard box.
There are lots of cardboard boxes but...
If it's a cardboard box how about this one?
She found an empty box that had
soy sauce in it. She will give it for free.
Can you take it?
Are you doing an errand for your father?
Looks heavy.
Smart kid.
I will go to my dad's place.
You are heading there now?
Thank you.
There's no trash can in the office.
For this old district this might be a better way to throw things out in.
She's tottering along.
But it's light.
She put it down? Is she taking a break?
Right, left. All clear, I can continue.
Remarkable.
Her father has taught her how to be safe in traffic.
Head straight through the crossroad.
He's carrying a lot.
Wait, she turned left?
Heading for dads job.
The staff who were on the right route have to catch up to her.
Since she didn't head for the right shop this way is actually faster.
There are so many narrow streets around here.
Papa.
Yes? Oh.
They will be making the cream puffs now.
Making them now?
The heck?
Can I use this as a trash bag?
Yep. Will this do?
It will.
This will do.
I can use this. Thanks.
And I brought your water bottle.
The thing her father forgot.
This is amazing. You did it all by yourself?
Yep.
But An...
It shouldn't be the case that they haven't made cream puffs.
Do you see this, An?
I do.
A picture of the shop.
Will you?
I will go and purchase cream puffs.
Please and thank you.
Take care.
She has seen the front of the building this time.
I wonder if she will be fine.
She's looking at the pamphlet and comparing it.
The Japanese confectionary shop.
The shop is here if she turns.
However she went straight.
- Made to run.
- The adults are.
Rather than shooting they are running more.
So fast.
They must also be heading for that famous shop.
They can't keep up.
Cream puffs. Cream puffs. Cream puffs.
She's been out for less than 10 minutes.
"She's already back" the shop owner must be wondering.
Cream puffs please.
They haven't baked yet.
I see.
It will take a bit longer. Please come again.
I will be back later.
Despite having seen the picture of the correct shop.
She didn't notice that this is a different shop?
She runs so much.
She's going back to her fathers place.
And the staff is trying to reach the office first.
How rough.
She went straight ahead?
Better visit the shrine.
The shrine?
Everyone is competing against An.
So many are coming out.
The shrine.
Why all of a sudden.
When out for walks with her mother she always visits this shrine.
These rocks are called Shimeishi and can be found in the ocean.
They've been here since over 100 years ago.
Jingle jangle, she's rich.
How many yen will she put out?
She's not putting anything in?
I have no clue.
A shame.
She's already leaving?
She didn't even make a wish.
The cameramen have no clue anymore.
They are being made to follow her whims.
An is giving the fight of her life.
But what she intends to do is hard to decipher.
She's so busy.
They are still making them.
They are still making them?
What did the old guy say?
What? It was an old woman.
Old woman? And she's making them now?
Wait, was there ever a woman running that shop?
Which shop did you go to?
He noticed it.
Did you go to the wrong shop?
The shop is this way.
Go towards the shrine.
There are many narrow streets here but if she goes this way it will be easy to find.
Just go this way.
That's right. It's easier to spot from this direction.
I will go this way.
Why why?
Why this way?
Her conviction is strong.
She's inherited this from her dad that she refuses to bow down from her opinions.
What color coin should I use?
She came back.
The brown coins.
She didn't know the kind of money to put in the box.
So that's what it was.
I will be back.
I see. The shrine is that way.
[Sponsor announcement]
I wish my mother will not be sick.
The mother said she had a sore throat.
Rather than the cream puffs
the most important thing is mother.
Ah, it was over here.
I forgot.
Cream puffs. Cream puffs.
The shop is just outside of the gates.
Why is she going to the side?
I'm sweating.
From all the running.
She taking a small break.
She's just taking the blouse off.
She's confirming that she didn't forget anything.
Admirable.
She should see the shop just up the road.
The cameraman has gone in first.
Look behind you. Behind you.
Dunno.
She went back even though it's right there.
Why can't she spot it?
Ah, An?
Did you purchase it?
Great that you came back.
She didn't mention the shrine.
No.
Did you not spot it?
Yep.
It wasn't there?
An, perhaps you didn't see the picture.
The front looks like this. The sign has green and red letters.
I'm supposed to look at this?
An was looking at the cream puff picture.
She wasn't looking at the facade.
Off you go. This way.
Around the corner here. Take care and thanks.
This is the 4th trip.
This time she is looking at the shop facade.
Can she find it?
It's right there. The green and red letters on the sign.
Ah, found it.
Thankfully.
Right, left. All clear, I can continue.
Nice.
She's doing it properly.
But she's also hurrying.
She was asked to purchase two.
Welcome.
One cream puff two of those.
Two? Okay.
He has them. These are those made with wasanbon sugar.
One is 175 yen. She put out a 1000 bill so now her purse will jangle even more.
She became even richer.
Yes.
Do you know the way back?
Please don't get lost again.
Please wait a bit.
Phew.
A reward.
It's a cookie.
Enjoy it.
She received a reward.
You're welcome. Take care on your way back.
Thank you.
After saying her thanks.
Right, left. All clear, I can continue.
Being safe in traffic.
Bye bye.
She can finally return.
I will give it to dad.
Cream puffs.
Yep.
You managed to buy it?
Amazing.
I found it by myself.
Perfect.
Let's take some pictures.
Here I go.
She's properly assisting with the reflector board.
The dad looks cool as he is focused on taking the pictures.
See?
Thank you.
You can eat this one.
That's why she likes photoshoots of food.
Delicious.
Ah, she forgot. She ordered cream puffs at this shop.
And the dad doesn't know.
That's right. That's right.
He only knew about the shop over there.
He really made her walk around.
There was a proper reason to get those.
Why did you come to the shrine?
I saw you were crying a bit during the conundrum.
I couldn't stand it.
I was touched when she properly asked
for her mothers good health.
Very touching.
Makes me curious about the cream puffs she ordered.
On the way back from the errand.
I wonder until how late the old lady waited for her.
As a gift for her mother that had a sore throat
they apparently collected it on the way home.
That's great.
The bus will be here in a bit.
These brothers will ride a bus to complete their errand.
He's so small.
The 4 year and 3 months old brother and his little brother
at 2 years and 4 months who keeps asking if it's coming.
Shuya
Kanaya
The one who planned this errand and let his little brother join is their mother.
She's standing there.
As their mother I am confident that they can handle it.
Some strong words.
She has a special memory associated with them.
The city of Ikeda in Tokushima prefecture where the dad who loves mountains was brought up.
The dad purchased a house with a nice view.
The wall is full of family pictures.
When the kids were smaller or that time they visited Okinawa.
In the four years of their marriage the wall has already filled up.
But the dad is no longer with us.
He died 2 years ago.
He left for his lumberjack job as usual on that day.
Location of the accident
But a tree suddenly fell on him.
When papa died I cried so much.
The two of us did. Every evening.
It was just after the little brother was born. The one who was always by his mothers side was the 2 year old brother.
It hit me like a switch. I don't remember when.
Suddenly I just decided not to cry anymore.
I won't cry anymore. Won't cry
in front of the kids anymore. Not again.
But on that day I decided that while there are dads and mothers I need to fulfill both of those roles.
The big brother behaves properly after having watched his mother from the sidelines.
When the little brother becomes unmanageable the one to take the reins is the big brother.
It's like he has taken the responsibility of his father.
I rely on the big brother.
The big brother loves to make his mother happy.
His father loved tulips.
Just as he loved nature.
So for the errand they've decided to get some flowers for him.
Kanaya at 2 years and four months still doesn't talk.
But he's fine with his brother on his side.
He depends on him.
The bus which is running late finally came.
It came.
Stop, please stop.
He noticed the brothers hands.
What a relief.
What a relief. This bus comes once every 2 hours.
They rode it.
They rode it. It's hard to see because of the tinted windows.
The windows on the bus are tinted.
The cameraman rehearsed this shot with the bus that passed 2 hours earlier and has waited since then.
Eh? With this type of windows we can't look inside.
Can't see a thing.
The cameraman on the bus.
Big brother looks serious.
And with his bright red cheeks.
What about the youngest of them?
Getting sleepy from the ride but he has nothing to worry about. Since his brother is by his side.
Protect him, big brother.
He's falling asleep.
The bus has arrived at the terminal.
This is also where they should catch it on the way back.
He's fast asleep.
We are getting off, Kanaya. You can't sleep here.
They've received the bus fare separately.
Oh no, this is for the flowers.
Oh no, he took out the 1000 yen bill.
Now the purse is full of spare change.
Let's walk to the flower shop.
Yes, they have to walk to the flower shop.
The road is straight forward.
They always come by car here with their mother.
They might not notice when going by car
but the street is on a slope.
Which they have to ascend on the way back.
Furthermore it takes about 2 hours to go there and back.
There's no time to roam around.
Better hurry.
They have to walk in line
since the pavement is narrow.
He's properly following his big brother.
Kanaya doesn't speak but he's good on his feet.
Hole.
Hole?
They are taught to walk in the line
where the holes are by their mother.
His brother is checking if Kanaya is walking properly.
After the check they can continue.
Pushed him.
But their speeds are completely different.
Little brother who can't speak a word wants to call out "wait".
Brobro.
You've become capable of saying "brobro", Kanaya?
His first words and they were "brobro".
A rapid development on this errand.
When you follow your brother with all your might you grow strong.
Hand.
Hand hand.
He even said "hands".
Even at home there are times
when he doesn't want to hold hands.
But today is an errand and his brother is his new father-figure.
Ah, it's over there.
They can see the flower shop.
Their father would often stop by
to purchase flowers for his wife.
He would get the flowers of the season every week.
Their father who worked in the mountain-side especially prefered bigleaf hydrangea.
Even their mother comes here every week.
The shop owner is an acquaintance.
Welcome.
Where's mom?
She's at home.
Did you and your brother come alone?
What a smart kid.
What did you come here to buy?
Flowers.
For dad?
Everyone remembers that his dad used to come here.
Carnations, lillies and sunflowers.
They have all kinds of flowers.
The shop owner is making them a bouquet.
Is there any color you would like to add?
Red.
Red, right?
Like this.
I see. Adding red has made is livelier.
The big brother has a nice taste.
Please add a pink ribbon for mom.
For mom, right?
That's what his father used to do too.
This flower?
Will you give this to your mother?
He decided without any hesitation.
I will wrap it for you.
Yellow is his little brothers favorite color.
Cute.
Aren't they?
Since they are a present.
The ones he chose were alstroemeria.
Also called Lily of the Incas.
The old man is even giving him a card to write on.
He can even write?
- He can write?
- That's amazing.
What is he writing?
- What is this?
- No clue.
What are you writing?
Thank you.
I can write it for you.
It said thank you?
The man wrote thanks to the mother.
Dad.
Also to your dad?
And thanks to his little brother too.
Hand it over both of you.
Thank you.
you.
Take care.
Be back tomorrow.
Back tomorrow?
There's only an hour left before the bus departs.
And they have to purchase some things first.
The supermarket is next to the bus terminal.
What they are getting is coffee and udon noodles.
Hurry up, Kanaya.
Hurry.
They've started going up the hill.
Even if he is asked to hurry...
Kanaya.
They haven't noticed when going by car
but it's pretty steep.
This way.
This won't work.
Do your best.
They won't make it at this pace.
Kanaya.
Give it all you got.
No matter how much you shout for this 2 year old who just spoke his first words he doesn't know what "hurry" means.
But he is properly walking above the holes.
I see.
Adhering to the rule
This way he won't walk into the street.
His brother has decided to leave him behind.
Is that okay?
I will go by myself.
They won't make it at this pace.
He has decided to go shopping ahead of his little brother.
Over the holes. Over the holes.
The supermarket is within sight.
I'm sweating.
The road is flat here.
The supermarket is right there.
This is a large-sized supermarket.
At this moment how is Kanaya doing?
With two traffic lights ahead of him if he walks
above the holes he will reach up with his brother.
Move forward.
But there's only 30 minutes before the bus leaves.
Will they make it?
Oh no.
The big brother has arrived.
I would like some coffee.
Concentrated coffee?
He found the coffee at the beverage aisle.
Is your mother looking for this?
Only for dad?
Only for dad.
Smokes and coffee reminds them of dad.
And there must also be some udon here.
He remembers well always getting these with his mother.
His little brother loves udon.
Heavy.
Is it really that heavy?
I made it.
He found all he needs.
I wonder how Kanaya is doing.
He was told to walk on the bumpy lines after the holes.
I see.
The supermarket is within sight.
Great.
It's straight ahead.
Where's brobro?
Brobro is still in the supermarket.
Putting all the items in the backpack.
Thank you very much.
Time will run out if you don't hurry.
- Better hurry.
- Hurry.
It's 10 minutes to and people have started gathering.
Where's Kanaya.
He believes Kanaya has kept walking far ahead.
He should be around here.
And at that time.
Brobro.
It's Kanaya.
He's calling.
Where are you? Where are you?
Where?
Kanaya.
Brobro.
Found him.
Just like his brother believed.
Amazing.
Brobro.
Isn't it nice that he can say brobro now.
I got coffee and udon.
He's talking normally to him.
Udon and coffee.
Come to the bus stop.
The little brother is amazing.
Kanaya, do your best.
Amazing.
Finally leaving the bumpy lines they get together for an emotional meet up.
Kanaya.
He really did his best not to cry.
Remarkable.
What? Aren't we going to hold hands?
He clearly put out his hands.
Since he made it this far by himself he wants his brother to finish on his own. Like a father.
They made it just in time with 5 minutes to spare.
They gave it their all.
The bus home doesn't have tinted windows.
With this we should be able to see the two from outside.
Back to the cameraman who waited for over 2 hours
he put a lot of care into getting a glimpse of the two.
Original Song:
藤田麻衣子 - 素敵なことがあなたを待っている
Do you best.
Where are they? Huh, they aren't there?
Can't see them cause they are asleep.
Even big brother.
From all the stress surrounding the trip.
In the end we didn't get a single glimpse of them going either of the directions.
It's the bus stop after crossing the river.
If they don't wake up they will go all the way to the mountains.
Their mother is waiting at the bus stop.
She's wondering if they made it to the bus.
They did.
Sound asleep.
It's coming.
- Are there any kids on board?
- Yes.
- Can I take a look?
- You're welcome.
- Must be asleep.
- I bet they are.
There they are.
Could you please wait a little bit longer?
Kanaya who kept walking above the holes.
Shuuya.
Shuuya who has become brobro.
You've arrived.
He gave it all he had.
He looks so surprised.
Mom, did you come all the way to get us?
Exactly 280 yen. Thank you for taking care of us. Ah, and I'm sorry it dragged out.
She also thanks the other riders.
Hold up. It wasn't just a dream?
I really did go on an errand.
It's fine. He even brought proof.
Amazing. Are these flowers for dad?
And are these for mom?
Why did you write here?
Just to make you happy.
Thank you very much.
Thank you. I saw it. Also for dad.
I wrote it to you, mom. And also for dad.
Dad, they've become able to purchase flowers.
Let's eat udon with broth.
Her laughter has returned to her voice.
Here you go.
And Kanaya has started speaking. He said "brobro".
As usual next to their father you find flowers and coffee.
Father, let's depend on big brother to bring you flowers.
Father lives on inside both of Shuuya and Kanaya.
- What a perfect errand.
- That's true.
At the beginning when the mother was standing strong I thought what a hard mother.
Well said.
I thought what a hard-disciplining mother
but then it turned out that she was kind.
I cried a lot. Especially considering the younger is 2 years old and staying by his brothers side.
I think that boys have a strong feeling towards wanting to protect their mother.
Such as wanting to be helpful to their mother.
And especially when there is a younger brother in play the older becomes aware of the role the play.
It was irresistible.
There was a big brother here who was crying a lot.
Wailing.
- I'm sorry. I just couldn't keep it in.
- I kept hearing "uuh uuh" next to me.
Seeing Shuuya was almost like watching myself.
Well brobro.
Don't be dumb.
But this is the first time I've been able to say it. Brobro.
- It's your first time saying it? I see.
- Brobro. Exactly.
Next will be our youngest to go on an errand for this time.
A small town called Nishiiya in the mountains of Shikoku.
A 2 year old and 2 months old will go on an errand.
If you go there you will notice that hardly any cars drive on the road. It's a very quiet place.
This is the only shop here.
Food, alcohol, soy sauce, tissues and even emergency drugs are available here.
The towns convenience store.
It's been in operation for 87 years.
This shop hasn't changed and people love it for it.
The ones running it are the Kitas.
Since this place is so safe and our kid is capable her mother has asked us to film the errand.
Say "welcome".
- No way.
- This kid?
- She's so small.
Isn't she just a toddler?
Can this kid do it?
Bread please.
We don't meet the children until the day of shooting.
Yumemi
Our program aims not to prefer any children over others.
Today we have Anpan bread.
She can talk.
Is it really this kid?
Not an older sister or something?
We called out the mother.
Is that kid Yumemi?
- Is it Yume?
- It's Yume.
- Isn't she too small?
- She's small?
- Can she go on an errand?
- An errand? Yeah, she's in a good mood today.
- Mood? Are you confident?
- Yes.
When I told her to go to the swings she ran towards it alone.
So it's really this kid. Since the 16 staffers came all the way from Tokyo let's just see how it plays out.
Poi.
She's cleaning up.
So many toys. The bag is going to be full.
Yeah, this bag might not be enough.
Can it all fit in?
She can conversate.
She understands quantities.
Yeah, it won't. Do we have another bag?
It won't be able to close.
Let's have a look if we do.
Will she be able to spot the right item.
There ain't one.
Ain't one?
We've probably run out.
What to do?
Even if asked such a question.
She's holding the remote to the AC.
What?
Hello, Yu.
I have a request to make.
We've run out of bags.
Huh?
But I'm waiting for the electrician and can't leave home. Wonder who can purchase them instead.
Yume will go buy them.
Yes.
Will you buy them? Really?
Okay.
It's at the old man Kita's place.
Pass the school, go up the hill and then buy it.
Are you up for it?
Yes.
A bag? Really?
Can I really make this request?
For real?
I have another request.
Another request?
I want this.
A toy egg.
It's an egg.
What's this?
I would also like eggs for todays lunch since we've run out. Can you do it?
Yes, of course.
It's the usual route to the shop.
She was asked to get bags and eggs.
We've left a camera on the floor.
Mom, eggs... wait what's that?
Immediately spotted it.
Amazing.
I guess it was left by a construction worker.
What is it?
Be careful.
Yes, departing.
Departure.
She has to sit on each step to go down the stairs.
Each step requires this much effort.
Take care.
Heading off.
The mother is a former Japanese teacher.
A real pro in education.
A besides bringing up a kid she's already brought up two older sisters.
And she has taught Yumemi that she can accomplish anything. She can even talk really well.
Wait, she stopped.
Sticking to the wall and checking out her surroundings.
Will she go back now?
She started moving.
Oh, she's going out after all.
She's cautious.
Yumemi is careful.
She has started spinning.
Spinning one round.
Then another.
Mama.
Mama? Will she go back home?
That makes sense.
She disappeared.
Where to?
She started climbing the hill.
This road leads to the shop.
She's putting all her power
into climbing the 13 degree slope.
She stopped.
It's her mama.
Do your best.
Ah, she's watching her.
Is she crying?
Do your best.
Do your best. Off you go.
The one crying is the mama.
Yumemi isn't crying.
Do your best.
One two. One two.
One two.
She suddenly turned her back and started picking her nose.
Do your best.
Departure.
Her mom isn't there to stop her from picking her nose.
She's really going for it.
We might've underestimated her.
Still going up the hill.
She stopped again.
Looking back at her home.
She's making a grimace.
Is she going to cry?
Her seeking pose.
Where is mama?
Mama.
Her shouting out pose.
She's so cute.
Mama.
All that searching and shouting out but mama isn't there.
She keeps searching.
What should I do. Mama...
This is her thinking pose.
She can't go home.
She's really going for it?
She's hard to read.
Yumemi has reached the top of the hill
and is heading for the shop.
She's greeting our traffic patrol.
Hello.
It's straight ahead. The shop's
red banner is visible from here.
I can see it too.
She knows to walk on the edge of the street.
She's walking on the stone lids
like her mother taught her
She stopped.
Oh, the cameraman was in the way.
We are sorry.
Did she fall?
No, she's just sitting. This is the usual spot she has a break when she's out walking with her mother.
Is it someone she knows?
The old lady of the health clinic.
She greets them every time they go for a walk.
And she's even bringing candy?
Thank you.
Here you go.
She knows to properly say thanks.
Her cherished Madeleine cakes.
This is the best.
Delicious?
Bye bye.
Not only candy but watching and protecting from afar that's the love that goes around in this town.
Amazing.
I will keep walking.
After a short rest and she's ready to walk again.
There's a Madelaine crumb left on her cheeck.
She has arrived at the shop.
She was asked to get bags and eggs.
Coming from outside it's quite dark inside.
She's intimidated by going in.
Did you come by yourself? How clever you are.
What do you need?
Eggs? How many?
Two? Two eggs?
No way she can carry two containers.
No way.
But the old lady took out two eggs and placed them in a bag for her.
How kind.
Cause that's how they were sold in the old days.
They will never be able to sell this container.
The 83 year old husband.
Good morning.
Enjoy the conversation with this tiny customer.
Did you come alone? How clever you are.
She's being praised.
Getting eggs?
She does?
Mama loves them.
And she was able to come by herself.
She's become more conversational since last.
Thank you.
It's a frog.
What is this thing?
2 years and 2 months and an 83 year old.
Their conversation tempo oddly suit each other.
She's so excited.
Yumemi, you still haven't finished the errand.
Yumemi, are you only getting eggs?
She's searching for the forgotten thing in her mind.
What did mama ask you to buy?
And bags too.
She remembered.
When she's asked she will remember.
The old lady brings out the bags for her.
She also knows that she needs to pay.
Here.
Putting out 500 yen and getting her money back. She did it.
Praiseworthy.
I will give you this.
Thank you for saying thank you.
Thank you.
To avoid the eggs from cracking he puts them in her purse.
Safe.
Say your goodbyes.
Bye bye.
She won't say goodbye?
Doesn't want to go home.
While they say goodbye the old man slowly moves away.
Will you be fine?
Yumemi finds it hard to go away.
-What a weird scene.
- Gramps be careful of things behind you.
What?
The old man is now much further away.
This is quite moving.
And with that the old man...
disappears from view.
Their bond is so strong.
Alright Yumemi, that was the goodbye.
After having so much fun she remembers her mother.
Mama.
That's right.
Do your best.
She's taking a secret shortcut through the school.
She knows about this?
Amazing.
She can see her home from here.
Her mother can see someone in pink clothes.
Yu.
Oh, mama.
Welcome home.
I'm home. I brought the bags.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Her mother thinks she forgot all about the eggs.
Thank you.
Amazing.
Both the kid and the mom are.
One by one she climbs the stairs with all her might.
The goal is her mothers arms.
Thank you for getting it for me. Welcome home.
I'm home.
Welcome home. Thank you.
You got the bags for me?
And you forgot the eggs?
Yes.
I have them.
You do? Where are they?
Are they in there?
Here.
Open.
What's this?
Amazing. Amazing.
These are the eggs.
They are in there and they didn't crack.
All thanks to the old man.
What will we make with these today?
Don't do that. They will break.
Since these are eggs.
Do it.
Cracking the eggs for lunch.
You did it.
Made omurice with the eggs.
How nice.
Thanks for the meal.
Yu, the eggs you bought are delicious. They really are.
That's nice. But Yumemi isn't putting the eggs in her mouth.
Why?
Say aah.
No go.
Are you sure?
Here you go.
Mama can have it.
I want mama to enjoy it all.
Since she purchased it just for mama.
Todays noon nap. I wonder if she's
talking to the old man in her dreams.
The mother is amazing.
Isn't she? I've never seen a 2 year old like this.
The only one who cried was the mom.
The bye bye scene with the old man too.
The way he stepped back.
First time seeing an old guy doing the moonwalk.
Old guy moonwalk?
A 2 year 2 month year old who can talk this well while she can hardly descend stairs
both the mom and Yumemi are remarkable.
Right.
The "open" reveal was amazing as well.
It was like a magic show. Open. So cute.
I was worried about the eggs after all that hugging.
At the end yeah.
She was going like this.
And the "sorry for keeping you waiting".
Saying "sorry for keeping you waiting" and "open" such precious grown up words.
Sorry for keeping you waiting...
Sugiyama how are you feeling right now?
Sugiyamas kid will go on an errand now.
Watching the previous segments they are all full of drama
but after my son came back I kept asking how it was but he didn't tell me much.
so it will be my first time seeing it today.
I wonder how it will be.
- Excited?
I'm really looking forward.
Sugiyama mama please introduce the clip.
I think my son did his best.
Please enjoy this clip.
Ai Sugiyama who reached the world No. 1 in women's doubles.
No. 1 in the world is impressive.
She won 3 grand slams in the doubles.
Amazing.
Having reached the No. 1 ranking she is called The Super Woman by the tennis world.
She had 62 consecutive Grand Slam main draw appearances which won her a guiness record.
In 2009 she retired from her 17 year old tennis career.
Her husband is a former pro-golfer.
Even though he is Japanese he was born and raised in Kenya.
Now he's Ai's manager.
Here is Yuu who is 3 years and 8 months old and who loves to play with balls.
Wonder which one of the parents he is taking after?
Let's first see him play golf with his father.
Is he a golfer?
Amazing.
Or is he a tennis player?
Well done.
He has his game face on.
Okay, next is mommy.
Ai's tennis club.
It only felt naturally to have the errand
be centered around this place.
We want him to always face challenges.
Sugiyamas 3 rules to bringing up a kid
It's the first step to accomplish things so that's why we put stress on seriously faces challenges.
Next is not putting limits to their ability
if I keep telling them that they can't do X thing
that will really destroy the will of my child so instead I will tell them that I believe in them.
And the last one is as expected: Waiting.
Those are some splendid rules but some rules are meant to be broken.
They aren't.
Like making him eat without waiting after saying "Hurry up and eat".
There is a big gap between reality and the ideal.
And at the club they make him help them out such as picking up balls on the court.
You are almost done. Once you are done come to us.
Not putting limits on their ability.
I will be exhausted if I do it alone.
You will but you are almost done.
I wanna do it with mama.
Okay but only 3 balls.
Hasn't she just been made to pick up balls by her son?
What was the meaning of this?
Yuu easily got away with that.
The dad has a theory on why it's hard to accomplish the ideal.
There's a gap between what he is being told and what he wants to do.
That's right. But it takes time to realize.
- I am the one who is best put together.
- No way.
That's what I think.
They cuddle him while being being afraid of breaking his back.
The mom has thought of a plan
to make him want to go on an errand.
If we directly ask him to do it tomorrow he probably won't.
It's not about having him do warm ups but we need to give him the resolution to accomplish it.
With resolution is how you greet the world.
Will it be fine?
Is dad missing the resolution?
I'm crying now.
What kind of tears are those?
He cries so easily.
I am so nervous.
He said he's the best put together of the two. Ai seems to be the one.
It's finally the day of the errand.
They have made him help out extra for a month.
- Good morning.
- Look at this.
It's still dirty over there.
I know that.
One whole month of this kind of exchange.
He must be ready to prove himself helpful.
This helps a lot.
He enjoys being praised.
- He's so determend.
- Nice.
Okay.
Thank you. It's become really clean.
The balls are all over the 4th tennis court if you could...
Okay, let's go after putting the brooms back.
Hurrying to the fourth court.
- Nice.
- Amazing.
The face of a working man.
Not pretending to help but actually being helpful.
Thank you.
I did it all.
Thank you. You helped out everyone.
Yep.
He has come to appreciate helping others out.
He's ready since the cherry blossom has bloomed at the club.
They have a cherry blossom viewing party every year.
And this year they have a special cake to go with it.
And with this cake the errand begins.
It's amazing.
A racket?
Do you remember it, Yuu?
The racket is made from chocolate.
That's what it is!
Same racket that mom used to play with.
It's the same type of racket that Ai was using as a player.
She sent the racket to the cakemaker
and they created a replica.
And the father left the racket at the cake shop on purpose.
Where's the racket?
The racket? Here.
No no, the real racket.
The theatrics have begun.
I mistakenly left it at the cake shop.
He's saying that he forgot it. This is terrible.
Without it you can't play tennis.
- That's right. This is no good.
- We're in trouble.
I forgot it.
I'm begging of you. Can you bring it?
I will? All by myself?
You can do it.
Is it okay if it's lost? It's my most precious racket.
I used it when I was a player.
That's right.
Will I go all by myself? But that's a first.
You can do it.
How come?
I don't want to do it.
Sleepy? So for the party...
I'm sleepy.
Being sleepy is an excuse.
Alright. Let's check if it's cold outside.
His father is taking him outside.
It's fine. Come. Tell me if it's cold or not.
As your mom said you will become energetic from walking.
The dad's reasoning removed the excuse about being sleepy.
Look at this racket once more.
This means a lot to your mommy.
- Remember it, Yuu.
- I'm begging you.
What?
I want to go with mom.
"I want to go with mom". That's not an excuse.
He still struggles to find the willpower.
Let's send you off.
Can you go?
I can't go.
Really?
They must seize this moment.
Exactly. Find that energy.
He has lots of power.
I want to keep crying.
Harvesting the energy from crying.
Alright. Try to cry with all your might.
Here is a mother who is experienced with tears having to appear before finding the willpower.
The mother is just smiling through it.
If you have to cry then cry but
turn that energy into something
and do something with it. That is crucial.
Of course, Ai knows all about finding the willpower.
Tell me what you dislike about it.
I will become a missing child.
You will definitely not. Follow the road straight ahead. You don't have to turn even once.
Just has to go straight.
It's simple.
When someone yawns then it means that they are sleepy.
That's just an excuse.
I get it. When you are nervous you yawn.
She thwarted yet another excuse.
What if I become lonely.
This is reality.
I get it. I have prepared something
so you won't get lonely.
They've even thought of a way to avoid him from getting lonely.
A teddy bear. His name is Daiji (precious).
As a baby he would wrap it in a towel
and never ever let it out of his sight.
Mommy will be in trouble without the racket.
He tries to avoid going by taking Daiji out.
Then it can't be helped.
Let's cancel the party.
His mothers final measure.
It's fine. If you can't do it then fine.
Meanwhile, his father is in the parking lot.
- He's not witnessing any of this.
- That's right.
Will he go? I want him to but...
His father also can't find the resolution.
He's close to letting him give up.
I will refuse in front of everyone.
I will tell them that Yuu can't do it.
His mother is resolute that he has to go.
No way.
No way, right?
And at that moment Yuu's crying changes.
I will go get it.
Will you? Thank you.
Will we meet again when I come back?
Of course. That's a given.
Hug me for 5 minutes and then I will go.
Okay.
Something took hold in Yuu's heart.
I will hug you for 5 minutes so you can gather your strength and decide to go.
Yuu, you are mammas child so you can definitely do it.
Tell me when you feel strong enough to go.
And then wait. (Rule 3)
Tell me when you are ready.
Can you go?
He found the willpower.
I will go.
Remarkable.
Alright. Let's do our best.
If it's you, Yuu, then you can do it.
Take mama's...
Can do it.
The good luck charm contains his mothers wish.
This is a special backpack.
This is for rackets.
Rackets can fit in it.
Papa attached this special band to it.
The father thought of this and created it.
There's a hole at the bottom that the grip can go through.
Will he be able to explain this to the cake maker?
Alright. Ready to go.
Please do it. Thank you.
Can you go from here or should I follow you to the road?
If it's Yuu, then I can do it.
Amazing.
Off you go then.
He suddenly changed.
He's gathered all this energy from crying
it's almost like he's a different person.
Alright, I can do it.
You can do it.
It's straight forward and downhill.
He needs to pick up the racket from the cake shop.
At the convenience store he was asked to get 2 packs of three-color rice balls as well as a cherry blossom steamed bun.
Yuu likes to be seen by people and held in esteem.
But today he is all alone which is hard for him.
At this moment someone who is always watching Yuu, believes that he can accomplish this.
- Amazing.
- What is?
I could never do this errand.
- Of course you could.
- I see but...
- Whose kid do you think it is? It's my kid.
- Hey, make some room for me.
Did he feel their confidence in him?
Yuu started running.
Right, heading towards the cake shop.
Erm wait!? There's a convenience store on the way there? Actually there are 3 right around here.
The blossom viewing party basket is in the 100 yen convenience store not here.
The things he was asked to get
I bet they aren't here.
A pink steamed bun as requested?
Found it?
Found it.
It's a thank you "Heisei era for being over" bun.
Not it.
No three-colored rice balls
but he picked up mitarashi rice balls.
Please and thanks.
Unfortunately both of them are off.
They are close enough.
Today it's a cherry blossom viewing party.
His first conversation on the errand.
Because of the party I had to come alone today.
Amazing, he can converse.
That's the spirit.
It's my first time coming out like this alone.
Properly paying.
From 1000 yen.
And getting the money back.
He was living in Chigasaki prefecture and he's coming home today
He is?
back to Japan.
That's the usual Yuu.
Chigasaki is in Japan, though.
Since I will become a young boy...
Yesterday was a kindergarten entrance ceremony​
and he's proud to be considered a young boy.
Can't forget this.
No good. He forgot just like his dad.
Thank you.
He bought the wrong things but he feels accomplished now.
He can do things even if people aren't watching.
Nah, they were watching.
Switch it up.
What are they doing?
Alright, let's split it.
They are sharing it!
What's up with this comedy duo.
From their expensive apartment.
I can see. Can you?
They are watching over him.
Such a good relation.
That was funny.
Peew.
He dropped something.
Oh no, Daiji.
It's Daiji (precious) the teddy bear.
He dropped Daiji and ran off and as an exception the staff called out to him about Daiji.
He didn't notice.
It's dangerous running so close to the road and you seem to have dropped something.
Huh?
Is that brown thing not yours?
Daiji isn't there.
It fell off from there.
Daiji was with him when he learned to walk and of course they always slept together.
And when he rides a car or when they went to France he can go anywhere as long as Daiji is with him.
This 6th generation Daiji who is a bit dirty.
- 6th generation.
- That much?
Never leave my side.
Alright.
He's exhausted from going down the hill. For those times...
Energy injection.
It's candy for revitalizing him.
Candy.
"Please eat it when you feel exhausted" his mother said and put it in his pocket.
He's walking again.
Yuu who came to a sudden stop started walking again.
Here I go.
It's the cake shop.
As part of the Swiss owned hotel
here they make their own original cakes.
Looks so yummy.
He came to pick up the racket his father forgot there.
Hello.
The owner and chef.
Please give me a racket.
A racket?
Mama used to play tennis.
Mama's racket? I will go look for it.
Must be inside the kitchen.
He was able to explain it.
The chef understood it too
that this is an important racket
Is this the one?
He's making sure that this is mamas racket.
Not like many people forget rackets in this place.
Please put it in this red bag for me.
Explaining this will be difficult.
This one.
This one? Will it fit?
It will.
It's bigger than the bag.
Not this end. From here.
There's a hole down here.
That's right.
Ah, there is a hole.
Amazing.
And put it through here.
He was able to explain it.
Amazing.
And then put it through here.
I am?
You're sweating.
Chef, we appreciate your help.
It's your fault.
Cause he's using all his effort.
The chef is using all his skill.
- Chef!
- Chef, thank you very much.
That's perfect.
That's right.
Wanna try it out?
Fits perfectly.
It is?
This is fine.
Alright, take it back to your mother.
Mothers important racket and the groceries.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, chef.
The 100 yen convinience store where the requested items are on the other side of the road.
It's very close to where he's walking right now.
I wonder if he got the racket.
They can't see well from this angle.
Can't see at all.
Even if no one is watching over him
Yuu is doing just fine, mother.
- He finally went out.
- He did.
- How has it been so far?
- It really took a while to get him to leave.
I was worried if he would be fine but gradually his behavior changed so I started having confidence in him.
It changed the moment he left.
Even I was surprised by that change.
Now I understand the strength of your son
but I also understood the weakness of your husband.
Yeah, the husband.
He was so anxious the day before.
Even he didn't understood why he was crying.
Even said that he couldn't do the errand.
About this teary-eyed father
he is in fact in the studio today
Yuu's papa, where are you?
Thank you very much.
Since you came all the way,
why don't you come and sit here with us?
Isn't that right, everybody?
Come and watch.
From "my first errand" to "my first trial".
The father is on trial now.
He's already crying.
Just finished wailing.
Papa, please share how you feel.
I can't find the words.
- Mama is so strong.
- She is.
Just like she said. If I was alone in this I would immediately give in and go with him to pick it up.
It was mostly cut out but I was in that car for long mumbling "isn't it enough already".
I kept thinking about giving up but
Ai said that this kid can definitely do it.
Her confidence in our son was so strong that it started rubbing off on me too.
- It's the strength of a mother.
- What a cool mom.
It's time to go shopping again.
He needs to get 2 packs of three-color rice balls as well as a cherry blossom steamed bun. Then back to the tennis club.
Since he doesn't have to hold the racket he can raise his hand.
The father really thought of everything.
Isn't the camera too close?
No, it's fine.
Camera
Oh no.
For those times...
Suspicious.
Too suspicious.
Weird. No one behaves like that.
"Why is he playing tennis here?"
he wonders but he didn't notice the camera.
Amazing.
At this moment.
Yuu, take care.
The chef was watching over him.
Bye bye.
As expected, he does best when people watch over him.
He has arrived at the 100 yen store.
The cherry blossom viewing party basket is right near the entrence.
Found it.
He found the rice balls and was asked to get two.
- Remarkable.
- He knows to get two.
That's right. Here's another one for Yuu to talk to.
296 yen, please.
We are having a party. Mama, Yuu and papa will eat this.
Is this an important racket?
This is the racket that accomplished the first place.
Amazing, isn't it?
My mom used to be a tennis player
back then she used this racket.
Of all people, this is Sugiyama Ai's racket.
What kind of player was your mother?
Was she a great player?
Yes, she lost to everyone.
TN: He mistakes the preposition.
Tiny mistake but results in the opposite meaning.
- He's pretty wrong.
- It's the other way around.
She would lose to everyone.
She didn't lose to anyone.
Don't forget like your father.
Don't forget this.
Thank you.
Looks heavy.
Ah, he's there. Isn't that Yuu?
It is. Have a look.
And he's carrying something.
- I can't see.
- I want to see. I beg of you.
He's begging.
- Alright, have a look.
- Are you sure?
What they can't see is his expression.
And of course they can't see what he bought either.
He accomplished everything he was asked to do.
He's entering the convenience store again.
He already has all he needs.
What is he going to purchase?
He picked up the racket and purchased all that's needed so why did he go into a third convenience store?
What is he getting?
He really loves stores.
That's enough.
You can't carry all that, Yuu.
They could see he was carrying a lot.
There are no needed items.
Just come home.
There's nothing more to get.
What will he purchase?
Where is Pamu?
Pamu is the name of the tennis club.
Go back to Pamu?
I just want to go back to Pamu.
I want to go back there since I was running an errand and now I want to return.
Pamu isn't the name of a house so what is it?
In a court you go like this.
That's right.
A tennis court?
You would have to go up the hill.
Can you go up there?
You can?
I can do it.
Thank you.
Then please do your best.
Splendid.
He knew the way, of course.
He just wanted to talk.
I see.
Alright. I will go.
His resolute expression is different from his crying face.
But this power was born from his crying.
Mama must be waiting.
Mama's world No. 1 has been entrusted to Yuu.
This is so heavy.
Yuu is back at the tennis club.
Yuu!
How amazing.
I purchased this.
What did you buy? And my racket?
Thank you, it's my important racket.
- It's perfect.
- Amazing. Thank you.
You did a great job.
Did you manage to ask for it?
- At the cake shop?
- Did you ask the cake maker?
From happiness since you did so well. I think you are amazing.
Why are there tears coming out?
Where's the cake?
- First show us what you bought.
- Tell us, tell us.
The chef gave me...
Ah, mama loves those.
These things.
That's right mama. I thought mama loves these so...
That's right. I love mitarashi rice balls.
Amazing.
It was fun on my first errand.
He was happy to do it in the end.
Please eat this.
Time for the cherry blossom viewing party.
Wonderful.
Yuu did his best for the party. Thank you.
Did his best.
Nice smile.
Thank you, Yuu.
He was asked to get them but these are mama's beloved mitarashi rice balls.
Not that good.
Not that good?
Super tasty.
Everyone, be careful that it doesn't get caught in your throats
so please eat it slowly
He's worried about them.
Hey Yuu, what do you want to be when you grow up?
Cuisine.
Chef?
Neither golf nor tennis
but Yuu might become the worlds best chef.
- Splendid.
- It was splendid.
Got them because mama loves them.
That tugged at my heartstrings.
Yeah, at first I thought that we should get rice balls matching the color of cherry blossom
but normally I go for mitarashi rice balls and usually go for them so he must've been observing me.
- I totally thought he had made a mistake.
- That's right.
but it was to show gratitude towards his mother.
Father, are you okay after watching this?
Too much crying.
Well... I'm lost for words.
- Are you okay?
- Definitely not.
You were crying throughout.
And one staff member had a camera in his racket. What was all that about?
Who holds a racket like this?
What a cute kid. And just like how we watched a mother raising their boy this time we have a 4 year old girl.
Inami in Toyama prefecture is a
flourishing town built around a shrine.
Wood crafting is famous there and many sculptures around.
Amazing.
And there we find a bustling road leading up to the shrine.
At this kimono fabrics store we find a 4 year old girl.
Here is Sae who helps out her mother.
Admirable.
She does everything in earnestness.
She loves working at the shop and
she also helps out her grandmother.
Readying the spare change. Grandma brings them every day this to a supermarket close by.
Putting the change in a bag.
Taking off.
Off you go.
Mother.
Make sure to work hard and come back.
Grandma has been out for 20 minutes.
Yes, yes.
A call from her.
Ah Sae, she's saying that she forgot the money.
The 50 yen coin bag.
What?
The grandmas strategy.
What? Okay.
Found it!
They hid it.
I found it.
Sae is full of energy.
What should we do, Sae?
Does this mean that she will go on an errand?
Was it underneath it??
Sae, can you bring this? To Asamo.
You did?
Got it.
Alright.
The flowers for Buddha have withered. Can you also get some fresh ones?
Yes.
The town next door is after the big crossing
grandma's shop is in the supermarket
she can buy the flowers in the same building.
Take care. Take your time.
Off I go.
Sae, has been begging to go on
an errand so it can't be helped.
It's my first time.
TN: Ending a sentence in dawa is very lady like and cute.
So fun.
This is her first errand and it's spring.
She has arrived at the crossing and this sculpture has been made in Inami.
Welcome to Inami.
It can talk.
From here on the scenery immediately changes.
A wide crossing with no obstructed view
and since few cars pass there are no traffic lights.
She always crosses with her grandmother.
Right, left, right.
Sae never looked back once.
She looks and walks forward.
Ah, she crossed.
She crossed it.
It's hot.
Sae broke a good sweat.
She has a towel in her right for wiping her sweat
in her left pocket she has a towel for tears.
What are the carving today?
A dragon or a daruma?
She considered asking them
but she can't today.
I have to go to Asumo I can't do other things.
The pink roof is where she is headed.
I finally approached it.
Just like mother said, if you go
straight then it's right there.
I can go by myself. How great. I'm a genius.
A genius.
Ah, it's cool. Always great with air condition.
This is her grandmothers shop.
Grandma, I brought you the things you forgot.
She gave it her all just for her grandmother.
It was beneath the pillow.
Thank you so much. I was in trouble.
Grandma, please don't forget.
Now it's all there. Thank you for bringing it here.
Please do.
I will get flowers too.
In fact, a monk will come visit grandpa house.
Hello.
I came by myself.
Uwa, so many beatiful flowers.
I'm completely at loss.
Flowers for buddha, they are all made to be similar but it seems like she's found the best one.
These are cute.
Flowers for buddha, I will go home with these.
You dropped your wallet.
Her important purse given to her by grandma.
380 yen please.
She has two 500 yen coins in her wallet.
Since I'm just a kid I don't know if this is enough.
Just one 500 yen coin please.
She always handles the loose change
but today is her first time paying.
Thank you.
Here you go. Thank you.
Ah, it was cool inside.
It's April and the Hokuriku regions' summer has begun.
That's right.
It's become hotter than before.
Clank clank clank sounds can be heard.
She's almost home.
Yep.
Hot today.
Everyone watches over her
and that's why she can do her best.
This town raises and holds children dear.
That's been going on for years
and is now part of normal life in Inami.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I was able to do it.
I was able to go by myself.
Really? You are remarkable.
Splendid.
On my way back it was way hotter than the way over there.
She's sweating a lot.
Was it fun?
It was fun.
So it was fun.
Which is why the mother conceived a second errand.
She will go visit the temple to call the monk over to their home so that she can pray at their home altar.
There are many temples in Inami so her mother is trying to give her clear directions.
If you go this way, on the right side there is a spinning blue and red thing, right?
It's a spinning barber's pole.
With it to your back you will have the temple in front of you.
Butsugon temple.
It is. You understand?
Oh, that one?
Alright. Got it.
Good, good, good, good, gooooood.
Nice smile.
I will head off.
My life is so full of errands.
What's up with this song.
This isn't her first errand, it's her second.
She's looking for the spinning barber's pole.
Spinning spinning, where are you? Spinning.
Ah, it's there. Seems like it's their day off.
She passed it by.
Was hard to see.
And that's right this is the temple.
The cameraman races ahead of her.
Wait, she stopped.
She turned back.
That's odd. Her mother mentioned this spinning pole but it's quite inconspicuous.
Why can't this errand veteran see it?
Mother, it wasn't spinning at all.
Even if it isn't spinning that's the right one.
I stood with it to my back.
Was there a temple?
There was but there are temples here and there so I wouldn't know.
She really gave it her all.
Cause that's what kind of town it is.
I will tell you.
I will put this on you.
She put a glittering bracelet on her right hand.
Do this and it's the temple on the left.
To the right of the spinning pole.
I understand.
Do you understand?
Did you see it though it wasn't spinning?
It wasn't spinning.
I thought it would but it's their day off today. I'm sorry.
Mother, you were slightly bad.
That's right.
This errands veteran is ready to departure.
Okay, I've understood.
Say "excuse me" in a loud voice.
I'm fine.
You will fall if you run.
She can do it if she understands what. That's Sae's good point. But she is getting tired. This is her second errand today after all.
And it's hot.
Alright, she has arrived in front of the pole.
It's fine even if it doesn't spin.
With it to your back there is a temple on the right and one on the left. Which one is it?
- So that's what it was.
- That's hard to discern.
According to the bracelet that her mother put on her.
This one?
That's right. The temple on the right. The Butsugon temple.
Glad she got it.
This is her first time alone at a temple.
- Scary to be alone at a temple.
- It is scary.
Straight to the main building.
One step at a time. The talkative Sae is really quiet right now.
Excuse me.
She calls out with a loud voice.
No one comes out.
She won't cry. She won't be perturbed.
Excuse me.
She calls out in an even louder voice this time.
But no one comes out.
Why not?
There's also a building over there.
That's right. This is the building where the monk lives which is also called Kuri.
The door is open.
If she goes inside and calls out loudly then the monk will come out but she doesn't go in.
She can't bring herself forward.
It's dark inside and smells heavily of incense.
Since this is the way she better
fight through the scary feeling.
The bracelet her mother gave her is her only support.
Alright, I will head in. At that moment...
The bracelet broke.
She picks up the beads but she can't fix it.
Sae, is this all too much?
She won't go home. These are all new
experiences for the 4 year old Sae.
And then this expression.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Thankfully.
Who's there?
From within the dark someone approaches.
Isn't this Sae?
Yes.
But it's a familiar face.
This is the monk.
Please sit down.
What's wrong?
I will receive this.
Here.
It's a gift for Buddha.
I called you but you were a bit slow so I was wandering around.
- Slow?
- She was slow.
Please forgive me for being slow.
It's alright.
Is it? I see.
Let's go right away.
This errand was a success.
I was on so many errands today.
I came to visit Buddha and I...
The words burst out of her in one go.
Yesterday I went to the ocean.
Which ocean? I forgot that.
You forgo..
My father played soooo much with me.
I see.
My little brother was with me.
And mother. We were four all in all.
Now we all know what Sae has been doing all week.
I'm home.
Sae, did you do your best?
I chose pink carnations.
Flowers from her first errand.
The monk from the second errand.
Breaking a sweat from all the hard work and deep in prayer, her grandpa would be proud.
Having fought through two errands
she now fights off sleepiness.
This was Sae who loves giving her all.
She really did.
11 years later.
The place we are meeting with Sae...
Is this an outdoor stage? No no.
The girl wearing the aqua green is climbing the wall.
It's Sae.
Sae who still loves to give it her all is now in 3rd year of middle school where she's a rock climber.
In elementary school she came 3rd in her prefecture within the C-class.
In first year of middle school she became the first in B-class in the prefecture.
She also won a second place in another bouldering competition.
Amazing.
And this spring she became number one in her prefecture in the group of young girls.
A little more and she will win in the Kanto region.
She fell.
So tough.
She puts chalk on her hands from her bag and goes straight back to it without a break for her muscles.
That was all the break she got.
Taking the place she failed as a new challenge.
She grows strong from all the climbing.
This time she climbs only using the red stones.
She has accomplished it when she attaches her rope to the clip above.
She did it.
Please lower me.
We asked Sae about why she becomes so perfectly focused while climbing.
I love the feeling after I've accomplished a climb.
As I become able to climb more difficult ones I become so happy that I just can't stop doing it.
What kind of child has she become?
I wonder...
I might not have changed that much after all.
I still love to excel in everything.
And I never stopped breaking a sweat.
Please.
Always outperforms on her second try.
Now she only climbs on the green stones.
Her closest goal is to pass to the National Athletic Meet and perform well there.
Scary.
And then she hopes to do well at the Junior Olympics.
She also accomplished it in her second try.
Please lower me.
She does this all by herself. She has developed a splendid view of the world.
What does she want to be when she grows up?
I love science so either sports science or nutritional science. That would be a lot of fun.
This was Sae who is radiant from all her hard work.