Here's Gackt!
Aren't you sleepy?
- Ah, because he doesn't sleep much.
Is it not a problem at all?
- I'm more energetic if I don't sleep.
Well I suppose you sure
are energetic now...
No he's not!
I mean comparatively...
- Then, when in your life have you ever...
thought "Man I slept well!" and how long was that?
Maybe about 3 days...
You slept for 3 days?
- I have.
That's like being in a temporary
state of death!
If you were like that for any longer, cotton
would have been stuck up your nose!
I'm glade you woke up on the third day.
You don't sleep that much either do you?
I don't sleep much either but
not as much as him!
Why don't you sleep?
- If I sleep for long I get a headache.
Man... you'r weak!
What the hell is that?
- I get headaches when I wake up after a long sleep.
I'm the same.
- So when you open your eyes,
you're like "My head hurts..."?
I wake up from the head aches.
So while sleeping you feel head aches and wake up?
Like "Uh, it HURTS!".
That's horrible.
Apparently he's training his body a lot now.
(can't catch exactly what he says, but he
doesn't seem to approve much)
Gaku-chan can do that thing... Jackie Chan push ups.
What's a Jackie Chan push up?
- This was just a randomly found,
recently among my group...
- You're totally intent on doing it!
Can I show it?
- Yeah show it.
You okay?
What's it like?
We just randomly started seeing if we could do this.
Well...it's like this.
Oh, that's impressive!
No way I can do it!
(Ma-chan do it!)
I JUST SAID I CAN'T DO IT!!
He clearly just said he can't do it!
I don't even feel like trying that!
Don't even feel like making
a fool of myself.
No way, impossible.
It's definitely going to hurt.
I was hoping that you would
Matsumoto-san.
Isn't there anything else?
This is a little to hard.
We do lots of things among the
members, just to see if we can do it.
We do this one often at the moment.
That would be hard too! Maybe you can
do a one handed push up?
Why is it always me doing everything?
I probably can't do it.
No way! This is going to be impossible!
Like this right?
No, no, no.
This is painful.
Why would you think of trying this?
Oh yeah, there's some talk that we
should have contest
as we haven't done one for a while.
Remember how you did it before?
And he couldn't win at all so...
What should we do?
Tell me something that you've
won at before.
I don't want to suggest something and
win, because it would be too easy.
What is there..?
Are you good at bowling Gak-chan?
Bowling?
I don't like the style of bowling.
This? (bowling movement)
You know how I always
wear black clothes?
Why the hell are bowling shoes white?
Well yeah, I suppose I haven't seen many
black bowling shoes before.
Just wear black ones then...
But they don't have any for rent!
They're always white...
Just buy them!
So they have to be black?
There already are black balls...
- No, the ball is black and I'm in black,
why is just this part white with some sort of blue stripe!?
Well I understand. Can you handle
the white bowling pins though?
That's okay.
- Eh? Why?
Because I've got nothing to do with it.
Oh because it's not
something you wear...
And it's pretty far so...
- Oh I get it.
Well we'll have a talk with the directors and arrange a black alleys and black pins.
If it's possible to have it pitch black.
- Oh if it's pitch black I'll do it.
Or better yet completely dark. (as in lightning)
Well we'll have a think about it...
- Alright then, the song's name?
Last Song.
This is a song released in December
last year rearranged acoustically.
You're reading it in monotone!