Wait, Yuta. Tuck in your shirt.
I'm off. I'll be home
today around 7:00.
Okay, have a nice day!
Thanks for waiting.
Were you here long?
Not long.
Shall we go?
Kodera
I'm home.
Oh, welcome home.
Is the bath heated?
Yeah.
You got home from work early.
Yeah, and your job must've run late.
It's the end of the month.
I've been running around
to meet my quota.
My hips can't take it.
Mix it thoroughly and then
spread it on the surface.
Sensei, I didn't come to work
here to do stuff like this.
After that, put this on top.
Are you listening to me?
What is that?
Seaweed boiled in soy sauce.
Seaweed boiled in soy sauce...
Yes.
It's just a theory of mine,
but side dishes that go well with rice
usually go well with bread, too.
This should only be eaten with rice.
This bread is topped with pickled
daikon radish slices.
That should be eaten with rice, as well.
Office Landlord:
Toyama Yoshie
You've got a lot free time, as usual.
Oh, Yoshie-san.
Please try my pickled bread.
No thanks.
I'm hungry, but not that hungry.
It's unexpectedly good, you know.
The word "unexpectedly"
does not inspire confidence.
How are you going to make
the monthly rent like this?
I'll have last month's for you soon.
By the way, it's actually
the month before last's.
What made you think you
didn't owe that one?
Is there work coming to this office?
Attorney:
Hakamada Yukio
Please don't worry.
We have a number of ongoing clients.
Right, Shinozuka-san?
Yes. One client.
Temp:
Shinozuka Rina
You've only got one,
so don't exaggerate.
Hey, Kanae-chan.
Hakamada's Assistant:
Nonomura Kanae
Yes?
You're gathering material for your
lawyer manga while you
work at this office, right?
Yes.
Can't you use the manga
to advertise the firm?
I don't have that kind
of authorization yet.
I have syndication, but I'm
still treated like a newbie.
How useless.
Seriously useless.
Um...
Hello.
Oh. Kodera-san.
I was waiting for you.
Please.
That's the ongoing client
he mentioned.
Her husband's cheating on her,
and she's considering compensation.
I see. She's pretty, isn't she?
I captured my husband
having an affair.
Client of this episode:
Kodera Kiyomi
Whoa...
Good job.
And thank you for this.
Iron Spy Woman
Marilyn
It had useful information, didn't it?
Private Investigator:
Umemoto Kurumi
If you need to know the rest of the
story, I'll let you borrow more.
I have all 108 episodes,
up to season 10.
No, thank you.
This should be ample evidence.
In all honesty, it's
incomprehensible to me.
Why would my husband be
attracted to a woman like that?
Excuse me a second.
You're right. She's plain.
You're way prettier.
How typical.
The partner in infidelity is usually
less attractive than the wife.
Men have low standards.
Especially men like this.
I also have this.
I took this in front of
that woman's home.
This is...
Double adultery!
She's married, and she has a child.
They look like a happy family
from the outside.
She should be happy enough.
Why would she cheat?
Speaking as a woman,
I can't understand it.
I cannot forgive this woman.
I understand...
Kiyomi-san, you know...
Compensation can be collected
from the mistress, too.
What?
Divorce Chaser
~Let's Turn Your Tears into Money~
Divorce Chaser Episode 2
Double Adultery! A Grueling Court Battle!!
Sorry. Were you here long?
Not at all.
You can be late tonight, right?
Yeah. I told him there's a mother's
meeting at the elementary school.
My wife said she'd be late, too.
We can take our time today.
I represent Kodera Kiyomi-san.
My name is Hakamada.
I'm his assistant, Nonomura Kanae.
Kiyomi's husband
Kodera Fumiya
Fumiya's lover
Togawa Yuko
Kiyomi's representative?
I'd like the two of
you to see something.
What is this?
They were taken last Friday.
Both of you have spouses, and yet...
you seem to be intimate
with one another.
As a representative,
let me ask you directly...
Were the two of you having
an illicit affair?
You're at a loss for words.
I'll ask you again.
The two of you...
Were you doing it?
Well...
We have a lot evidence.
I think you might as well own up to it.
We did it.
That's judicious of you.
No, we didn't.
What?
We're not having an illicit affair.
No, no, no matter how you look
at it, you went to a hotel...
I never went in any hotel.
We just had lunch at a place
in front of this hotel.
This is a hotel district.
Why would you have lunch—
He and I have been friends
since high school.
We discussed our family life. That's all.
If you don't admit it,
this will go to court.
We don't want to go to court.
I don't care.
What?
It will take time.
And attorney fees will
be nothing to sneeze at.
I don't need an attorney.
Hakamada Law Office
A trial?
Yes.
She won't admit to it.
There's no other choice.
Actually, I've been
struggling with something...
I don't know if it's right for me to be
compensated by the mistress.
I think it would hurt her
innocent child and husband.
But...
I will go along with it.
What?
Based on what you've told me,
I've made up my mind.
I'll fight it out in court.
But, if it goes to court,
won't that lessen the compensation?
Well... in most cases.
Then, we should bill the husband for
compensation. He confessed.
But she's the kind of woman
who lies and says she isn't cheating.
I won't be satisfied
until I crush her.
Let's calm down first.
Sensei, say something.
Understood.
I'll make preparations for the trial.
Sensei!
Please do.
Going forward, there's someone
you must have on your side.
Kiyomi. I am sorry.
You admit you cheated, then?
Yeah. I do.
I'm truly sorry.
How long has it been going on?
Since the class reunion last year.
Oh...
We were both in drama club.
We were just club mates at the time...
But, at the reunion, she said
she liked me and stuff...
I got carried away.
I'm really stupid.
Stupid! I'm stupid!
Don't torture yourself.
I understand your feelings.
Huh?
You always hear about affairs
that start at class reunions.
Don't worry.
I'm on your side.
No matter what.
Kiyomi.
Why must the husband be on her side?
He's a major culprit, a cheater!
Our opponent this time
is quite a conundrum.
In order for the court to accept
the fact of the adultery,
we need sound evidence.
Thus, it would be faster to question
the culprit of the illicit affair.
It would be more
convincing and real.
She's a housewife, so usually
we'd meet at noon on a workday.
It was convenient because I have to
make my rounds out of the office.
I see.
Most of the time, we went
to love hotels in Shibuya.
They have places that give
discounts during workdays.
What days are those, specifically?
Let's see...
Just a second.
I have a points card.
Hotel
Charlotte
So many...
Yeah. I have another one.
Sorry. That was insensitive of me.
No, you're helping me a lot.
Anything else?
Well...
There was a time their rooms were full.
It was only once, though!
In that room.
What?
But it was only once.
Oh.
Anger Anger Anger
Statement
They even did it in your home...
Hearing it made me nauseous.
I had no idea he was
that insensitive.
He's desperate to get
himself out of trouble.
Well, that's to our advantage.
Think of it this way:
Every word he speaks will turn into money.
I understand.
I will make preparations for the
hearing based on this statement.
My husband says he'll go to court, too.
He said he'll bear witness,
and do anything I ask.
Tell him you don't want him to.
Huh?
It happens often. The party in
question takes the stand,
has an emotional outburst,
and hurts the case.
I'm worried that's what
your husband might do.
That's true.
Aside from that, to have the
upper hand in the hearing,
there are two things I need
you to drag out of him.
What are they?
First, you have to make
him say, "I did wrong."
That will make it clear that Fumiya-san
and Yuko-san had an illicit affair.
How is that?
Sexless or infertile marriages
can be seen as an existing break
between husband and wife
and make it more difficult
to receive compensation.
We have to eliminate
all those arguments.
I see.
And the other thing which you have
to drag out of your husband...
He has to say, "My partner
was the instigator."
I'm sorry. I truly did wrong.
So you feel you've done wrong.
Yeah. I absolutely did wrong.
I absolutely did wrong.
You've always been supportive of me.
When things weren't
going well at my work,
you worked at home and
helped our finances.
When I got in the scooter accident,
you nursed me and never left my side.
I am truly grateful.
I'm your wife, it's only normal.
Kiyomi.
You and I haven't talked
like this in so long.
I feel like we're newlyweds again.
I know.
One final thing I'd like to know...
Did you instigate the affair?
What?
Well, that...
Did you?
No, she did.
Yuko's the one who suggested we
go to a hotel after the reunion.
I think she said, "let's get
together" more times than I did.
I see.
So, she instigated the affair.
That's right. She was the instigator.
She was the instigator.
I understand.
I think I've told you everything.
I'm glad you recollected everything.
Thanks.
I did it for you. Of course I would.
Something went wrong with me.
Sorry, okay?
Kiyomi.
Anyway, please sign here.
Oh, yes.
Isn't the husband saying, "she was
the instigator" his subjective opinion?
Yes.
It doesn't carry as much
weight as evidence.
What's the point, then?
Well...
Look forward to the hearing.
Court of Law
The first oral proceedings
I didn't think a case like this
would be held at district court.
Where did you think it would be held?
Since it's a domestic case, I thought it
would be at the domestic relations court.
A compensatory action between a married
couple can be held at domestic relations court,
Compensatory Lawsuit
Divorce suit between married couples → Domestic Relations Court
Compensatory lawsuit against guilty party in illicit affair → District Court
but when the guilty party is on
trial, it's held at district court.
I see.
Subsequently, on January 9th,
the two had a tryst
in room 502 of the Hotel Charlotte,
at which time they had their
second sexual encounter.
Lastly, to repeat,
every rendezvous they had was
instigated by the defendant,
as Fumiya-san has stated.
That is all.
She's quite worked up.
Wow, you're good.
That is...
not true.
I never seduced him, not once!
Fumiya-san seduced me every time.
Huh?
That's right.
I was forced to see him.
And he raped me!
Ra...
...pe?
Now, hold on a second...
Please stay calm, Kiyomi-san.
So, you were raped, and the
relationship was one-sided.
Yes.
Exactly.
Hakamada-sensei.
Why didn't you make a counterargument?
Actually, it was lucky
Yuko-san made that remark.
What?
It's not Yuko-san who we're
fighting. It's the judge.
What?
Who is lying?
Who's statement should be believed?
It's her word against ours.
Statements made in angry outbursts
make the judge suspicious.
So, in order to drag that out of her,
you purposefully made her mad by
revealing Fumiya-san's statement
about her being the aggressor?
This is getting interesting.
Please inform Fumiya-san
about what happened.
I raped her?
That's ridiculous!
Ah, wait a second.
Does this look like she's being forced?
Whoa...
So, Yuko-san is lying, correct?
Of course it's a lie.
Yuko was the lead in this play.
This cosplay was Yuko's idea, too.
Memories of our drama club
days came back to us...
and we got crazy hot with
each other that day.
Man, I'm mad.
I'm fighting back with all I've got.
I'll give you whatever evidence you need.
She has to pay for her offense,
through and through.
You're right.
Love hotel photos
These photos were taken on
June 8th at the Hotel Charlotte.
It is clear that they
went to the hotel,
The third oral proceedings
and then she dressed up in
a high school uniform,
and thereby engaged in illicit actions
by her own volition.
That is all.
I was being threatened.
Please elaborate.
After he raped me, he took
those pictures of me.
He said if I refused to see him again,
he would show the photos to my husband.
That is why I met with
Fumiya-san repeatedly.
That school uniform was also his idea.
Don't worry.
The more stories she tells,
the greater our advantage.
After all, she has no proof.
I have proof.
Huh?
Proof?
She does?
The audio recording I have here
is proof that he threatened me.
Come on, let's get started.
I don't want to. This is wrong.
Refuse all you want.
But what would your husband
say if he saw these pictures?
Please...
I can hand the photos out
to your neighbors, too.
Please, don't!
Then get on your knees like always.
Come on. Se—
That's right.
Indeed, I realize there was an
illicit action, the one time.
It was because I was taken by force.
He began making threats like this,
and he made me
meet him many times.
But, I never did it with
Fumiya-san willingly!
I was desperate to protect my family.
Does the plaintiff have a rebuttal?
Sensei.
May I have a copy of the audio recording?
Then get on your knees like always.
Come on. Se—
It gets cut off at the end.
I hear "se."
What word starts with "se"?
Maybe "sex"?
Are you sure that voice
is your husband's?
Yes. I'm sure.
Or maybe "kiss" (seppun).
If Fumiya-san did make
threats, what will happen?
Then it would be difficult to
get compensation from Yuko-san.
Only if it's true, that is.
I need for you to ascertain,
if in fact your husband
made the threats.
I will.
I know. It's "missionary position" (seijoi)!
Come on. Let's get started.
I don't want to. This is wrong.
Refuse all you want.
Hakamada-sensei.
But what would your husband say—
Did you go about this the right way?
Meaning?
You could've gotten a
much higher compensation
if you had charged the
husband from the outset.
And it wouldn't have gone to court.
Do you have a way to save Kiyomi-san?
I don't know.
What?
Every client has their own unique pain.
I won't need you any more today.
Good work.
Oh, Kanae-san.
Could it have been "missionary position"
(seijoi) after all?
Who knows?
What?
Of course I didn't threaten her.
I've already told you.
She was the instigator.
Are you into S&M?
You know me.
I prefer just the "M" part.
How interesting! Double adultery...
I love the grueling battle
between the two women.
This episode is based on the
current case at the law office.
In next week's episode,
Editor at Tokiwa Publishing:
Tabata Misato
the mistress is going
to get crushed, right?
Yes, that is what will happen.
Cafe waitress:
Mizutani Sara
I feel it.
That mistress will assuredly
receive divine punishment.
There is no mistake.
Well...
Huh? Is she wrong?
Am I wrong?
In the actual hearing,
there are some ambiguities.
I see...
And, yes. The protagonist lawyer.
Does he only take on divorce cases?
Yes, that's the premise.
According to this,
divorce lawyers don't get
paid much for all their work.
Why would he specialize
in this field?
Now that you mention it,
that's a good question...
That is a good question.
That's a good question.
Hakamada Law Office
I don't want to. This is wrong.
Refuse all you want.
But what would your husband
say if he saw these pictures?
Please...
I can hand the photos out
to your neighbors, too.
Please, don't!
All right, then get on
your knees like always.
Come on. Se—
"Se"...
You're so loud!
What time do you think it is?
Umemoto-san.
What are you doing here at this hour?
I got so bored,
I started watching the forbidden fifth season.
Of what?
"Iron Spy Woman Marilyn,"
the greatest series in history.
Watch one episode and
you're hooked to the end.
It's the forbidden fruit.
This is bad.
We're in a crisis here.
I'll take a rain check
on that cherry pie.
Oh. Can you make us some coffee?
Sure.
But same to you, Sensei.
Why are you here so late?
I was examining the audio recording evidence.
Oh yeah. That's the creepy
one I've been hearing.
In this drama-freak's opinion,
it's a bad script.
It's not scripted.
The situation was real.
Not a chance.
It's obvious they're reading lines.
The guy actor especially.
Does it sound that way to you?
A high school drama club
could do it better.
Drama club...
Excuse me.
Oh, Kiyomi-san.
Good morning.
Is Hakamada-sensei here?
He's not here yet.
I'll call him.
Hello, Sensei?
Where are you?
I'm doing a little research.
Kodera Kiyomi-san is at the office.
Hakamada-sensei.
I asked my husband about the threats.
How did it go?
He said he never made them.
May I have a copy of
the audio recording, too?
I'm going to let my husband hear it.
That won't be necessary.
What?
There are some things I need to
ascertain before the next hearing.
Court of Law
The fourth oral proceedings
This is the threatening
email Fumiya-san sent.
In 3,000 words he states
that he'll destroy my family
if I don't continue seeing him.
Your Honor.
Proceed.
Are you sure this email
was sent by Fumiya-san?
The sender's email is Fumiya-san's.
Understood.
Thank you very much.
Is that all?
Yes. It's more than enough.
Your Honor, if I may?
Proceed.
Can we replay the audio recording which
has been presented to the court?
Come on. Let's get started.
I don't want to. This is wrong.
Refuse all you want.
But what would your husband
say if he saw these pictures?
Please...
I can hand the photos out
to your neighbors, too.
Please, don't!
Then get on your knees like always.
Come on. Se—
Upon examination of the audio recording,
there was no sign of
fabrication or editing.
Clearly, the voices are those
of Fumiya-san and Yuko-san.
However, there is
something dubious about it.
Therefore, to clear my doubts,
I ask for the defendant's cooperation.
What?
Please read from this script.
Here.
Here goes.
Come on. Let's get started.
I don't want to. This is wrong.
Could you read it with more emotion?
You were active in high school
drama club, after all.
Come on.
Think of this place as the stage.
Let's go.
Come on, let's get started.
I don't want to. This is wrong.
Refuse all you want.
But what would your husband
say if he saw these photos?
Please...
I can hand the photos out
to your neighbors, too.
Please, don't.
All right, then get on
your knees like always.
Come on. Se—
All right, then get on
your knees like always.
Come on. Se—
...n-s-e-i.
Next.
"Sensei"?
Oh, happy day,
for the pompous sensei
to show his true colors.
My apologies.
I got carried away with the play.
This in fact is a script from
a high school drama club
Fumiya-san and Yuko-san were in.
After School Humiliation
I borrowed it from
Yuko-san's alma mater.
It's an erotic comedy tour de force,
in which high school students take
revenge on a spartan female teacher.
Quite a provocative scenario
for a high school drama club.
The dubious aspect is this.
Kazuya: "Come on, let's get started"
Yukie: "I don't want to, this is wrong."
The audio recording presented as
evidence and the script...
are absolutely identical.
Yuko-san and Fumiya-san were
high school classmates.
They were also in the drama club together.
According to Fumiya-san's statement,
conjuring their past
would make them hot.
Memories of our drama class
days came back to us...
and we got crazy hot with
each other that day.
The two of you had the script on hand...
and while recalling fond memories...
the two of you reenacted
the play, thus the audio.
That's not—
Listen, Yuko-san.
The audio recording and the
threatening email
can easily be proven false.
By the way, you will
be penalized for fraud,
for having fabricated evidence
to avoid a monetary lawsuit.
You'd be digging your own grave
if you were to persist any further.
We rest our case.
Court of Law
Judgment day
All rise!
Bow.
Be seated.
I will now render my verdict.
The court has decided that there
was indeed an illicit affair
between defendant, Togawa Yuko, and
plaintiff's husband, Kodeara Fumiya.
Hence, the defendant is ordered to
pay two million yen to the plaintiff.
All right!
You won, Kiyomi!
Hakamada-sensei.
Thank you for everything
you've done for me.
No.
You're the one had had to endure it.
For now, I'm relieved about
the judge's decision.
I didn't know what was going to happen
when she brought up the threats.
I wasn't worried at all.
It's more difficult to prove that
an adulterous affair did not happen.
The compensation fee
might have been less,
had she confessed to it from the outset.
Is that right?
If there was even a little confession,
the court might show mercy
and decrease the amount.
But Yuko-san destroyed
that chance, all by herself.
Good job, Kiyomi.
Darling.
Congratulations.
Did you see the look on Yuko's face?
It made me feel good.
But you only get two million
for all that work, huh?
You deserve more, don't you?
Please don't worry.
Kiyomi-san is due for more compensation.
Seriously?
How does that work?
I'm glad I cooperated.
I'm glad you had such a
fine attorney on your side.
Darling.
This is for you.
What's that?
Divorce agreement?
Divorce Agreement
I am divorcing you.
What?
Didn't I tell you?
I was going to divorce
you from the start.
So, darling.
Will you compensate me?
Compensate you?
Wait a second!
I cooperated with you.
Were you tricking me?
The nerve.
After all your cheating,
after all blaming
it all on the mistress,
after all the boasting you did
about the steamy details...
Did you think we could go
back to the way we were?
Here's the statement proving all
of your adulterous activities.
Statement
When the affair started.
The number of times of
physical relations.
You even stamped and signed it.
Not even a fine attorney of my
caliber could counter this.
Computing the compensation fee,
it comes out to three million.
That's about the size of it.
Three million?
This is a joke, right, Kiyomi?
Have mercy.
Wasn't it you who said that an offender
should pay for it,
through and through?
By the way, you can
pay it in installments.
Sensei, you were always going to make
the husband pay, too, weren't you?
It's the law, that if the
entire sum of the compensation
were taken from the
spouse's illicit partner,
we cannot sue the other party.
Then how were you able
to sue Fumiya-san?
If there is a divorce, then
compensation is higher.
Compensation for illicit affairs
Compensation is higher when there is a divorce.
I presented the case to
the court on the premise
that the couple are
not getting a divorce.
So I was able to sue Fumiya-san
for the difference.
3 million yen (compensation fee) - 2 million yen (Yuko's suit) = 1 million yen
Lawsuit to husband Fumiya
I hope Kiyomi-san was satisfied.
She got compensation from her
obnoxious husband and partner both.
I wonder about that.
What?
At least we got what we could.
Um, Sensei?
Yes?
Why are you a divorce lawyer?
Oh, the bread's ready.
It's pickles bread.
Try it fresh from the oven.
No, thank you.
But, you haven't had lunch!
Yes, but it's fine.
This one turned out especially good.
Really, I'm fine.
But, you should accept...
I'm fine!
Are you sure?
It's awful.
If I stay with him, I'll kill him.
Next episode
You can't even keep house properly.
You're the one who left me!
I won't give you a penny!
I won't allow it!
Divorce at Middle Age, After Compounded Suffering!
A Housewife's Scream of Agony!
I can finally divorce my husband.
This drama is a work of fiction.