Subtitles by: /u/CatZombies
Airdate: 2020-01-10
Well, let's hear today's final request.
Next up, Yasutomi Seiji-san, 42-years-old, from Osaka Prefecture.
A request from a self-employed person.
"In the room of my junior from our motorcycle group,
we've discovered a peculiar object."
"That is, hidden inside his bath unit's bathtub,
there's a photo album-like object."
"Perhaps the previous tenant hid it there, or
they forget it. We don't know, but
it's definitely hidden in a place where it can't be removed."
I see.
"Why was it hidden in this place?
Are these photos that they don't want to be seen, no matter what?
The mystery continues to deepen."
"In order to get this album out, would you lend me your skills?"
"Thank you very much." That's the request.
Didn't you think "Where is inside his bath unit's bathtub?"
This won't come out, no matter what they do.
They want to try to get it out.
That's really scary, isn't it?
This is really mysterious, huh.
That's right. That's why the request has come in.
Did we get the album out without incident?
Please take a look.
Right, why won't it come out?
Here? Ah!
So thin!
It's the last line piece in Tetris.
Ah!
Hello.
Eh? Yasutomi...
I'm Yasutomi.
Ah, the client.
And this is your junior?
Yes.
The person who lives here.
You're holding the cat?
Ah, so it doesn't get out.
Inside the bath unit, there's an album?
Does it count as inside? There's an inspection window.
Inside of that window, there's an album.
While he was inspecting it,
The plumber tried to take it out, but...
He said "Do you want me to remove it?"
"No matter what I do, I can't get it out."
It's smaller than the access panel.
No, no, no. It was put in there, so...
That's right.
This is it.
Eh!?
It's here. This access panel.
Oh!
Wait a minute. Where is it inside here?
Under this. It's under here.
Ok, well, how about you take a look?
Seriously? Seriously?
Wait, wait a minute. This is really hard to do.
Ah!
This?
This white thing?
That's it.
It's an album.
That it is.
That's definitely an album.
Eh? It can't come out of here?
It can't
It can't come out.
Give it a try.
It's an album. Without a doubt, it's an album.
It's coming out.
It won't come out.
Ah.
That's right.
Eh? I can't get it horizontal.
Ah!
Will it come out like this?
Ah~
Wow! It's really tricky to get out.
It won't come out.
Eh? You know what,
it being hidden gives the impression of it being dirty, right?
Dirty...
If you think about it normally, they'd be photos you'd want to hide.
Like photos of your adulterous lover.
I also think this is a bit of a strange phenomenon.
Eh?
Another one appeared, right?
That's right. There's another album since before.
Another album appeared.
Huh!?
There's another one stuck in there.
We thoroughly tried to get it. Really.
When we were both looking...
There's another album that wasn't there in the beginning...
It definitely wasn't there?
There was only the white one.
Only the one we saw before.
There's another one. I haven't seen that one yet.
Wait a minute. That's scary, scary, scary, scary.
Sorry, could you bring me my wallet?
I want to taste some salt.
I carry it around with me.
It's amazing you have that on hand...
That's suspicious!
It's not good if you have a white powder in your wallet.
Take this carefully, since it's salt.
Salt, right?
It's salt. Say it's salt!
Say it's salt, seriously.
It's really salt.
It's really salt, right?
Removing the albums.
It's there.
Ah...
This is it.
That's it. That's it.
Wow, it's really there.
Huh? What's written on it?
Natural Album is written on it.
How is it? Will it come out?
No, it seems to be the same size.
But that...
This is useless.
Can we break this up?
Is that no good? You rent, right?
I rent, so break it up is a bit...
To take all of this out,
it'll cost around $5,000 I'm told.
Eh~?
So, that's no good.
We're already paying too much for the new director.
How did it get there with this entrance?
There's one there.
And propped up is the one we first discovered.
How did this get in there?
There isn't anything like another access panel, right?
Like behind the mirror?
Isn't that really scary?
Oh!
Nothing.
This is?
I haven't seen that before.
Woah, it opens!
Isn't that an attic, basically?
What's going on?
There's something.
No way!?
There's something. Wait.
No way. What's there?
A Christmas tree.
What's this? You put it there?
I didn't put it there.
No! Scary, scary, scary!
Wait a minute, what's going on here?
I get it. I get it.
From up here, it went down like that.
Ah~
And then it probably was up here.
Hidden.
Yeah.
Then, an earthquake made it fall.
An earthquake or something. We don't know, but something made it fall back there.
So, we can get it out from here.
Nakade-kun, give me a hand.
Alright.
Thanks.
Rope fishing strategy.
Umm, where about?
Here goes.
Okay.
Got it.
You've got it?
Got it tied?
It's a little cramped.
Cramped?
You can't see anything from up here.
Try raising it now.
Okay.
Woah, it's really heavy.
Is that so?
I've got it! I've got it!
I've got it!
I have it!
I'm holding it.
The second album. The second one.
Is it coming?
Just a bit more.
Ah! That startled me.
That's startled me. My, oh my.
Why are you surprised?
You have "Natural"?
Alright!
Alright, we've got them.
What now?
If we could return them,
that'd be a good thing.
Looking for clues of the owner.
Let's open it.
Stand it up.
Oh.
Hmm.
There's something written.
Eh?
"On the way to Himeji Nagusa Waterfall"
"1995" is written.
A woman and a man. A couple, huh.
Probably so.
1995 is 24 years ago.
24 years ago.
Ah~ it's this person.
Do you know them?
No, no.
It's because this one's a close-up.
This is a close-up. The guy was a little far away there.
This is it.
These two are our protagonists.
They have a really good relationship.
These two have been to various places together.
Aw, they're so lovely.
Ah, so that's how it is.
They're kissing.
On the cheek, on the check, right.
This is a very nice album. Really.
Is this here?
Eh?
It's here!
Woah!
It really is.
I-i-it's here.
This is that veranda.
No doubt.
A name is written.
Hiro-chan. Jun-chan.
Wait, can we ask your landlord?
Hello?
Hello, excuse me.
The people who lived in the apartment...
Explaining the situation to the landlord.
When I bought the old apartment, right?
It must have been around 20 years ago now.
Around 20 years?
If they were a tenant since the time I bought it, I'd know.
During that time, did a person named Hiroshi and
a person named Jun live here?
As far as I know, they did not.
Not by that name.
None?
No one.
Ah~
Before you bought it, the previous owner
do you know where they are?
Calling the previous owner's workplace.
I'm calling.
Let's give it a shot.
"This is SoftBank."
"The phone number you have dialed is no longer in use."
"Please check the number and call again."
So, for as to why they went and hid it in that place,
perhaps they broke up and
a new girlfriend came along, so he hid this.
He forgot it, then left.
After that, it fell.
Couldn't that be the case?
How do I say this? Um...
I'm glad it was a happy item.
That's true.
Are you going to keep it?
Well, if I keep this...
Eh~?
It's not Hiro-chan, is it?
Did he come for it?
What's with that ending?
What was that!?
What was that ending?
The doorbell rang, right?
What's that face?
It was the delivery man.
We weren't able to contact them, so
we don't know anything else.
If they watch this, someone might say "that's me".
That's right. So if they want to,
the client's junior, Nakade-kun, is keeping it safe for them, so
it'd be nice if they came to get it.
Thank you very much.