Let's get started
Please welcome our first guest
It's Viking's Kotouge!
It's the real thing!
The real one
This time, I'm bringing you a yearly project
The 2022 Prank Ranking
That's great
It's that time of year again
Every year
The first one was you
-Yes
I did both 2014 and 2015
This is the ninth time this year
Have you ever been allowed to prank anyone?
I've done my share of screwing people over
There was a time during one prank
That I was the one pranking, but also being pranked
There is also this process
The feeling of being flipped when wrestling to make a four-figure leg lock
-A reversal
Yes, when I realized it I thought
You're the one who always gets screwed, so why are you screwing someone else?
Yeah
2022 Prank Ranking
First up, number 10
Gerardon's Attack Nishimoto with 7 times
That's a nice name
Next up are two with 8 times
Diane's Tsuda and Panther's Ogata
I thought there'd be more
Number 7 is
Nelsons Wada Bunch with 9 times
I do see him all the time
Next up is number 6
Joy with 10 times
Eh, why?
Since the beginning of the survey in 2014
He has appeared more than anyone else
Always in the top ten
The next three are tied
Yasuko, Nishkikoi's Hasegawa
And Oda
As the 2021 King of being pranked
He has failed to win a 2nd time in a row
Next up in 2nd place was
Nadal
It's true. I always see Nadal
He was at the top of the list in 2020 too
This time he's 2nd
What are you filming?
And then, in first place
The Mommy's Sakai with 21 times
Wow
A gap of 5 times with 2nd place
Sakai is 2022's King of Being Pranked
That's the result
In this group of funny people
What's the deal with Joy?
-It's impressive
What kind of pranks?
Don't remember
It's really awesome to be on the list with these guys
And he's been on the list 5 times so far
Yes, and at the top of the list
※Joy is synonymous with the word "top"
Did you just say "joy" as in "top"?
Hamada, you'll get penalized for that
Used the word "Joy" when saying "top"
There are so many words that can be used instead
So, one day in January
We reported the results to Sakai
Morning
For the year 2022, you are the person that has been pranked the most
Eh?
Really?
Have I been pranked so many times?
Something's wrong with this guy
But it's true, now that I think about it
I used to read scripts for hours without realizing they were just for a setup
So, as usual
Sakai will go through 7 pranks in one week
Will he notice?
A whole week of pranks
That means this year's "Prank King" is Sakai
Oh, is that so? Thank you
Well, saying thank you seems kind of lame
It would be a lie to say I'm looking forward to it
You should be able to find them all, right?
Because I get screwed over a lot
I think my sensors are still working just fine
We've got a few tricks up our sleeve for Sakai
It's January and the cicadas are chirping in Kagoshima
There's a shock on the doorknob that's not on the same order of magnitude as static electricity
You can tell, can't you?
The star of the moment's home is super small
Who knows?
The background of the Zoom conference looks synthesized, but it's actually a real view
That's interesting
The interviewer laughs his ass off no matter what is said
The number of words in the narrator's lines is clearly too many to say in the time available
But it does happen once in a while
The color of an old man's nipples in a hot spring is not something people can obtain
Not something people can obtain?
The camera will follow Sakai for a week
Throughout which he's subjected to the seven tricks
1 week later he will be asked to identify what happened to him
And state what was a prank
Will Sakai be able to get it all right?
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you
It's been a long week
I don't even feel alive anymore
Strange things have happened
There's been a sense of constant tension
So I think I've noticed a lot
You've guessed...
It should be fine
The first thing that Sakai considered to be a prank is
In an interview with a magazine
There was an older man who laughed at everything I said
An overreacting older man
Was it a fake laugh?
That's right
No matter what I said, he laughed, even if it wasn't funny
The best reception i've ever had
I think that guy is suspicious
Don't make it sound like a disaster
You've been popular lately
I've been busy
You've been gambling, have you?
On racing
Ah, racing
Doing the math, it's about five million dollars
5 million?
You made 5 million?
I lost 5 million dollars
Lossed, ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
No matter what The interviewer laughs his ass off
It'd make you angry
Right-handed steel ball, left-handed rowboat
-Ah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
That's awesome
Laughing super hard
I didn't say anything that funny either...
The guy's laughing so hard he's banging on the table
After circling Yoshimoto
I see
Now its come full circle
It's so exaggerated
We talked about H, the comedian
Scared
You're gonna break the table again.
-I'm sorry
It's not that funny
He ended up hitting it with a wet towel or something
I spilled my coffee
Sometimes you can't go because of covid
Fingernails are all curled up
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Are you okay?
I was wearing jeans
Got coffee on my new sneakers
My brand-new sneakers
I'm sorry
Wow, that's super hot
Are you okay with what you're drinking?
If this isn't a trick
I really can't forgive this guy
So I'm hoping this is a trick
So, Sakai got one right
Ahahahahahahahahahahahaha
Spilled coffee doesn't help
So annoying
I'm sure I would guess this was a trick
Sakai Thinks It Was a Trick
I'm confident in this too
There was a job to remake a sitcom from the past
My character was a marriage scammer at a shrimp farm
And was the star of that remake
How is that possible?
You think it's impossible?
-Absolutely impossible
I'm sure it's impossible
So many impossible things happened on the set
The cameraman was wearing the exact same clothes as someone else
The dresser gave me a different set of shoes
They weren't the same. They were from different manufacturers
I was thinking "this whole thing is a scam"
The whole thing is a prank
Sakai is referring to this sitcom remake
It's been on TBS World's Finest Mysteries for a while now
All the shrimp that were raised died...
So, it's no longer possible that he'll get everything right
So fast
Sakai Thinks It Was a Trick
The first time i've visited the neighborhood ramen store
I just moved in a little while ago
There was a guy was was supposedly the store manager
Super busy with all sorts of stuff
I said a bowl of ramen with soy sauce
He said, "Wait a minute. I'll come back later"
But then I looked around and realized I was the only customer
Furthermore
At 6:00 a.m., my intercom rang
The guy downstairs in my house told me
You had a fight with a woman yesterday, didn't you? A big one
But I wasn't even at home that night
And the next morning at 6:00 a.m., he rang again
You brought a girl home again, didn't you? You had a fight
I think it was a prank
This is a horror story, isn't it?
I always take my clothes to the coin laundry
Because I don't have a washing machine
I turned on the washing machine in the laundry room
And found some unrecognizable old man's clothes in there
It's disgusting, isn't it?
Not right at all
What kind of life does this guy have?
My new apartment
There was a pile of human shit under the mailbox
How does he know it was human?
Sakai has had so many amazing events in his neighborhood
5 consecutive wrong answers
That's amazing. A great life
Sakai Thinks It Was a Trick
Sakai, who only got one question right
Reveals the last trick
Someone said they wanted me to do a promotion for Tochigi Prefecture
Let me record the narration for the animation
Have you ever worked as a narrator?
Yeah, I've been called in as a narrator for the regular program
Your voice has great texture
I'm so glad you said that. Thank you
They told me to finish my lines before the scene changes
The lines that start in the middle of the scene can't be finished until the scene changes
Then read 01:07, 01:13.
-Okay
I'd like to recommend two places in Tochigi that you mustn't miss
First up, the three apes who are known for not looking, not talking, not listening
Okay. Thank you
So let's go to 01:19.
-Okay
First up, the three apes who are known for not looking, not talking, not listening
The famous three apes
It's a warning not to listen
Don't look at this!
Don't speak unless spoken to
Keep a straight mind...
I'm sorry please pause for a moment
Its a little slow
Thee most important part of the description was the middle
But he made me read it super fast
We can't finish this narration without reading it
Oh, yeah
I'm sorry. Read it again, please
Ok
First up, the three apes who are known for not looking, not talking, not listening
The famous three apes
It's a warning not to listen
Don't look
Don't speak unless spoken to
Keep a straight mind...
I'm sorry
Out of time
I'm sorry. It's a shame about this one
So close
Sorry, please try again
I'm sorry
First up, the three apes who are known for not looking, not talking, not listening
The famous three apes
It's a warning not to listen
Don't look
Don't speak unless spoken to
Keep a straight mind...
He did it
How was it?
Thank you
-Is that all right?
I read really fast
But the other guy said it was OK
So let's go to 01:30.
-Okay
That was fast
The second one is a sleeping cat. Sorry
That was fast... sorry!
Sorry I just feel like I'm reading too fast
Because your own voice feeds back
I laughed out loud when I heard myself read it so fast
哒哒哒一顿输出然后接下来是睡着的猫
That's the dish in the picture
That's a long line
Bean curd is a soy product, when you make soy milk
The film formed on the surface of soymilk when cooking is fished out and dried to form
Unlike the flatness of the Kyoto variation
It has existed since the Edo period
Sorry
This line has to be said before the interview
I don't think the instructions for the thing are necessary
Bean curd is a soy product, when you make soy milk
Know all about bean curd
The film formed on the surface of soymilk when cooking is fished out and dried to form
Unlike the flatness of the Kyoto variation
The tofus is rolled
It has existed since the Edo period
This one's gone again
Auntie's bean curd
So annoying
The guy at the store said to be sure to add this note
I see. There's no way to cut it down, is there?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
-It's okay. I'm trying. I'm sorry
Bean curd is a soy product, when you make soy milk
The film formed on the surface of soy milk when cooking is fished out and dried to form
Unlike the flatness of the Kyoto variation
This type is rolled into many layers
And is haracterized by roundness and fullness
It has existed since the Edo period
Thank you. Thank you very much.
-Is that all right?
That's a big help.
-Thanks.
He did it
Because the staff is very conscientious
I don't think I've ever done this kind of animation before
But, how to put it...
I wouldn't have been called in to record this, would I?
So the result is as follows
Only two of them were right
You got two correct
Two?
So little. Only two
Only two?
No way! No way! I don't want it to be true
Which one do you have the most confidence in?
Magazine interviews
That's right.
-That's great
That's what I'm talking about. That's suspicious
Eh, what else is there?
The one who complained that I'm noisy is a pain in the ass
The guy who complained about me was horrible
That we don't know
Don't know?
Neighbor Complaints
Is that true? Do I have to move?
I hate it when people like that live downstairs
You also guessed correctly about the narration
Ah, the narration
Indeed
It was really exaggerated at the end
This presentation is really just the tip of the iceberg
There are many other places in Nikko that I hope you will visit
One of the three most famous waterfalls in Japan
The 97-meter-high Huayan Falls
A stunning driving route with 48 curves
Iroha-zaka and other sightseeing routes connecting downtown Nikko with Lake Chuzenji and Oku Nikko
There's more?
So long
Awesome
Nakamiya Shrine of Nikko Futarayama Shrine in the center of Futarayama Honsha in Nikko City
You can visit quietly and slowly
Receive the mighty power of the God of Victory...
Seeing the spray was the point of failure
As soon as the screen changed and the fountain starts spraying I knew i'd failed
Nakamiya Shrine of Nikko Futarayama Shrine in the center of Futarayama Honsha in Nikko City
You can visit quietly and slowly
Receiving the mighty power of the God of Victory...
Water's coming out
The water squirted out and I felt like shit
I rerecorded it so many times
After telling the two correct answers
We revealed the ones he failed to get
How can this be ignored?
The five that Sakai ignored are revealed here
How can these be overlooked?
Nipples too?
Sakai San was born in Meguro-ku, Tokyo
Have you been to Kagoshima?
Kagoshima. I came here for a Youtube shoot
-I see
The cicadas! Is that so?
That type of prank?
Who could have known?
It's so nice. Kagoshima is so nice
There's something you can't see in Tokyo.
-Yes
And the cicadas are incredible
He heard it
Oh, it's winter, so is it weird that the cicadas are chirping?
I didn't even react when I heard it
Because I thought it was warm in Kagoshima
So the cicadas are still alive
That's what I thought
Thank you for your hard work
A beautiful background
Thank you for taking time out of your busy schedule
-You too
It doesn't look like it
In this special spring program
Awesome
I'm going to do a whistleblower investigation on show business seniors and juniors
He's not in front of a background, he's actually there?
The actual background
He's always been an active figure in comedy
Takes good care of his juniors
By the way, if you look closely at the background
There's a car coming through
It's not as if there aren't elements that can be detected
I see
That's awesome
No, I can't see it
You went to the spa in the meantime, didn't you?
Yea
The local elders were in
What color is it?
How can you say about this?
It doesn't seem impossible
This guy's nipples are too green
Indeed
This?
How could you possibly find out?
Yeah
Who's going to look at his nipples?
You might think it's a leaf that's stuck to it
You don't look at other people's nipples
Indeed
Well, that's a nice detail
Don't you remember the electricity?
What's going on? How can you ignore that?
That was a lot of electricity.A lot of electricity
This is obvious, isn't it?
It went all the way to the top of my head
But lately I've been wearing sweaters and down jackets and stuff
It's electrifying
There's always static
I thought that's what winter was all about
The last one is
Did you go to any celebrities' homes during this time?
Yes
How are you?
This is Sakai from The Mommy
Hello hello
That's not a good choice.
-It's a bit much
We went to Junichi Ishida's house
On a program called Treasure Hunt
Thank you. Wow, this is great
This is too much
It looks stylish
It's bad. They're bad
Well, that's great
The TV's so close, it's right in your face
Yeah, it's not that big
It's a fancy TV
I've been feeling so bad about it...
It was so narrow, it felt like the TV was this close
The TV is too close to the couch
The TV is huge, but it's so close
Can we go upstairs?
-Yes
Oh
Is this the bedroom?
Yes
Is this where the family rests?
Sort of
How many kids are in the house?
Three.
-Three
Barely sleeps four here
Mostly the kids just sleep here
That's ridiculous
Junichi Ishida's life is going well, isn't it?
That's a relief to hear
That means Sakai got two out of seven questions right.
-That's right
There's not much to go on
What do you think?
Instead, his personal life is a little more difficult
Maybe it's like this
There's feces and stuff
The pranks were good
But Ishida's part was a bit sad.
-It's a bit sad
There's a problem with the selection
This is a horrible program
Such bullies
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
It's FUJIWARA's Fujimoto!
Now that I'm here, you all know what's going on
Eh, it's over, right?
-Yes, it is
Yeah, late last year's smash hit, MONSTER LOVE
Is the last kiss still lingering in everyone's mind?
I remember the kissing scene and the sound
The hourglass necklaces? I want one of those. I did a search
It takes about a month to restock
Yeah, they're selling like hotcakes.
-Really?
No, but... you want it?
Why would you want that?
It was the talk of the town
The couple, Kuro-chan and Richi
What's their life been like since then?
We've got a video, guys
If it's too long, I can't bear it
Why?
If it's too long... shorter is better!
-It's true
This is the second segment today, Right? Is there a third one?
-No
No! It's gonna be long!
"No."
What's going on?
No! It's so long!
The day before the Monster Love Finale
Delicious
I'm sorry I called you before work
We're really seeing too much of each other
-Yeah, right
I just saw you two days ago
I saw you three days ago
I've seen you too many times. I'll see you tomorrow, too
Good friend
What do you mean?
-Today
You'll know all about it after MONSTER LOVE airs tomorrow
Ah, yes
The finale
You know
There's someone I'd like to introduce to you today
Wait a minute
What's going on here?
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. No, no, no
The day before it aired
What's that look? It's a very angry look
Then I'll bring them here
So nervous...
Wait a minute
Hey, are you serious?
-Wait a minute
That look
Didn't expect this at all
Here we go
Kept you waiting
Nice to meet you, I'm Richi
I know you...
Well, this is my girlfriend
Girlfriendy~
Really? Really... wait a minute
Really?
I'm seeing her. I'm seeing her
Really? It's not a lie?
Super emotional!
It's not a lie
I'm sorry I kept you in the dark. I'm seeing her
You were with me on your birthday!
It's true. All three of them are crying
Eh, really?
Thank you. Thank you. Please take care of this monster
Not a monster, human being!
I'm sorry. I can't breathe
Must be super happy
Is it really okay?
What're you saying!?
I just want Kuro-chan
With such a cute girl?
This will never happen again!
Seriously, what's so great about him?
Everything
Look past all the gross parts he has a good heart
-Gross?
Wait, I'm really...really impressed
I thought you were going to be alone for the rest of your life
I didn't think it was possible for you to be this happy
You're the first one I wanted to tell
This development is totally confusing
An outrageous statement
Next for this person
Excuse me
Dancho
Ah, hello
First meeting
It doesn't feel like the first meeting because I've been watching you on TV
So little response.
-What are you eating?
Indeed
This is my girlfriend Richi
Before the final installment
My girlfriendy, I got her!
Is it ok?
What do you mean is it ok?
Socially
What do you mean socially?
What do you like about him?
Everything
That's what everyone's asking
Just say one
Just one...
Saying everything is too sneaky
What do you mean by sneaky?
I think he's the funniest guy in the world
He's not that funny
Why?
I really wish you'd come to that live show the other day
It was super unfunny
-No it wasn't!
This guy gets cold feet and then exaggerates and yells, "Don't-"
It was a bad audience, really
But yeah
I don't know if I should say
He's got a girlfriend, hasn't he?
Hiro seems to have gotten a girlfriend too.
-Eh?
Wow
Don't lie to me. Its impossible for a guy like that
That's why it's Double Happy
It's not Double Happy. Don't bundle me in with him
I haven't heard anything
Hiro is a monster
What's wrong with that?
Also, they met two good friends
Who?
Nice to meet you
Not necessary, right?
Eh, wait a minute
You don't have to show this part, do you?
It's my girlfriendy~
We're dating.
-Really?
We're been seeing each other~
It's true
I've found my baby
Wait a minute. I have tears in my eyes
Why are you crying?
Everybody's crying
Really?
Cool it
-What?
Surprised
-Surprised?
Give me a kiss
They're in public
Don't. It's disgusting
This is a parallel world, right?
It's real~
So boring
While introducing Richi to people I know
I think I forgot the most important thing
My parents
Very true
Indeed
So filthy
What is this picture?
Hello?
Mother
What's the matter?
There's someone I want to introduce to Mom, so I'll put her on the phone
Eh?
Nice to meet you
I'm dating Kuro-chan
My name is RICHI, nice to meet you
Ah~ Is it really okay?
Really, he's a great guy. I like him a lot
Thank you
It's nice of you to say you like him
What do you mean, "It's nice of you to say you like him"?
Thank you
-I'm so happy
Mom, don't forget to watch the show
Downtown is scary. I don't want to watch it
I'll see you later.
-No, Mum
You always watch the same stuff
Really, don't do anything that will make her cry
Ok
Good luck
I'll try not to make her cry
Okay, over
End with "over"?
Mom, thank you. Good night
Okay. Good night
I'll be happy.
-Ok
So nervous...
Nervous?
Uh-huh
We should get in touch with your mom and dad
What's going to happen?
What are you doing now?
Well, there's someone I'd like to introduce to Mom
Bit worried
Ok i'll listen
Is that all right?
Ah, now I'm on the phone
I'm sorry to call so suddenly
Uh, I'm Yasuda Dai Circus...
Oh, i'm Kurokawa... Kurokawa Akihito
That. I'm sorry
Which one is it?
The daughter you raised with so much hard work
Keep making her cry
Did a lot of...
Ah, yes. I'm sorry
Crying every episode, yes
That, yes
I really will cherish her
I'll arrange to have dinner with you soon
Does Mum have any favorites?
You like meat?
I know a great place
A nice conversation
I'm sorry to call you so late
I'm sorry, i'll pass you back to your daughter
How's it going?
Pretty normal
Nice guy? That's great
Ok, I'm hanging up
Richi is very natural
Introduced my boyfriend to my parents for the first time
So nervous. I'm still nervous. I couldn't talk properly
It's a great day
I've told everyone
What a day
Its been great
It's on. It's on, Richi
Watching together
It's on! It's on! It's on!
Ah, Michopa
Wah!
Tasted Miku's hand
Genius.
-Genius?
That's not exactly genius, is it?
Richi, i've got something right here
What kind of genius is this?
Get it off for me
What's with this guy?
Did you get it?
Why don't you watch the program instead?
Tasted Richi's hand.
-Ah, I love it
Great!
Watch the show!
I got it
Richi tastes better
Miku tastes awful
This guy
-What are you talking about?
I mean it. I mean it
That was awesome. That was very moving
Moved?
-Yes
A classic scene
I've never said anything like this before
Crying
Richi is also crying
Here we go
Don't, don't!
Everyone's screaming!
The tongue is disgusting
Stop screaming
It's a show of love. It's a show of love
I want to kiss
What a mess
Watch the program!
Don't do this!
Wow, it's the same, they synchronized
Ok
So happy
Kissing while watching your own kissing footage
Its novel
-It's awesome
The back of two kissing Kuro-chan's heads
It's like a picture within a picture
You guys, you're forgetting one more thing, aren't you?
The idol group Richi quit, Tonai Boushou (Somewhere in Tokyo)
There's more to come, isn't there?
It doesn't matter
Really? Go somewhere else
You can't just watch the video
There's more?
More?
So long
Kuro-chan's in love...
No~
Double, double ready...
It's too long~
We have to support them
It's enough
Let's have a cigarette
Why? Why are you taking a break?
I've been clean for years, but I'm gonna smoke
Is it that bad?
Merry Christmas
It came out.
-That's great!
You really don't know how to clean up
Merry Christmas
Cheers!
She's no good either
Ah, this is delicious
Won't clean up
Tasty
I'm starting
Ah, that looks so good
Yummy!
-Yummy
Really, this guy
The more I see of this guy, the more he pisses me off
Such a happy Christmas
Yeah
Why don't you clean up your room?
So happy
Let's make a lot of memories together
I baked cookies
Eh? Really? No way!
Scary
I thought you never cooked
Well, I don't, but i'm trying
Miku taught me how to bake cookies
What is Miku up to?
Crushed cookies
Indeed
She said "I want to make good memories with cookies"
Well, can I smash them again?
No you can't
I wont, I'm just kidding
Eat
Eh, that's great. That's really great
You're kidding. You broke it
Ah, I am truly loved
I can keep watching this
The end of the year brought Richi's last job as an idol
Countdown TV New Year's Eve Program
A three-person team
Yeah
Thank you for your hard work
It's finally over
Richi is no longer a member
It's kind of hard to believe. Wait a minute
It's been three people every day
I can't believe it yet
No!
It doesn't feel real. It's not real, is it?
It's over
It's over... you worked hard
Thank you
You're the ones who made me an idol
Right
Last time
Really is
You shouldn't be going up and down like that
If you only I didn't fall in love with Kuro-chan
So, we hope you'll be happy as Kuro-chan's girlfriend
Okay, thanks
Be happy.
-I'll be happy
And so Richi's life as an idol end
And the recruitment for a new member begins
For which over 1,000 resumes were received
So, Watanabe, the head of WACK, the company in charge, and Kuro-chan reviewed the materials
Leading to the first round of selection of 100 cleared candidates
How many people do you want to add in?
How many people are good? I'd like to wait until after the selection process
Thank you for attending the auditions
I'm Kuro-chan. He's Watanabe
So, first of all
Please introduce yourself and state why you want to join
And sing a song that you're good at
Then please begin
Sunglasses? Sunglasses?
Awesome
I didn't have a good relationship with my parents growing up
So i've always wanted to be an idol
Why are you wearing sunglasses?
-Do people still wear sunglasses to auditions?
I've said it since I was in elementary school
But I ended up being laughed at
But my parents laughed at me the most for what I wanted to do
That's why I cut them off yesterday
Eh?
A lot has happened, but i'm here today
So heavy
One verse, please
Underestimating the business, isn't she?
By the way, what does Riko look like with her glasses off?
I'll take off my glasses. Here we go
Not bad. But also cute with glasses
But also a beautiful girl with glasses off.
-Thank you
I kinda like the girl with the glasses
You work as a caregiver, right?
Yes, I'm a caregiver
Let me give you an analogy
If I cry, can you show me how you'll stop me?
Ok
What?
Kuro-chan, what's wrong? What's going on?
My toys were taken
Ah, your toys were taken?
I see. Then I'll give you a new toy
What kind of toy?
Bubu toys
What's a "bubu"?
Bubu's a car. Have you ever been in one?
I've never been in one. It's scary
Then let's sit together. It's not scary when you're with me, right?
I won't cry anymore
Really? That's great
Thank you
From that point
How old are you?
6 years old
Six years old?
Is it okay?
Ah, Kuro-chan, long time no see
I think you've forgotten about me
"Long time no see"?
We've had dinner together about five times
Also went to karaoke
Eh, with me?
But Kuro-chan was respectful and didn't try to hit on me
Didn't make a move?
Eh, wait a minute. Five times?
We had okonomiyaki at BochiBochi in Ebisu
And went to Shibuya to play darts
Then back to Kuro-chan's place
Serious dating
Eh, we went there?
No, i'd usually play darts after going to BochiBochi...
Gold package?
And then take someone home, right?
Trying to do it, right?
Must have been tempted at the time...
So, these 10 made the first cut
Successfully shortlisted for the second selection
Out of 1,000 people, 10 stood out
There are 10 people left
How are you going to screen them?
For today, I'd like to keep half of them, five of them
Select five
Then decide
I'm sorry
Can I ask you to sing?
-Yes
Can we stop for a second?
Can you sing more popular tracks?
What to do...
What do you think?
She's a good singer
A good singer
Seems kinda good...
But didn't stand out very much
Judging seriously
I'm 16 years old, I'm a freshman in high school, and my name is Izuki
Senior year, you're still young
Can you put your hair back?
-Yes
A real audition
Your face is so small
Thank you
Like a little bean
-Thanks
What a comparison
Can I ask, are you wearing something underneath?
Yes
Of course she is!
No... I just wasn't sure
Thought you wanted a challenge today
It doesn't matter either way
Longer hair
What does it look like tied back?
It's like this
That's just the way he likes it
Uh-huh. Very cute, very cute
Beauty queen, right?
No no
That's up to me
Why are you so angry?
Shimada
It's not a panty check
Giant's Sadaharu Oh
What'll it be like?
Imitating him
Its the wrong way!
Its like that
So, i'll announce the results of the second selection
First is...
Chihiro, congratulations!
Great
In second place
Sachiko, congratulations
Izuki, congratulations
Nozomi, congratulations
Shimada
No, don't say that
Kino, congratulations
So these five made it to the final stage
Which of them will become the newest member?
So, the decision will be made at a later date
Plus there will be some footage of Richi and Kuro-chan's New Years holiday
Look forward to it
So reluctant!
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03