Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Harisenbon
In the past there was a verification
Will tsukkomi comedian's say "You're gonna sing it?"
-Yes
Situations were created to encourage them to say "you're gonna sing it?"
We verified it with 5 people
Only FUJIWARA's Fujimoto said it
Ah really?
-Is that so?
Mr. "You're gonna sing it?" Hamada...
-No, no, no...
I can't believe you didn't say anything.
-Well, I really wouldn't
That was a bit shocking
-It was really shocking
He's usually quick to attack
-No, no, no
This is it
Because of this, it is necessary to bet on the reputation of spiteful comedians
So, we bring a new spin on this
Like "you're gonna sing it?" tsukkomi comedians will retort regardless of the situation
I hope they'll do it
-Hopefully
Really hope
For the boke you can't really tsukkomi either
It's impossible
It's like trying to open your mouth with the sides shut
I can't do it
No, no, no...your analogy is too much
Awful, ~Deep kiss~
Aren't you resisting a bit too much?
Next, will they really say "you're gonna XXX?"
It'll be verified in different contexts
Also...
If you can't take it, get out
Discouragement contest for mild-mannered entertainers
Also, is it true that comedians regularly receive memorable and creepy fan letters
Like "you're gonna sing it?" tsukkomi comedians will retort regardless of the situation
In the previous "You're gonna sing it?" verification
You're gonna sing it!?
Fujimoto was the only one who reacted as expected
These were the results
Indeed
This time, we created 5 scenarios other than singing to conduct a similar verification
The first target is
Hashimoto
Last time
He failed to retort
What is the phrase he is expected to say this time?
"You're gonna eat it?"
The setting is a sushi restaurant
The person making the sushi will suddenly eat it after presenting it
What will happen?
This happening in private would be pretty scary
How do you know about this place?
Feels so high-class
They first have some appetizers
Singapore seems like a hot place
Seems so
Is it okay to just wear sunscreen there?
Uh, yeah...
Are you still in touch with your previous girlfriend?
No contact at all
Don't you want to get in touch again or something like that? Could you?
Talking about career and love as if they were OLs, during the the middle of their conversation...
Finally, it's time for sushi!
Will Hashimoto say "you're gonna eat it?"
Hard to say
Here is the snapper
-Thank you
You'd be shocked, right?
The same as last time!
He couldn't tsukkomi
This is very difficult, its too surprising, right?
Here is the snapper
-Thank you
Taste test...
Is it because I'm a comedian that he's playing with me a bit?
Still doesn't understand the situation
As there was no immediate retort, it seems he's not aware its a prank
So, we continue to verify
Squid
A little frightened
Great! Great!
Start from squid, great!
I thought it was a trick. Scary
White shrimp
It's squid.
-And shrimp?
We let him eat two rounds to relax
Sashimi
Master...
What's going on?
After that, this occurs one in three rounds
Wait...
No, no, wait...
As a result, he's unable to say anything
So, we disclosed the truth
That's no good
Wait... that's enough
His face is red
Brain... his brain is sick, right?
What the hell?
Do you know what the program is?
The only one who would do such a thing is that show, right?
Something like "you're gonna sing it?"
Tsukkomi comedians will tsukkomi in any situation
This isn't normal
In this kind of high-end restaurant, no one would do it
Its too confusing for it to be taken away
But I thought maybe that was just his style
You wouldn't say "you're gonna sing it", but how about something similar?
In front of the camera and in ordinary daily life
It's a completely different story
I don't live my life like i'm constantly on Wednesday Downtown
So, acknowledging the comments made
Next we decide to conduct an on-camera verification
The next target is
Komoto
Although he is not the tsukkomi of his group
He often takes such a role on variety shows
The key word for this challenge is
"You're gonna kick it?"
In a fake soccer show
The referee will suddenly kick the ball
Will Komoto say "you're gonna kick it?"
Let's go everyone!
15 minutes into the game
Komoto is fouled
And has a chance to take a free kick
Clever setup
What a serious expression!
Not a comedian right now
Scatter a bit, you're too bunched together
So serious, feels as if he'll be angry
He is on camera after all
Doesn't understand
Couldn't say it
Who could?
Nice goal!
The truth is revealed
Why do you keep playing soccer like nothing happened?
Unbelievable things have happened!
Not stopping?
Hey, it's not right, it's not right
Thank you for your hard work
We wanted to see if you'd say "you're gonna kick it?"
Its not something to say in this situation
So, the next target is
Jinnai Tomonori
This one is reliable
What is the situation this time that will encourage him to say "you're gonna do it?"
Art Star Discovery Center
In this fabricated show
Hiking Walking is a guest
I will drink the coke and hold back my burps
While saying the station names of the Yamanote Line loop in one breath
In this setup
The female host will burp instead
It should be easy to say in this situation, right?
The result?
To say it to a woman though...
I mostly drink ten bottles a day
This one's gonna be funny
This gets laughs in the theatre
He'll say it, right?
He's not in "off" mode
Tokyo
Araracho
Shinbashi
You're gonna burp?
Awesome!
As expected of Jinnai
He did it
Shinbashi
You're gonna burp?
What's going on?
Wait. Wait a minute. Hey?
You burped too, so sloppy!
What a slob. Who was it?
Here we reveal the truth
What a quick response!
Thank you for your hard work
As expected
Eh?
Thank you for your hard work
We wanted to see if you'd say "you're gonna burp?"
Oh, eh?
I didn't say it on purpose, it was a reflex
If this was real it'd be bad
I really said it by accident
So, the next target is
Toshikazu Miura
What is the situation this time that will encourage him to say "you're gonna do it?"
A flash mob marriage proposal
This time there will be a flash mob of women sitting on chairs in this open square
The propsal will be made by
A seemingly unconnected person
So, the "surprise proposal" has begun
I'm Toshio
As you can see, the fake show is shot from the beginning
Then, on site
Music seems very appropriate
Without further ado, the flash mob starts
Ah, here we go
Not bad. Which one is the boyfriend? Not here yet?
At this point, Toshio is watching in the car
And the scene suddenly shifts at the end
He will witness the moment first hand
You still don't understand the situation, do you?
Hasn't figured it out yet
Thinking "what's this? It's great"
Oh, the number of people has increased
Where's the boyfriend? Hasn't made an appearance yet?
Such a long lead up
Then at this point
Boyfriend-type
Finally someone with the aura of an important person comes into view
So
Ah this one? Boyfriend? This is the guy, right?
Toshio is led correctly
So, the verification is setup perfectly
At the moment when the flash mob was approaching its climax
The scene comes to its conclusion
Why do I feel so nervous?
Hello
So embarrassing
Good afternoon
Must think it is the right person
The result?
Hmm?
Wait...
No...
Eh?
Couldn't say it
Eh...
I will make you happy all your life
Is it this one?
Please marry me
Ok
Eh? Is it supposed to be this guy?
Hang on
Hey hey hey
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
I'm so confused
Eh? Is he your boyfriend?
Yes, he is.
-He's your boyfriend?
It's you?
Eh...
Not you? No, no, wait
Hey!
Really?
Questioning him non-stop
Hooo—
No, it's not the time to make a scene
It's not the time to make a scene
No, no... this...
Congratulations to both of you!
I thought he was the boyfriend
I was watching him the whole time
It turned out to be you, right?
Although he made some comments
He didn't say "you're gonna do it?"
Difficult
So, we reveal the truth
Thank you for your hard work
So close. What happened?
This is Wednesday Downtown
Eh, really?
Wednesday Downtown?
Just this?
What is this... what is it?
Is it a test of some theory?
-Yes
If you're a tsukkomi, you'll say "you're gonna do it?"
Ah, a test of whether you'll do it or not
Whether you'll do it straight away
No, no, this is too...
The word "you!?" was stuck in my throat
But I wasn't sure whether it was ok or not...
Eh~
I want to do it again...
I really wanna hit them with it without thinking
"You're gonna do it?" like that
The last target is
Viking's Kotouge
The key word is
You're gonna jump?
When bungee jumping, after the countdown
The staff will jump instead
You'd think it was an accident
Really would
Hello, I'm Viking's Kotouge
What a beautiful day!
Recording on a sunny day
As you can see, a fake program was used to take Kotouge to Gunma Prefecture
To ensure he doesn't realize, we shoot him wandering outside for 1 hour
He's doing it very seriously
Tasty
Next is the famous thing in Minakami-cho, the bungee jump
Eh~
No no...
I don't want to! It's awful!
When you are young, you are not afraid of this sort of thing
As I get older, I get more and more afraid
Starting to get scared now
Since I became an old man i've become afraid
A very noticeable emotional plunge
We won't actually make Kotouge jump
But we still lead him to the 42m high bungee jumping platform
Whoooo
I can't do this, I can't jump!
So scary, I can't do this
It's a no go
Bungee is a no go
I really can't do this
This is really impossible
As Kotouge is gripped by fear
The final useless preparations are made
Can you stand up?
Oh wow this is really impossible
Ah so scary, oh, wow
So scary!
Finally, it's time to bungee jump
That... although I can
But this is the last time
Last bungee
Will Kotogue say "you're gonna jump?"
So, let's get started
Countdown
10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3
Whoa!
You'd react like that
Simply not the time to comment
His reaction is the same as if he jumped down himself
This is more like an accident
Jumped yourself
Eventually, he commented
However, it's not "you're gonna jump?"
Its too abnormal
Jumped yourself
So, we revealed the truth
Thank you for your hard work
Wed?
-Correct
It was Wed all along...
If you're a tsukkomi, you'd immediately say "you're gonna jump?"
No way no way
Absolutely no way
No way
Looks so happy
No, no, no, no
No way I can say "you're gonna jump?"
The fear is way too dominant
If I was in a more normal mental state
Maybe i'd say it
On this occasion i'm just engulfed by fear
It's impossible to say it
Now I know I don't have to jump
I'm super happy!
My voice has gotten louder too
In summary
It's hard to say
Unfortunately only one person did it
What do you think, would you be able to say it?
At the bungee place, no way
You'd think someone has just died
Only extreme people like Jinnai and Fujimoto would say it
Normal people wont, just these two abnormal ones
But out of all of them Jinnai's worse the most boring
That... please do not say that directly
Who could say such a thing?
If it was me i'd surely say it
Looking at each of those I kept thinking i'd say it
I keep thinking, "I'd say it if I were you!"
That is, all five? All of them?
I was thinking "Again I would've said it!"
I want to see it
Let's welcome the next presenter
Knights
I'm so sorry
What's going on?
A towel was thrown at me by Kobori
That's enough!
We haven't even gotten over that yet
So impactful
But also thanks to the program team
The number of customers at the Toyokan has increased.
-Is it true?
Yes, more young people are going
That's great.
-Great
It's improved the scene
A little bit of self-hatred can make the audience laugh
Awesome.
-But their relationship hasn't changed for the better?
The relationship is still bad, but there are laughs
Kyomaru and Kyouhei, who are very close to each other, aren't getting any laughs
Don't make jokes like that
We thank them for their appearance
This time we bring a theory about "lecturing"
-I'm scared
Have teachers and seniors at school ever said this to you?
"If you don't want to work then get out"
In fact, even if someone tells you to get lost
There's no way you'll actually walk away, right?
It's true that you wouldn't leave
"Get out" actually means "don't go"
That's true
So this time we bring the following theory
Will anyone ever follow the "get out" statement included in a lecture?
Got it
-That's what you'd think, right?
"Get lost", "get out of here" etc
And "Do you know why I am angry?"
Obon loves to say that
When it comes to screwing people over
-You're really almost done
No mention of a disbandment at all, but just angry
Is it going to be replayed again?
We are not here to replay it
We've brought a new theory
Will anyone ever follow the "get out" statement included in a lecture?
This time, we asked four artists who are kind and not angry types
Competition who can use the shortest time to force back the whole target
Lecture Elimination Contest
The first challenger is
Nana Suzuki
She's not the angry type
Good morning
-Good morning
The junior about to be lectured is
What to drink, what to drink
Nishino Miki
I have a simple question
Very puzzled
-What's wrong?
After doing a number one in the toilet, do you wipe from the front or back
What is she talking about?
From the back.
-Yes, from the back
I am also from the back
Will anyone do it from the front?
I've called about 10 people and asked them
Nine people from the back, one from the front
It's hard to imagine that this is a lunchtime girls' gossip
In the midst of a heated conversation
It's finally time for Nana Suzuki, who has never been angry with her juniors, to lecture
But I think you are quite powerful, you're often on TV
Working hard
But actually not
I also often search myself online
-Really?
I search a lot
The search results for Nishino Miki are all "super similar to Suzuki Nana"
"Super similar" or something like that
It's starting to get a little scary
This really makes me stressed out
Ah, stress?
Body movements too
I hope you won't talk like that again
No way... you mean me?
She asks the other to change her persona
This far-fetched excuse is used to start the lecture
I often gesture a lot when I speak
It's what i'm known for
So I hope that when you are on TV in the future
Don't make hand gestures
So scary
It's scary to be told that
It's painful, isn't it?
Don't...
Nishino is hesitant to let her claim this privilege which is not a privilege
Next time you're on TV, don't make hand gestures
And don't let people say you look like Suzuki Nana. Can you do that?
Well...
Is there an answer for this?
It is very difficult
But... I don't do it purposely
If you don't understand what I mean you can leave now
That... I can't leave
Scary enough
But you don't understand me at all!
-No, I understand everything
Sitting still is also a bit difficult to do
At this point, the first "get out" is sent out a little early
Is she proficient
Seems like she's used to it
But the junior Nishino will not go so easily
If you don't understand, get out!
Get out now
How can I change it?
Feels like she has a lot of anger
I will try...
Just wear handcuffs on TV, isn't that good?
Wearing handcuffs on TV...
That way you can't make gestures
Hand gestures are not possible
Amazing
But then I won't get screentime
It's true that it can't be broadcast
I really did not mean to imitate you
Just unconsciously
No hand gestures now either
Ah, sorry
No hand gestures allowed
Yes
Now go or get handcuffed
Go or get handcuffed?
At this point, the ultimate choice of "leaving" or "handcuffs" is presented
Not moving at all
Staring blankly!
What to do?
-No, no, no
Go or handcuffs
Next, a silent showdown
She lasted so long
It's been five minutes
Super scary
Okay, I'll go
Seriously, go
Really, go now
-Ok
Wait, really?
Are you okay?
It's scary, right?
Get out of here!
-That...
Awful!
Scary as hell!
Way too scary
It's really too scary, Nana-chan...
-It's awful
Get the hell out of here!
Get out of here!
So, Suzuki Nana ended at 6 minutes and 24 seconds
Here we revealed the truth
Poor thing
Why's she escaping?
What's up?
We're on the same side
Nishino, who hadn't fully understood the situation, returned to Suzuki's side
What's going on?
Really scared me.
-Why?
I thought i'd been cursed
Possessed by an evil spirit
It's fake, not real
I thought that if I left, we would never see each other again
Goodbye forever
So happy. Thank you
Great!
I'm really scared to death
Still afraid
Real feelings
The next target is
Viking's Nishimura
Confident?
How can I say it? I am a person who
First of all, I don't lecture juniors
Never get angry either
By the way, have you ever been told to "get out"?
I have before
When was it?
A manager gave me his card
When I was given it I said "ok, i'll pay with this"
Then I put four or five rounds on the card
The next day, after he found out, I was told to get out
Did you really leave?
-I left
The kind of man who will walk away on demand
Can he get others to flee or not?
A public performance
can get 50,000 or 60,000 at that time.
-Great
But that's about it. It's only on occasion
Before King of Conte I got 40,000 at most
Ah, i've taken over then
They tentatively have a casual conversation
One pork hot pot, please
Is it for two people?
-Yes
Ok then
After the clerk leaves, the lecture begins
What did you order?
Ordered hot pot
Hot pot?
Is this ok?
Yes
No way, why would you be angry about this?
Hot pot?
Yes...
Clearly heard it at the time
How many servings?
For two
Are you looking down on me?
Why?
Too weird
With the Hot pot order as the first issue
Nishimura devises a fascinating setting
A taste minefield
You can't get it right!
This...
You should understand!
You just don't get it
-I'm sorry
It sucks
Enough, you can go for today
I'm sorry
Here the "get out" is launched
It's impossible, right?
Sorry
All right, just get out
Did you order hot pot?
-Yes, I did
Then get out of here.
-I'm sorry
It's too uninspiring
You have to eat alone if he leaves
Sorry
I think this is more balanced
What the hell is hot pot, you!
Sukiyaki is more like it
Why order hot pot?
It's impossible to order hot pot normally
Hot pot...sorry
-Get out
I'm sorry, I was wrong
Please don't make me go
No, you're really off the mark
It's obviously you, right?
This is the Achilles heel of comedians
What kind of hot pot did you order?
It should be Sukiyaki!
The correct answer is neither hot pot nor sukiyaki
But the off-the-mark Nishimura is at least interesting as a comedian
Even so
What are the vegetables in sukiyaki and hot pot?
First, Sukiyaki
Chrysanthemum
-Mmmm
Cabbage
-Mmm
Carrot
Konjaku
-Konjaku is not a vegetable
You should really get out of here
Why can't you read out the vegetables in sukiyaki?
There are many more
Onion
Uh-huh. Onions are perfect.
-Yes
You should really get out of here.
-Sorry, sorry
Sincerely get out!
You can't even tell me the ingredients of sukiyaki, you're not even close to being good enough.
-I'm sorry
Sukiyaki has much higher status than shabu-shabu
-Yes
I'll remember
Why don't you just get out?
Seriously, really need to get out of here.
-Okay
If you don't understand this...
-I'll go
What can I do?
-Sorry, this guy won't leave
Please get him out of here
-Shall I make him go away?
Sorry, I'll leave now
Miss, I'm sorry. It's okay
Miss, please take him out
Get him out of here
I'll go by myself. It's fine
You should really get out of here.
-I'm sorry. I get it
Get the hell out of here!
-I'm so sorry
Using the rough trick of getting the staff's help
Nishimura achieves success after 12 minutes 38 seconds
Don't cause others trouble!
The next challenger is
Panther's Ogata
The target is
Ah, it's Takashi
Just the two of us?
Trendy Angel's Takashi
As the presenter you should have done it yourselves
But after watching the VTR just now
For authenticity, Obon Kobon would be better
Get out!
Get out of here!
It's happened!
Next is Panther's Ogata
But
I've never met an Ogata fan
That's not right, there are some
Ogata fans don't exist, right?
-They do
He mistakenly chose a junior who is used to messing around
Making it difficult to start the lecture
However, after an hour, finally
My child. You held her when you came to my house
Didn't you feel her up?
So disgusting!
When holding her
That's disgusting
I just held her normally
So you did!
A bad vibe
Due to struggling to find a point to lecture on
Ogata becomes angry for no reason
Impressive
Your persona is that type
I hope you can pay attention to how you make contact
Not listening at all
But everyone would do it in this way
-They wouldn't!
Okay, okay, get out
I'll leave later
It's not a matter of a when
I told you to go now.
-In a bit
What? Are you t underestimating me? Sitting their vaping
I am now really angry
Sorry
Saying sorry but still smoking?
No smoking
You get out of here, I'm really in a bad mood
But after that
No drinking
You are completely ignoring me
I am 41 years old, how old are you?
How old are you?  -33
33 years old
You're not taking me seriously
No drinking
I'm 8 years older than you
But I was born earlier in the month
-That has nothing to do with anything, okay!?
The idiotic conversation went on like this for more than 15 minutes
And Takashi eventually stands up out of boredom
Bored
Sorry
Sorry for what? I can't forgive you
Get out of here now!
The final challenger is
DJ KOO
Today you'll be lecturing
Do you usually get angry?
I'm not very loud...loud... lou-
You already know the content, right?
Curry? The case of the curry department?
Do it properly!
The lecture is given at the Avex-Management Academy
To Hama, a junior who starred with KOO
Many new projects will be held in 2019
Special events
Have you written down a few of your ideas?
Is it written on paper?
Idea list
I didn't write it down
-Why? What happened?
Wait, wait, wait, wait a little bit!
Wait a second
You...
-Yes
If you don't want to do it, don't do it
Don't do it
You can leave today
Sorry, you can go now
A sudden increase in horsepower smoothly leads to the request
A perfect transition
Suddenly so scary
However
For example, what do you think about the curry scene in the future
Scene?
The scene of curry. Tell me about it from your point of view
Curry scene?
-The curry scene
Similar to the "music scene" and "hip-hop scene"
It's already very popular
The curry department should make the atmosphere hotter
-Yeah
What are you talking about?
Where did the momentum go?
The unaccustomed lecturing suddenly cools down
I often go to Shimokitazawa Curry Music Festival
Shimokitazawa Curry Music Festival...
Very popular now
Taking notes
More stores than in Jimbocho
There are more than one hundred
This is what I want you to write about
He's too focused on this meeting of the curry department
What do you mean "this"?
Seems to have completely forgotten the "get out" thing
Even more so than
Prepare for the start of the show 3-2-1
What is this?
To the point of being completely unintelligible
So, we revealed the truth at this point
Didn't say "get out" at all
KOO
Did you forget to say "get out"?
Ah, I see
In conclusion, the winner of the lecture contest is Nana Suzuki
What do you think?
The Suzuki Nana part is too shocking
A little too scary
Quite impressive
This kind of person being angry
They really emit a different kind of terror
It's really shocking
Is that an act? I can't help but feel that she's actually like that
Scary indeed
To sum up, the lecture in the...
That's pretty impressive. All kinds of things happened
Very scary stuff
I also hope that Obon Kobon will continue to work hard
Get out of here!
Sorry, I can't get out
It's all over for you. Just go. It's over
Sorry, I can't go
So scary
What a horrible exit
That's it. Thank you all
Now is everybody's theories
Tonight's presenter is
Kenji Tamura
As stars, you must have all received letters from our fans, right?
Are there any letters that are particularly impressive?
What have you received Naomi?
A letter written about dating me
That we're in a relationship
Although long-distant, he made a lot of effort
Very daring
He would call me and say he was sorry and all that
He's delusional, right?
He was carrying out this series of activities by delusions of grandeur
And also say "I really want to see you"
"But we can't see each other because of Yoshimoto's rules."
So scary
It was like that
Have you received any strange things in the mail along with fan letters?
I once received a seemingly ordinary letter
It says "I'd like to be by your side to support you, but I can't."
"That's why I'm giving it this you as my stand-in"
Then sent a clay doll over
The thing that guards the dead
That should be placed around the deceased
I thought I was still alive and well
So, today I bring a theory about fan letters
Please take a look
Comedians receive memorable and creepy fan letters
I see
We just talked about a lot of creepy things just now
Do you have any experiences of this? Being in the idol industry
Because the firm checks everything in advance
If it contains strange things...
It will be checked in advance.
-Yes
For example, if an address is written on it, they'll cut it out
Or use markers to black it out, etc
So I haven't experienced this sort of thing
Ok, so this time we asked people from all walks of life
And the only one with the least stringent inspection system was that of comedians
They just get random gifts
They're delivered in the same way
They send anything to us
I also received a letter that was so thick that it was strange
Comedians receive memorable and creepy fan letters
Creepy fan letter ①
Cookie
You're the creepiest, right?
What impressed me the most was
About 3~4 years after debuting
There was a girl who was so short it was hilarious
So rude
She was a brunette with hair like a doll
The appearance was really like a Japanese doll
But with normal clothes on
The girl appeared suddenly
She often came to see my show
She had folded a thousand paper cranes
She handed me a thousand paper cranes with a red wabi-sabi design
Then he said to me, "Please take it"
I then received a thousand paper cranes
When I got home, I unfolded them
Restored the paper to its original state
On the reverse side of the pattern, in small letters, it read
"I hope you will like me", written all over it
A fan letter in the form of a thousand paper cranes
You know how some people can write characters on a grain of rice? It was like that
Must've used a super fine pen
Creepy fan letter ②
Kamaitachi's Yamauchi
I received a postcard
I was told that "I have a fan letter for you"
On the front, it said "To Kenji Yamauchi"
Then on the back, "I've been watching your show on TV"
"I support you from the bottom of my heart and look forward to hearing from you if I can."
"I'll be looking forward to hearing from you," it read
But the name on the front
"Kenji Yamauchi" was written on a separate piece of paper
I was curious about the extra bit of paper
So I carefully pulled it off
Underneath, it said "To Oguri Shun"
I thought, "Why'd you give up and compromise by sending it elsewhere?"
"This person is too determined to give up"
A letter from a determined fan
You'd think she'd at least rewrite it for me
Creepy fan letter ③
Viking's Kotouge
Sent by a man?
Well, it was sent by a male fan
He would wait for us at the exit after each performance
The fan letter was written on about 7 sheets of letterheaded paper
"Kotouge's comedy is the source of my life and vitality"
The "Hearing your lines is like being caressed by lightning all over your body" kind of thing
Used language like a novel
Then with another 3 sheets of paper
"I can't believe I just wrote 7 sheets."
He wrote an apology letter
Which was also included and sent in
He came to every show for about 4~5 years
An emotional and apologetic fan letter
He works in an eel shop
How do you know that?
At the end of the letter, he wrote the address and phone number of an eel shop
And his own cell phone number, email address and LINE ID
He was desperately trying to convey his personal information to me
Then once, on a day off
I thought I'd go to this eel store
It took about three and a half hours to drive there
It was already late afternoon when I reached it
I went in and found that this guy was not in because he had gone to dinner
Then about a month later there was a show again
I got another letter
After reading it, I found there was a letter and something else
He put his work schedule in there
Why do I have to work around your schedule!?
Rest days other than the regular Monday holidays
Every time since then, the duty roster of that eel store has been put in the letter as a matter of course
Creepy fan letter ④
Hiroshi
A house schematic
A layout of 2LDK was placed inside
※LDK indicates the layout of the house "L" stands for living room "D" stands for dining room "K" stands for kitchen 2LDK means two rooms and one bathroom
A letter was in there, too, and it said
"I rented this house to live in with Hiroshi"
"I've already arranged a guarantor"
Their signature and seal was on it too
Then it said "All that's left is Hiroshi's signature and seal"
I haven't even met her
A fan letter describing having taken the liberty of finding a home for the both of them
This is very similar to Naomi's
And it also said "Please pay the rent every month"
Creepy fan letter ⑤
Audrey's Kasuga
How can I put it? What I always see is
"I will visit you at a certain time on a certain day in a certain month, please wait for me at that time."
His address was leaked
I also get these fan letters that want to control my schedule
I also received a lot of fan mail directly at my home
Don't you get scared when this happens?
Usually'd be scared
But they're kind enough to warn me in advance
I see
But once there was no warning at all and I came home to find someone waiting for me
For Kasuga whose address was public
How long have you been living here?
Not only fan letters, but also gifts were also sent to his home
When I had a cold
I had a lot of things piled up in front of my house, condolences and so on
It made me feel like I was dying
I felt like "i'm not dead yet!"
Bouquet of flowers, drinks, and so on
In the middle of that was a refrigerated box
I thought "what is this?" and opened it
There was some porridge inside
A refrigerator full of porridge
That's awful
And
Another thing was placed in front of my house
Like a garbage bag, something big
I thought "it's another prank or something"
I grabbed the garbage bag and tried to remove it
Then a hand suddenly grabbed me from below
Inside the garbage bag...
There was a woman
A woman?
A surprise appearance from a garbage bag
I tried not to react too strongly
I said "can you get out of the way?"
The person said "ok, ok fine" etc
She probably thought i'd be a little more exaggerated
Creepy fan letter ⑥
Nonstyle's Inoue
There was a letter full of how much the person liked me
This dumb guy
Then she said, "The students in my class don't know what's good about Inoue."
"That's why I'm always talking about Inoue during break time or after school."
"I desperately explained to the entire class, including the teacher" something like that
Then I suddenly saw the next page which read
"After doing so, I was gradually bullied by everyone."
Fan letter expressing bullying
Poor thing
Creepy fan letter (7)
Higashibukuro
I had a scandal in the second half of 2013
Fans were almost reduced to 0
Basically just one person waiting for me at the exit during that time
She gave me a letter
But after reading it
"Even with a scandal like that, I have a way to redeem you."
Wrote something like
"Ask someone for guidance, and your past will be cleansed."
"The only way to purify all this is to enter this religion."
And then they were persistently trying to persuade me to join the church
What did she look like?
Really short and with a doll's haircut
Fan letter to strongly persuade others using mind tricks
Is it the same person as the previous one?
This picture is reused
Creepy fan letter ⑧
Really?
Ungirls' Tanaka
No way
I said something like I have 100 million in savings on a TV show
Got fan letters like "Can you lend me 2 million"
Fan letter with Tanaka's cash in mind
What were they going to do with the 2 million?
It seems like a lot has happened
"I have 2 million in debts"
"I cant live and pay the interest"
So I need to pay back 2 million first
I want to pay all the debts together
Ten it said, "I will belong to Tanaka"
Three letters have been sent from the same person
The third letter had the repayment plan written on it
40,000 per month
It'd take a little over 5 years to pay back the money
If they paid back 40,000 a month
They also wanted an extra 10,000 for themselves
Said it should be possible with your salary
Said they wanted to go to various places to play
Want to learn English conversation
You should forget English conversation for the moment
Shouldn't the extra 10,000 be returned to me as well?
Should pay me back 50,000 a month
Surely too naive
Finally
Creepy fan letter ⑨
Egashira 2:50
20 years ago in the first month I checked the mailbox in front of my house
Inside was a New Year's card
Then I looked at the reverse side
It read "Happy New Year"
It was written in pubic hair!
New Year's greeting card with a pubic hair
If it was a woman it'd be okay but it was a man so I feel super disgusted
In summary
That's about the extent of what can be said on TV
What is this?
What do you mean it's okay if it was a woman?
Why?
But there are really ones that want to borrow money
The private messages on the social media have a bunch of these
Want to borrow money from you?
Loads!
You also get them?
Yes
Not really anymore
But there used to be from time to time
I did lend some
It's a lie, right?
Don't start!
Because of the silence so you must be lying
So obvious
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03