Today's presenter is...
It's Tamura Kenji!
Nah, you're messing around aren't you?
Yes?
What do you mean "messing around"?
It sucks when you make a joke and it's not funny.
What do you think Uchida-san?
What do you think of my hair Uchida-san?
It's like uhm...
You look like a mafia boss.
You're joking right?! You can't be serious!
That'll get you assassinated!
For your summer holidays...
...Matsumoto, what did you do?
I went to Hawaii.
How lovely!
I have money, so yeah...
It's not good to say that!
Your likability will go down!
This time we have the perfect theory for summer holidays at the beach.
People buried in the sand at the beach have no choice but to accept being questioned for an interview.
Are you preaching?
They can't just run away!
We have done many interviews with random people in the city.
But people often say "I have work", or "I'm in a hurry" and refuse.
These people have all the time in the world.
They can't move!
They can't even use their hands.
They're completely restrained.
After this, we conduct our investigation at the beach.
Today we investigate the theory: People buried in the sand at the beach have no choice but to accept being interviewed.
We find ourselves in Shonan, with many people coming to enjoy the beach.
Just as we get started...
...we find the first buried person of the day.
Staff: Do you have some time right now?
Yup, no problem.
As expected, he accepted the interview.
Staff: Who are you with today?
Umm...we kind of became friends out of nowhere.
You're saying it's a group date.
It's not a group date.
Staff: Did you pick them up?
They picked me up.
It was a reverse pick up.
It was not a reverse pick-up!
Right?
Next is this slightly scary-looking group.
Will they accept our interview?
Staff: Do you have a bit of time right now?
Yes.
Staff: An interview is ok?
These guys also accepted our interview without any issues.
Staff: We were actually looking for people being buried.
There are a few over there.
But if we were to compare, ours is at a higher level.
For some reason there is a rivalry with the neighbors.
So naturally we went over to talk to the other group.
Staff: By the way, there's a guy being buried right next to you.
Considering the number of people we have, I think we're winning.
Staff: So are you thinking about them a little bit?
Yes.
This group's competitive spirit was also sparked.
Staff: They're starting to compete.
As a result of both side's attacks...
...the burials have escalated on both sides.
And then...
Staff: Can we have a moment?
You made it out alive!
Staff: Which one do you like?
I mean, one of them is pretty flat.
The other one is big.
Staff: The one in white?
If I were to choose one...
What's going on?
The bigger one.
The one in white.
Staff: Are you a virgin?
I am a virgin.
What's that all about?!
So off-topic!
Looking beyond the virgin, there was a suspicious mountain of sand.
Staff: Excuse me...
Staff: Do you have a bit of time?
Yes.
Staff: You were looking over here, right?
I was looking, yeah.
Staff: Did you bury him after seeing us?
Yes.
They were just a few attention-seeking high schoolers.
So we ignored them.
Behind them, after seeing the TV crew...
...this group quickly starts digging.
Many people at the beach just want to be on TV.
We came aross some high-quality burials.
Could it be that they buried him vertically?
Staff: Do you have a minute?
Yes, no problem.
This guy said ok too.
Furthermore...
Staff: Do you have a minute?
Ah...um... well... sure.
Staff: You have some time right now?
Not a problem.
Staff: Do you have a minute?
Sure.
Every interview we did was ok.
It's a couple.
Wait, the girlfriend is...
what is she doing?!
She's only touching
him there!
Next...
What was that cut
just now?!
Staff: Excuse me...
Staff: Do you have a bit of time right now?
Sure.
Staff: What country are you from?
We came from Vietnam.
Staff: In Vietnam, do you bury people in the beach like this?
Yes, it's quite common.
Staff: Right here...
Staff: ...the waves are looking quite dangerous. Aren't you scared?
It's not dangerous, everything is ok.
I think it's ok.
Japan is safe, it's ok.
Japan is safe, so being buried next to the ocean is no problem.
Next...
Staff: Excuse me.
Staff: Do you have a minute?
Yes...no problem.
Staff: How old are you?
I'm 20.
Staff: Are you a student?
I'm a student.
Friend: He's Aomori.
I'm from Aomori Prefecture.
Staff: What are your thoughts on this beach in Tokyo?
It's amazing.
Aomori does't compare to this.
Staff: Do you have a message for your parents in Aomori?
Dad and mom - are you doing well?
I have been doing very well.
We've found the trickiest burial of the day.
Staff: Excuse me.
Staff: We're with Wednesday Downtown.
Staff: Do you have a minute?
He can't hear you.
Staff: EXCUSE ME...
Staff: CAN WE HAVE A BIT OF YOUR TIME?
No...I'm in pain.
Staff: It's not "I'm in pain", can we have a bit of your time?
My eyes hurt.
In conclusion, people buried in sand at the beach will accept an interview if their ears aren't covered.
Ah, so that's how it is.