Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let's get on with our first presenter please
Please welcome FUJIWARA!
Hello everyone, we are comedians
-Welcome
We are a comedian combo, thanks for having us
-It's a combo!
This time we bring you the second instance of a five-year-old theory
The theory is this:
The 2nd "You won't realize something is your own possession if its in the hands of someone else"
Here it is!
It has been done before
There are many copycats of this theory on youtube
-Really?
Yes, quite a few
Must have good reviews
Then its possible that our program is the one copying it
Possibly, possibly, this program could do such a thing
No one will find out if we copy something anyway
So then,
Will the subject notice the items have been taken out of their house?
Huh?
And
Verify that all comedians have their own "Asakusa Kid"
Once again, we will verify whether or not people can tell items are theirs when they are in the hands of others
So, with the assistance of their managers
The personal belongings of the subject are taken from their home
And presented to them in different scenarios
Semi-thief behavior now
The first target is
Morita
Good morning
Fake meetings are set up to test the targets
The first items are set up in this cafe
Recently, Morita moved into this 2LDK apartment
In the living room is a poster of Muhammad Ali
Just saw it
Seems easy to spot
However, it was hard to notice because it was behind him
During conversation, the topic of interior decoration comes up
The poster seems to match this cafe's style
A framed photo ... I did buy one
Ah he's spotted it
He's noticed it
Ah, this one
Huh?
You don't think it's your own, do you?
It's this one
Yes, it is
-Just seems like a coincidence
I recently bought this one
Ali?
-I recently bought it
Yes, this one of Ali
Mine is probably a little bigger
No, no, it's the same it's the same
Shameful
-Feels different in different spaces, right?
Bigger than this one?
-Bigger than this
Yeah, at home it seems bigger
Muhammad Ali
-Yeah, this
There is obviously no subtle difference in size
In short, Morita did not realize the item was his own
The next item is a sofa
That's bold!
I'm most interested in furniture, especially furniture stores
It's integration into the environment is too good
Since I moved place I thought I'd buy a load of new stuff
There's sofas and ...
-How much did the sofa cost?
Sofa... uh, I think ah about 400,000
What's a 400,000 sofa like?
Actually it's nothing special, doesn't look very high grade or anything
It's a corduroy sofa
Just like that one over there, pretty much the same
It's huge!
Is that one corduroy?
It's really similar to this
Doesn't it just feel like his own home?
Its not the kind of thing that looks very high grade
Not very extravagantly made
Hasn't realized it's exactly the same
They bought a similar sofa
Similar
Having your home and a new trendy place like this set up the same feels really good
Didn't realize
Although it looks exactly the same,
He fails to think "The items are actually exactly the same"
After that, he ignores the mannequin placed at the entrance
The store owner and I really have the same taste
Later on, a fake gourmet report
It's not too late, let's go in and take a look
Inside...
Hello
I'm Morita, thanks very much for having me
T-shirt...
It'll get oily, so annoying
-It's going to smell
And then,
So you like American casual too?
Yeah, although I don't only wear American casual
I also like to buy vintage stuff
Yeah yeah yeah, I actually have the exact same t-shirt
Really?
-Yeah
Is this vintage?
-Yes, it is
The same, exactly the same, really, probably
The fumes are so annoying!
Really alike
Even so, he still didn't realize it's his own possession
So, we set an even bolder trap next
The pork face and beef tongue is tossed with soy sauce
An individual dressed entirely in Morita's clothes
Liver and diaphragm are flavored with miso
Welcome, one?
Full body
Please sit here
So they're open for business!
And...
It's pretty crowded
A couple dressed in Morita's clothes
A girl too?
Awesome
Two new customers
Morita finally begins to awaken due to an unmistakeable feeling of familiarity
However, after that too
Still no reaction?
More female customers dressed in Morita's clothes
Way too many people!
Girls
This store is so popular!
-Yes
Excuse me, here is your potato salad, please enjoy your meal
Ok
A response so cold that one wouldn't think he was on location for a food review
And then,
Regulars who like American casual...
So many!
We all know each other pretty well
-Yeah seems like it
Welcome
A whole group of guests resembles Morita
Please sterilize over here. Three of you, right? Please sit here
Can't take anymore
They're all American casual...
That's not the point
Faced with such an unusual situation, Morita's state no longer reflects that of an on-location shoot
Here we add the tenth person
American casual again
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Give me a minute. Hey, what the hell is this?
Realized
I have all the same ones, hey!
Thus, the truth is revealed
What is this, seriously!?
No, you guys almost got... ah
It's all mine!
They're all wearing my clothes
"You won't realize something is your own possession if its in the hands of someone else"
No, no... if you say so, I guess
I only realized because you did it to this extent
Which of these clothes is the most expensive?
That, that, that
-How much is it?
110,000
So old and expensive?
What did you do before this?
Before coming here?
-Yes
I had a meeting before coming here
The Muhammad Ali poster!
Ah ah ah ah
Ah, sofa!?
From my home!
It is indeed unexpectedly difficult to realize
But anyway, all of you get out of here!
Don't suck up the fumes in here
Don't let my American casual absorb the smell here
The next target is...
Good morning, Sakai here
Good morning, I'm TBS' announcer Yasumi
Will Sakai realize?
This time the stage is a thrift store
The store is currently selling a lot of Sakai's personal items
Can he realize?
After all, there are many items around
Not long after the shooting started,
Eh? There's have CUTRATE stuff
Eh? Just 100? Really?
I have the exact same thing
-The exact same thing?
When I bought it it was expensive
This is even cheaper than in the Philippines
Next...
Eh?
I think I also have this
You have this at home too?
-Eh? Yeah...
Being faced with a prepared product that is very much to his taste
The Switch is so cheap!
Sakai becomes very excited
Seriously?
All the things I like!
-It's great
Next, in the appliances section,
Sakai's TV and refrigerator have been placed
Even this is for sale?
-Impressive
This... seems
Isn't that what this is? It's...
Ahhhhh, this is it!
And,
AQUOS, ah!
Eh? It's so cheap!
I bought it for about 80,000
-Eh?
Still hasn't realized
I should've come here first
Should just moved into the store and live here
Actually, Sakai just moved from his hometown in December of last year
King of Conte
This time, we took advantage of his absence and removed all of the belongings
So messed up
A big project!
And put them up for sale in the various sections of the thrift store
Wow, there's a bed!
How is it?
Wait a minute.
It's about time to realize
Eh？
This is too similar
Is it similar to yours?
-Yes
But it's not possible!
It's true that it can't be exactly the same
-Yes
Safe
Next,
They also sell teeth
-Wow so disgusting
What's this?
What's going on here?
Although this item seems unexplainable
These are actually Sakai's baby teeth from his home
Baby teeth?
-Who the hell knows?
Who would be impressed by this?
Teeth
I want these teeth
It's someones personal belonging, right?
-Yes
You want to buy the teeth?
-I want it
Unbelievably, he buys it without realizing it's his own teeth
He won't realize?
-So interesting
This must be a global first
Purchasing your own milk teeth
Lastly, the clothing area
About half of the clothes hanging on the shelves here belong to Sakai
Surely he'll realize now
Wow, so stylish!
Eh? Eh?
What is it?
-Eh?
Huh?
Am I at home?
What's the matter, Sakai?
You can't be at home
Eh？
Why do I have the impression that I have all of these?
Gross...
I bought this for, like, 60,000
But it can't be the exact same thing...
The size is also the same
-The size is appropriate?
He pulled something out?
Red LARK, that's what I smoke...
Even the cigarettes are the same?
Why'd you put it in the pocket anyway
This is too much of a coincidence
It seems that you and the previous owner have the same interests
This kind of thing...
Even the cigarettes you smoke are the same, right?
Can such a thing happen?
Unfinished cigarettes in the pocket?
Actually took it out
But I don't think it's possible that it is yours...
Yes, yes, indeed
But... the apartment I moved into has a lot of bad people around
You mean someone stole from you...?
If that's the case, it's too gross
But isn't it strange that it would be sold here?
Sakai realizes he may have been the victim of a crime
Finally, we added more significant items
That is...
A 20-year-old sweatshirt autographed by Ogura Yuko
I see
And then,
He is particularly fond of Yuko
What's going through his mind
What's up?
Really...really?
What's going on?
What is it, Sakai? Do you like Yuko?
You like her?
Isn't that good?
Good isn't... it's not good
Eh? Why?
Eh? Why is it here?
How much is it?
-2400
I don't get it, this is a bit scary... I'll buy this one first
No, this is your own
Buy... I bought... I don't get it
Sakai falls into a state of confusion and begins pacing back and forth
Scary scary scary!
Where is this store located?
It's in Ayase
Ayase, right? In Adachi...
Adachi...
What's wrong?
Does it matter where you are?
No... Adachi....
No, it's not, how should I... eh?
Not good
-Don't say what you shouldn't say
This kind of thing also happens, right?
It'd be strange if it did
This is not what businesses in Adachi do
And so, the imagination begins to flood the brain with negative thoughts
Just in case, Sakai purchased back all the clothes he could with the cash he had on hand
Yep, I bought a load of stuff
All of this only cost 9,000
So cheap!
An hour later...
You couldn't not be scared
-Completely empty
Eh？
One hour after the end of the on-location shoot
You couldn't not be scared
-Completely empty
Eh？
Eh?
Scary!
-Scary!
Nothing...
Eh?
Eh? What's going on?
This is my house, right?
How would you have gotten in?
Faced with this radical change,
Sakai doesn't seem to be convinced that this is his place
Thought you were in the wrong house?
So scary
What's going on?
Huh?
Haaah...
Oh, no. Is he okay?
-Sitting down
Eh? There's nothing left
At last, we finally told him the truth
Absolutely nothing. Who are you? What are you doing?
What is this? How...what the hell is this?
This is my house, right?
What do you think?
Maybe not. Eh?
This should be my home
Because I used the key to get in
Ah, wait, eh?
Eh, no way! So gross!
Is this really the case? Huh? Because just now
I thought it was strange
I just went to a very strange place
It's not a strange place
Yuyu Market
Its not a strange place
Did something happen?
Ah, they all took it away?
The whole place is empty?
Sold it all? Sold to a thrift store?
Wait, that's weird...then I have to buy it back!
No, no, that's not the point
Why is your brain wired different to ours?
I need to buy it back quickly!
Oh but thank god, I thought i'd died
You thought you were dead?
When I was shooting on location, I thought, "Oh, I'm dying"
I thought I had died and someone was helping me sort through my belongings
In summary
you'll think your stuff has been stolen or you hung yourself
What nonsense are you talking?
So that's how it is
What do you all think?
A girl should be able to realize right away, right?
-Yes
One's taste and the feel of the clothes
Especially when wearing a jacket, the clothes would change according to their body type, right?
With this it should be obvious
You'd definitely realize
-Ah really?
Sakai is abnormal
Generally, you'd think seeing LARK cigarettes would be enough to realize it
-Yes
There are many strange aspects, right? Like buying his own baby teeth
It would be understandable if you knew that it was your own milk teeth
But he bought it thinking it was someone else's teeth
People don't generally buy other people's teeth, do they
What's he gonna do with it?
"I thought I was dead."
-"I thought I was dead."
Thought someone was helping him sort out his belongings
-On the way to the afterlife
Shouldn't have told him the truth and just kept watching
How he'll live after having already died
Let's welcome the next presenter
Who is it?
Please welcome, Football Hour's Goto!
-Thank you for having me
"Koching" isn't it, "Koching"
"Koching" has arrived
What the hell...
First of all, Hitori
Congratulations on "Asakura KID" being a huge hit!
※Film based on Takeshi Kitano's autobiography, released on Netflix last December and topped the popularity charts that week
That's awesome
Thank you everyone
Matsumoto-san also watched it
-Yes
It's wonderful
I think it only left out one thing
I wanted to see the whole thing with the axe
※Last September, Takeshi Kitano's car was attacked by a man with an axe, but fortunately, only the window was broken and the occupants were safe.
That would have to be a very long shot
How much longer do you want it to be?
Sorry...
It's a really outstanding piece of work
And there's a song that is featured in the movie
Also known as "Asakusa KID"
And so, this time I bring you a related theory:
Every comedian has his or her own "Asakusa KID"
This time, we found a few groups of struggling comedians
And encouraged them to compose lyrics pertaining to their current situation
To sing their own version of "Asakusa KID"
I see
For comedians, especially when they are young, it is common to experience hardships
Even Downtown, who quickly became big stars, also suffered, right?
Of course,
For about four years...
Three or four years of our lives were not great
-Yes
The period where you can't make enough to live on
That's right, that's right
And having to do part-time jobs on the side
Was there a period when you live on borrowed money?
We had to borrow money from ours seniors and so on
-Yeah
We borrowed from Momoko
Ah, Momoko
And Tomiiz helped us find work
-Ah yes, yes, yes
I didn't know what I was doing, but I just kept pressing a button
Inventory
It was probably sending Morse code to North Korea
No, it's not!
Now that's working for a living
The salary for a job like that should be pretty good
Oi!
Verify that all comedians have their own "Asakusa Kid"
For this theory, we assembled three groups of artists with more than 20 years of experience
A group of hilarious entertainers that still can't make a name for themselves
Firstly,
With 25 years of experience: AL-Shalaqani
Waiting for a bus next to you
Next sentence next sentence
-Pretending to be a clock
That's not something you can pretend to be!
Ten years ago, they were finalists in "THE MANZAI" for two consecutive years
They had stepped on the ladder to stardom
Please allow us to make an appearance on stage first
The work they get as comedians today
Is just a few stage performances each month
Do you have any work scheduled after this?
There is no more work
No more today
I should say there is no more after today either
We used to have about 20 shows each month
Now only 10 left
Or maybe less
Of course, we don't have any TV work
Although i'm not sure if it can really be considered income
What a place to do a close-up
About ten or twenty thousand
In all honesty
Mine is about three...four...less than 50,000
Formed in 1997
Even gonna shoot this?
Looking back, it's clear they've entered the later stage of life
Rent is 25,000
For these comedians who only earn tens of thousands of yen each month
Life is difficult
Meanwhile, Seiwa, who is in charge of writing, is already married
So, to secure a living
He acts as a lecturer to earn a meager income
Barely getting by
If the income could increase then of course i'd be very happy
But if it really worried me I wouldn't be with him in the first place
As long as I work a little harder to fill in the gaps, it is not a problem at all
Really nice wife
The main source of income for Shiro Aikata is part-time jobs
Working at a bathhouse
From about 4:00 am to 8:00 am
Three to four days a week
I make about 60,000 a month from it
Because it is impossible to live like this
I also work in a curry restaurant
Opened by the comedian Makio
I'm the store manager of the Shinjuku branch of his curry store
A hard-working life
I once had to take out a very large loan
In total about 12 million
-The sum total
Total
Shiro owes a large amount of a large loan due to his exposure to pyramid schemes during his early days
When the loan had accumulated 4 million in interest
I cried and asked my parents to pay it off for me
Your parents sold a mountain, didn't they?
-Yes, they did.
50 years-old and still waiting for their big break
Although not an impossible task
Our lack of progress in the past few years is clear
And we're getting on in years
What exactly is the reason?
And what helps them to persist in a world which offers no guarantees?
To repay the kindness of those who have taken care of me, I just can't give up
We must also repay the kindness to our partner
Being finalists in THE MANZAI for two years in a row
That's entirely due to my partner
Not having been able to progress any further is my problem
I think it's because we haven't proven how interesting our style is
As long as my partner is still writing performances, I won't give up as a comedian
Sometimes I would like to say "why don't we just quit"
I think giving up before making it is unacceptable
25 years of total dedication to manzai
Step by step, they continue toward the future on the road of uncertainty
So, please enjoy this song by the two members of AL-Shalaqani
That performance where I met you
A layman named "Shiro"
You who were supposed to be the audience
You acted like an idiot for me
In a silent hall in Shinjuku
A performance hall with only nine audience members
Knights, Audrey and even Ujiko
Guys of the same generation have all made their mark
Thought there was no longer a place for us
As we were overtaken by Nishikigoi
Witnessed the reversing success of two fifty-year-olds
Although we always held the dream of "Someday"
I can't keep letting my wife...
Work six or seven days a week
You have to carry the family on your shoulders
This idea is deep-rooted in my heart
Rent...I'm really sorry for not being able to pay on time
I haven't been in touch with you
-Don't say that. It's okay
I'll definitely pay it off when I hit the big time
That would be great!
Don't say we aren't young anymore
That we've never had a taste of fame
Don't say we're worn out
What...what?
You want to win an award, or something?
I don't particularly want to win an award
-This show
It's pretty "eh----"
The next two artists who couldn't scale the heights of popularity are these two
With 29 years of experience, Nichokenju
Who's idea was it to perform this segment?
In recent years, if they've had the opportunity to appear
It's almost always with one of their wives, Yukiko Nonomura
However, in actual fact
The two of them were popular at Osaka's 2-chome theater
Super popular
-Yes
Unimaginably
Iconic and harmonious stars with an overwhelming power to attract support
People say we were fast for our generation
"You can't walk without causing a riot in the street," Jinnai used to say
"That's what popularity is" was commonly said
As long as we were on the performance list, the audience was almost all there to see us
So the two rode this momentum all the way to Tokyo
And even appeared once on the stage of the M-1 final
They were on track to become household names...
Although they are a year below me, I was really impressed by them
It's not over the top to say that they were the pillar of the 2-chome theater
After all, without them there would be no one to see
Thanks to their popularity, our generation is what it is today
Why didn't the two of them make a splash in Tokyo?
I think its down to pressure
"I don't have anymore strength, but I have to keep rushing ahead"
The popularity at the time was so high that they were forced forwards
Both Yoshimoto and the fans egged them on
If you enclose that with a circle...
Now, in terms of their current work
They have only a handful of stage performances left in a month
Manager
How much of their total work currently is comedy?
Comedy just accounts for about 30 percent
Kohori is the group's writer
His attitude toward manzai started to change about ten years ago
In response to this situation, his partner said
Kohori said "I'm here to entertain the public, so I need to try many things"
Although I understood his feelings
He puts equal effort into all of them
Manzai 1, music 1, rakugo 1, like this
Manzai 5, music 1, rakugo 1
If it was like this then l wouldn't have had a problem
Recently the number of people coming to see our performances has been decreasing
Armed with just a microphone to determine victory and defeat for 20 to 30 years
Kohori's heartfelt feelings are...
If only performing manzai was enough then i'd be very happy
But...
The reality is very different, I have four children and must rely on other jobs to support my family
Honestly, that's it
So...it's ready for today, right?
No... what do you think manzai is?
The reason why they won't give up manzai is...
The reason why I sometimes put them on the same stage with myself is
They're kind of in a transitional state
So I want to help give them the motivation to continue to work
It's like "I'll take the lead first"
Currently, his wife, Nonomura, who is active on television, is mainly responsible for the household
Letting Nonomura work alone
I think it is not a long-term solution
What she wants to see the most is for me to achieve something in manzai
So i'm am a bit anxious about this point
I don't hate Kohori
And I really like Nichokenju
If there's less and less opportunities
If you can't get on TV
Instead of becoming like that
We should take advantage of the time when people still know and remember us
Anything is fine, just do it, I think
I really hope that in the New Year he won't be at home
But instead, I can see Nichokenju on TV
Do you have any goals for the future of Nichokenju?
After all, we started our manzai career once already, so we need to restart once again
We must rely on our manzai talent to conquer everyone
Nichokenju's work is really interesting
But I think it's important to get the word out on the street
The two of us just really love manzai
However, our talent alone hasn't led to popularity
It's been 29 years
That's right, right? You want to conquer everyone with your manzai talent, right?
A once iconic group come back to face the upcoming half-century
With hope that one day their manzai talent will help them conquer
Please enjoy this song by Nichokenju
Met you at NSC
※Yoshimoto's Academy for the Nurturing of Comedians
With a playful outrageous attitude
Bit the bullet and reluctantly became a combo
And your scripts drew me into a vortex of laughter
After a while, we were already a regular member of the "Super Alloy" team
※Yoshimoto Super Alloy popular variety show that aired from 1997 to 2000
Double pistols with 100 rounds of laughs
Rode the wave to Tokyo
Pretentious and annoying
The idiot neither making a sound nor playing dumb
To be funny, "manzai is enough"
I believed that one day I could get ahead
However, the number of our performances is declining
By the 29th year
I still think "these two people are really cool"
Making people laugh brings happiness so I think it's a great job
Nichokenju are really great
I really hope I can keep watching them forever
In a large venue
Where I can't believe so many people came to see Nichokenju
I really want to create such a scene
Rakugo and the band, don't be too enthusiastic
On the stage, two people standing side-by-side
Don't stop writing
Of course, I still love your words the most
You really want to win an award?
It's not like that!
Next is the last group
Good morning
26 years' of experience: BlackPinnerSOS
I've known them for a very long time
What do you think?
I intend to support them from now on
Starting now?
-Yes
Starting now...
Its also fine not to
Then why don't you just lie and say you're already supporting them?
How dare you say such a thing!
The third group of struggling comedians are BlackPinnerSOS
26 years ago, a 16-year-old high school duo suddenly appeared
Our live performances were very popular at Ota Production
It was hard to even get a ticket
"I called at the same time as the sale started but couldn't get through" or something like that
And there were unimaginable amounts of screaming
After the show, there were 20 to 30 people waiting outside
Girls followed us all the way from the performance venue to the station
1 2 3 Black…
With the advantage of youth and appearance
They flew head-first into the battlefield called "comedy"
Really evil location
That's it!
※VOCABULA Heavenly Kingdom - A super popular variety show hosted by Tamori from 1992 to 1999
Once VOCABULA ended
The number of programs featuring work like ours began to decrease
Later on, it became impossible to muddle through with a lack of momentum
After that, their high school student status disappeared and their popularity dropped
And they faded into media obscurity
The only weekly show left now is Mache Variety
※Live stream
Is it a webcast?
-Yes
Any work in theaters?
Performances are basically none now
The two men are now 42 years old
I'm coming!
You brought friends
Yes, friends have come over
Naito is the father of two sons
To protect his family
I am a professional mahjong player
Playing this game is my job
I play four-player mahjong on the internet, and when I log in this comes up on the screen
I play against players from all over the country
On the other hand, Aikata Yamano works part-time at an izakaya
At the same time he assists the running of his family's cosmetics store
I'm also preparing to take the judicial exam
A lawyer comedian,
I don't know if there is a precedent, but it seems to be unheard of
I wouldn't be a proper lawyer
But if the party is absent I would be able to get involved, saying "I object" and so on
Although i'm not sure yet...
"Caught vandalizing public property." "Caught and sentenced to how many years in prison."
Although it is not very clear...
But I hope I can use it in some way to help our comedy progress
The world of comedians clinging to their dream at all costs
Although I am considered to be a comedian
But as i'm not so famous, when people ask, "What is your profession?" I can't answer "I'm a comedian"
Our writing or whatever has never really been acknowledged
Only we think we are comedians, but no one sees us as comedians
If you want to be a comedian...
I hope that one day I will be able to say "I am a comedian" without hesitation
After debuting at the age of 16, they fell back to earth after only four years
After that, they continued to lurk for the next twenty years, living a hard life as comedians
So, please enjoy their song
Met you in the first year of high school
The two weird guys in the same class
Caught the attention of TV shows
Became "high school stars" overnight
Signed by Ota Productions and became a favorite on VOCABULA
In the summer of 18 years old, the peak of life
After taking off our uniforms, our value plummeted
Abandoned by TV and banished by theaters
Now humbly playing on the turf of newcomers
And lived a life of being teased by Miyashita Kusanagi...
Living a life of of part-time work
In the spring of 42 years old, I lost my home
Because of their age, there's no way to participate in competitions
It would be nice if he could inherit this store that I have worked so hard on
After all, it's not good to say you're an comedian at 42 years old
If you're a professional mahjong player, then people think you're the type of a person that can hold down their job
That's what I say, but I always add a little note
That he's "also a comedian"
Even if the family worry
Please wait until I can be called an "comedian"
One day I will be able to say it with a clear conscience
"Who are you?"
"We're comedians, you asshole!"
Thank you for watching!
That was a long one
Hamada-san has some thoughts
He kept saying "No, no, no" under his breath
The video was very well done
I just don't get why its quite often like this when you come
I don't know if you're trying to win an award or what
Just want to win an award, you asshole!
You think of me in such a way?
So, Hitori,
How do I say this...
Although I thought i'd feel very emotional
I actually wasn't really moved by it
No resonance at all
The last one, BlackPinnerSOS
We are really good friends
Met at the age of 16
I'm going to meet Naito later
We do a radio show together every week
-Oh really?
He's speaking as if he only has one live performance left every week
Why doesn't my broadcast count?
Its every single week!
Maybe they want to focus on how much it has decreased
-Show that they're having a hard time
So because of this I wasn't moved by it
But these three groups have been selected for this, so...
Very true
-Actually, it's...
They're very lucky
So they have some star power, right?
There are so many groups like them
So I hope more of them can get opportunities such as this
Indeed
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03