Chosen by parents! My son is shining in this theory! Special!
The next guests are...
Nice to meet you
Thank you for having us today, thank you very much
I'm Kurokawa Kaori
I'm his wife, Kurokawa Miyuki
I see where this is going
They are the parents of Kurokawa Akihito, more commonly known as Kurochan
This is the first time
I saw his parents
Kurochan, who has participated in 32 theories, up till now
Additionally, involved in various themes such as Monster house and Monster idol
I've actually been watching all of them
I've been watching it as well
But my heart somehow feels disgusted sometimes, seriously
He always does weird things, right? Such as lying
When I see those things, my heart aches
First of all, let's see which theory does
she thinks her son is shining the most
I personally like the theory about the race between pigeon and human the most
Because he didn't say anything strange in that episode
So that one gave me a good impression
Kurochan's mother
is an earnest person
Pigeon and human, starting from a random location
Who will the one to arrive home first?
Theory: In terms of homing instinct, humans can do better than pigeons
Since he doesn't have any cash on him, so I thought he will rack his brain to think of a solution
But then, he still ends up using some nasty tricks
Exactly. To ensure a fair race with the pigeons, Kurochan's wallet and smartphone have been confiscate, however...
I'll take this, thank you very much
I'll make good use of the money you gave me
He held a photography event on the spot,
and earned enough money to buy a train ticket
I'm going back home with the help from everyone
He has always been like this since childhood
Don't know if he is clever or cunning
In regard to money, Kurochan has been demonstrating his cunning cleverness since childhood
When he borrowed money from his younger sister
Although a normal people will pay back
However, that kid has been thinking about excuses to not pay back
And he said "I'll let you be my elder sister, so give me money please"
So he means that he's now the younger one, and his younger sister is now his elder sister
And because she's now the elder one, she should give him money
I have no idea what he's talking about
The story continues, Kurochan's cunning cleverness escalated when he became an university student
-He's pissing me off
-Sure he is
When he's 22 years old?   -Yeah, around 20 years old
He said he want to get a hair transplant   -Yes, yes
He said he wants to get a hair transplant, and asked us to give him money
Around four hundred thousand yen...   -Yeah
Did he really get a hair transplant?
I don't think so   -No idea, he never mentioned it again
All he did was taking money away from us
He's probably good at asking for a favor
But I believe he's not doing these kinds of thing to other people
Hopefully he didn't
I told him not to do these things to other people
Yeah, when it comes to money
So this is Kurochan, someone who is obsessed with money
He really looks
like a bad guy
Even when he became a comedian, he has been asking for money from his parents until recently
Until very recently
Before he was 30 years old, he asked for $150,000 yen per month
He asked for $50,000 yen per month after that,
only until 2 years ago, when he reached 42 years old
Which has been a famous story
We told him not to borrow money from other people
When it comes to money, just rely on us
His parents are really kind
Therefore that guy is living an elegant lifestyle
When I was on a business trip in Tokyo, and went to meet him
I asked him "where are you going now?" and he said "I am going to the beauty salon"
And I thought how dare you go to those
places? You don't even have money
Back to today's theme
Which theory does Kurochan's father thinks his son is shining the most?
Well, probably the "Future Kurochan"
I'm able to watch it and laugh the whole way through it
The man's lie and love being trifled with prophetic tweets
Being under complete surveillance for 10 days, the documentary "Future Kurochan"
Let's sit down and then talk   -Wait a second...
The pitfall is of course in front of the bench
He's got to know
that it's there, right?
From how Rei-chama is positioned, it's clear Kurochan appears to suspect something
I was thinking about how great you really are, and...
This whole week I was thinking about how great you are, and...
And I was thinking if I like you, and...
I do
I just wanted to put that out there clearly   -Thank you
Thank you
He means that
"I'm believing you"
I really do like you, so...
He's gonna be
double shocked if
there's indeed a trap
So, let's sit down and talk   -Yes, let's sit down
This is heartbreaking   -So heartbreaking
She's running off   -Truly heartbreaking
She's running! She's running!
She's hopping away
This must be traumatizing...
Yeah, this gonna result in trauma
Isn't he crying already? Come on...
Kurochan, hang in there   -Climb on out
Good things will happen   -Exactly
Kurochan...
I can't watch this, come on...   -This is just...
This is just...too heartbreaking
I can't look at this
Climbing out from there like that
Ah, she's gone, Rei-chama...
Ah, this is Rainy Blue's playing
He's not saying a thing   -Not a word
This is truly heartbreaking
He got on alone   -This really went too far...
He came with another person, but is leaving alone...
Such an epic film   -Even the greatest actor won't be able to make this face
I like that face   -You're good, Kurochan, you're fine
Still filming even when he arrives home
This is really something
Those good memories, look at his happy face
He stored it at his home, huh?   -From the matching pair
He's looking at it
What's he going to do?
What will you do?
What's happening?
Ah, hello, Sae-chan
Sae-chan?
Eh? A different girl?
Do you like meat?
And the most memorable scene in Future Kurochan is...
Rei-chama's glass
Everything went just as we imagined
I hate it, that's nasty, licking someone else's things
As Kurochan's mother, how do you feel when you see him licking the glass?
I feel like vomiting...
I start to wonder am I really the one who gave birth to this kid, seriously
And I thought "so this kid is doing these kinds of thing"
"No wonder he's not attractive to women"
"Because he's doing these kinds of thing, and being aired on TV"
And in regard to this "glass licking act"
Kurochan's nieces are very disgusted as well
They say he is no different from a scumbag
And call him "shit" and "bastard"
How did you feel when you hear them call him with those words?
I was really angry
Why should he be scolded by you kids?
Oh, so she's on
Kurochan's side
So I stood on my son's side, and chewed my granddaughters up
Ah, of course, he's
Kurochan's mother
Although he's a scumbag, he's still her son, who she gave birth in pain
Don't call him
a scumbag
She's angry even if the ones who scolded him are their relatives
Furthermore...
Some other comedians call him "baldy"
Whenever others talk bad about him on tv shows, I can't help but feel angry
Thereafter, I will never watch any shows with that comedian
Whenever he appears, I'll change the channel
She definitely dislikes me...
For example, which comedian talked bad about him?
Everyone, right?   -Yeah, everyone
Not much people is treating him nice, so...
What if you have to choose one?
Fujimon?   -Fujimon-san
So in conclusion, these are the two theories that Kurochan's parents think their son shined the most
In terms of homing instinct,
humans can do better than pigeons
Future Kurochan
Given this precious chance to meet his parents, we've decided to ask a bunch more questions about Kurochan
Is he a restless sleeper since childhood?
Well, I know he snores very loudly
But I never saw him tossing and turning when he sleeps at home
So I didn't know about this until I saw it on TV, and I thought "that's terrible"
Is his room very untidy since childhood?
No, no, not at all
He has been living with his sister in the same room, so...
So he's probably showing his true color after he left home
No one will come
With complete freedom
When did he start having hairs on his back?
Who cares?
I never saw him naked
So when I saw that on TV
I thought like "Eh?..."
It must be disgusting to sleep with that thing...
To be honest, I know nothing about him
He didn't have hairs before   -On his back?
But come on, it couldn't be gene mutation though
By the way, does Kurochan's father have hairs on his back?
I don't have hairs on my back
Including all our relatives, Akihito (Kurochan) is the only one
Does he cry a lot since childhood?
That thing cries all the time
He cries every time I scold him
Whenever we say like "Did you do this?" or "That's no good"
Then he will cry and say sorry
Well, he's probably fake crying though...
That thing is malicious
They are so mean
How else is he different from others?
He was conspicuous during secondary school
While everyone else is wearing shoes, only Akihito is not wearing
Because he don't like wearing socks
When others told me "What happened, Ms Kurokawa? Your son is barefooted"
I was like "Eh?..."
I was shocked, I'm always getting shocked by him
Young Kurochan showed so many facets to his personality, which even shocked his own parents, furthermore...
What was his future career plan when he was a student?
His high school teacher asked him about this
And he said "I want to become a hero", a hero
He said "I want train myself in China, and stay in some remote mountain"
"And I'll soon become a hero"
This guy is unbelievable...   -He's already in high school
Then his teacher told him "there's no jobs for hero, there's no such occupation"
His teacher told him, right?   -Yes
And I thought "is this kid retarded or something?..."
That's all from Kurochan's parents
So that's all from Kurochan's parents
Kurochan's mother seems like a kind and earnest person
Yeah, his mother is really earnest
And she probably loves Kurochan so much
Yeah, she's standing on his side
So she probably hate both of us   -Yeah
No, no worries
They hate Fujimon the most
Eh? But actually, they should hate Kinoshita from TKO the most, right?
*Kinoshita from TKO is famous for mistreating juniors, and Kurochan once said that Kinoshita made him kneel down and scolded him while stepping on his head
Well, there's no need for Kurochan's mother to change channel then
However, since there's still a lot of mysteries left after interviewing with Kurochan's parents
So, this time, we invited this person to today's show
Please come in
Oh, so it's him
Here I am, everybody!
Kurochan, you watched it too, right? How do you feel?
Yeah, I watched it, and I'm sure that the staffs are asking those questions with malicious intent
How come?
They were like "Hey, Kurochan's mother, he's licking other's glass, how do you feel?"
Is it necessary to ask those questions?
Well, but it's the fault of the person who licked it though
Yeah well, although it's my fault, but I was actually so drunk, so...
So I don't even remember it, to be honest
You don't remember it?
It's not in my memory*
*The phrase "It's not in my memory (記憶にございません)" is always used as excuse by Japanese politicians
That make things worse
There's nothing we can say if he put it like that
He's truly a useless person   -Yeah, a useless person
No, I'm not a useless person, listen to me...
Of course you are, you asked for $150,000 yen every month right?
That was unbelievable   -It surely is
And $50,000 yen per month only until 2 years ago
You're already earning, right?
In another perspective, I'm actually being dutiful towards my parents
You two seems to be misunderstanding me
When parents don't need to worry about their children anymore
They'll think "oh, so the kids are fine on their own, they don't need us anymore", and may therefore even die sooner
I'm just trying my best to let them worry about me
And trick them into thinking "this kid won't be able to survive without us", and thus making them live a longer life
I've therefore asked for money on purpose
That's all from Kurokawa suspect?
No, I'm not a suspect
You surely are a suspect   -No, it's not illegal
So that's what you think, Kurokawa member?
*When the suspect is a public figure, Japanese media refer to them as "members"
No, don't use the word member too
They both mean the same thing
Come on, you're earning now, you should be the one to give them money
You're earning a lot, right? You told me your annual income before
I told you, but that's...   -You told me, right?
But I need to pay taxes...   -Let Downtown know your annual income
Eh?
Come on, tell them your annual income
Eh? Did I tell you, Jinnai-san?   -Yes, you did
Eh? Really?   -Yes, you definitely told me
It was even in the news
Oh, really?   -Yes, it was
Tell us about it
$960,000 yen for Kurochan
Sorry, that was a dull moment   -What do you mean?
He probably did a wordplay Boke   -Yeah, 96 and Kuro
Kuro has the same pronunciation with 96
That's not what we're talking about
That was such a gentle Boke
Just tell us then, Jinnai
30,000,000 yen   -Why did you say it?
It was in the news
Wait a second, that's a dull moment from both of you
No, no, that's not a dull moment...
That conversation was...
I wanna go home
No, no, no way
Come on, Jinnai-san, don't drag me with you
I'm the one who got dragged, dude!
The news said that you're earning 30,000,000 yen
So scary, I wanna go home
This guy is earning 30,000,000 yen
Because there's a CM at the same time...
Anyway, did you buy any present or give any money to your parents?
Good question
No, not yet, but...
That's terrible
No, because we're in the time of Corona, and of course, I thought about doing something for them afterwards
For example, what do you plan to do?   -Tell us
For example?
Make a promise with your parents now
I'll buy them a neckerchief
It has been a while since I last heard that word, you're buying them a neckerchief?