...where we investigate theories from our everyday life.
Tonight's presenters are...
It's Kamaitachi!
Let's get right into it. Today we've brought a theory...
...regarding a type of food that everyone loves.
Let's take a look.  Here it is:
If you send the smell of curry into a meeting, the person will eat curry afterwards.
I don't think there's any doubt about this one.
Today we investigate the theory:
If you send the smell of curry into a meeting, the person will eat curry afterwards.
Today we've brought in six comedians for a meeting before lunchtime...
...where we will be sending in the smell of curry from the next room.
If all six eat curry after the meeting, the theory has been proved correct.
Our first target is...
Abereru-kun.
He's so bald!
As they start the meeting for the fake show...
...we begin our grand curry plan!
And then...
Do you smell something good?
Something smells good, right?
It smells like curry, doesn't it?
Did you eat some?
Staff: No, I didn't have any.
It smells amazing.
We continued to send in the smell of curry.
Staff: OK, that's it for today.
Thank you very much.
The meeting is over.
Abareru-kun is in the driver's seat as he leaves the TBS office.
From here we enlist our friends at the HAL detective agency.
We continue the investigation.
After driving for 10 minutes...
...we arrive at Koujimachi, where Abereru-kun's next gig is.
When suddenly...
...Abereru-kun stops and stares at a parked car.
On that car?
Curry.
Abereru-kun's destination is...
CoCo Ichi. (A curry restaurant chain.)
With Abereru-kun we have cleared the first level.
He really went!
Staff: Excuse me.
Staff: We're with TBS, can we interview you for a bit?
Wait, what?
Staff: What did you eat just now?
Just now? I had curry.
Staff: Curry?
Yeah...
Curry with spinach.
Staff: Why did you eat curry?
What?  Why?
Because I was hungry? No?
Staff: Any other reasons?
The smell.
Because of the smell.
Staff: The smell?
Yes.
During the meeting..
...it smelled so delicious.
So we explained today's theory to him.
What is that?!
I fell right into your trap.
This is embarrassing.
The next target is...
...Viking's Nishimura.
Just like before, we send in the smell of curry from the room next door.
That smells good.
Staff: It smells good?
Yeah.
Is it curry?
We finish the meeting.
And then Nishimura heads over to...
Where is this?
Sukiya.
While beef on rice is their specialty, Sukiya has a diverse menu.
What did Nishimura end up eating?
Staff: Nishimura-san, pardon me...
Staff: We're with TBS.  Can we speak to you for a minute?
Sure...
Staff: What did you eat just now?
Just now?
I had curry.
CLEAR
We explained today's theory to Nishimura.
Yeah, it did smell like curry.
Staff: Would you say that influenced you?
Ah...I don't really know the answer...
Why the hell not?!
Ugh...I don't like this!
That's so frustrating.
Am I really like that?
Did I really eat it because of the smell?
Of course!
Next we have...
Anthony from Matenrou.
Isn't there a really strong curry smell?
Am I imagining that?
Staff: No, it does.
It does, right?  It smells like curry.
What's going to happen?
After walking around Akasaka for five minutes...
Anthony walks into...
...an udon restaurant.
However, if we look at the menu...
...there's still a chance.
Staff: Anthony-san, excuse me.
Staff: We're from TBS.
This is scary...
...what's going on?
Staff: We want to ask you a couple of questions.
Staff: What did you eat just now?
Udon.
I was eating udon noodles.
Staff: Udon?
Yeah.
Udon...I was eating curry udon.
CLEAR
Staff: Why did you choose curry udon?
Why? Wait, what is this? I'm scared.
Why? Why?
I wonder why?
It's because the room smelled like curry!
That's it, that's probably why I chose to eat it.
That's it, I was thinking of eating udon...
So we explained today's theory to him.
What is that?!
Wait, so I ate it because of that?
Yes.
I feel like such a dweeb.
Everyone feels like that.
Our next target is...
Arapon from Anzen Manzai
That smells good!
It smells like the curry I eat at home.
However, the store he entered was also an udon restaurant.
Hi - ohh what's going on?
Staff: Good afternoon.
Good afternoon.
Staff: Just now, what did you eat?
Just now? I was eating curry udon.
CLEAR
I mean, you would...
I don't know, would you eat it after that?  I did.
Next, the fifth target is...
Kuro-chan
It really...
It really smells good, doesn't it?
Staff: Does it smell good?
Yes.
Curry?
Staff: The smell of curry?
Yes.
Kuro-chan, is it ok
to follow you?
We also have success with Kuro-chan.
Brunch: Veggie curry.
Instead of rice, I'm eating it with veggies.
Healthy! Extra veggies with a small portion of curry.
However, in reality...
...he was hiding the rice under the veggies.
In fact, it was two servings of rice plus udon.
A lie was smeared with extra carbs.
Lastly we have...
Noda Crystal from Magical Lovely.
We sent in the smell of curry like we had done before, but...
Staff: About five years?
Yes.
Staff: Do you remember how much you were smoking in those days?
I think it was a pack a day.
Unlike the others before him...
...Noda doesn't mention the smell at all.
After the meeting...
...he went from Akasaka to Ogikubo by train.
The restaurant Noda entered was...
...a yakitori restaurant.
The theory was not proven true.
Actually, I don't like curry.
In conclusion, some people don't like curry.
So...what did everyone think?
It's brainwashing.
It feels like somehow this can be used to influence people.
By the way, backstage today...
...there was a curry lunch, and a regular lunch.
Which one did you eat?
The non-curry one.
I didn't eat either of them.
I didn't eat them, either.
We...wanted you to have one or the other.