Welcome to Wednesday Downtown
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Who is it?
Savannah's Takahashi!
It's Takahashi!
Looks in good spirits
It hasn't been that long, right?
So, today I bring you a regular segment
Hamada-san's favorite "someone" series
The scary one
Hamada, is it not your favorite?
-I do like it
This time, we bring you a new spin on it
Please take a look
Is it possible for a comedian to make the person hiding in the room laugh
I see
A reverse prank?
Indeed
This is a good plan
The rule is within thirty minutes
They can do anything
But if the person that is thinks "they're trying to make me laugh" then they're disqualified
Otherwise the project will be too tasteless
The person involved has to be cautious
Because they shouldn't laugh out loud
-Indeed
What do you think will happen, Matsumoto?
I think it'll be tough for the comedians
If there's not a question of whether it can be broadcast or not
They may do some twisted XXXX
If you watch it in VR you'd definitely laugh
Surely laugh
Is it possible for a comedian to make the person hiding in the room laugh
The first challenger is
Morishita
I've been in this situation before
Yeah
I don't think it'll be that easy to make the person laugh
Whoa...
Tough...
This time, we gathered ten extras of different ages and genders to be the "someone"
They select the target from the extras themselves
Done
A man in his 20s
Not bad
What do you think?
Should be OK?
The ideal choice is about 30 years old, more than 20 years old is almost in the target range, right?
Sounds like he's experienced
Ideal target is 30 years old
Morishita first leaves the room first and the house empty
This is when the extras are hidden in the closet
Preparation work completed
A surveillance monitor is set up in front of him on the pretext of "finding a time to scare him"
After waiting for 30 minutes
Morishita returns home pretending not to know anything
The challenge begins
The extras must be nervous
Gonna laugh out loud, right?
To show authenticity, Morishita first rests in bed
Why do you need that pose?
3 minutes after starting
It's finally time to start the first round of combat
Hey, that...
Hatsase, you
Pretending to be on the phone with his partner
The segment to be performed tomorrow has not yet been decided, right?
Very realistic
What to do?
Do that one? Ok
The one with the big demon god balls
Attack 1 A Dumb routine
Laughing
The one with the big demon god balls
The first attempt caused a snicker
After that too
No, Slippery Beethoven is a bit old, right?
What is this name?
What about the one with the oyster pie girl?
It has to be a baby stag beetle, right?
So first the big demon balls
Balls appear to be able to elicit a response the easiest
But unfortunately the target did not laugh out loud
Morishita also doesn't know which he reacted to
I hope Morishita will realize that the target can't resist balls
Right at that moment
Wait a minute...Oh no!
I'm sorry, I'm overdue
This is bad...
Yes, right now
It's already 2:00
At 2:00 I must drink my medicine, sorry
Anyway, please, stag beetle diapers
Ok ok
This is bad
Unbearable, unbearable, unbearable
How can you laugh at this? It's scary!
Scary!
Meow Meow
Meow Meow Meow Meow
Failed in combat, right?
Meow Meow
Its like a horror film
Too far from funny, right?
Meow Meow
He's scared to death, isn't he?
What kind of battle plan is that?
Wow!
Satomi, don't come out again
Attack 2 Multiple personality
Enough, right?
It's too complicated, right?
It's morning, right? 5:00 in the morning, right?
It's 2:00 p.m. here. I'm sorry
I'm sorry I got mad at you
15 minutes left
Call
Thank you for your hard work
Yes
Eh?
It's late?
The funny video?
Sorry
Fine
Then I'll shoot now
Attack 3 Self-shooting
Nice
-Very natural
This does happen
It's me
Sasaki, who has traveled from a parallel world
A serious routine
Me
Frontal attack!
It's a special bowling ball
It's quite effective
And
I...
I'm Chiaki from another world
I am Inoue Kouzou from a parallel world
Inoue Kouzou
It worked. I saw the teeth
It took Morishita 24 minutes to complete the challenge with an imitation of Inoue Kouzou
Doesn't feel like a parallel world version
At this time the staff send the news of the successful challenge to Morishita
What? What? What?
Eh? Who is it? Who are you? Who is it?
Wait a minute...who are you?
He still pretends to be scared by the hidden performer
Is this needed?
The truth is revealed
Then
What is it? What is this?
Who is this acting for?
Morishita continues playing the role of the target
How did it feel to hide?
It was hard to hold in a smile all the time
The real content is then explained
Laughed?
-Yes
Yes!
Really happy
As happy as when I entered the third round of R-1
The next challenger is
Makino
The same lottery was conducted
To decide the target
The target is placed in the lower level of the closet
The challenge begins when Makino returns home
Upon entering
Sports underwear, waistband and men's underwear
She changes into a costume
This can be considered an attack
She suddenly starts to eat dango
You'd laugh at this
I think it's good!
Attack 1 Can't eat dango horizontally
It's hard to eat dango
Playing dumb doesn't work
Next
Hello?
Attack 2 Phone call
I have an old cracked hemorrhoid
From birth until now
But this doesn't work either
So
Practice time
Everyone does this
Attack 3Rehearsal
Discounted fish in supermarkets
With fat or without it?
I can tell!
Forty Party Forty Party
This won't tickle a 60 year old's funny bone
Wont work over 20 years old
When eating a good steak
Forgot about sushi
I spit, straight to the core!
This segment also fails
There are no more...
Empty... gone...
No more
There's nothing in the top of the fridge either, right?
So, in a last desperate attempt
Future, future
This is bad
No good
-No?
Super interesting though
At this point we force termination
This is a foul
Why completely naked?
There is nothing else to do but to take it all off
At the end of my tether
I've heard that if you take it off, you can get a laugh
I actually couldn't stop laughing
The next third challenger is
Morita
For Morita, a more difficult challenge is prepared
There are five people hiding in your house.
-5 people?
Please make all 5 of them laugh
Five people, it's quite difficult
This time, the five people are hidden as shown above
The challenge is to make all these people laugh
This challenge is called
THE IEMONEA
*Spoofed of THE IROMONEA, a variety show
Aim to make 5 people laugh!
Ah, I'm exhausted
Very natural feeling
Morita's initial battle plan is
Attack 1
Fart
The one in the middle is going to laugh
-Straight away
Laughing!
Successfully made a women in her fifties laugh with fart noises
Hello?
Is it convenient now?
Something for FRIDAY
*FRIDAY - Magazine which sometimes reports cheating celebrities
Well, I have some inforation
I want to sell it to you
It's about New York's Yashiki cheating
Attack 2 Selling comedian gossip
Everyone is listening with great interest!
Photos have been taken
Not a photo of the cheating scene
It is a photo of drinking with the cheating partner
Listening carefully!
How much can I get?
20…
Oh really
Well, 20...20 is a bit low, right?
When selling TKO Kimoto's news before
There was 60
So it was you!
No, a 60 percent negotiation
So, in comparison, the 20 for New York is a bit less, right?
Listening to it, listening to it
"It was you!" might make them laugh
Do you accept those kinds of things?
Do you also accept info about harassment?
It's about Rice
Too weak?
4,000 yen? Eh?
Another laughed!
No, he is also the King of Conte champion
Later
Attack 3 Competitors on dartboard
By hanging his competitor's pictures on the dartboard
He made a man in his 40s laugh too
Throwing darts straight at New York
The pace is very good at this point as he has amused three
Coming
Morita doesn't know how many people are left
I'm sorry you had to come all the way out here
Come on in.
-Excuse me
Is that Hyouroku?
At this point he is joined by his junior Hyouroku who has been prepared in advance to elicit laughs
Morita finds an excuse to go out first
And lets the others watch Hyouroku alone in the house
Handed over to Hyouroku?
Morita's cigarette
Is Hyouroku a bad guy?
What kind of clothes are these?
Attack 4  Unauthorized smoking
What a unique smoking position
Very in synch with the bear behind him
Like a composite photo
What are we watching?
How old is Hyouroku?
Morita's bag
Hyouroku's a bad guy!
Going through other peoples bags
How can you laugh at this?
This thin bald headed guy is too scary
Opening everything!
What brand of clothes are you wearing?
Wow, that's a lot of money
You can't laugh at this, right?
This thin bald headed guy counting money is so scary
Put it back first
Hyouroku stage
What is this plot?
Attack 5 Hyouroku steals 70,000 yen
So there are people that'd laugh
Now there's only one person left
This one is very tolerant
Morita gives Hyouroku 10,000 yen for the taxi upon returning
Take a taxi back
When graciously sending the thief Hyouroku out
The time ends
Very strong
The staff reports to Morita that he failed to make all five laugh
It's so annoying, really
Just like before, he pretends to be surprised
Eh?
Enough already
Ah!
What is this part?
The search is quite fast
Oi!
Unfortunately, that's it
There was one person left
Because the time ran out
It's as bad as failing at IROMONEA
Really
In summary
Now accepting challengers
What do you think, Matsumoto?
There was a pattern of doing their routines
Indeed, under the pretext of making a video
Came up with a reason to perform
Incidentally
After filming
She was scolded by her manager, who is much younger than her
What was she doing
"How can this be broadcast!?" she said
But it's actually on the air!
Indeed, when I look back on it now
Her shouting "future future" was pretty entertaining
No futuristic feeling at all
Let's welcome the next presenter
Who is it?
He's here!
-Its Fujiawara!
I remember.
-Yeah
What follows is not a theory
It is the continuation from last week
MONSTER LOVE
Here we go!
Last week Kuro-chan's new project began
Everyone has already seen the first episode
Of course
Here's a brief review
9 women claim to like Kuro-chan, who knows nothing
Among these 9 are people just pretending to like him
Two were selected for elimination
And both were just pretending to like him
That's what happened
So now it's down to these 7
They are arranged in order of Kuro-chan's preference
Starting with Miku
We also don't know how many people are lying.
-That's interesting
Now, they are going to start living together in Okinawa
What will happen?
Let's watch
Getting wet!
Typhoon, hurry up!
A very exciting beginning
Here, here
Hurry up!
Trying to escape the weather
This place is awesome!
Awesome!
Amazing!
Its like an art museum!
The 2nd floor is also very luxurious
Absolutely luxurious
Except for one who could not attend due to the typhoon
The six women here will start living with Kuro-chan
By the way, the absent Nodoka is also a pretender
Cheers!
Since we've toasted
Are there any places you would like to visit?
Ah, I do. I want to go to the aquarium
Aquarium?
Not bad
Who wants to go to the aquarium?
Ah, everyone!
I want to go
It's suitable for a rainy day too
Then pack your bags first
To the aquarium yo~
Don't go swimming in there yo~
What are you talking about?
What a boring conversation.
-Yeah
Talking is boring
This opening
Very beautiful
What a shot!
So annoying
Do you need to make it so fashionable?
Annoying
Ah its the one that's just been completed
Awesome
Looks like Nemo
Isn't it?
So cute!
So annoying
-Boring as hell!
A little like Kuro-chan
So cute!
I have something to say to Kuro-chan
To me?
-Yeah
This approach of taking the initiative is suspicious
Can I?
-Sure
Let's go
Whoa
Crocodile
It's not moving
Look here. Crocodile
Its really not moving, but pretty cute
Isn't it impressive? It's big.
-Yes, it is
Eh? Two people talking alone
Is this happening?
You said you wanted to ask me something. What is it?
Before, you said I am the cutest
You said you liked me the most
That's what this guy says to everyone
Then the ranking is revealed
Yes, I said so
But when it was announced
I wasn't first, I was second
Yeah
-He said he likes her the most
Qualified
It's not the same as what he said
Second
A little concerned, right?
Ah~
What "ah~"
Remember?
I'm not sure why
Are you concerned?
-Yeah
Well, that...
If you are the first to be called
People will know that I obviously like you
What does it matter?
The other girls may be jealous and annoyed at you
So I chose you second on purpose
Misdirection, misdirection
I want to be first
Is that a valid reason?
You know... for you
I want you to feel at ease
What are you talking about?
-So gross
I'm a bit worried
-Worried?
So annoying
-What a playboy
But feeling uneasy like this
You'll like me even more, right?
Yeah, but i've been kind of concerned since then
After coming to Okinawa I still think of you the first
Really? Really?
-Yeah
Must have said the same to others
Thank you
Pretty direct
So direct
You know, i'm not looking for a fun relationship
Such a cool face
I'm serious
So disgusting!
I can feel the tingling of fate
Tingling
Great, I'll remember those words
In turn, what you're saying to me now
You're not lying to me, are you?
It's not a trick
He's suspicious
Really
Can I trust you?
-Yeah
I believe in you
He believes
-Isn't it a little early to believe?
The weather is so bad
We whipped up some food
If you want to eat
Eh? Did you guys make this?
We did
Who made it?
Me and Naru
Ah, the 2 of you did it?
So impressive!
I better eat it while its still hot then!
Yes, please do
Great!
Yes, it's delicious
Is it good?
Great!
Mildly spicy
Huh?
An individual action
What's she doing?
Excuse me
Oh, Miku!
Can I sit next to you?
Oh, of course!
Excuse me
Please sit down
Eh? You're alone?
Everyone is resting
So close
So I came over
Definitely lying
You came over
Came over
Not sure yet, right?
1 person came
Eh? What will you do if I'm the big bad wolf?
Die!
Please don't say "die!"
I'm embarrassed
I have something to ask Kuro-chan
Want to ask me?
How can there be?
Last time I... was your first choice
Disgusting feet
You chose me first, right?
She was first
In Kuro-chan's mind
Am I number one?
Of course
You see!
Really?
Really. Why are you laughing?
It feels like...
At that time, I was very happy to be chosen
But today, at the aquarium
You and Richi were alone together for a long time
She cares about it
He's so popular!
So I feel a little uneasy
Exposed!
Why do you feel uneasy?
Because in the order of your choosing, you were first
Do I not have anything to worry about?
His lips are so annoying
Didn't I just say that?
So angry!
The ranking says it all
I've been watching you
Here we go
Calling me by my name like that is pretty embarrassing
Ah so cute!
So don't want me to say it?
No it's not that
If you call me "Miku", can I call you "Aki-kun"?
Oh surprisingly she knows his actual name
Aki-kun?
Then I'll call you "Aki-kun" from now on
I don't really want to go back
Can I kiss you?
No, right?
She's attacking!
He's in danger
(Ok)
I'm shy, can you close your eyes?
Seriously, this is bad
Oh, there?
This guy!
You're very bold
So gross!
I can't do this kind of thing normally but I want to because it's with Aki-kun
"Very bold"
Miku, you're not lying to me, right?
He said it!
I'm not lying to you!
You really like me, right?
I like you the most
You don't trust me?
No, I believe you
Seriously, this is so tiring
Saying something like "this is so tiring"
I'm so tired of watching this
Before that, you said "die!"
It's an endurance test
So, what do we think? Miku is on the offensive!
She initiated a kiss!
Here, right?
Although it is the cheek
Although it was on the temple
I don't know what to think 'cause it was on the temple
Although it was there
How do women feel watching it?
Miku is very suspicious, as is Richi
Richi has been from the start
Yes, both are very suspicious
Really?
-Alone at the aquarium
Yeah
The weather has been bad the whole time, is that a problem?
-Don't worry about it
Will there be a sudden power failure and Kuro-chan will have been killed?
This is not a mystery drama
Will it clear up tomorrow?
The weather forecast says it will be sunny tomorrow?
Sorry I called you all here
It seems there is a place with a lion statue experience
Lion statue experience?
Experience "making a lion statue"
He means make a lion statue themselves
There are places where you can make your own lion statue
Idiot!
Well, it would be nice if we could go
Originally I wanted to have a barbecue in the evening
But looking at the weather, it can't be done
So, we'll do an octopus party instead
Great!
Takoyaki party
So lets divide into two groups: shopping and lion statue experience
I said its a lion statue making experience!
To make a lion statue!
Who wants to do the lion statue experience with me?
-I do!
Making experience!
Everyone?
The quickest to raise their hands were
Naru, Richi, and Risa, right?
Get some octopus
Super big!
They split up
Do we need that much?
-No, I don't think so
This one, right?
-There are also small ones
Super happy when there's just 3 people
Wow, this is awesome, huh? There are so many kinds!
Super cute~
Let me ask you
Lion statue experience
-Lion statue making experience
What kind of relationships have you been in before?
Only really one to speak of
And only for about 4 months
Never even held hands
No?
-Nope
So, I am very eager to be in a relationship
What about you, Ri?
I usually pursue people I like
Confess to them and then go out with them
Very good at talking
Even if the other person has other girlfriends
I always thought, "It's okay because I like him," so I went out with him anyway
You knew they were dating someone else?
-Yes
Even if it is the kind of person seems like a playboy, it's ok if I like them
Suitable for Kuro-chan
If we have time to be together
If you like them you're ok with it
-Yeah, if I like them
Eh? But that wouldn't end up happily though, right?
This is a trap, right?
I think i'll still feel happy
How is it possible?
For you to be treated so casually...
Although I haven't known you long
The thought of it annoys me
So cute
Isn't Kuro-chan really handsome?
Seeing him in real life he's even more cool
-Yes, really
When there are only 3 people...
He seems more handsome than I expected
-I know
They too...
No one knows who's sincere and who's lying
Maybe they are testing each other?
He's got a good physique and big hands
Super gentle
-Super gentle!
I really think he's much more handsome than on TV
The people who went shopping put in a lot of effort!
So lets hurry up and start the octopus party!
Cheers!
So happy!
Sorry
Awesome!
Delicious!
Kuro-chan, you made it super delicious!
-Is it good?
Looks very happy
Wait, this is wasabi, right?
Why is there wasabi?
I wanted to play Russian roulette
We're gonna eat it?
-Yeah
No, wait
Then close your eyes
Kuro-chan isn't participating
You're not allowed to look
Kuro-chan's not eating
The king's entertainment
What's up?
I feel a draft
Indeed the typhoon is very strong!
What, what? What's wrong?
Seems like a very strong typhoon
Typhoon
What the hell are you doing?
No. 12
Strange image
What is this guy doing?
Stinks!
She said it!
Exposed!
Seems so stinky
What a stinky typhoon
Finally said it
So smelly
Seems so smelly, so smelly
A large typhoon is approaching~
Keeps saying he stinks
What stinks?
Doesn't something stink?
She said you "stink", right?
Probably because of that? Although she said so
MONSTER IDOL and others often say I have bad breath
So she probably remembered from there
And though it'd be funny to say it because of that, so it actually made me happy
I think it was to make things more lively
It doesn't actually stink?
It doesn't stink!
Super non-smelly
It must stink
Everyone can open their eyes
Ah, I can't tell
3 2 1
Then please eat at the same time
Kuro-chan's not doing it
Ah, it's me
Eh? Wait...
No, no, it's me
What's going on?
It's everyone~
So stupid. What the hell?
Everyone yo-
Going to be hated
Going to be killed
My nose hurts
So bad
Ah, so happy~
He is the only one laughing
Wonderful, what a great life this is
Is it okay?
No replies from anyone
Thank you for your hospitality
Drinking alone at night
Kuro-chan
Ah, you're drinking?
I was wondering if we should go out for a drink
Now?
-Yeah
Okay!
Can you?
This girl said he doesn't stink
Finished it all in one gulp
Let's go！
There's no way he doesn't stink
Want to go~
Cheers to Risa and Kuro-chan drinking at a bar alone
A toast to the bar
Brain isn't working
Tasty
-Yeah tasty
That... you clean up nicely
You look like a beautiful actress
No, no, no, no
No, no, I'm just a chatterbox little girl
A chatterbox little girl?
We often see this expression
When we all go on a date together and go to dinner together
I don't really take the initiative
Not as straightforward as Miku or Richi
"I like you"... I can't say it on my own initiative
So i'm very envious of them
No, she's good
Oh, really?
-I really think so
It's only the first day, but I'm a little concerned
Like, how to say... where I am out of the 6?
First, of course.
-Really?
Is it true? No lies?
No lies
The usual routine
I wouldn't lie to you
You can lie to other people as long as you don't lie to me
Really?
Self-centered
Because I like Risa the most
I want to believe in you
Can you look me in the eye and say you're not lying to me?
I can
Can you say it?
Of course
I am not lying to you
Really?
Really
I'm not lying to you either
Obviously lying!
I am so happy
It's been a long time since my heart beat so fast
Clever. Very cleverly put
That shows that i'm really not lying
Can I kiss the back of your hand?
You can, I want you to kiss it
You want me to?
-Yes
I like you the most
I don't believe it!
So soft
Eh, but only a kiss there?
Only a kiss there?
Terrible, terrible
Don't do that!
So warm
I've got goosebumps
An impactful image
Excited?
Disgusted
I got two
Ok ok, I believe you
Can you say this sort of stuff to others?
Ever said anything like this?
I can't say what Kuro-chan says
Not everyone can
He's really a playboy
A total playboy!
Its because he really wants to have a girlfriend
Thank you for waiting!
Next, I'll announce who I like
In order from 1st to 5th place
What'll he do?
The one whose name is not called at the end
Will have to say goodbye today
1st place is
There's gonna be trouble
Risa
She climbed the ranking!
Thank you
What excuse will be made this time?
Next in 2nd place is
Angry?
Miku
Last time she was 1st
Then
3rd place is
Mami
Thank you
4th place is
Mina
Whoa, a big change!
Thank you
These two remain
Richi looks like she's gonna cry
5th place is
Richi
Deliberately left to the end
He's used this tactic before, right?
Indeed he has
Today we are saying goodbye to Naru
The reason I didn't choose you
Is I see you more like a sister
I don't think its possible to be lovers
So I didn't choose you
Really?
One last time, do you really like me, Naru?
No I don't
Eh? You didn't you sign up because you like me?
Good good good
Eh? Why?
No... you seemed to like me so much, it's too strange for it to be fake, right?
No hesitation
I thought you really liked me, so I answered you with all my heart
I can only think of you as a sister, that's why I made my decision
Eh, why?
So you didn't sign up?
Why do you look so sad now when you didn't sign up? Why?
I don't get it at all
Because she was eliminated, right?
Eh? What's going on?
Reluctant to go, right?
No, no... didn't you lie to me?
Why this expression... Eh? What's going on?
I don't understand
Don't like me?
Not really
What's going on? What's going on?
Really?
Eh? How many girls are there that don't like me?
That's four out of nine people so far
Then there must be a lot of them
Is there really any that like me?
There are?
So I need to find them out of these 5?
I'll find them, i'm tired of being duped
I told you, didn't I?
I am here to find a girlfriend
Well, not just this time... I've tried every time
When I find the one this time, she'll become my girlfriend
And then?
Marriage!
You'll get married?
Yes!
Seriously?
I'm not playing around with love
Whoa so cool!
It's going well
Already overcome a lot of hurdles
Well, that's it for this time
She was so quick to answer
Because she was just pretending
No hesitation at all
"Do you like me?" "No."
She downplayed it
Like the speed of a street interview
And Richi said his mouth stinks
So what's going on?
I think Richi is pretending, and couldn't help but admit that he stinks
Reflexively, I said "it stinks".
-Indeed
But it can't always stink
Kuro-chan?
-Kuro-chan
Because at the lion statue experience
I told you its a "lion statue making experience"!
What the hell?
What does it mean?
Lion statue experience is to experience being the statue, surely
What is he talking about?
Does it matter?
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03