Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
It's Chidori!
Hello everyone, thank you for having us
This time we bring you a very interesting theory
Does anyone here smoke?
I have already quit
Matsumoto, did you quit?
-Yes
How long did it take? Was it long?
It was tough as at one point I used to smoke 5 packs a day
5 packs a day?
100 cigarettes
Hamada smokes electronic cigarettes, right?
Yes, yes, not the real kind
A lot of comedians don't smoke anymore, I also quit
Daigo is a very heavy smoker
-Yes
He gives that impression I guess
Except for this sort of situation, he's always smoking
In private he's just a cloud of smoke
It's really one after another
- It's true, I can't see all that well most of the time
It gets worse when there is a competition
At the time of M-1 I was on two cartons
20 packs?
So, this time is a theory about smoking enthusiasts, please take a look
People who love to smoke will go for it even if the road to the smoking area is full of challenges
I see...
I'll go wherever the hell I need to
Will you fight for your life?
-Of course I will
If I tell you that the smoking area is there
My head will still be there later
Daigo will definitely be there
To get to that point?
Sometimes on a location shoot, even if there's only a 10 minute break he'll go to smoke
That goes without saying
He would really go to smoke and make the staff and guests wait for him
Even if he is reminded not to smoke while shooting on location
He said, "If I don't smoke, I can't go on."
I go to smoke to take care of the staff who are also addicted to smoking
Let everyone also have a 10-minute break, that's what I think
No, no, no, you are forcing the issue
Next, smokers will carry out a variety of fancy challenges to be allowed to smoke
I'll definitely climb up
And
A partner who shows signs of being brainwashed by a diviner
If they propose a change of name, the other party will never agree to it
I am the director, my name is Taguchi
And, do celebrities remember the names of the attendees they're having a meeting with?
An on-site spot check
What is the name of this gentleman?
People who love to smoke will go for it even if the road to the smoking area is full of challenges
Those chosen as targets are the biggest smokers in the entertainment industry who smoke more than two packs a day
The five people were assembled for a fake program
And lured to an abandoned school in Atami
Dragging people to Atami
There is some free time prior to the official start of shooting
No matter what difficulties they encounter, will they really fight for their lives for a cigarette?
The first smoker comedian is...
Who could it be?
Thank you
Unagi
This man can smoke
These artists took a two-hour non-smoking bus ride from Tokyo to arrive
Smoking's not allowed on the bus anymore
Thus, when arriving at the scene, they were all dying for a cigarette
So, what will happen
Can I smoke?
-Yes
Unable to contain his excitement anymore
As soon as he leaves the building, he rushes to the smoking area, cigarette in mouth
But there...
Definitely not seeing anything good, right?
Eh?
What the hell is that?
Difficulty Level 1 - Smoke in the smoking area
Is this on fire?
Eh?
Will Unagi really smoke in this setting?
Looks like a fire
Who would dare to go in there?
Excuse me?
The place is completely on fire
Strong fumes!
The smoke stinks!
After confirming it wasn't really on fire
Must be going in
Can't see anything
He really went in
Cigarettes may have such a magical power
You have to be inside to smoke it, right?
Although the door was open, he enters the smoking area before lighting a cigarette
Really can't see anything at all
Can't even see if he's smoking
Even so, he's gotta smoke
After smoking, the plan is disclosed
Are we shooting already?
How do you feel?
Huh? No?
What is this...what is this whole thing?
Smoking... smoking area?
After communicating the project to Unagi
Is it that funny?
I did smoke
Even if it's difficult, you'll still go for it
Even if it is skirting the edge of the law
You'll also walk the red line out of desperation
It's definitely a fight to the death
After gaining a better understanding of this smoker's psychology
The next smoker is...
Morita
Again, soon after the meeting...
Where can I smoke here?
You have to go outside the campus to smoke it. It doesn't matter, right?
-It's okay
Told by staff that the smoking area is outside
Morita follows the signs
This time the smoking area is set up in...
A circular 1.5km route
Will people who love to smoke really not avoid traveling long distances to smoke a cigarette?
Difficulty Level 2 - 1500 metres to find the smoking area
All are quite disciplined
500 meters after the start, he has walked one-third of the course
What has appeared?
Difficulty Level 3- Vicious dog blocking the road
Eh? Eh?
A wild dog!
Nicotine vs. wild dog
So scary so scary
So scary!
Keeping an eye on him
It's a skinny Doberman
After that, he climbed all the way up the trail
Too far, too far, too far, too far
It's too far
Then it's downhill
Too far away
Really complaining a lot
There it is!
15 minutes after he left, he finally arrives at the smoking area of the school
15 minutes?
Must be tough
I've already done a big circle, right?
Getting annoyed
So hot, so hot!
Difficulty Level 4 - 90 degree C sauna smoking area
He's still going for it
So hot!
Really smoking
Scary
Are you serious?
You'd definitely still want to smoke
Cigarettes are impressive!
Even so, Morita didn't leave the smoking area until he finished his cigarette
It did feel farther than you'd think it'd be
But I always feel that the smoking area is too far away
After seeing a Doberman
I thought it might be a trap
As long as you want to smoke
You will never go back until you've smoked, right?
Once the addiction takes hold, no matter what obstacles are in the way, there's no turning back
That's the sad thing about smokers
The next smoker comedian is...
Kaminari's Manabu
Doesn't give the impression of a smoker
The time is 8pm
Can you even see your hands at this time?
It feels a bit scary
It is dark inside the abandoned school without electricity
Scary
In such a condition
Is there a smoking area?
-Smoking area is...
Take the lantern
Difficulty Level 5 - Fear of Darkness
Like filming a paranormal location shoot, one must go through an abandoned school at night to the smoking area
Whoa, scared the hell out of me
Despite being scared to death, he doesn't look back
Following the signs he makes his way outside
Lurking in this deep darkness is...
Whoa!
SASUKE kindly lent us one of their obstacles
This program loves SASUKE, right?
The ashtray stands at the top of the incline
Special Production Smoking Area Tower
Is this not a smoking area?
There is only one option
How does it work?
You want to smoke so badly?
That's how much he wants to smoke
So difficult
You need good shoes for it
Definitely can't climb up, right
Try your best
One more time!
What?
So difficult
Wrong side
It feels as if this is the end
This is the end
So funny
Its hopeless
Wants to smoke so badly
Beaten down by incredible difficulty, he falls into despair
And so the project is disclosed
In fact, this has long been exposed
If he still acts surprised then he's lying
There's no way around it
Absolutely no way
There's no solution to this
Only those who are willing to gamble everything can achieve success
So I can't succeed here
How are you feeling now?
Still want to smoke, want to smoke even more actually
And so, the day after the start of this verification
Three difficulty levels are set up on the way to the smoking area
It has thus become even more of a round of SASUKE
The first challenger of Cigarette SASUKE is...
Sumo wrestler and smoker comedian artist Akatsu
Looking forward to this
Akatsu suits this program
No smoking here, right?
I love SASUKE and Akatsu!
Can he overcome all the barriers on the way to the smoking area or not?
The first hurdle is...
1 - Gate of Weight
What is this?
Despite taking some time, he finally overcomes the barrier with a cigarette in his mouth
Where the hell is it?
Next is the second hurdle
Here?
2 - Ladder of knots
No, no, no. How is this possible?
The mouth says no, but the body...
It's a real climb!
So much effort just to smoke a cigarette
This ladder is ok, right?
For a mere cigarette
I can't believe he's doing this
All just for a cigarette, the rope ladder is also successfully passed
Cigarettes are terrible!
This fully illustrates the horror of cigarettes
Back in the building
Where?
Here is the third hurlde
What the hell do you want?
3 -  A protective moat
I still have my phone with me
A moat
This thing can be called a moat?
This sucks
Snow white snow white sneakers
And so, Akatsu...
Oh, using his head
Using a nearby wheelbarrow
He passes the moat area with a little foul play
The last thing standing in his way is...
Can just smoking a cigarette be so difficult?
Seriously, just let me have a good smoke, okay?
No. You must go to the smoking area.
What is this theory?
Akatsu has basically recognized the situation in the face of the towering smoking area
He put the cigarettes on the floor...
-Yeah
What is the result?
It hurts!
Your body is not suited to this
I have not done this kind of thing before
Come on...
No chance, no chance
So hot, so hot, so hot
He just wants to smoke a cigarette!
This height, to be honest I think it can be done
But...
Barefoot?
Is barefoot better?
Akatsu is impossible, the recoil is scary
Hot hot hot
Reaching a tower smoking area is no easy feat
The recoil is too intense
It hurts so much!
It doesn't take long to become physically and mentally exhausted
And so
Akatsu leaves as if he has remembered something
Gonna smoke on the side?
-What's wrong?
After all, he hasn't smoked yet
Yeah, hasn't had a puff yet
With one hand, he holds a rake he found somewhere
And so...
He's gonna hook and climb up it?
His posture looks like he's playing for real
What kind of athletic event is this?
Is this guy nuts?
Good, good, good, keep up the good work!
Dangerous!
So slippery
You can do it!
It hurts!
Surrender
What an great effort!
What's the point in disclosing now?
It's not like it was a prank
It's nothing, really
What a pity!
This is basically cheating
There are no rules here
I just want to smoke
Indeed
And so, the final challenger is...
Panther's Ogata
Ogata can really smoke
I'll go have a cigarette.
-Okay
1 - Gate of Weight
The first barrier of the gate of weight
Easily passed
2 - Ladder of knots
Next, the rope ladder
Everyone just really wants to smoke
Climbing to the top without any doubt
No questions so far?
He's already there
3 -  A protective moat
What the hell is this...
In order not to dirty his beloved AIR MAX
He likes sneakers a lot
Oh its AIR MAX
He crosses the border barefoot
And so
Only despair remains
That's a great expression
Upon being able to see the smoking area, Ogata now understands
Not dry enough
He climbs to the beginning of the final level
What're you gonna do, Ogata?
What the hell...
Maybe he can do it?
Because he has good motor skills
What a pity
So close
Its promising
This time, I feel like there's a chance
Low-waisted pants
Don't worry about the low-waisted pants
Go for it!
Go, go, go!
So close
Next time you can climb up, right?
I'm cheering him on
Damn it!
Played soccer at Sendai Yuying High School
Number 10, Ogata
His sports level is still alive and well
And he slightly touches the top of the smoking area
I'm already here, so i'm definitely going to get up
It's already obvious, it's that show again
It's revealed!
What a pity!
Damn it!
Definitely climbing up
Obviously just wants to smoke a cigarette
Awesome
Can he go up this time?
I feel like he'll be able to go up this time
Hold on, hold on
So awesome
You can go to SASUKE now!
Success! Success!
Cigarettes
Oh here we go here we go
Smoking in such a place...
It must be very sweet
Simply cool, right?
In summary
As long as its to smoke a cigarette, climbing a towering wall is a child's play
Too impressive
Really wanted to smoke
They want to smoke, its something I can understand
Especially recently the number of places where you can smoke is decreasing
So the desire has grown stronger instead
It seems that after a lot of effort, smoking is better, but I still don't really understand it
That seems to make sense
Also, it's great to smoke in a very clean place
Like a very clean country station or something like that
Places where the air is particularly clean
But Hamada does not care about the rules when it comes to smoking
Hamada often smokes wherever he wants to
That's not good
Hamada smokes even in places where people don't smoke?
He thinks the rules don't apply to him
That's why juniors who want to smoke will gather around Hamada
Mobile Smoking Area
Let's welcome the next presenter
Who is it?
Oh, here we go. Here we go. Great
It's Kazutoyo Koyabu
Thank you for having me
Although this is a bit sudden, do you believe in divination?
Do athletes really believe in fortunetelling and such?
If I have to choose, I think I'm the one who believes in it
I believe in it.
-You believe in it?
Although there are real diviners
But there are also tricky suspicious people
There are people who want to cheat even if they are obviously incapable
I think there are good and bad
And so, the theory I bring today is
A partner who shows signs of being brainwashed by a diviner, if they propose a change of name, the other party will never agree to it
I see
So, a partner who is suddenly obsessed with suspicious or tricky diviners
Starts wearing suspicious Buddhist beads and holding suspicious crystals
Starts drinking suspicious water
All of this would make it obvious
It's not a serious kind of look
Terrible
Wallowing in an atmosphere of deception
Such a partner suddenly proposes to change the stage name of their group
"No, no, what are you talking about?"
We validate the theory of whether or not the partner will have such a response
I see
If Downtown's Hamada..
Hamada already always wears very suspicious Buddhist beads
They're not suspicious
-Now a little less, I guess
There was a time when you wore them to here
All the way to here
Occasionally you could see an elbow poking out
Only when bending
Occasionally the flesh will be caught in it
A partner who shows signs of being brainwashed by a diviner, if they propose changing your name, the other party will never agree to it
The first duo to be tested is Kaminari
Takumi, pretending to be obsessed with divination, proposes the name change to Manabu
So, one week before the implementation of the prank
What happened to that one?
I was introduced to a teacher in Saitama.
He said as long as you wear this it'll bring good luck, so I put it on
What a good actor!
But he said just wearing it doesn't make it that powerful
Suddenly? Suddenly?
This crystal, I don't put it at home, it's good to carry with you
It's too strange to carry it around with you
What?
For a whole week, Takumi is supposedly awed by the diviner
It will be like that
It'd be a bit worrying
Watch RoboCop
Dumbass!
Wearing this at the performance?
I don't need to take it off during the show
Good morning
-Good morning
How does it feel?
-Sounds like he believes it
Oh, really?
-Definitely
As such, the proposal to change the name goes ahead
But before that
Did you hear from Yamamoto (agent)?
Eh? What?
Although I was the only one who was chosen, that...
I'm going to be the host on "King's Brunch" or something
Wow, that's awesome.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah
Brunch is very influential, ah this'll help us in the future
Very helpful for the future
Our appearance fees will increase too most likely
Go up a notch, for sure
Because it is KING
From April
-I'm really happy for you
Such a nice guy
In such a way, by giving a false report
The stage is set for the "its thanks to the diviner" statement later
Finally, the changing the name prank begins
Can I talk to you about something?
-Hmm
So, I'm gonna start this thing in April.
-Yeah, yeah
My stage name is Takumi Ishida now, right? I'm using my real name.
-Yeah.
"Takumi" is usually written in hiragana.
-Yes, it is.
It's not a good idea to be a comedian and use hiragana.
What's not good? You researched it?
No, the teacher said.
-What teacher?
So, the Saitama
That teacher said it?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, that teacher...
You have to change your name after being told?
Well, I was wondering if I should change my name.
You're out of your mind, aren't you!?
What's wrong?
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Takumi's... eh? What's going on?
And I...
-Hiragana, right?
Yes, the teacher said to change the hiragana part
Although the prank has just started, the negotiation is in full swing
What is the name Takumi wants to change to?
Ishida?
Yes, I'll use the kanji: Ishida Yume (Dream) Mon (Door)
Are you out of your mind? I can't even read it
It's a borrowed word...
-Not a borrowed word
Manabu has become the straightman
If I change the name to something other than Takumi
People who have been calling me Takumi won't be able to to do it anymore so it'll be tough for them
The number of strokes is better
Yumemon? Takumi?
Dream Gate?
It's not read as Takumi
Yumemon can be read as Takumi...
No, it's Ishida Mumon (Dream Gate). What the hell is that?
To be honest, I'm scared too.
-What are you afraid of?
It's only been a week since I got this from my teacher.
Such a big job coming in one week
Do not be mistaken, it is because of your own efforts
But I didn't do anything, it not my effort
No. You've tried hard. You've tried hard.
Just living in general
You're working hard
It is difficult for other comedians to notice the effort
Yes?
-Yes, yes, yes.
Your success isn't down to Buddhist beads
No matter how many times I have to say it, its because of your own efforts
This guy has become like a teacher
Trying to brainwash him, right?
You appeared in the M-1 Grand Prix under the hiragana name Takumi.
Were you a Mumon (Dream Gate) at that time?
But perhaps we didn't win because my name wasn't Mumon (Dream Gate) at the time
It's becoming like a diviner's tone
Divination of this type, you don't like it?
-It's like...
You've spent money, right? You've been fooled into buying something.
I haven't been fooled, its my money to spend how I want
You were fooled into buying stuff
You're not that type of person, Takumi.
But our popularity has been stagnant for the past two years
It'll change. It's okay, it's okay.
But the reason nothing has changed in the past two years is...
It' s only been two years, no need to rush
-But
Only two years, no need to rush.
I put on the beads and so on with the idea of trying it out.
One week later, the Brunch job came up.
So I think changing my name might be a good idea
But other people can still call me Takumi, it's just that the characters are different.
Our Manzai, the start of all our routines
"What's wrong, Takumi?" "What's wrong, Manabu?"
This is how it starts, right?
When you say "that, that, Takumi-kun", the kanji for "Mumon" (Dream Gate) will come to mind
It's gross!
It's not that big of a deal
I'd be thinking, "This guy is Mumon! (Dream Gate)"
It's not Mumon, it's Takumi
I can't believe there are people who are so gullible
Consider the feelings of person who has to be hit on the head by such a guy, okay?
I mean it.
-I'm not being lied to.
I'm not convinced
It's really not convincing
Take it off already, it's so hot.
What? Don't you hate this kind of stuff?
Getting really mad
I do not want to associate with such people, I really can't trust people who buy such things
It's not like i'm asking you to buy something
No, wait, wait, wait.
It's my own business.
-No, no, no.
Your life is my life and my life is your life
To work together, hand-in-hand
Wow, so cool.
How moving
A guy buying shit like that, wearing it and believing in it, changing his name and so on.
I'd think, "Are you kidding me?"
Your life is my life
The childhood friends from the nursery school who later became partners
Life partners who have been working together for a long time
Now being deceived by a suspicious diviner
And wants to become "Dream Gate"
Anguish and resentment fill his partner's heart
I really want to change my name to Dream Gate Takumi from April onward, is that okay?
-No
No?
Absolutely not?
-If that's the case then let's disband.
Disband if I want to change my name?
Disband, its unbelievable and unreasonable
That the person who has worked hard with me up until now
Was fooled into buying something by a shitty guy and wants to change his name
Can't do it, can't do it, can't do it, can't do it.
If it's gonna go on like this then lets just disband
Give me the guy's contact information.
-Why?
I'll call him.
-No need.
A real man
I'm really gonna call him
-There's no need
I'm going to say, "Are you fucking kidding me?"
-No need for that.
There's definitely loads of victims who need to talk to the police.
I'm not a victim in terms of results, I got the job at Brunch.
No, no, no. This has nothing to do with Brunch.
As the group is moving towards disbanding, the truth is quickly disclosed.
What!? Ah, seriously, enough!
What is this?
What do you think?
Wednesday Downtown
Correct answer
-I knew it
Seriously...
This is awful, seriously awful
Were you scared?
-Absolutely
Did you notice the water?
I noticed it
Noticed it
Have you noticed that I've been drinking this?
-Yes.
I found it very suspicious.
Ah, don't drink it.
-This costs 5,000 yen. 5,000 yen.
So stupid, isn't it?
Unbelievable!
That's it. The next duo is
Impulse
So realistic
For this, the trap is prepared in advance
Fortunetelling and my current situation can be linked pretty well
※Atsushi Tsushita was dropped from Yoshimoto due to a dangerous driving accident 17 years ago and only just came back
He'll probably say "Ah, here we go again..."
I don't know
That or "I can't do this anymore"
In the end, what will happen? I'm looking forward to finding out
I am also very nervous
I've never set anyone up before
So, for the first time in 21 years of the group's existence, he will prank his partner
In the past a fortuneteller told me "you're possessed by eels"
That's not impossible.
-Absolutely impossible?
I'd be slippery like an eel
That's pretty accurate I guess
-Accurate!
Impulse's name changing prank begins
First
Have you ever prayed to Buddha to get rid of misfortune?
Can't say I have
In my hometown there's a diviner
Like a teacher
The thing I'm wearing now was made for me by him
That's a lot of beads
This one is awesome
After I put it on, I had a good time.
Who is this person? He's a fortune-teller?
More of a diviner than a fortuneteller
Fortunetelling, and mediumship, he does all sorts
What the hell?
Beginning with providing some details of the diviner
The topic moves to name changing
He said "It'd be better if you change your name."
Huh?
Stage name change?
-My name
Comedian name
I have 15 strokes in "Seshita", which is not a problem.
But in "Tsu"
-Hmm
It doesn't have enough strokes
So i'm thinking to change it to Tsutsumishita Revolution
The number of strokes is good cause it has 20
It's not strokes, it's in katakana.
From now on, changes have to be made
So that's why it's "revolution".
-Yes, yes, yes.
I think it's good
You want to become a "Revolution" yourself.
-Yes
You really want to change it?
-If I can
So is it that you are thinking to change it
I felt good when I saw it
Or is it that you do not want to change, but after being told...
Ah, it's not that I don't want to change
You want to become "Revolution"!
Yes, a person you can trust.
You'll get stuck that way.
-Stuck?
Stuck in a storm of Katakana, Impulse Tsutsumishita Revolution
I'll keep being called Tsutsumishita though
Something like Revolution is impossible
I don't need to say it, right?
-No need to say it
But at least when introducing myself
I will say "I am Tsustumishita Revolution, please take care of me" or something like that.
You'll say it like that?
I am quite annoyed by the name change thing
I'm opposed to it
But in the case of the "Tsutsumishita Revolution"
I think it is possible
Tsutsumishita Revolution
Really? So... I can register this stage name...
Eh? Is it that urgent?
Because it is April
It is if you want to change...
From April 1st...
Unexpectedly, Itakura does not defuse the change to "Tsutsumishita Revolution".
Is "Revolution" OK then?
You don't have any particular opinion about me becoming a "Revolution"?
Instead of saying, "I agree," I would rather say, "It's none of my business."
What do you mean "none of my business"?
When you are asked "Why did you become Revolution?"
If you can answer well, then its fine
If I can answer the question well?
Don't talk about "because of the number of strokes"
That's ok?
All kinds of ... well, it's better to not to say
Surprisingly, the name change was approved
And so, the truth is revealed
This is probably the first time I've experienced this kind of scene
I really feel uncomfortable right now
I thought, "He finally went to the gods and asked the ghosts".
It just so happens that in his current state it's a real possibility
Well, it's just the status quo, the status quo.
-It's not impossible.
You were very gentle
Yes, I was a little scared.
But if I say "you can't do that"
And then he'd yell at me like "Are you kidding? This is the truth".
In this sort of situation I think its best not to say too much
To people who have been brainwashed like this
But ultimately, what I thought was
Tsutsumishita Revolution is actually pretty good
Don't you think it'll be a big hit?
I think it's got a good ring to it
Next, the final duo is Yasei Bakudan
Of course, Cookie will be the one setting the trap
But he has already changed his name once
So this time, the element of divination is removed
As he will directly propose a name change to his partner
How will it turn out?
I...need to change my name
Change your name?
-Yeah.
Not Cookie anymore.
-Eh?
That's a shock
It says "the number of strokes is not good".
Number of strokes?
Mm-hmm.
Change to what?
Change it to Aihara YOU
※ A female entertainer who was active from the late 80s to the first half of the 90s.
What is it? Is it "Yasei Bakudan's Aihara YOU"?
Aihara is Aihara, YOU is the English YOU
Even when you became "Yasei Bakudan's Cookie"...
You were "Yasei Bakudan's Kawashima" and then "Cookie".
Although at first I thought "huh?"
It turned out pretty well, right?
No idea what to say about "Aihara You"?
The number of strokes and so on, some people really care about this sort of thing...
It's good energy
Is it to be announced externally in this form?
Announced in today's interview program
Oh really?
Yes, so i'm telling you first.
Well, it's still interesting, right?
It's good to try all kinds of things
As expected of the great wonder, Rossy
He also easily ignores the name belonging to someone else
He's impressive to ignore this
So, a proposal to change the duo's name is also brought up
A two-person thing now
To change our name as a duo
Eh? Change our name?
Yes, I'll need your agreement, of course.
Change to what?
I want to change it to "Peter Pan" because I am "Aihara You".
What do you mean? I don't understand
The number of strokes for "Peter Pan" is not good
Peter Pan in katakana and hiragana isn't good either.
So we should change it to "flying human" and pronounce it as "Peter Pan".
Flying...flying human?
-Flying Human
Although it seems to be "flying human", it is pronounced as "Peter Pan"
Like one of those strange names
※キラキラネーム：Parents choose strange Chinese characters and change the pronunciation to name their children in order to make them sound good.
Oh
By the way, in the interview done beforehand
Do you think your duo's name change will be approved?
I think it will be unpleasant
A name cultivated over the space of 24 years is important
Inside will he feel unpleasant?
I want him to feel bad about it, I hope he thinks the name is important
I see
-Indeed
In light of Cookie's comments, what will happen?
Is it possible?
-Yes, I think so.
No need to stick to a name, we can use a variety of names
So it's okay, it's perfectly fine.
This is completely fine, the way the duo looks remains the same anyway
In short, from now on, we are "Peter Pan".
-"Peter Pan".
"We are Peter Pan", right?
Agreed without a hitch
So, finally, the move to have Rossy change his name begins
In this case, you also change your name
We change the name of the group, I changed my name too
If you don't change, it might be a bit weird
Change together will be better
"It's like this. It's like this." It's perfectly fine.
I guess
It is perfectly fine to change it
This one is also OK'd without hesitation
This look of indifference is almost one of fear
The new name is?
Sisounou (abscess) Ro
Surely he won't go for this one
Since your name now is Ro, and Si
It'll be easy to move to this from Rossy
It's the same thing as me as Cookie
It becomes easier to say Coo
So "Sisounou Ro" is okay, right?
"Sisounou Ro"? "Peter Pan"?
Well, "Peter pan"...
Well, if the number of strokes is good, this is fine.
"Hello, I'm Sisounou Ro" like this
"Rossy has changed, I am Sisounou Ro"
That's it, then, I think. In today's interview.
-Hmmmm
So it's an interview with a focus on the name change
I'll get the agent to make sure this is focused on
Ok, understood
Is that OK? Like this
Yes, it's perfectly fine.
Then I am "Peter Pan's Aihara YOU".
Then I am "Sisounou Ro's"
-No.
Eh? "I am Peter Pan's Sisounou Ro."
-That's it
It's become like this.
-This sort of vibe
Yes
-OK
In summary
Rossy is an unusual beast
Awesome
-Impressive
This is the result. What do you think?
The initial segment was very moving
A duo's love
Yes, it is.
-Very cool.
But the other two, what is happening to Yoshimoto's groups!?
There's not even someone called Sisounou in the Takeshi Gundan, right?
Surprisingly easy to accept
The personality of each group is clear
-Yeah
What the hell, is Rossy trying to go home early?
That was his well-considered position
Feels like even if he's asking him to give him a XXXX he'll go along with it
"You can have it."
-"You can take it all if you want"
Next is everybody's theories
Today's presenters are Chocolate Planet
Don da ke!
-Slow walk slow walk
Super popular
The audience in the back is going "Wow!"
-Thank you all very much!
It was unresponsive when we came before.
-Yes, there was no reaction before.
I guess its fine to say we're popular, then. Thank you very much.
Pretty popular
-Although he says so himself
I would like to ask you all
Do you remember the names of program staff?
Yes, I remember
It's only right to remember if it's your regular program staff.
This time, the theory related to this is
Do celebrities remember the names of the attendees they're having a meeting with?
I see
Self-introduction is always over at once, right? I'm director such-and-such
After listening to it, do you really remember it or not?
Honestly, i'm not very good at remembering people
There was an overseas location shoot before
To travel around the world for a week to five countries for recording
I didn't know the name of the director until the second country
Did you know?
I wrote it down, but I don't think it's that important
I won't remember them till I die or anything
But it is definitely better to remember names
Hamada does it best
He just calls everyone "you bastard"
I've never said such a thing
"You bastard", something along those lines
-I've never called you "you bastard" before.
"You bastards are working hard today."
Do celebrities remember the names of the attendees they're having a meeting with?
I really can't remember. It's really bad.
So the first target was
This guy is definitely not listening
Viking's Nishimura
Impossible for Nishimura
Hello
He is called under the guise of a fake meeting
I am the director, Kobayashi
Kobayashi is a tough one
After saying the name clearly and unmistakably like this
We rush in instantly
Straight away
※After 30 years in the wrestling business, he will retire on January 4, 2020.
Then
We will now give you a simple test
If the answer is wrong
Liger will punish you
So please answer well
So the question
What is this gentleman's name?
Eh? Did you introduce yourself just now?
Introduced at the beginning
Uwa~
As a member of civilized society you should remember other people's names...right?
Yes, otherwise it is not polite.
Then please answer
Sawada!
Incorrect
I don't know, wow, tragic
Unfortunately, as the answer is wrong
I'll leave it to you, Liger.
-Okay
And so
Let' go
What is this? It hurts.
It hurts up there, too. It hurts up there.
Nishimura is uncivilized
It hurts. I'm so sorry.
The next target is
Little Vegetable Club's Okani
I'm the director, Taguchi
Very clearly stated
You should know that.
What is this gentleman's name?
Wait...wait a minute
Taguchi
Correct
Right answer?
Absolutely correct
Next, Diane's Tsuda
What is this gentleman's name?
Matsuda
Correct
What is this?
Eh, wait, so it's ok?
A name just heard can be remembered in general
Next, we increase the number of staff from one to three
Raising the difficulty
This is so hard
The participant of the challenge is an individual who is known to be very attentive and responsive.
Dressing very handsomely
So trendy
Yoshimura
Such an interesting look
I'm Taguchi, the director
I'm Ishizawa, the writer
I'm the assistant director Sano
And so
Eh, what is going on?
What is this, it's too fast, right?
So the question is
What are the names of these gentlemen
Please answer the names of these three
Give me a moment
Do you remember any of them?
Probably this one and this one I can answer barely
You're the assistant, right?
I don't remember
Taguchi is in the middle.
Correct
Who is the writer...
Ishizaki
Ah what a pity
Incorrect
And so
Grit your teeth and remember the name!
Remember, remember
Let's go
The final target is
Looks powerful
Seems like she'll remember
SKE48's Akari Suda
She claims to remember the names of all her fans
So we challenge her with six staff members
They look alike!
How will it go?
This is so hard
I am the president of the production company Shooting Star
My surname is Honaga
She's writing
Suda immediately records the staff information in her notebook
As she usually has the habit of writing down names in a notebook
This time, however, she is given a closed book challenge
So the question is
What are the names of these gentlemen
Please answer the names of all people
※The names of the people appearing in this project are actually all borrowed from professional wrestlers
Honaga, right?
Correct
Kushida
The next answers are all correct
Taguchi
Last man left
Eh, the last one...
What was it again...
I'm really sorry...
Suda
Unfortunately, the answer is wrong
Therefore
It hurts it hurts it hurts it hurts
Super painful
Thank you very much for your hard work.
-Thank you for your hard work.
She's an idol!
Ah wait a minute, please come here and wait a minute
But it's awesome!
Please wrap up the segment
5 seconds, 4 3 2
So here's a question
Please come over here
This staff member has been on the location shoot today
He is a director
What is the name of this director
Eh, you're testing me?
Yes, in fact, the morning of this day
A staff meeting with Liger took place
I'm the director, Hisano
I'm XXX, thank you
They were certainly introduced
Can't even see his face but he told him his real name
Will he remember it or not?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Eh, is this real? Seriously?
Who's going to hit me?
If the answer is wrong, the director, Hisano will punish him
Definitely has an iron fist of rage!
If you don't get it right, you'll be slapped by Hisano
Hisano...
He said it!
He screwed up
Thank God!
Grit your teeth and take it like a man!
Prepared?
What the hell, seriously
This is completely screwed up
In summary
Remembering and using names should be done carefully
What can you say, the presenter said it first
Beautifully presented and completed beautifully
He said the name so obviously but he clearly didn't remember it
To be fair, I don't remember the male presenter's name at all
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03