Subbed by flydaychinatown
How is everyone? This is a news show that introduces many things from around the world.
I'm the anchor, Giles Besson.
Around 400 years ago on this day, Musashi and Kojiro had their legendary sword fight at Ganryuji.
What's happening around the world today?
Let's ask our panel.
First, let's turn to our economic analyst from New York, Ghorchyan Afshin. Hi, Ghorchyan!
Hi, Giles!
Thanks for asking me to join you on the inception of this great show.
Thanks for coming from so far to join us.
We're awaiting your sharp analysis of economical news!
Of course.
Andn ow the Youth Org. Chairperson, Natalia Bazarova, Hi Natalia!
Hi, Giles!
You look beautiful, as usual.
Thanks. I want to focus on the energetic eyes of Asian children.
She's been practicing that line.
Excellent!
That's such a cute opinion.
Let's do lunch some time.
OK, I'll think about it.
Next, Japan's greatest comedian, Masatoshi HamaTA
Ah, thank you. Good evening!
Excellent!
I'm awaiting your funny reactions!
Ok.
And Hamata's sidekick, Hitoshi Matsumoto!
Thanks, good evening-
Oh!
Matsumoto, you look ilke Ken Watanabe from "The Last Samurai!"
Totally the same!
That was hilarious!
Giles, that was funny!
That funny?
Just go along with them, I guess.
Hamata, if you can think of something funny, go ahead.
He called you "Hamata."
It's "Hamada!"
So, on to our news!
Hey, It's "Hamada!"
From the Philippines, Roberto Gabishan.
Hi, I'm Roberto Gabishan from the Philippines.
We have a weird cafe to show you.
In this cafe, the owner gives a strange "service" to his customers.
Let's go see what that service is!
Come on!
So, we ventured to the cafe "Mon Ama Rik."
As we entered, the owner was waiting for us.
The owner, Bong Omega, was waiting for us with another "service" to show us.
Bong, what kind of service are you going to show us today?
It is a totally free service! But there is one condition.
If the customer's reaction is good, they get their food and drink for free!
What kind of reaction? Look at this, whatdja think it is?
Invented in Japan, it artificially simulates the sound of someone farting!
That makes the sound of a fart?
Yeah! Why don't you try it out? Just sit on it!
I farted! I farted!
It was a pretty good reaction, too!
I start laughing at the reaction our customers will have when they sit on it!
So we set up three hidden cameras in the cafe
Bong and Roberto waited for their first victim.
And then!
Here she is! She's pretty hot, too!
Hey there! Honestly, this was kind of a "candid camera."
It was a great reaction! You can order anything you want for free!
Next is a guy who's kind of scary.
Here he comes!
Hey there! Honestly, that fart was "candid camera."
Did you really think you farted?
Next, another guy.
Wow, this guy looks pretty scary!
He turned pink!
You really surprised me!
We thought so too!
Next is a couple.
Who's gonna fal for it? The boyfriend?
Did you see that? What a reaction!
What was that sound?
It wasn't me!
He said "it wasn't me," better help him out!
Was that really what happened?
So today we introduced a mischevious cafe in the Philippines.
Call us again when you have a good idea!
I already figured one out! Next time you come
it will make us famous all over the Philippines!
Thanks, Gabishan.
What did you think of that report, Ghorchyan?
Well, America is focusing the most on the Philippines out of all of Asia
but that shop owner was crazy!
Thanks for your sharp opinion.
How about you, Natalia?
Well, I disagree.
I think that the Philippino children look energetic and strong!
Excellent!
What about, you Hamata?
It's "Hamada."
That wasn't funny at all.
I see.
Why do they get so many laughs off such a lame reaction?
Well, that's a different opinion.
I guess Japanese Gay-nin don't get it.
So next is Thailand...
Just kidding, Matsumoto!
I was pretending to ignore you!
You can ignore me for all I care.
But yeah, the laughs were pretty lame. Well...
Well, when that happens, how do Japanese Gay-nin react?
Hey!
Holy shit this is lame!
No one will laugh at this!
Matsumoto, show us how a Japanese Gay-nin reacts!
Man, this sucks!
No way, no way-
Wow!
Hilarious!
Funny as all hell!
Japanese Gay-nin are the best!
Stop calling us "Gay-nin."
It's "Geinin."
And now, we have a commercial.
It's not "Gay-nin." It's "Geinin."
Next, from the Philippines again, we have Robert Gabishan!
Hi, this is Robert Gabishan, again.
Why the hell did he bow?
Next, we'll look at a store that gives away money!
Could this be true?
Let's go see!
We went to downtown Cebu to see what was going on and found a long line. What's happening?
Are you attending this event?
Yeah! It's Awesome! If you try hard you can get a lot!
Being able to get money for free is great!
Boss, why are they all coming to your store for free money?
Well, the economy has been bad and all. I thought this would be a good way to bring it back.
I hadn't sold a single TV set, so I guessed if I got a lot of people in front of my shop, someone would buy something!
I sell way more than I give away now!
We wondered what this free money event was, so we watched...
Good luck!
Start!
One peso...
Two pesos...
Three pesos...
You get as many pennies as you can plug your nose with.
That's all for you, they're slipping out. You get three!
Next is a guy who has trained in the art of nostril stuffing.
Wow! He's stuffing a load in there!
He stuffs a load in...
However!
I'm done!
He stuck them so far in that they won't come out!
You did a great job!
That's right, I got 17 pesos!
I'm going for the record next time!
That's great!
Next is a taxi driver.
He got 14 pesos in.
This guy found a good way to stick his money in.
Wow, you're doing a good job!
He stuck 16 pesos in his nose.
This unemployed guy tried his luck.
Hey, don't stick it in so far that you cry, idiot!
17, 18, 19, 20, 21! Good job!
Chief, great job with this! You have a lot of customers, too!
Yeah, the other guys just take all my money and go home.
I have to think of a different system or something.
So with this unique event, that's all from me, Roberto Gabishan!
Thanks, Gabishan!
It was a great idea, Ghorchyan!
You know, America thought that the philippines will come up with some crazy shit, and they totally did!
Got it. How about you, Natalia?
Well, I totally disagree.
Instead of noses, I see eyes!
The eyes of the Philippinos are energetic and strong!
Excellent!
How about you, Hamata?
It's "Hamada."
No matter what Ghorchyan says, you always say "I disagree," right?
She always disagrees.
She won't say anything back.
What's this? Wait a moment!
Hey Ghorchyan...
you totally look like Nicholas Cage, huh?
I'm so embarassed!
Ha ha ha ha!
This is pissing me off.
Hamata, what do you think?
Do people ever say you resemble someone?
Well- It's "Hamada."
And no one has said that, but that video...
Matsumoto looks like Ken Watanabe though, right?
You don't give a shit about my comment.
Japanese Gay-nin really are number one!
Excellent! Excellent! Exceleeent!
Listen to what Matsumoto has to say, dumbass!
Matsumoto!
Matsumoto...
What did you think of the video?
How much is one Peso anyway?
We can't really judge how much they made.
One Peso is two Yen.
Two yen?
Well, I guess even though they tried so hard, they earned very little, huh?
It's tough for them.
But, it's free money.
Well yeah, but even though it's money,
it's not enough to buy anything!
Well, even if they can't buy anything,
the communication between them all is important, right?
Why the hell did you get so serious all of a sudden?
I don't get it!
That's not funny at all!
They're fucked up!
Hold on...
Excuse me!
Matsumoto, please continue.
But I'm already done.
Okay.
Hey!
Not this again!
What the hell?
It's going to be so lame!
Show us your Gay-nin spirit, Matsumoto!
Wow, this is so lame.
Seriously leave me out of this.
It's no different from the people in the video.
How is he gonna stuff those in?
Ow ow ow ow ow ow!
Matsumoto, you can really stuff it in!
Matsumoto, you really have some guts!
Ahh, Matsumoto...
We're just playing around.
Japanese Gay-nin really are hard workers!
What the hell?
It's good you did it, though.
You totally got him to do it!
Seriously Giles, you're the best!
The best!
OK, that's everything. I'm Giles Besson.
See you next week! Bye bye.
Hamata, Matsumoto, you guys did a great job!
Really great.
He's a great sidekick.
Yeah, just like "Last Samurai."
Yeah, cause you don't look like a ninja.
Gay-nin Gay-nin!