Translation and typesetting done by Jomato Subs
(u/SunThroughTheStorm)
En
Enjoy
Enjoy guys
[Cocorico Channel]
Okay,
let's start today's biology class
Yes, sir.
The theme of today’s class is
Sharks
Ooh, sharks, huh
When it comes to sharks
there are so many amazing things to learn
So guys,
for sharks, worldwide
how many different species do you think there are?
Hmm
The answer:
It's thought that there are over five hundred species world-wide
So you're just gonna tell us.
F-five hundred. Got it.
And, within those over 500 species,
Japan alone
has over a hundred
And,
out of these 500 species
About half - over 250 of these species
are said to live in the deep sea
Oooh, over half huh?
So, the deep sea
Deep sea, specifically...
Guys...
Mm?
'scuse me
Er...
As you all might already know,
"deep sea" refers to areas of water
over uh... 200 uh... meters deep
Hmm?
What's up?
The sea...
Since these areas are so deep...
When you think about it...
the deep sea... the light doesn't...
Hm? What's wrong?
Sensei?
The light doesn't...
because it's so deep...
Sensei?
What’s wrong?
Those sharks... uh....
If you put yourself in their shoes...
Since the light doesn't reach them...
Sensei? What's wrong?
Sensei?
Sorry about that
Huh?
Hahaha…
Huh huh huh?
Sensei, what just happened?
The light just…
what what what what
a life without light...
What was that?
What just happened?
I just feel like it must be so hard to live like that...
Aaah
But… uh…
If you think of it from their perspective...
Yeah, but why are you crying?
Why cry?
Huh huh huh huh?
Sensei?
S-seriously, what's wrong?
He's really going at it…
Why?
Wh-why?
What's wrong?
Sensei
Huh?
What? Whoa whoa whoa whoa....
What what what?
When it's so dark...
What? You’re gonna keep going?
Living in that darkness...
Jesus, this guy...
I guess I'm just thinking
If you look at it from their perspective...
It must be so hard to live like that
Hmm...
Whoa whoa whoa, what happened?
Why all of a sudden
Ever since that deep sea thing
you've just been crying the whole time
You just-
Are you really okay to keep going?
Sorry about that.
So out of these deep sea sharks...
Uh... uh...
Some... stay still...
While some swim around to look for foo-
What what what what?
They just keep swimming...
What was that just now?
looking for food... all the time...
Seriously, what the hell?
What the hell is wrong with this guy?
He can barely keep himself up now, what should we do?
What kind of sudden switch is this?
What is this?
Like seriously, what's going on?
What's going on?
Sensei…
We're in the middle of class...
Like mid-lecture...
Seriously man, you’re freaking me out
Can you call someone?
Anyone?
It’s no use…
Huh?
It’s no use…..
No use?
Absolutely no use...
Absolutely no use?
What's no use?
It's just so difficult...
So difficult... living like that...
Sensei
You can’t be empathizing with the sharks that much man…
Th… y…
Huh?
Tha… yo…
Thank you...
Thank you?
To what? To whom?
What? Huh?
Wh-what do you mean? What are you thanking?
They're so… they're so…
thank you...
Thank you to what though? To whom?
Sensei?
Whoa, what the hell?
You're scaring me man…
Huh? What's going on?
Uh... um...
Sorry about that…
Yeah…
Sorry sorry.
Uh…
Hahahahaha…
Huh?
Hahahaha…
Hahaha…
What’s going on?
Uh... Yeah... I'm really sorry about that...
Oh no, here goes again…
Here goes what again?
Seriously, I have no idea what’s going on here...
I don't get what's going on in his head, this guy
He's on his knees... He can't even stand up anymore...
Sorry about that. Uh... uh....
Yeah...
Class is over for today
Huh?
Uh... uh...
If you have any, uh, questions, I’ll be in the, uh, teachers room.
That’s it, bye
What the hell was that?
Weirdo...
Thanks for watching! Make sure to show your support by liking the original video and subscribing to Cocorico's channel!