Winning
People that entrust guidance, dreams and romance to a single post card
There is a man who continues to live life by winning contests...
Delushious~♥
Nasubi
Can people live by only winning prize contests?
The challenge is to win prizes by phone or postcard entry
The goal is to reach 1 million Yen in prize value.
Denpa Shonen Prize life contest
In the part one we saw Nasubi during the first half of the year from January to June 1998
To reach the 1 million Yen goal another 550,440円 remains
We will continue with the final part of the
Prize life contest struggle to the death!
He has reached the Japan goal with joy!
But then Prize life contest in Korea START?!
And the emotional goal event witnessed by 1000 people!
Plus also what Nasubi did after the event in this special movie!
Everything about the prize life contest is revealed right now!!
Nasubi's Denpa Shonen Prize life contest
Conclusion
Nasubi in July 1998
These are the entries for July, please watch in slow mode.
A total of 5,787 entries
Today, from the morning he writes postcard entries,
But there is no prize news at all
However there is one thing on his mind...
"Recently, I haven't won anything I can eat."
Nasubi hasn't won anything since the seaweed last month
And this month he has only won a sewing set
Honestly...
And Nasubi doesn't know that project has already started
Nasubi's room internet live stream!
Nasubi's room live broadcast internet video feed
By the way, this is the Nasubi live stream headquarters
Wearing staff T-shirts, 50 people watch over and control this 24 hours a day
Using the joystick they must cover up Nasubi's parts at all times
A live broadcast first ever historical challenge!
They could not let their guard down for even a moment!
Aaahhh!!
Watch out!
Be careful!
Please enjoy this staff under high pressure tension footage
This morning Nasubi is writing letters when...
Knock knock, Delivery Service
What is this I wonder?
I won a hair dryer ♥
I'm really not winning any food here
I can't eat this hair dryer can I...
A win?!
A win! Is it food?
But...
A how to video for removing bad armpit odor
I really can't eat this kind of junk
I'm in no situation to worry about this kind of thing!
It's true he is in no situation for that.
It's here, It's here, something came today too ♥
But...
Dammit!
This won't swell my stomach!
Small vacuum cleaner ♥
"Everyday there is a lack of food, yet I have 2 vacuum cleaners."
That's right, there was another he won before
Again, nothing I can eat!
I want to win food!!
Nothing came that he could eat, the winnings for July!
526,040 Yen remains until the 1 Million Yen goal
Nasubi in August
These are the entries for August
A total of 6,306 entries
Nasubi is writing as usual today
But as always...
"There is no winning food news."
Then...
Knock
Special delivery
A win!
Is it food this time!?
But...
This is not it !
But you know what... This is cool
No flavor though...
Something pretty cool with no flavor is...?
Pocket Board by Docomo ♥
TL:Mobile phone attachment to send 10 Yen E-mail upto 2kb!
"Dear lord! Next time can you change it to a little something edible, please!"
The next day
Was his wish able to reach God!?
I wonder what kind of thing has arrived ♥
But...
"It's a double, another double!"
Tooth brush and tooth paste set ♥
Like the vacuum cleaner before, this is the second toothbrush win
However this time...
Toothbrush x4 yay!
So many wins ♥
This is the one I got previously
Then Nasubi...
First time win
Second time win
Double toothbrush technique power
"Stop with these stupid wins! I need food!"
Nasubi is becoming desperate
BUT!
It started to bleed ♥
Bleeding for the second time too.
A few days later...
What could it be this time?!
Then...
Could this be...
I knew it
It's rice ♥
This is the 3rd rice win
Nasubi does his long lost winning dance
But his reaction is strange...
But you know... Although I'm happy to have alot of rice...
I'm really searching for something....
Something with a strong flavor you know...
Something fatty, juicy and greasy
I want some side dish!
I keep winning rice, so of course I want some side dish!
If I only had side dishes...
It would be only natural that I'd want  to eat rice!
Humans are such disgustingly selfish creatures.
Nasubi is having his only rice dinner
Today I didn't win any side dishes again...
Without side dishes... Summer will never come for me.
To reverse these thoughts he wins something wonderful that indicates the start of summer...
The start of summer item is...?
Inflatable ring ♥
However
I feel sick
Feeling sick?
There certainly is a reason for that
"When I received it, there was no meaning to it. All crumpled and flat"
"But when I began to inflate it, I soon ran out of stamina..."
"And my head became all dizzy"
"I could see water fleas here and there floating in front of my eyes"
"It was a bad situation!"
And after this a big event that will certainly tell Nasubi summer is here!
Nasubi is writing a letter when...
What happened?
Hm?
"The air-con stopped...!!"
Hold on a sec...
Hey! Why did it suddenly stop like that?
Two hours later
This heat is uncomfortable
I should open the window
It's just getting hotter with it closed
Ah, the locust are singing
Then two hours later ...
Nah. I can't write postcards in a situation like this
It's too hot.
The next day
Good morning (Day 201)
Or rather, It's HOT!
Hot, hot, hot, hot hottttttt!
Today, Nasubi has stopped writing postcard entries
Work!
Then...
Beep ♥
(Breeze)
It's working ♥
Air-con restoration dance!
"Although I don't have any idea about what happened..."
"What a fearful thing."
After this a definitive summer item is won...
What is a defining summer item?
Watermelon ♥
"Speaking of watermelon, we should do that thing!"
Towel
Vacuum cleaner
Watermelon
"Suikawari" (Watermelon pinata)
Start!
Spinning begins!
1, 2, 3..
10...
However...
Where's the Melon? I don't know...
Bi-nasu in a pinch!
You shouldn't play with your food you know.
He cuts the watermelon with the knife from the cutlery set he won
Then...
Ta-da~ ♥
Let's eat ♥♥
"I finished eating it all today!"
Thank you for the food!
But...
You know what...
"I want a side dish..."
The next day
Has Nasubi's wish been answered this time?
Oh! Look at how delicious the wrapping is, it could be sweets!
I'm feeling good about this! ♥♥
Ohhhhh? What is it?
That is!
What the heck!!
It's a lighter
A lighter cannot fill my stomach
I can't eat this !!
But here Nasubi...
We now have flames from the lighter hey!
Yehehehehe
The sight of the flame invokes...
God of fire
He begins to pray
Please guide Nasubi to some side dishes!
Please make this a reality
I put my faith in you!!
At that moment the God of prizes heard Nasubi's prayers
What gift did God grant him?
What can I say about this!
What a beautiful item
Beautiful?
This is a feeling that Nasubi has been defeated huh...
Nasubi has received pickled Nasubi!
TL:Nasubi is Japanese for aubergine / eggplant
Pickled aubergine!
My prayers were answered ♥
After a long hiatus, a winning dance!
Aubergine
Rice
Accompanied with rice.
Pickled food goes really well with rice you know! ♥
"I'm so glad to be born Japanese."
The next day the God of prizes will also smile down on Nasubi.
The next day
What did he win?
Weider sports jelly drink
It's sweet ♥♥
It's been so long since something sweet he completely looses himself in the moment
He completely forgets to do his very important ritual...
That is...
The winning dance as a display of gratitude
The God of prizes has now gone silent on Nasubi
One week later
I haven't won anything for about a week now...
Another week later
This is getting serious!
"It's been 2 weeks since I won weider jelly drinks and haven't got anything since..."
It's been a long time since I haven't had any wins like this
Then Nasubi...
Hirosue Ryoko poster
He prays to Miss Hirosue.
The next day
Today he is writing postcards
Then...
Slap!
What's that sound?!
Oh!
It's post!
It's just a letter so it wont be something important...
Featuring the Spice girls,
SPICE the Movie (JP 25 July 1998 release)
Discount ticket...
Dammit!
It would be better if it was a VIP invitation
But this is a discount ticket!!
This is a bit harsh...
Then...
Slap!
What's this sound?
It's the post
What is it I wonder ♥
I hope it's not anything like last time...
That was a painful experience
Nasubi has high hopes as he opens the letter
However...
Pffft...
"Don't send me this junk!"
Car navigation and car audio pamphlet
You're not even close to being a prize!!
Could it be the curse of forgetting the winning dance?!
The next day
The pickled aubergine is finished
and it's back to eating plain rice
Paper prizes....
Paper prizes just keep coming...
But the God of prizes will keep the paper prizes flowing.
The next paper prize is?!
Free English lesson ticket
This is the second time he won it!
Dammit!!!
Nasubi super rage !
I give up.
Savage attack of the paper prizes!
These are Augusts winnings...
Until the 1 million Yen goal...
461,926円 remains!
Nasubi in September
These are the entries made for September
A total of 4,792 entries
It's been a while since hearing the sound of knocking!
Has the anger of the prize God settled?!
But...
It's good that something has come
It looks like a paper prize...
"I've won 4 sequential paper prizes!!"
Judging from the sound, it's really paper
"Useless freaking paper!!
I'm gonna tear you up into a million pieces!!"
A poster of Miss Hirosue ♥
This is the second Hirosue poster win
Now I have 2 Miss Hirosue posters hanging up...
What extravagance ♥
After winning a Hirosue poster,
The God of prizes seems to have settled down...
But once again that sound comes to haunt Nasubi...
Slap!
But what's inside?
"What!! Why!!"
Car navigation pamphlet...
Gods rage has still not settled...
"Dammit! Dammit!! Dammit!!!!!"
To remove this bad fortune,
He doubles down on post card entries
A few days later
Please pay attention to Nasubi's skin tone!
As you can see, he's sunburnt!
To be honest, how this happened was...
Like this
Summer holiday THE BEST ♥ ♥
Nasubi's summer holiday
After not leaving the apartment for 8 months
The staff gave Nasubi this present ♥
Has he lifted the unfortunate curse also?!
However...
♪ A-Nasubi, A-Nasubi, A-HeadPHONE! ♪
He won a pair of headphones!
I won Headphones YO!
Song by Nasubi
Even though, I won them YO
It's all good Zu- Zu- Cha!!
Zu- Zu- ZuCha!
Zero significance YO! Zu- Zu- Cha!
Look!
No sound can be heard...
"Can my prize luck only move in one direction downwards?"
A few days later
A win!
However...
"This prize is a great jump up in uselessness in comparison to the headphones..."
A CD-ROM Encyclopedia
The next day
He is writing postcards this morning with high hopes of a win
However...
"Today... Today that sound echoed once again throughout this room"
Slap!
Yet another paper prize?!
But what did Nasubi see?
It's the post but it's quite a big item...
WHAT?!
What could it be that has made Nasubi so happy?
W-w-Whaaat could be inside I wonder~?
What the heck is this?!
The 51st Japan Cycling championship event video
The next day
This situation is pretty bad huh
Please, give me a good day!!
Will today be a good day?!
However...
Slap!
"Today... Today also the post was delivered..."
This slim packet, I wonder if there's anything inside
I hope that it's something that will make me happy in here...
Please!
HOWEVER!
I've been deceived...
Learner drivers new students information brochure
"Wonderful!! Such a splendid delivery!!"
Nasubi RAGE!
The next day
Will today be a good day?!
Slap!
"As always, it can't be helped, but until the moment I look inside I always have great expectations!"
However!!
My mouth was stuck wide open...
Hotel brochures
"If you're gonna send me these, at least make them free stay!"
These prizes are so worthless!
Literal junk!
I cannot use!
Zero help!
Why is it turning out like this?
"If everything is happening like this then the only explanation Is that I'm cursed and becoming possessed by evil spirits!"
The next day
Will today be the...
Slap!
Again, it's only letters.
In regards to the entries for this prize holiday,
Thank you for participating.
The holiday invitation selection...
WHAT?!
He won a holiday?!
But unfortunately you were not selected as a winner.
SHOCK!
But...
However!
It says 'however'!
However, this time as a reward for your entry
As a show of our appreciation...
As a show of appreciation? What's this?
The normal travel package price is 129,800 Yen ....
But we can offer you this special information discount price of
Just 99,800 Yen ♥
DOUBLE SHOCK!!
What sad, unfortunate news.
I can't take it anymore!!
Not a single thing he could eat this month,
These are Septembers winnings
440,626円 Remains until the 1 million Yen goal
Nasubi in October
These are the entries for October
A total of 5,875 entries
Recently, all I have been getting is
Nothing but paper style post items
"Are you scared to come here, prizes?!"
Then...
No wins for the duration of a week
Nasubi does nothing but write as many entries as possible
However...
"I'm not even receiving any post at all now."
The signs of death are starting to show...
Nasubi's prize life contest is in the greatest pinch of all
We must do something for him!
That is...
That day at midnight...
The producer appears!
Then
Road trip
Where did we arrive...?
Take off the mask
"Although the atmosphere differs, the all-star prize decoration inside makes for a bustling room feel"
We moved?
Correct ♥
Feng Shui ♥
That thing everyone's been talking about?
After seeing Nasubi's streak of misfortune, the staff decided to move house for a second time to increase his luck
Thank you very much!
I'll write postcards untill my hands fall off!
I'll do my best!
Feng Shui BANZAI !!
However the staff have again made a big mistake this time also!
Last times mistake was...
After completing the move to the new house first time
I can't find my rice.
I'm sure I had rice...
Then!
Sorry, sorry, I left it in the truck
They forgot the rice!
It's okay to forget the other stuff, but not the rice !!
No, but the truck...
It's not the trucks fault!!
NASUBI RAGE !!
And this time...
Oh?
Oh-h-h-h-h-h-h?
The rice isn't here!
The staff forgot the rice again.
Where did they put it?!
Here.
Hmmmm~~~?
Hmmmmmm?????
He finally discovers it.
They shouldn't mess around like this!
He writes many entries for wonderful prizes hoping to win.
Then...
"I have spoken this comment many times up until now..."
I want some side dishes!
A flavor with impact!
Something greasy!!
The fatty food he won before was...
Duck breasts ♥
In June he won the Duck breasts and hasn't had anything in the 4 months since!
"I want to eat something fatty!!"
"And finally that moment in my prize life contest has come!!"
Is it a long awaited win?!
Finally, is it the first prize of the new house?
Yes, yes, yes, yes
What's this, what's this?
This.... Box....
Nasubi seems to know what's inside by just looking at it
He he he ♥
Time to open!
I knew it. It's that.
And!
This is only the first new house prize!
It's finally here!
Just what is it?!
I won potato crisps! ♥
Look how many there is ♥♥
Nasubi is very emotional, and it's a long awaited winning dance!
"I cannot even remember how many months it has been since I have done a winning dance with such power and vigor!"
"I danced with my full body and soul!"
Let's eat ♥
How should we open it? Like this, is it not?
It's open
"The delightful smell of potato crisps."
"As I opened my mouth wide and placed the potato crisp inside,
I lost all recollection of awareness in that moment"
"It was as if something in my body had parted and flown away."
It's great...
The best...
Another win!
What did he win?!
Anmitsu set (Fruit in syrup and anko bean paste)
"Nasubi's prize life contest has gone from Hell to Heaven"
Delush ♥
This is... !!
Horsehair Crab
The house move was a great success!
He wins several great prizes in a row
Vegetable Juice
Golf shoes
What has he won?!
VHS player ♥
He does the headbanging winning dance
But
"A VHS player alone is no good though..."
That's right
BUT!
THAT'S RIGHT ♥
I have a VHS player...
I also have a TV so...
"All I need now is a video tape!"
Video library 2 tapes total!
"For this whole 9 months I haven't seen any moving images, only still pictures. Either way I've not seen a single second of broadcast TV"
Let's begin with watching the cycling race video
Switch on!
Uwaah! It's on!
It's on, It's on, It's on, It's on, It's on, It's on, It's on, It's on, It's on,
It's on!
IT'S ON !!
Nasubi dances to the BGM with excitement
It's moving!
It's MOVING!!
After not seeing moving pictures for 10 months Nasubi is super excited!
And next is the how to cure armpit odor video!
Here we go
Another exciting dance to the BGM from Nasubi
Then...
Oh!
Oooh!!
Moving women!
It's been 10 months!
After not seeing women for 10 months Nasubi is super excited!
As shown in the illustration, it is thought that people who have dried earwax tend to have no armpit odor...
Yet people with soft earwax seem to have body odor
That's how it is
With the additional house move, these are wins of October!
Until the 1 million yen goal another 318,126円 remains!
Nasubi in November
These are the entries for November
A total of 4,460 entries
My hair is getting pretty annoying
He wants to do something about his long hair...
It would be ideal if I could win a headband or even an elastic band...
"However!"
"Unexpectedly, a sudden flash of inspiration struck me!!"
The outcome...
Ai-in
TL: Ai-in is a 90's pop culture phrase coined by Ken Shimura who's comedy skits featured this gag hairstyle
"I remembered that I won a sewing set and there was some elastic for panties in it!!"
"So I tied it into a band and put my hair up with it!!"
Nice ♥
Body fat scales
Possibly due to the new hair style, Nasubi is on a high pace winning streak!
Leather belt
Zatoichi phone card x3
Sniff Sniff
This smell !
Could it be...
This smell !!
The king of all Autumn flavors Matsutake mushroom!
(The most expensive mushroom in Japan)
Also 3 of them !!
Let's take big bites!
Toasted Matsutake
Nasubi bites into Matsutake for the first time in his life!
"This is serious!!"
"The texture of the Matustake in my mouth is exceptional"
"The delecate fragrance encompasses not only the mouth but also..."
"Penetrates to the tip of the head, instantly sparking"
"It's gone..."
Yet another win!
What did he win?!
Oh?!
This is...
That's right
This is it !
Without this, I suffered many hardships...
What's that...?
Toilet paper ♥
"Now I can poo whenever my heart desires!"
It's really been 10 months....
Since I've touched toilet paper
Well then, well then...
Let's give it a go shall we?
Nasubi goes to the toilet...
Is he having a poo?!
It's been a long time since I have used the toilet paper holder
10 months of troubles !
Well then, let's shit! And give my ass a wipe ♥
For the first time in TV history!
Mankind's toilet scene complete broadcast!
But!
No good, it's not coming out...
"I look forward to the next time I poo ♥ "
This is...
Am I dreaming?
Playstation ! (Real) ♥
During Nasubi's prize life contest...
It was around 8 months ago...
Densha De GO!
Plus!
Special controller!
And then!
About 6 months ago...
It's a TV ♥
Nasubi has won what he needs!
Prize life contest woooo- Wonerful ♥
Uwaaahh! Here we go!
Densha De GO!
START!!
The train is departing! Amazing!
"It's Densha De GO! Densha De GO!"
"I forgot about time, myself, everything and played Densha De GO! Like a NEET!!
As a result...
He played all night.
Nasubi is totally absorbed and plays nothing but the game.
Once again the sun has set.
"I'm..."
"I'm a complete prisoner to Densha De GO!"
As a result!
He played all night.
Entry into the 3rd day straight of Densha De GO!
"I'm..."
"I'm a complete slave to Densha De GO!"
Just when will Nasubi stop playing Densha De GO!?
That was pretty good just then
At that time!
But you know...
"What the heck am I doing?"
"Then I decided."
Playstation BAN
I realised this is a bad situation!
It's certainly very fun but...
Densha De GO!
"I'll stop from tomorrow."
Since the Playstation BAN he has made great progress towards the goal.
Mayonnaise
10kg rice
Hair growth tonic
Today, he wins something like that thing 6 months ago!
When Nasubi saw it...
The most surprised face since the start of prize life contest!
It's here!
It's here!!!!!!!!!!!
What is it?!
It's meat ♥
In June he won duck breasts, the first meat in half a year!
But really, it looks very high grade...
"Cow meat!!"
Certainly...
These are steak cuts ♥
Grilling.
It's been 6 months since the smell of cooked meat...
Ahhh~ it's great!
It's cooked.
Look, check out how thick this steak is!
But then!
Fuckfuckfuck I dropped it...
Nevertheless...
Let's eat
Nasubi isn't fazed by it.
But you know what, I have this luxury cutlery...
Just biting into it like this right here...
Wouldn't be very entertaining...
So...
Using the towel as a napkin, and the potato crisp bag as a plate...
We shall dine with formal etiquette
Some suitable BGM for this situation would be a classic piece...
Hey maestro! Start the music.
Vivaldi's 4 seasons
We shall dine!
How is the flavor of meat for the first time in 6 months?!
Delicious!
He begins to shed tears of joy
The next day
Another win today!
Oh! This is a quite a heavy item I've won
A pear, an apple or even a potato...
That will make me very happy
Then
Nasubi laughs.
Another food item?!
What do you think it is?
This is...
It's my tent ♥
It's so spacious !
Look
Amazing space!
With all this space... I could live in it!
So...
This is nice ♥
Prize life contest in a tent START!
An exceptional month of November with these wins
Until the 1 million Yen goal, another 161,886円 remains!
Nasubi in December.
These are the entries for December
A total of 2,546 entries
Morning
Nasubi is living in the tent now, however he still continues to relentlessly write postcards out. Nothing has changed.
Then...
Could it be the tent life prize contest first ever prize?!
Is it the explosive power of the tent?!
However...
Any prize is a good prize but...
He doesn't seem very pleased...
What did he receive?
What's this??
In a tube.
It feels like a paper item again...
Paper prizes.
Worthless prizes that only lead Nasubi into great depression
He anxiously opens it
What popped out before Nasubi's eyes?!
Nasubi bingo! Bingo !! BINGO !!!
What did he win?!
I won Ryoko Hirosue 1999 calender ! ♥
He goes to do the winning dance!
BUT!
"There is no space to dance..."
So...
Tent life is finished.
The room is back to it's normal feel
Then...
This time a winning dance
Next year, for a whole year, I can live together with Miss Hirosue
There is already hype for next years prize life contest!
Surrounded by 3 Miss Hirosue, Nasubi's prize life is in pretty good shape!
Feather pillow
Food wrap (1 years worth)
Reinforced suitcase
Just then!
Yet another win?
However...
"What the heck are you?!"
"Just why in the world are you here?!"
What's going on!??
It's a tire ♥
Four wheel drive Nasubi ♥
"Dear lord! You were out by just one letter! If only it was 'Daiya'."
TL: Taiya = Tire, Daiya = Diamond
"That would have been the finale of my prize life contest for sure?!"
"But... My dreams are only dreams..."
However!
Right at this moment the staff realise a very serious situation!
This 4 tire win is worth 84,000円
In other words, the total prize earnings are 969,114円
To reach the 1 million Yen goal, all that remains is 30,886円 !!
The goal is right in front of Nasubi's eyes!
And then after this...
Finally reached the goal?!
What did he win?!
Nationwide department store 10,000円 gift voucher!
Getting close!
From here the count down to the goal begins!
A photo album of Antonio Inoki ♥
By the way, the price of this photo album is 10,000円
The sound of the approaching goal!
Gold balls ♥
The value of golf balls is... 4,800円
Until the goal another 6,086円 remains!
A pan! ♥
The price of this pan is 5,000円
So close!
Rice topping seasoning ♥
Has he done it?!
500円 value.
!
And so that moment has finally come.
Yes, yes, yes something came today too!
Oh!
It's here.
White, shiny, troublesome!
What did he win?!
I won some rice ♥
What's the value? 750円
So that means...
The total prize winning value is 1,000,164円
And that means!
The 1 million Yen goal has been reached
and the prize life contest is over!
The one man who's fate was to open the winning ticket
He started from zero, completely naked
With only a endless supply of postcards.
During that endless eternity of time
That man only had one goal in sight
And now that special moment is finally here
It took 335 days to do, but for the first time in human history a man has completed this unprecedented savage challenge.
So we have come to a conclusion
That is...
People CAN live by only winning prize contests!
But Nasubi...
Ok! I'm gonna give it my best!
He's writing out postcards!
FUCK!
Nasubi hasn't realised he's reached the goal!
We have to tell him!
So...
That night
The producer appears
It's time to tell Nasubi he reached the goal...
This time the producer has brought something along...
That = Party popper
The goal celebration is confetti blessings
But Nasubi...
What's going on?
He doesn't get it at all.
The producer continues the blessing ♥
Get it?
I don't understand
What's this?
Party popper...
Correct!
I understand it's a party popper ok...
When are they used?
I guess when you want to congratulate someone...
Super correct!
Then perhaps...
I made a million yen?
Super Super Correct!
Huh? Wait a sec, hold on, hold on, excuse me...
For real?
Really, truly, honestly, for real?
Yep!
I did it!
Denpa Shounen prize life contest Nasubi GOAL !!
Congratulations!
Then the producer...
Get it?
Yes!
11 months and one day ago I got naked.
Their my clothes right?
It all began with this talk.
Strip ♥
11 months ago, without this pre-requisite we would never have been able to start
11 months and 1 day ago confiscation of clothes
Can I ?
Yep!
The return of clothes
Thank you for everything
It's the real deal!
We'll be outside
Nasubi... Pants... Here we go!
This is the moment he wears pants and is re-certified as a member of modern society after 11 months!
First is the right leg
The left leg follows
All that's left is to pull them up now!
This is the last farewell to the Nasubi mark!
Pants installation complete!
These are my socks!
From here Nasubi takes great pleasure in getting dressed one item at a time
And when he has finished getting dressed...
The morning has come.
I finally made it!
However...
After this Nasubi's body has a wierd reaction...
... It's kinda itchy.
So...
Yeah, actually this feels the best ♥
Nasubi mark revival
Naked.
A plethora of presents awaited for Nasubi as a congratulation
Prize life contest celebration present 1
It's Ramen ♥
The food he wanted to eat first was Roast pork Ramen
It's the intense flavor he desired for 11 months
It's great!
Prize life contest celebration present 2
Korea.
What comes to mind?
Grilled meat.
Correct ♥
Prize diary last year on page 1998.11.13
"I wanna eat grilled meat!"
You even remember those kind of details...
Thank you.
A second gift from the home of grilled meats, Korea.
For the first time he tries ribs and nearly passes out!
Prize life contest celebration present 3
Take off the mask!
Just as I thought...
The Amusement park.
Nasubi's carefree enjoyment is a complete knockout!
Prize life contest celebration BONUS!
Shopping
Those are Korean market Kimchi pots.
However, these are preparation for a new film production...
Here, the producer...
Where are we staying?
Huh?
Eyemask
Headphones
Kimchi
Departure by car.
After a 5 hour drive...
We finally arrive.
Well... Please take off the eyemask
Where are they?
Kimichi
Huh?
Strip ♥
Can people live in Korea by only winning prizes?
Nasubi suffers massive shock
But the producers words have moved Nasubi's heart!
But this time, the goal isn't 1 million Yen
This time the goal is... To get to Japan by plane
A one way ticket
Then...
I'm naked again ♥
Faithful
Cusion
If you don't want to do it, just say.
I want to do it!
Can people live in Korea by only winning prizes?
Korean postcard
Nasubi starts naked
Win prizes from magazines and newspapers
With two language dictionaries
And earn 46,900円 worth of prizes to get from Seoul to Tokyo (Economy class)
And the challenge is to use Korean postcards!
Denpa Shounen Prize Life Contest in KOREA
Nasubi in January 1999
These are the entries for January
A total of 2,086 entries
This is the first time I've tried to write in Korean...
I have no idea about it really.
Nasubi struggles to write out Hangul characters
Then...
Isn't it dinner time soon?
Simple Kimchi dish
Looks good doesn't it
Kimichi dinner time
To ration, he eats 3 pieces of Kimchi
And this is all he eats for a whole day.
Lid from pot
"Korea, the home of Kimichi. It's great!!"
A fue days have passed
Nasubi again writes postcards all day today
He is still slow paced, but takes great care.
But there is one thing that worries him
That is...
I wonder if these will really be delivered...
"I wonder if the Korean postal service and everyone involved in the prize contest can really..."
"Can they read my crappy Hangul writing?
I'm very concerned..."
After this, a lovely nostalgic sound pays a vist to Nasubi's room.
What's this sound?!
During the prize life contest in Japan, that was the depressing sound of worthless paper post
But Nasubi...
Oh?
What was that?
The sound came from the entrance!
He didn't notice that it was the same sound
This is!
Judging from Nasubi's delight, could it possibly not be paper post?
However...
It's paper.
It's here! Something came!
Considering all the paper prizes where worth 0 Yen...
Has he forgotten the Demon that is paper post?!
I got some post! ♥
But what is inside?
Some kind of paper...
Probably notification that you did not win.
Perhaps it says, perhaps perhaps I don't know maybe
And this is...
"Catalog"
Then Nasubi...
It's a catalog! ♥
Yay!
He is still pleased.
And also...
A winning dance!
Why is this man pleased to the extent that he will dance?
Listen carefully here to Nasubi's words...
This is proof that my postcard got delivered! ♥
"It doesn't even matter about what I get..."
"As long as there is a response from the postcards,
I know they are arriving through the post!"
"That is far more important, valuable, wonderful and beautiful!!!"
My head is in the zone for writing postcards now!
And the next day
Today the moment he's been waiting for finally comes
Delivery
Oh!!
"Finally its time! The time has come!"
A package... for me?
Please sign
I have to sign! Er, um.. ok ...
Sign here please
감사합니다 (Thank you very much)
"I won something!"
"Today's prize is rewarding in more ways than one!"
This time its a real package delivery! ♥
So overjoyed there is no need to look inside. Just dance.
"I've been waiting and waiting and waiting forever!!"
"Prize life contest in Korea official prize number 1 !!"
Yes!
I'm winning for real now
I'm getting real deliveries
Although he doesn't even know what he's won yet
Just the fact its been delivered is making him explode with joy.
What is it?
Just what is inside?
What's inside? What's gonna come out?
Ta-da! ♥
Huh?!
What's inside?
It's Kimchi ♥
Mr.Kimchi, I'm Nasubi. I already have some Kimichi, I eat it.
What are you for Kimchi?
But
Kimchi just won
Let's eat ♥
Eating.
Then...
It's great!
Nasubi in February and March (1999)
These are the entries for February and March
A total of 4,616 entries.
I did it!
First prize
Kimichi
From here...
I will start the countdown for the journey home!
Just you wait Tokyo!
Just you wait!!
TV
The plane ticket home goal prize life contest in Korea is progressing nicely with winnings.
Grill wire
Wool panties
Millet
Mute the TV
Then...
Oh! It's heavy...
Heavy!?
It's not as heavy as the TV box but...
This is still pretty big you know!
It could be another electrical item with this weight... ♥
After the TV what is the 2nd electrical goods prize?!
Surely... If this was another electrical prize...
Wouldn't we have exceeded the goal?
I could go back to Japan right?
What's in this box...?
What is it?
WHAT??
The contents are...
Oh! There is bubble wrap packaging...
Bubble wrap?!
These are high precision instruments!
Expectations are rising for an electrical prize!
But
This has come?!
It was different than expected.
This is different, but good!
What?!
I knew it
Just what did he win?
Ohh~~~hohoho...
What could it be for Nasubi to make such a strange voice?!
Bananas ♥
And what's more...
A box, a whole box of them!
It's banana... Banana !!
I told you, this is a banana!
But right now Nasubi is in a serious situation...
By the way, right now his prize earnings are...
45,300 Yen
To reach the 46,900 Yen goal he needs
Another 1,600 Yen
The value of these banana is 2,500 Yen
(10 bunches=25,000 Won / 1Yen=10Won)
So that means...
His total earnings are up to 47,800 Yen
So, that means!!
The goal of 46,900円 has been reached
Prize life contest in KOREA complete.
That's right! Nasubi has reached the goal...
BUT!
Eating a banana he starts writing postcards!
Nasubi hasn't realised he reached the goal!
We have to tell him quickly!!
However...
Eating and searching a dictonary... What, what a happy feeling.
It's great ♥
After seeing Nasubi's determination, the staff thought that...
From Seoul to Tokyo the plane ticket is 46,900円 in Economy class
After trying so hard, economy class is just not good enough.
So...
Rank up to Business class!
So that means!
We also rank up the goal price! (57,300円)
Untill the new goal he needs another...
9,500円
Good luck Nasubi!
The next day
To get the business class ticket, he is again eating and writing entries.
Then...
Is it a win?
It's a win !
Shall we open it?
What could be inside?
Its Tea ♥
But Nasubi...
But you know... It's only tea, just 2 small bags of tea leaf...
"At fist glance my thoughts are that it seems this is not very expensive, high quality Tea leaf!"
The goal is still plenty far away huh...
Tea, no matter what, this stuff can't really help...
This is trivia time.
The tea that Nasubi received was from the
famous Korean Shinroan region
This is the most expensive tea in Korea, the Ujeon variety.
The unrealized price of this tea is 14,000円 !
(2bags 200g =140,000 Won 1 Yen = 10 Won)
So that means!
Total prize earnings are 61,800円
The goal of 57,300円 has been reached
Prize life contest in KOREA complete.
Nasubi's reached the GOAL !!
But !!
Kimchi pot lid
Like this we turn once
Twice
It's 3 times for a tea ceremony right?
He hasn't realized the goal has been reached, and enjoys some tea.
Wonderful Tea etiquette
Then
Let's do it!
After seeing Nasubi's determination, the staff thought that...
After trying so hard, business class is just not good enough.
So...
Rank up to First class!
So that means!
We also rank up the goal price! (81,600円)
And that means...!
To reach the 81,600 Yen goal he needs...
Another 19,800円
Good luck Nasubi !!
Pork rib seasoning
As expected, Nasubi gives it his best
Bamboo Sword
Picture frame
Live Octopus
Fox scarf
Hey you're pretty cool right?
I wanted a companion for a while now!
Speaking of Korea...
Nasubi is struggling to name his partner
Just then one word comes to mind...
How about Kalubi?
So... What will the name be for his Korean partner?
Bi-kalu is a name with a good feeling!
A new friendship is born with partner Bi-kalu
and Nasubi thinks he will bring good luck!
Total prize money so far is...
73,590 Yen
To reach the 81,600 Yen goal, he needed another 8,010円
And the prize this time is a Fox scarf worth 12,000 Yen
So that means!
The total prize winning value is 85,590円
So that means!!
The 81,600 Yen goal has been reached!
Prize life contest in Korea is compete!
This was his first time in the country and also experiencing the language.
But regardless, he climbed that wall with great courage.
And for the second time, he conquered the Prize life contest in a foreign country
The victory took 91 days to reach the goal (Total prize value 85,590 Yen)
But !!
With Bi-kalu watching, he starts writing postcards!
Nasubi hasn't realised he reached the goal!
We need to tell him quickly!!
However...
Bi-kalu, I'm gonna do my best to write post cards ok!
After seeing Nasubi's determination, the staff thought that...
The goal was 81,600 Yen from Seoul to Tokyo by First class
After trying so hard, it's just not good enough to go straight from Seoul to Tokyo.
So...
Trip to Paris inclusion scale up!
So that means!
The goal has also...
However!
Surely I've reached the goal by now...
Crap! He realised!!
So...
Night time
The producer appears
Holding the light, the producer searches for Nasubi.
Nasubi sighted!
But here an accident happens to Nasubi..
Ah! I'm sorry!
The torch slipped and hit Nasubi right in the crotch!
As a result...
Nasubi has awoken ♥
Huh?
Shall we go?
Not knowing the goal situation, he is taken out the room
Where we going?
Nasubi is being taken to...
Denpa Shounen Naked festival! March 28th Broadcast
The goal arena in Japan
There, Matsumoto and Chuyan along with 1000 audience members waited for Nasubi's return
This is Nasubi's... Waiting room?
Firstly, please watch this...
As usual Nasubi will be wearing headphones and an eye mask, accompanied by the producer
And will be brought here and put in the waiting room.
Then, Nasubi will take off the headphones and eye mask...
And the countdown will begin!
As he doesn't know about us or anything here please be quiet
The countdown will commence 3,2,1 and when zero is reached...
This... Box will fall away!
He's here, Nasubi is here!
Nasubi appears with the producer on stage
Of course as he is wearing headphones and an eye mask he knows nothing about the situation.
With 1000 people watching the waiting room
Nasubi takes off the eye mask
And does something that surprises everyone!
He starts to get undressed!
What should I do about my pants?
Should be ok to take them off
Naked ♥
After this, the Naked festival greatest highlight will be shown!
Nasubi ! Congratulations for reaching the goal !!
Congratulations for reaching the goal!
Well done!
Nasubi !
He's frozen!
Applause!! Nasubi congratulations !
Congratulations Nasubi
Can I come in? Is it okay to come in? Please excuse us!
Ah! Sorry, please excuse us!
Hello Nasubi...
The, the house collapsed...
Your house, here, Nasubi's room collapsed...
Then all these people...
Why they are laughing?
Do you know where this is right now?
Do you... Know where... This is... Right now?
Huh?
Anyway, what is this?
Nasubi, you have finally reached the prize life goal!
Congratulations!
Well done! Congratulations!
All these guests have come to this arena to see Nasubi reach the goal
That's the reason they're all here, as guests!
Is that so... HUH?!
So that's why we're all here?
Nasubi you reached the goal !
Oh? Is that true?
It's over! Congratulations!
Ah! Thank you very much!
With a thousand people in the arena the goal has been reached!!
So Nasubi, it's been 1 year and 3 months you've been in the prize life contest...
During that time there has been global trouble !!
Global??
Please watch this !
January 15th 1998
In Tokyo there was record heavy snow on that day.
I won!
This unknown mans challenge had begun...
With pure determination to send postcard entries
Prizes brought great emotional high's and low's
He garnered attention of everyone throughout Japan!
Then he moved to Korea and even more people noticed him!
For that period of 1 year and 3 months Japan had a record breaking Nasubi fever that swept the nation!
He began gaining stardom when first noticed by the media!
Many magazines and newspaper featured articles on him!
One even featured his face on the front cover!
But the Nasubi fever doesn't stop here.
Nasubi's challenge was also featured on the English national TV station BBC and broadcast world wide!
And the diary he poured his hearts feelings into...
Titled 'Prize Diary' there was 4 books covering Japan and 1 that covered Korea.
Over 800,000 copies where sold and it became a best seller!
During this period book 2 was so popular it ranked first with the most sales and also book 1 in fourth place simultaneously!
And also! Nasubi's prize life contest part 1 video already sold over 100,000 copies! How wonderful to watch!
Nasubi never knew about it but also...
It all began on the day he won the dryer...
Nasubi's room 24 hour live stream broadcast!
With over 1.6 million views total...
This set a record in Japanese internet history for the most web hits!
(as a paid service)
When he hit the 1 Million Yen goal, he ate ramen for the first time in 11 months
To be honest, this clip is very serious...
That's because...
It's a ramen commercial!
Enjoying ramen simply like this is being used for national broadcast!
It's great
It's not great.
It's fate!
That 'fate' pork ramen brand is... 'House'
Amazing! Congratulations!
Then appearing before Nasubi's eyes,
his first meal on returning to Japan.
Let's eat!
It's a Natto festival!
This is Japan!
Then he has a press conference with the media and finally...
Denpa Shonen naked festival has come to a close.
Now please enjoy this post goal personal footage.
What was the first thing he said off stage?
They got me pretty good.
After leaving the event arena they travel to a hotel.
(Deep breath)
It's been 1 year and 3 months, but the prize life contest...
Is really finished this time.
From here Nasubi begins to digest the reality of reaching the goal.
But then that man appears!
Chuyan ♥
(Chuyan appeared in Denpa Shounen hitchhike Europe to Africa)
Do you. Know where. You are. Right now?
Huh?
Chuyan and Nasubi met for the first time today
He wanted to congratulate Nasubi once more, so he came to the hotel.
Well done for reaching the goal
Thank you
Please sit down
Good job
Thank you very much
Are you pleased?
I was pleased but...
I didn't understand it at all.
Yeah, I thought that...
Then Chuyan notices something
It's Nasubi's handwritten diary!
Your diary... good
(Chuyan is from China using Japanese he learnt from Takashii Ito during their hitchhike)
Super intresting
You've taken time to read it?
What?
Can you... Speak Korean?
안녕하세요 (Hello)
How do you say 'Thank you'?
고맙습니다 (Thank you)
Ehhhhhh! It difficult...
It difficult...
Hello is 'annyeonghaseyo'
You are super tough! If I was alone then I probably die.
You must been very alone, are your feeling ok?
Are you a pervert?
Soon...
Do your best!
Three days later...
Today, 'Naked festival' will be broadcast.
This is where Nasubi learns about everything that happened
The programme has started! (9PM)
It's me!
I'm really on TV!
Huh? R-mania? I definitely heard R-mania
Wow, it's really being broadcast.
'Naked festival...'
It's the studio set from then!
It's that arena!
I'm getting goosebumps, my back is tensing up!
What do they mean 'secret story'?
Hahaha it's me
What an idiot! How embarrassing
Woah they're really showing it all!
He's naked!
What? 81,000 Yen? Only that much?
Well done, Well done
Of course I wouldn't notice that!
First class?
What? What the heck are you talking about you fuck!
Hey wait!
It's not 1 Million again!!
Damn right I noticed! That was close!
Steadily entering the arena through a sea of cloud is Nasubi's waiting room
That's...
The house that fell down?
You bastards!
Coming out being lead by the hand
In front of all those people, I didn't know anything, just walking...
Here it is
How many times...
Amazing!
Nasubi... The end!
VHS raws, translation, timing and typesetting by iiharima 2016
Please support Nasubi @hamatsutomoaki he is a charity and aid worker from Fukushima now