[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
When I got invited...
I honestly...
...didn't think this was something I could do.
"Kaeru Pyokopyoko Mipyokopyoko Awasete Pyokopyoko Mupyokopyoko"
I actually love to come up with new material.
But I don't really see myself as a comedian.
As for my art style...
Well...
I've been living my life in a sort of 'improvisational' manner.
Not a single one of my members goes along with any of my jokes.
No matter how hard I play the funny man, they will refuse to play along as the straight man.
So I think I've been living in quite the harsh comedic environment.
All the Sumo of my generation were taught to remain stoic even in victory.
R-Right...
We were taught to show respect for our opponents and were never allowed to laugh.
Now, I've gotten older.
And now I'm a regular in all these variety shows where I laugh all the time.
So yes, I don't think I have any advantage over the other members.
So dangerous!
That could have gone very bad.
Taking that angle?
An orange card!
"You see..."
"I..."
Yellow!
You were smirking the whole time.
Oh no...
You just laughed.
Katsunori Takahashi... Red card!
-The first one?!
-There it is!!
-Goto did some excellent work for us out there.
-No, no, not at all.
You sure stirred things up.
-Goto did some excellent work for us out there.
-No, no, not at all.
You sure stirred things up.
Alright, here we go.
That's so painful!
Everyone's gotta get ready.
I need to cool my ass down!
You should.
That really hurt!
You've got quite the swing.
You think so?
Yeah.
Yo! Yo!
Yo!
How ya'll doing?
Ken Griffey Jr. is here.
You're right.
Oyakata, are you Ken Griffey Jr.?
The left-handed batter, right?
-That's right.
-I am Takanohana!
The left-handed batter, right?
-That's right.
-I am Takanohana!
Yo! How you doing?
That's pretty funny.
Are you a rapper?
Yes.
Yo! Yo! Yo!
Yo!
He's got a big body so it works.
-Huh?
-It's over?!
That's it?
Amazing.
That was fast.
He made such a big deal and just left...
So even Yokozuna give up that easily, huh?
Right, they are touted for their unremitting tenacity.
I actually wanted to ask everyone for some advice.
Sure.
With the pandemic, streamed shows have been getting more and more popular.
So we got a great opportunity here at Amazon Prime to produce our very own show.
And our project was green-lit after some discussions with the higher ups.
-Really?
-Amazing.
So Kishidan will be producing a new drama series at Amazon Prime. (EN" 1)
Amazing!
That's great!
So Kishidan will be producing a new drama series at Amazon Prime. (EN" 1)
But we actually haven't cast the protagonist or the antagonist yet.
So if anyone here is interested I'd love to hold an audition right now.
Sure.
I'm honored.
-Thank you.
-Let's try it out.
Alright.
You can take a look at the script.
Here you go.
Please take a look.
"True Account: One..."
That's right.
The title is "True Account: One Night Carnival".
And it is actually my original idea.
So if you open the first page, you'll see that my role is still undetermined.
But most of the other roles have already been cast.
My girlfriend's part will be played by Suzu Hirose.
The homeroom teacher part will be played by Mr. Makidai.
The delinquent former student part will be played by Mansion Kubota.
Mansion? (EN: 2)
Mansion Kubota?
Yes, the former member of Iitomo Seinentai. (EN: 3)
And for the part of me as a child...
It will be played by Kinya Kitaouji. (80yo actor)
-Mr. Kitaouji will play you as a child?
-That's right.
Yes, he's already agreed to play the part.
He's playing a child?
Yes, Kinya Kitaouji will be playing my childhood self.
Those are some peculiar casting choices.
And the bloodthirsty killer will be played by Mr. Tamori. (EN: 4))
What's with all the explanations?
And Asami Kumakiri will be playing the role of Ayumi Hamasaki.
Ayumi Hamasaki?
Huh?
And Asami Kumakiri will be playing the role of Ayumi Hamasaki.
That's right.
Anyway, most of the roles have already been filled.
Isn't this amazing?
Now I'd like to hold some auditions with all of you.
But first, who would like to play the leading role of Sho Ayanokoji?
Could we have everyone audition once?
-Sure.
-That would be great.
Could we have everyone audition once?
-Sure.
-That would be great.
Alright, we just need to get the first person into the outfit.
So, who would like to go first?
I'll do it.
Alright, thank you.
Please come over here.
Over here.
But there are no lines...
No lines?
Didn't he write anything?
Is it ad-lib?
They must be doing ad-lib.
They must be.
Once I stepped into the room I could immediately feel that the mood was different from the usual Documentals.
-Oh, really?
-Yes.
Like they're not looking at the right places.
-Like they're just wandering around?
-Totally!
Even if they look at you, it doesn't seem like everyone is on the same page.
Well, that's to be expected.
Right...
Are you teaching wrestling to small kids now?
I am.
Like middle-schoolers?
Well, it's not just children...
But I'm also teaching adults now.
Oh, is that so?
They're having a normal conversation.
It's just your usual small talk.
Even though they were going at it moments ago...
Right? What's going on?
It feels like they're just on stand-by waiting for the show to start.
Look at them.
But they might forget about the show and accidentally laugh.
He's playing with the whoopee cushion again.
That was so out of the blue too.
This guy is unleashed.
Sorry for the wait.
I thought it best to have him wear the actual costume.
-I'm ready!
-Alright!
I will play some music, are you ready with your line?
H-Huh?
Line?
Yes, there's a line in the script.
Please read it.
Huh?
Comedy rivals!
Just one line, huh?
I see.
-Hold on...
-What's up with the botched timing?
Alright.
-One more, please.
-Go ahead!
We're going again.
He was pretty late, wasn't he?
Alright, please come out with the music.
Go ahead!
Wanna come hang at my place?
-Cut! Thank you!
-What the heck is this?
Well, I wanted you to pack more punch into that delivery.
Like: "Wanna come hang out?".
Alright, let's go to the next person.
Musaka, could you get changed?
Okay, okay.
-Changed?!
-Just do it in that outfit.
Okay, okay.
-Changed?!
-Just do it in that outfit.
Sure thing.
Oyakata is falling asleep!
Oh, you're right.
Is he awake?
-He's sleeping.
-Oyakata is sleeping.
He is.
It must not be funny at all.
Look.
He looks so uninterested.
-He really does.
-Totally.
He looks so uninterested.
-He really does.
-Totally.
Alright, are you ready?
Okay!
Please go ahead.
I'm playing the music.
I'll turn every single one of you into minced meat!
Cut!
What a powerful delivery.
Thank you.
We needed Katsunori for this.
That was wonderful.
Thank you.
Alright...
-Oyakata, would you like to give it a go?
-Yes.
Is he even gonna fit in the costume?
You can just put it over your clothes.
He's doing it.
-He goes along with everything.
-He does anything he's asked to do.
He's always up for it.
He never refuses.
He just keeps going.
That's the path of the Sumo for you.
Is it?
Yes.
-Alright, please go ahead.
-Sure.
-He even had a second look at the line.
-He sure did.
-Did he memorize it?
-I think so.
Your delivery was extraordinary.
-It was pretty cool.
-Wonderful.
I'm ready!
Alright, please go ahead.
Playing the music now.
Here we go.
It's Trump!
I'm Sho Ayanokoji, my interview count is 21. (EN: 5)
Isn't it body count?
Cut!
Alright!
What about this one?
What do you think?
I don't know!
I can't tell!
Shingo was also in the danger zone.
Did you laugh?
He said 'interview', didn't he?
Let's check this one out.
-Yes!
-Let's!
Two people are guilty.
-Huh?!
-Two people?!
It's Shingo and Sho.
It's still a bit unclear...
So let's check it out.
I'm Sho Ayanokoji, my interview count is 21.
Isn't it body count?
Thanks!
Alright, let's look at Mr. Ayanokoji.
I'm Sho Ayanokoji, my interview count is 21.
Isn't it body count?
Cut!
Thanks!
I don't know about this one!
-I was just being very enthusiastic with the 'cut'.
It might have sounded like a laugh.
I just had this sudden urge.
-To go big!
-I see...
Yeah.
What do your penalties look like?
I think it's yellow, yellow.
Yellow, yellow?
Orange, orange!
Double?!
So strict!
-He's so harsh!
-So harsh!
Okay...
-You've gotta get it together man.
-Understood!
-Understood.
-Are you serious?!
Yes.
Let's go.
I think it might be time to send Fujimon in for a visit. How about it?
Shall I?
- Can you do it?
- W-What should I do?
- The mood is so weird.
I was so surprised.
He's doing it again!!
Is he crazy?!
He might be doing this just to appear busy.
This is crazy, he's on another level.
You'd never think he was sane!
He's not doing it?
He's not doing it!!
He ain't doing it!
Just forget about the script!
This is bananas!
That's done!
Move on!
This is tough to watch!
-It's over already!
-Move past it!
Alright Shingo, would you like to go next?
Yes.
Alright, go ahead.
Fujimoto...
Hello.
-Hello.
-It's been a while.
You were over there, huh?
Of course, I've been here all this time.
Everyone has been working really hard.
But let's do something else.
How about a game?
-Right.
-Let's do it.
I'm ready.
Alright, oh...
-Please go ahead.
-This is the last one, come out!
I am Sho Ayanokoji. My salary was 70 '000 yen last month.
Cut!
Thank you.
That was great.
-It suits you.
You look like the real Sho.
Well, should we...
The mood is strange now, isn't it?
You're right...
I mean, after you've finished with all this...
-You know what I mean?
-I wonder what it is...
I'm sorry...
The room goes silent, you can hear a pin drop.
Right?
But you know, Fujimon has been in these kinds of situations before.
And he's actually pretty good at acting.
Not at all.
-How about you give it a go?
-We don't need to.
Just once, please.
I mean, you guys just get into this strange groove after a while.
We won't, you have to trust me.
I mean...
You don't want to see me do that, right?
Why aren't you speaking?
-Well, we do want to see you try.
-Of course.
Hold on, you've all done it already.
Including Katori.
So it's enough already.
You've been doing the same stuff over and over.
Right, Oyakata?
But Oyakata just expressed his desire to see you try it out.
Don't you think that's enough?
Really?
Hey! You're doing that again?!
Huh? Did he just...
He just laughed...
Who?
Who was it?
Didn't he just laugh?
He was making a joke...
Huh?
Who?
You laughed, didn't you?
Come on...
He laughed at his own joke!
But he's acting like he didn't laugh.
Was it Katori?
- He definitely laughed.
- I think you're out this time.
I mean, you were laughing!
Sorry, I didn't catch it.
Really?!
Who was it?
It was Katori.
He laughed at his own joke.
If that's true... Then he's out, you know?
Not like this!
I mean...
- He set up the joke and ended up laughing!
- I will be the judge of that.
I mean, he did laugh.
Alright, let's have a look.
He laughed!
Don't give me that!
But Oyakata just expressed his desire to see you try it out.
Don't you think that's enough?
Really?
Hey! You're doing that again?!
Huh? Did he just...
I'm not seeing it.
-Right?
-He laughed.
Hold on, I'm not sure.
I didn't laugh.
But you did.
I really don't know about this one.
Don't we have another angle?
I don't think he laughed.
No way, he did.
I didn't.
You didn't, right?
Yes.
No, no, no!
Seriously?!
We don't have additional footage!
Do you guys have it?
We don't!
The main camera didn't catch it, sorry!
You didn't get it?!
We don't!
The main camera didn't catch it, sorry!
You didn't get it?!
What?!
No way...
I think Oyakata has the best look.
Oyakata, what do you think?
I-I didn't really see his face.
Why?!
What do you mean?!
You were looking at him!
I just sensed his presence.
Alright then.
I'm gonna be super strict on him, okay?
-He's out if he slips up even for a second.
-Right.
-Alright then.
-It would've been weird if he got no penalties for that.
I mean, you started all of this.
Why am I the bad guy?
- I didn't laugh.
- We can't do much about this situation.
But you did laugh.
Honestly...
You can tell me the truth later.
You don't have to tell me now.
Alright.
But I swear you laughed...
B-But... W-Well...
Well?!
What is that supposed to mean?!
What was that?!
Now?!
Now's not the time.
-Oyakata...
-You farted again?
You didn't laugh this time.
But your timing was a bit off, Oyakata.
-How come you're all silent all of a sudden.
-Yes...
Didn't he just laugh?!
-He didn't.
-Really?
He didn't laugh?!
Why are you covering for each other?
I mean, you're not exactly enemies but...
Right?
-This is a battle.
-You're in a battle, right?
-Protecting each other is kind of a strange choice.
-Right.
Yeah.
Alright, there's a strange vibe going on so let's pick up the pace!
-Let's have some fun, okay?
-Yes!
Alright!
Why don't we play with this?
Like a test of courage.
And the one who gets the closest wins.
Or we can also play rock, paper, scissors, hammer, helmet.
Okay?
That sounds good.
You guys haven't played it, have you?
What about you Oyakata, have you played before?
Yes.
This one, right?
Which one?
Rock, paper, scissors?
-And then...
-What?
And then you hit.
And the other person covers themselves with a helmet.
The winner gets to hit.
Right.
And the loser has to wear the helmet.
And we go back and forth.
Alright.
-Okay then.
-Great.
-Oyakata is always up for anything, isn't he.
-Yes.
He never refuses.
Yes.
Alright.
-Sorry.
-But there's only one helmet.
-How come no one is laughing?
-Right?
Right?
-Alright, let's do it.
-Let's play.
-Alright.
-Let's go.
-Let's!
-Let's go!
- We always play these kinds of games.
- I really think Oyakata is extremely funny.
You're right.
-Let's go with this hammer.
-Which one?
Oh, you're right.
Oh, we also had the Harisen.
He's inflating it again!
Alright, let's play!
I'll go first then.
-I...
-Hiro!
Here I go!
Alright, Mr. Baseball!
Alright.
-Can you do it?
-Yes.
-Alright, let's get fired up.
-Yes!
-Yeah!
-Alright, let's get fired up.
-Yes!
-Yeah!
Come on!
-Alright.
-Here we go!
-Rock..!
Ready? Go!
Rock, paper, scissors, hammer, helmet!
Rack...
Did you just say 'rack'?
He totally slipped.
'Rack'?
Uh-oh.
Is he safe?
No way, he's out.
He can't run away from this!
He was having so much fun.
I mean...
You're just staring right at me!
You were having too much fun playing the game.
You really laughed.
He's right, he's totally right.
Everyone in the back agrees.
Yes.
-Alright, let's get fired up.
-Yes!
Come on!
-Alright.
-Here we go!
-Rock..!
Ready? Go!
Rock, paper, scissors, hammer, helmet!
Rack...
Did you just say 'rack'?
It's undeniable!
Hold on, hold on...
This...
It's undeniable.
He was already smiling at the beginning of the game!
You were so happy to be playing!
No way!
Like you were a boy on a school trip!
I wasn't enjoying it that much!
-But Kamiji was still unscathed.
-Oh, really?
So he'll be getting a yellow card.
Understood.
So he's still safe.
Thank you..?
Alright!
-From now on...
-I'll be careful!
But Katori also laughed...
-Huh?
Katori laughed earlier, you know?
You're still on about that?
On no...
The stares between these two could kill!
Let's keep going then.
Let's do it!
-Alright...
-Let's go with them.
-Oh, the battle of the pompadours.
-Battle of the pompadours.
Who has the strongest pompadour?
Alright.
Alright then, this is the battle of the pompadours.
Let's go.
Ready? Go!
-Rock, paper, scissors, hammer, helmet!
Huh?!
You're so bad!
He's too kind.
So bad!
I mean...
But he's making the face of a winner.
You're so bad at this.
Can we go again?
You can't.
That loss was pathetic.
You're actually blocking, what I personally think is the best angle.
Sorry.
We need that footage.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
-So you lost because you were worried about that, right?
-Okay, let's go again.
-Alright then.
-He couldn't concentrate.
Let's go again.
Sure.
Let's go.
Ready? Go!
-Rock, paper, scissors, hammer, helmet!
You're so bad!
Are you even trying?
Are you?
Look at Oyakata's face!
I mean, Katori, are you even trying to win?
I've always been like this...
Always been?
Always...
What does that even mean?
This is the type of idol I am.
That's why Kin-chan likes me. (EN: 6)
Can't we go again?
Let's just do a speed round.
-I'm not doing this on purpose.
-What the hell are they saying?
It's just that Kin-chan prefers simplicity.
Kin-chan is coming up quite a lot.
You're very analytical.
Right, he's doing some crazy self-analysis.
Should you even be saying this stuff?
Kin-chan prefers the clumsy version of Shingo.
I don't think you should be the one saying that.
Kin-chan...
Kin-chan?
You've been going on and on about Kin-chan for a while...
"Now, I will ask all of you to kill each other"
Hold on.
They ain't doing that!
It's just rock, paper, scissors, dammit!
This guy is mental!
He's so unhinged.
Guys, come on.
This guy is mental!
Don't move, don't move!
I've decided!
Everyone's gotta have that killer instinct.
Yes.
So we're going for real?
We're going all in, right?
Yes.
Right?
-Yes.
-There you go.
It's not a game anymore.
-You have to go in with the intent of killing each other.
-You're right.
Katori, let's drop all the pretense.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
Let's do it seriously.
The stakes are high.
Alright, we'll start once you say the phrase.
Yes.
Alright, first...
-Now...
-Wait, wait, wait, wait, you're too early.
Yes.
Hold on, look at me.
-Yes.
-Okay.
You'll say your line as I say 'start' and the game will start.
Like the opening of a tournament.
Alright.
Let's go!
"Now, I will ask all of you to kill each other"
He's saying it a bit differently now.
Ready? Go!
-Rock, paper, scissors, hammer, helmet!
Close.
That wasn't close at all!
He lost!
He was humiliated.
And he put it on backwards.
I'm shocked.
Shocked...
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Let's stop with all the apologies.
I mean, you're just ruining the mood with that stuff.
You feel me?
-Lightly, right?
-Let's keep it light!
- I'm really bad at this...
- Katori... I get that you're bad at the game, but you're spoiling the vibes!
Shut up!
What's your deal?!
Who do you think you are?!
I am trying my best here!!
From the very start!
Everyone's been trying hard!!
What more do you want?!
Idiot!!
Don't dilly-dally!
Dilly-dally?
I told you not to dilly-dally!
Let's stop this.
I'm being funny!!
"Let's stop".
I'm funny!!
Sorry, sorry.
Dammit!
You're not going hard, huh?
Bastard!
Now, now...
That was so sudden.
Bastard! Bastard! Bastard!
"Now, I will ask..."
Look at Katori!
He just cackled so hard!
Who?
He's cackling!
That's a definite out.
Alright!
Let's go!
Thank you!
That was odd.
So strange.
I couldn't hold it in anymore.
Perfect timing!
You totally laughed.
-I didn't laugh.
-You're getting the red.
I didn't.
He's saying he didn't laugh!
Alright, Fujimon was in here so...
Yes.
Who laughed?
Katori of course!
Are you sure?
He cackled in my face!
-Did you see it?
-I did!
Are you sure?
Y-Yes, I saw it!
I clearly saw it!
He was right in front of me!
Now, now...
That was so sudden.
Bastard! Bastard! Bastard!
"Now, I will ask..."
Look at his lower lip!
He's cracking up!
I can't blame him.
I would have laughed too.
Thank you.
It's undeniable, right?
Katori, you're out!
Damn it!!
I can't deal with Oyakata.
Oyakata is so funny.
-Oyakata is dangerous.
-He's so good!
Amazing!
Alright, Katori is out!
-And Fujimon, let's go home.
-Yes!
Alright, Katori is out!
-And Fujimon, let's go home.
-Yes!
Really?
-And Fujimon, let's go home.
-Yes!
Really?
Yeah.
I can't take those lines anymore!
Good work!
Thank you guys!
-Thanks!
Good work!
You know, I love improvising all those angry rants.
Like the one with Fujimon.
I am trying my best here!!
I had this desire to do tons of these kinds of scenes while I was on Documental.
It just feels so liberating.
It's so good.
And then comes Oyakata.
Bastard! Bastard! Bastard!
"Now, I will ask..."
It's such a shame...
- Here we go!
-Alright!
It's starting.
You know, this thing.
Kobayashi, what should we do now?
Do you still wanna go in?
-Go on.
-I'm just gonna stir the pot.
I don't know if it'll be good though.
Go ahead.
You know, I was actually looking to get some advice.
-More than advice, I wanted you guys to see something.
-Right, sure.
-Would you entertain me for a minute?
-Sure!
What is it?
Over there?
Yes.
Alright.
Is it an image?
Must be.
Right.
It's pretty...
Hello.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Hello.
-Alright guys.
-Yes?
You're all stars in your respective fields, so we're gonna play a game you've never experienced before.
-Oh...
-Sure.
Alright.
It's our only chance!
-You're finally in a variety show, so let's take advantage of that!
-Right.
Without further ado, the first person to fart wins!
Start!
Alright, fart by my ear and you win.
Fart first and you win.
Alright, get your bodies moving!
Oyakata is nodding along.
-He is?
-Yeah.
He was nodding.
Are you ready, Oyakata?
-I was about to fart earlier.
-He said he was about to fart!
There's not a single sign of a fart in me.
I'm gonna beat you guys to it.
Oh, they'll also lose if Kobayashi beats them to it.
I always fart though...
Come on, Hiro!
"I always fart though..."
That's hilarious.
I mean, everyone farts.
Oyakata, when you eat that cold Oden...
...did you pretend it was hot?
Yes.
That was quick!
-What a quick response!
-Instantaneous!
That was such a fast reply.
So fast.
Hold on.
-Musaka.
-Yes?
What were those belly tattoos for?
Well, I just thought they were cute.
Just because they were cute?
Yeah.
Don't you agree?
They're nice.
-Right?
-Here I go.
Here it is!
Whoa, amazing.
Amazing!
We've got a winner!
He did it!
He really did!
It must be his youth!
Hiro, are you allowed to do this kinda stuff?
No way!
He's forcing it!
That was good.
Is he allowed to do that?
Really?
I'm scared for his future.
Totally.
It's ominous.
We're still doing the challenge.
Just when I want to, I can't fart.
Huh?
Was that Musaka?
-Was it you?
-Yes.
What?!
-Huh?
-You sure ripped one out!
He smiled!
-After the fart?
-He smiled, right?
-He did, right?
-Yeah.
-Did you just smile as you announced your fart?
-Yes.
He laughed all on his own!
You just smiled as you said: "Yes, I farted".
He laughed at his own fart!
I was just so relieved I got to let it out.
Does that happen?!
-Are you serious.
-So I ended up smiling.
I couldn't look at it properly.
He just smiled normally after the fart.
He was like: "It was me!".
Just when I want to, I can't fart.
Huh?
Was that Musaka?
-Was it you?
-Yes.
-Huh?
-You sure ripped one out!
He smiled!
-After the fart?
-He smiled, right?
He was smirking moments before.
He sure was.
You're slipping, Oyakata.
I know.
But honestly, that was pretty funny.
Alright, Oyakata gets an orange card.
Orange!
At last, your second card!
His second one!
There's only 40 minutes left!
-40 minutes...
You know, I'm always farting... Why can't I do it now?
How would we know?!
-We really have no clue.
-That was so close.
Alright, here we go.
Drinking mineral water was super helpful.
Did you drink some?
I did.
I drank about half a bottle.
The gas will slowly travel downwards if you hold your burps.
Hiro was in the middle of it...
So there might be more.
But he's so young.
-His intestines are still young.
-You think that's a factor?
It's so frustrating.
I wanted to fart first.
But those two are taking the longest time.
Here they come.
Does it squeak?
I was just peeing.
Oh.
Sorry.
I would've cracked there.
Sho was getting changed.
Where is the sound coming from?
I think it's from the mouth.
-What's that?
-I think...
Do they sell those?
They do.
Is it a figurine?
You know, I always see Matsumoto on TV...
But he really lifts a ton of weights.
He's got some big arms.
You can even tell through his shirt.
Who does he look like?
It's me!
Isn't it Matsumoto?
-I don't think so.
-Yeah...
What's with this song?
Is it for a cooking show?
No, this one is from Tetsuko Kuroyanagi's...
Wasn't it Tetsuko's Room? (EN: 7)
Tetsuko's Room?
I'm actually on the episode that airs on the 2nd.
Oh, really?
Yes, it's been a while since I've been on.
It airs on the 2nd of June.
Ms. Tetsuko was very healthy.
Where is he?
Who?
Oh, he's here.
I came all the way from south Asagaya.
Are you one of the Asagaya Sisters? (EN: 8)
He does look like them.
Isn't he a bit too tan?
And very muscular.
I have no idea who this is?
You look like Otake from Summers. (EN: 9)
You look like that old lady who was giving commentary on the Coronavirus pandemic in the early days.
What was her name?
-What's your name?
-Huh? Did I say something wrong?
-What's going on?
Can we ask your name?
Well, we're on TV right now so...
I can't give you my real name.
Can I give you a nickname instead?
Sure.
I'm Hiromi.
-Hiromi?
Her bracelet is very similar to the one Sho was wearing.
That's such a useless statement.
-Come again?
-Her bracelet.
Oh, it looks similar?
Yes, wasn't Sho wearing just one like it?
You know, these are very popular at the moment.
-Is it a fashion statement?
-Yes.
I see.
Oyakata, please ask a question.
She's got a nice body.
She sure does.
She works out.
Thank you.
What's that?
You know, I actually also have a lookalike.
Right...
W-What's that?
I want you to guess who I look like.
Sure.
You'll know once I put this on my face.
Really?
That was like Oyakata's rapper's outfit debacle.
You're right!
-You can do it like this.
-Oh, you're right.
I'm going in.
Right...
Can you tell?
No...
Hold on, let me have a better look.
Hold on.
Who is it?
Do you know?
What?
Is he supposed to look  like someone?
Yeah, it seems so...
Are you Japanese?
Yes, I am.
With that hairstyle?!
My name is made up of two Kanji characters.
Isn't he some sort of panda?
I don't think so.
-Two Kanji...
Dan Mitsu?
Oh no...
No, no...
That was weird...
What was that?
- He doesn't look anything like her!
- That's the first funny thing he's said!
And we've only got 16 minutes on the clock.
I just can't remember the name...
-Do you know who it is?
-Yeah.
There are too many quizzes!
Why does Kamiji like quizzes so much?!
I mean, he got his break on "Quiz Hexagon II".
Their name is two Kanji characters.
Right...
And it's also their stage name.
I'll give you a hint.
Alright.
Pu.
Pu?
But he said it's a Japanese person, right?
I really resemble this person, although that was a long time ago.
Are they Japanese?
-They were pretty famous back then.
-He said it was a Japanese person.
Renho!
Wrong?
Are they Japanese?
They are.
Pu?
Chiaki? (EN: 10)
Correct!
Huh?
Does Chiaka have that hairstyle?
But you don't look like her.
No way.
Two Kanji...
It was two Kanji.
-Oyakata has already accepted it.
-Two Kanji...
He's accepted it?
What?
I mean, you do look like her.
I do, don't I?!
You really do.
He does?!
Are you serious?
- Ton of people tell me I look like her.
- This guy is on another level!
He's not sane!
He doesn't look like her!
He's crazy!
It's from when I used to work with Ucchan Nanchan.
-From when you used to be on Pocket Biscuits?
-That's right. (EN: 11)
Wanna see this?
You're starting to look like her.
I want Chiaki and the girl from Asagaya to do something.
Totally.
The girls from south Asagaya.
Who was she supposed to be?
I wonder as well...
What's going on now?
I just wanna show the resemblance.
He really looks like her, doesn't he?
With the pose and all.
-To Chiaki?
-He just took that pic, right?
He really looks like her.
Just move past Chiaki!
Oh, sorry.
What was that?
What was it?
-The picture.
-On the screen.
He just took his picture...
Is this your victory Sake cup? (EN: 12)
Yes.
Who's that?
Who is it?
Isn't that Mori's face?
The truth is...
What?!
Did he photoshop his own father's face?
-You also hold out a seabream, right?
-Yeah, a big one.
Takanohana is doing something.
-It's pretty heavy.
-Look at him.
Is he drinking?
Whoa!
The victory cup!
You're kidding me!
This guy is unreal!
-It's the victory cup.
-Huh?!
Is that alcohol?
Is he drinking alcohol?
-What?
-What's that?
Water.
-Water?!
-Just tell them it's alcohol!
-It's tasty water.
He has won.
It's time for Takanohana's impersonation show!
First off, we have Takamiyama!
Twofold! Twofold!
Next up, Kakuei Tanaka!
I mean... Well...
Ehm...
The island of Japan has to be reconstructed.
And lastly, Shigeo Nagashima!
He's in trouble.
Oh no.
R-Right...
-Huh?
-Oh no, oh no!
Bang bang.
Oh, that wasn't it.
You were just doing Gushiken.
Right...
"Now, I will ask all of you to kill each other"
There's only 5 minutes left.
-What?!
-Only 5 minutes!
-That's right.
We've gotta kill each other for real now.
Yeah, we do.
He's gone.
That was close
Some people were about to crack!
Oyakata is really funny!
His talents are wasted here.
They really are!
Don't these guys have the ability to look at the clock?
They're so carefree.
- Come on guys, just do something!
- Anything!
Just do something to the person next to you.
Make them laugh!
It's like a boxing match!
Shoryuken!
This is the final round guys!
This is pretty funny.
Shoryuken!
Hadoken!
It's hilarious.
- Musaka has no clue as to what this is!
Hadoken!
Shoryuken!
- Musaka has no clue as to what this is!
- He doesn't know what a Hadoken is! (EN: 13)
Shimura-ken!
He's not targeting the right people!
Tanaka-ken!
He's just looking at his feet now...
Tanaka-ken?
This isn't from his generation.
Those were a lot of different 'fists'.
How is everyone doing?
-Is this Oyakata?
-That's Oyakata.
We're doing well.
The results are! (EN: 14)
It's Hamada!
Where's Matsumoto?
-Where's Matsumoto
-No way!
The results are!
It's Hamada!
He's looking for Matsumoto.
Where did he leave Matsumoto?
- Do they have the time to do this?
- "Where's Matsumoto?"
He's got nothing more to say?
He asked: "Where is Matsumoto?".
"What's going on?!"
He's isolating.
I think I had something else prepared.
Hold on...
Huh?
-They have to...
-The results are!
His voice is so toned down!
"Where's Matsumoto?"
No one's listening.
Keep the Osaka dialect!
Who is that?
Keep going.
-He's riding a skateboard.
-Why?
The skateboard.
-What's going on?
-What's with the skateboard?
He was riding that Skateboard.
You're good.
Can you ride?
It's my first time?
Really?
Huh? It's your first time?
Amazing.
He's trying something with Oyakata.
-What's up with Musaka's getup?
-Yeah.
Oh, they fell off.
-It's starting to get crazy!
-It's getting crazy!
I sure fooled you all!
My name is not actually Hiromi!
Here we go!
He was pretending!
I am Sho Ayanokoji!
Whoa, that hair!
Look at it.
What was that?!
- He ruined his hair for that?!
- What?!
He even put makeup on.
He...
He's normally like that, huh?
He's done it.
That's so funny.
-You got it back so quickly.
-So quick!
That was very good, theatrically speaking.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Alright, only 30 seconds left!
-30 seconds!
"I'm Mori...
I smell shit on my hand even though I haven't touched any"
"I'm Mori...I smell shit on my hand even though I haven't touched any"
This is all over the place!
There's no structure!
- And I don't get the skateboard either.
- Right?
- What's up with the skateboard?
- Why was he riding it?
- And I don't get Musaka's get up either.
- What's up with the skateboard?
- Why was he riding it?
- And I don't get Musaka's get up either.
- And the glasses too...
- Is Musaka a blue demon?
Oh, it's over!
It's over!
We're done.
Oh my...
It's over!
I'm sweating!
-My ass hurts...
-This was something else.
It's crazy!
The length is amazing.
-It's very creepy.
-That's Hamada, right?
Nice work everyone!
That was wonderful!
Everyone put up a wonderful fight!
-The end was very good!
-Really?
That was wonderful!
You were pretending to be someone else right?
And then you uncovered your identity at the very last moment.
But you know... I think I lost something precious in the process.
No, not at all...
Alright, let's bring in the other contestants.
Awesome!
Good work!
Good job, guys!
You all put up a great fight!
I am touched.
It was truly amazing.
Alright then!
The winner of Documental is...
Takanohana Oyakata!
It's Oyakata!
Amazing!
-Awesome!
-Amazing!
I'm shocked!
-He was extremely funny.
-Amazing!
Oyakata, congratulations!!
-He was extremely funny.
-Amazing!
Oyakata, congratulations!!
Congrats!
Does it fit?
I think so...
Whoa, that's a tight fit!
We managed to get it on.
Here is your prize money!
10,000,000 Yen!
Oyakata!
Please take the mask off!
Yes.
Right, right.
Sorry about that.
He was very close to being kicked out.
But he barely managed to avoid expulsion.
Hiro was also trying really hard to keep things going.
You think so?
You tried really hard.
It was very funny.
So Katori, how did you feel?
It was very tough.
Musaka and Oyakata were just normally conversing at one point.
That's right!
They were doing small talk for the longest time!!
Musaka, what was that thing at the end?
Right, the blue demon outfit.
I had actually prepared a Namahage. (EN: 15)
I had the whole outfit ready, and I was gonna make a joke about Nama Hage (Bald Head).
But I didn't have time to change...
I'm glad you didn't!
That would have flopped so hard!
Today was a great day!
Congratulations!
-Congrats!
-Congratulations!
Here we go.
I mean, I ended up setting the record for fastest laugh at the beginning...
-That part looks a bit like my home.
-Oh, really?
I was desperate.
I lost my confidence at the first half.
I thought I was gonna get kicked out.
But Hiro really helped me out a lot to get the jokes right.
"Now, I will ask all..."
Anyway, I just tried my best to be as stoic as possible.
"Mama, can I eat this?"
It was so funny.
It really was.
But it was a completely different game than with all the comedians.
Is that safe?
-Is it safe?
-Will he be okay?
No, no, no!
It's just Frisk.
-It's Frisk...
-Yeah, but still...
It's just Frisk.
Oyakata looks a bit mad.
I mean, they do say comedians laugh the most.
Maybe that's why we didn't get many laughs this time.
But we were laughing our asses off in the back room.
But there was a monster among them.
"The results are!"
It's Hamada!
"Where's Matsumoto?!"
- "Where's Matsumoto?!"
- No way!
"Where's Matsumoto?!"
Isn't that amazing?
Where did he come up with that?
I don't even think Hamada's ever said that before.