Within "Documental",
What have been your favorite funny moments so far, Mastumoto-san?
For example, something that someone did
Well...
I think those would be the parts
that weren't intended to be funny.
The moments they tried to do something fun
but it didn't really work out, and then they panicked.
Those weren't planned at all.
I think unintended disasters like that
end up being pretty funny.
It got in my eyes! It got in my eyes!
But if you don't do anything,
then nothing will happen.
So I think that in the end
we have to try to make a disaster happen.
But if you deliberately attempt to create chaos
from the very beginning,
it's going to look fake.
You don't know, Kitamura-san!
So we try to face the situations up front,
and laugh along with them.
I think that's what's really funny.
It got in my eye! It got in my eye!
He put on this makeup for one show
And the next show also needs him to be in this makeup, right?
We're going with orange, then!
It would be amazing if you could eat it
He laughed!
Come on!
Didn't you say?
That's so embarrassing
But you!
The most noticeable thing is
the hangnail!
What a shame!
Ugh, Kitamura-san is coming
He's totally coming here
Nobu!
Today's special is!
Just a penis here
You're out!!
Eh, he's out?!
Nobu went and did it,
it was pretty insane.
Everyone was like that.
The four of us who went to watch.
Will this still work?
Drop it.
Let's give up already.
I'm taking it back.
Here we go!
Alright, what should we order?
The curry looks pretty good.
What do you want to eat?
What about a Katsudon or something?
Katsudon?
Yeah.
No!
Why not?
They don't have any Katsudon?
Then what about some squid?
Squid?
Yeah.
No!
No. This isn't working.
What do we do, then?
So they only have pizza?
Pizza and...
There's some stuff here.
Paella.
Let's just decide something...
Anything you want to eat is fine.
You can't eat any meat, Koyabu,
so you choose.
Paella sounds good.
We can go with paella.
Let's order some great steak with the paella.
No, we can't do that.
It has too much meat.
It sounds good, though.
What about...
You can't eat it, right?
Chorizo grilled in foil?
No way.
Boneless fried chicken.
Just eat around the bones.
What about the caesar salad?
Sounds good.
Katsudon?
No way.
Inarizushi?
That's good.
Caesar salad?
Okay.
A caesar salad with inari topping?
A caesar salad with inari topping?!
A large paella with plenty of seafood,
a pizza, regular round shape...
Something like that?
Anything else?
Pizza and paella.
Is that enough?
-Then, that's our order
-This is a real phone, right?
I've never ordered any deliveries, though.
Is that okay?
You've never ordered any deliveries?
Yeah, I used to leave all that to my mom.
Wanna give it a try?
The number's...
You're far-sighted?
I can still see it, though.
Why are you looking so far away, then?
Because it gets all trippy when I'm this close.
No, I can't see it.
Too close!
I can't see it.
There it is, there it is!
I'm going to order this for real, Goto-san.
Yeah that's fine, that's our order.
Wanna go take a look while the food comes?
Whose? Yours?
Just to kill time, though.
Hello, thanks for calling us.
I'm Ando from Ariake Pizzeria
and I'm in charge of your order.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to make a regular order...
Okay. Thank you very much.
Our orders are taking about 40 to 50 minutes
to arrive right now.
40 minutes?
Why don't you try asking him
to make it a little bit quicker?
I'm sorry, that's just a bit too long.
I wish we could get it a bit quicker,
if that's possible at all.
We're going to make our best effort
to have it get there as fast as possible.
Try asking how many minutes quicker they can make it.
I'm sure they have their own schedule.
But it won't hurt just to confirm.
Don't ask, don't ask.
I'm sorry.
Hello?
Sorry if this is an inconvenience
as a first time caller...
Yes?
Could you give me a number of minutes?
I'm sorry, but we have other customers.
And we've already confirmed delivery times
to them, so...
No, we're talking about the pizza right now.
You left the fridge wide open.
I want a round M size pizza.
Go with an L!
Change that M to L, please.
Large size, right?
Yes, thank you very much.
Understood.
We have three types of pizza.
Soft crust, bread-style dough,
cheese crust, Italian bread-style,
Hey, I'm telling you the fridge's open!
and thin and crunchy crispy-style.
Please choose one type.
Bread-style or crispy?
I prefer crispy.
Let's go with crispy.
The fridge's open.
Is that okay, Kato-san?
Crispy?
What other options are there aside from crispy?
Let's go with the soft crust.
No, leave it.
Yeah, soft crust.
No, it was crispy!
They're gonna get mad, for real.
Change it to crispy, please.
Take this more seriously!
Hey, it's still open.
We might be recording at the studio, though.
What are you doing?
Do you want your crispy dough type
extra crispy?
Alright then.
Thank you very much!
This one next.
Why don't you close it?
Alright.
What are you doing?
I'm getting pissed off...
Stop that.
Give me a break already.
It's all warm now...
It's hot! So hot!
And you're so close to it, too.
Who are you calling?
I'm ordering the paella.
Why is that sticking out of your nose?!
That's because you're rushing me!
I have to wait and stand by here!
We're not close to you right now.
What do you mean?
Please call back later.
Why did she say close to me?
Come on, Goto!
It's Goto-san!
Goto-san!
What did they mean during a delivery?!
To be honest, I was thinking
it was going to be Goto
Let's take a look, then
Who are you calling?
I'm ordering the paella
Why is that sticking out of your nose?!
That's because you're rushing me!
I have to wait and stand by here!
We're not close to you right now.
What do you mean?
Please call back later.
Why did she say close to me?
This one's spicy!
You're safe just this once, Goto!
Next time, it doesn't matter who it is,
just a tiny smile and you're out!
Alright then, thank you very much.
That was very close.
I had never heard that before!
Saying "close to you" during a delivery call?!
Were they talking about their physical store?
Here we go!
Can I show you something until the delivery gets here?
I was taking a look at this sign book I had
that pissed me off back in the day.
I think the system of making boring kids write
was pretty annoying to begin with.
There are third year sign books?
Sure there are, we had them at my school.
There's a lot of nonsense here.
The guys from the previous year
really got on my nerves.
Brings back memories.
Can I show it to you guys?
Look at this.
This guy is from my same class.
"I am god."
"One trio, please."
I don't think you can figure out their meaning now.
"Boy, embrace ambition."
That's not something you'd say.
I don't even see you saying "boy."
Well, this is pretty much it.
I don't think he was thinking about anything
when he wrote this.
There's also some in English.
"Take a chance."
And then a sideways "get a chance."
You got along pretty well, huh?
I really don't see the point.
Well, you were in high school.
This one really annoyed me.
"Men don't lose a duel until the very end."
No, you're definitely going to lose at some point.
What about you?
Where are you?
Koyabu-san?
What's written on mine?
Which one is it?
There it is!
This one here.
The one after the "Sail your ship into the windy sea."
Everyone called me one by one
to ask me what I was thinking.
Why don't you read it?
Koyabu, Koyabu.
Read this.
We'll I'm a performer, you see.
"I ain't gon' die" (Editor's Note: Quote from "101st Marriage Proposal". Hamada explains the plot in "Shocking Confessions 2" GnT ep 698)
Well, that's basically it.
"Move forward."
Everyone was moving forward.
That's the most likely scenario.
This is pretty bad.
I don't know if they still have a sign system
like these sign books nowadays,
but I think they should just drop it.
It would be better for you if they did, of course.
Things are becoming pretty fun, Koyabu-san.
His was the funniest.
Pretty shocking, right?
Don't go to alumni meetings!
I never thought you were that kind of guy.
What's with him?
With whom?
Michio.
What are you doing, Michio?
I was thinking of preparing an omelet
until the delivery gets here.
I really don't want your omelets.
We don't need omelets now that the delivery's on its way.
I'm concerned about your hygiene.
That's right.
Let's play a game until its here.
Let's do that!
-It's really simple.
-That's a good idea!
Zakoshi-san knows it, too.
You see, I really like mimicking stuff.
So I was giving it my all to imitate a cat earlier.
I think giving it your all is better.
It doesn't matter what you do,
as long as it's simple.
So if I write "airplane", for example...
You have to mimic an airplane.
-Right.
-So everyone...
-Everyone has to do it?
Take one, one by one.
So we have to give it...
-We have to give it our all, right?
-If possible, yeah.
Oh, that's a "frog", huh?
Anything's fine, though.
Anything's fine?
Okay.
What if someone writes something like "sugar"?
Do that.
Then write sugar!
"Sugar" is impossible.
Who asked you for your opinion?
I'd like to write any requests, too.
Tits.
What do you do with tits?
That's a sweet smell!
Is he vaping?
Is that water tobacco?
No, it's just regular vaping.
Give it a try.
You don't inhale it?
Should I inhale it?
It's making a weird noise.
It's going to explode...
This is pretty strong.
Did you inhale it to your lungs?
You can't do that?
Anyone smokes here?
What do we do?
-Push here.
-Push it.
Here?
Isn't this pretty hot?!
I've never smoked regular cigarettes before.
So this is pretty scary.
That's hot!
-That's hot.
-Yeah, that's hot.
It's worse than I imagined.
Pretty hot, huh?
That's really hot.
That's because you don't smoke, obviously.
So what about the mimic?
It's done.
Alright. Ready?
Then... Who is going to start?
This is weird.
What was that?!
For real?!
Sorry.
That was real?
Do you only get buggers on your right nostril?
Yes.
Why?
They've only been coming out from your right.
All the way from my nose?
Why does that happen?
That's insane.
They're all gooey.
I have like four different nose conditions.
You have... four conditions?
I'm allergic to polen,
I also have sinusitis,
and rhinitis, too.
That's just three, though?
Okay, are we doing this?
Sorry, sorry.
Let's do this.
I don't really get what we're doing,
so just once...
Okay, so let's play something fun
until the delivery gets here!
Goat!
Are you taking that long?
He's not there yet.
Not without some sound.
What kind of door is that?
He opened a door.
That's the farm thing...
A fence?
Yeah, a fence.
One of those with a door.
Alright.
That's all?
Huh? What just happened?
What the hell is this game?
You just have to do it.
Once you do it, you have to stay
in character for the next turn.
You have to stay in character?
That's a bother!
So he's still the goat?
Me?
I guess this is our fate.
Please do it.
You've been doing it wrong all this time.
It says "Guitar Samurai"
You're doing it wrong.
I don't know what to do.
That's true.
So I'm the guitar samurai, didn't you say?
Yousui-san?
Didn't you say?
Too bad. Are you doing okay?
Come on Yousui-san.
Too bad, too bad, too bad!
I'm the guitar samurai!
This is annoying.
Didn't you say?
What the hell is going on?!
What?
It's sugar! Damn it!
What are you doing?
He came out? From where?
What kind of sugar is that?
Is that rice?
It's dissolving in water.
Are you dissolving in water?
He dissolved, but the water's cold
so he's now frozen?
That's sugar?
Stand back up.
Didn't you say?
"Panda"
-That's a panda?
-A panda?
A panda's tits!
Who the hell are you?
That's delicious.
Do the damned panda!
Hey, you.
Everyone's doing it, so take it seriously.
I'm doing it.
What are you talking about?
I'm doing it!
Why don't you cut it out?!
I'm a panda
that's touching a panda's tits.
That doesn't make sense.
You're insane.
If you're not doing the panda
You have to act like a panda.
That can't be called a panda.
No, no, no, I was doing it.
I was a panda cub.
Pandas don't say "panda tits."
Okay, I'll do it all over again.
Why do you get your next turn right away?
-Then what do you want me to do?
-You saw what you have to do!
Why doesn't Kato get another one?
Just Kato-san.
Pick one more.
Do it, do it.
Goto is doing sugar right now.
I'm sugar, yeah.
Sea.
Do it.
Go, sea.
Oh yeah.
You're soaking wet!
Oh yeah!
Tenryuu Genichiro? (EN: Professional Wrestler with a "unique" way of speaking)
Tenryuu...
Tenryuu!
Tenryuu wouldn't say Tenryuu.
No. I'm not Tenryuu.
Tenryuu?
You're supposed to be Tenryuuu!
Is he smiling?
Tenryuu?
He's smiling.
He smiled!
You're smiling!
For sure!
Well I have to make a face.
No, no, no!
I had to hold back a couple times.
Yeah, for sure.
You were definitely smiling.
You fooled me.
Is he safe?
He's out, out!
This is hell.
I didn't quite catch that.
I didn't see.
Was Katou smiling?
I was imitating Tenryuu.
That's not Tenryuu at all.
That's just... well...
We're telling you that face is out!
That's right.
Tenryuu...
Tenryuu!
No. I'm not Tenryuu.
Tenryuu?
You're supposed to be Tenryuu.
Is he smiling?
Tenryuu?
He's definitely smiling.
You're smiling.
Smiling, for sure.
Does that count at all?
You might have been smiling.
Damn!
That's close!
Second one.
Even Katou has gathered some points, though.
You're under attack.
Tenryuu?
That's definitely not Tenryuu.
You smiled,
so take this as an opportunity to stop that face.
For real!
We agree.
-It's horrifying.
-It is.
Sorry.
Alright, let's try again.
Yeah!
One more.
Here we go!
Can I do Nakao Akira to clean the palate? (EN: Japanese Actor)
To clean the palate, yeah.
Do it if you feel like it.
Clean the palate?
Can I do it?
Nakao Akira is normally like:
"That's Shino, right?"
"And Shino is that, right?"
Or something like that.
But my Nakao Akira is...
"That's Shino, right?"
"And Shino is that, right?"
Is your hand meant to be speaking?
"That's Shino, right?"
I want to mimic something else.
Can I do it?
Mimic?
Yeah, but I need to get ready.
Are you taking long?
No, not really.
One more?
While we wait.
Here's a very exaggerated Miyagawa Daisuke-san. (EN: Comedian. He was in previous seasons of Documental)
Miyagawa Daisuke-san is normally like:
"That's no good!" or something like that.
But my exaggerated Miyagawa Daisuke is...
"That's no good!!"
That's no good!!
It's no good.
Alright.
I survived.
Don't do that.
-It was an exaggeration.
-Really exaggerated.
Yeah, an exaggeration.
-Ready?
-We're ready!
Can't wait.
I'm Kim Jong-nam. (EN: Kim Jong-un's older half-brother)
I'm Kim Jong-nam.
He looks the exact same.
He's identical.
Basically the same person.
You might have gotten killed
if you were at that airport. (EN: Kim Jong-nam was assassinated at an airport in 2017)
Masao would've.
Yeah, I know.
You're basically the same person.
Sorry.
May I?
-Sure.
-Just once...
Just look straight ahead.
Straight ahead.
I want to go to Disneyland. (EN: Kim Jong-nam was arrested in Japan when he was using forged documents to visit Disneyland)
I didn't see that.
Sorry for using other people's passports.
You're out, you're out!
Did it!
That was rough!
Zakoshi-san in front of the mirror.
That was amazing.
It's time!
That was rough.
I didn't have a good shot.
I didn't get a clear shot of Zakoshi smiling.
But it was perfectly clear at the end.
The camera got it at the end.
That's your first time.
It's not my first time, though.
Alright, let's take another look.
I want to go to Disneyland.
I didn't see that.
Sorry for using other people's passports.
So that's a point for Jirou,
and since it's Zakoshi's first time...
Let's go with... yellow.
It was Matsumoto-san who told me that initially.
That I would've been killed if I went there.
To the airport.
Here we go.
The delivery's not coming, huh?
Yeah?
Sorry for the wait.
This is the pizzeria.
That's right, I forgot about it.
Sorry.
Sorry for the wait.
So sorry.
Sorry for everything on the phone.
That's okay.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Thank you very much.
How much is it?
We've already received payment.
That's right.
Thank you very much.
Kitahara-san?
I'm Kitahara.
He's Kitahara-san.
Kitahara-san.
That's the delivery guy.
Kitahara-san, would you like some jelly?
He's not eating jelly.
You can't give him any jelly.
-You can't do it.
-Can't do.
He's going to ruin his uniform.
Not at all.
-Thank you.
-Thank you very much.
If you'll excuse me.
How polite.
The pizza's here.
-Who's hungry?
-What was it?
I can't remember.
Yeah, I know.
-That would be pretty bad.
-If it happened.
Things would've gotten lively.
Yeah... Hey.
Just like when you took that hat.
Really?
Though it's really different from that time, I guess.
How's it looking?
It comes off pretty neatly.
-That's huge!
-Sorry!
I'm taking one slice.
I'm taking one too, then.
That's good.
It's really good!
Thanks for the food.
That's almost half of it!
Is anyone not eating?
What about Katou?
No way am I eating!
Why are you like that?
Think about the time!
The time?
What are you talking about?
Why?
Time?
We're almost halfway there.
I can't eat this late at night!
It's almost midnight.
Are you stupid?
You're stuffing yourselves at night.
You can't lower your guard
with your eating schedule!
You don't know that?!
Lowering our guard?
You're lowering your guard!
When you're eating...
...it's over for you guys.
What? What?
You were too careless, so it's over.
What are you doing?
That's fine.
All because you're stuffing yourselves like idiots.
What?
I'm going to shoot.
Why? Stop it.
I'm going to shoot this.
But I like that!
I don't care.
If you like it, then say so!
That's what we've been doing all along.
I'm shooting.
Ouch!
It didn't make a sound.
I'm going to shoot again.
He's popping the balloons.
He's pulling them.
It really doesn't make a sound at all.
It's a miracle.
So this wasn't broken?
Changing the subject, huh?
Time for the weird-face bucket.
Wanna do it?
I did it earlier.
Koyabu-san, wanna do it?
The weird-face bucket.
I don't mind, but I don't think
anyone's going to laguh.
Since it's just making weird faces.
Look at this.
How many times are you going to do it?
How many times is normal?
Three times is the standard.
Koyabu-san is going to do it three times.
What's with this?
-If I'm covering my face then...
-It'll work out, it'll work out.
Your scores have been getting lower, huh?
Was that too bad?
-You're grading him?
-Yes.
He can get a high score?
You can't change that.
It got better.
Better?
Yeah.
So should I emphasize them more?
It's not changing.
That's the same.
They're all the same.
That was the same.
In the same order.
You lowered your guard.
-What?
-By doing that,
You absolutely lowered your guard.
What do you mean?
It doesn't matter anymore.
Any last words?
Are you going to kill him?
I'm going to die?
Do you have any last words?
Tell my family that I'm sorry.
Pretty good, huh?
Yeah.
Huh? It's our turn?
Everyone's looking this way.
Sorry about that.
Sometimes I get like that.
I'm really sorry.
No, it's fine.
It's fine, but we were all wondering
what the hell you were doing.
I thought it was fun.
I've been like this for a long time.
I'm sorry.
Okay, Miyasako-san...
-I'm really sorry about that.
-It's okay.
I've always been the type to get like that.
-Don't touch me.
-No, really...
Are you angry?
-I'm not, I'm not.
-You really are!
I'm really sorry.
I really regret it.
Please forgive me.
Please forgive me for real.
He said he's not angry.
I'm not angry.
You are!
You're angry, Goto-san.
If you did it for a good reason,
then that's good enough!
See?! You're angry!
You just got angry!
I'm not angry!
You are, you are!
You definitely are!
He just got annoyed.
Are you angry at that?
See? See?
He's angry.
He's not angry.
I'm really not.
You're angry.
That's scary...
You know I have aichmophobia?
See?
-Aichmophobia?
-Fear of pointy/sharp objects?
What's aichmophobia?
And both were pointy?
Aichmophobia, yes.
And both things were pointy?
Don't you mean acrophobia
instead of aichmophobia?
-What's aichmophobia?
-That's aichmophobia, right?
Chains!
That's scary.
Don't show up
just to bring stuff like that.
That's pretty crude.
Are we really okay with giving him a weapon?
You lowered your guard.
Don't hold onto that!
That's enough.
What are you doing?
You definitely lowered your guard.
Is that your end goal?
See? You're angry!
I'm not angry.
I'm speaking calmly.
You're angry.
Is that Doraemon?
Doraemon!
That's right.
They're angry,
so go and get them!
-Are you limping?
-Are you angry?
I'm annoyed by a few things,
yeah.
Your skin is pretty unkempt.
Unkempt? Me?
I brought a beautifying face roller.
A mini 4x4?
Watch out, watch out....
This is not a beautifying face roller.
It's a mini 4x4.
Fly away!
Watch out!
-Hey, watch out!
-Are you okay?
I think he's okay.
-I'm fine.
-Are you okay?
-That was scary.
-"Are you okay?"
Stop it, you!
-Are you okay?
-Hey, wait a second.
Hey wait. What are you doing?
Something's here.
When you do something like that....
That's amazing, but Kato....
Look behind you.
I'm Sugishita!
Sugishita?
—Is he your partner?
—I'm the special agent.
My name is Sugishita Ukyo. (EN: Detective from "Doraemon")
Do you have a moment?
Just a moment.
I'm worried about the details.
I'm glad there are so many of you here.
So let's start from here.
You're a beauty, huh?
And you're a beauty, huh? A beauty,
A beauty, a beauty
I'm skipping this one.
You're a beauty, huh?
You...
You know why I skipped you?
No.
That's because...
You're ugly as fuck!
Chief Secretary!
Let's go.
Ukyo-san...
Was he this kind of person?
Not at all.
This is just an exaggeration.
And did his hair look like that?
I want a smoke so bad.
-Hey, Goto...
-Yeah?
Think about how I feel.
What?
You're always hosting on TV and stuff...
-Isn't that right, Gotou?
-Yeah.
But I'm your senpai.
And yet I'm here...
-...with this piece of cloth.
-Yeah...
I just want you to know how I feel.
But that's your own choice, bro.
-Just once, though.
-That's what you chose.
Just once.
Try to understand how I feel.
-Well...
-You can do it over your clothes.
-Over them?
-Sure.
How do you think I feel when I do this?
What's going on?
Over them?
I don't get how you wrap this around you.
That's right.
I do this myself, so...
-You do it yourself?
-That's right.
That's pretty deep, huh?
You get it? Make sure it's sturdy.
Make sure it's sturdy.
Okay!
You're lifting him up!
-Watch out!
-You're lifting him up.
I'm flying, I'm flying!
I'm flying!
I've seen an octopus do that before.
That's scary.
Miyasako-san.
Remember what's happened before.
This isn't really fun at all.
It's going deep in here, too.
More than here.
Watch out, you're going to end up coughing blood.
Only Miyasako-san can stop it, though.
Here's worse than here.
It's pretty tight!
Are you okay?
Poor guy.
You can't do that.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
-I told you you can't do it.
-You're right.
Gotou can't take stuff like that.
No, it's fine, really.
I was up in the air!
How do you tie this properly?
This cloth.
I know how to do it.
Do you really, though?
I don't think so.
—I can do it myself.
—Show us.
Miyasako-san, you look kind of...
I want to see how tight you do it.
That's no good.
Because in the future
I'd like to do it, too.
This is bad.
That's a look you only see once every nine months.
You do this right here...
Are you learning how to do it?
You tie it around here.
I've seen this before.
And you raise it over here.
—Over there?
—Yeah.
I know this.
Up?
Yeah.
You know it, Miyasako-san.
You know it.
That's the worst thing to do right now.
They're not stopping until somebody gets hurt.
Miyasako-san... it hurts!
It hurts!
Sacrifice... sacrifice... sacrifice...
He loves to do it on the neck, huh?
He loves it there.
Let's stop this.
I think I've seen this somewhere before.
The only ones having fun are you two
and Miyagawa-san.
We've just been here.
Right?
For a while.
Hey, it hurt me too.
You sure swung it around.
You're a damned gorilla.
That hurts!
Who's going to do it?
Who are you?
Hello there.
I'm Sakurai from Mr. Children. (EN: Japanese Pop-Rock Band)
What?!
Hello there.
I'm Sakurai
from Mr. Children!
Hello there, hello there!
I'm Sakurai from Mr. Children.
And so we've ended up in a loop.
This is pretty bad.
I'm Sakurai.
You idiot!
Koyabu was in trouble too!
For real!
I was about to burst.
Right, he was doing it all over the place!
-And Koyabu was in trouble!
-Yeah, Koyabu was close!
We don't get to see your face like that often.
I thought that it was Matsuyama Chiharu for sure.
Maybe a freestyle version. (EN: Japanese Folk Singer)
But it was Mr. Children!
It was a complete mess!
Hello there!
I'm Sakurai from Mr. Children!
This is really bad.
You idiot!
It was really funny, though.
This is clearly a point to Zakoshiyoh.
Wait, if he's that far ahead...
Then you get a yellow.
-Thank you very much.
-A yellow...
A yellow?
-It's just your first time.
-Still a yellow.
-A yellow, huh?
-It's the first time.
Come to think of it, we're past the halfway point.
Half there already!
Half!
Finally!
Here we go!
So when it comes to points...
Kato and Zakoshi are ahead.
But Kato's almost out, so...
And Miyasako gets that one point.
Zakoshi and Miyasako are looking pretty good.
I saw something on TV the other day...
What?
I caught a cold,
so I decided to make a cup of noodles.
I poured the water and got ready to take a bath,
but I ended up pouring the hot water on the guy
sitting on the sofa.
I tripped.
It was Yamada Gorou-san.
So he was like "What the hell are you doing, you idiot?!"
He was insanely mad.
But I'm smart and I liked him, so...
I was there wiping his neck.
I'm sure it was hot, though!
I couldn't say no.
In any case, can anyone give this back to him?
I took a strand of his hair.
From Yamada Goro-san.
Did you tear it off?
You have some hair there?
-Did you tear all that off him?
-I was pretty shocked when I saw this in my hand.
He didn't notice?
-You took all that at once?
-All that just by pulling?
And it came off like that?
I started stumbling because I couldn't walk straight,
I ended up bumping into a wall.
You felt it?
Last time I saw an ad with him on it,
he still had it, though.
Can someone give it back to him?
Someone that knows Yamada Gorou.
I'm sure he's going to get pretty mad.
It would be better if you gave it back himself.
I just felt that if I did that, he'd say...
"Give it back you idiot!"
Or something like that.
He's that kind of person?
I didn't think so.
He's like that?
He speaks like that?
Wanna watch a video?
-Wanna watch it?
-Let's do a screening session!
-Some pictures before the video, though.
-Sure.
I'm curious about these pictures.
I had to check it wasn't just a photoshop.
This is a wrestler.
A wrestler?
-Yeah, yeah.
—So what?
At first I mistook him...
...for Yoshiko from Ganbareruya.
I mistook that guy.
The wrestler?
Yeah, yeah.
The wrestler...
...and Yoshiko from Ganbareruya.
I mistook them at first.
Is it showing yet?
They look the same!
-Is it a photoshop?
-It's not.
-It has to be.
-Isn't it her?
They look the same.
She's just like that.
They really look almost the same.
-Yeah.
-And this is a guy?
He is.
So he hides his tits like that?
Just like Ayumi.
Yeah, for sure.
So I checked on Yoshiko.
But she was in the hospital.
But when I went there, she looked like this.
This is Yoshiko.
-You can't tell them apart.
-That's not the wrestler?
Oh no...
That's a terrible picture.
Looking at her like this,
she looks the same as always.
-Isn't this the wrestler?
-That's Yoshiko.
That's freaky!
It moves?
-That's a video?
-This is Yoshiko.
That's weird.
Well, I'm sure it was rough for her.
Yeah, yeah.
Alright, got it.
That's what I was curious about.
-Time for the video?
-Is it okay?
-Sure.
-Let's do this.
Can I show mine?
I used this for a solo show I was doing the other day.
Can I show you guys some of it?
Really? Okay, let's go.
Hello there. Good day.
I'm Sean Ben-man. (EN: Not 100% sure about this, might be "Sean Bean-man" or "Shonben-man")
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Sean Ben-man. Ben-man.
Ben-man, Ben-man.
I'm Sean Ben-man.
Nice to meetcha!
That was a lie,
so I'm going to go all out.
You see, today I had to wait and wait.
Seiya, Seiya, wait!
Seiya lost!
He's at it again!
—That was bad!
—That was too much.
Gotou-san was laughing too!
I wasn't!
I managed to hold it in.
What was with that video?
You're really insane!
You were laughing, Seiya.
Seiya was definitely laughing.
—Let's take a look.
—He even laughed out loud.
—He definitely did.
—That was hilarious.
I'm Sean Ben-man.
He's too into it.
I'm just exaggerating.
Now he looks like a reactor!
The reactor's going too fast...
It's hilarious.
That was too much.
You sure can hold back with this, huh?!
This is just insane.
It's insane!
He's making the same face for like 60% of it!
Alright, orange for Seiya.
That's bad.
—You're almost out.
—It's the second one.
Zakoshiyoh-san is too much.
Zakoshi is messing everyone up.
That was too much right now.
We have to change our strategy.
I can do anything on video, right?
Yeah, videos are free.
—There's still some left?
—There is.
Are we going to watch more of the video?
Do it. It's only halfway done.
I'll leave that to you.
Here we go!
It's not done...
So that... is resuming?
Resume, resume!
There's still some left!
I'm going to do it till you don't laugh anymore.
It was some kind of subliminal attack.
I didn't think that guy could pull off something like that.
Here we go!
There are still three hours left.
Still three hours, huh?
And three hours is still half of it.
Alright, you ready?
We're not done yet.
Go on.
Are we going to be okay?
This is our eight season after eight years.
What's that "South Sea Hoax" in the background all about?
The title was great.
The title wasn't so good this time around.
"Zakoshi's stinking movie..."
It was all nonsense...
But it was much better than before.
Much much better.
This is getting really dark.
And the venue was weird, too. The Zakou temple.
I used to do performance art in Nakano a long time ago.
This is too much.
We can't go back after this.
This is the main attraction.
What did the people at the venue say?
A subliminal effect.
See? Subliminal.
You laughed? Seiya, you laughed?
Seiya.
I was about to explode.
All this time.
Why weren't you laughing?!
All you had to do was look away.
Alright!
I see!
-I guess it's over!
-It's over.
Its over, huh?
-It can't be helped.
-No!
Let's take a look.
The Zakou temple.
I used to do performance art in Nakano a long time ago.
This is too much.
We can't go back after this.
This is the main attraction.
What did the people at the venue say?
A subliminal effect.
See? Subliminal.
I see, watching it again...
No way, no way, no way!
It's impossible.
Well, that's right.
It's impossible!
Seiya...
You're out!
Another point for Zakoshi!
Amazing.
Zakoshi-san is too strong!
It's impossible not to laugh at this video!
He's going to win again.
I still have more.
Like five more.
No way, no way!
One more.
No, no way.
Leave them for next time!
-Just one more!
-One more?
Wanna watch one more?
That's too hard.
I'm sure it's just like watching porn.
Can I say something first?
I think the main problem is just that
I probably like Zakoshi too much.
As a comedy act in general.
Hello there.
I'm Sakurai from Mr. Children
When jelly got in my eyes,
I thought that I might make it today.
But Zakoshi's videos were probably
enough to make me laugh a thousand times.
That video was too much.
I laughed with no regret.
I'm going to laugh at that no doubt.
If you're going to do it, I'll do it back.
I forgot.
A monster was there!
-Other than Iron Man?
-Yes!