[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
I love jumping into unusual situations.
And I thought this would definitely be fun.
I'm getting sleepy!
Ouch!
Not being able to laugh...
...I've never experienced anything like this before.
"Mama, can I eat this?"
So I should just have this expression the whole time, right?
I'm thinking of playing it slow and steady.
After all, I've been on the show before.
So I think they might try to attack me.
I took off my hat.
They know my weakness.
So I have to toughen up at this stage.
I will try my best to control my feelings and make it out.
Thank you.
He kissed him.
-So I have to issue you a card, Takahashi.
-Right, understood.
"Mama, can I eat this?"
We got him.
It's a yellow card.
For Katori.
Shingo?
You had it coming.
Gee, the craziness is starting up again!
Oyakata's reading voice is so exquisite.
I completely agree.
Alright, here we go!
Would you all like to do some tongue twisters?
Are we back?
-Tongue twisters...
-Yes.
Let's say each one three times in a row.
Three times in a row?!
-Let's do it.
-In a row!
-We just draw a card?
-Yes.
Kotori, please go ahead.
Oyakata is really great.
Alright.
This one.
Three times in a row?
Three in a row.
"Nyanko Konyanko Magonyanko"
(Kitty, kitten, grand-kitten, great-grand kitten.)
-Amazing!
-Wonderful!
They are normal tongue twisters, huh?
They are real ones.
Me? Okay.
"Akapajama Aopajama Kipajama"
(Red pajamas, blue pajamas, yellow pajamas)
Well done!
Sho was in trouble just now.
Alright then.
"Migi Mimi Mini Nikibi"
(Right Ear Mini Pimple)
He's so slow with it!
"Migi Mimi Mini Nikibi"
(Right Ear Mini Pimple)
He's so slow with it!
"Migi Mimi Mini Nikibi"
(Right Ear Mini Pimple)
Pimple?
I couldn't hear him.
Ah, a pimple!
"Migi Mimi Mini Nikibi"
(Right Ear Mini Pimple)
A small pimple, right?
What the heck is he reading?
Oyakata must have some bad eyesight.
He must be farsighted.
Again?
"Migi Mimi Mini Nikibi"
(Right Ear Mini Pimple)
How can they not laugh?
He's going again.
Oyakata is going again?
Go ahead.
He passed it to Sho.
He gave up.
"Kaeru Pyokopyoko Mipyokopyoko Awasete Pyokopyoko Mupyokopyoko"
(The frogs jump, three (times) jump, together jump, six (times) jump.)
Oyakata!
"Kaeru Pyokopyoko Mipyokopyoko Awasete Pyokopyoko Mupyokopyoko"
(The frogs jump, three (times) jump, together jump, six (times) jump.)
Oyakata is struggling.
"Kaeru Pyokopyoko Mipyokopyoko Awasete Pyokopyoko Mupyokopyoko"
(The frogs jump, three (times) jump, together jump, six (times) jump.)
Oyakata is struggling.
That's so funny.
Why is he the one having trouble?
He's the one that set up the game!
Right?
"Sumomo Mo Momo Mo Momo No Uchi"
(A Japanese plum is a peach, a peach is also a peach, both Japanese plums and peaches are a kind of peach)
Right?
"Sumomo Mo Momo Mo Momo No Uchi"
(A Japanese plum is a peach, a peach is also a peach, both Japanese plums and peaches are a kind of peach)
Shingo, go ahead.
That was good.
"Chosakusha Shujutsuchu"
(The writer is undergoing surgery)
"Chosakusha Shu-"
"Chosakusha Shujutsuchu"
(The writer is undergoing surgery)
One more?
"Chosakusha Shujutsuchu"
(The writer is undergoing surgery)
"Shuju- Shujutsuchu"
"Shujutsuchu"
Whoa, I can't do it at all.
This one's really hard.
"Shujutsuchu"
Oh no, Oyakata's face is making me laugh so much.
I haven't done a lot of acting so I'm super bad at this kind of stuff.
But this one's one of the hardest.
"Shujutsuchu"
Oyakata, you should give it a go.
Oyakata is going next.
Good idea.
Oyakata has overcome many battles already.
We're listening.
I see.
"Chosakusha Shujutsuchu"
(The writer is undergoing surgery)
Isn't that a bit slow?
Yeah...
"Chosakusha Shujutsuchu"
(The writer is undergoing surgery)
"Cho-katsu-sha Shujutsuchu"
You nailed it.
You got it.
He really nailed it.
He really did.
Katori has been going after Oyakata, hasn't he?
"Namamugi Namagome Namatamago"
(Raw wheat, raw rice, raw egg)
Katori has been going after Oyakata, hasn't he?
"Namamugi Namagome Namatamago"
(Raw wheat, raw rice, raw egg)
He's slow.
"Namamugi Namagome Namatamago"
(Raw wheat, raw rice, raw egg)
He's slow.
"Namamugi Namagome Namatamago"
(Raw wheat, raw rice, raw egg)
He's pretty slow.
"Namamugi Namagome Namatamago"
(Raw wheat, raw rice, raw egg)
Slow, huh?
"Namamugi Namagome Namatamago"
(Raw wheat, raw rice, raw egg)
Slow, huh?
He is.
Alright, here goes the last one.
"Boku Bob Furo Babu Tounyu"
(Me Bob Bath Bubble Soy Milk)
I don't get it...
What does it mean?
What is that?
So weird.
"Boku Bob"?
"Boku Bob"
-"Furo Babu Tounyu".
-"Furo Babu Tounyu"
This one's quite peculiar, wouldn't you agree?
Hold on...
-"Boku Bob Furo Babu Tounyu"
-What does he mean by that?
How does it sound when you say it in Mori Shinichi's voice?
"Boku Bob Furo Babu Tounyu"
I'm gonna use this now.
So please do Mori Shinichi's voice again.
In Mori Shinichi's style.
-Right, like Mori Shinichi?
-Yes.
In Mori Shinichi's style.
-Right, like Mori Shinichi?
-Yes.
"Boku Bob Furo Babu Tounyu"
That's pretty good.
Not even a flinch!
"Boku Bob Furo Babu Tounyu"
Can you start over?
Sure, sure.
Alright, please go ahead.
"Boku Bob Furo Babu Tounyu"
He only did the voice the first time!
What's with that melodic tone?
"Boku Bob Furo Babu Tounyu"
He's almost singing it.
You don't have to sing it!
"Boku Bob Furo Babu Tounyu"
"Migi Mimi Mini Nikibi"
Say it fast!
Is it hard?
It is.
It sure is.
A blender?
What's that?
Well, just like Katsunori, I also...
I had a very early flight from the countryside...
And I couldn't sleep at all.
I'm getting a bit sleepy now...
It's Frisk. (EN: 1)
Is that really Frisk?
Frisk?
He pulverized some Frisk.
Looks like drugs.
Is that safe?
-Is it safe?
-will you be okay?
You're not thinking of inhaling that through your nose, right?
That's the most effective delivery method.
Can we really air this?
Of course, it's just Frisk.
But you shouldn't inhale this stuff.
But this is the only way to fight my sleepiness.
Seriously?
I've been doing it for a while.
-He's doing it cause he's sleepy?
-Here I go.
Is it more effective this way?
Amazing.
No, no, no.
You seem to hate it.
That's so dangerous.
Oh no!
You hate it.
Look at Oyakata's face.
Right?
Oyakata seems a bit mad, no?
Do you always do this?
Yes, I do.
Aren't you worried about people getting the wrong idea?
-Are you okay?
-The wrong idea?
I mean...
The wrong idea...
Doesn't everyone do this?
Oyakata is up to something.
How about we play a game that will wake us right up?
There he is.
Takahashi is back.
He is!
It's been a while.
-It's been a while since we last saw him.
-Right.
Katsunori is finally back.
Ah, Katsunori!
You should do a tongue twister.
I just wanted to give you guys something.
It's a present.
I brought some food from my hometown.
These are called Sukaman, and they're from my home town in Yokosuka. (EN: 2)
Sukaman...
My dad actually made these.
-Really?
-Yeah.
So, I wanted to play this russian roulette-inspired game.
One of these is really spicy.
-Oh, that's scary.
-I see...
So we can play that game.
And maybe we'll get some blood pumping into our systems.
Sho...
Help!
Oh, he can't breathe!
He's running out of breath.
Someone has to take the mask off.
Are you alright?
Katsunori!
He's always going for Oyakata.
-Take it! Take it!
-He's choking.
He looks like a thug.
Thank you.
And he's written the Katsu Kanji for Katsunori.
This makeup must have taken a long time.
What was that just now?
Oh, it's this.
Candy cigarettes?
Thank you.
You're really kind.
Ready?
-Thank you.
-This brings me back.
Katsu.
Yes.
"Onore Ni Katsu"
("to conquer oneself")
-"Onore Ni Katsu"
My parents must have been thinking of that when they gave me this name.
My father's name also has that same "Katsu".
-This Katsu?
-Yes.
He's called Katsuaki.
Oh, really?
He made these Manju.
-Oh really?
-Yes, so let's eat it on three.
Alright, let's eat at the same time.
-Let's go on three.
-Okay.
-Only one person's gonna get the spicy one, right?
-That's right.
Only one is spicy?
Is it really spicy?
Will I die?
-It's totally safe.
-Alright.
Will he die?
Alright, everyone ready?
Yes.
Alright.
Let's cheer for this encounter and our time in this space.
He thinks he's gonna die.
Thanks!
-Cheers.
Oh no.
Ah...
Who got it?
Who?
It's spicy.
Katori?
-I think I got it.
-Right...
Sho too...
Is it spicy for everyone?
Are all of these spicy?
-They must all be spicy.
-All?
It's in every single one.
All of them, huh?
It's got red bean paste.
So hot!
Hot!
This is full of Karashi! (EN: 3)
Not all of them are spicy!
Oyakata, did you get it too?
So spicy.
Right?
My stomach hurts!
Mine is not spicy.
-No way, no way.
-Really?!
He said it's not spicy.
So hot!
Do we have tissues?
Where are the tissues?
He looks so funny with all that makeup.
-It's super spicy.
-Really?
He looks so funny with all that makeup.
-It's super spicy.
-Really?
So spicy!
Really?
-What's that?
-So hot.
-The tissues are over here.
-Oh, to cleanse the palate?
Yes, let's cleanse our palates.
Is it Chanko? (EN: 4)
Chanko?
Hold on a sec.
What is it?
What? What?
Oyakata has brought some Chanko with him.
It was super spicy.
You should use the tap.
Oh, right.
Katsunori, you're alright, right?
I'm fine.
It was no big deal.
Was it that spicy?
So dangerous!
Dangerous...
That could have gone very bad.
Taking that angle?
You've gone and done it.
-You messed up!
You just laughed so normally, like you were at home hanging out.
That was so dangerous!
So dangerous!
You must have forgotten.
This kind of thing always happens.
Every time.
-There's times where you laugh about nothing in particular.
-Right...
-Katsunori Takahashi!
-Yes!
I have to give you this!
An orange card!
-It wasn't that big of a reaction...
-Right...
So let's have a look.
And please be careful of this kinda stuff.
So dangerous!
Dangerous...
That could have gone very bad.
Taking that angle?
At that moment I just forgot about the whole thing.
That's right.
No matter how long you're in here, you'll eventually forget.
-Yeah...
-Yes...
You're so close to being thrown out.
Don't worry, I'll keep it together.
You'll get the red card next time.
Alright, do your best.
-Will do!
-Thanks!
Alright, do your best.
-Will do!
-Thanks!
I'm super nervous.
-These guys are so tough.
-Totally.
-There's no cooking oil.
-No, no, no.
What a pickle.
You're right.
It's not here.
I need some tissues.
I can't believe Yokozuna made up Chanko.
I'm so happy!
What?!
-Yokozuna's Chanko?!
-Amazing!
-Awesome.
-Is it the real deal?
I'm so happy.
Me too.
What is it?
Let's clean up a bit.
What is this?
They're cleaning all the dangerous stuff.
He's going somewhere.
And he's left the pot behind.
He left the pot.
Why is he leaving the scene?
He's back.
He did nothing.
He didn't pick anything up.
He just took a peek and turned right back.
Why?
I didn't look at his clothes.
This guy is scary.
-What's he doing?
-Is he looking for something?
Chopsticks?
-Oh, he was looking for the chopsticks.
-Totally!
There he goes.
But why'd he go to the locker room?
It was spicy enough to make your stomach hurt, right?
It was super spicy.
Wasn't that Karashi?
It was Karashi paste.
Karashi paste?
There was some inside, right?
Right, right.
I mean, they were normal Manju, but we added the spiciness for today.
For that russian roulette game.
He's not uncovering it!
Come on, you don't have to wait for it to boil!
Has he even turned it on?
I heard a beep.
Really?
I think I did...
Is he waiting for something?
Isn't it ready?
It's a hot pot so he must be waiting for it to boil over.
This...
Is that on?
Yes.
It smells good.
-He hasn't done anything...
-But he just said it smells good.
It's pretty...
He's keeping us in suspense.
You don't have to make it boil!
But he must be planning something.
Waiting for the perfect timing.
He said it smells good.
This is bad, they're wasting so much time.
The other guys aren't doing anything either.
Right, right.
Are they all waiting for the hot pot?
And everyone's silent.
He's loitering again.
He's left the pot's side again.
And the other guys can't do anything about it.
This is getting scary.
Where is he going?
What?
The other guys should try something.
Instead of being silent...
-Right...
-Right?
They've got to act.
They are on high alert.
They should start asking questions.
I'm so hungry.
Here it comes.
-What's his angle?
-I'm hungry as well.
Yeah, me too.
-What's his angle?
-I'm hungry as well.
Yeah, me too.
Small stomach?
Well, yes.
It's only been about three hours though...
Oyakata, do you usually cook?
Yes.
From time to time.
What is he trying to do?!
He hasn't opened it yet.
But you left home pretty early on, right?
-You didn't have to make all of the Chanko, did you??
-Right.
Most people think you don't have to...
But it's something everyone has to do.
But you were also promoted very early on, didn't your senior-junior relationships turn on their heads?
Yes, that would happen often...
He's not opening it, he's just talking.
For example, I had to do triple the amount of cleaning.
And that's how I got a strong body.
I see...
Your legs and hips get stronger.
All the cleaning work is really hard on the body.
I would clean really huge rooms.
You also got to train your legs every time you pooped, cause we had the Japanese bathrooms.
Really?
You had to have strong legs.
Here it comes!
He opened it.
We saw it!
I'm so happy.
-Isn't that Oden?
-It's Oden! (EN: 5)
I'm so happy.
-Isn't that Oden?
-It's Oden! (EN: 5)
-There was Oden in there.
-It was Oden.
It's just a normal oden.
-What?
-Oden...
-Well, since my days as the Yokozuna...
-It's just normal Oden.
...I have been very good at eating hot food.
I can eat any hot meal.
You can take the heat?
Yes, I can take it.
Hold on, that's just Oden.
It's not even hot.
There's no steam or anything!
It's room temp!
-I'm pretty good at eating hot stuff.
-It's lukewarm!
I might even be cold!
You have to show a bigger reaction!
He's just eating the Oden normally!
-He closed it!
-He closed it.
No, no, no!
Takahashi! Takahashi! Takahashi!
-He's in trouble!
-Guys, you have to make a joke!
Say something!
This...
-Is it hot?
-Yes.
It's warmer.
Can you check?
Is it hot?
Can you eat it?
Is that okay?
It must not be that hot.
What?
Is it hot?
Hot, right?
Should we wait a bit longer?
Was it hot?
It's not something spicy again, right?
What was the point?
What was the point of that?
I think we had to wait a bit longer.
-You think so?
-Yes.
Just a bit longer.
-We'll eat once it gets a bit hotter.
-Right.
-It's really good Oden.
-You think so?
He's totally touching it.
It wasn't hot?
It wasn't.
We want to eat it while it's piping hot.
Piping hot, huh?
It was a bit lukewarm.
Right.
-Right?
-That's weird...
He's touching the pot!
He's all over that pot!
You can't be touching it like that!
But it took so long for him to get the joke out!
You're touching it...
Why did he even pretend it was hot?
You should try it again once it's hot enough.
Totally.
How about we use that spare time and do an impersonation contest?
What?!
I see!
Sure.
Are you guys good at impersonations?
-I'm not very good...
-Me neither...
-Really?
-I'm not... that good either.
-Well, they don't normally do this kind of stuff.
But I was curious about the kind of impersonations we could do.
I totally get it, I'm also very interested.
I'm not very confident, but let's try it.
I'll go first since I brought it up.
-Did someone write names inside?
-Yes.
That's right, we'll be doing an impersonation of the names in the box.
Pikachu.
Oh, like that, huh?
Pikachu...
Pikachu!
Something like that?
I don't really know... I've never watched Pokemon...
-I just went with the flow.
-I don't know either...
I don't know.
Does he have a special ability?
Yes, he does.
What is it?
He has the "100,000 Volt Thunderbolt."(EN: 6)
100,000 Volt Thunderbolt!
He doesn't actually say it.
Oh, he doesn't?
He's a mouse, after all.
100,000 Volt Thunderbolt!
He just said it doesn't say it.
He doesn't say it...
He doesn't talk?
Is Ash the one who says it?
-Ash?
-I mean, you're just saying it like Dayu Koume. (EN: 7)
Ash says the move with his normal voice.
Like this?
That's totally wrong.
Do you know Dayu Koume?
He's totally sleeping.
Really?
Do you know Dayu Koume?
He's totally sleeping.
Really?
You think so?
He's nodding off for real.
He's a very famous comedian, you know?
See?!
He must be sleepy.
-He was sleeping.
-Hold on...
Oyakata, you were nodding off just now, weren't you?
No...
-He was sleeping!
-Are you sleepy?
I wasn't sleeping.
Not at all.
Dayu Koume.
Do you know of him?
-Dayu Koume, huh?
-Damn it!
Dayu Koume.
What is going on?
This guy is very intense.
-Right?
-He's awesome.
He actually wears a Chonmage. (EN: 8)
Damn it!
Is he a singer?
No, he's a comedian.
Oh, a comedian.
Not like that.
He does a very high voice.
This is going off the rails.
Damn it!
Look, look, look at him!
It's hard.
Sho!
Sho is in trouble!
Would anyone like to go next?
Looks like the Oden is almost done.
The Oden is done.
Here we go.
What perfect timing.
This is bad! This is bad!
It must be really hot.
This might work.
It was a bit too hot!
He put it down immediately!
But that's amazing.
Is he gonna eat it?
This is crazy.
He did say he was good with hot food.
-Are you good with hot food?
-Yes.
Won't it hurt your throat?
Are you really gonna be okay?
He's eating.
That's amazing.
He's super strong.
Look at them!
I mean, he's been eating Chanko since he was young.
Amazing! So strong!
But it looks like he's struggling a lot.
Oh no, Katori is in trouble!
He's really strong.
He's eating it straight out of the boiling pot.
-That's amazing.
-He's still going.
Is it true that the Yokozuna gets to eat the Chanko first?
Well...
You have an order, right?
The Master is first.
-The Master eats first, huh?
-The Master goes first.
I see...
-You should try eating some of the radish or konnyaku.
-Or the meat dumpling.
He did the radish earlier.
And the Jonidan at the end just eat the broth with some rice, right? (EN: 9)
That's right, I also struggled with that when I first joined the stable.
The Jonidan get all the scraps.
We didn't get to eat the main dish.
Pick the other one.
He's cooling it down!
He's shaking it up.
What is the point of all this?!
What is he trying to do?!
There's no point if you try to cool it down!
This ain't Yakiniku! (EN: 10)
And don't drop it!
How can he eat that?
Is he regretting it?
You'll eat it straight away?
That must be super hot!
What does he wanna do?
Really?
Yes.
But I think konnyaku is still manageable.
-No way, it's gonna be bad!
-You think so?
-He's going for it.
-Okay, okay.
So tough!
Crazy!
Oh no, oh no!
There’s no way I could do that...
But he's super tough!
He's very tough.
Egg!
It even has Ganmodoki! (EN: 11)
Can you also manage the boiled egg?
That's too hot.
The radish must be blazing hot.
The radish, egg and the Ganmodoki.
Are you going next?
-Right, the Ganmodoki.
-Yeah.
Excuse me.
It's gonna be super hot.
The egg is the hardest.
The egg?
The egg is dangerous!
Sho... Sho...
Is he doing it?
Oh no...
-That's so dangerous.
-Are you really gonna do it?
It looks super hot!
He's gonna burn himself.
So hot!
Be careful.
The pot is steaming.
Two birds with one stone!
Alright!
This is bad.
Danger! Danger!
Is it hot?
It’s not, right?
He can't even chew it.
Is it hot?
Go drink some water.
I'm fine.
You know I used to live in a dorm when I was a student, so I'm good with this stuff.
Oh, really?
Oh, you used to be in the baseball club.
That's right.
Yes, so if you didn't eat fast you didn't eat.
Right...
But this is really boiling, huh?
You should go for a smaller one.
A radish?
-No way, the radish is the worst!
-It's gonna be hot!
Scary!
Whoa, that's gonna be hot.
It's gonna be hard.
Could you put it back for a second?
This is gonna be tough.
The egg was too hot, I didn't even have time to react.
I bet it was... Are you okay?
But when I was a student I had to eat piping hot meals.
The first years had to prepare the meals for the second and third years.
Is that so?
You can't blow on it.
You can't be doing that!
Hot!
Hot!!
Course it's hot...
That's that.
-You thought you could handle it, huh?
-It flew.
-Oyakata is in trouble!
-I'm so sorry.
Oyakata is on another level.
Oyakata is amazing.
-He really is.
-That's amazing.
He did two in a row.
I'm so sorry about that.
No worries, no worries.
We can't eat it anymore, it's all yours now.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
Where's he going?
He's walking again.
-Why?
-Where's he going?
Why?
-Is he mad?
-Is he pissed?
He's pissed?
He got really drastic mood swings!
For real!
Alright.
Who would like to go next?
Shall I?
Go ahead.
Oyakata is not here.
This is impossible.
-Huh?
Hold on...
-This is impossible.
-Let me see.
Should we see it first?
Should we look at it?
Will you?
May I?
What is it?
Is it alive?
It is alive, barely.
It's alive?
It's barely alive.
Can I give you guys a hint?
Sure.
This one's probably really hard...
Is it a character?
Should we not look?
How should I even impersonate this?
I don't know it.
-You know it, don't you?
-Yes.
Then you should give it a try.
It looks good on you.
But we're giving it away with this already.
You have to say "I'm starting to get sleepy".
-Did you figure it out?
-Yes.
-It's something like this.
Like this, right?
These are not the actual glasses though...
You get it, right?
What is it?
Isn't it Naoko Ken? (Jp singer/actress.)
No, it isn't Naoko Ken.
But he said it's barely alive.
Something like this, right?
Oyakata is finally here!
Here he is!
The real deal!
Please.
Please?
Is it a Sumo song?
Now!
Takanohana's impersonation show is about to begin!
First off, we have Takamiyama!
Twofold! Twofold! (EN: 12)
That's so old!
Next up, Kakuei Tanaka! (Former Jp PM)
I mean... Well...
That ain't a Sumo wrestler!
Next up, Beat Takeshi! (EN: 13)
Idiot! Bastard!
Idiot!
Comaneci!
And lastly, Shigeo Nagashima! (EN: 14)
It went swoosh, bang and bang.
It is time for the encore.
Do you have any encore impersonation requests?
I do.
Mr. Nagashima please.
It went swoosh, bang and bang.
There's gotta be something other than that!
Manager, how should I hit a forkball?
I just can't seem to hit those forkballs.
R-Right...
-That's Gushiken!
-It's Gushiken! (Yoko Gushiken)
Oh, Sho is in trouble!
-That's Gushiken!
-It's Gushiken! (Yoko Gushiken)
Oh, Sho is in trouble!
Gushiken?
It's Gushiken!
He's back to being the Takanohana I watched as a kid.
Someone should throw him around.
Totally.
But do they know?
I mean, they should know.
"Now, I will ask all of you to kill each other"
"You see..."
"I..."
"About Papa..."
-I have to put an end to this.
-Yeah.
Totally!
This one's on Sho.
He had accumulated a bunch of faults.
Totally.
He's the one that set it up...
This one was overdue.
This person was trying to hold in the laughter for the longest time.
And I will be giving him a yellow card.
It goes to Sho Ayanocozey.
Yellow!
Yellow...
You were smirking the whole time.
Right...
"You see..."
"I..."
"About Papa..."
I can't believe that backfired...
It backfired!
You were trying to protect yourself?!
That was quite shocking.
Alright, let's go.
-Alright!
-Let's go!
Here we go!
It's begun.
It certainly has.
We're at the 2 hour mark.
At the very middle.
-Right?
-Yes.
Hold on, I'm gonna go erase this stuff.
Sure.
-You guys keep it up.
-Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Is that gonna come off?
Alright, time to take this off.
Man...
Sho, you've got a lot of impersonation-related games, don't you?
Sorry about that...
No worries.
I wanna give it a try.
Impersonation?
Yes.
I might have put in way too many names.
I might have messed up.
There's tons of names here.
That's right.
There's that many?
Satomi Ishihara.
That's gonna be hard.
Yeah, it's a tough one.
I'm an actress.
That's too general!
An actress?
What kind of person are you?
Someone that would say "I'm an actress"?
An actress that would say "I'm an actress", right?
Who could it be?
I'm very popular.
-Hold on...
-That's not specific at all.
Very popular?
She's never said that!
She would never!
Yes?
Come on...
There's no way they'll ever figure it out...
That's so random...
I mean, are they playing charades or what?
I have acted with her.
Hold on, you just went back to being yourself.
You're changing characters.
Were you talking as Shingo right now?
Now...
I-I might be taking a break from acting at the moment...
She's taking a break?
Well, yeah...
She's taking a break... Ah!
Ehm...
Satomi Ishihara!
Alright!
Oyakata did nothing just now.
Oyakata!
Nothing at all.
But I don't think she speaks like that.
I don't know about that.
That was not an impersonation, right?
Oyakata is scaring me.
I have actually worked with her.
So you must know her well.
But you did act a bit like her.
-I don't think he did...
-It wasn't close at all...
Would you like to try?
-I don't think he did...
-It wasn't close at all...
Would you like to try?
-You should give it a go.
-Please go ahead.
Over here.
Shingo!
Huh?
I have always loved you!
I never should have married that man, and instead married you!
She'd never say that.
He just said the worst thing...
He said a horrible thing...
That's no good.
Really?
-Yes...-Yes...
Alright, I'll try again.
"That man"?
What's with the sharp tongue all of a sudden?
I'm glad I married that man...
But I've always loved you more.
-Can't say that either.
-Really?
Guys, I want you to take a look at this.
Oh, he's back.
It's amazing.
You see... At my age...
I still get fan letters.
Right...
And some of them are quite strange...
So I want you to have a look.
-Whoa, amazing!
-Fan letters!
You get this many?
Amazing.
Surprisingly, I get quite a lot of these.
And you put them in a Ziplock?
I put them in a Ziplock.
"Mr. Katsunori Takahashi"
"Hello"
"I'm always looking forward to all your work, I am a big fan"
They often start with something like this.
I'm sure you guys also get tons of these.
"I became addicted to your sexiness and adult appeal after watching you in Mr. Tadano's Secret Mission"
-Right...
-I watched it too...
"Nowadays, watching you is my reason to live."
"Thank you."
"I wanted to give you something that would make you happy, so I drew a portrait of your smiling face."
"I don't mean to be presumptuous, but it would make me extremely happy if you could hang it somewhere."
That's so nice.
-I'm so grateful for that.
-That's so great.
And this is the drawing.
Let's see.
That's amazing.
This is it.
Who's this?
-That's Katsumi...
-It's Katsumi Takahashi... (Japanese actor/VA)
-He certainly is Mr. Takahashi...
-Isn't that Katsumi?
One Kanji is wrong.
-He wasn't in Mr. Tadano's Secret Mission though...
-Right, one Kanji is wrong...
That's Katsumi Takahashi, isn't he?
I don't think so...
Really?
-He's not in Mr. Tadano's Secret Mission, right?
-Yeah, he isn't.
Alright, I'm going to the next letter.
-Are you moving on?
-Yes.
"Mr. Katsunori Takahashi, nice to meet you"
"I am a senior woman, and I just turned 75 this year"
There's a lot of range.
"Watching your acting has become one of favorite things to do"
"Recently, I have started attending an India-ink painting class"
"I'm still inexperienced but I hope you'll like the drawing"
Another drawing?
You seem to have a lot of artist fans.
Yes...
Another drawing?
You seem to have a lot of artist fans.
Yes...
This is the drawing.
It's an ink painting.
-But that's Katsumi.
-It's Katsumi again.
Does Katsumi have a lot of fans?
That's Katsumi, right?
Totally!
Is everyone getting confused with your names?
I mean, certainly...
Whenever we work together I have certainly mistook his changing room for mine.
This person is from overseas.
"You are a wonderful actor"
"I drew a picture of you"
-Another painting?
-That's so cool.
A picture?
There you go.
Isn't that a Banksy?
This one's coming from Banksy, isn't it?
And it's Katsumi again.
Katsu-Bansky.
This is crazy.
This looks like me, no?
-What does he mean by 'crazy'?
-That's amazing.
Crazy?
Oyakata, what do you think?
-It could or could not be you...
-It's definitely not him.
He ain't getting it at all!
-Banksy?
-Banksy!
-This is a Banksy!
-Bansky sent it to you!
Banksy drew Katsumi.
And then he sent it to you...
Isn't that amazing?
Should we send one of you guys in there?
You'll step inside and stir things up a bit.
I just want to blow some fresh air in that room.
How about it?
-Goto, you wanna go?
-Should I?
Alright, so I can laugh, right?
Yes, don't worry about it.
Thank you for showing us that.
I'll be back!
Let's change the atmosphere.
Are we done with the impersonations?
We were doing it just now.
Hello!
Excuse me.
-Hello everyone.
-Hello.
Oh my...
-Yes?
We still aren't allowed to laugh, right?
-Of course.
-Right.
Yes.
Oh, there it is.
-Go ahead.
-Thank you.
Hello.
-I'll leave this for now.
-Are we doing more impersonations?
Are you guys still doing that?!
I mean, there's still tons of names left...
But these take such a long time.
Give it a go.
Here's the hint: He's a big senior in the industry.
Sure.
You see...
Huh?
I...
I know that you...
...are innocent.
So... Please...
Follow the letter of the law...
You knew immediately, didn't you?
You don't know?
You definitely have worked with this person.
And you as well, Shingo.
Anyway, he speaks really quietly.
Quietly, huh?
Does he walk on a limp?
-Not really...
-Is he your senior?
-On a limp?
-Of course, he's my senior too.
Can't we just stop it with these quizzes?
Stop?
You've been playing this guessing game this whole time!
You're right.
Why are you here all of a sudden?
I just wanted to have a little fun with everyone.
I just thought it'd be fun.
Yes.
But how about we do something else?
-Sure.
-You're right.
How long are we gonna have this on?
Right?
Don't give me that.
Are you gonna eat it later or what?
I already ate.
I was watching, you know?
It's not like I'm here out of the blue.
I've been watching from behind the scenes.
I'll keep it on if you're gonna eat again.
I'll turn it off.
-You'll turn it off?
-Yes.
But it's still on.
He just closed it.
Oh really?
Yes.
How about you have one?
He's very good with hot food.
Oyakata can handle hot food.
He's very tough.
-Konnyaku...
-He's going for the konnyaku?
Konnyaku...
Seriously?
Are you really fine?
For real?
Yeah...
Isn't it hot?
But it looks like you're in pain.
Delicious.
-Is it?
-Yes.
Maybe it's not that hot...
How about you try some?
I'm fine!
Why would I do it?
We've already established that it's hot.
Look at all this steam, of course it's hot!
The lid is hot!
Which one?
-This is bad for Goto.
-Go for the radish.
Right?
The radish is impossible!
Don't force yourself.
I'm feeding myself?!
You guys aren't gonna make me eat it?
It's damn hot!
How can you eat that?!
He's amazing.
It's not hot.
It's not hot?!
It's scalding hot!
Look, I'll eat another one.
Hot!
This is crazy!
How can you eat this?!
And how'd you manage to eat the egg?!
That was something else.
I wouldn't have expected less from you, Goto.
It was way too hot, I couldn't even give an appropriate reaction.
That was so hot!
Shall I go next?
You showed us some great reactions.
-You're doing it?
-Yes.
The egg is super hot.
Eggs are super hot.
Egg...
You just got a hole-in-one into that cup...
-You just got a cup-in-one!
-A cup-in-one!
That was close.
Not at all...
Wasn't that hot?
Are you okay?!
It was fine.
-No one's laughing.
-I'm fine.
I think all of them are kind of smirking but...
It's hot, isn't it?
Of course.
Huh?
-You have to go for the egg next.
-The egg?
Yes, the egg.
It smells good.
Ready?
Yes.
This is bad...
What? In one bite?
He's not even flinching.
Crazy.
That's amazing.
Looks so hot!
You're trying so hard to keep the poker face!
-No...
-Poker face?
I mean...
You've got a river running through your nose!
Delicious.
Is it?
I have seen that expression in one of his press conferences.
Really?
Yes.
Delicious.
That's amazing.
That's really something else.
It really is.
But going like this...
That was a very nice reaction, Suzuki.
Suzuki?
Who's Suzuki?
"Who's Suzuki?"
I ain't Suzuki, you know?
Suzuki!
I mean, you didn't introduce yourself.
I apologize.
Who?
Don't you know who I am?!
We've worked together plenty of times, haven't we?!
Who do you think I am?
Suzuki...
Suzuki?
How about you? We used to be regulars on that show, didn't we?
Yes...
You know my name, right?
-I mean, we were wondering when Suzuki would make an appearance.
-You're Suzuki, right?
That's not it?
-He's not Suzuki?
-I'm not Suzuki!
Kubota?
I'm not Kubota.
He's from Toro Salmon.
Oh, right...
Musaka, what are you digging into your nails for?
Sorry, I've just had this callus for the longest time.
He's Uchida.
Uchida, huh?
No, no... Who cares about all that?
Let's try that!
A little test of courage.
-Sure.
-Test of courage?
Test of courage?
Baseball butt spanking.
What?!
Whoa, I can't do that.
Let's spank some butts!
Can't do it?
No way...
Why are we doing it?
What's the point of this?
-I mean, we're just trying to find out who can take the most hits.
-No warning hits?
Yes, no warning.
-Alright, I'll go first.
-Would bare butts be better?
You're going?
I'm used to this kind of thing.
You are?
-He was in the baseball club.
-Let's do it.
I mean, I'm not 'used' to it per se...
I don't think they do that in normal baseball clubs...
Hiro, let's go.
What?!
-Me?
-Yes.
What?!
But everyone's my senior here...
-Is that how it's gonna be?
-Hit him as hard as you can.
For real? For real?
Is the hitter gonna rotate, or what?
There's no need to.
But he's my senior...
This way is better.
Should I ramp up the force?
-Sure.
-Alright then, I'll start gently first.
I can still go.
With ease!
Piece of cake.
That was pretty hard...
But wait...
Can I really go harder?
He'll be fine.
I see.
-Alright, here I go.
-Sure.
-I can keep going.
-That was nothing.
-A bit harder?
-Yes.
Here I come.
Ouch!!
They're not laughing.
Did anyone laugh?
That must have hurt.
Did Musaka crack up a little bit?
Just a little bit.
Kamiji too.
-Kamiji as well?
-Yes.
-Kamiji too.
-He tried his best.
That hurts!
Alright then...
I have nothing but my guts so...
Are you serious?
I'm glad I worked this hard!
He volunteered.
He's a musician... He's my senior in the industry...
That's right, he is!
Don't hold back.
For real?
-Yes.
-Go ahead.
Here I go.
Ouch!
Must've hurt!
That was bad.
Are you alright?!
I'm fine.
Is it sore?
Alright, I'll go next.
Alright, let's try!
Hold on, can someone swap with me please?
-It's fine, just do it.
-Seriously?
Katsu.
Right?
It hurts when I sit.
It's really bad if he gets you in the thigh.
I'll go right around here, okay?
-The thigh...
-The thigh must hurt.
Hold on...
Oh no...
You just laughed.
He laughed.
He did?
Yes, Katsunori just laughed.
-He just let out the most casual chuckle ever!
-He sure did!
Yes, Katsunori just laughed.
-He just let out the most casual chuckle ever!
-He sure did!
It was so casual!
But why?!
No way!
He was so relaxed.
What a chuckle!
Right...
You just laughed as if we were on a break!
What are you doing?!
That gave me a shock.
There was nothing going on!
Yeah...
It was so sudden.
He was having so much fun for some reason.
I see, the whole atmosphere made him laugh?
I just have this desire to please people.
Can we have a look at the replay?
-Yes.
-Let's go.
Katsu, you're something else.
I'll go right around here, okay?
Ready?
Hold on...
He laughed!
They even startled him with the alarm!
Is this your third card?
Yes it is.
What?!
Katsunori Takahashi... Red card!
-The first one?!
-There it is!!
Damn it!!
Our first dropout.
Are you for real?!
See you guys.
-Thank you!
-Good work today!
I was super frustrated with myself.
What happened to you?
Well, first of all, there were no comedians this time around...
So the tempo was incredibly slow.
Not much was going on.
So, I wanted to play this russian roulette-inspired game.
...so I was desperate to do something.
I mean, I didn't know if they would find it funny.
But I just thought I had to be proactive.
They’re kissing.
And I just ended up laughing unintentionally.
All of them were unintentional.
All of them.
I'll turn you into minced meat!
"Now, I will ask all of you to kill each other"