Subbed by RAIDEN1017
This time the participating comedian knows who the other five participants are.
Usually, they do not know who the other contestants are.
Do the contestants change the jokes they prepare or their stance compared to when they don't know who is coming?
I don't think they change it.
I think they have to do what they want to do.
You lost weight.
I am still fatter than Arisa Mizuki.
Why are you comparing her to you?
You lost weight and became prettier.
If I were a contestant, I would think of a way to attack Zakoshi.
Do you want me to apologize!?
No.
IIIIIIIIIIIIIIII'M SOOOOOOOOOO
Exaggerated Desuyo.
RYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYY.
Cookie is so close!
This move is very funny.
I can't imagine Zakoshi laughing out loud at all.
I want to destroy the image people have of him
Documental - Season 10
Episode 2 “Therefor They are Strong”
That's just violence!
Are you okay?
Yuriyan!?
Oh, shit!
Are you okay?
Are you okay, Yuriyan?
Don't touch her boobs.
Yamamoto laughed.
Yamamoto laughed?
Yamamoto-san laughed.
Of course, it's a yellow card.
I understood.
- That was early.
- Yeah.
Yeah, it was very early.
Okay, I got really mad.
Yamamoto was under a lot of fire.
I felt sorry for him.
They may change their point of attack.
I will restart.
Excuse me, if you are not a pedophile, please prove it.
Do I have to do something again?
Are they going to attack Yamamoto again?
Prove it.
Please prove it.
Come here.
- He's like a fat Akira Nishikino.
- Indeed.
(Note: 1)
How do you like it?
I don't think anything of it.
How rude.
Again?
That's too much.
Don't do that!
You don't!
You have bloodshot eyes.
- What?
- Your eyes are bloodshot.
What's going on here?
It's as stiff as a rock dude!
You got an erection?
It's as stiff as a rock!
What's stiff as a rock?
His dick.
What's with the bruise?
My bruise has nothing to do with this.
What are you doing?
And you have an erection.
Your dick's as stiff as a rock!
What do you want?
You don't say that!
I feel sorry for Yuriyan.
Come here.
He's dangerous.
Don't touch her boobs.
I would've laughed at that.
It sounds like a beast.
I would definitely laugh.
Her nipples were stiff.
Really?
It was like a gravel stone in a shrine.
Don't touch her nipples.
I don't know if a junior like me is allowed to say this, but you should go to the bathroom with him.
I'll give you my condom.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
It's 7.34mm.
Kubota!
Isn't it thick?
It's very thick.
It's usually less than 1mm.
If you put it on, it will look like this.
7mm is very thick.
- Can I open it?
- Of course.
I've never seen anything like this.
It's as thick as squid skin, isn't it?
Squid skin!?
What the heck is this package?
It's gold.
This is a condom exclusively for Yamamoto-san.
Does it cover the balls too?
This has two separate tips.
It's like a two-headed snake.
Is his separated?
His must have two separate urethra.
It looks like a two-headed monster.
So why don't you guys do it in the bathroom?
That's what bathrooms are for, right?
- That's right.
- It's for having sex.
Also, it's for Watabe.
(Note: 2)
- Watabe?
Yuri-chan, who do you want to have sex with?
Which one shall I choose?
Yamamoto-san, please take your condom.
I ripped this.
Hey, this one ripped.
This isn't thick at all.
So you can make a baby with it.
This doesn't make me feel safe.
Sorry.
This is so weak.
Why did you bring this?
It doesn't matter.
The other day I found a 0.01mm condom in Yuriyan's bag.
(Note: 3)
That's why I brought mine.
- You have a condom, too, right?
- Yes.
- 0.01mm?
Do you like the thinner ones?
I really prefer 0.00 mm.
That's the same as not wearing anything.
Have you ever had sex?
- Yes, I have!
- No, you haven't!
- I have!
- Don't get excited.
I have!
0.00 mm...
Don't do tsukkomi at the right time because I would laugh.
Should I not do this?
Yeah.
It is not right to tell me not to do tsukkomi.
Everyone is a boke.
Then I'll do an exaggerated Boru-juku.
(Note: 4)
He's going to do it suddenly?
"Maaaneee."
(Kind of.)
That's different, though.
This is the normal one.
And this is the exaggerated Boru-juku.
Maanee Tigers?
Desane.
(Note: 5)
I wanted you to do it naked.
It would definitely be more funny that way.
If you were wearing clothes, it wouldn't be funny at all.
Really?
I'm going to go change.
You're zero fun when you're wearing clothes.
You're really not funny when you're wearing clothes.
Don't...
He laughed!
He definitely laughed.
Even though he attacked on his own.
He blew himself up.
He laughed at the accident.
It's an accident.
It's a rule of nature.
A rule of nature?
How weak I am. How weak I am...
It was an accident!
You all know who laughed.
- Coo-chan!
- Yes...
You smiled.
It was an accident...
Why did you laugh?
Why is that?
Because I heard that sound unexpectedly and laughed.
You were relaxed, like you were at home?
I laugh easily at unexpected things.
Yellow card.
Be careful of the unexpected.
Shisho, you make a lot of unexpected jokes.
You drop things suddenly.
When I do jokes normally, they don't laugh because they're so defensive.
That was very funny when the condom was on your hat.
- That was hilarious!
- That was insane!
It's tough.
Sorry, Yamamoto-san.
Here we go.
That's a lot of baggage.
I don't know whose luggage any of this is.
Let's clean it out.
Yes, let's do so.
Yuri-chan, I'm sorry I touched your boobs.
It made me happy.
- Huh?
- It made me happy.
Really? Then I'm glad.
- Seriously, yours were soft.
- Thank you.
Was mine soft?
It was firm.
Yuliyan's was firm, wasn't it?
She was wearing a bra and hers were small.
She forced me to touch her boobs.
Don't say to a woman that your boobs are small.
No, I was just answering her question.
- By the way, after the red light comes on, it's safe time, right?
- That guy's lighter is huge.
It's not good to apologize to someone at that time.
I don't think we should talk about that kind of backstage stuff.
You say that, too.
Don't call me you, call me Cookie.
Kawashima.
Don't call me by old name, Yamamoto.
So Yuriyan...
Don't point the finger at me.
Didn't you learn in school not to point fingers at people?
Don't apologize...
They want him out?
Because if you apologize...
Don't talk with a broom, you look like a monk.
Oh, monk.
Come to think of it, you tried to become a monk once, didn't you?
And you ran away from the temple in the middle of your training, right?
(Note: 6)
Something like that did happen.
Chairman Osaki was angry with you.
Was he angry?
President Okamoto too.
(Note: 7)
Hey, Yamamoto!
What's wrong?
How long are you going to keep sweeping?
He's under heavy fire.
Yamamoto, laugh two more times and get out of here.
What the fuck is this!?
Shouting much?
What's with this fucking vibe!?
Yamamoto-san, don't...
What a small hat!
How small.
Your head got bigger?
Is your hat small?
Or is your body bigger?
- My body is big.
- Really?
That's cute.
- It's small.
- huh?
- Really?
It is about this size.
- It is about this size.
- Huh?
- Really?
What's that hat for?
Where did you buy it?
Huh?
I know you heard him.
I don't have to answer that!
You shouldn't say that...
You don't have to answer that?
Okay, I'll answer.
I ordered this.
I see.
I thought this would make you laugh.
It was funny.
Would you all like something to drink?
Ah, drink.
I'm thirsty.
There were several kinds of that.
Soda, green tea, oolong tea, water, coffee.
I want a soda.
Apple juice, orange juice, and alcohol.
Oh, is there beer?
Is there alcohol?
And some eggs.
Are there eggs too?
Nobody wants this?
- Why don't you eat that?
- Okay.
Do you drink eggs?
You ate it in the shell.
Can you eat it in the shell?
Can you swallow it?
Swallow it.
The shell is sticking to my throat.
He can't eat raw food.
He can't eat any raw food!
Come on!
Are you okay?
Yuri-chan, did you see that?
Comedy is patience.
"Comedy is patience."
Orekara Manabe
(Learn it from me.)
Yes.
I'm Kaori Manabe.
(Note: 8)
Oh, nice!
She says any kind of nonsense, doesn't she?
Excuse me, can you hold these?
Please put these on my shoulders one by one.
I will crack them between my face and shoulder.
- I want to see it!
- Wait a second.
Please put them around here.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Your mole has hairs.
Everybody, come here.
Sorry, hold on a second.
Oh, two hairs grow here!
No, one hair has a branch growing out of it!
Ichi no eda?
(A branch?)
This is unusual.
Ichinoeda-san?
Are you Ichinoeda-san?
I'm not Ichinoeda.
- Ichinoeda?
Inazo Nitobe also has a hair here.
(Note: 9)
- Are you growing your hair?
- Yes.
Ichinoeda-san.
...Then, please put it here.
I can't look at your mole.
You can't?
So Kotouge do this.
How can I do that?
Every time you place it on my shoulder I will crack it.
We don't need three people for this.
Let's do it in a streamlined way.
I will help you.
Am I to place this here?
I want to crack them one by one.
Don't suddenly place them on the other side.
So if you place this here, I....
I know!!
What do I do with this?
Please hold this.
Coo is so close!
He was about to laugh now.
It fell out.
I'm done.
There are still some left.
You haven't cracked a single one.
You're weak today.
You didn't crack any of these.
Good Morning it's Sun.
(Note: 10)
Good evening.
Good evening, Ichinoeda-san.
Hi, I'm Ichinoeda.
Hello!
Good Morning it's Sun.
He's laughing.
You're a fool.
How foolish.
Don't laugh after egging yourself on.
It's a foolish thing to do.
You're bleeding.
Really?
It's okay.
You're bleeding.
I didn't mean to laugh.
I don't know, maybe I'm embarrassed.
That's why I smirked.
I'll watch the replay and judge.
I can't judge yet.
You just laughed.
You laughed.
You just laughed and bled.
You laughed and bled.
I was caught off guard.
- I was caught off guard.
- Yeah.
Because it's fun.
Yellow card.
Yeah, it's fun.
Be careful.
Good luck.
Thank you!
Don't show me that mole.
Why are there two hairs on it?
If I see that unexpectedly I would laugh at it.
What were you guys doing?
Here we go.
We were egging each other on.
Then Kotouge laughed.
I messed up!
I'm growing this hair.
I heard I shouldn't pull it out.
- I want to pull it out.
- Let's pull it out.
If you pull it out, I'll go crazy.
- What happens to you when I pull it out?
- I have never pulled it out.
I've been growing it.
This hair has been growing since I won M-1.
And I've got another one.
- After M-1?
- Yes.
Then this hair is Murata's.
(Note: 11)
- Give that to Murata.
- Who's that? I don’t know.
He's your buddy.
You look like him.
- You look so much like him.
- Yeah.
I'm not as fat as he is.
Please line up beside him.
He looks so much like him.
Don't get on the podium.
If you get on the podium, you won't be able to line up.
Why are you standing here?
You can stand in third place or first place, whichever you like.
Okay, first place.
They really look alike.
Yamamoto-san is fatter than Zakoshi-san.
You are too fat.
I don't like his fatness.
Can you do an exaggerated impression?
- What?
- Can you do an exaggerated impression?
- Of course.
- Do it.
Shall I do it first?
- Okay.
- Then I'll do it first.
First, show me your normal impression.
Zakoshi, show me a normal impression without exaggeration.
Okay, normal one.
Then, this is normal Zakiyama.
(Note: 12)
"Kuruuuu."
(Comiiiing.)
Then, try an exaggerated Zakiyama.
KUUUUUU
RUUUUUU
That's different.
Then show me the real one.
Real one?
How can they stand it without laughing?
Really so.
Are you Zakiyama-san?
That's nice, I want to try that too.
Go ahead.
Coo and Kubota.
They are close.
She stopped.
I found it.
Zakoshi is close too.
I dress differently than you.
Right.
But you are a woman.
I can't let you dress like this.
You can't do this.
You can't do it, Retriever.
Don't call her Retriever.
We call her Yuriyan.
Lien.
Don't say it like Shinsengumi.
(Note: 13)
Who remembers that?
I miss this.
Lien!
Don't say it like Shinsengumi.
Don't tsukkomi me.
You want to say "What the hell"?
"What the hell"
"Hello"
"We are..."
Hello!
We are Duo.
Nice to meet you.
Duo?
Is she all right?
We are Tokyo Hoteison.
Nice to meet you.
(Note: 14)
And, this is the exaggerated Tokyo Hoteison.
Kotouge!
What the hell.
What's a Kachan?
What's the exaggerated Kachan?
This is Kabuki.
(Note: 15)
What's a Kachan?
So what's a Kachan!?
This is Kabuki.
It will be an hour in a few minutes.
- You right!
- How fast!
You guys don't laugh easily.
Time goes by fast.
Because we're the winners.
Well, you guys are the winners, no doubt.
Then, I'll do the exaggerated mayor of Nagoya city.
(Note: 16)
Yuriyan is not here, but okay.
He bit the medal.
First, this is the normal mayor of Nagoya city.
Where did you get that out of?
It wasn't like that.
This is entirely different!
And this is the exaggerated mayor of Nagoya city.
Desaanee.
Go(su)!
(Note: 17)
He didn't bite the medal.
You burped.
He said "Go".
You burped at the end.
You burped.
This is not a burp.
You said "Go".
You ate the gold and burped.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
I'm wearing nothing but a shirt.
Really?
If you do that, we won't be able to stream this.
You're wearing nothing but a shirt?
That's terrible.
This is not shooting a porn video.
- Then just show it to us.
- Why don't you take a peek?
We have to decide if we can stream it or not.
So I'll take a peek.
What's he going to do?
- Then look at it.
- Okay.
If I turn up your clothes and see you naked, I will be criticized.
So please open your legs.
- I'll get on the skateboard and through between your legs.
- That's a nice idea!
Are you okay?
Can you do it?
Then I'll try it.
Okay, let's go!
Here we go.
How was it?
What the fuck are you doing?
I'm going back.
What did you see?
Wait a moment.
Yuriyan, you are...
You're a female comedian, right?
Yes...
Kotouge-san, you should see that too.
I won't know unless you explain it to me properly.
- What?
- What's going on?
Tuck in your head.
Ouch!
Ow!
Don't kick me with your toes!
Pull your head back a little more.
Don't move!
Yes...
- Take a good look at that.
- Yes.
And explain it to us.
Oops.
Oops!
Not good?
-What did you think?
-I think they can manage to stream this one.
I'm not sure either.
Do you guys think we can stream this?
I think we can do it.
Let me see it.
Yes.
I see.
This is how it looks inside!
I was still in the middle of changing.
I see.
She had something on her hip.
Please turn around.
Let me see.
What is this?
Yeah, I had no idea what this was.
I was in the middle of putting them on.
Is it beads?
You want gold in your anus, not in your mouth, right?
Did I look like I wanted to put gold in my anus?
What are you saying?
A gold...?
What is this?
What's that round thing?
Hey, hey, hey, come on.
Is that really in your anus?
- You've been putting gold in your anus?
- That's teribble.
It's a faucet.
- A faucet?
- Ah, I see.
It's a joke item.
I was surprised.
Don't be nervous about this.
Oh, I remember that one.
- what the hell does this remind you of
- He remembered something.
But I'm relieved.
I was nervous.
I was embarrassed too.
OH, YEAH.
I'll do an exaggerated Akira 100%.
(Note: 18)
"You guys are getting nervous, aren't you?"
OH, YEAH.
This is the worst.
She tied a string to it!
Why did you take off your hat?
CUT.
Then I'll do the surgery.
Excuse me, I'll do a simple surgery.
Are you sure?
I'll do a simple surgery.
Sorry.
Cool.
Nice.
This looks like a beetle larva.
Oh, good.
Oh, you look nice!
Do the one you just did again.
Again?
Hey, it's not here!
Not here!
Kubota, watch out!
Damn!
It's not here.
I blew myself up!
Damn it!
Even though you attacked me.
I was having too much fun.
I was having too much fun!
Oh, I shouldn't have done it.
How simple it is.
This happens all the time.
Kubota!
Yes, I laughed.
You attacked him yourself and you laughed.
I laughed at the simplest things.
Yeah.
Let's see the replay.
This is funny.
I'll give you the card this time.
Damn it!
I blew myself up!
Yellow card.
Damn it!
The cards began to be passed out to the group.
It hasn't been an hour yet.
Yeah.
Here we go.
I'll do this one, too.
Yasumura-kun.
This is the exaggerated Yasumura.
(Note: 19)
"Don't worry, I'm wearing this."
It's sticking out.
But my chimbou is sticking out.
(Note: 20)
I'm definitely worried.
Don't worry, I'm wearing this.
But my chimbou is sticking out.
That's not good enough.
Don't worry, I'm wearing this.
But my chimbou is sticking out.
Stop calling it chimbou.
My chimbou is sticking out.
Don't call it chimbo.
How many times is this guy going to say chimbou?
I wish that Zakoshishou-san's chimbou would come out more.
Chimbou!
Chinbou-kun?
Welcome to chimbou.
I AM CHIMBOU!
Interpret: He is Chimbou.
MY NAME IS CHIMBOU!
Interpret: His name is Chimbou.
Chimbou is very important to him.
CHIMBOU IS CHIMBOU!
Interpret: Chimbou is chimbou as you know.
CHIMBOU
OH YEAH CHIMBOU!
Interpret: Chimbou is always watching over Africa from his underwear.
CHIMBOU, OH, CHIMBOU!
Interpret: Chimbou is to me as chimbou is to your hearts.
BOUCHIN CHIMBOU.
Interpret: Bouchin and chimbou are the same.
&%*%^@#*%^&@.....
Interpret: And for you...
Interpret: In the end, it is Chimbou and piss.
What do you mean?
In the end, it's chimbou and piss in your heart.
In other words, it's a chimbou.
In other words...?
It's a Chimbo Chokan.
(Chimbo Secretary)
Chimbo Chokan?
It's like a Kombo Chokan?
(Cabinet Secretary)
Chimbocho!
It's Jimbocho, right?
(Note: 21)
Is this about Jimbocho?
Chimbocho seems to mean Jimbocho.
Chimbocho!
What?
What the hell is this!?
Moon Crystal Power!
(Note: 22)
- Chimbo Ninja!
- What the hell!
Kotouge!
What are these guys doing?
That's insane.
Chimbou Ninja.
Chimbou Ninjas are coming through.
Chimbou Chimbou Chimbou Ninja
Chimbou Ninja.
- Chimbou Ninjas are coming through.
- Chimbou Ninja, Chimbou Ninja.
If they touch him, he might become a Chimbou Ninja.
Chimbou Ninjas are coming through.
He didn't become it.
Why didn't you become it?
Are you okay?
He hit his own eye.
Aren't you out?
He overshot it.
Are you okay?
Kotouge is so close!
Why aren't they laughing?
This hit me in the eye.
你好(Hello.)
I'm from China.
China is advanced in science.
Especially, the research of cloning is very advanced.
All the best people are being cloned.
Clones of you were also made.
I'm scared!
I will give you this document.
Let's look your clones together with me.
Then follow my instructions and look at them.
That's so...
- They will be afraid to look at this.
- Yeah.
I'm sure you all would be happy to have your own clones made.
In other words, you guys are excellent.
If you are not excellent, your clone will not be made.
Rright.
It's amazing that they have already made clones of you guys.
Let's look at the first one.
Who is it?
It's Yuriyan Retriever.
- This is me.
- Oh, Yuriyan.
This is an earlier photo.
- An earlier photo?
- Yes.
Your clone has already been made.
- It looks a little different. But it's your clone.
Your DNA is very important.
- This is scary!
Yes, this is very scary!
Now look at the next page.
This is almost me.
But...
Yes.
This is a very excellent clone.
What can this clone do?
She is just breathing now.
What the hell!
I really want to say "What the hell".
Can't this one speak?
- Then let's look at the next page.
- What the hell!
It's very funny, though.
- It's Zakoshisho.
- It's me.
You're very good.
- That's why your clone was made.
- Really?
- You are the L-1 winner?
- R-1.
(Note: 23)
- And Decumental?
- Documental.
- You won it twice.
- You are very good.
- Yes.
That's why your clone was made.
- The Chinese all want a clone of you.
- Really?
Let's take a look.
You became a comedy duo.
This is Arapon.
(Note: 24)
Who is it?
It's Arapon.
Now turn the document sideways.
He already exists!
Turn it sideways.
Look at the next page.
It's Toro Salmon.
As you all know, they are the winners of M-1.
They're very good, too.
(Note: 25)
Of course, their clones were also made.
Turn to the next page slowly.
First, it's Kubota-san.
This is your clone.
Who is this?
He looks like he could be somewhere.
He is very good.
This is a failure, isn't it?
No.
This is a failure.
This is weird.
His mouse looks like it's higher up.
Look next to him.
He looks like someone.
His face is very long.
I've seen this one before.
Me too.
Let's look at this zoomed in picture on this page again
Let's look at this zoomed in picture.
- Isn't he the comedian we often refer to as "I’m so frustrated"?
- What?
- Ah, it's Kato.
(Note: 26)
It looks like Kato.
Then let's look at the next page.
- Oh, Kotouge-san.
- It's Viking.
- They're very good, too.
- Are you the King of Conte winner?
- Yes.
- You are very good.
(Note: 27)
- Your buddy is Nishimura?
- Yes.
That's why your clones were made.
They are very good clones in China.
They are both excellent.
Now let's look at the clones.
It's scary.
They looks like they could be somewhere.
His head is long.
It's disgusting.
Kotouge's head is shaped like rice.
They look like Akina.
He has a very long head.
(Note: 28)
His eyes are kind of far apart, which is weird.
I've seen them before.
- Yeah, I've seen him before.
- They look like they could be somewhere.
They look like Akina.
Yeah.
Let's look at this zoomed in picture on this page again
They are Akina.
Their faces are totally different from the originals, but there are more distinctive differences.
Look at Kotouge's ears.
How small!
It's like a cork.
Nishimura's are small too, but his are even smaller!
His ears are too small.
His right ear has a pointed tip.
It's like a hook.
This is Chinese cloning technology.
Yamamoto is next.
Let's take a look at Yamamoto's clone.
What kind of clone did they make of him?
Then let's take a look.
It says something.
They haven't made his clone?
"Keiichi Yamamoto - His clone does not exist."
"Keiichi Yamamoto was not worthy of cloning after careful investigation.  It was determined that posterity does not need his DNA."
"Therefore, the cloning of Keiichi Yamamoto and the sale of meat wrapped rice balls are strictly prohibited."
Unfortunately, you are not good enough, so your clone will not be made.
Sorry.
It's okay.
If you want to resume selling meat wrapped rice balls, please apologize seriously to Kin-chan.
(Note: 29)
I see.
Thank you.
- Do you have a minute?
- Sure.
Where did you go this summer?
- I didn't go.
- Me too.
- I didn't go anywhere either. But I wanted to do something.
- What?
- Please sit here.
- Me?
- Yes.
I like to collect beetles and stag beetles.
So I want to...Excuse me.
It's honey.
Please be patient a little.
It's alright?
This is a beetle!
- Are you serious?
- So big!
- This isn't ordinary beetle, is it?
-  Is it alright?
- So big!
- It's beetle?
Is it beetle?
- That's terible.
- It has three horns.
- Are you sure that it's safe?"
- Yes.
- Is this a Hercules beetle?
- Yeah, it's a pretty good one.
(Note: 30)
Is it alright?
- I want to see these sucking honey!
- You wanna see it!?
I'm scared!
Excuse me.
Is it okay?
Ouch!
Ow!
Oh, it's great!
Its feet are digging into my scalp.
Ow-ow-ow-ow...!
- Shall I make a video?
- Please.
Ouch!
Ow!
These feet...
- These are sucking it!
- Really!?
These are sucking the honey.
This is an amazing scene.
You stink.
Ouch its...its feet are digging into my scalp!
Watch out!
- What's wrong, Cookie?
- Cookie-san is close.
Ouch!!
Don't make loud noises!
Because the beetles will be startled.
Ow-ow-ow-ow...
Don't move, I'm shooting a video now!
They are sucking honey!
Ow-ow-ow-ow...
I will take one off.
Sorry.
Is this a female?
Ow-ow-ow-ow!!
Beetles are scraping his scalp.
That's insane.
This thing is really hungry for honey.
It has big nails.
Hey! It's eating your hair follicles!
Eating my hair follicles!?
Is it serious!?
My hair follicles...!
That's enough.
It's okay!
- Sorry, Kotouge-san.
- Don't worry. This will be a good memory.
Those things were very honey sucking.
That was great.
Really?
I could really feel it digging into my scalp
This is the first time an insect has appeared in this room.
That was great.
Hey.
Can I do "body impression" of Akiyama-kun?
(Note: 31)
Yes.
It's you.
Hey, he's taking the piss.
Piss?
Ah.
This is an icicle.
Are you cold?
It's been cold lately, right?
That's why the icicle got stuck in my urethra.
Are you saying that an icicle fell down and got in there?
It's not your frozen piss, right?
The icicle had a "hole-in-one" here.
It's so cold.
I'm hot, though.
Yuriyan, touch it.
May I touch it?
I found it!
Wait a second!
What's this duo?
Oh, it's out!
He made it so that this will pull out of this.
What happened?
Oh, it's cold
It's cold
Why isn't everybody laughing?
It's cold.
What are these guys doing all the time?
I'm embarrassing!
Why?
Because I'm not wearing pants.
Then put something on.
Yamamoto-san, come here.
Please fan yourself.
You are my senior.
You can fan harder.
What's wrong, Yuri-chan?
What are you doing?
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
A little.
You are certainly not disgraceful.
You are kneeling on the gloor desperately fanning yourself to see your junior's panties.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
You are naked and kneeling on the floor.
And you're fanning.
So cute.
Who are you?
Can't you talk?
You can't talk?
He closed with his elbow
Huh?
Did he just laugh?
He turned around so I couldn't see him.
Yamamoto-san, fan her butt.
- Yuri-chan, is that okay?
- Yes.
Please do it.
What's this?
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
You were going slowly, rubbing your feet on the floor.
You are pathetic.
Don't fan your armpits with someone's fan.
This is a fish head.
"Gyo Gyo Gyo! It's Sakana-kun!"
(Note: 32)
This stinks.
"It's Sakana-kun! Gyo Gyo Gyo!"
It's disgusting!
Gyo Gyo Gyo!
Let me eat some puffer fish poison!
Poison! Poison!
This guy is scary.
"It's Sakana-kun! Gyo Gyo Gyo!"
"Gyo Gyo Gyo!"
This is real tuna skin.
Yeah.
I absolutely hate this kind of thing.
The reverse side is absolutely gross.
It stinks!
So gross!
And it stinks!
This smells like your armpits, not fish!
My armpits stink?
Your armpits stink.
How could you wear that?
Why go to all that trouble just to make us laugh?
Everyone does it.
It stinks!
God... that smell!
It stinks around here!
It stinks!
I'm confident of....
This is what I was confident about.
Don't you wonder how these guys hear the sound?
I wanted you to flip it like this.
"Wow, what a disgusting face, and such small ears!"
"What small ears!"
"Hey, what's with the ears!?"
Didn't you think so?
Look at his ears.
This looks like pig's intestines.
Why does he keep looking at Coo?
Oh, it's Tiger Mask.
(Note: 33)
Hello.
"Liger-kun and all my fans in Fukuoka,"
"Please wait a little longer until I feel better."
This is the impression of Satoru Sayama during an exhibition match in Fukuoka Dome.
(Note: 34)
"Liger-kun and all my fans in Fukuoka,
Please wait a little longer until I feel better."
I don't know that.
He said that?
Do you just repeat it?
Do you want to repeat that?
Liger-kun
Please wait a little longer
Please wait a little longer....
What?
Please wait a little longer.
Huh!?
He showed his face.
No wonder he is angry.
"Don’t mess with me."
"Don’t mess with me, hey."
Don't take my mask off!
"Don’t mess with me!"
"I'll kill you!"
- I am Satoru Sayama of Shooting gym.
- I miss it.
(Note: 35)
"Don’t mess with me!"
I almost forgot about that.
Cookie is so close!
"Don’t mess with me!"
I'm about to laugh because I watched it on TV.
"Hey, kick me here."
Why?
Kick here.
"Don’t mess with me!"
"Is that your best kick?"
"I'll kill you!"
Watch out!
"Don’t mess with me!"
"Hey, don’t mess with me!"
"I'll kill you!"
Did he do this?
"Please wait a little longer"
He didn't do this.
"Liger-kun and all my fans in Fukuoka."
How many times are you going to do the same thing?
"Please wait a little longer until I feel better."
He wouldn't say that.
"Don’t mess with me!"
He endured.
What?
What's wrong?
She keeps looking at me.
What is this?
What's this?
Kotouge, what is that?
This is...
The pig's blood.
I feel sorry.
Tasty?
Yes.
It tastes like livestock.
Taste of being tamed?
It's black magic.
It really smells like blood.
- It's pig's blood.
- Really?
Look, someone's here because you drank pig's blood.
Oh, Koumedayu?
(Note: 36)
He is identical to him.
Did Coo laugh?
How about it?
- Did he laugh?
- He might have.
I don't like the sound of that.
- I hate "Chan."
- It's a high-pitched sound.
Kotouge.
Don't do that.
Why'd you stop for a bit?
I hate that sound.
I thought it was the numeral one.
He sounds like him.
But it was a chimbou.
Chimboooooou!!
That's enough.
When you say it, it's over.
Enough with the chimbou.
It's over.
Somebody pull my chimbou out!
Hey, chimbou.
His voice sounds very similar to Koumedayu.
You wanna be a woman?
Don't say "chan."
He always hits him.
Why would he hit him?
How long can you endure getting hitted?
It hurts, right?
It doesn't hurt that much, does it?
It's no big deal.
I going hit you harder little by little so tell me when you reach your limit.
You want to know the limit of this, don't you?
Yes, I want to know.
Okay, I'll start off gently.
The first hit is about this much.
How about this?
It doesn't hurt at all.
Next.
How about this?
This doesn't hurt either.
Next.
Did that hurt?
How many times did he get hit today?
It hurt more the third hit than the second hit.
Then...
A big one.
Cookie is so close.
Can I do it with this?
won’t it hurt if you hit him with that?
It's scary
This is quite dangerous.
What if he bleeds out?
You shouldn't do that, it's scary.
I know it's dangerous.
This is hard.
Wait a second.
Are you massaging your scalp?
I don't want you to bleed.
- Yeah.
- Let's not do that.
You massaging your scalp won't help.
Are you guys underground fighters?
Why do you want to be hit so badly?
You said you'd do it, so do it.
Are you all right?
I'm worried.
Because you are my favorite senior.
Your favorite senior?
If you insist, shall we do it?
How about you hit him after you hit me and Zakoshi-san?
Like one, two, three.
Yeah.
You hit us to build up momentum.
Here we go.
If you think it is dangerous, please stop.
You can't stop after you do it.
This is dangerous.
See?
How hard should I hit you the first hit?
This was quite painful.
What's wrong?
I want to do it!
Huh?
Stop it, you're a woman.
You can't.
Yeah. you can't.
What?
I don't think you can.
Why?
Why not!?
(Why can't I do it?)
What did she say?
What are you doing?
It doesn't hurt that much, does it?
Nice.
Nice!
This is never going to end.
Please, stop fighting.
Please.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
How many times did he get hit?
He's been smacked in the head all day.
You want us to see the video?
- Yeah.
- I'd like to show you a video too.
It started.
Everyone be careful.
Do you want to play a game?
Yeah!
- Then control it with your telekinesis.
- Yes.
Here we go.
Let's go.
Get the coin.
(Note: 37)
Jump.
Let's go.
He bumped his head repeatedly.
You are not good at it.
You must suck at telekinesis.
Let's go.
Get the coin.
Jump.
Jump!
- It's the star!
- Get the star.
It's a star with Yoshimoto's mark on it!
Let's get it.
He has no jumping ability.
That looks like it hurts.
Control it properly.
Here we go.
Control it!
Of course.
I'm controlling it properly.
Jump!
Let's step back!
Let's step back and get the star.
Got it!
- It will get a little faster.
- And he got a little younger?
- Let’s go.
It's golden.
Shit.
It was too fast.
You have to control it.
His neck was twisted.
Here we go.
Jump!
Okay.
Jump here.
You did it before.
You can do it.
You can do it!
He barely made it!
Hang on!
Something's coming!
It's Hyoudo-san!
(Note: 38)
Hyodo-san?
Oh, his hat got caught.
Only the hat is left.
Here we go.
Please control it properly!
Get it!
Okay.
Wait for a moment.
It's coming!
Let's cross!
- He was sent flying.
- Did he survive?
He is bald.
Is it serious!?
No one is laughing.
The next is the last.
Here we go!
Please get it!
Ah, you're lucky.
Please get on this.
This should move forward!
Oh, you are lucky!
Let's move forward!
He's so bald.
This is a hat factory.
Hat factory?
Oh, cute!
I see.
- He died.
- Who?
Who died?
Daisuke.
Daisuke died?
Why?
Where did he die?
- Did he die in the back?
- What happened to him?
I make a lot of images.
Those are made by my telekinesis.
Really?
Now I'm going to show one picture here.
I'm going to transform it with my telekinesis.
I want you to see it.
Let's start.
I will use my telekinesis.
I make Daisuke's face small.
Oh, it's smaller.
So small.
I will turn him back to normal!
Yes, he is back to normal!
He's not back.
I'll do Hanako next.
You do it to Hanako too?
Daisuke is back to normal, so I'll do Hanako next.
No, no, no,
What's normal about this?
Then I'll do it for Hanako.
Come on, Hanako!
I'll make Hanako's face smaller!
This is tremendous telekinesis.
All right, become small! Become small!
Look at Daisuke sometimes.
Become small!
Yes, I will turn her back to normal!
I will turn her back to normal!
Hold on!
Plese hold on!
Maybe my telekinesis is not strong enough!
Hanako is very powerful!
Is Hanako powerful?
Get back to normal, Hanako!
Look at Daisuke from time to time.
Come on!
Hanako is out of control!
Oh my God!
I'm sorry!
She is going to eat Daisuke!
Daisuke, fight!
Go, Daisuke!
Do they fight with their heads?
Go! Daisuke, go!
Beat her!
Daisuke has absorbed Hanako.
This is paint.
It's as if this is a married couple.
This is what a married couple is.
There's something weird about his body.
They are a good couple.
They are a cute couple.
What are we being shown?
He's too small.
They are a good couple.
Look at his shoulders!
How cute.
He’s a whole different person.
- Ah, they are a good couple.
Right: I believe that aliens exist...
Left: I believe there are UFOs...
Look at his shoulders.
And Hanako next to him.
Hanako is mad.
Ah, this is them normally.
This is them normally,
It's so big!
His hand was swollen!
Coo just laughed.
He laughed.
Coo was laughing while showing it.
Who?
I didn't laugh.
Maybe you laughed?
Maybe you were laughing.
Earlier you were grinning.
It's not me.
I think he was laughing.
Who?
Coo-chan.
He was laughing afterwards.
You were laughing too much for the aftermath of an accomplishment.
Let's watch the replay.
He had been grinning for quite a while.
His smile was wonderful.
Orange card.
Watch out.
You did your best, though.
Someone will be in this room soon.
Someone will come.
I looked at the big hands and laughed.
What kind of punchline is a hand getting bigger?
You know best how hilarious your jokes are.
Subbed by RAIDEN1017