Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!
I'm Kataoka Ainosuke (Editor's Note 1)
Okay, so today... um...
We're doing "Documental"...
I kind of want Norika to see... (EN: 2)
something quite interesting.
Okay. Sorry, that was too simple.
No, that was a great impersonation.
I haven't had much chance to practice,
so just leaving one or two impressions,
would make me happy.
There it is, there it is.
It went that way, sorry.
A last one, a last one. Sorry.
Everyone is doing their best with gags.
I don't think there are any comedians
that don't do gags one way or another.
Because they have a keen eye different from other people,
and can tell what's funny and what isn't.
I didn't have any intention
to play the straight man.
A grandma's is more like this...
See?
And an electric one is more like that.
So he's out?
You're out!
This is Wangan!
Wangan! Wangan!
Alright! He did it!
Matsuo, you're out!
Here we go.
I'll do it with my phone.
— How?
— Just connect it.
Do we have any coffee?
I want some coffee.
How do you make coffee?
Coffee? You do it here, like...
You come here and—
Someone's...
Someone's here!
Excuse me, I am Shireman Peter
from Yoshimoto Entertainment.
And he is a fellow employee.
I'm Jaratiyaka Virendla
from Yoshimoto Entertainment.
— Who are they?
— So you're...
...the guys from the contract, right?
— That's right.
— Seiji-san?
— A contract?
— Here and now?
They had foreigners like that?
Is everything okay?
What's your position?
I'm in the sports department at the moment.
— Sports?
— This is none of our business.
We're employees.
From the Corporate's Main Branch.
The Sports Department is here to sign a contract?
— That's right.
— Seiji-san?
— We're doing it for Seiji-san.
— Why?
Seiji-san, are you signing a sports contract?
No clue. We didn't talk things through the other day.
About the contract.
You should've gotten that done with.
Then why don't you guys do it with me?
We're not doing sports!
But in the end it's the same, right?
Sports and comedy.
Please take a look if you're participating.
But when I did this before,
they told me to take it with me, and so...
I had a particular condition, that I wouldn't look at stuff that arrived while at work,
if I had to split earnings.
So that's...
...why are you people speaking English now?!
No splitting is crazy, man.
That's insane, Seiji.
That's completely impossible.
What are they saying?
I'm making life changing decisions,
so please don't speak in a language I can't understand!
We're sorry...
— They don't get this!
— Seiji, Seiji, Seiji...
Don't say that.
Seiji is smiling for sure, though!
Can't you speak in English about that over there?
We can't speak Japanese right now, so...
Why?
It's easier for us in English.
Why?! Why?!
What's the deal with that?
We're very sorry, but with our current skill level,
we can't speak much more than that.
They could be talking behind your back, you know?
Is it a serious contract?
It's serious, yeah.
Yeah, that's why I'm so confused with these two,
when it's such a serious matter.
Maybe they're just underestimating you a little,
Seiji. I think that's it.
I think so as well.
They're definitely looking down on you.
He's smiling.
He's smiling for sure.
They're definitely looking down on me with this.
We think it would be necessary to negotiate.
But you see, this just doesn't...
We can't do this with a guy like this.
He looks like Yamamoto Tarou. (EN: 3)
This can be trouble later, though.
Trouble...?
When I'm signing a contract that will change my life,
this is just no good.
Besides, I'm signing a contract
with Yoshimoto in the middle of "Documental".
That's one big forehead, huh?
For real.
This isn't going to work out without some English.
Tell him.
I am very sorry. This is very important,
and we know you're busy right now.
We're not even having a conversation like this.
Just sign it.
Now that these two came here like this,
it's just like Fujimon was saying.
I know you're in the same generation, but...
...they're looking down on you.
Not at all.
That's why I had you take a picture,
when guys like these show up, right?
We're signing a contract...
...with an attitude like this?
This isn't even a conversation anymore.
Take this and please leave.
Sorry. It's just...
I'm sorry.
Let's do it again. Again.
No, twice more.
Two more.
— Sorry.
— We're very sorry.
Let's meet next time.
— Good job.
— I feel sorry for them.
— That was hard.
— Come on, man, that was just...
It was hard.
Let's just have them leave.
I guess a lot happened, huh?
Peter.
Bananas are great.
Love stories.
Again?
— Love story?
— Me?
I got a girlfriend recently,
so yesterday we went out to pick strawberries.
And I was very nervous.
I was thinking about today all the time.
I was just thinking about Seiji-san's contract,
and I didn't pay any attention.
So my girlfriend got a little upset.
I'm very sorry.
She's still angry?
I just couldn't get Seiji-san out of my head.
I couldn't even think about my girlfriend.
I didn't care about the strawberries.
If you say that...
It's all Seiji-san's fault.
Even if you say that, it's not my fault.
But now I think I brought someone bad luck.
But he couldn't concentrate on picking strawberries.
A story you remember well.
That's difficult...
You can do it in Japanese.
Yeah, Japanese is fine.
A story that I remember well...
Back when I had hair,
I was a newscaster on TV.
— Amazing.
— On a national network.
You were a newscaster?
Where?
Sri Lanka, my home country.
Sri Lanka?
You were a newscaster back home?
I see!
I think that's enough.
Sorry, it's just...
Good job!
You were here a long time.
That was long.
Just look at the contract, man!
Everything about the contract was Seiji's fault.
I can't do that under conditions like that!
Of course you can!
What are you doing?
Wanna do the Yoshimoto Quiz Lumine?
You were talking about that for a while, huh?
He has wanted to do it for a while.
What's the Yoshimoto Quiz Lumine?
Just do the Yoshimoto Quiz Lumine once,
together with us.
— Just once.
— Can you get it right?
I think I've maxed out my skills recently.
No way, that's amazing!
And so, having done that,
it might be a bit unfair.
I mean, that's what I think, I guess.
So I'd like you to play the best three.
That's from Fujita's perspective?
What should we guess correctly?
— First place.
— That's someone's name.
So we just have to guess the best three.
The question is, um...
Who's the most likely to go home immediately,
after the show is over. That's the ranking.
Ah, I get it now.
There are some people like that, right?
A ranking of who goes home first?
So someone who looks like they'd run off immediately?
I don't think there's anyone exactly like that, but...
— Let's do this already!
— There are no absolutes, okay?
Third place!
— A quiz already?
— Come on already!
So who's in third place?
No, no, let's start from first place. (EN: 4)
— Show it on the count of three!
— Three, two...
We just have to guess who the hell is in first place.
But we can't do this if we don't catch your drift in the first place!
Like, what happens when you say "this is first place"?
I open the first place.
— That's no fun!
— It's fun!
You should just count down from three!
That doesn't matter, just get it right!
We can't predict or adjust for trends!
You can if you guess second place!
In any case just show us third place!
— Come on already!
— Why third place?
Just do this already.
— Just get it right!
— Do third place already!
— Then get it damned right!
— Show it to us!
That's Maeda-san from the hurricanes.
Maeda-san from the hurricanes?
We have time, so show us third place.
Open third place already!
I have to do it for you?!
Show us third place!
Past Tsutsumishita.
So... So...
— "Past"?
— That's the name of his act?
That's why I told you to show us, we can't pick up any patterns.
Any others have additional stuff like that?
They all have things added to them?
No, not at all. None of the others.
— I'm sure they do!
— For real?
The others don't have anything.
Show us second place!
What if they do have additional stuff?
Nothing additional.
I told you, didn't I?
So I'm sure first place must be...
I get it.
This isn't like I imagined at all.
It's not fun at all.
Then we should do it like you had in mind.
I tried but you forced me to show you.
Cover them up and let's go again.
Show them to us, cover them.
I had a lot more excitement in mind.
I wanted to do a simulation like that.
We're sorry!
Alright, then!
Having maxed out my Lumine skills...
— This again?
— This goes after that, okay?
Third place is Past Tsutsumishita.
It's a "who goes home first" ranking,
So just get ready, and...
Wait a second, and answer.
I think third place is Past Tsutsumishita.
— So what is it?
— You think so?
— I do.
— Alright, let's take a look.
I'm going to be using Futtonda's system for this. (EN: 5)
I don't really get Futtonda.
Sliding like...
So like a futon?
Correct!
— One point.
— Amazing!
No way, yeah.
Shall we do this?
Second place is...
What do you think?
— Well...
— You want a hint?
No... I think it's Non Style's Inoue.
— That's close!
— I'm wrong?
That's close!
— No way, no way, no way!
— Way, way, way!
That's a shame!
Look, look!
That said Inoue!
— I saw it!
— Inoue Ma!
— No way, no way, no way!
— Way, way, way!
I think I see Inoue. but not the "Ma".
Yeah, you're right.
Ma Inoue isn't written there.
— Is this fun?
— No, Fujimoto-san.
— Is this what you wanted to do?
At least let us get to first place!
Please just give us first place.
That's Inoue, of course.
Inoue? What Inoue?
The deputy chief, general manager!
Correct!
Is this meant to be fun?
— Okay, first place.
— Is this meant to be fun?
— I think everyone agrees...
We're all trying to get hyped up for you.
First place, first place.
Someone who goes home like...
We got this far, let's see first place.
I guess first place really is...
So first place goes home for real so...
I guess Haranishi is pretty quick.
He's super quick in going home.
And he doesn't have an excuse?
— None at all.
— There's also Reiji.
He's quick, yeah.
He leaves quick even when working, since he's driving.
— I wonder about that.
— Maeda from Hurricanes?
Who are you trying to hide?
— That was just Reiji-san.
— Why did you do that all of a sudden?
— Reiji-san.
— Reiji-san?
Not Haranishi?
Koba-san said Reiji-san and you started moving that.
Okay, so who is it then?
Which one is Fujimon trying to ignore?
Fujimon is ignoring...
Just figure out which one you're going with.
He was moving it when
he went all "that's close!".
I just wanted to do it when you were close.
You're talking about that movement?
So which one was closer?
Fujimoto-san.
— Huh?
— He was closer.
See? It was Fujimon.
Maybe I was right.
Just say it clearly then.
Haranishi from Fujiwara.
Alright...!
— Way, way, way, way!
— No way, no way, no way!
Correct!
— Got it!
— It's correct!
Congratulations!
Fujimoto-san gets the first place!
Okay, so next question.
That's enough.
— The question is—
— I said enough!
Let's go.
It was incredibly quick.
Especially Haranishi-san.
Haranishio, yeah.
Who's calling him "Haranishio" anyways?
So what's next?
— So Haranishi-san is...
— Now I see a trend.
I guess you could call it a trend.
At least Haranishi-san definitely is one to leave really early.
He is.
So after seeing him,
and how fast he leaves,
Murakami Shouji-san said something in particular.
That's the quiz?!
Tell us already!
We may just be starting, but still tell us everything.
"Is Haranishi there?" or something like that?
— Yeah.
— A single thing?
"So that guy left already?"
What's next? (EN: 6)
He's gone?!
"Haranishi went home already"
"Ben! Ben!" and then.
"Ben! Is Ben there?!"
No one's gonna understand that.
He doesn't call Ben Yamagata like that anyways.
— And his disciple,
— When he's in the unicycle.
Like the comedian that lived in Bangkok.
Right, right.
He doesn't call Ben Yamagata like that.
— They're wings.
— You can't understand that!
— Ben!
— Ben is right here.
— He's not here anymore.
— Ben's not here.
He's not here?
Is Ben here, though?
"He's not here?
Is Ben here, though?"
No, I think it goes more like "He's this and that, after all".
— Sort of like a metaphor, right?
— He says that a lot.
That's a good one. Ready?
Yeah, pretty much.
Are we going to understand the metaphor though?
Well, let's see.
We probably understand it,
but I think it's geared towards older folks.
So it's something older people would come up with.
He's a jet...
A jumbo jet?
He's just like a falcon?
— He's just like Carl Lewis!
— No.
An NSR with a limiter cut on its chamber?
Say what?
Or an RZ350 with Nanahan Hunter.
Shouji-san would never say anything like that.
By the way, I'll give you another hint.
It's not about speed.
— Got it.
— It's about disappearing.
Vanishing?
That's good, that's good!
Kobayashi-san.
Fujimoto-san. Got it?
He's vanishing.
Is he Wakaooji-san?
He just vanished.
That's Wakaooji-san from Mitsubishi.
His finger looks like this.
But in Manila in the Philippines, it turned out he had it all along.
Okay, okay, okay, okay!
It's time?!
— It's not time.
— Something about a chameleon?
Since they disappear.
That has to be it! There's nothing else.
It's just not there...
That's the only possible answer.
Alright, let's do another round.
Two more tries then.
Aren't you too hopeless already?
I don't know anymore.
Something with Kamaitachi?
— That's enough.
— Yeah, that's enough.
Something about a phoenix?
— No.
— Tezuka Osamu?
Tezuka Osamu?
Fujimoto-san already said two.
One more.
— Something about Nessie?
— No.
— The Tsuchinoko?
— Not the Tsuchinoko either.
Maybe it wasn't Haranishi to begin with.
No, that's not it. You used your second one.
— Bigfoot?
— A unicorn?
Not a unicorn or bigfoot. One more.
That's all I have.
A giraffe written with its difficult kanji?
— It's over, it's over.
— We all said two options.
We all said two options.
I'll show you the correct one.
He's gone?
He's just like a dying cat.
No one thought about it even for a second?
Shouji-san...
That's just...
Alright, one more.
That's enough. Enough already!
— Yeah, that's fine.
— Please make one more.
Stop it, you liar!
— Please one more.
— That's enough.
We haven't even tried for a hundredth time.
That's enough!
Want to play Karuta?
Come on, I have a game, too.
— Want to play?
— Sure.
Let's do it.
Though it's an easy game.
I'm getting kinda hungry.
Yeah, me too.
Wanna eat some ramen?
I want to order something.
Let's order some sushi.
— Not sushi.
— Why?
We have Getty!
Let's get a pizza for everyone.
A pizza, huh?
You know how to play the Harmonica?
You put it here over your folk guitar, right?
You put the harmonica in your mouth and we'll hit you.
That's too much.
You lose if it makes a sound.
It's going to make a sound for sure.
What are we going to hit them with?
Anything's fine, really.
You have some wood logs?
Who's the strongest?
— This is good!
— It's gonna hurt.
What are you going to do?
With this?
This is bad!
That's definitely gonna hurt!
And yet you're going first?
— Why me?
— It's just fair!
As a sample!
Okay, get the chair ready.
I'm gonna do it.
Are we all going to do it?
Just wipe it with the sanitizer!
Can you stop it, Fujimon?
Why?
Because Fujimon is always the most...
This is kinda nasty.
He's the cleanest.
I'm the cleanest.
Not really.
Just wipe it.
Anyone has a tissue?
A wet tissue?
I can get one.
I hate this.
He's a beauty.
He just smells so good.
Ah, you noticed earlier when you kissed?
Let's do this, let's do this.
— For real.
Okay, Seiji.
And he's so damned soft.
— Damned virgin.
— For real.
— What are you doing?
Drop it, man!
So who's going to do it?
— I'll do it.
— No, no, no...
Are you hitting...?
Just how bad are you going to do it?
I just need you to remember the rules.
I'm going to do it like this.
Isn't that too much?
That hurts.
That's gonna hurt a lot.
So he can't match the sound?
— No, no, he can't make any sound.
— If he does, he loses.
So put this in his mouth.
— He's pale!
Too pale!
Pretty neat.
Let's go!
No, this is gonna hurt!
Do it around here.
That's gonna hurt for sure.
Just let me... think this through.
In your mouth, in your mouth.
And hands behind your back.
So that's how it is?
That's how it is?
— I can't drop it either?
— Feeling the pressure?
Let's do this.
No, no, come on.
This is torture.
Let's go.
— He held it.
— Too soft.
Do it a little more.
No, no, no, no.
Are you stupid?
If you do that I'm going to make a sound of course!
Sorry.
That looked like it hurt.
Ouch.
Sorry, I missed.
He didn't have it in his mouth?
Sorry.
Seiji, are you going to put it in your mouth?
It's not fun otherwise.
Sorry.
I think we have to look at an example.
— I don't get it.
— Let's do it once.
The inventor!
Let's do this for once!
Okay, wait.
You can't do it no matter what.
No matter how many times.
Do it with strength, for real.
Kind of the same as with Seiji earlier?
That's pretty bad.
Of course, like my second time.
Yeah, like the second time.
Wait a second.
Around here.
Here I go.
— I heard that.
— For sure.
— He's not holding it.
— He's making a lot of noise.
— A lot.
— The second time is impossible.
You were doing it since the first time, though.
You made a sound.
I feel like Seiji might've smiled.
Come on, Seiji.
— That looked painful.
— It hurt like hell.
It hurts like shit.
Why don't we do that?
Let's do rock, paper, scissors, and decide the order
from the winner to the loser.
Ah, I get it.
We're the last ones anyways, right?
Okay, wait, wait a second.
Okay. I have a suggestion.
If someone manages to hold it in,
they get to hit the next one.
Switching it up.
That's pretty great.
So the one getting hit now hits the next one?
— We'd be switching.
— If they hold it in,
they can do it.
This is fucking endless then.
Don't hold back.
You're smiling, aren't you?
You're smiling?
He was smiling.
You were smiling for sure, man.
He was really smiling!
That's when you laugh?!
He was smiling a lot!
He was smiling all along!
That's how you can tell a sadist apart.
What's going on?
You'd been doing it for a while!
You had a little too much fun?
He was smiling a lot, right?
He was definitely smiling!
He was happy to be getting good at this.
He was basically just doing his job.
Besides, you were almost grinning
all the time while doing it!
He was grinning for sure!
He totally forgot!
I'm sorry! I was just enjoying the game.
— I'm sorry.
— Also, Seiji!
You were almost smiling all along!
I was just waiting for you to show up.
That's right, that's right.
But we didn't get to the actual strike.
It's been a general problem for a while already.
We were just having a lot of fun!
That's no good, though.
You can have fun, but the challenge is to not smile.
I've got an orange already, so I'm in trouble.
I knew I was in trouble and had to hold it in for real.
Let's take a look at Coo-chan, then.
I'm sorry!
Don't hold back.
He's smiling already!
He's definitely smiling already.
He's totally smiling, right?
I get the feeling that it was around that moment.
It's not quite grinning, though.
But he admits it himself anyways.
So that's all there is to it.
Also, Seiji.
Seiji didn't quite smile, but still...
He's smiling?
He's not smiling.
He kind of is a little.
He's grinning.
He's smiling!
You did that all the time!
That was a smile!
And it wasn't just once!
Come on, Seiji.
All the way from Sri Lanka!
Long Sri Lanka!
To be honest, right now we're over three and a half hours.
So he has been like that for almost three full hours.
Well, alright, first...
Your first one.
Thank you very much.
That's his first?
We have to take him down gradually.
We have to do it gradually somehow.
And also, Seiji.
You're out!
The Chihara brothers!
I see!
For real!
Come back as a zombie!
I want Fujita out already.
Why me?!
Well, it's just that...
I just want him out already.
Fujita is... Fujita you're...
You're not funny at all, so keep trying.
That stings, you know?
No, no, you're funny week to week.
You're killing me here.
Don't puke so quietly.
But I'm really trying here.
— Leave the stage!
— Leave!
You don't belong here!
With this, the Chihara brothers are out!
That's right!
But the Chihara brothers might come back as zombies!
What will be the joke?
They told me not to smile all the time.
They sure did.
To be honest, I think I might've been smiling a lot.
This is an important time in my life,
so don't speak in languages I can't understand!
We're sorry.
You don't get it!
Seiji, Seiji, Seiji!
Seiji is definitely smiling, though!
Are you gonna keep going?!
Not yet, man!
He's having the best time of his life.
I just have to hold it in.
— You can barely do that though.
— Barely, yeah.
But I love this.
Here we go.
It started.
— So?
— Are we gonna keep going?
The harmonica, the harmonica.
In your mouth.
Do it for real this time.
I don't think I could hold it.
You're awesome, Koba!
Because it hurts, right Koba?
It takes some training.
You played rugby, right Koba-san?
We loved this shit back in rugby, yeah.
Let's go.
That looks painful as shit.
How was that?
How was that just now?
— That was a sound.
— No way.
That was a sound, yeah, it was.
Okay, next one please.
Koba-san.
— Give me a tissue.
— Wipe it, wipe it.
I'm surprisingly fine with this.
Kobayashi-san, you're a pretty tough guy, right?
He's not gonna tell you to go full strength, though.
But still,
Koba-san has taken good care of me for so long.
I'm really sorry, Koba-san.
But I don't want to be too lax with this.
Ready? Here I go.
He's super weak.
He's making a lot of noise.
What do you say, Kawamoto?
No, no.
That's definitely a lot of noise.
You lose, man.
That one?!
No, no, no.
Can you hold it?
So this means that leg's stronger?
That doesn't make any sense.
I'm right legged, after all.
I see.
I used to do this with my left leg all the time while practicing.
With beer bottles and stuff.
I get it, I get it, I get it.
With beer bottles?!
That's pretty badass.
Here we go.
Sorry.
You're awful!
"Sorry"?!
Time to change.
— That was the loudest so far.
— He's the weakest.
And it was high pitched and everything.
Why are we hitting Oguchi?
I'm sure Shoji's pretty strong.
He does work out.
This is the worst.
You have to do it around here.
This is pretty bad.
That has to hurt!
Karate students used to do it like this.
— That's how they trained.
— Right.
That hurts!
That really hurts!
Why are we changing the conditions?
That hurts!
That's pretty painful.
It hurts like hell, huh?
You laughed!
You even took your time to fall!
It hurt too much!
Of course it hurts!
I wanted to do it at least once.
It hurts too much!
You stopped it once, though!
For real! I thought I broke my foot!
What's going on?
He said he wanted to stop the recording at least once!
I'm at my limit.
— I see.
— It hurts!
You laughed like an old lady.
He took his sweet time!
I was at my limit.
I had to make some noise at least.
Well, sometimes you do laugh because it hurts too much.
That was a laughter I hadn't heard before.
That was a painful laughter.
It hurts like hell, huh?
I was at my limit.
What was that?! Tried to escape?
That was a desperate laugh.
The bottle really hurts.
It hurts like hell.
Sorry about that.
I did the bottle myself.
Okay, Kawamoto gets...
...an orange!
And also...
Fujita, you're out!
Huh?! Why?!
— Right?
— I wasn't laughing!
— There's no way I'm out!
— Why?
I've never heard of someone being out for being boring!
I think I even got a point for myself.
Me too, probably.
— Really?
— Yeah.
So uh, Koba-san.
What now?
Wanna eat pizza?
We could order sushi as well.
Sushi and pizza?
Sushi and pizza sounds good.
I want to eat sushi and pizza.
Also, I kind of...
I'd like to try out some physical gag.
Yeah, later.
Thanks for calling.
I'm Ota from Ariake Pizzeria.
Excuse me, I'd like to make an order.
Understood. Thank you very much.
Can you please tell me your phone number?
The phone number?
— Yes?
— The phone number...
Uh...
The phone number...
Should I just go with my personal one?
080...
Is he stupid?
Can you tell me your name as well?
— My name?
— Yes.
— Let's go with Fujita.
— Fujita-sama, right?
So now I have to go no matter what.
To receive it.
So what's your order?
But it seems like Amazon is going to broadcast this as well.
You're kidding me?!
They can't do that!!
Uh, I'm sorry.
— I'd like a crab quarter,
— This guy's an idiot.
Rock, paper, scissors!
See? He's not looking.
Get it?
Momentarily, yeah.
Rock, paper, scissors!
I have scissors.
You can't do anything against the powerful double scissors.
What kind of dough do we want?
Dough...
Let's go with an Italian super crispy,
and a hand toss.
With a hand toss.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Why did you withdraw?
He with—
He has been smiling the whole time.
He has, yeah.
— Right now.
— Have fun with the game.
— Anything else?
— Right now.
— Have fun with the game.
— Excuse me for a second.
— Rock, paper, scissors!
What pasta do you want?
Rock, paper, scissors!
He's good!
Rock, paper—
What?
What happened?
He laughed just like that.
What the hell happened?
What was it?
I didn't find out about anything.
Cookie laughed?
That's good!
We have to keep going!
Cookie has moments like this a lot!
He does!
He laughs in the weirdest moments.
More like he's having fun.
And then there was also Kawamoto
while playing rock, paper, scissors.
He was smiling quite a bit!
He was when he was playing with me!
He was smiling, right?
I guess, it's kind of inconclusive.
Yeah, that's true.
Rather than smiling, I was just... uh...
Going like that, you know?
"Huh, I see."
— You were smiling!
No, I wasn't smiling.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper—
— That was a full out laugh!
— You could see his teeth!
He knows he lost!
Alright, Cookie, last chance.
It's time!
This is serious!
There it is, there it is.
Because this one was huge.
You just have to get him to have fun.
And since we ordered the pizza with Fujita's name,
you're out when the delivery gets here.
Why the hell?!
It's complicated.
At least make me laugh!
Why are the rules different just for me?
Want us to make you laugh?
That's exactly what I want you to do!
Making me leave without laughing is just...
— He took the order.
— I just took the order.
You're out even without laughing.
Fujita, whenever you do your one-shots,
you just have that "I wanna die" expression on your face.
My father's enemy!
It's just that today I kinda...
laughed until I couldn't stand it anymore.
I almost cried from laughter.
It was complete insanity.
The winner is...!