"Who Is The Real Celebrity BASIC,
threehour programme in spring!"
The spring grading consists of
super basic tests that
they should obviously guess right.
The Spring Grading consists of tests
on basic knowledge they should know.
The correct answer is...
For example,
in the string quartet performance,
they'll compare the most expensive
musical instrument
to one that lacks a string.
The tasting test
is also a basic test
of comparing
the finest quality squid
to Kanetsu Delica Foods'
unreleased product, Hobohobo Ika,
which is made with fish paste.
Are you kidding me?
Of course, if they get it wrong,
their rank will go down,
and eventually
vanish from the screen at the end,
so be careful!
In the New Year, we asked our guests
to spot the firstrated items.
In the Spring Grading, we'll do some
very basic tests to check whether
you know things that a person
should naturally know or not.
You should stay as firstrated
celebrities till the end, naturally.
That's right...
First, from great families,
Team Nagashima and Koizumi,
Mr Kazushige Nagashima
and Mr Kotaro Koizumi.
Team... Nagashima?
Yes, Nagashima and Koizumi.
And Koizumi.
That's right.
Our backgrounds are powerful.
Don't say that!
Because we're from
powerful backgrounds.
Maybe you are, but don't say it.
Yeah?
How is this?
I bump into Mr Kazushige
at various places,
like sports club and restaurants.
I see.
It feels very reassuring.
Currently, I'm not nervous at all.
That's good.
Will you be quiet?
Please do your best.
Okay.
The two gentlemen came
from the same hometown.
Team Kagoshima,
Mr Show Aikawa
and Mr Toshiaki Megumi.
Are you confident?
Very confident.
Of course.
Then maybe Mr Show won't get
anything wrong and Mr Megumi will?
"You host various
informational programmes
and you don't know that?"
Everyone will say that, right?
You look so happy!
You look happy!
Next, Team Born in February,
Blood Type A,
Mr Ryuta Sato and Miss Karina.
Team Farfetched.
Yes.
What's that team?
We think so too.
But the scale of our team is huge.
We represent everyone in Japan
who was born in February
and has blood type A.
We can't lose this match.
From Team Soccer, Mr Yoshito Okubo
and Mr Yuji Nakazawa.
I disappeared the last time.
I reflected on my mistake,
and got myself in shape for this.
I'll be perfect this time,
don't worry.
It was my condition last time.
Are you confident?
I'm very confident now.
Good.
Next, Team Yokai Housemate,
Miss Fuka Koshiba
and Miss Marika Matsumoto.
I really love this show
and I've always watched it,
so I'm happy, but when I'm here,
I get nervous and my throat is dry.
You don't seem to eat much
expensive food.
Don't say that!
It's prejudice.
There's no way someone from Kansai
eats nice food!
What about you, Miss Marika?
I'll show you my character as
a firstrated celebrity this time.
Last time, you also...
talked in that composed manner
and kept falling.
That's embarrassing.
Johnny's representative,
Team SixTONES,
Mr Jesse and Mr Yugo Kochi.
How do you feel?
Well, we're nervous,
but Jesse is confident!
Thank you.
I was told I'll be fine
if I do that.
And you, Kochi?
I'm the most normal one
among SixTONES.
He's the oldest too.
Yes, I'm the oldest,
so I'll get the job done.
Do your best, then.
We will.
Okay.
Thank you.
From Team Idols and Comedians,
Nogizaka46 and Oideyasu Koga.
Three ladies.
I think Nogizaka and Oideyasu Koga
are very compatible.
What?
But it's possible
you will make each other fail.
Like you guys guess it right
but they don't.
I was a cook for five years.
I'm confident in my taste buds.
He worked at a pub,
but it was exploitative.
Gosh, stop it...
We aren't talking about
the work system!
The difficulty of beatboxing
is even much lower...
Good morning...
Do it properly!
Hey!
Impressive!
Deceive them if possible!
We'll make them all guess wrong.
Right?
It was impressive.
I'm counting on you
in the real thing.
They'll compare professionals
who won the second place
in an international competition,
to comedians who only mimic.
First, a super easy question.
This is the first test.
It's red wine.
In the New Year,
celebrities had to guess
the best wine in the world.
But this time it's the basics,
so you'll taste
red wine and white wine
and guess which one is red wine.
You look down on us.
You won't taste the red wine
in the New Year
that costs 1 million yen,
the table wine will be
a 3,500 yen red wine
and a 6,000 yen white wine.
But it's red wine and white wine!
You can't get this wrong.
Indeed.
It'll make me laugh.
It's impossible.
They will be the representatives.
This time, Team Nagashima
and Koizumi from great families
will cause a big incident
that'll stay in the show's history.
Please go to the Check Room.
Thank you.
Please do your best.
I'm counting on you.
Please taste the red and white wine
and choose the red wine.
They'll taste red wine
and white wine
and say which one is red.
It's a super basic test.
We prepared a Spanish red wine
and an Italian white wine this time.
"Correct: Finca L'Argata 2017"
"Wrong: Toscana, Ansonaco 2018"
The first one is this gentleman.
Hello.
This is what it's like?
Oh, Kotaro! This will matter.
His father was a Prime Minister,
his younger brother is a Diet member
who is a minister.
Mr Kotaro Koizumi comes from
a grand family in real life.
"Kotaro Koizumi"
Are you confident?
There's no way I'll be wrong.
Right?
It's red wine and white wine.
I had it yesterday too.
So you won't get it wrong.
That's right.
He wears a pair of dandy sunglasses
so that he can't judge by colour.
He looks so handsome!
So handsome!
I'll taste it now.
First, wine A.
"Wine A"
He drank it in one go.
Is it okay?
Okay.
So quick!
It's cool!
Don't change it.
Use your first inspiration.
Okay, go.
I'll taste this.
Next, Wine B. If you get this wrong,
your former Prime Minister Daddy
will shout at you.
"Wine B"
Oh? He's confused now?
Oh no. Oh no!
This is bad, I think he's confused.
It's more difficult than I thought.
His answer is...
The red wine is...
A.
I think that's fine. Yes.
I thought it tasted more like
red wine than Pinot,
so I knew right away
that it has to be A.
He's fine.
First, Mr Koizumi's answer is A.
I'm sure it's this one.
"Waiting room A"
Here, he'll watch what other people
do on the screen
and wait for the result.
"He can watch other people
do the test"
It's the first impression.
You can talk now, but don't keep
going on and on during the test.
I can't hear him
if someone else talks.
Kazushige, you've only shown
what's bad about you.
He scolded Kazushige for real.
I'm so scared.
The next one is...
Hello.
I'm nervous.
It's Miss Karina.
She made her debut
as a fashion model
and played the protagonist
in one of the most popular dramas.
Miss Karina is active
as a talented actress.
How do you feel?
I guessed the 1 million yen wine
right last time.
This time it's red and white wine,
so I want to guess it right.
She looks so cool.
So cool!
First, Wine A.
"Wine A"
Oh, she drank a lot.
"Hmm?"
Is it a bit difficult?
Next, Wine B.
Now, it's B.
It looks like she's sulking.
Well?
It's difficult?
Yes.
I think if the next person...
chooses B, I'm going to lose
my confidence at once.
Which answer will she give?
Her answer is...
B is red wine.
They're divided.
They're divided!
Right away!
"Worried"
Oops! It's dramatic already.
B is more mellow,
it's got a bit of red wine's...
aftertaste.
Their opinions are divided.
But that means
either one will go down.
Yes, right away.
They're different.
It's a simple test,
but their opinions
are already divided.
He's not here! Are you kidding me?
"Waiting room B"
Oh! Are you kidding me?
We're guessing red wine, right?
Yeah, it's red wine.
Was it A?
Hang on. Karina, you guessed
the 1 million yen wine right...
Next, it's this gentleman.
Hello. Excuse me.
Okay, it's Jesse.
Please, Jesse! Do your best!
Their debut single sold
a million copies,
the group of six represents
Johnny's next generation.
SixTONES's Mr Jesse.
Mr Jesse, what do you think?
They look down on us too much.
I drink wine as well,
I have a soft spot for wine
in a good sense.
Okay, next.
It's okay.
It's good.
First, Wine A,
chosen by Kotaro Koizumi.
"Wine A"
"Oh"
He doesn't look confident.
No.
Oh, I'm worried!
Taste the red wine and white wine
and choose the red wine. That's all!
Okay.
Next, Wine B, chosen by Karina.
He drinks it up in one go.
"Wine B"
What?
He laughed.
He doesn't know?
He doesn't.
Just decide if it's red or white.
Yes, I'm counting on you!
His answer is...
This.
"Wine B"
Kotaro has a crisis!
Wait a minute...
B tastes richer.
It has more flavour and depth.
It tasted like red wine
when the flavour filled my mouth.
I see.
Good, he has a reason. It's okay.
Two people went to B.
Is this okay?
Well...
After Karina, Jesse also chose B.
Okay, here I go.
Thank goodness!
Jesse, you're here.
Jesse, you choose B?
I think it's B.
Next, it is...
Hello.
Okay, it's Mr Okubo.
Yoshito!
Yoshito, do your best!
Top scorer.
The first striker
who became J League's top scorer
for three years in a row,
former player in Japan's
National Team, Mr Yoshito Okubo.
You know there's
red wine and white wine, right?
Sure, I do.
Don't look down on him too much,
of course he knows.
I had tasted and compared them once.
They're totally different.
I know what they're like.
I see.
I remember it.
Okay.
The top scorer looks so good
wearing the pair of sunglasses.
First, it's Wine A.
"Wine A"
He sticks his little finger out.
He looks so rough!
He stuck out his little finger.
Okay.
"Lonely"
Did you hesitate?
But they were obviously
a bit different,
so I thought it was B.
Next, Wine B,
which is currently in the lead.
Wine B.
I'm counting on you.
Okubo played for Spain, the place
that produces good quality wine.
He should naturally know
the answer, but...
What?
They're the same!
I know it's hard to choose.
He can't decide.
Hang on. Hang on.
He'll only say
whether it's red or white.
It's okay, you can do it.
He couldn't decide,
but his answer is...
It's A.
Oh!
He said A.
A.
"Feels safe"
What? It's different.
It's two and two?
Two and two.
They taste almost the same,
but the aftertaste of A
was more astringent.
The opinions are divided.
Divided!
This is interesting!
The proud top scorer of Japan
can't miss this easy goal!
It makes me so nervous.
Yes!
Good!
I'm happy.
I'm so happy!
Sorry, I can't shake your hands,
but that's how happy I am.
I'm so happy.
That's rather scary.
Yes, I was here alone.
Hello.
Oh no...
It's twototwo!
Is the correct answer A or B?
Next, it's this gentleman.
It's Mr Show.
He's here!
Here comes Mr Show.
I'm counting on you, Big Bro!
Please do it!
Will Mr Show know?
Debuted as a member
of Isseifubi Sepia,
the VCinema Emperor, Mr Show Aikawa
has appeared in over 100 movies.
"Show Aikawa"
Mr Show, do you usually drink wine?
Not at all.
You don't?
No.
I don't drink wine at all,
but I know if the wine tastes good.
So you'll know
whether it's red or white at once?
Of course I will.
Red and white are...
Mr Show...
Is that okay?
You say you'll know?
They're different colours.
No, you won't see its colour.
Is this okay?
Mr Show.
Everyone worries about you.
This is bad.
Everyone teased Mr Show Aikawa.
Pay attention to how he looks
in sunglasses.
He wore it.
I've seen this before.
It suddenly looks like VCinema.
It really is VCinema.
He's well known as a heavy drinker
among celebrities,
but we're worried about wine.
"Wine A"
He only needs to choose
whether it's red or white.
I hope Mr Show will come here.
Which one will Mr Show choose?
He also drinks Wine B coolly.
"Wine B"
Which one?
He doesn't know.
Right?
It's a bit doubtful.
His answer is...
B.
Are you kidding me?
Yes!
Yay!
It's the astringency.
Somehow...
The flavour exploded in my mouth
after I drank it.
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
Really?
Did it explode in your mouth?
No.
Big Bro Aikawa
doesn't usually drink wine
so we're a bit worried,
but now B is in the lead.
Wow!
Thank goodness!
It's B, right?
Right?
Mr Show chose B.
I wish he had come here.
Room A gets worried again.
The next one is...
Okay, it's Miss Marika Matsumoto.
She was on top of the actresses
in the first half
of the year's ranking last year.
Miss Marika Matsumoto
always boasts when she talks.
Miss Marika, what do you think?
Yes.
I think it's a problem
before common knowledge.
I don't even need to smell it,
there's no way I wouldn't know.
Right?
She's cute.
She probably embezzles money.
First, Wine A.
"Wine A"
She drank it in one go.
She nods.
It's quick.
She's confident.
I can't trust her somehow.
It looks like she knows.
Miss Marika is confident,
she tastes Wine B next.
"Wine B"
That reaction just now was big.
Oh?
I know. I know why you're confused.
What?
Which one will she choose?
Her answer after hesitating is...
Oh! Now it's three to three!
Wow!
That's impressive!
Now we can't tell.
Good...
It's three to three?
It's divided.
When I tasted B,
it was very astringent,
so I thought it was red,
but the impact of the first one
was very strong.
That's amazing!
They're completely divided.
They divided into three and three.
Yes.
Maybe we should do this
in the New Year too.
Yes, the very first question
is good.
It's perfect.
It is.
It's only to taste the red wine
and white wine
and choose the red one,
the development is incredible.
"Delighted"
We've been waiting.
Only the few of us?
It's perfectly three to three.
Three to three.
Well.
Mr Koizumi, you're confident, right?
Even when I think back now,
I'm sure A was the red wine.
Yes, you'll be okay.
I see.
Miss Karina, you chose the other.
What do you think?
B had an aftertaste,
the aroma that I smelt
was like red wine.
Hello...
"Is the red wine A or B?"
The correct answer is...
Our last participants
finally make their appearance.
Hello...
The last team!
Here they are.
It'll depend on them.
M1 Grand Prix 2020 finalists,
talented solo comedian duo,
Oideyasu Koga.
What about you, gentlemen?
There's no way we'll get it wrong.
Exactly, in the usual case.
We'll make them regret
making this a test.
Seriously.
Good!
Of course.
First, Wine A.
"Wine A"
I see.
Okay.
"Wine B"
Next, Wine B.
It's fast.
Do they know?
Kogaken knows.
He got it quickly.
Kogaken is sure he's right and nods,
and Oda is only staring
into the void.
"In a trance"
Will they choose A?
Or B?
Their answers are...
They're different!
That's amazing!
Wow!
They're different.
I'm getting a bit worried.
Wow... Is that so?
They're different.
I tasted astringency in B.
I see.
B tastes more fruity.
That?
I think A was more fruity.
That's right.
Please let me tell you,
I'm very confident.
I see.
Kogaken, do your best.
We'll choose B, then.
Oda went along with him.
Yes.
B...
Which one? Please...
A obviously was the red wine.
Exactly.
B...
But can their opinions be so divided
on whether the wine is red or white?
Hello. Hello.
It's surprisingly few!
It's half and half.
It's perfectly two halves.
Half and half!
I'm sure it's this.
It has to be.
Its flavour was different.
Is he so confident?
But the people in Room B
could've been deceived.
That's right.
The fateful announcement
of the result!
Thank you for your patience.
Celeb Master will go to the room
of the correct answer. Please wait.
Here I am!
Please come here!
Please!
Master, please!
I'll open the door
of the correct answer's room.
Please.
Please
Please come!
Please...
Please!
We want to stay firstclass!
The correct answer is...
"Waiting room A"
Please come here.
"Waiting room B"
What...
Yay!
"B: Correct"
"A: Wrong"
Are you kidding me?
Hey!
Wow!
Yay!
Amazing!
That's right.
Mr Show, everyone thought
you wouldn't know,
because you don't drink wine.
I knew when I drank it in one go.
I see. Miss Karina, you too.
I often buy a pack of six bottles
of red wine online,
it was worth doing.
Kogaken, it was brilliant.
I was very sure.
I tasted the astringency of tannin,
so I chose B!
Congratulations!
Let's go back.
Yay!
Yes!
The correct answer is,
B is the red wine.
This red wine has a nostalgic,
calming aroma and flavour,
its smooth texture
and harmonised taste
are its characteristic.
And A is a real white wine
made from white grapes.
The aroma of this white wine
resembles red wine,
but if someone drinks wine often,
they should be able to tell.
People who got it right are back!
Well done.
Wonderful!
Thank you.
Wonderful.
It was brilliant.
Well done.
People who chose the wrong answer
are back. Come in.
Oh? It's tiny.
"Wrong answer entrance"
This is how it is?
Thank you.
It's okay.
Please have a seat.
I'm sorry.
I think it was difficult.
Mr Koizumi, how was it?
I had no idea
it was so embarrassing.
So embarrassing!
Next, a string quartet performance.
But...
The wrong answer has one string...
and this has two strings missing!
Wow, this is bad! We already have
three teams of common celebrities!
But there'll be more drama,
a spring storm is coming!
The next test is...
"String quartet"
String quartet performance.
In the New Year, celebrities
had to choose the performance
with musical instruments that cost
a few billion yen.
This time,
we test you on the basics,
so the level is much lower.
I see.
The correct answer is
a performance
with string instruments
used by professionals,
and the other one is a performance
with string instruments
with one or two missing strings.
You can't even call it music.
It's noise to music lovers.
That's right.
A quartet performance of
two violins, a viola, and a cello.
Both answers will be performed
by an internationallyacclaimed
string quartet,
Quartet Integra.
"Quartet Integra"
The correct answer is performed
with firstrated string instruments
that cost a total of
250 million yen.
This time, the wrong answer
is done by cheap string instruments
for beginners,
and all four string instruments
have one missing string.
Among them, one violin
has two strings missing.
A performance of string instruments
with missing strings
can't be called music!
Whether it's played
with decent string instruments
or ones with strings missing.
Just choose between the two.
Wait.
That's all.
If you listen to sounds of a string
instrument with a missing string,
you can't tell?
Wait...
Usually people wouldn't listen
to that.
Mr Hamada, I have a question.
What is it?
Even if the string instruments
have one or two strings missing,
and if they're so professional
that we can't tell the difference,
they'll probably play
with another string to deceive us,
and the bow won't be caught
by the string?
It'll make weird sounds if it does,
so they'll play it skilfully.
They'll play skilfully?
Of course.
But even if they do, the sounds
from the missing string are missing.
No, I played cello last year
Shut up!
The people here will do
the easiest test
in the history of our music test.
You only need to give
the correct answer quickly here.
Representatives, please go
to the room to have a rest.
Thank you.
Please do your best.
Keep your rank there!
Everyone, stay at that rank.
Which quartet performance is played
with firstrated string instruments
with all four strings?
These four teams
will be tested first.
Let's start our test!
Here they are.
Okay.
He's a former pro baseball player,
and now works
as a multitalented entertainer.
Mr Kazushige's only fault is that
he always says things uncalledfor.
I listened to violin performances
a lot last year,
it was on a television show.
I listened to live performances
of string instruments
played by Chisako
and Miss Hirotsuru.
I think I can do it.
I see.
The first protagonist he played
was in the drama "ROOKIES,"
which was very popular.
Talented actor Mr Ryuta Sato
also appeared
in many other popular titles.
I really love music,
and I listen to various genres,
so I really want to get this right.
That's right,
and she got the first one right.
She built a comfortable path for me,
so I'd like to continue on that.
She played her first protagonist
in the first movie she starred in,
and received the Blue Ribbon Award
for the Best Newcomer
for "Kiki's Delivery Service."
Young actress Miss Fuka Koshiba
represents the next generation.
I cleaned my ears just now,
so I can hear clearly.
What the heck?
Yeah? Okay.
X JAPAN's YOSHIKI produced
their debut song,
leader of Johnny's popular group
SixTONES, Mr Yugo Kochi.
I've been listening to songs
of SixTONES that use violin,
so if I believe the music I always
listen to when I go to the room,
then I'll be fine.
I'll be okay.
I see!
That's right.
Go!
Viewers, please think together
with them.
We'll also listen
to the performance.
There'll be one or two strings
missing.
First, string quartet performance A.
"String quartet performance A"
This is Performance A.
I see.
Next, string quartet performance B.
"String quartet performance B"
This has been Performance B.
Totally different.
What do you think?
I agreed with Mr Show.
Please ask Mr Show, it's the same.
Which one is correct?
I think B had more depth.
I see.
It had more depth,
which means no missing string.
I see.
Does anyone agree?
Me.
A lacks something.
You're saying
the correct answer is B?
You choose A?
The volume of B was smaller,
so they were trying not to get
the bow caught to cover it up.
I see.
On the contrary,
I think A had more depth,
the sound of its bass...
I think it's obviously richer in A.
We argue this much here?
Over there...
What's the point of that?
They're going to fight hard there.
More people chose B at the studio.
Kazushige had listened to Chisako
Takashima play violin many times,
which one will he choose?
This is Mr Kazushige.
I think it's B.
His answer is...
It's B.
Oh! Just as I thought.
I see.
There was no string missing,
so I think it was more powerful.
I see.
Kazushige chose B, which is also
the majority at the studio.
"Waiting room B"
Okay.
I don't like being the first one.
Next, it's music lover
Mr Ryuta Sato.
He skips lightly and appears.
"Team Born in February,
Blood Type A, Ryuta Sato"
Mr Sato looks confident.
He does.
What is his answer?
The correct answer is B.
Wow! He's full of confidence!
Full of confidence.
It's the depth and weight
of the sound,
Performance B
was overwhelmingly better.
It can't be wrong! It has to be B.
Miss Karina, you also think it's B.
You two agree, right?
I'll sanitise my hands.
Without any hesitation
he goes to Room B,
where Kazushige is waiting.
Oh, it's this, right?
That's what I think,
but I don't know.
I felt its weight and depth.
You felt the depth.
Yes.
Thanks.
Good. This is great.
Next, it's Miss Fuka Koshiba,
who is so well prepared
that she cleaned her ears.
"Team Yokai Housemate, Fuka Koshiba"
I feel sick...
She said she felt sick.
She's probably very nervous.
Despite her nerves,
the answer she gives is...
It's A.
Oh?
Right?
Is this right? I'm scared!
She's scared.
The reason is...
I think the high notes
went up smoothly,
I liked this one more.
But... Okay, I'll choose this.
Her answer is different from yours,
Miss Matsumoto.
It is.
They played the first one skilfully,
I think it became narrower.
That's right.
I hear them talking in Room B...
I want to go back!
She wants to go back.
Because she's alone.
This is awful.
I'm sorry, Miss Marika!
"Waiting room A"
Can I sit at the centre?
I knew this would happen...
Fuka cleaned her ears
before coming here just now.
It's impressive
she cleaned her ears.
Is the correct answer A or B?
Now, we'll tell you
the correct answer at the studio.
Now?
The correct answer is...
What?
No way!
Are you serious?
Now, we'll tell you
the correct answer at the studio.
Now?
We'll know where
the people after them will go in.
I see.
Let's do it!
The correct answer is...
A.
Yes!
Right?
What? No way!
Yes!
Right?
What? No way!
I'm sure about it.
Impressive!
I'm sure it is!
No way!
I'm sure it is.
It has to be.
I'm so sad.
The two guys at B are sure
they got it right.
Yeah.
Fuka, why don't you come here?
I want to! I want to go there now!
Did you know the answer?
A is the correct answer,
a quartet performance
with all the strings.
She got it right,
but she keeps looking down!
She looks sad.
She's so worried that she sighed,
but she answered correctly.
Kazushige, Chisako will definitely
beat you up with her bow.
Please change your slippers.
Miss Karina has also become
a common celebrity.
I see, it keeps going down.
You'll keep changing
if anyone chooses B.
No! Kochi!
Next, it's Mr Kochi
from Johnny's new star, SixTONES.
Which one will Kochi answer?
You said A.
I said A.
Will he choose
the correct answer, A?
His answer is...
The correct answer is...
Come...
B.
Why?
Mr Jesse, please come to the front.
You can't stay
as firstrated celebrity.
He got you involved.
The first one didn't have depth,
the musicians played it carefully.
What are you talking about?
It's enough! Stop commenting!
On the contrary,
when I listened to B next,
it had so much depth.
I'm so embarrassed!
I'm embarrassed.
Jesse, it can't be helped,
this is what he thinks.
Please use
the string instruments of B
to play for SixTONES.
I'd like them to be played
with our band.
Shut up!
A band with missing strings?
Indeed!
It seems SixTONES will have
a quartet performance
with missing strings
in their concerts.
Excuse me.
Yes!
I'm a bit happy.
Thank goodness.
Thank you!
They look proud.
They're sure they're right.
Why are you fist bumping?
This fist bump is so embarrassing.
The fist bump is embarrassing.
He's a pro of music.
Yes, I've been listening to it.
Kochi can't get it wrong.
That's right.
Oh, I'm happy.
Fuka, come and join us!
I want to!
It's only three guys here now.
Yes.
We'd like a beautiful lady here.
Yes, we do.
These three teams
will have the test next.
He has a 33year career in showbiz,
and is also a member
of the comedian duo Honjamaka.
Mr Toshiaki Megumi hosts
a daytime information programme.
I'm sorry,
but I'll get this right easily.
I've been hosting the show
"MUSIC FAIR" for 18 years.
That's right.
I'll know right away.
The difference in sound. I see.
Former player in Japan's
National Team, Mr Yuji Nakazawa.
He had played twice in the World Cup
when he was active,
and was the key
of SAMURAI BLUE's defence.
I can hear my teammates' voices
in the cheering of 60,000 people,
and I know when supporters boo, too.
I can hear booing,
and I think the one
with missing strings
will be like booing.
That's the way you think?
That's right.
From Nogizaka46,
Miss Yuki Yoda, Miss Asuka Saito,
and Mizuki Yamashita.
Last year was the 10th anniversary
of their debut,
the national idols
are extremely popular.
We sing to live music
performance too,
Mr Akimoto will be angry
if we get this wrong.
I think we can do this.
First, the correct answer, A.
"A: Best quality that costs
a total of 250 million yen"
"Violinist: Kyoka Misawa"
"Violinist: Rintaro Kikuno"
String instruments need four strings
to play elegant music.
Two or three strings will limit
the sound they can make,
even the same piece
will sound totally different.
Next, the wrong answer,
rubbish string instruments
with missing strings.
Watch carefully
how the musicians play it.
"B: Cheap string instruments for
beginners with missing strings"
In fact, the most important violin
that plays the melody
has two strings missing.
I hope someone, even just one person
will come.
It feels so awkward to be alone.
Will the remaining three teams
choose the correct answer, A?
First, daytime show host Mr Megumi,
who wants to stay firstrated.
"Team Kagoshima, Toshiaki Megumi"
Okay! Wait, he's here.
I'm counting on you.
Guess it right.
His answer is...
Ah! He messed up!
No! This...
No!
I see...
When I thought about
how to tell them apart,
it was how the low notes unfolded.
Low notes.
So embarrassing!
It's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing
to say it in that tone.
I clearly felt the low notes of B
unfolded better.
Well, Mr Show also said it was B.
Well, I also said it was B.
It can't be helped.
People keep gathering
at the super embarrassing Room B.
Yes, Mr Megumi!
Yes!
Welcome!
Hello.
Thank goodness!
It's B, right?
We have a great lineup, don't we?
Yes...
Thank you.
Welcome.
They're so sure they've won.
They are so confident.
"B: wrong"
On the other hand, she got it right,
but looks worried
because she's alone.
"Worried but correct"
Next, they don't want
to go down again.
It's common celebrity, Team Soccer.
Okay...
Okay, Mr Nakazawa is here.
Now...
It's funny enough to watch.
I think there's a clear difference.
Don't go there.
It's about which one is that.
What does he mean?
He's saying something pointless.
Is Nakazawa okay? His answer is...
The correct answer, right?
The correct answer is A.
Wow!
Amazing!
Yay!
He made it.
Amazing!
His hearing is good.
First, B...
Among the 60,000 supporters,
it was saying, "Stupid Nakazawa,
dumb Nakazawa!"
It sounded something like booing.
But A sounded like, "Nakazawa,
you're amazing, you're cool!"
It was easy on the ears.
Well, his answer is correct.
It is.
Say whatever you want!
Wow!
Impressive.
I wonder what she's going to think.
"Whoa! A dark guy came in!"
"I can't trust him!"
The dark guy has arrived.
Oh, someone came!
"A: correct"
Don't worry.
What?
Nakazawa went to the other room.
It makes her feel relieved.
Don't worry.
Really?
She feels relieved
when Mr Nakazawa goes there.
They are so arrogant!
Can they be more marked for death?
They're totally marked for death.
Nogizaka46 will decide whether
we'll lose all firstrated celebs
in test two.
Really? I want to hold on to this.
I want to remain firstrated.
The last team
is Team Idols And Comedians.
Can they hold firmly on to the seat
of firstrated celebrities?
It's now!
Please!
We're counting on you!
Don't all choose B.
Okay, raise the correct answer, A.
Let's do it.
Ready, go.
Hey! This is awful!
This can't be helped.
They all chose B.
Hey!
I hate this!
It can't be helped.
No!
Apologise to Mr Akimoto!
They used string instruments
with missing strings in A,
then used decent ones after that,
so they were fired up.
That's why!
Yeah.
Don't agree!
It's enough!
Thank goodness we agreed.
It's better
if your opinions were divided!
Be divided!
Please! Don't look so sure!
We wished you would be divided!
They chose
the rubbish string instruments
without fighting,
and enter Room B,
where embarrassing guys gather.
Ready, go.
Oh, here you are!
Yay!
Yes!
Welcome!
So embarrassing!
No...
Don't show him on screen!
Welcome!
I'm so happy!
It's four guys here.
Mr Megumi spreads his arm
to welcome them.
Welcome!
He's showing them the way.
Whoa...
Don't worry. It's okay.
Really?
The fateful announcement
of the result!
Here I am!
Please...
Celeb Master will go to the room
of the correct answer.
I'll open the door
of the correct answer's room.
Mr Hamada, come here!
Don't worry.
"B: wrong"
The correct answer is...
"A: correct"
"Useless prayer"
What?
Yay!
Congratulations!
My mic fell.
"A: correct"
Yay!
Congratulations!
My mic fell...
Yay...
What?
Are you kidding me?
His face! Mr Megumi!
Mr Megumi!
Fuka is crying.
Yay!
What did you think when he came in?
I felt really relieved,
because I was alone the whole time.
Oh, thank goodness!
Oh, your hearing actually is good.
Thank you.
Brilliant.
Are you kidding me?
This is bad!
Oh no...
People who answered wrong
are back. Come in.
There are many.
What?
"Wrong answer entrance"
We don't usually see
Mr Megumi like that.
Welcome back.
I messed up.
You guys sat there so arrogantly.
Mr Kazushige is bowing.
Okay... Come in, come in.
That's right.
Come and sit down.
There are too many of you!
There are many!
So many!
There are so many!
Come, Yuki, hurry up.
Okay, let's check now.
We have no firstrated celebrity!
There is none!
It was only test two.
Only this team
is secondrated celebrities.
What's this?
We have no firstrated celebrity
after test two.
This really is a spring storm.
What will happen at the end?
"Who Is The Real Celebrity BASIC,
threehour programme in spring!"
The spring grading consists
of super basic tests that
they should obviously guess right.
The Spring Grading consists of tests
on basic knowledge they should know.
The correct answer is...
For example,
in the string quartet performance,
they'll compare the most expensive
musical instrument
to one that lacks a string.
The tasting test
is also a basic test
on comparing the finest quality
squid to Kanetsu Delica Foods'
unreleased product, Hobohobo Ika,
which is made with fish paste.
Are you kidding me?
Of course, if they get it wrong,
their rank will go down
and vanish from the screen
at the end, so be careful!
The third test is...
"Hamburger steak"
Hamburger steak.
You're going to taste and compare
hamburger steaks A and B.
The correct answer is a very common
hamburger steak made with
minced meat bought at a supermarket.
It's very common,
so you must've tried it.
The wrong hamburger steak
also used beef,
but the other kind of minced meat
is different. It's this...
It's minced pig or deer testicles.
What?
What did you say?
It's pig or deer testicles.
Can you tell?
Deer?
To sum up,
choose the hamburger steak
made with minced beef and pork.
Will you explain it
in a bit more detail?
What's that? More detailed
Testicles.
These are the representatives.
Just choose the hamburger steak
you usually eat.
Representatives, please!
Thank you.
Let's go!
Please go to the room.
Just choose the hamburger steak
you usually eat.
Okay, let's go and eat.
That's right, your usual one.
The first one is...
Thank you.
He wants to make up for his mistake
in the quartet performance,
common celebrity, Mr Ryuta Sato.
"Ryuta Sato"
Hamburger steak is my favourite!
Right?
I'll guess it right at once.
You'll know.
I'll be back triumphantly!
The first four groups' wrong answer
will have pig testicles added.
Hang on...
It doesn't feel wrong at all.
First, hamburger steak A.
"Hamburger steak A"
First, it's A.
He loves hamburger steak.
Yes.
Next, B.
Please open your mouth.
Open your mouth!
One of them has testicles added.
"Hamburger steak B"
Ah...
What reaction is this?
I'll guess the common one?
Of course.
The one with no testicle?
That's right!
Which one has no testicle?
This is the correct answer.
"Hamburger steak B"
It's simply because A has a taste
I've never tried before.
So, first, Mr Sato chose B.
Nobody is in either room, right?
Okay...
One has added testicles,
"addicle" for short.
It's harder to choose the wrong one.
The next one is...
Common celebrity,
actress Marika Matsumoto appears
with an enchanting smile.
"Marika Matsumoto"
How will you do, Miss Matsumoto?
I'd like to show you my status!
The way you talk is good. It's good.
She's curious about the side.
Her right side...
First, hamburger steak A.
"Hamburger steak A"
She reacted quickly.
An actress shouldn't choose
the testicles.
Next, hamburger steak B,
which Ryuta Sato chose.
Is this testicles or not?
Which one will she choose?
"Hamburger steak B"
She keeps nodding.
Yes, and Mr Sato too.
Come here! Come here!
Her answer is...
Okay.
"Hamburger steak A"
Oh, they're different!
They're different already.
Whoa!
A is a really plain,
common hamburger steak.
B tastes like it,
but the taste is somehow different.
I see.
I am sure it's A.
Their opinions are divided.
Wow...
Oh my god, this is bad!
The answers of hamburger steak with
testicles are already different.
It'll be okay.
Oh?
Why? Am I wrong?
Did I get it wrong?
We chose different ones.
What? Really?
You seem sure it's A.
I am sure it's A.
I thought the taste of A was unique.
Really?
Yeah.
Is the one who chose hamburger steak
with testicles Marika Matsumoto
or Ryuta Sato?
"Is A or B correct?"
Okay, I'll tell everyone
in the studio the correct answer.
What? Already?
Already?
We'll just see where
your teams go inside.
It has to be funny.
It's going to be funny after this.
Okay, the correct answer is...
Which one?
A!
"Correct: A"
He's wrong.
Miss Matsumoto is right?
I see.
Miss Karina, your chairs will be
changed, please come forward.
How cruel!
It's cruel.
Somehow B had a weird taste.
Really?
Marika Matsumoto chose
the correct answer.
Yes! Cobblers!
Did they do a good job
and deceived me?
"B: wrong"
Golden spheres are accumulating!
What will be this person's fate?
Here he is!
It's A!
There's no way a member of the grand
Koizumi Family chooses testicles!
I overthought it a bit
in the first test on wine.
Do you have any advice?
"Secondrated celebrity"
Please do give me your advice.
Say something now!
We're asking if you have
any advice or not.
Hamachan...
Yes?
No.
First, it's the correct answer,
the common hamburger steak.
"A: Minced beef and pork"
It's this one. Kotaro,
this is the real hamburger steak.
Oh? It doesn't feel right?
He's tilting his head.
He looks confused.
Next, if you choose
this testicle hamburger steak,
the former Prime Minister
will scold you.
"B: Minced beef and pig testicles"
Delicious!
See? I knew it.
It's made like that.
He can't afford to fail three times.
What is his answer?
The common one made with
beef and pork from the supermarket.
Which one?
"B: Minced beef and pig testicles"
See? I knew he'd choose that.
I knew it!
I couldn't help saying delicious.
It was as delicious as
the hamburger steaks I've tried.
You see?
See? I knew this would happen.
The taste of this one is lighter,
so I think it's B.
Oh? Testicles taste light?
Okay, Mr Kazushige,
you'll change into sandals.
They're sandals for the loo?
That's right.
You say it like "the weird guy."
"Yes, that's right."
"That's right, I'm the weird guy."
It makes me nervous.
Everyone does this every time.
I'm impressed.
Kotaro, aka "Cobblertaro" Koizumi
shows up pleasantly.
I'm more confident in this
than the wine.
I knew right away.
"Cobblertaro Koizumi"
Thank goodness!
Welcome.
This is okay, right?
It's what I think.
But we've already had
different answers,
so I was very worried
before you came.
Oh no.
It's this situation.
Kotaro is laughing.
Whatever.
I hope Daddy Junichiro
isn't watching this.
The next one is...
Kochi is here!
Kochi!
SixTONES's Mr Kochi will surely lose
fans if he chooses the testicles.
"Yugo Kochi"
Mr Kochi, what do you think?
I make hamburger steaks myself,
so I only need to choose the one
that tastes like my usual ones.
That's right.
I'm confident.
First, the correct answer,
the common hamburger steak.
"A: correct. Minced beef and pork"
He'll fail twice in a row
if he gets this wrong.
That's right.
Jesse, you answered yours right.
Yes.
Next, the wrong answer,
hamburger steak with pig testicles.
"B: wrong.
Minced beef and pig testicles"
Please choose B.
Come!
Which one will he choose?
Let's not be Testicles Johnny's.
"Let's not be Testicles Johnny's"
The moment he raises B,
he becomes a Testicles Johnny's!
What is his answer?
The hamburger steak I know is...
This one.
Yes!
Impressive!
Well done!
Amazing!
The texture is like what I make,
this one is more chewy.
So I choose A.
Good!
Thank goodness.
"A: correct"
The taste of B was more familiar.
"B: wrong"
The flavour of A was stronger.
This is something
you shouldn't get wrong.
Thank goodness.
Wow...
This one, right?
Is it? Is it really?
Well...
Starting from this team,
they'll taste deer testicles.
That's right.
Will the taste change?
The first one
to try deer testicles is...
Here he is! Please do it, Big Bro!
It's Mr Show.
Yes.
I think he's good at this.
Big Bro, make sure you don't choose
the deer testicles!
"Show Aikawa"
There's no way I don't know!
Right? Just choose
the common hamburger steak.
Just choose the normal flavour.
Yes, the one you usually eat.
If I think it's a bit different,
that means it's wrong.
That's all.
It's easy.
You can count on me!
It doesn't look weird at all.
Not at all.
He looks like that when he wakes up.
He has a bite of the correct answer,
the common hamburger steak.
"A: correct. Minced beef and pork"
He has five children, so I think
he's had hamburger steak many times
with his children.
That's right.
Next, the wrong answer.
If he chooses this, he'll totally
lose the dignity of emperor,
even his family will ignore him.
It's hamburger steak
with deer testicles added.
"B: wrong"
How is it?
Okay...
I'm counting on you.
Which one will Show Aikawa choose?
His answer is...
Which one?
Well...
I'll choose the hamburger steak?
That's right!
Yes, you will!
He just wants to check, Mr Hamada.
The one with no testicles is B.
Oops...
The time needed till I swallow.
It took me much less time
to swallow B.
Doesn't it depend on you?
Senior, you're right!
Thank you!
It makes me feel relieved.
Yes, it makes me feel relieved.
When Mr Show comes, Kotaro too...
They've won.
They surely think they won.
It was more crowded in our room
last time, right?
Mr Megumi went, "Welcome!"
Like, "Welcome to the room
of the correct answer!"
Indeed.
Testicles Big Bro joins them
in the Testicles Room!
"Testicles Big Bro"
Wow!
Thank you!
It's B, right?
It's B.
It can't be wrong!
They're totally different.
Totally different! I've never had
hamburger steak like that.
No...
I can sit here and feel relieved.
It stayed.
It took me some time.
It did, right?
Yes.
Next, their duo's name will change
to Oideyasu Kogan if they're wrong.
It's Oideyasu Koga.
"Kogaken, Oideyasu Oda"
First, the correct answer, A.
"A: correct. Minced beef and pork"
Is he wearing an eye mask?
Maybe he isn't.
Right?
Next, B. Hamburger steak
with deer testicles added.
"B: wrong.
Minced beef and deer testicles"
Oh.
I see.
Which one is it?
I want Mr Kogaken here.
Yes, we do.
Oda will say B
and Kogaken will say A.
I'm scared!
Please guess it right.
Which one?
The common one.
The common hamburger steak. Okay.
Yes, that's right!
What the heck?
They don't want to be wrong.
Please...
Please come, Mr Kogaken!
The gentlemen's answers are...
"B: wrong.
Minced beef and deer testicles"
There's nothing you can do now.
Kogaken chose that.
They agreed.
Yeah.
Are you serious?
"Correct, but worried"
Really?
Yes!
A is more chewy.
When I swallowed, I think there was
something like fibre remaining.
I see.
I don't think it's suitable
for making hamburger steak.
He said it!
"Not suitable."
But it's hamburger steak.
"Oideyasu Kogan"
The new duo Oideyasu Kogan
has formed!
They agreed and go
to the Cobblers Room together.
Oh?
Thank you.
Thank you...
It has to be!
It is, right?
They're totally different.
I also thought they were.
Yes.
They guessed the correct answer,
but they are quiet.
"Silent"
Lastly, Mr Yuji Nakazawa,
who will change his name to
Yuji Koganzawa if he guesses wrong.
He guessed the previous quartet
performance correctly.
You never know.
Maybe he'll guess it right.
Nakazawa is sharp today.
First, the correct answer,
the common hamburger steak.
"A: correct. Minced beef and pork"
Okay!
Oh? Is he actually sharp today?
This matters...
It decides if you can stay or not.
Next, the hamburger steak
with deer testicles added.
Don't choose this one.
"B: wrong"
Don't choose this.
You're eating the wrong answer.
He's nodding.
The way he nods...
I have a bad feeling about this.
Okay.
He nodded after B.
He has made up his mind.
Okay, which one will he choose?
So, I'll choose the common one?
That's what I said!
I'm telling you that's right!
Big Bro, we can't tell now.
Like it was scripted.
And his answer is...
The correct answer is...
B!
Okay, wrong!
That's right.
Yeah, it can't be helped.
Yes! Here he comes!
Look...
What?
"Even more worried"
When I ate A,
the texture and the taste
were not like the hamburger steak
I usually have.
They tried to cover it up,
but they can't deceive me.
You've been deceived!
You don't eat it usually.
Yuji Koganzawa joins them too!
"Yuji Koganzawa"
Hello.
Yes!
It's this one, right?
There is no way this can be wrong.
When I see this scene...
Yeah.
Let's do fist bumps.
It can't be wrong...
It can't be wrong.
I'm sure.
It's a standing ovation.
This is the most embarrassing!
The fateful announcement
of the result!
Here I am!
"Celeb Master enters the room
of the correct answer"
I'm sure we're okay...
He'll just come in smoothly.
I'll open the door
of the correct answer's room.
The correct answer is...
Oh...
"A: correct"
I'm sure it's okay.
"B: wrong"
Congratulations!
Yay!
"B: wrong"
What?
No way!
Are you kidding me?
Impossible! Impossible!
I give up.
Oh jeez.
Jeez...
But if there are only
a few people...
The other room looks like
they've won.
Exactly!
Are you kidding me?
I had no idea.
I can't believe it!
Does that happen?
You must be kidding me!
The two people who got it right!
Welcome back!
Well done! Brilliant! I'm impressed.
Well done.
Amazing.
It feels great, right?
The studio is so bright!
People who guessed the wrong answer
are back. Come in.
"Wrong answer entrance"
He's picking a fight.
Welcome back. Thank you.
Have a seat.
Who would've thought you'd choose
the one with testicles added?
This is ridiculous.
I don't think you can make it with
the usual minced meat,
even if you want to.
I don't think so.
No.
Will you stop making excuses?
Sorry, Yoshito.
Now most of the board
are the blue ones!
Secondrated!
Thirdrated here.
You'll really vanish at this rate!
This is bad...
Oops, all teams are in this
wretched state after test three.
Later, Team Nagashima And Koizumi
from great families
will do something outrageous!
Stay tuned!
Test four is this.
It's beatboxing.
You'll compare two performances
of beatboxing, a technique that
plays music using only the mouth.
That's right.
There are three options
A, B and C in this test.
One of them is the "absolutely no"
answer they shouldn't get wrong.
If they choose this,
they'll go down two ranks.
No!
Two ranks down at once!
To sum up,
if thirdrated celebrities go down
two ranks, they'll disappear.
You two will surely disappear.
Already?
Yes.
The correct answer
is performed by a group of four
who had won second place
in an international beatboxing
competition, SARUKANI.
They're very famous.
The correct answer is SARUKANI,
a group of four beatboxers.
In an international beatboxing
competition held last year,
they were the first Japanese group
that won the second place.
They're currently a beatboxing group
that attracts a lot of attention.
And...
In the wrong answer,
one comedian will replace
one of the pro beatboxers.
It will be this comedian,
please look at the door.
It's Cocorico's Mr Shozo Endo!
Ho ho ho!
Don't say ho ho ho!
We look forward to it.
Come on...
You have no firstrated celebs
already.
I'm a bit surprised. I see.
Mr Endo is wellknown
for how well he sings,
but it's the first time
he tries beatboxing.
Yes, the first time.
Have you been practising?
I was practising all the time.
He has practised for about 50 hours.
What I carry this time is different.
May I?
I'm carrying this.
Wonderful.
It's a collab with Mr Hamada.
A collab hoodie with
Mr Masatoshi Hamada.
I'm really going to go and make it.
And then...
And the answer you mustn't choose
will have one more comedian
on stage. Here he is!
"Two beatboxers, two comedians"
Hello.
It's Onigoe Tomahawk's Kinchan.
From four professionals to
having two fewer and adding them.
That's right.
It's half amateur
and half professional.
And Kinchan had only practised
two hours.
Well, I mean,
Mr Kazushige is only
a profligate son.
Thirdrated.
What are you talking about?
Don't call me thirdrated
or profligate, idiot.
My background is powerful!
Exactly. I'm sorry.
It's a supereasy question
to choose the performance
by all pro beatboxers.
There's no way they'll choose
the beatboxing by comedians, right?
They are the representatives.
If Team Nagashima and Koizumi
from great families
choose "absolutely no,"
they'll vanish at once.
What do you think, Miss Karina?
Actually, I really love SARUKANI,
I watch their YouTube videos
and their Instagram.
Is that so?
Each member is really unique,
it's awesome.
I see.
I'm sure I'll know.
There'll be something foreign.
That's right.
And you?
My son watches their videos
on YouTube,
so I'm confident.
So you'll know. Okay.
I think so.
Jesse will go?
That's right.
The two of us among the six SixTONES
members do vocal percussion.
I see.
So I think maybe it's perfect.
That's great.
Okay, representatives, please go
to the room and stand by.
Don't get excited
and perform yourself.
Stay secondrated.
Please.
Do your best to stay where you are.
Or you'll go down one rank or two.
Later, comedian beatboxers
are going to cause a big drama!
First, these three teams will do it.
Please listen to it
in the studio too.
Yeah.
I want to guess it right.
They'll perform Hamachan's
famous song "WOW WAR TONIGHT."
Viewers, please think together
with them.
First, beatboxing A.
One, two, three, four.
Next, beatboxing B.
Two, three.
What?
This is difficult.
I can't tell.
Next, beatboxing C.
Two, three, four.
It's difficult.
This is impressive.
I can't tell.
Did the two amateurs really join?
I...
B is correct?
That's right.
Kotaro chooses B.
What do you think, Mr Show?
I think C was the one without noise.
I see.
C is the most probable one.
And you, Nakazawa?
I think it's C.
C was professional? I see.
It's professional.
I think B was the most organised.
Miss Marika?
I think B was
the professional performance,
A is the second best,
C is the worst one.
Wow.
What about you two?
I think it's B.
I think B is the professional one.
I think C is the one that
the two comedians joined.
This is bad.
Yeah?
At the studio, B is the majority,
Toshiaki Megumi,
the former music show host
who answered the quartet performance
wrong is here first.
Here he is!
He's here...
Will he agree with Mr Show?
What will he choose?
"Thinks it's C"
His answer is...
The correct answer is...
B.
I had many opportunities to listen
to professional musicians play,
so I naturally know
the sound of firstrated music.
I think B and C are tricky,
but no doubt B was done
more skilfully.
I see, it's B first.
Mr Show, you chose C,
but Megumi chose B.
Well...
What will the fate of the former
"MUSIC FAIR" host be?
"Wrong on quartet performance"
Next, Miss Fuka Koshiba, who guessed
the quartet performance right.
Here she is.
Miss Koshiba.
She got the one just now right.
We'll see where she goes to.
Yeah.
The answer she gives
after worrying about it is...
B.
It's B.
"Thinks it's B"
The part where the song ended
was very beautiful, I think.
I see.
A lovely smile.
Pretty.
Koshiba will decide whether they
stay as common celebrities or not,
she also goes to B.
You're here!
Oh!
Thank goodness!
It's really difficult, right?
It was.
Excuse me.
I had no idea.
Next, their answers on
the quartet performance agreed,
but Nogizaka46's three ladies
embarrassed themselves
by guessing it wrong.
We'll see whether you'll go
from second to thirdrated,
or lookalikes,
if they get this wrong.
Their answers are...
Wow!
This is impressive.
Wait, I've seen this before.
Yes, we have.
Isn't this bad?
This...
We saw this scene just now too.
We chose B as well.
I remember this!
I would pay to listen to B.
I know,
I want to listen to B properly.
But what happened just now...
But...
They're so pessimistic!
That's really...
Consider that too.
B was wrong last time,
so this time it's B.
Indeed.
All of them chose B.
Wait, I don't know now.
Nogizaka, Megumi got the quartet
performance wrong and chose B.
I've seen this before.
It's an awful Deja vu.
Excuse me.
You're here.
I'm happy.
We feel relieved,
We feel relieved.
but the way it goes like this
hasn't been good so far.
It looks like Megumi
is at a hostess club.
"At hostess club"
The level is high. It's expensive.
Is the correct answer A, B or C?
We'll tell everyone at the studio
the correct answer.
I'm happy.
The correct answer is...
Please be B!
B.
Yay!
That's right...
Thank goodness!
And...
The Absolutely No Room.
Okay...
C.
Thank goodness!
Thank goodness.
Everyone, did you know the answer?
The correct answer is B.
It was performed only by SARUKANI,
the famous Japanese worldclass
beatboxer group.
Professional beatboxers like us
practise every day
to improve the quality of sound.
So compared to amateurs,
besides the sound,
even the tempo and the stability
of volume are completely different.
Maybe it's bad
to have so many people.
It's a big scary.
Maybe it's a trick question.
They look worried,
but they all guessed correctly.
But later, the comedian beatboxers
will cause big drama!
Next, these four teams,
including thirdrated celebrity
Kazushige Nagashima, will be tested.
Okay...
Let's begin the test!
Now, please watch and compare it
with the comedians' performance.
Mr Shozo joins them here?
First, it's the wrong answer,
A, of which Cocorico's Endo
will do the percussion.
Three, four.
"A: wrong. 3 professionals
and Cocorico's Endo"
He's good.
Wow!
It was good...
It was good.
Impressive.
Next, the correct answer,
B, performed by the four worldclass
professionals, SARUKANI.
"B: correct. SARUKANI, second place
in international competition"
"Percussion: Kohey"
"Base: RUSY"
"Bass drum and others: KAJI"
"Trumpet and others: SOSO"
They're good.
Now that you mention it.
It's a decent performance.
Next, the absolutely no answer,
C, by Endo and Onigoe's Kinchan
who plays the bass
after practising only for two hours.
"C: absolutely no. 2 professionals,
Cocorico's Endo, Kinchan"
He's doing a lot!
This! It's this!
His breathing sound!
Oh no.
What's this?
Oh!
The participants are confused.
Kazushige probably can't tell.
He surely doesn't.
He's thinking hard.
Mr Kazushige's thinking hard.
"B: correct"
I have no idea when I listen.
It's difficult.
Will they choose
the correct answer, B?
First, also a beatboxer,
SixTONES's Mr Jesse.
Jesse!
I'm counting on you, Jesse!
If he chooses C...
His answer is...
B.
Yay!
Nice!
Brilliant.
Impressive.
Nice!
I judge by the volume
when I listen to music,
the volume of B was the most equal
and I heard every note,
and no doubt C was performed
by comedians.
Wow, this is rather good.
Impressive!
What a relief!
That's someone
who had done it before!
He successfully stays
as common celebrity.
You're here!
Wow!
Jesse!
Yay!
Welcome!
It's very lively there.
They meet up at this club.
Next, Karina, who claimed
being a fan of SARUKANI.
"Karina"
She said she listened
to their music.
Yes, it's a lucky question.
Yes, it is to her.
Yes, an easy question.
Her answer is...
I'll say it.
B.
Wow!
I'm impressed.
Impressive.
Wow, everyone answered correctly
so far.
Wow! Amazing!
Everyone chose B!
We're so happy.
Wow.
Thank goodness!
But this is also...
Yeah.
Is this okay?
But if they think about
what happened so far,
they might think
there are too many people.
I think they're a bit worried too.
Like, "Could it be..."
Seeing how it goes, it's possible.
Next, Yoshito Okubo, who had also
listened to SARUKANI.
Okay...
He's here!
It's okay, he is very confident.
Really?
He'll be okay.
He looks confident.
Secondrated or thirdrated?
Or will you become lookalikes?
It's okay.
His answer is...
A.
Oh! The first different answer!
It isn't C...
Well, it's fine.
I think they were trying a bit hard
to do B and C.
When I heard them,
I thought,
"Wow, they're making effort."
A was the easiest on the ear,
so it's this.
This...
He'll be alone when he's there.
This is awful.
It's bad to be in A alone.
It feels lonely to wait so long
on his own.
Pay attention to how he reacts
when he opens the door.
Wow! Are you kidding me?
Nobody is here?
Wow!
But it'll be impressive if you win.
You might win by yourself.
I might win alone.
You might.
Mr Kazushige, just don't choose C.
Just not C.
Well, there's a chance.
If you look at his face.
Yeah.
Lastly, it's thirdrated celebrity
Kazushige Nagashima,
who is at the end of his rope.
He'll vanish at once
if he chooses C.
Okay, it's here.
Here he is.
I hope you can stay!
He'll vanish the moment he raises
the card of C.
Oh no.
A would be good.
Do your best, Kazushige!
Do your best!
His answer is...
It's no use thinking.
Do your best!
"C: absolutely no,
2 professionals and 2 comedians"
He vanished!
Are you kidding me?
He messed up!
We've vanished now?
Are you kidding me?
I thought the voltage of C was high
at last.
He is sure.
This is bad.
It's unexpected.
Mr Kotaro Koizumi has vanished.
Nagashima vanished,
so this time, Hollywood Zakoshisyoh
will play him exaggeratedly.
Is it this room?
What? No one is here. I messed up...
I don't want to be on my own.
Hello.
Everyone chose B?
It's interesting!
Okubo!
We're in different rooms.
This is fine.
"Nagashima"
I don't know anymore.
The fateful announcement
of the result!
Oh jeez!
I'll vanish if it's the worst one.
I give up.
He's already vanished
and became Zakoshi,
but please enjoy his own
nervous facial expression.
Here I am!
Okay!
"Useless praying"
Please come!
Please!
We can't lose this fight.
"Futile expectation"
I'll first open the door of the room
that makes you go down one rank.
That's what he does?
"A: wrong"
I see!
That's right.
I'll be happy with that.
Let's do it.
Wait...
Don't come here...
"C: absolutely no"
Oh, I knew it.
Thank goodness it's one rank down.
One.
Yes. Thank goodness!
Oh, I knew it.
Thank goodness it's one rank down.
One.
Yes. Thank goodness!
What?
It's one rank down...
It's either B or C!
Oh no!
It's us.
What?
Thank goodness!
You go down one rank,
but you're hanging in there.
But I'm happy.
It can't be helped.
I'll open the door
of the correct answer's room.
It has to be B!
If I don't open your door,
you go down two ranks.
Let's do it.
He'll come...
Sorry, Kotaro!
Congratulations!
Yay!
"C: absolutely no"
What?
Kotaro, sorry, I messed up...
Team Nagashima And Koizumi
from great families
got all the answers wrong today.
There are two more questions,
but they've already disappeared.
Everyone, what a fight, oh?
Oh?
Hang on.
They vanished.
You can't see our forms?
No.
Because you aren't here.
We'll disappear?
You have disappeared.
We've disappeared?
It's too early. I wish you would
stay for longer.
But there are two more questions.
Everyone, think carefully.
It is the Koizumi Family
and the Nagashima Family.
This is bad.
The moment Mr Kazushige raised C,
the whole crew
buried their heads in their hands.
Yes, indeed!
I felt so restless.
Exactly.
What do you guys think?
Will you make the Koizumi Family
and the Nagashima Family
your enemies?
Absolutely not...
Not at all.
Let's restore them
to lookalikes first,
they'll vanish if they get the next
one wrong. It can't be helped.
But is it okay to give them grace?
That's what I want to ask.
What do you think?
Are you not happy?
But it's the rule, so no.
I think it's okay, though.
Hang on.
No...
Oda, you're nice!
Kogaken! Kogaken said no.
I'm just playing dumb, obviously!
Koga, I'll make it clear.
My dad and the Koizumi Family's dad
are influencing Japan.
Wait!
That's...
No, that's...
None of us can afford
to make them our enemies.
Yeah...
We'll restore you to lookalikes,
is that okay?
Thank you!
You're lookalikes,
Okay!
so do an impression of them.
Yes! What would you like?
So we'll show their faces for now.
Camera six.
Okay, please do it.
How about this?
Who's that?
Impression of my dad.
Please come back!
It's our special rule!
Team Nagashima and Koizumi
makes a comeback!
But you'll vanish
if your answer is wrong next time.
Of course!
I'm sorry.
We'll stand.
Yes, please.
I'm happy!
Okay, let's do our next test!
Test five is this.
"Coloured carp"
It's coloured carp.
This...
coloured carp is called Swimming
Jewels and Japan's national fish.
Since they originated 200 years ago,
they've been undergoing
selective breeding
to create coloured carps
that are even more beautiful.
Nowadays, the coloured carps
Japan is proud of
are loved by about 50 countries.
We'll check whether the participants
are good judges or not.
The correct answer is a coloured
carp that costs 3 million yen.
3 million!
That's right.
If it wins on a competitive show,
the promising coloured carp might
cost over 10 million yen.
That's right.
The wrong answer is
a very ordinary coloured carp,
which costs 10,000 yen.
That's right.
Spot the difference.
It costs 3 million yen currently.
Yes.
And 10,000 yen.
This time, we have the cooperation
of TANI FISH FARM.
Its scale is the largest
in the Kanto region.
The coloured carp are kept in
a place as big as Tokyo Dome,
and there are 100,000 carp.
Among them, we prepared
the three representative species,
Taisho Sanshoku and Showa Sanshoku.
They should know the topclass
3 million yen carp at a glance.
Please announce the representatives.
From Team Yokai Housemate,
Miss Marika Matsumoto.
Thank you.
This one?
From Team Soccer, Yuji Nakazawa.
Okay, thank you.
No honorific?
I see, I'm thirdrated.
From Team Nagashima and Koizumi,
the guy who looks like
Kotaro Koizumi.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
The other participants are as shown.
Team Nagashima and Koizumi came back
by special favour,
so don't vanish again!
Okay, first,
common celeb, Miss Matsumoto.
It's 10,000 yen and 3 million yen?
There's no way I'll get it wrong.
Right? Okay.
I think they'll look
totally different.
I'll know the moment I see it.
"Ha!"
Sorry.
Why are you laughing?
Nagashima!
Why do you laugh?
He looks more like
Kazushige Nagashima.
Is this okay?
Okay, and...
You really look like him.
Thank you.
Amazing.
You look exactly like him.
I'll put this on you.
You look so like him!
Thank you.
This isn't Mr Koizumi himself.
How about this, Mr Lookalike?
Well...
I haven't answered
one question correctly.
He said it.
Yes, this team lost every time.
I'll choose the correct answer
and pass to Mr Kazushige's...
lookalike.
We want to do one more question.
Yes.
I'll get this one.
Okay, representatives, please come!
To the room and stand by.
The one that impresses you!
That's right! Okay.
I'll go with my instinct,
without thinking too much.
Isn't Kotaro amazing?
He got all of them wrong.
Me too.
What?
I also failed twice in a row.
They both lost every time.
I can't believe this...
I'm shocked.
Two kinds of coloured carp
are standing by here at A and B.
They'll come in pairs
to observe the carp carefully.
First, Kotaro Koizumi's lookalike,
who can't afford to vanish again,
and secondrated celebrity
Show Aikawa.
"Show Aikawa"
Kotaro, I'm counting on you!
Yeah, this one matters.
I want to do one more question.
They'll take turns to look
at the carp for 30 seconds each.
Our viewers will start from A.
"Coloured carp A"
It's beautiful.
Next, B.
"Coloured carp B"
3 million yen.
There's no way I'll know.
Oh...
Please compare the two carp
at last.
This one is beautiful too.
This is difficult.
What do you think, Mr Megumi?
I think it's B.
Oh, I see.
And you, Jesse?
I also think it's B.
A moves like it's looking for food.
A carp that costs 3 million yen
won't do that.
Come on! You don't know that!
The orange part of B is larger,
it somehow fascinates me,
but I'll outwit them and choose A.
What will Kotaro choose, then?
First, Kotaro Koizumi's lookalike,
who really is
at the end of his rope.
Kotaro, choose A!
We'll remove you mercilessly
if you're wrong.
His answer is...
This.
"Coloured carp B"
I think it's B.
Oh...
It's B.
B.
Different from yours.
They are both swimming leisurely,
they have the vibes too.
"Poot"
Are you okay?
You fart now?
Now?
Coloured carp B...
Do you call it classy?
I felt something like that.
I missed half of that.
Exactly.
The sound of his fart.
Whose fault is this?
Mr Hamada!
Do your job properly!
I'm sorry.
He said B...
How can the host fart?
Okay, I want to see Mr Hamada
at the end.
Will this be Kotaro's
first correct answer today?
Or will he vanish again?
Who Is The Real Celebrity BASIC,
threehour programme in spring!
The spring grading consists of
super basic tests that
they should obviously guess right.
The Spring Grading consists of tests
on basic knowledge they should know.
The correct answer is...
For example,
in the string quartet performance,
they'll compare the most expensive
musical instrument
to one that lacks a string.
The tasting test
is also a basic test
on comparing the finest quality
squid to Kanetsu Delica Foods'
unreleased product, Hobohobo Ika,
which is made with fish paste.
Are you kidding me?
Of course, if they get it wrong,
their rank will go down
and vanish from the screen
at the end, so be careful!
Next, secondrated actor
Big Bro Aikawa,
who didn't even know
the taste of hamburger steak.
Mr Show must be good at this.
He looks at rhinoceros beetles
all the time.
Rhinoceros beetle and coloured carp
are different.
They are. I mean, he would look
at living creatures.
His answer is...
The correct answer is A.
Oh? It's different.
It's different.
They're different.
The black of A was vivid.
I see.
Somehow it looks
more attractive to me.
They've chosen different answers
already. A and B.
They're different already.
What will happen?
Their opinions are already divided.
Oh... This is the first time
I enter Room A.
Mr Show chose A?
"Worried"
Go somewhere easier to see.
The remaining five teams
will do the test together.
Coloured carp B is indeed...
Next, coloured carp B.
"Coloured carp B"
It's hard to tell.
This is...
"Waiting room B"
Failed twice in a row
personally today,
Ryuta Sato hasn't performed well.
Which one will he choose?
Which one?
His answer is...
This is the correct answer.
B.
It is much more radiant.
It wasn't only
the carp in the water,
the whole zone B... what is it?
The atmosphere was different.
Someone who got two questions wrong
is really unconvincing.
Kotaro too.
Yes, indeed.
Now, the two gentlemen who got
two wrong answers in a row are in B.
Hello.
Oh, wow!
Oh, wow...
Well...
"Waiting room A"
But you haven't gotten any right.
Exactly.
You can't say thank you.
We lost together just now too.
Is the three million yen
coloured carp A or B?
Now, we'll tell everyone in
the studio the correct answer.
Wait, I will vanish now?
That's right.
Yes.
If he got it wrong.
The correct answer is...
B.
Yes!
Kotaro!
Thank goodness.
Kotaro...
You made it, Kotaro!
As expected.
You guys will stay.
Mr Kazushige continues to be
a lookalike.
Did you know the answer?
B is the correct answer,
the three million yen coloured carp.
A good carp needs to have
a symmetrical body,
and it swims beautifully.
Regarding the pattern, there should
be black spots on the white body.
This is the secret of a good carp.
I haven't
answered one right, either.
I'm gradually
losing selfconfidence.
I've got none.
Why do I feel defeated?
Don't worry.
You answered correctly this time.
On the other hand, poor
Team Kagoshima falls to thirdrate.
I got all five questions wrong.
Impressive.
"Thirdrated"
We have one more thirdrated team.
Next, Oideyasu Koga will decide
if the team will stay secondrated.
Okay, here they are.
Their opinions will probably
be divided.
Will they choose B?
Ready, go.
See? They're divided.
Oh, not this.
Give the correct answer.
The first one I saw? Okay. Sorry.
The expensive one?
Yes.
What?
Gosh!
Why?
He scared me.
The fin of B was white,
and the texture was fine.
It was very beautiful.
The two carp were totally different.
You're safe.
Thank goodness!
Nogizaka is safe.
They stay secondrated.
They almost got it wrong
for a second
but managed to correct it.
Yes!
Thank you!
I don't think you're happy, though.
Don't say that...
Nice. It's lively there.
"Worried"
I think Mr Show hasn't given up.
Or he wouldn't sit like that.
Indeed. He's sitting like that.
"A: wrong"
Three teams answered B so far,
and Miss Marika Matsumoto
wants to stay "common."
Here she is.
If she goes to B,
she'll stay as common celeb.
What does the lady think?
Her answer is...
It's B.
Why don't you say A?
When I saw B, what is it?
Something... The aura was different.
You're safe.
Yes.
Common. Common celebrity.
Amazing. Yes.
Wow.
Impressive.
Now four teams besides Aikawa
answered correctly.
Oh!
It really is this!
As I thought.
Good...
Nice. It's lively there.
I'm sorry...
Sorry, Senior.
We didn't mean it.
Well, you would naturally
be excited.
Mr Show is getting a bit worried.
He got a bit worried.
"Rather worried"
Will our lonely Big Bro
get any friends?
Next, common celebrity,
SixTONES's Mr Kochi.
It's him.
Kochi.
This matters a lot.
Which one will he choose?
The three million yen
coloured carp is...
B.
Yes!
Wow!
They impress me.
Kochi has answered many correctly.
They all impress me.
Okay, it's one against five now.
Wow!
Good...
Welcome.
"Hopeless"
Will Show Aikawa fail on his own?
Next, it's Yuji Nakazawa.
He doesn't know at all.
He doesn't.
He doesn't know.
Will he choose
the correct answer, B? Now, come!
The three million yen carp is...
B.
Nice!
What?
Nice.
Wow, he guessed right.
Amazing!
Wow, everyone besides Aikawa
answered correctly.
Yay!
This has to be the correct answer!
"A: wrong"
Well, I had no idea it would make me
feel so worried on my own.
The fateful announcement
of the result.
Here I am!
"Celeb Master enters the room
of the correct answer"
I want just one correct answer.
Yeah.
Really.
That's right.
The correct answer is...
"Has not given up yet"
Please...
What...?
No...
Congratulations!
Yes!
We made it! We made it!
Yay!
Yay! Yay!
Congratulations!
Your life is saved.
The last one.
Good for you.
You can now go to do
the last question.
Darn it!
It's so annoying.
Now, everyone, the gentleman
who got it wrong is back.
"Wrong answer entrance"
I'm sorry.
"I'm sorry"
He's going to perform harakiri.
I admit defeat.
Thank you.
Thanks, really.
Big Bro Show, you only know
about rhinoceros beetles!
Let's do our last test!
This is the last test.
"Deepfried squid"
Deepfried squid.
"Lookalike"
Celebrities taste and compare
expensive beef in the New Year,
but this is the basics,
so you'll taste deepfried squid,
the common folks' dish
everyone likes.
That's right.
There'll be three options,
A, B, and C, in this test.
What? Again?
Again?
Make it two!
Give us only two options!
I have to choose among three.
This is the last question.
Listen carefully.
First, the correct deepfried squid
is made with fresh squid
from Toyama Prefecture.
Looks delicious!
This is the correct answer.
The wrong deepfried squid is made
with imported frozen squid.
The one
you absolutely shouldn't choose
isn't even squid.
Not squid?
Please come forward!
"Come forward"?
What does that mean?
Hello!
This is the Hobo Series'
manufacturer,
Kanetetsu Delica Foods'
official character, Tecchan.
Kanetetsu.
I think some of you know
Kanetetsu Delica Foods
has been selling HoboKani,
which tastes like crab but isn't,
and other products.
And this time, you'll try...
Hobohobo Ika.
There are two "hobo"?
Two times "hobo."
Like HoboKani,
it is made with fish paste.
To sum up, it's fish paste cake.
Fish paste cake!
It's not squid.
The developer isn't confident,
so it hasn't been commercialised.
What?
That's right.
If this time
it can deceive even one person,
the product will be commercialised.
Wow!
The day you choose Hobohobo Ika...
It's only fish paste cake.
Taste and compare real squid
and fish paste cake,
and choose the right one
in this easy question.
You almost can't be wrong!
Common celebrities will be promoted
to firstrated if they get it right.
Yes!
If you can stay "common" till here,
you're already firstrated.
You'll be firstrated
if you answer correctly.
But Mr Hamada...
If you choose Hobohobo Ika,
you'll vanish.
What? Why?
What? Just once?
At once?
If you get it right,
you're firstrated.
If it's wrong, you vanish.
It's so harsh!
These are the representatives.
They'll be awfully embarrassed
if they disappear.
So please don't disappear!
Okay, go to do the last question!
Representative, please!
Let's be firstrated!
We'll be firstrated.
Please do your best.
Wow, it's fun.
Now, everyone. The last question.
I'll tell you
the correct answer now.
Beforehand?
It'll make us so nervous!
It's fun!
The correct deepfried squid is...
C.
If a common celeb chooses it,
they'll be back to firstrated.
That's what it is?
C is correct.
Now, "absolutely no."
The Hobohobo Ika.
Hobohobo Ika.
B.
I see.
Frozen is A.
Knowing this,
let's have a drink together.
The best thing to go with sake.
That's right.
You'll vanish at once if you
choose B, so don't choose it.
Promise me. Promise!
The first one here is...
Thank you.
Mr Kazushige Nagashima's lookalike,
who had vanished once
and is at the end of his rope.
It has started.
We start from Mr Kazushige?
Mr Kazushige is here first.
Right away!
He has to choose C
for this team to stay.
Only C for you.
Only C.
You'll vanish the moment
he raises the card of A or B.
Not even A.
That's right, not even A.
They're already lookalikes.
You can't go down further.
First, it makes them go down
one rank and disappear.
The frozen squid...
"A: wrong"
Mr Kazushige always eats good food.
I can't tell.
He can't tell.
Wait...
It's something he usually eats.
That's right.
Then, Hobohobo Ika,
which isn't squid.
He has to know this.
"B: absolutely no"
They must be totally different.
It's not commercialised.
It's fish paste cake.
What?
It doesn't feel wrong?
Now, C.
Correct answer, the expensive squid.
Just choose this!
It's only C.
You can only choose this.
I can't decide. Which one is it?
From Toyama Prefecture...
Say C, and you'll be right.
Comefrombehind.
Mr Kazushige, C! You can do it!
Vanish if he says A or B.
I'll pluck up my courage.
Will we see Zakoshi again,
or will he stay? His answer is...
The squid from Toyama is...
C.
Wow!
Amazing!
They survived!
Impressive!
Amazing!
Thank you!
You survived!
It isn't the taste.
It's the texture.
C was the chewy one.
Impressive!
Amazing!
You each got one right.
I hit it once,
and he did a home run.
Amazing!
Oh, someone, please come.
I feel lonely.
This is a miracle. Amazing!
He got his first correct answer
today at last.
Next, it's Toshiaki Megumi,
who wants to hang on to thirdrate.
Mr Megumi. I'm worried!
Mr Megumi.
First, the frozen squid that
makes him go down one rank.
I don't want to be
a lookalike, either.
Indeed.
As the host of a daytime show,
he can't afford to mistake
fish paste cake for expensive squid.
"C: correct"
Megumi, do it! Megumi!
What will he choose?
Say B, Megumi!
Don't say B, no matter what.
Do it, Megumi! Do it!
The expensive deepfried squid...
Do it...
is C.
Yes!
Wow!
Amazing!
It's correct, so they stay
as thirdrated celebrities.
It was the most chewy one.
As a strategy,
the hardest one is probably
the most expensive, in fact.
Wonderful.
Amazing.
You stay as thirdrated.
Megumi barely stays as thirdrated
and goes to C, where Mr Kazushige's
lookalike is waiting.
Oh!
Bye.
Oh, wait!
He closed it.
He thought it was over.
Oh?
You chose the same as me.
You're in trouble.
This is bad!
It is.
But they answered it correctly.
That said,
they're supposed to be right.
"Worried but correct"
Next, thirdrated former
Japan national football team player,
Yoshito Okubo.
I can't see at all.
It feels right. Let's do it.
We start with a feint,
the wrong answer, frozen squid.
You'll be lookalikes at once
if he chooses this.
I've repeated many times.
Hobohobo Ika
hasn't been commercialised.
There's no way they can mistake it
for the real thing.
"C: correct"
Okay, do it.
I'm counting on you!
Choose B!
Not B!
Choose B.
Will he score the correct goal?
It's A.
Oh.
"A: wrong"
What's wrong?
Mr Nakazawa!
He went for the tepid one.
We wish he'd just do it.
C was very chewy,
but I won't be deceived.
No...
They didn't deceive you.
But A should be just delicious.
A must be just delicious.
Okubo becomes a lookalike now.
I'll go in.
Oh, no one is here yet.
But I'm sure it's A.
It has to be A.
He is very confident,
but everything was halfbaked.
The next one is...
Thank you.
Miss Karina.
I'm counting on you.
She'll be okay.
I'll do my best.
Secondrated celebrity, Karina,
who has personally won
twice in a row today.
I got the imitation crab wrong.
Imitation crab is delicious!
It is.
So I'd like to try again.
That's right.
She chose HoboKani by mistake,
but she won't choose Hobohobo Ika
by mistake, too, right?
It's a revenge match this time.
Yes.
Choose Hobohobo Ika.
First, a bite of the wrong answer,
frozen squid.
"A: wrong"
You'll become thirdrated
if she chooses this.
This is the Hobohobo Ika
she mustn't choose.
"B: absolutely no"
What?
She likes imitation crab.
She's impressed and wowed.
I'm at risk, am I not?
She won't choose the Hobo Series
again, right?
You're eating the correct answer.
It's this one.
Choose this.
Expensive squid.
Okay.
Wow!
Surprisingly readily.
You never know.
Say B!
Choose B.
She'll say B.
Her answer is...
B.
What?
Are you kidding me?
Really?
She vanished!
Are you kidding me?
They vanished!
It's imitation crab!
Only B has an obvious sweetness.
The flavour also exploded in
my mouth after I ate it, so it's B.
Karina really can't do
the Hobo Series.
Yeah.
Her taste buds love the Hobo Series.
Replacing actress Karina, who is
enchanted by the Hobo Series...
Okazu Club's Okarina will play her.
"Karina is played
by Okazu Club's Okarina"
"B: absolutely no"
No one is here!
"Karina"
Are you kidding me?
Oh, Miss Karina.
Karina.
Ah! No way!
Yeah, we all chose differently.
But wasn't B sweet when you ate it?
It totally will be
commercialised now.
They've decided to sell it.
It's true.
It will be commercialised.
They should use Miss Karina
to advertise it.
It's delicious.
People will buy it.
"Karina"
Now, keep deceiving other people
and make the product a big hit!
Next...
Now, it's them!
They're here!
I see!
We're counting on you!
Get tricked by B!
Their opinions have agreed no matter
if it was right or wrong today,
Nogizawa46.
"Team Idols and Comedians"
Raise B together.
Will they disappear too?
Raise B.
At least have divided opinions.
They are united.
They said they were close.
Maybe their tastes are similar.
It feels so right.
No, it doesn't.
Look at this.
She's in a bit of a bad mood.
It feels right on them all.
Please!
Mr Akimoto, are you watching?
Nogizaka's members won't mistake
fish paste cake for squid, right?
Choose B.
Okay!
Not B.
Choose B at once.
Make a miracle.
No.
Don't all choose B. Please.
Choose B.
Okay!
Not B.
Choose B at once.
Don't.
Their answers are...
"Absolutely no"
We're different.
Oh no!
Hang on!
Yes!
Hang in there!
Miss Saito!
It's B!
I couldn't choose between B and C,
but C tasted like the frozen thing
I usually order.
That's right.
Stop talking!
Don't say anything!
I think the texture of C
was the firmest,
so I thought it was frozen.
B tasted fresher than that.
That's Hobohobo Ika!
Senior! Miss Saito!
It's B!
Beat them up!
Beat them up, Miss Saito!
But you two chose B.
But you're our senior.
No, it's fine.
I can't take the responsibility.
We'll choose B.
Yes!
No!
Just not that one!
Not that one!
Bye, Oideyasu Koga.
This is bad!
This is getting exciting.
Okay!
Senior, you can't do that!
Not this!
Replacing the vanished idols
we can't meet,
Zakoshizaka46 will play them.
"Hollywood Zakoshisyoh
plays them exaggeratedly"
"Yamashita, Saito, Yoda"
I'm scared.
"Karina"
Miss Karina is here!
"Saito, Yoda"
Come here.
Come here... Thank goodness.
I'm happy!
I feel a bit relieved.
But everyone is different.
Wow, really!
Yeah.
It's hard to say.
Two teams vanished in a row.
Among the drama,
common celebrity, Mr Jesse, who may
be back to firstrated, is next.
But now it's better to choose
either C or B.
Rather than the halfbaked A.
That's right.
First, it's A,
that puts them one rank down
and very halfbaked on TV.
"A: wrong"
He's laughing.
Wow, delicious!
Right? It's delicious,
even if it's frozen.
Next, Hobohobo Ika,
which makes him vanish at once.
What?
That's right. Jesse,
your reaction is correct!
Yes!
It is what you taste first.
It's delicious!
I'm scared!
That one just now is bad!
That "delicious" just now was bad!
This is bad.
That's the "delicious" he says
when he eats something delicious.
This is bad!
Yeah, they're all delicious.
"Saito, Karina, Yoda, Yamashita"
Then, the correct answer,
expensive squid, which lets him
return to firstrated
if he chooses it.
Firstrated or vanish.
Please, Jesse, let's be firstrated.
They're clearly different?
What will happen now?
Please!
C or B? C or B?
Say B!
Firstrated!
Come here.
His answer is...
I'll choose.
A!
What?
Hey!
Not interesting at all!
Go all the way wrong!
Not funny at all.
Whoa...
A is the worst choice.
What the heck?
It's the most balanced one.
It was neither soft nor hard,
how about that?
Look at this guy.
He's not funny at all.
Jesse caused an incident
in every sense
and falls to secondrated celebrity.
"A: wrong"
Mr Okubo.
Oh, thank goodness!
I feel really relieved.
Really? Are you kidding me?
Wow.
It's A?
What...?
Well, now it all depends
on Miss Koshiba.
That's right. We'll see if you can
become firstrated.
We hope she can really make it.
We definitely want her to.
The last one is...
Miss Koshiba, we're counting on you!
It depends on her now.
It also depends on
common celebrity Miss Fuka Koshiba
to bring them back to firstrated.
Let's return to firstrated
glamorously.
C will bring them
back to firstrated.
First, the halfbaked one rank down,
frozen squid.
I think she'll think it's delicious.
The girl came from
the Kansai region.
Everything is delicious.
Next, it's fish paste,
and not squid.
"B: absolutely no"
Oh, girls like it.
No, Fuka.
Well, Karina chose it.
Both Karina and Nogizaka chose it.
All the beautiful ladies.
No, not this...
"Hobo Karina"
And the correct answer, C.
You only need to choose this.
I hope she'll return
to firstrated, though!
Okay!
She can't decide.
I'm so nervous!
Now...
Just don't say A.
C or B.
A is the most boring.
Don't say it's boring.
Directly.
It's C. It's C.
Her answer is...
C or B. C or B.
"A: wrong"
What...?
Are you kidding me?
I think the taste of B
was the richest.
Oh!
C was also rather chewy.
I think frozen squid
is rather chewy,
so I chose A by elimination.
The last common celebrity we had
high hopes for was the most boring.
It was boring.
She was serious...
Yeah, it can't be helped.
Well...
"Halfbaked secondrated"
In the end, she goes down to
the most boring secondrated.
Hey, welcome.
I worried nobody would be here!
Welcome!
We're both common, right?
That's right.
Thank goodness someone is here!
Jesse, you think C is frozen, right?
Yes.
Karina, you too?
Well, I thought C tasted like
frozen squid.
Which one was fish paste,
Miss Karina? C?
I think Hobohobo Ika is A.
It's your room.
This conversation is funny!
I want to keep listening to it.
"Saito, Karina, Yoda, Yamashita"
The fateful announcement
of the result!
I want to get the last one right.
End with a correct answer.
They've already vanished,
but please enjoy the nervous looks
on their own faces.
Here I am!
Please!
I'll open the door of
the correct answer's room, but...
I'll first open the door of the room
that makes you go down one rank.
Go down one rank?
I see.
I see...
It's C, right?
Don't open it...
No!
It's C, right?
I think it's C.
"B: absolutely no"
Don't come here.
I'm scared.
"C: correct"
The room that makes you
go down one rank is...
Oh!
Please leave.
No way!
You aren't interesting at all.
What?
"A: wrong"
Oh!
Please leave.
No way!
You aren't interesting at all.
What?
This is the room
you go down one rank.
Frozen?
This is frozen?
It's frozen?
What?
A is one rank down?
Thank goodness!
I'm scared...
It's either one, right?
No way!
We're either correct or we vanish.
Two ranks?
I'll open the door
of the correct answer's room.
No...
If I don't open your door,
you'll vanish!
Let's do it!
Let's vanish.
Yeah.
The correct answer is...
Voom!
"C: correct"
"B: absolutely no"
Congratulations!
Wow!
Really?
Hamachan, I finally see you!
Congratulations!
Wow!
Really? Really?
Hamachan, I finally see you!
"Saito, Karina, Yoda, Yamashita"
Oh!
I already gave up.
It smells like old people here.
Yeah.
Old people smell
is in the atmosphere.
Everyone in B has vanished now.
They've vanished?
We've vanished!
Ryuta, I'm sorry!
But it was delicious!
It was delicious.
Big drama!
Spring storm raged,
every team is secondrate or below,
not to mention firstrated.
It's not fun!
Okay, all the tests have been done,
let's have a look at the result.
Two teams
of secondrated celebrities.
Thank you.
One team of thirdrated celebs.
Two teams of lookalikes.
Yes!
And... not here!
Not here!
It's cleaner now.
No common
and firstrated celebrities.
What's wrong with this episode?
This team didn't look like
they would disappear.
No.
Indeed.
Miss Karina, what... what the heck?
The Hobo Series suits my taste buds.
I'm amazed.
It was delicious.
They are all delicious.
Nogizaka too.
What was that?
I think Miss Yamashita and Miss Yoda
should listen to other people.
I'm sorry!
But you were saved once, came back,
got one right, and passed the baton.
I passed him the baton,
and he successfully got it right.
You stay here as lookalikes.
I think we'd win
if there were six more tests.
No, we would be exhausted.
It's too long.
Don't vanish this time
in the MiniGrading.
First, red wine.
The correct answer is...
No way!
I...
Next, a string quartet performance.
They sound the same.
Yeah.
The correct answer is...
Wait...
And the hamburger steak
with testicles mixed.
The correct answer is...
Yes!
Wow!
Beatboxing.
The correct answer is...
Yay!
Yes!
I'm so happy.
See?
Can they stay as secondrated?
It's coloured carp.
We're different.
The fins are strong,
if they look weak...
No, it's the pattern.
The correct answer is...
Yes!
It matters.
Right?
Last one, deepfried squid.
You'll vanish at once if you say B!
Their answers are...
Yay!
Oh, he vanished!
You vanished! You vanished!
It shows the bad parts of me.