Who Is The Real Celebrity,
an autumn of food and art,
three hour special programme!
Our firstclass celebrities
have gathered here again.
They'll identify firstclass items
like wine and musical instruments,
but it's autumn now, so we'll do
a very simple check on food and art.
You'll naturally answer
all the questions correctly.
They're watching closely.
Our viewers.
They'll say...
"They don't know something
so simple?"
First, it's Team Bigwig,
Mr Koji Ishizaka, Ms Mariko Kaga.
Are you confident?
No.
No?
You disappeared once.
I see.
But how about Ms Kaga?
Ms Kaga has never paid,
so she doesn't know the price.
I want to say it once!
Senior and junior of
the same agency, Team K Dash,
Mr Masaaki Sakai
and Mr Katsunori Takahashi.
I have a lot of experience.
That's right.
I think I'm going to answer
many questions correctly,
and break the record.
Good, that's good.
Right?
And you, Mr Takahashi? There's
a chance you'll make him fall.
That's the role I play today.
You shouldn't! Give it your all.
Yeah.
Team Doctor X, Miss Ryoko Yonekura
and Mr Masanobu Katsumura.
You had disappeared as well...
We had.
Are you confident this time?
But...
Compared to last time.
I've accumulated much experience.
Of course.
Probably...
You can probably do it?
I guess we can.
I guess we can?
Team Visual Kei.
Mr DAIGO, Mr Sho Kiryuin.
Mr DAIGO.
To put it simply, it's ZI.
ZI...
What does it mean?
Zettai Ichiryu,
Absolutely Firstclass.
And you, Mr Kiryuin?
Talk more about it...
It's fine. Are you confident?
I came here with Mr GACKT last time.
The pressure...
At that time,
The pressure from Mr GACKT
was great,
the atmosphere will be cheerful
if I'm here with Mr DAIGO.
Wait, you're teasing Mr GACKT!
Absolutely not!
Really?
I'll answer all questions right.
Okay.
Next, three members
from Johnny's form
Team Gymnastics World
and Vanishing My First Love.
Well, Johnny's...
That's right.
They do everything skilfully.
Our senior, Chinen is here,
so there's a pressure
we have to get everything right.
But he doesn't look reliable at all.
I am obviously reliable.
I can do it.
You'll survive?
We will.
Two actors in the spotlight now,
Team The Words They Speak,
Miss Nanase Nishino,
Mr Kento Nagayama.
Who is the leader?
Miss Nishino...
What? Me?
He's my senior in every way.
That's right.
But I heard our seniors...
had gone through things like that,
so I'm a bit nervous.
They look important, but they
disappeared. So do your best.
I want to keep the fluffy slippers.
Please do your best.
Team Comediennes And Idols,
Borujuku and Sakurazaka46.
Maybe you'll be fine
if it's just the three of you,
but you've also got those three.
It's food today, right?
It's possible that
only we will survive.
We'll be fine.
I'm sorry, but it won't look good
if only you three survive.
It's okay, just show Tanabe, then.
Only her.
Wait...
Zoom in at me.
The theme of this episode
is an autumn of food and art,
so we've prepared various tests
about autumnal things like food,
music and painting.
They'll distinguish the pro
from the amateur
in the Taiko Drum performance.
Wow!
You're in high school?
Yes, students from
Japan Aviation High School.
Wonderful.
Amazing.
The high school students
will compete with the pro,
the performance of their souls
will cause drama!
If they answer the questions wrong,
their rank will fall immediately
till they reach the abyss,
and disappear at the end.
Let's start now!
This is the first test.
Have a look!
It's matsutake mushroom.
It's food in autumn.
That's right, matsutake mushroom
is the symbol of autumn food,
you'll try
a matsutake mushroom Dobin Mushi
and a soup that tastes like
matsutake mushroom,
but without any used.
You'll compare the two
and tell us which one is real.
For the correct Dobin Mushi,
expensive matsutake mushroom
from Iwate Prefecture
that costs 12,000 yen
per 100 grams is used.
The other one is an instant
matsutakelike soup
that used artificial flavouring
to imitate the flavour of matsutake.
You'll just distinguish the real one
from the instant one.
It's easy.
That's right.
They will be the representatives.
Just so you know,
if you get it wrong,
you'll be too embarrassed
to walk outside.
Okay, representatives,
please go to the waiting room.
Thank you.
Do your best...
Please go from the door there.
See you.
I hope no chair will be changed
when they come back.
Is it okay to let her go first?
I'm a bit worried,
but she looks like matsutake
mushroom in the outfit today.
Oh, stop it!
The first contestant is this lady
in her matsutake mushroom outfit.
It's Miss Yonekura.
She eats lots of delicious things.
Of course.
It's the first one, so it matters.
What?
Is it okay?
Probably.
You're okay?
Okay, let's go.
First, it's A.
She checks the rising aroma
very carefully.
I think I already know.
"Dobin Mushi A"
You definitely shouldn't hesitate.
Mr Katsumura, does the look
on her face say she knows?
She's already at a loss.
I wish I could do this.
Next, it's B.
"Dobin Mushi B"
She keeps smelling it.
She finally drinks it.
She was afraid to drink it.
Oh?
Okay, she tried both A and B,
which one will she hold up?
What?
May I?
Her answer is...
This!
Oh, B...
B wasn't very fragrant...
Wait, should I choose
the fragrant one?
Am I deceived like that?
This is bad.
She is totally at a loss.
If I can choose...
it'd be B.
What's that?
Why does she choose like that?
"It'd be B."
The lady who never fails chose B
after hesitating for a long time.
I'll go in.
I'm the first one,
so nobody is here.
It feels good. I'll have a seat.
"She can watch
the other people's tests"
She'll watch the other people
on a monitor here,
and wait for the result
to be announced.
Next, it's this gentleman.
Okay, the next one
is Mr Katsunori Takahashi.
Katsunori, you can do it!
Katsunori, pick the right one.
His toned body doesn't look like
a 56yearold's,
firstclass actor
Mr Katsunori Takahashi
can still do action scenes.
I haven't tried Dobin Mushi
many times.
I've been to many
good restaurants, though.
Of course.
Yes.
But you'll fall together
if you fail.
That's...
Even if you say that to me...
It's the first time I see Katsunori
so nervous.
Oh?
I feel sorry for him.
His teammate
is much more senior than him
in his agency and showbiz,
so Mr Takahashi can't afford
to downgrade him.
So quick.
Taste it.
It looks like he's drinking sake.
Isn't he drinking too much?
He should taste sip by sip...
Drink water. Water!
Right?
He's a bit careless.
Yeah.
Drink water.
He isn't going to drink any.
Drink water!
You're so noisy!
Without resetting his taste buds,
he goes on to try B.
"Dobin Mushi B"
He just drank B.
I see.
It'll be cool if he guesses right.
The taste is delicate.
He drinks the water now.
What's the point
of drinking water now?
His answer is...
Oh!
"Dobin Mushi B"
Thank goodness.
"Feels relieved"
The taste of B is a bit peculiar.
So I think it's this.
I see,
Miss Yonekura feels relieved too.
Someone will go there.
I see, to the room, right?
It'd make her nervous
if their answers were different.
Here it comes! Salary Man Kintaro
joins Michiko Daimon!
Oh...
Thank goodness!
Oh, I see...
No?
I thought it would be B.
I think it's here too.
Right?
By the way, Ryoko Yonekura
disappeared last time.
Yeah.
Next, it's this lady.
It's Miss Kaga.
Oh? Here she is.
I'm somehow nervous.
Proves that you're alive.
After she debuted at 17 years old,
firstclass actress Ms Mariko Kaga
had been active at the forefront
for 60 years.
Ms Kaga,
matsutake mushroom Dobin Mushi...
I'm very confident.
Whether it's artificial or not...
Obviously.
The very confident Ms Kaga
tries A first.
"Dobin Mushi A"
Somehow...
Maybe she hadn't
tried it a lot before?
She's been smelling it.
Maybe.
Ms Kaga seems sure about it.
Next, it's B,
which currently outnumbers A.
"Dobin Mushi B"
Oh?
What will she choose?
What?
Which one will Ms Kaga hold up?
Her answer is...
"Dobin Mushi B"
Wow...
It's B.
Everyone chooses B.
Yes!
It was difficult,
but this one was more awful.
What? She said something serious.
It was awful.
She held up the one she thought
was real and said it was awful.
Wow!
It was the first time.
The sharptongued actress
Mariko Kaga also chooses B.
Thank goodness!
It must be this.
Yeah.
We're okay.
Thank goodness,
I hope we all guessed right.
They all chose B because
there was no decisive factor.
It is going to be dramatic.
"Dramatic from question 1"
His grandfather
is a former prime minister,
his wife is Keiko Kitagawa,
firstclass celebrity Mr DAIGO
is from a grand family in real life.
To be honest, I tried
matsutake mushroom the first time
when I was in primary four.
Wow!
I'm impressed.
While I'm a vocalist, I'm also
a "Dobin Mushist" of matsutake.
Okay, how about you?
Talk longer...
Before I drink it,
may I take off my gloves
for good manners?
Do it before you start!
You do it now?
Take it off before you go in!
He has good manners.
I'll try.
Can he identify the taste he's been
familiar with since primary four?
"Dobin Mushi A"
He didn't smell it.
He drinks it right away.
I didn't know there was matsutake
when I was in primary four.
Next, it's B.
The rock singer who has been eating
matsutake for 33 years,
which one will he choose?
"Dobin Mushi B"
It seems B is better...
I'll say it.
His answer is...
The correct answer is...
B.
"Dobin Mushi B"
I first tried matsutake mushroom
in primary four.
It's the only thing he says.
It isn't too rich,
the taste is just right and perfect.
Ms Kaga said it tasted awful.
So far, all four chose B.
It's unusual.
Oh, glad to see you!
I'm happy.
Yay!
Lovely.
That's the 33 years of experience.
I'm so happy!
This must be the right answer.
Have a seat.
It does make us feel relieved,
but they could all fail together.
What drama are we going to see?
It has to be dramatic.
Winner of Japan Academy Film Prize's
Newcomer of the Year,
Mr Kento Nagayama is active in films
and dramas
with his solid acting skills.
First, he tries A,
which hasn't been chosen by anyone.
"Dobin Mushi A"
Next, it's B, which everyone chose.
"Dobin Mushi B"
Which one?
His answer is...
Miss Nishino, I'll guess it right.
"Dobin Mushi B"
Everyone chooses B.
I have a feeling that B has
the original flavour
of matsutake mushroom.
If A is the correct answer...
What should we do?
"Worried because
there are too many people"
We can't go back.
I don't think it's possible.
Now, five people chose B in a row.
Yay!
Welcome!
Welcome...
Thank goodness...
Oh, thank goodness.
Sakurazaki46's Risa Watanabe,
Hono Tamura, Ten Yamasaki.
The top idols are popular for
their overwhelming performance.
This is the first test.
But Dobin Mushi...
Can you tell?
This is bad.
Are you guys okay?
Maybe we should let Tanabe do it.
Get it right and come back.
We'll do our best.
The young girls haven't really tried
matsutake mushroom before.
At their age, they'd think
instant soup tastes better.
Right?
Indeed.
"Dobin Mushi A"
Please...
Please.
Which one will the idols' taste buds
think is the real one?
"Dobin Mushi B"
Will their opinions be different
or the same?
It'd be surprising
if they're the same.
It'd be impressive.
Yeah.
The girls' answers are...
No...
Different.
Their thoughts are different.
The senior, Watanabe chose A.
That's right.
Yeah.
The one in the middle is the senior.
Miss Watanabe.
The taste of B is milder,
and it was very easy to drink.
What I think is the exact opposite
of Hono's,
A is milder,
and B is richer than A.
Maybe I got it wrong,
but I could taste a bit
of the fragrance of yuzu.
B?
Yes.
So I'm confused now.
Let's choose B.
Shall we?
B...
B!
They decided to choose B.
The senior compromised.
Well done!
It's unusual.
It's good team work.
If it is as biased as this...
They look like they're at a funeral.
What the heck?
Right? It's weird.
"Gradually getting worried"
They don't want more people to come.
Excuse me.
Yay!
Thank goodness!
Is B the correct answer?
Or will there be a plot twist?
Lastly, it's this team.
Okay, the last team.
Do your best.
The boys...
What will happen?
From the two groups in Johnny's
that will lead the next generation,
Snow Man's Mr Ren Meguro
and Naniwa Danshi's
Mr Shunsuke Michieda.
My seniors had treated me
to matsutake mushroom before.
I've never tried matsutake.
Let's see what will happen.
I'll do my best not to make us fail.
Right?
Yes.
They're the exact opposite. One has
tried matsutake, but one hasn't.
"Dobin Mushi A"
They first taste
Dobin Mushi A carefully.
They just drink the soup.
Next, Dobin Mushi B.
"Dobin Mushi B"
What will they choose?
Okay.
What's the answer
of the two centres of attention?
Oh?
It's different.
What will they choose?
Different answers.
A tasted richer.
It did.
B is a bit light.
I know what you mean.
One would imagine the instant soup
to be richer, but...
I totally know what you mean.
But if you think in a different way,
because they use good matsutake,
I think maybe they would
intentionally make the taste richer.
What will they do?
It's hard to choose.
I chose B because I was at a loss...
I couldn't decide either.
I'll trust you about
the taste being rich.
Finally A.
I'll choose A too.
A? Is it okay?
A.
"At risk"
The B group is speechless.
It's possible only they'll win.
It'll be amazing if it's A.
Yeah.
Pay attention to their faces
the moment they open the door.
Whoa, we messed up.
Did we mess up?
Nobody is here?
That happens?
Oh, this...
Are you kidding me?
It's full!
Everyone went to B.
The correct answer is...
Please!
The fateful announcement
of the result!
Thank you for your patience,
Celeb Master will go to the room
of the correct answer, please wait.
Please, let it be B.
Here I am!
Ah...
It's totally possible
that we're right.
Let's be confident that it's A.
Okay!
Please come!
Okay, I'll open the door
of the correct answer's room.
Come here...
Really, come here!
I'm scared.
"Wins alone if it's correct"
The correct answer is...
Please!
What?
Congratulations!
Of course...
"A: Incorrect"
Are you kidding me?
Wait a minute...
This is horrible!
Good...
Good!
You did it!
Well done!
I'm impressed. Well done.
Okay, let's go,
everyone who got it right.
Darn it! It's so frustrating!
So embarrassing.
Everyone who answered correctly
is back.
Congratulations. It's amazing.
Brilliant.
Amazing.
Please go to your seats.
Brilliant.
You did very well.
Stop dancing!
We did it.
You did very well.
The people who got it wrong
are back.
Come in.
"Entrance for wrong answer"
I'm sorry, Mr Chinen.
Please return to your seats.
I really don't want to return
to the studio.
"Ordinary"
Only one team was downgraded.
It's an excellent start.
However...
An unexpected serious incident
happens after this.
Yes!
I can't stand this guy!
This is the next test.
"Cello"
It's cello.
Everyone makes noises.
Autumn is the perfect season
for classical music,
you'll listen to a piece played
on cello, the musical instrument
loved by Japan's famous writer,
Kenji Miyazawa.
The finest quality cello that is
the right answer was made in 1694,
by Italy's Giovanni Grancino.
The market price is 120 million yen.
The valuable cello can be called
a cultural heritage in the world.
That's right.
The wrong answer is a cello borrowed
from a music college student.
Yes.
Both cellos will be played
by firstclass cellist,
Ms Sonoko Muraoka.
Both cellos will be accompanied
by a Steinway piano.
That's right.
A 120 million yen cello
and a music college student's cello.
Okay?
Naturally you'll get it right!
During the first test,
you've been watching the screen
and enjoying yourself.
You'll go next.
Don't say something like you won!
After he drank the soup,
you went, "Drink water! Water!"
Everyone stays in firstclass
besides the three Johnny's guys.
It's a good result, but something
unbelievable is going to happen.
Representatives,
please go to do the tests.
Please.
This way.
Please come here.
Please be firstclass.
That's right.
Yes.
Have you acted
with anyone here before?
I don't think so.
Not Miss Yonekura, either?
I haven't either.
But I told her just now too,
the reason I debuted, the one who
chose me to join this world
was Ms Mariko Kaga.
That's right.
I had participated in
the Japan Bishojo Contest,
I was told the reason I won
the Special Award was because
Ms Kaga nominated me.
Wow!
Amazing!
Thank you so much!
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
While the great actresses
talk about the past excitedly,
the first three teams have come.
Well then, see you.
Wait...
Mr Masaaki Sakai has been an actor
for 70 years,
he is one of the leaders in
Japan's group sounds and a legend,
he can't answer the question
on music wrong!
Cello is a musical instrument.
Musical instrument.
My ears are reliable.
I see. Your ears are still good?
Of course.
Are your ears still good?
Pardon?
You know,
the way you talk to me
stresses me out most!
Please do your best.
How can I not?
Of course.
Participating in
the Kohaku Uta Gassen four times,
Golden Bomber's Mr Sho Kiryuin.
"Golden Bomber, Sho Kiryuin"
I'm a musician who writes
lyrics and songs,
I flatter myself that I've listened
to various kinds of music.
Also, I answered many questions
wrong last time,
so I must get rid
of my bad reputation now.
Yes.
Of course.
Miss Nanase Nishino
gained popularity
as Nogisaka46's
first generation member,
and is now active as an actress.
I had sung some songs in the past,
I think I'll be okay.
You'll stay firstclass?
Yes.
Which one is the sound
of the world's best cello,
which costs 120 million yen?
Please think together with them.
"Cello A, Cello B"
It starts now.
Let's listen as well.
Okay.
First, it's Cello A.
Isn't Mr Masaaki dying?
I think he's still fine.
Yeah?
Maybe he fell asleep.
Next, Cello B.
Viewers, do you know which one?
What do you think?
We both think it's B.
We think it's B.
I see.
What does the trio there think?
Our answers are the same.
Really?
Yes.
It's B.
Really?
Yes.
You are also a musician,
so I'll ask you.
Well, my actual job is musician.
Well, it's B.
Wow, that's amazing...
Yes.
I think it's A.
A?
Why do you think so?
The high note played by B
kind of bothers me.
It was so...
You heard that?
I did...
I heard that.
The look in your eyes was scary.
Naturally I would.
I'm sorry!
It's...
I said sorry!
Okay, okay, sorry!
I think it's A.
I see.
It sounded like cello.
It's a cello, though.
Okay.
Everyone at the studio chose B,
except Mariko Kaga.
Which one will the legend of
Japan's music industry choose?
"Masaaki Sakai"
Which one will Mr Sakai say?
I'm counting on you.
His answer is...
What's he doing?
What are you doing?
Hurry up!
It's so long.
Masaaki!
B.
Right?
For cello, how natural the low notes
sound matters most.
In that sense,
A sounded like a young
musical instrument.
It has to be B!
Mr Katsunori, do you agree?
Yes, I also think it's B.
I see. You agree with him?
Yes.
Okay.
Mr Masaaki didn't hesitate
to choose B.
Excuse me, I'll sit confidently
on a chair.
"Waiting room B"
Okay.
Depending on what
the Kohaku singer chooses,
the situation will greatly change.
Can Kiryuin do it?
I'm counting on you!
Speaking of Kiryuin,
when he came with GACKT
and did the musical instrument test,
only he answered the important
music question wrong...
I'm very sorry.
He slid to kneel in front of GACKT
in this dark past.
He must not make a mistake
this time. What's his answer?
It's B.
Yes!
The sound from the low to midrange
was very rich,
I wanted to keep listening to it
for a long time.
Also, it sounded expensive,
so it's B.
Mr DAIGO, did you also choose B?
Yes, it's B.
You agree.
Brilliant.
I hope Mr Sakai is here.
Please be here.
Yes!
It's B, right? Thank goodness!
Thank goodness!
Good.
Naturally he would.
It can't be wrong.
We're fine, I'm sure about it now.
Yes.
I'm sure.
It has to be B.
Thank goodness.
When the new and old popular
musicians chose B,
what will the former firstclass
idol Nanase Nishino choose?
Miss Nishino.
I see...
Her answer is...
Yes. It's this.
She chose A!
She chose A.
"Cello A"
What is it? The sound was solid,
the weight sounded like
100 million yen.
I see.
Well, we don't know yet.
The former Nogisaka46 idol's answer
is the opposite
of the senior musicians.
Not here...
Nobody is here.
She went to A?
I'm all alone.
Oh, she went to A.
A...
It's A.
You think it's A?
What? I'm worried.
Is A or B the correct answer?
This is the correct answer.
What?
Okay, I'll tell everyone
at the studio the correct answer.
We'll see which room
the other people go in now.
The correct answer of the question
just now is...
What?
No way!
I'm amazing!
Impressive, Ms Kaga.
Brilliant, Ms Kaga.
Really?
A is the correct answer.
You're a musician!
Really?
Amazing!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Masaaki, hey!
What?
Just look! I'm sure he still thinks
his answer is correct.
Can you hear us?
Yes, I can.
What a pity.
But are you sure I lost?
Yes.
Did you know the answer?
A is the correct answer
and the 120 million yen cello.
Compared to other cellos,
a Giovanni Grancino has more body
and a wider range,
its characteristics are the depth of
the low notes and the clear sound.
Also, the richness in sound given
by its 300 years of history
is totally different.
Will anyone come here?
Miss Nishino, don't worry,
your answer is correct.
I thought it was B
when I listened to A.
That early?
I feel reassured.
The more they say,
the bigger the wound will be.
The "firstclass" card is removed.
You're "ordinary" now.
It changed completely
at question two.
He messed up.
Oh, it looks like this now.
Next, it's these two teams.
Here?
Yes.
With a career of 59 years,
great actor, Mr Koji Ishizaka
is also knowledgeable about art.
She answered the question right,
Yes.
please continue that.
If you get it wrong, I won't accept
you in "The Peaceful Town."
Appearing in 121 shows
only in the first half of this year,
Borujuku formed less than two years
ago, but they're gaining popularity.
We are confident.
Really?
My mother had been listening
to cello since I was in her womb.
I think I had heard about it.
Really?
She listened to it
after she gave birth.
Really?
First, the correct answer, A.
"A: The 120 million yen
Giovanni Grancino"
"Pianist Eri Tanabu"
The cello is young.
It sounds dry.
Next, the wrong answer,
a cello borrowed from
a music college student.
"B: Cello borrowed from
a music college student"
First, Mr Koji Ishizaka,
who will be expelled
from "The Peaceful Town"
if he doesn't choose A.
Okay, what will Mr Ishizaka choose?
Ms Kaga chose A.
His answer is...
The correct answer is...
Oh!
Brilliant!
Amazing!
Impressive!
That's Team Bigwig for you.
The high notes of this cello
sounded clearer,
so I think this
is the 120 million cello.
It's easy, so stop talking.
Ishizaka goes to the correct room A,
where Nishino is waiting.
Oh, I feel a bit relieved.
No, I'm not confident at all.
What? He went to A?
What?
The looks on their faces
are a bit weird.
"B: incorrect"
They're surprised.
Their faces are paler.
Yeah.
Can Borujuku continue
to be firstclass?
"Borujuku"
But will Anri fail them?
Anri is assertive.
The ladies' answers are...
Okay, ready, go.
They're different!
The ladies' answers are...
Okay, ready, go.
They're different!
Anri, continue with B!
The sounds of both are heavy,
but the sound of B resonated
from the top of my head
to the tip of my toes.
I felt like I was being played.
You felt you were the cello.
Yes, the sound was similar
to my first cry.
What?
It's how natural the sound was.
Miss Tanabe, go! Miss Tanabe, go!
My soul trembled
when I heard the notes, like "Gua!"
B's resonance was good,
but there was some difference
even between
the regular sound of Cello A.
What will Anri do?
To me,
I'm sure B resonated better,
but when Miss Tanabe said
her soul trembled...
You listen to Taro Hakase's music,
right?
Yes.
Isn't it a certain reason?
Okay, sorry, we'll choose this.
Thank goodness!
You're still firstclass.
You stood up.
Thank goodness!
Brilliant. You stay firstclass.
Miss Tanabe.
Well done, it's correct.
More and more people go to Room A.
What?
Oh, thank goodness!
I feel relieved!
Thank goodness.
We outnumbered them.
The number.
Thank goodness...
Are you kidding me?
You feel safer
if there are more people.
They're having fun.
Mr Sakai?
Yes.
Do you feel worried
that you two are on your own?
We know about music
to a certain extent,
we were certain that it was B
at first,
but now our belief is shaken.
But it's B.
B, right? It's B.
It's B.
I won't answer.
He's unusually honest.
Finally, it's these two teams.
Besides "Doctor X,"
leading actor Mr Masanobu Katsumura
also stars in many other big hits.
How about you, Mr Katsumura?
You've already got it right.
That's right.
The pressure is great.
Pressure...
Do your best!
Look!
What's that attitude?
But I have a friend in Switzerland,
who's a pro cellist.
What?
So...
You're used to the sound?
More than the others.
You said it.
Sorry, I'll take back my words.
14 years after his CD debut,
Hey! Say! JUMP's Mr Yuri Chinen
is also a presenter
of Gymnastics
World Championships 2021.
I made my debut at 13 years old
in the music industry.
I see.
I'll be okay!
You listened...
You need to clean up their mess too.
Yes, we must hang on to "ordinary."
See how long they can keep
the current state.
"A: The 120 million yen
Giovanni Grancino"
I'm sure it's A. It must be.
You're confident.
Very confident.
Me too.
"B: Cello borrowed from
a music college student"
If it's just the two of us...
But I decided at first...
He isn't sure anymore.
First, Masanobu Katsumura, who has
a cellist friend in Switzerland.
"Masanobu Katsumura"
Kacchan has to guess this one right.
The answer dedicated
to his friend in Switzerland is...
B.
You naturally think so.
He failed.
I thought you had a friend?
I think there was some impurity
in A.
Impurity?
There's impurity in the 120 million.
B has...
The sound had more depth.
I think.
I see.
His wrong answer did secondary
damage to his friend in Switzerland.
Thank goodness!
Wow!
Musicians...
Musician...
Thank goodness!
You know about cello.
Yes.
I'm worried.
Our answers are different.
"Worried"
Why do you think it's B?
I thought it sounded elegant.
They're fist bumping.
Fist bump...
A celebration.
"Fist bump of victory"
Next, Johnny's Chinen, the only team
that was downgraded in question one.
"Yuri Chinen"
Here comes Chinen.
Can he show the senior's will?
Okay.
His answer is...
It's B.
"B: Cello borrowed from
a music college student"
Hey...
Hey, Johnny's!
The start of the high notes
was smooth,
I felt comfortable
when I listened to it.
That's good.
Mr Meguro and Mr Michieda...
Green slippers...
It's only question two.
"Secondclass"
Here I come.
Welcome.
Somehow I feel relieved.
Thank goodness...
Good...
They are so happy.
But we don't know yet.
Right, we don't know yet.
That's right.
The fateful announcement
of the result!
Here I am!
The room that Celeb Master enters
is the correct answer.
Let me open the door
of the correct answer's room!
I'm scared!
I'm scared.
He's going to open this door!
The correct answer is...
"Praying in vain"
Yay!
"A: Correct"
"B: Incorrect"
Wow...
This was difficult.
Let's form a band together!
Let's form a band.
I was so confident I was right.
"Unexpected defeat"
I'm so happy!
Oops, now only three teams
are firstclass celebrities.
I wonder what will happen
in the end.
Okay, people who got it wrong,
come in.
"Entrance for wrong answer"
Please return to your seats.
Oops...
This is what an ordinary celebrity
looks like.
But I'm an ordinary celebrity.
Mr Katsumura, you'd better
get in touch with your friend.
I was the only one who consider him
a friend myself not him...
Sorry. I'm really sorry.
Who Is The Real Celebrity,
an autumn of food and art,
three hour special programme!
Our firstclass celebrities
have gathered here again.
The theme of this episode
is an autumn of food and art.
We've prepared various tests about
autumnal things like food,
music, and painting.
They'll distinguish the pro from
the amateur
in the Taiko Drum performance.
Wow!
You're in high school?
Yes, students from
Japan Aviation High School.
Wonderful.
Amazing.
The high school students
will compete with the pro,
the performance of their souls
will cause drama!
If they answer the questions wrong,
their rank will fall immediately,
till they reach the abyss
and disappear at the end.
Our next test is this.
"Jazz session"
Jazz session.
We prepared a jazz piece performed
with seven musical instruments,
saxophone, trumpet, trombone,
drum, piano, double bass, and flute.
You'll choose an answer
among A, B, and C.
Listen carefully.
The musical instruments
used in the correct answer
are firstclass ones
used by professionals.
But the other two are played with
only cheap musical instruments
professionals would never use.
For the wrong answer,
among the seven musical instruments,
four are made of plastic.
There are three professional ones
and four toy musical instruments.
That's right.
And for the option
you mustn't choose,
among the seven,
only two are musical instruments
used by professionals.
The rest are four plastic
musical instruments, and worse,
the other one is someone's mouth.
That's the composition.
You can't even call that music.
The mouth...
Your rank will go down two if you
choose the Absolutely No answer.
Be careful not to choose it.
It's scary.
Okay, we'll announce
the representatives.
Okay, from Team Bigwig,
Ms Mariko Kaga.
Okay, please do it.
From Team Doctor X,
Mr Masanobu Katsumura.
Okay, please do it.
No...
I don't want that!
I just failed and it was traumatic.
Then you must recover lost ground.
That's the love of our staff.
They are the representatives.
Make sure you don't choose the one
performed vocally.
No!
Representatives,
please go to the room.
Please come here.
Thank you.
Kento, you must hold out.
If four of them are plastic,
then it should be rather obvious.
We start from
the three ordinary celebrities
who can't get another answer wrong.
Kacchan goes first?
The leader.
He was forced to.
I feel sorry for him.
He looks worried.
Traumatic...
He has an air of despair.
The same professional musicians
will perform all the pieces.
You can hear it too, please listen.
"Performed by professionals"
First, it's A.
"Musical Instruments A"
Next, B.
"Musical Instruments B"
That was B.
Yes.
Lastly, C.
"Musical Instruments C"
It's difficult.
It is, but I know the one
performed vocally.
I tried to look for one played
by a different instrument.
I see.
The double bass of B was
performed vocally.
That was vocal?
Yes.
It's A or C.
Okay.
Which one?
The sound of the bass...
You won't say?
Please tell him.
A or C.
I think it's C.
I see.
Does anyone agree?
But C...
Miss Nishino?
You think it's C?
I thought it was C, but...
I totally thought C was the one
performed vocally.
C was performed vocally.
Before Kacchan says it.
I couldn't decide between B and C,
but I could hear various sounds
that weren't uniform.
I see...
So I end up picking B.
I see.
That's what I thought.
I'm not confident at all.
The problematic guy comes
right away.
"Wrong answer in cello question"
He comes first?
Your partner said B.
Yes.
His answer is...
I'll go with this.
What?
C...
Correct!
I felt the confidence of using
real musical instruments.
So I'll choose C.
He agrees with you, Mr Masaaki.
Yes.
You two think the same.
"Guesses B"
Masaaki and Katsumura both
got the cello question wrong,
their opinions are the same again.
"Waiting room C"
Please...
Next, the junior
of Masaaki's agency.
Here he comes.
He's here...
Choose C!
His answer is...
This one.
Oh?
B.
I can't stand this guy.
You don't know yet.
He just doesn't agree with you.
The first one sounded a bit plastic.
The third one...
I think I heard a man humming.
It isn't B.
Senior Masaaki insists it's C,
ignoring him, the junior chooses B.
Not here...
"Waiting room B"
Where's Mr Katsumura? It's C...
Katsunori chose B?
It's divided.
We did.
Here I go.
"Rock singer DAIGO
must not get this wrong!"
But Sho Kiryuin's band
is an air rock band.
Mine is an actual band.
I'm going to show you
the difference.
Really?
Yes.
His answer is...
The correct answer is...
B.
"Musical Instrument B"
He's relaxed.
This is the only option for me.
The sound was very uniform.
Everything was in harmony,
but I also sensed the swing
of jazz music properly.
What do you think, Kiryuin?
Actually, I also thought it was B,
so we agree.
You agree. I see.
I'm jealous. It's nice when you
and your teammate agree.
Yay!
You're here.
The two gentlemen became animated
right away. On the other hand...
"Waiting room C"
No way!
He's talking to himself.
To himself...
Now, we'll tell only our viewers
the correct answer.
The jazz session played by
first class musical instruments is
A!
That means nobody chose
the right answer. It's outrageous!
The Absolutely No session
performed vocally that will
downgrade them two ranks is...
C!
Oops, he messed up again.
"Two ranks down"
What will the four remaining teams
choose? Let's check it out!
First, the correct answer, A, with
all firstclass musical instruments.
"A: correct answer, seven
firstclass musical instruments"
Doesn't A's bass sound like humming?
So...
A?
Next, wrong answer.
B, which four among the seven
musical instruments are plastic.
"B: wrong answer, four are plastic"
"Plastic trumpet"
"Plastic saxophone"
"Plastic trombone"
"Plastic drums"
"Firstclass: piano,
double bass, flute"
Lastly, C,
which downgrades two ranks.
In addition to
four plastic musical instruments,
trombone is performed by Mr AFRA,
the pioneer of beatboxing.
"C: Absolutely No,
plastic and vocal"
"First class: piano, double bass"
"Plastic: saxophone, trumpet,
drums, flute"
"Vocal: trombone"
You must not choose C!
First, Sakurazaka46, the top idols
who performed on Kohaku Uta Gassen.
They won't be the same.
No.
It was also divided just now.
The answers
of the three ladies are...
Oh!
Amazing! All of them are correct.
What?
They're the same.
What will happen?
Wow!
It's unusual they're all the same.
I think it was the most uniform.
The sound of the drums of B
was a bit too loud,
and I couldn't hear the other
musical instruments clearly.
I couldn't choose between A and C,
but A was easier to listen to.
If they all think the same...
It must feel good.
It's reassuring.
Mr Akimoto,
Sakurazaka46's stock is soaring!
Please...
Nobody!
"A: correct"
No!
They messed up.
"Wrong but confident"
No reaction from him, maybe because
he's sure he is wrong.
"He is sure he lost?"
Now I feel really sorry for Kacchan.
"People at the studio
don't know the correct answer"
Next, Ms Mariko Kaga, who performed
remarkably well today.
"Mariko Kaga"
I'm counting on you...
What will Ms Kaga choose?
Yeah...
What is the answer
everyone wants to know?
First, it isn't A.
Oops! She got rid of
the correct answer right away!
It was easy to hear the sound of
all the musical instruments of B.
It was too good
and it bothers me somehow.
She does it with doubts.
So I'll choose C this time.
Are you serious?
I think he's going to be delighted.
He got the best ally.
She got rid of
the correct answer first,
and chose the one that will do
more damage to confidence.
Wow!
Thank goodness!
Thank you!
It's C.
It's C, right?
Yeah.
B was too beautiful.
Right?
Yes.
That's why I chose C.
They try to convince themselves
somehow,
and they're saying various things
in their minds.
Please! I hope C is correct.
"Correct but worried"
What?
Maybe the girls don't sing
to live music often?
Occasionally...
Usually karaoke?
It really is occasionally...
Yeah.
It didn't feel like jazz.
Girls at their age
don't listen to jazz.
No.
A is correct, but the girls
are made a fool of.
Hold out a bit longer!
This time, the young people
are all excellent.
Mr Kento Nagayama can stay
firstclass if he answers A.
He needs to hold on now.
Which one will Mr Kento raise?
His answer is...
A.
Oh!
Firstclass,
chosen by firstclass...
A?
C has to be wrong.
I think I heard the sound
of a vocal performance.
B is...
The sound of the trumpet or
something bothered me at a place.
It's quite equally divided.
It's divided.
Mr Kento Nagayama successfully
stays firstclass!
Oh!
He was a bit disgusted.
He was a bit disgusted
because they were young.
Come on!
Ms Kaga isn't here.
No, she isn't. She chose C.
Kento, it's wrong!
A is young.
They're young.
I liked the sound.
They're still a bit...
It's close to the age of toys.
I guess jazz is too soon for them.
Now we want to see
all the young people get it right!
I'm counting on you!
Chinen, it's now.
It depends on where they'll go now.
They'll be correct if they say A.
Ready, go.
We chose differently again.
Yeah.
It's divided.
Divided.
It was the power of A and I was
carried away by the music,
so I choose A.
I just got the first answer wrong,
so I'm not confident.
Yeah.
But they're different questions!
What will they choose?
We'll choose A, then.
Okay.
A.
Yes.
Chinen, is A okay?
I wanted to choose B.
Meguro didn't compromise...
He didn't.
Johnny's would've failed
if Chinen had answered.
They barely hung in there.
Please!
Mr Nagayama, the other young guys
are coming.
Please be there.
"Pay attention"
No!
He held his head.
Did he look down?
A...
It's A.
We actually saw nobody just now.
All the young people are at A.
Yeah.
A is the sound for children.
The fateful announcement
of the result!
Here I am!
Please!
I'll start from opening the door of
the room that downgrades one rank.
I'm happy with just one!
One down...
Let's do it.
"A: Correct"
"B: Wrong"
"C: Absolutely No"
Oh?
What?
Are you serious?
Oh no! I'm scared...
I don't know...
Oh, please!
It could be two ranks down!
I knew it. We're right.
We did it.
Oh, thank goodness! I'm so happy.
"Strangely confident"
That means this isn't correct.
There were toys?
I knew it wasn't B.
I'll go open the door of
the correct one. Please be patient.
Please!
Which one? Please!
Not two ranks down!
We don't want to go down two ranks.
It's awful.
If I don't open the door of
your room, you go down two ranks.
Here I go.
"A: Correct"
Open it! Okay! Come here!
Congratulations!
We did it!
Thank you.
Congratulations!
We did it!
Thank goodness!
Well...
"Boom"
That's correct?
Oh!
Nice!
They were right?
He got it right.
C is the unexpected answer
that brings you down two ranks.
The young people...
So the two people in Room C
will go down two ranks!
Oh no!
No!
What's this?
Slippers for the toilet.
They feel so uncomfortable!
Okay, the people who answered it
correctly are back.
Congratulations! Well done. Amazing!
It was brilliant.
People who got it wrong, come in.
"Entrance for wrong answer"
I was so sure it was B.
Ms Kaga...
That had to be C.
Oops.
Look at that.
Yes.
Her legs are spread wide.
We've done the third question,
most of you are secondclass.
The team here is thirdclass.
He went down three ranks by himself.
After three questions,
only two teams stay firstclass.
After this, a serious incident
will make you doubt your eyes.
The next test is this.
"Taiko drums"
Taiko drums.
In the season of music,
the fourth test
is a performance of the soul music
of Japanese people
with Taiko drums
that appeared in myths.
Compare the performance
by professionals
and high school students,
and guess which one
is performed by professionals.
First, the professionals
of the correct answer
is Japan's famous
Kodo Taiko Performing Arts Ensemble.
They've done over 6,500 performances
in 52 countries in the world.
The wrong answer is fourtimes
champion in a national tournament,
a prestigious school of Taiko drums
with brilliant achievements,
Yamanashi Prefecture's Japan
Aviation High School's Taiko Band.
Actually, their baseball team
played at Koshien this summer,
and they used Taiko drums
to cheer for them on the Alps Stand.
That's right.
Some people have gone down a lot.
If the secondclass celebs
aren't careful,
you're going to disappear.
Where did you buy these slippers?
That's...
If you say that, look at theirs.
The top and the bottom
are so unbalanced.
Indeed.
Okay, we announce
the representatives.
One representative will do the test.
From Team The Words They Speak,
Miss Nanase Nishino.
Please do it.
From Team K Dash,
Masaaki Sakaikun.
Okay, please do it.
I haven't been called "kun"
in a long time!
From Team Doctor X, Ryoko Yonekura.
Okay, please do it.
They're thirdclass.
I'll do my best.
The other representatives
are as shown.
Team Doctor X, if you fail again,
you'll be in trouble.
Representatives, please go
to the room for your test.
Please come here.
I'm content with being secondclass.
It's a bit...
Now is where they should hold on,
especially the firstclass ones.
First, it's thirdclass
celebrity Yonekura
and secondclass celebrities
Masaaki, Kiryuin.
The three teams at the edge
of a cliff, it's time!
You're both musicians, but you got
everything wrong. What's that?
We do more variety shows.
Among musicians.
Yeah, actually.
I'll get it right this time
and show you I'm a musician.
That's right.
And you?
Sakaikun.
I'll get it this time.
Yeah.
I won't forget about the cello!
You got the question
your teammate got wrong too!
I thought it was C.
That was close. So close.
You...
You need to hold on now.
Don't give me that.
I'll listen with my heart.
Right?
Wait, which one matters more?
My heart or my skills?
Both?
Did You really ask him?
Yeah, I asked the wrong person.
Wrong person?
Yeah.
Which one is the professional's
Taiko performance?
Please think together with them.
First, Taiko drums A.
"Taiko drums A"
That was A.
Yes.
Next, Taiko drums B.
"Taiko drums B"
That was B.
Is anyone confident?
Is it A or B?
What do you think, Mr DAIGO?
I think it's A.
Why is that?
I sensed that A was played
in a more technical way.
Oh.
Kacchan.
A, I think.
A sounded heavier.
I felt the power of adults.
I see.
I also think it's A.
How about you guys?
I thought it was B.
That's okay.
And you, Sakurazaka?
Two of us think it's B,
and she thinks it's A.
B and A.
Yes.
Ms Kaga, and you?
It has to be A, I think.
It's A, if you must say?
Yeah.
When the opinions at the studio
are divided,
Masaaki Sakai, who got the cello
question wrong, is here first.
"Masaaki Sakai"
What will Masaaki choose?
His answer is...
The performance of
experienced drummers is...
Taiko drums A. I'm sure.
I see.
"Guesses A"
You don't use ears to listen to
Taiko drums, you use your heart.
He said it.
Guys, come here.
"Waiting room A"
I'm waiting here.
I'll make it warm for you.
Will he get it right this time?
Next, the one who also got
the cello question wrong,
secondclass musician, Sho Kiryuin.
Here Kiryuin comes.
I'm counting on you.
He'll decide whether
you'll be downgraded or not.
His answer is...
It's A.
"Guesses A"
Both performances
were powerful and great,
but if I have to find fault,
in B, the part where the drumming
gradually got more powerful,
the attack wasn't uniform
and it was obvious.
I see.
Mr Masaaki must feel relieved now,
if someone else goes there.
"Feels relieved"
The two people who got
all the answers wrong today chose A.
Wait, is this okay? Is it?
Here you are!
Mr Sakai!
It's the same pattern as last time.
No, we'll get this one right.
Yes, this time we'll get it right!
This time...
They got the last one wrong.
In Room B.
Yeah.
In Room B...
Yeah, the same two people.
Next, if she gets this wrong,
she'll become a lookalike.
Team Doctor X's Ryoko Yonekura.
Excuse me.
Really, she must hold on now.
Her answer is...
My answer is...
A.
Reason, it's the reason.
Reason...
It was mellow, powerful, and heavy.
What is it?
Like, I'm glad I came here today.
She said something nice.
But they all...
Yeah, they're in the same room.
Now, it's three A's in a row.
Oh!
Yay!
Thank goodness...
When I listened to it,
I was on the verge of tears.
Oh...
It was amazing...
Amazing! All three of us are here.
I'm happy!
Isn't this obvious, then?
Nothing can be more powerful!
Yes.
Next, it's the two
secondclass celebrities here.
Okay...
They're really difficult to walk in.
What do you think? Taiko drums...
I wonder...
The high school students
are also good.
I think so.
I think it'll be very difficult.
I see.
Who in your team will go?
I'll go.
Chinen.
What about you?
I had played Taiko drum
in one of my performances,
thousands of people listened to it.
I can do it.
You said it!
Okay.
Chinen has experience in Taiko
drums, this question must be easy.
"Experienced in Taiko"
Which one will he choose?
We'll win straightforwardly.
They can announce the correct answer
is A now.
Yeah.
I can't afford to lose again.
"Thirdclass"
That's very unbalanced.
Yes.
Yuri Chinen, the only guy
who knows Taiko drums.
His answer will change
the situation.
Chinen, now...
The answer
everyone wants to know is...
It's B.
It's divided!
It's divided.
The strength of each part...
You can hear the part played
by small Taiko drums. It's obvious.
I see.
It was easy to listen to.
So it's B.
I think it's right.
I see.
One goes to Room B.
"Experienced in Taiko drums"
Chinen, who has experience
in Taiko drums,
goes to an empty Room B.
The people in A were confident,
but it doesn't look favourable now.
What?
Whoa, are you kidding me?
What? He went to B?
What?
Are you kidding me?
Oh, three people there!
Chinen?
But he said he played Taiko drums.
Yes, I played Taiko. I did...
Really?
I have experience!
B?
Next, Team Bigwig, Koji Ishizaka.
Kaga at the studio guessed A.
Mr Ishizaka, you'll get it, right?
Yes.
His answer is...
It's B.
"Guesses A"
The bass of both had the power
that typical Taiko drums have,
I think it's the timing
that cuts in,
is where the difference between
the pro and the precision
of students executing
what they learnt.
So I think it's B.
"Unhappy"
Now it's three versus two.
It is hard to tell!
Oh!
Oh?
Thank goodness!
It's B, right?
I think so.
What?
Mr Ishizaka...
Mr Ishizaka and I are incompatible.
But many of the people
in A are hopeless.
Wait...
Don't say that.
Indeed.
Is the correct answer A or B?
I'll tell everyone at the studio
the correct answer now.
Which one?
Let's go. Taiko drums,
the correct answer is...
A.
"Correct answer: A"
Oh no.
Well...
What will happen to me?
Did you know the answer?
A is the correct answer.
They're professional Taiko
Performing Arts Ensemble, Kodo.
My belly can feel it.
Well done, the three of them
got it right.
"A: Correct"
A sounds textbooklike here.
The part it does a crescendo.
He's talking.
He's wrong, but he's talking.
Right?
It's the most embarrassing.
Oh my God!
So Johnny's and Bigwig
both go, "Oh my God!"
The treatment is different.
Wow...
I like this.
Wow, how did you find these?
Lastly, it's the two teams
of firstclass celebrities.
First, the correct answer, A.
"A: Correct. Kodo Taiko
Performing Arts Ensemble"
I think the performance of
the students was amazing too.
We, Kodo, don't play
only with power,
we play each note properly,
bearing in mind to bring out
the rich sound of Taiko drums.
This is the correct answer, A.
Yes, the professionals.
Now, a performance
by high school students,
which made two teams wrongly think
they were professionals.
"B: Wrong. Japan Aviation
High School Taiko Band"
This is wonderful too.
Right? B is wonderful too.
I hope he'll come here.
That's right, everyone,
this is the correct answer.
First, it's firstclass celebrity,
from Team The Words They Speak,
Miss Nanase Nishino.
Here she is!
What will she choose?
Can she stay firstclass?
You'll stay firstclass
if you choose A.
B.
Oh!
"B: Japan Aviation High School"
She couldn't stay firstclass.
The more you think...
Actually,
both of them were powerful,
there wasn't a great difference,
but I'll choose B.
The high school students are happy.
I think they're happy.
Right?
It's a fantastic memory.
More and more people
go to the wrong answer, B.
Oh, thank goodness!
Good...
We've got more friends.
Thank goodness.
Yikes, yikes, yikes...
We don't know yet.
It's three to three now.
Yes, it's exactly half and half.
Lastly, the only firstclass
celebrities left, Borujuku.
Borujuku is here.
Please...
Now is when you must hold on.
It's A...
Will they choose A
and stay firstclass?
Ready, go.
Oh, it's divided!
It's divided again.
It's divided.
I think the strength was played
more elaborately in A.
I know what you mean, I do,
but I think
it's because they're young.
No...
No. That's fine...
Choose A!
Sure, A's performance shook my soul.
And my heart danced too.
But this has a longer history.
And weight.
They keep persuading her.
Hang in there!
I'm confident.
I think it's this one.
Rock, paper, scissors.
No. It's the weight.
Yes, the weight.
B? I'll choose B, then.
Now all the firstclass celebrities
are gone!
It's the majority.
It can't be helped.
It's okay, the weight is...
Oh! There isn't
any firstclass celebrity left.
Okay?
Yeah.
"Sure they are right"
Thank goodness...
Whoa...
"Correct, but worried"
Those in A are feeling down.
That's unexpected.
The two firstclass teams
are there...
The fateful announcement
of the result!
Here I am!
"Celeb Master enters the room
of the correct answer"
Please!
Please come here!
I'm going to open the door
of the correct room!
The correct answer is...
"A: Correct"
"B: Wrong"
Congratulations!
Yay!
Yes!
Congratulations!
Yay! Yay!
Yes!
"B: Wrong"
She's right.
Gosh! I was right!
She was right.
How about this?
Oh, I'm crying!
Yeah, A was powerful.
I was on the verge of tears!
Thank goodness!
Wow...
Both firstclass teams got it wrong.
Oh, what a pity.
Right?
I'm so angry at myself!
It's frustrating.
It's so frustrating!
People who answered correctly
are back.
Wonderful! Well done!
They entered the studio with their
heads held high. Congratulations.
Yay!
You were nervous at last, right?
It was amazing.
Yay!
They answered it correctly.
Now, the people who got it wrong
are back.
"Entrance for wrong answer"
What a pity!
It's frustrating!
Here they are...
They're apple boxes.
It's so frustrating...
Everyone, there is no
firstclass celebrity left.
All are gone after this.
It's "ordinary celebs" at the top.
But you must stay here now.
Yeah...
The thirdclass and secondclass
teams only have two questions left,
so it's quite possible that
you'll disappear at the end.
Yes.
I see.
Oh dear! Now we have three teams
of thirdclass celebrities.
Maybe most will disappear
after the two remaining questions.
Who Is the Real Celebrity,
an autumn of food and art,
three-hour special programme!
Our first-class celebrities
have gathered here again.
The theme of this episode
is an autumn of food and art.
We've prepared various tests about
autumnal things like food,
music, and painting.
They'll distinguish
the pro from the amateur
in the Taiko Drum performance.
Wow!
You're in high school?
Yes, students from
Japan Aviation High School.
- Wonderful.
- Amazing.
The high school students
will compete with the pro.
The performance of their souls
will cause drama!
If they answer the questions wrong,
their rank falls immediately
till they reach the abyss
and disappear at the end.
The next test is this.
Painting.
What? Painting?
Painting is a must
in the season of art.
That's right.
There will be portrait paintings
and portrait photos.
You'll compare the two
and guess which group is paintings.
- Yes, one group is photos.
- Yes.
But this time,
we made it easy for you.
You won't be comparing just one
but three paintings
and three photos.
Just choose
which group is paintings.
That's all. That's right.
We'll know.
Mr Ishizaka said it was unbelievable
and they're difficult to tell apart.
He gave us pressure.
Realistic paintings are popular now.
- What?
- Realistic ones are popular.
You're already making an excuse?
Get your act together!
You said that, but you dropped
two ranks at once.
Just go!
You finished?
Well...
- Representatives, please.
- I'll announce.
Team The Words They Speak,
Mr Kento Nagayama.
Please do it.
Team Bigwig, Koji Ishizaka.
- Yes, please do it.
- It's me again?
Team Doctor X, Katsumura.
Yes, please do it.
These are the representatives.
Compare portrait paintings
and portrait photos.
Choose the group of paintings.
That's all.
Okay, Mr DAIGO.
Really, if I don't hold on now...
My wife is also involved, so...
- Do your best, really.
- Yeah.
Or people will say her husband
is second- or third-class.
That's true...
Okay, here. Katsunori.
Well, regarding paintings,
nobody does it worse than Katsunori.
He's the worst?
But it's paintings or photos.
Well, he just got one question right
- and kept our rank here.
- That's right.
So he told me to do my best.
Please do your best.
And you'll go, Kacchan.
Seems I will.
What are you going to do?
She got the last one right.
Yeah.
You know, my eyesight
is getting worse...
Your voice is too soft!
I know that.
He said he'd lend me
his reading glasses.
What's that conversation?
Representatives, please go
to the room for the test.
Compare the photos and paintings
and choose the paintings.
It's photos and paintings!
- It's easy.
- Easy.
There are three portrait paintings
and three portrait photos each.
They have 10 seconds to look at each
one. This question is very easy.
First, it's the hopeless three teams
of third- and second-class celebs.
Okay, everyone.
They'll compare the two groups
like this.
Now, first one of group A, open.
"Which group is painting? A or B"
It's painting.
Next, first one in B, open.
Next, it's B.
It isn't the same person?
This is difficult.
Okay, let's keep going.
Second one in A, open!
I can't tell!
Second one in B, open!
Both groups look like paintings.
Third one in A, open!
Why me?
He is smiling happily.
A lovely smile.
Well then, lastly,
third one in B, open!
I don't know...
It must be easy
after looking at them for so long.
What?
I can't tell.
It's difficult!
After looking at them,
please choose the paintings.
- Yes, choose the paintings.
- Not the photos.
I do think it's difficult.
First, going down three ranks alone,
third-class celebrity
Masanobu Katsumura.
Okay, here he comes!
He's here.
If he gets it wrong,
they'll be lookalikes at once.
I'll choose B.
I see. B.
It was very difficult to see.
My eyesight makes it worse.
The battle was tough.
But the eyes of the baby girl
in the middle of group B
were very bright.
I think they were made to look
like eyes in a photo.
I see.
If I get this one wrong,
Ms Yonekura probably won't ever talk
to me again.
"Got all wrong today"
The guy who got all the answers
wrong and spoke weakly chose B.
"Waiting room B"
B. B.
I can't afford to get this wrong.
Will this plague gain more friends?
When you think about your teammate,
you would think
- you mustn't fail.
- Is that so?
Yeah, on the day
you become third-class.
It's tense over here!
How could he get
the Taiko drum question wrong?
Next, it's Koji Ishizaka,
who'd seen appraisals
of many works of art over the years.
"Will be told off if it's wrong"
Now, we'll see which one
Mr Ishizaka chooses.
But I heard he paints every day.
I see.
He'll know.
His answer is...
Well, yes.
Okay, I'll just go with this.
Good.
It's okay. Thank goodness.
He didn't go senile.
The eyes of all three were the same.
I mean group B.
This is the way to draw
realistic eyes,
their styles are uniform, and I
think photos wouldn't be so uniform.
- I see.
- It's difficult.
Both gentlemen chose B.
Not yet?
Your third-class friend
will join you soon.
- Wow!
- There you are.
Thank goodness!
Thank goodness.
It's only you and me now, right?
Yes.
He looks happy when someone comes.
Be quiet...
Looks like a rescue squad has come.
You're with the plague who got
all the questions wrong today.
Is it okay?
"Got all questions wrong"
Next, it's second-class celebrity
Katsunori Takahashi.
You can't downgrade
your senior Masaaki Sakai again.
"Katsunori Takahashi'
Here he comes.
Katsunori, I'm counting on you.
The former handsome man.
His answer is...
This one?
Oh!
- Katsunori chose A.
- Oh, no.
That's hopeless.
The Mr Hamada in A...
It has a depth
at an unbelievable angle.
I thought maybe the proportion
was changed when it was painted.
I think the Mr Hamada in group B
looks younger, but even so...
does he show such a casual facial
expression in front of people?
- Is he teasing me?
- Yeah.
Maybe.
But I think it's A.
Katsunori chose A,
the opposite of the two gentlemen.
Will this decision make or break?
Oh, nobody is here.
Are you kidding me?
- He didn't come.
- No!
What?
Oops.
"Waiting room A"
I didn't know the answer at all.
I really have no idea.
Is the painting group A or B?
I'll tell you
the correct answer here.
- Really?
- Yes.
The correct answer of painting is...
B.
Yay!
That means...
What's he doing?
Well...
"A: Wrong"
You can't tell paintings and photos
apart, you're in big trouble!
They go one rank down
and fall to third-class celebrities.
Did you know the correct answer?
The correct answer is B.
The painter was Mr Takeshi Nagase,
who's said to give life to a canvas.
"Acrylic paints, oil paints,
airbrushes are used"
The artist pursues
extreme reality thoroughly.
I thought group B
looked a bit three-dimensional.
Katsumura got
his first correct answer today.
Next, it's Team Gymnastics World
and Vanishing My First Love.
They'll be lookalikes at once
if they get this wrong.
"Shunsuke Michieda, Ren Meguro"
Here they are!
I'm counting on you!
I can't say anything, though.
True.
Please!
Their answers are...
Ready, go.
Good...
My excellent juniors!
Thank goodness!
The third one, Mr Hamada, in B,
if it's actually a photo,
it looks very three-dimensional.
Yeah.
They're reliable!
Brilliant. Good for you.
Okay...
They barely stay third-class.
- They're here.
- They're here...
- Come.
- Thank you.
Thank you...
We thought it would be B.
Whoa... they all went there.
"A: Wrong"
Most of them will go to B!
Katsunori is in A!
Will anyone besides Katsunori
mix up paintings and photos?
Next, it's second-class celebrity
DAIGO.
Okay, DAIGO.
He'll be fine.
His answer is...
B.
Correct!
It obviously is B!
Yes, there's no way
you can get it wrong.
- Here he is.
- Many people.
We totally outnumbered the other.
I did it...
- I did it.
- We'll win.
- Yeah.
- We did it.
This is bad...
See? Katsunori is gradually
getting disheartened.
"Extremely worried"
Next, it's ordinary celebrity
Kento Nagayama.
Here he comes.
Now we'll see what Kento chooses.
Which one will you choose?
This one. B.
He got it right too.
Thank goodness!
Now we finally have to ask,
"What's the matter with Katsunori?"
We'll all beat him up!
Seriously!
What?
Now it's five versus one.
Wow!
Thank you.
"B: Correct"
Great.
Everyone went to the other room...
Why do you fist-bump?
- Thank you.
- Why do you fist-bump?
"A: Wrong, B: Correct"
Okay, all of you go to B.
Leave Katsunori on his own.
Will Katsunori end up losing alone
and be humiliated?
Lastly, it's the girls
of Sakurazaka46.
"Sakurazaka46"
- Here they are.
- Sakurazaka.
- You can do it.
- We'll see where they go.
Okay, which one?
Ready, go.
It's divided!
It's divided, but...
- I'll trust you.
- Let's go to B.
We'll choose B.
Okay, Katsunori is alone!
Thank goodness!
It's lonely.
"Loses alone"
Now Katsunori will surely lose
on his own.
Excuse me.
Wow!
Maybe it's really good.
- It's nearly perfect.
- Amazing.
Yay!
This is bad...
It has to be us.
- This is amazing.
- Yes, it is.
He looks dejected.
"Lost fighting spirit"
- What are you doing, Katsunori?
- That reminds me.
When he was in university,
he had hit on my niece.
Really?
That has nothing to do with this.
It's true, but I just remembered.
When he was
at Aoyama Gakuin University.
He's cheerful.
Before he knew it...
Big drama after this!
The fateful announcement
of the result!
Here I am!
"Celeb Master enters the room
of the correct answer"
I'm going to open the door
of the correct answer's room.
The correct answer is...
"B: Correct"
"A: Wrong"
Idiot!
Thank goodness.
Yay!
Idiot!
Yay! Thank goodness!
Thank goodness.
Yay!
I'm so happy!
It would've been cool
if he had won alone.
"Loses alone"
Okay, people who answered correctly
are back.
Wonderful. Well done!
Please come in!
Brilliant.
Brilliant!
Wonderful.
- Everybody got it right!
- Yes.
Hey...
Okay, the person who got it wrong
is here. Come in.
It must feel lonely.
"Entrance for wrong answer"
His knees must hurt.
- He's embarrassed.
- His knees must hurt.
Katsunori.
I'm so angry at myself!
The third one on the left--
Okay, then.
Okay.
With one question left,
there are now four teams
of third-class celebrities.
I have a strong feeling that many
will disappear at the end.
Okay, let's do our final test.
Yes!
Okay, out last test is this.
Taste from three options.
Autumn is a season of food, so
you'll eat three dishes, A, B and C.
First, A is omelette-wrapped eel.
It's minced eel wrapped in egg.
And B.
Scallop salad.
It's scallop and daikon radish
mixed with mayonnaise.
And C.
Vinegared crab. It's crab
and cucumber mixed with vinegar.
But only one of the three is real.
Just one.
In other words, the other two are
the Imitation Series sold by
Kanetsu Delica Foods.
To put it simply, imitation crabmeat
made with fish paste.
Please choose the real one
among eel, scallop, and crab.
That's right.
Eat the crab, scallop, and eel
and just guess which one is real.
It's a super lucky question.
You can't mistake food made with
fish paste that's totally different
for the real thing, right?
Because it's obvious
and you should know this,
so no matter which wrong answer you
choose, you'll go down two ranks.
That means third-class celebs
will disappear.
Second-class will barely stay.
Sorry, we do this every time,
but if the ordinary celebrities
get the last one right,
you're back to first-class.
It's a chance to make a comeback.
Yay...
We do it every time. The others
will either disappear, or...
Third-class will disappear
if you get it wrong.
If we get it right?
You stay third-class.
- We won't go up?
- No.
- We won't?
- Were you listening?
The ordinary celebs will go up.
- What about third-class?
- You stay the same.
Maybe I'll punch you?
You're scary.
They are the representatives.
Four teams are at the edge
of a cliff.
You'll be shamed forever
if you disappear, so don't do it.
Representatives, please come!
Please come here.
Will anyone make a comeback
to first-class?
Do your best, Kiryuin.
It sounds easy, but it's difficult.
It looks difficult.
- Okay, everyone.
- Yes.
I'll tell you
the correct answer now.
You'll see
whether they're correct or not.
When they enter the Absolutely No
room, they'll vanish.
Seriously?
Okay, the correct answer is...
C.
So when they choose A or B,
third-class will vanish.
Do your best.
We want them to vanish
like "bon bon"!
Most teams in the front row
are at risk.
Here and there are at risk.
The third-class celebrities
are at risk.
If you don't choose the correct
answer, C, you'll vanish.
Okay?
The first one here is...
The first one is...
The third-class celebrity who'll
vanish if she's wrong, Mariko Kaga.
Okay.
Oh, no, even I am nervous.
I'm not on her team,
but I'm nervous!
It's over
if she chooses either A or B.
- I see.
- Yes.
They have to be blindfolded.
- It feels so right.
- Is this okay?
I can't see.
It feels so right.
How rude...
First, the omelette-wrapped eel,
which is made with fish paste.
Is it omelette-wrapped eel?
"A: Absolutely No, Imitation Eel"
Okay.
She ate it rather quickly.
- She didn't taste it.
- She didn't.
Next, it's scallop,
which is also made with fish paste.
Her palate would be unsophisticated
if she chooses this,
so she'd vanish.
Okay.
Ms Kaga is quick!
It's quick.
It looks like
she didn't taste it at all.
Is this okay?
She doesn't seem
to have tasted the food.
Next, it's the correct answer, C.
She only needs to choose this.
"C: Correct. Real crab"
- It's taken her the longest to eat.
- Yes.
Which one will she choose?
Not anything besides C.
Yes. She'll vanish the moment
she raises the card of A or B.
Will the great actress choose C,
the correct answer?
It's difficult.
Oh?
It's difficult, but it's C.
But B was made too well.
The scallop?
Yes.
It was made too well.
It's difficult. I'll choose C again.
Wow!
Wonderful! Impressive, Ms Kaga.
We don't have to vanish.
Wow!
I sensed a bit of shell in it.
No way.
So it's...
Maybe it's real crab.
It's impressive
if that's how far you go to do this.
Wow!
Wow, impressive!
Brilliant.
Wow, amazing!
Now you're safe.
She said that,
but was there really shell in it?
- I don't think so...
- No.
No, right?
She either got it wrong,
or someone hates Ms Kaga.
Hard bits...
It's difficult to walk in these.
- Okay.
- Mariko Kaga barely survived!
She stays put
as a third-class celebrity.
The next one is...
Thank you...
"Third-class celebrity
Ryoko Yonekura"
This third-class celebrity
is also at the edge of a cliff.
It's Ryoko Yonekura.
Okay!
Let's see whether Kacchan
will vanish or not.
Oh?
"Might vanish"
What's this? I really can't see.
It suits her.
The lady who never fails naturally
knows which one is real.
First, the fish paste that'll make
her vanish if she chooses it.
"A: Imitation eel"
She loves eel, so I'm sure
she won't choose the first one.
I see.
Next, B.
It's fake scallop. She'll also
vanish if she chooses this.
"B: Imitation scallop"
And C. Will the great actress choose
the correct answer and not vanish?
"C: Real crab"
I hope Ryoko will come here.
"C: Correct"
It looks difficult.
She can't decide.
Good.
Okay, choose.
I have no clue at all.
She'll vanish the moment
she holds up A or B.
What's the answer of Michiko Daimon,
the lady who never fails?
"B: Imitation scallop"
Yes!
Not yet!
Are you kidding me?
Surprisingly, now...
"C: Real crab"
Can she answer correctly?
That was close!
Half of me disappeared.
Her fateful decision is...
- No!
- Yes!
She vanished after all.
Okay, she vanished!
"Not worth showing"
Thank you.
Only his voice.
We only hear his voice.
Either the fibres are well made,
so I feel that it's scallop,
but I can't tell
if it's a real scallop.
She failed!
Michiko Daimon failed!
I thought she never failed.
I'm afraid the lady who never fails
has made a huge mistake,
so Hollywood Zakoshisyoh X
will perform exaggeratedly for her.
"Yonekura"
"B: Absolutely No"
It was C...
I couldn't decide...
between B and C...
"Yonekura"
It's C after all?
Yes, it's C.
The next one is also...
Okay.
From the Johnny's
at the edge of a cliff,
Yuri Chinen, who answered
all the questions wrong today.
He'll decide our fate.
First, it's A.
Eel made with fish paste.
You can't get it wrong, can you?
It's delicious?
Next, B. He'll also vanish
if he chooses this.
"B: Imitation scallop"
Okay, Meguro, Michieda,
get ready to vanish.
Wait, no...
- Please let us pray.
- Please.
As the senior, will he be able
to show his pride at the end?
This is real crab.
What will he choose?
I think it isn't A.
Good, choose B, then.
Which one?
- Man up and choose B.
- Which one?
Choose B.
"Vanish if it's A or B"
- His answer is...
- Okay.
I think...
it's B.
"B: Imitation scallop"
Yes!
Okay, he vanished!
Goodbye, Mr Michieda, Mr Meguro.
People keep vanishing!
Are you kidding me?
I think I felt the fibres of scallop
in the texture.
Good! Chinen, good!
Yes!
Hey...
Two people in a row!
There are more and more Zakoshi!
"Yonekura"
Thank goodness!
But... I'm not confident at all.
I had no idea either.
It's B?
"C: Correct"
The other group
is also at the edge of a cliff.
Third-class celebrity Masaaki Sakai
might vanish miserably.
"Masaaki Sakai"
Hey, Monkey Magic.
Please don't vanish
three teams in a row.
Which one? Will he guess it right?
Wow...
First, the fake eel that'll make him
vanish at once if he chooses it.
"A: Imitation eel"
He's going to say, "Delicious!"
Delicious.
"Delicious..."
See? He said it.
- He did.
- He said delicious.
Oh, no, Masaaki might be in trouble.
Next, B is also
the Absolutely No fish paste.
"B: Imitation scallop"
And the real one, C. You'll vanish
if you don't choose this.
"C: Real crab"
Will he be able to stay
without vanishing?
- What will he choose?
- Okay...
What's that? Really...
Go on. Choose A.
I'll say it.
His answer is...
Yes!
"B: Imitation scallop"
Okay, he vanished!
Now three teams have disappeared.
Goodbye.
K Dash...
The scallop of B tasted
most like scallop salad--
Yes! Monkey Magic!
He is finally back!
"Monkey Magic, GODAIGO"
The Son Goku who swept the world
has made an unexpected comeback!
"Sakai"
"Chinen, Yonekura"
Okay...
- Thank goodness...
- Did you wait for me?
We've been waiting for you.
She's sure.
She's happy and is sure she's right.
She definitely thinks that.
- A was wrong.
- Yeah.
But what was left in my mouth
after I ate C
was different from crab.
- There wasn't any crab fibre.
- No.
Not at all.
If you think about it,
Ms Kaga is amazing.
She is, but she looks lonely
being on her own.
Next, it's Sho Kiryuin, who wants
to stay in second-class desperately.
I'm counting on you.
I'm happy with being second-class.
- Right?
- Yeah, it's enough.
First, it's A. If he chooses this,
they'll be lookalikes.
"A: Imitation eel"
Next, the fish paste of B.
Don't choose this either.
"B: Imitation scallop"
And now...
What happened?
Are you okay?
- What's the matter?
- Is he okay?
What was that?
I wonder what happened.
Kiryuin is acting strange.
This is the correct answer.
"C: Real crab"
I'm counting on you.
- What's the matter?
- You okay?
I don't know.
- He seems to be looking for crab.
- Yeah.
He's looking for it.
What will he hold up?
Stay the same?
Or lookalikes?
"Lookalike if A or B"
Will he be able to choose C?
The real one is...
- A.
- Wait!
Are you kidding me?
That's unexpected.
It's the first A we've got.
"Chinen, Yonekura, Sakai"
- It's divided.
- It's divided now.
It didn't taste like
what eel is supposed to taste...
was cultured and injected in.
Of course,
it's the Imitation Series.
That's how natural food tastes.
Okay, I see.
You go two ranks down
from second-class celebrities
to lookalikes.
So the Kiryuin lookalike
goes to an empty Room A.
What?
It's an empty room!
"Chinen, Yonekura, Sakai"
His voice just now was incredible.
Many people chose B.
I can't turn Mr DAIGO
into a lookalike.
He already is.
No...
This is tough too.
It can't be helped.
Mr Umemiya and Mr Matsukata
both wore them!
The traditional...
It's extraordinary if you think so.
Yes!
- I must wear it, then.
- Yes.
Whoa...
Next, ordinary celebrity
who might come back to first-class,
Nanase Nishino.
"Nanase Nishino"
Now we'll see whether you can go
back to first-class or not.
"Back to first-class if correct"
She can do it.
- Really?
- Yes.
First, it's A,
which will bring her two ranks down.
"A: Imitation eel"
Can she tell?
Next, B, also a wrong answer.
"B: Imitation scallop"
You can do it.
B is good. There are many people.
"Chinen, Yonekura, Sakai"
And C, the correct answer that
only Mariko Kaga has chosen so far.
"Getting tired"
- Wow...
- Ms Kaga made herself at home!
Her back...
She's sitting on her back.
She'll be first-class
if she says C now.
Yes.
"First-class if C"
Her answer is...
It's A.
"Two ranks down"
- Really?
- What?
What?
No way!
"Chinen, Yonekura, Sakai"
I'm sure B was wrong.
I also thought C was too chewy,
and it didn't feel right.
- Kento...
- It's by elimination.
A felt most real...
I don't think it was the eel,
though.
The eel was the one that somehow...
What a shame!
She fell to a third-class celebrity!
"Third-class celebrity"
Mr Kiryuin!
I was rather sure...
Well, it was by elimination.
It's A.
Lastly, the three ladies
who will come back as first-class
if they get it right.
"Borujuku"
Here they are.
- You can do it.
- They look powerful!
They're masters!
Wear your eye masks!
- Wear your eye masks!
- They're wearing them.
- Anri isn't wearing hers!
- She is.
- She is?
Yeah?
They open their mouths so quickly.
First, it's A.
She keeps her mouth open.
You won't choose the fish paste
that isn't eel, right?
Wait, what she said at the opening
might turn out to be true.
Indeed.
"Only we'll stay first-class."
Next, it's B. They also can't return
to first-class if they choose this.
"B: Imitation scallop"
- Really, what will happen?
- No idea.
And this is C, the correct answer.
I like this scene most.
- I like Anri's face.
- It's the best.
Their ranking will go up
to first-class if they choose this.
- Will they be first-class
- It's hard to tell.
or third-class?
I want to go back!
Ready, go.
What will happen?
Wow!
What are their answers?
- Have you decided?
- Yes.
Ready, go.
- It's divided!
Wow!
This is amazing!
Oops...
"C: Correct"
The tinned crab lately is amazing.
No, Tanabe, shut up!
I thought for a moment it was C.
I really couldn't decide,
buy the more I chewed,
the richer the flavour became.
That's right. Tell her, Anri.
When I ate B, the scallop,
I thought the texture was like
the scallop sold at corner shops,
and I could taste the crabmeat in C.
Amazing...
They'll go with it, right?
They'll choose C.
Yes, but the flavour exploded
when I first tried it.
That's enough, Tanabe!
Wow...
What will you choose?
Ms Tanabe knows food better.
I was confused just now.
If I trust my instincts, it's C.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- Really.
- Please say it, then.
- We choose C.
- C.
First-class celebrities!
- Wow!
- Yay!
You made a comeback!
Brilliant!
Well done!
Wow!
They chose C.
"Chinen, Yonekura, Sakai"
It's divided.
Well done! They made a comeback
and are the only first-class celebs!
Let's go.
"The only first-class"
Welcome, ladies.
- Wow!
- It's Ms Kaga!
She's happy.
Ms Kaga looks happy.
She is happy.
- We are divided.
- Equally!
- It's divided equally.
- It is.
What's going to happen?
I've been choosing B
and got them all wrong.
You chose B every time?
I came here every time.
- How many did you guess right?
- Not one.
The fateful announcement
of the result!
Am I going to vanish?
They've already vanished
and have become Zakoshi and monkey,
but please enjoy
their own anxious faces.
Here I am!
"Celeb Master goes to
the room of the correct answer"
- Come!
- Please come.
Please!
I'm going to open the room
of the correct answer.
"C: Correct"
"A: Absolutely No"
"B: Absolutely No"
The room I open
is the correct answer's.
The others
will either vanish or stay.
It's possible
that we've already vanished?
We aren't shown anymore?
Let's do it.
The correct answer is...
No...
Wrong... Oh, no...
I'm scared!
What?
What...
Congratulations!
Yay! Yay!
I knew it.
Congratulations!
Yay...
Yay!
Really?
I've had enough...
We've already vanished!
The whole time we've been here.
We've vanished?
We've vanished.
Why have we vanished?
Because we got it wrong.
Yay!
You're back to first-class.
- Yay!
- It's amazing!
We must know our food.
You looked like you were in
your home's living room halfway.
Yes? Oh, right, you could see.
Those in B are already gone.
Oh, no...
We disappeared?
Yes. We've completely disappeared.
What the heck? It's pathetic.
It's dramatic! Three teams vanished!
Only one is back to first-class!
We have done all the tests.
Let's check.
There is one team
of first-class celebrities!
Brilliant! Well done!
I'm so happy.
Next, two teams
of third-class celebrities.
- And one team of lookalikes.
- Hello.
We had more teams, right?
Yes, we did. What happened?
You disappeared again.
Oops...
What's this?
Hmm...
It's Kacchan's fault?
I think it isn't that different.
- The one who mustn't fail failed.
- Yeah.
Indeed. And it's Chinen's fault
for your team.
Yes, I'm sorry!
It's Chinen's fault.
- And you two are both rubbish.
- What?
- What rubbish?
- Gosh...
Here I am.
Why don't you touch me?
Masaaki was a nice man.
We don't want to see Hama-chan's
Zakoshi after the mini test.
First, matsutake mushroom.
Their answers are...
The correct answer is...
Yes! Yes!
I can do it.
Cello.
- That was easy.
- Yes?
The correct answer is...
What?
- It was easy, though...
- It was...
Jazz.
Oh... I judged based on the trumpet.
Oh, the trumpet.
I didn't listen to the trumpet.
The correct answer is...
- It was the trumpet.
- Right?
Will he vanish as usual?
Taiko drums!
The correct answer is...
Yes!
Painting.
The correct answer is...
Good.
Lastly, it's food. Can he guess
correctly and stay second-class?
- Okay.
- Their answers are...
He chose the fishcake
and ended up being a lookalike.
Try to make it
on the New Year show next time.