For the past two weeks we've been holding the Hamada "Unthinkable" Trials!
Numerous shocking details had come to light over the course of trial,
with the first being....
That he is super sadistic!
In response to Wakky's boasts of having hard abs....
And to the director, Onuma who dressed up as a Red Panda....
...he was definitely sadistic.
Furthermore, gender is irrelevant with Hamada's targets.
This is how he treated Murakami from Morisanchu....
He does whatever he pleases.
In response to that, Hamada himself claims...
It's tsukkomi.
Tsukkomi!?
Rather than using words or simply hitting...
...squeezing them for her was the tsukkomi.
Not even a shade of remorse.
And that's not all!
He farts without embarrassment in front of other people.
And after that, without fail he...
WAHAHAHAHA
...cackles out loud.
This lack of delicacy is just unthinkable!
What was the punishment handed down to Hamada for his crimes!?
As you have observed, Hamada not only excessively obstructs
our jokes, but also those of young comedians.
The extent to which he harasses others has exceeded our expectations.
Consequently, he shall not be excused, and shall receive
the "Sing the Kaeru no Uta song with retches" punishment!
What in the world is that?
I don't wanna do whatever that is.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
Tonight, Hamada will be served with DIVINE PUNISHMENT.
Hamada Masatoshi's Unthinkable Trial
SING KAERU NO UTA WITH RETCHES PUNISHMENT
Enforcement!
Having received a guilty charge, Hamada was strapped to a seat.
Now, Matsumoto and co. will record retches of all musical scales.
What method will they use to completely stomp on sadistic Hamada's pride?
We'll insert twisted paper into his nose holes.
Normally people would sneeze, but since he's an idiot he retches instead.
So do you!
And we'll keep doing it until he retches out all musical scales.
Many kinds of retches then?
We'd like to hear many different retches.
You guys must be stupid.
Ok everyone, let's do this!
What the heck is that?
It's a "she", not a "that".
This is a lady who can sense perfect pitch.
She'll judge what musical note your retches are.
But what the hell are you gonna do with the recording?
Whaaat are you saying?
PUNISHMENT COMMENCES!!
I'll start first then.
Don't move!
What was that?
That was a LA.
We got a LA!
I want to get a MI, if possible.
Let's all try and get notes we choose.
C'mon MI! C'mon MI!
Same as before.
Another friggin' LA!
Don't make a LA sound.
DO NOT DO A LA!
Who could possibly choose what comes out?
Same one.
LA again!?
They've all been LA.
DON'T DO A LA!
I don't know what's a LA, and what's not!
Do anything but a LA.
We got a SO.
Oh yeah, a SO!
Stop moving.
The heck was that?
You went "Oooheee!""
Don't shove it up there so much.
What do you mean?
Not so quick...
That was a MI.
Alright, we got a MI!
Also, can't you make a louder noise?
Maybe try a thicker bit of paper?
Oh I see, and get a low tone?
That was a DO.
Let me wipe my tears.
Ow ow! The hell? It won't go in like that! Ow!
I'm saying it hurts.
It didn't make you retch.
Well it wasn't even in my nose!
At least put it in first!
Your face is soaked.
Why doesn't the sounds come out?
We still need these sounds.
Oh, can you play it again?
We need RE, FA and SI.
In addition....
Well you come and try doing it then.
Don't address her so rudely.
It was the higher DO.
Yay, we go the high DO.
I can't take any more...
No more, I'm telling you.
It was LA.
Yeah, he even said LA.
We need RE, FA and TI.
Yes, three more.
We don't have time to spend so long on this.
It's touching my eye.
We have a RE.
Hell yeah!
Stop making lame noises after you retch.
Did we get it?
It was a RE, like before.
A RE, huh?
I have to make an "AHHH!" sound?
Yes.
With only two sounds left, Hamada's progress stalled.
Unsurprisingly a sadistic person like Hamada is bad at handling attacks.
Stop making a painful face!
Huh, why?
Do it with a smile!
That's right.
It's as though we're bullying him.
Makes us look bad.
And like this, 15 minutes passed.
He really doesn't sneeze.
That was LA.
Really? Sounds like we're getting closer though.
LA, huh?
I think that can be a TI.
You just need a FA now, Hamada-san!
FA is difficult though!
I can't do it!
I wouldn't have a clue.
The tone lowered and became FA at the end.
Let's just use that bit.
We may be unable to use it, so please try again.
Maaan.... it hurts!
You're sticking it up too far Matsumoto.
What's wrong?
You're sticking it too...
Only coughs are coming out.
That's not funny.
I'll only cough if you leave it shoved up. Drag it in and out!
Here I am, trying my utmost hardest.
Yet, right in front of me Koba was yawning.
Kobayashi Hiromichi
Producer
What's the meaning of this?
Is it okay for a producer to yawn right in front of my eyes?
He was the judge.
He was completely nervous before as judge.
What are you doing...?
We should poke his ear a bit too.
What are you doing!?
Change his tuning like that.
Remember it's a FA.
It has to be even lower.
I'm gonna puke, you know.
Puke away then.
Jeez.
You only have a FA left to do!
Hurry up and do a FA!
HURRY UP AND DO A FA!
Ahhh man, this is crazy.
IT'S NOT WOOOORKING!
It's not working.....
Hey man, open your mouth.
Ohhh not my mouth!
It was too high.
Too high? But it's still a good method!
Too low.
No! Not the mouth!
Low? We're getting close though.
Not the mouth!
No! Use the nose. Nose!
We've got it.
YEAAHHH!
OK!
We got it!
So we'll now edit this and arrange it into Kaeru no Uta.
They can do that?
Yes!
After this is the world's most realistic frog's chorus by Hamada!
Don't miss it!
So we've been doing this "Sing Kaeru no Uta with retches" punishment,
and we'd like everyone to watch it today.
The staff had some negative comments regarding this.
They told us just then, right in front of us.
It's not a very pleasant video, they said.
Stuff you! You're the one that made me do it!
If it was Tamaki Hiroshi, it should've made for a more pleasant viewing.
Well, he is a good looker I guess.
Something innate to Hamada is causing people to feel sickened.
It'd be the same for anybody.
Well...let's just take a look, shall we?
Yes, let's watch.
So, here's the video. Enjoy.
CHORUS OF THE FROGS
Children
Hamada Masatoshi
Now, please listen to Hamada's cry from his soul in his
rendition of the "Chorus of the Frogs"
Friends from RICO MUSIC ACADEMY
The song of the frogs
(The song of the frogs)
can be heard.
(can be heard.)
Kwa-Kwa-Kwa-Kwa
(Kwa-Kwa-Kwa-Kwa)
Kero-Kero-Kero-Kero, Kwa-Kwa-Kwa
(Kero-Kero-Kero-Kero, Kwa-Kwa-Kwa)
What the heck was that!?
What the heck!?
That was surprisingly well done!
It's made quite well!
You'd start to feel sick repeatedly watching that while editing.
For sure.
A modern way of saying it is fugly fun.
It was fugly fun.
There's one where you go "Waaaghhh!"
Yeah, like a cry from the soul.
It wasn't too bad if it's only as long as that.
Since we were able to get such great retches
we made another song, that's not the Kaeru no Uta.
Serious?
Thought it may be a good idea.
Please have a look.
Children
DO-RE-MI
Hamada Masatoshi
Doe a deer, a female deer, Ray a drop of golden sun.
*BTW, the Japanese lyrics are very different. I'm just using the Eng version.
Me, a name I call myself, Far, a longer way to run
Sew, a needle pulling thread, La, a note to follow Sew
Tea, I drink with jam and bread, That will bring us back to DO.
Doe a deer a female deer
Ray, a drop of golden sun
Me, a name I call myself
Far, a longer way to run
Sew, a needle pulling thread
La, a note to follow sew
Tea, I drink with jam and bread
That will bring us back to Do.
Woah....
Yeah, that actually was a bit sickening.
The previous one was fugly fun but
this one was fugly gross.
This is a question for Matsumoto, who is said to be able to create a sound effect for anything.
What would Hamada's tsukkomi be if you made it into a sound effect.
For example, how does a dog bark?
Woof.
Oh my god! Dogs just can't stand that answer.
You'd be pissed if you saw an impersonation of you on TV
that looks nothing like you right?
And if he ain't funny, it's like you ain't funny yourself.
Dogs are equally pissed off in regards to the perception that they woof.
They go "Grrrrr!" when they hear that. That noise is the same.
They go grrr?
They actually do go "Grrr".
It's the same with tigers and lions. What's a lion's noise?
"Rooooaarrr!"
That's Oka Hachiro!
Oka Hachiro is a comedian mainly associated with Yoshimoto Shinkigeki. Not sure what relation is, but probably has a gag to do with roaring.
That's "Gaoo!". The audience won't even know.
It's because you've never heard a lions roar up close before.
"TAAAA!", that's it.
I am not joking.
TAAAA!
"Hey you there TAAAA!"
The "Taa" is fine, but what's with the "Hey you"?
Supposing that they could talk.
Okay then.
Well whatever. So what does a dog say?
It's hard to just pinpoint a dog specifically.
But you just specified that lions go "TAAAA!".
Well, we need to hear more than just that one phrase.
I'll start from even before they say it.
What do you mean?
I'll start from when they go for a stroll.
Wait, what?
I'll start from going for a stroll.
Okay then....
So, you're walking along a corridor like squish squish squish
What's the squishing about?
Well, if you listen really carefully, footsteps actually sound like....
squish.
Oh, that's what you mean. Right, since you make sound effects for everything.
Please continue.
Oh, you're fine with that explanation? You sure about that?
I'm definitely getting the dog noise from you.
How do you want me to do it?
The dog's....
Do I need to make it funny?
Everyone is eagerly waiting now, because it's not woof.
At this stage, it's hard for me to say something funny.
Yes of course. I know that.
It's basically impossible to pull this off now.
And yet, will you still make me do this?
You've got to tell us the sound effect!
Okay fine, I'll do it. Of what though?
What about cats? They go "Meow", right?
Yes, cats go "Meow".
Well dogs sound like "Woof" to me.
Yes, you're right.
What?
I think so too.
Wait, what?
Do dogs go "Woof"?
They do say woof.
It's not woof, right?
It's woof. They totally say "Woof".
Big or small, they all say "Woof".
"Grrrr, woof!", that's totally what they say.
What's your problem then?
What?
They're all exactly as they sound then!
Is that some sort of problem?
Well you're the one that objected before!
But I didn't object.....
You said dogs don't woof.
I'm just being made to do this.
You're the one that originally said that dogs don't woof.
But hey, don't you think.....that's your fault?
Why?
Aren't you just making me say these things?
I...I just wanted to have a normal conversation.
I don't understand.
You....You're just making me say this stuff.
It's so depressing.
What is he saying? You're the one that started saying
"You know what lions really sound like!?"
They say "TAAAN!".
You said that!
"Hey you there TAAAN!"
But, well, you know......that's
....just stupid, isn't it?
It's just stupid to continue saying this stuff.
Oh, this is kinda funny.
So now you start saying it's stupid.
I didn't start saying anything.
I'm being manipulated by these letters.
Then you should have just denied that
you can make sound effects for anything.
But if I denied it.....you'd smack me again.
I said "Yes, that's right", because I didn't want to be smacked.
You'd have smacked me if I couldn't think of anything too.
It's corporal punishment.
I try hard because I hate being hurt.
But there are times when I can't try any longer....
JUST SHUT UP ALREADY!
I'm trying hard, even with a blocked nose.
Then stop saying useless stuff and get on with it.
But you'll smack me if I don't say useless stuff.
I don't smack you often!
You smack and kick me.
I don't do it that often.
A normal 42 year old shouldn't even be smacked once.
I don't understand the difference between the popular words kimoi and kishoi.
Both mean gross, disgusting, weird sorts of things.
How should I use each word to sound like a young modern Japanese.
This is an important thing.
Yes. For example, you're kimoi.
What? So I'm kimoi, not kishoi?
I'm the kishoi one. WHO YOU CALLIN' KISHOI!?
Freakin' fools.
How do you differentiate...
Want me to turn you into a wax doll!?
Reference to Seikima-II's famous phrase from their song "Rouningyou no Yakata"
How do you use kimoi and kishoi differently?
Generally, kimoi refers to the actual person.
And the way he behaves is kishoi.
So, you're kimoi.
And you picking your nose is kishoi.
This is kishoi?
Kishoi generally applies to verbs...
...and the person is kimoi.
So, you're basically kimoi and
whatever you do is unavoidably kishoi.
WOAH THAT'S SO KISHOI!
That is so kishoi!
Every single step is kishoi!
....because you're kimoi.
Understand? I can't do anything kishoi.
Because I'm not kimoi.
That's just what you think.
You can't become kishoi if you're not already kimoi.
Yeah of course.
Only the chosen few are able.
People that are kishoi, such as yourself.
Shouldn't I be kimoi?
Which one was it again?
I'm kimoi.
If I move I'm kishoi right?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
So people like you have been stamped with this kimoi mark since birth.
It's not a soft stamp either. It's gonna make a bumps and stuff.
It's the type that stamps on using those bumps.
No idea why I said that twice.
Who gives a crap.