At a certain hot spring, there is an Inn where liars gather
I don't realllly like this series
This series?
You always leave unsatisfied, no matter what
Yeah
But apparently Yamasaki-san is really into this series
It's fun after all
He doesn't have fun at other places
I do!
Time to explain the rules of the Liar's Inn
A card is drawn at random. The person on the card must nominate someone else to tell either a  small, plausible, or massive lie.
The nominated person must improvise everything and maintain the lie!
So, the person to nominate the first liar,
Ah the nominator?
Ah, Endo-san
Endo-san, a plausible lie
This is something I'm worried about,
Tell us about your worries
Yes, I want to tell people,
Matsumoto-san, I've heard you didn't sleep for 52 hours
Really?
Yes really, cause 52 hours is a lot
Actually, I think it was longer than that
Like 57~58 hours I think
Why? You couldn't sleep?
Mahjong Marathon
You've been playing Mahjong?!
A marathon? You play Mahjong?
I suddenly got into it, I learned it last week
You learned last week?
I learned last week, and it's just too much fun
It's so fun now he can't sleep
Even now I can't stop myself doing this
Ah, when you lift the thing
Even if I do this, my other hand starts moving
I can't do just one, the other one moves too
They become synchronised
When you pass 50 hours,
When you do that, this one moves. And when you do this, that one moves.
They become synchronised?
Amazing, just 1 week
You've never done it right?
I have no idea
I don't know about it
What's the best hand?
I keep getting great hands
Yeah so like what for example?
I just say "PON!" all the time
TN: Players call out "Pon!" depending on their hand
If you use "Pon", it usually makes your hand worse
Ahhh yes yes yes yes
If you say "Pon" right?
Yes yes yes, exactly
So you don't say "Pon"?
What have you ever won?!
What have you ever done?!
What goal are you talking about?
Sorry, I mean like, making the hand better
Raising? Right, there are lots of terms for that
I just thought this isn't the time to talk about the rules in detail,
Instead shouldn't you guys ask more about why I'm doing Mahjong Marathons?
Like who I play with and stuff!
Who do you play with?
Who are the regulars?
There's Leah Dizon of course,
That Leah Dizon?
He saw her in a newpaper just now!
Yeah, in the break room!
Coincidentally! (x2)
He's just being influenced by the newspaper!
No no no no
It was just a coincidence, I just met up with her, but like,
If people think there's something going on between us it'll be bothersome for her
So I didn't say anything
Who else is there?
There's also ... Hiroshi Fuse of course
The actor?
You play with the actor?
He does seem like he'd be good at it
And also ... Tiger Jeet Singh
What a cast!
Tiger Jeet Singh?
Sometimes Tiger Jeet Singh isn't there
Tiger Jeet Singh comes and goes
Ah, sorry
I'm so sleepy!!
Well, you didn't sleep after all...
I'm so goddamn sleepy now!
I want to hear more though
I don't think I can, I'm so goddamn sleepy
But I still wanna play!!
Are you gonna play again after this?
Yes. People who've been playing for a long time only play occasionally now
But, since I learned last week, I guess that's how it is
When you learn new things at this age you just get so into it
I can see that
Su-Chi-Mo
Su-Chi-Mo?
It's so Su-Chi-Mo right now
What is Su-Chi-Mo? It's my first time hearing that
It's a catchphrase of mine
A catchphrase you've never said before?
I'M SLEEPY! SHUT UP! I wanna sleep!
Please just elaborate on your favourite hand
Just tell us what your favourite hand is
Yes, the last one, then I'll be satisfied
SUN VISOR!!
What the hell was that
A sun visor right?
Timed & Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
Improvisation Liar's Inn
Maintain the lie all the way through!!
Fully improvised! Liar's Inn
A card is drawn at random. The person on the card must nominate someone else to tell either a  small, plausible, or massive lie.
The nominated person must improvise everything and maintain the lie!
Hamada nominates someone to tell a plausible lie
Hamada-san, plausible,
Tanaka I've heard this about your family, your dad,
He's a banana farmer in the Philippines right?
Eh? A big farm?
He runs a massive farm apparently
I've known him since elementary school, no way
He controls some percentage of Japan's banana imports
Ah, you heard about that? Yeah, this is really just uh,
It was meant to be a secret, who did you hear this from?
When I was eating a banana, someone said to me "Is that a Tanaka?"
Maybe we've eaten a lot of Tanaka Bananas without knowing it
Where were you born Tanaka?
In the Philippines
Eh? No way!
You grew up in Osaka
No no, I did live in Osaka, I did live there of course
What about your Citizen Card?
Yes, it says Manila
Your place of origin?
My origin yes
If you go to a store, can you tell right away which bananas are yours?
I can tell (x2)
How can you tell?
Um, you know,
The straight bananas are our bananas
Those exist?
Our bananas are completely straight
Gross!
Oh, but I might have eaten one before
I remember thinking "Damn this is one straight banana"
Thai bananas are curved like crescent moons right? Ours are straight
Straight...?
Like, almost completely straight
Almost completely straight
Ahhh, like those ones
Right now, in like convenience stores and stuff,
You can buy those single bananas, those are ours.
Those are from Tanaka Farm
Tanaka Farm?
They're Tanaka Farm Bananas
What the brand name?
It's TanaFarm
TanaFarm?
TN: Couldn't hear this part
But you know, I never got the impression Tanaka knows about bananas
Oh really?
So then, is there something that sets tasty bananas apart?
Well, the thing about tasty bananas is ...
How can I explain this...
They have to be completely straight of course, and also ...
It's just so amazing, the ...
The vibe!!
I can't understand a banana's vibe
It's just awesome
A bananas vibe...
Could you explain that to us too?
What was he even trying to say?
Oh dear, this one
Hamada nominates someone to tell a small lie
HamaSho
I have to nominate right? Ok
Yes, a small lie
I heard you got petite plastic surgery?
TN: plastic surgery that doesn't use a scalpel
Where?
What did you say?
I heard you got petite plastic surgery
Ahh damn it man, you're my partner!
Would my partner really reveal this secret my agent is doing his best to hide?
Oh, sorry sorry
This whole time Okamoto and I have been meeting, it's been multiple weeks. I've been telling him to keep this covered up
Okamoto - President of Yoshimoto
Oh really?
And talking to Okamoto on the phone is a pain right?
Yeah, yeah there's a lot to talk about there. He has a really quite voice.
Whispers, that guy whispers
Sometimes all you can hear is him smoking the cigarette
Yeah!
Even though I'm talking
So he whispers like,
Yeah
Is it alright to say this on TV?
Honestly it's not that small a surgery
My nose came off!!
Nose came off?...
Your nose came off? Like in an accident?
Well, yeah, an accident I guess, or rather,
What do you want from me?
I want you to explain that surgery
Please explain!
No no, it just happens sometimes I hear
So it's not plastic surgery then, they just put your nose back right?
Yes yes, it's not plastic- Sorry?
Well to put it simply, yes
This is something that happens sometimes, and the doctor told me to be careful. He said these cases are on the rise.
There's a chance it could happen to us?
Yes yes yes
There's *paran* type, like this way
Oh mine was this way though, but some are like this
It's possible for your nose to come off like that?
And sometimes it can be like *paran*
And when it's *paran* like this sometimes you eat it an-
Even though I just found something!
Even though I found something funny to say just now!
Horrible right?
The split nose styles
This guy thought I was so funny he had to stop me
No no, it's just you kept saying "paran"
Hamada-san just came up twice
Yeah
Hamada-san nominates someone to tell a massive lie
He's gotten every type of lie
He's so good at this
I've recently realised how big of a liar Endo really is
I hate that kind of thing
Endo, you know, you always tell us in the break room you can't use an iPhone, and you've never used a computer,
You say that pretty often right? Like "I don't know what you guys are talking about"
But really, you hacked into the Pentagon didn't you?
..What?
What do you mean?
You're lying right?
I really can't talk about this
Is it so bad you have to,
You have to hide yourself with your sleeve like this?
Impossible
Is it worth covering hiding like that
Cause this is an incredible story
We won't broadcast this, we won't
We definitely can't
Well, if you ask me if it's true or false, well it's true
Eh? Then that means...
Is it alright for us to hear this?
Well, I talk to close friends every week about playing golf, and I was messaging them
And when I received the group message, there was a character I'd never seen before in there
And when I saw the recepients, there were names like Shimuzu-san etc.
But in the middle there was one weird name I'd never seen before
But well, I didn't know what that was, so I just replied
"Alright, let's play golf!"
And when I got the reply, that's when the Pentagon thing...
He skipped so much
Like I really had no idea that thing um...
Your a hacker, right?
You didn't do it yourself?
That's where it starts
So I got the reply, was it the Pentagon?...
It was someone who had questions about the Pentagon
It was a Japanese person. It was a Japanese person living in Hong Kong.
So not the Pentagon then
It wasn't the Pentagon
Well, let's hear more
So then, actually-
Let's listen attentively!
Yes please
I really shouldn't be talking about this
Let's shut our mouths
Endo! I don't understand anything! You haven't explained anything yet.
Yes, I don't understand either
What did he want to know?
So that old man in Hong Kong,
First time hearing Old man
It was something about America needing oil from the Arabs,
But like how do I say,
Something like, "If we don't invent a new weapon, we won't be able to get that oil!"
And then something that was basically like "Ah, that's true"
Who the hell are you talking to?
This is about hacking right?
Who are you talking to? I have no idea at all
Sorry, what we want to hear is how you hacked them using a computer, how did you do that?
You're a hacker right?
What does a hacker do?
What is hacking? What do you press?
After you open the laptop. What's the first thing you do?
After you open the laptop
What do I press?
Hacking
You have that thing right
Mouse
The mouse
Is it alright to say this?
What do you do first?
What do you use first?
What I use?
What OS do you use?
OS? I use this thing called OS-1
Don't say it like it's obvious
That heatstroke drink
It's for heatstrokes
This is bad, this really is
Well whatever, you turn it on and then?
Tell us
What do you do after?
Well it's a laptop, so I lift the lid. And then *Windows startup*
You went like that right?
Yes, so then, I use the mouse like this
Windows right?
Where do you move it to?
That, there's this empty thing right?
Empty thing?
Well first I go to Yahoo! actually
You go to Yahoo first?
I get it, I get it. I think I start with off with Yahoo! too.
I feel that too. Like you can't go wrong with going to Yahoo! first
So after going to Yahoo, well first I want to see what's going on in society
Yahoo Japan right?
Yahoo Japan
Yahoo Japan? Society? Oh the news.
The news, I go there once
Chiebukuro
Yes, there's also entertainment. And I look at everything there.
Well that's fine, you're allowed to look at that
The hacking
How do you do it?
On the Yahoo screen, there's like this search box right?
So I type "hacking" in there, and then look it up
You search for hacking on Yahoo?!
You search for it?!
You search up hacking?
After this: Hamada's new project?!
It's just gonna give you the definition of Hacking
Here I go
Matsumoto nominates someone to tell a massive lie
Matsumoto san's massive
I think this something that might make a big impact in the entertainment industry,
Apparently, Yamasaki is a dog
You used to be a dog right?
It finally comes out huh...
I don't understand what you mean
You don't right? He's a dog
But he's not a dog
I was shocked when I learned
Let's not tell lies like that
Yes let's not
Hamada-san thank you very much. Nothing makes me happier than hearing that
What do you mean?
It makes me so happy to hear you say "He's not a dog"
But just look at him...
I've heard he's a dog, I'm sure of it, I asked for confirmation so many times
Yes, there's no mistake there. A dog is a dog.
Dogs have really strong noses right?
Ah yes, I'm smelling things all the time. Like for example right now,
Like I can tell someone is eating an omelet right now
Nobody here is eating an omelet
Maybe somewhere faraway someone is eating
Yes, yes, if someone is eating somewhere faraway
What about Curry?
I'm really good at picking up food smells
Oh, you can smell it?
Of course!
Oh right of course
It's amazing you can't tell he's a dog
What about pooping?
This is a slightly rude story, but usually I poop at night
Like a dog?
That's not really a rude story...
It's not. Who cares what time you go.
I do have to make sure the litterbox is there
Who puts the litterbox there?
Isn't that for cats?
Isn't litter for cats?
I have the litter put there for me
Maybe my wife got it wrong, I don't know
Oh your wife does it?
Isn't that for cats?
I always use the litterbox. Otherwise I have no idea what to do/
Alright, excuse me, could you just tell us your dog name?
My name is Tama (Ball)
Isn't that also like a cat name?
It does sound like a cat name
It is
It's Tama... Tamarino
Tamarina
Tamarina?
It's Tamarina! Ah, I remembered
It's Tamarina
You forgot it?
Tamarina?
Tamarina
You're kidding right?
I just remembered, it was Tamarina. Tamarina. Yeah.
Ok ok. Tamarina.
Well I did it press it, I just couldn't stand it...
I couldn't Standarina
Here I go
Hosei nominates someone to tell a small lie
Oh you got it
It's a Hosei-Sho (Sho means small)
It's a Hosei-Sho
A Hosei-Sho
I heard this recently I think,
Hamada-san created a Punk Band, was that recently?
Seriously?
I think you better stop
Well, actually I'm not doing it yet,
I'm still looking for members
You haven't done anything yet?
Nothing yet, still in progress. You know like those small places in Shimokitazawa
In places like that, right now I'm...
I'm always gluing posters to walls recruiting new members
Gluing?
Well otherwise they can get ripped off
If Hamada-san puts up a poster so many people will come
Yeah but it's good to find someone with experience,
I just really want to do it,
Punk though right?
I thought of other stuff but I just had to do Punk
No way that's true
What about the name, for your band, have you decided on one?
Punk...
Punk
That's all it is
It does leave an impression
The Punk,
It's The Punk
The Punk?
The Punk
So exactly what the name is
Exactly
Oh so exactly as advertised
The Punk?
Yes yes yes yes
The band members have names too
What do you call yourself?
Me?
Hama-Punk
You know, you're like...
Aren't you ripping off your son?
TN: Hamada's son is in a band called the Okamatos, and his stage name is Hama Okamoto
You're just copying your son
That's the worst
I couldn't come up with anything ... Hama-Punk
Here I go
Hosei nominates someone to tell a massive lie
Yama-chan, massive!
A massive one...
This is something that made me feel sad for him when I heard it,
When I heard Matsumoto-san is under Tutankhamun's curse,
I didn't know how to react
After this: Matsumoto is cursed!?
When I heard Matsumoto-san is under Tutankhamun's curse,
I didn't know how to react
Sorry I don't understand ... Tutankhamun's curse?
It really is awful
If I had to start my life over, if you asked what kind of life I'd want,
I would say a life where I avoided Tutankhamun's curse
Right now too?
I've been under it this whole time
All the time!
When did it start?
Ahhh, it's already been...
I think summer of last year?
So recent!
That's why I'm still not used to it!
If I was used to it then fine. But I'm not so it sucks.
What do you mean by getting used to it?
You'll feel better after that?
I feel like you can get used to a curse. Especially since it hasn't even been a year yet
I feel like I'm still not used to it
What kind of curse is it? Is it painful to your body? What kind of effects does it have?
To sum it up, there's so much eye mucus!
There's so much eye mucus,
BUT THAT'S BASICALLY IT!!
It's just eye mucus?
I DARE YOU GUYS TO SAY THAT'S IT!
There's always so much goddamn eye mucus coming out,
There's no point in even mentioning the curse anymore
I used to mention it, I have Tutankhamun's curse
But I got so sick of saying it, it's tiring,
And everyone asking "Why" is so tiring,
So I've always got this goddamn eye mucus. In the morning I really can't open my eyes
But there's none right now
Yeah exactly I'm getting it treated by the doctor
With some nasty medicine
Drinking some nasty red medicine
You can cure Tutankhamun's curse?
You can cure it with medicine!
That's good then, the curse-
But it's SO bad, like,
There are side effects?
The side effects are awful!
Eh? Like what?
Like it's just awful. Like just so bad, like,
My nose mucus just won't stop coming!
That's it!?
It's either eye mucus or nose mucus
So you have to choose between one?
That sounds horrible
Basically all I can do right now is either stop the eye mucus or the nose mucus
Well in that case, isn't the eye mucus better?
That's what the doctor told me
"Matsumoto-san, you have to choose one"
Have you had those side effects this whole time?
There must be a way to get rid of the curse I think
Yeah, since it's a curse. You don't know how?
You don't how to get rid of it?
Ahh, I know how
You have to drink oil
Really hot oil
I couldn't do that
That sounds pretty awful
Yeah that's impossible then
You could die
You have to drink really hot safflower oil
It's incredible
You could die
I think your uvula would shrink right up
That's a serious thing
You can't get used to that right?
You can't you can't, I won't drink it
That's a really awful cure
But really, Tutankhamun's curse really is scary
I just wanted to say that again
Timed & Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband