The First Annual Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende, Chiki Chiki
Common sense test!
Endo Dokkiri (prank) Quiz~!!
So for today's topic...
before we actually explain it,
maybe it's better to have a look at this VTR first
Roman Holiday (Degawa's favorite movie)
The incident happened during "100 Questions Degawa Tetsuro"
(he must be lying about it)
Who is the person that Degawa admires?
Eh, who could it be...
Please keep an eye on the conversation between Endo and Matsumoto for this question
Please show your answers
Dad
Helen Keller
Mr Shimura
Mr Takeshi
Nagashima
Shigeo
So that's how it is
What's about Helen Keller!!
Helen Keller is true for everyone right
She's a top 5 for everyone right
(She's definitely an admirable person)
Not on my list though...
Eh, not on your list?
Yeah. sorry it's not
What's her rank?
Not even top 100
Are you serious man?
Learn more about Helen Keller dude
She's awesome
Helen Keller...yeah definitely awesome though...
Teacher Sullivan is awesome too
well yeah, but not on my list too
It seems like a casual conversation at first glance
Hosei did not miss out the sense of incongruity here
Yeah right
During the break time from filming,
this sense of incongruity is assured
Hosei: Helen Keller...     Matsumoto: Helen Keller...
Endo also knows about Helen Keller right?
Helen Keller right...
You don't know right?
Someone with superpower...
No, no way, really...
That's Uri Geller!!
That was close
I actually wanted to ask this back then
So he didn't get it when you say Teacher Sullivan
His face was like "what on earth are you talking about"
A doctor?
A nurse?
No, you're mixing up with Nightingale
Not a nurse!!
You know it's man or woman right?
A man...
Don't miss it when there's a 1/2 chance man
He got tricked by Uri Geller!!
Yeah, Geller is a man...
You answered it seamlessly only to find out it was wrong
I see, this happened in previous episodes
It does feel strange when you watch it again
He probably even thought that it's my Boke (Gag)
Yeah, he thought it's a Boke to answer that for an admirable person
Taking it further,
He probably thinks Matsumoto-san is having a dull moment
That's the worst
So for this time,
Actually all of our members did the 100 questions series
Except Endo
Didn't he?
So we thought about letting Endo to do it
Just to find out what do he even know
Using the 100 questions series as a camouflage
to test out Endo's academic ability with some common sense questions
The quiz will be easy right?
Very easy
Just common sense questions
Let's have a look at Endo on the other side
He always make that movement
Yeah yeah, he always do this
-Please wait a moment     -Ok
He won't hear the sound in our studio
He looks stupid
Long time since you said stupid
The way he wear the t-shirt is just stupid
100 questions have been prepared from various genres
to test out Endo's common sense ability
well this have some really good questions
-but the first question seems difficult     -Yeah, it is
so questions like the second one sounds good
Yes
Answer an idiom similar to "Even Homer sometimes nods"
I believe it's not that difficult right
So if everyone agrees, then let's start
Can you tell us an idiom similar to "Even Homer sometimes nods"?
The original phrase "弘法にも筆の誤り" refers to
Kōbō-Daishi, the grand master who propagated
the buddhist teaching as well as a famous Japanese
calligrapher, may also make writing mistakes.
Eh?
It's a bit...
It's too difficult all of a sudden
Ye...yes, eh?
Can you tell us an idiom similar to "Even Homer sometimes nods"?
Should have asked the first question
Yeah we should
He looks completely clueless
He's like "what are you talking about?"
He must be shocked
Monkeys also fall from trees
How come he knows the answer? What's happening?
Why did you ask that?
You knew the answer?
For the idiom?
Yes
It means even the most skilled, can make a mistake right?
He's starting to look smart now
The screen will change when this is pressed
He answered it
He's probably in doubt with the question
Yeah, he's like why are you asking this?
We have to ask some usual questions
Ask him what's your favorite road?
What is your favorite street?
We've all been asked about this
It's Meguro-dori (dori=street)
It somehow sounds stupid
He's like "it's coming, it's coming"
yeah like "this is it, this is it"
We shall start again for the next question
Then what about asking this question?
Yeah, we do want him to answer this
It's common sense, it's a good question
Can you tell us the name of Sunday to Saturday in English?
From Sunday in English?
He's in doubt that he's being quizzed right?
What? He's able to answer it isn't he?
He's seems to be smarter than we thought?
Endo's common sense ability is completely underestimated
He can answer, he definitely can
We've probably just thought Endo to be too stupid
No, no, no way
After that, Endo continues to...
Do you know the meaning of "ginger" in "ginger ale"?
Well...it's Ginger (生姜)
...answer the questions correctly
Can you tell us who is "Itō Hirobumi"?
The first Prime Minister of Japan
What is happening here?
There's already no more questions for today
If this continues, today's show will be ruined,
so what about asking questions from a different angle
Fake questions
People should normally notice this though...
Mixing questions into the common sense quiz
which are totally fake and non-sense
what kind of reactions will Endo show us!?
"Rashōmon" and "Ginga Tetsudō no Yoru"
are actually NOT written by Natsume Soseki
What is the famous novel written by Natsume Soseki, other than "Rashōmon" and "Ginga Tetsudō no Yoru"?
Botchan is one of the most famous novel in Japan, read by many Japanese during their school years
He'll probably end this by answering Botchan
That's the worst
Question number 55
What is the famous novel written by Natsume Soseki, other than "Rashōmon" and "Ginga Tetsudō no Yoru"?
Look, I told you
-Who is it again?     -Natsume Soseki
Ehhh?
He didn't even notice it's fake
You normally should though
Botchan
This is it!!
No Endo, that's not the main point
His answer Botchan was just as we predicted
There's a connection here between Natsume Soseki and Botchan, but not the other ones...
There's so many this kind of questions isn't it?
He's still in doubt of it...
Should it be like this?
-He can't spell alphabets     -I think so too
Really?
Well yeah, he was like that before
He wasn't able to spell "三權分立 (Separation of powers)" before right?
What about the Citizenship Obligations? The three obligations
That's in question number 15
Question 15 please
Can you tell us, what are the three Citizenship Obligations?
I've actually answered this in the previous episodes of Gaki no Tsukai
Yes you did
I'll answer it then
Compulsory education
Taxation
Eduction, taxation...
Eat?
Hey you did it before right!
-It pops up sometimes     -Yeah
Good answers pop up sometimes
And that's why we can't stop doing this
So citizens can't be on a diet
Yeah indeed
How about question 9
-Ahh sounds good     -Then let's go for it
Can you tell us the 3 requirements essential for Photosynthesis to occur?
Sunlight
Carbon dioxide
Starch
Starch? Potatoes?
Starch...Starch...
Starch is in it right?
Starch is in it right??
Yeah starch is in it, of course starch is in it...
Well yeah, it's this kind of questions
I see
Well he's just being truthful...just truthful
That's all
What about questions like the top 3 beauties or the top 3 delicacies
He doesn't seems to know the top 3 delicacies...
Can you tell us the world's top 3 delicacies?
Foie gras
"Triffles", "Troffles", "Treffles"
Caviar
Foie gras, "Troffles", Caviar
He said it's "Troffles"
Foie gras, Tri...Troffles, Ca...Caviar
He've been pronouncing it ambiguously on purpose for all this time
This is how he goes on with life
He've never eaten it before?
Should we add some normal questions?
Ah, so the usual questions. What should we ask...
What about his nicknames?
Like his nickname during primary school?
Won't he say it's advantageous for Tanaka?
Do he still thinks it's 100 questions?
That's being stupid too though
What is your nickname during primary school?
It's En-chan
-He must be thinking someone is answering it     -Yes, he definitely is
I thought 100 questions series should be asking these kind of questions
He's looking for these questions too
He must know how to calculate the area of a triangle right?
I feel worried about his maths
-Really?     -I bet he don't know
Let's have a try
Maths question number 8
Can you tell us the equation to calculate the area of a triangle?
Base times height divided by 2
Why is he talking like that?
I feel really pissed off
Answering it all of a sudden
It suddenly came to his mind isn't it
I think he won't know the area of a Trapezoid
I bet he won't know about Trapezoid
You're such a bad guy
Please ask him the area of a Trapezoid
Can you tell us the equation to calculate the area of a trapezoid?
I don't really know what is a Trapezoid though
What shape is Trapezoid?
If you don't know the shape of a Trapezoid then that's the end of the story
Yeah it'll be impossible to tell the area for sure
It's just impossible
BASE    x
HEIGHT  ÷
More and more questions coming up!!
What about asking the same question again?
What is the famous novel written by Natsume Soseki, other than "Rashōmon" and "Ginga Tetsudō no Yoru"?
Then get him to tell an answer other than Botchan
and hopefully he would say "wait a second, after all..."
No, he won't say that, we just tested that
Other than "Ginga Tetsudō no Yoru" and "Botchan", what is another famous novel written by Natsume Soseki
I see I see, that sounds good
What is the famous novel written by Natsume Soseki, other than "Ginga Tetsudō no Yoru" and "Botchan"?
I've said it's Botchan just now right?
-Other than Botchan     -Other than Botchan?
-Ginga Tetsudō no Yoru...     -He's noticing it right
...Botchan, and another one?
Come on, notice it man
Eh, what is it again?
What is this guy struggling with?
Ask him are you thinking about "Rashōmon"?
I think I've got it
I Am a Cat
Here it comes, a classic one from Natsume Soseki
Eh, Natsume Soseki?
-Ginga Tetsudō no Yoru     -Wow, it's coming, it's coming
I Am a Cat, Botchan, yeah it's right
He just said it's right
Ginga Tetsudō has completely chugged out of the station
Ginga Tetsudō translates to Galactic Railroad,
it's basically a metaphor to describe that
Endo is going completely wrong
There's no way to stop anymore
There's no terminal stations
He drank water
Let's go for some usual questions?
Let's go for some usual questions
What's the most abnormal sex experience you have had?
Well yeah, this is going to a bonus chance for him
Don't know will it be aired though
What's the most abnormal sex experience you have had?
He's laughing
With a women...
We both wore a helmet for motorbikes...
and did those things
What a fool
Both of them wore a helmet...
What about this, the world's six continents
I feel worried
Maybe start by asking him how many continents are there
Then you can't mention 6
Ask him to name all of the continents on earth
Can you name all of the continents on earth?
Eurasia continent
Africa continent
Antarctica continent
Oceania continent
Awesome
America continent
Brazil continent
That was awful
Ask him to answer it again
-One more time please     -Ehh
Wait a second, let me imagine the earth...
Eurasia continent
Antarctica continent
Africa continent
Oceania continent
America continent and Brazil continent
Why Brazil? Why is Brazil there?
It's probably a really big place in his mind
It's actually quite small though
So there's 5 continents
This is just horrible
Amazingly horrible
What about question 12 for science
Answer the five senses of the human body
Can you name all five senses of the human body?
I told him there's 5 this time
Mouthfeel
Mouthfeel? Mouthfeel?
He means taste right
The Sixth Sense
Come on, we told him it's the five senses
Mouthfeel...mouthfeel...
Leave mouthfeel alone
Pain-sense, the organ that senses pain, pain-sense
Never heard of that before
Pain-sense, the Sixth Sense
View-sense
Hear-sense... Sound, Sound
He got this, he should be able to finish it all then
That's all
How could that be all
Wow, that was amazing
I didn't know it was this horrible
Will he know about The Journey to The West?
You mean all of the members?
He should be able to name it...
Well, regardless of whether it'll be aired, let's give it a go?
Can you name all of the members in The Journey to The West?
Monkey
Eh?
Why phrasing it this way
Is he joking
Pig
Kappa (folklore)
Monkey, pig, kappa
Well, although it is...
They all have a name right
And lastly...a nun
Wow, he said a nun just now
That's just because Natsume Masako-san was acting for a male role
Maybe also ask him what is the story about
Yeah ask him to tell us the story of The Journey to the West
Please tell us the story of The Journey to the West
Story?
Well the monkey...
umm...
and kappa and pig was...
was together with a bald lady
That's enough
While they'll be in trouble with many happenings
If the monkey is going too far...umm...
The bald lady will punish the monkey by squeezing the thing on his head
Don't he know their names? This is pissing me off
It's Tripiṭaka Master, and he's not a lady
Revealing the prank to Endo!!
-Good work, good work     -Thank you
It's not 100 questions?
No it's not
When did you start feeling strange about it?
Well, I didn't really found anything strange
Ah, so you thought it'll be like this for this time?
I asked the staffs about having a lot of difficult questions
It's not that difficult at all though
Your answers to The Journey to the West was horrible
So you don't know their names right?
Masaaki Sakai right?
No, no no no
That's the name of the actor
You're just a television kid
That's not what we're asking for
No one would answer like that
We would never answer it like monkey or pigs...
But it's indeed a story about monkey, pig and kappa right?
-Well yeah, but they have their names too     -Name?
Is he in Dragon Ball, and wearing those Golden hoop
Yeah, it's in Dragon Ball
Exactly his name
Ah! Goku
-Son Goku     -Yes, yes, exactly
Ah, really?
I'm actually not really familiar with The Journey to the West
We know that, we clearly know that