Dressing room before rehearsal
Anything else?
We have some
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Around 30
- I see
They're all different courses
I'd say 3
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Hosei
They're all for Suga
Say that before
Well, yeah
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, is that what you meant?
But last year it was different, right Suga-chan?
Mhh?
He can't do that, right?
Itao!
Good morning
Itao entered the dressing room without permission
What's up?
Well, Shichihenge
Well... Shichihenge...
Eh? Today?
Yes
We didn't hear...
No, well, if you haven't heard it, well...
...Shichihenge
Guerilla-style
No no no no, well, that's-
You're laughing!
...you're laughing...
We're not laughing...
When we're about to film a Shichihenge episode we usually...
Have our guest here and we pretend to do stuff, you know...
There's no need for you to pretend to do anything
Starting from this year
But that's how we always do it
We're not even ready for it
Sorry but, that's...
I understand, sure
But anyway, about that...
But you know, he just laughed
So let's go with 1,000 yen
All of a sudden, Itao demands money
This is messed up, isn't it?
Who laughed...?
Tanaka did
Tanaka, did you laugh?
I didn't really laugh...
Hey, you laughed
I was... surprised? How should I say it?
Surprised? You laughed!
Hey, he laughed didn't he?
Who is he...
Who laughed?
This guy, this guy. Everyone!!
She says everyone laughed
Me? I didn't laugh though
You're kidding!
Anyway, gimme 1,000 yen each, please
We didn't lau-
Everyone...
Everyone laughed didn't they?
Everyone laughed
That's ridiculous, I didn't laugh
Where was she before?
She just appeared...
If that's the case...
Even if we pretend we all laughed, we should...
Ah yeah, then 1,000 yen will be donated to charity
Are we gonna give money to charity?
Well, this time though
I'm doing this for myself
So let's just not do the charity thing
Let's be clear about this, so if we happen to laugh...
Then what do we do?
Just give me 1,000 yen for now
You heard him, Tanaka
Itao keeps on requesting money against everyone's will
You laughed right?...
He clearly laughed
Alright then, I admit it
You laughed, man
We're having a meeting here, so...
Oh, sure, sorry about this
Thank you for dropping by
What was that for?
No clue...
That's not shichihenge
He just got in and forced us to do it
That's right
Did you laugh?
I don't think I laughed, to be honest
To be honest, the only one who laughed was Heipo
Yeah, Saito laughed
Director Saito Toshihide
He laughed to his heart's content
Yeah, he did
It felt like he saw a fairy or something
He really got him
EDITING BY SHION
TRANSLATION BY SHION & WA
TYPESET BY WA
fb.com/shionnotsukai
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
w--a.net/shappuri-agemasu-subs
There's something that's clearly pissing me off about that...
His "wife" isn't the woman
I saw at his wedding ceremony
That's a different person, isn't she?
That was surprising
Itao enters the rehearsal room again
Hey, Itao
What are you doing?
The second round of shichihenge
Are you actually doing this?
I know you said I can't and stuff
But I came here to do this shichihenge
Yeah, but you've decided this on your own
Please say something
So... the money...
Eh? Who laughed-
Well, everyone laughed just now
Someone went "ha ha ha ha"
Who laughed?
This guy, this guy. Everyone!!
Right? Everyone laughed didn't they
Alright then, let's pay up
We don't have a choice
Are you for real?
He's so persistent
I never agreed to this, but whatever
But that's not ok, Itao
You know the rules
This is extortion
No but, 1,000 yen is the rule, right?
We're still in the middle of our planning meeting
So please, can you stop coming so suddenly?
I bet our audience is puzzled too
Sure
Ok, miss wife?
For sure!
That wasn't a conversation!
I understand, alright
We're talking here
You're talking, alright
Alright then!
What's the point of this if his "wife" says we all laughed?
That was around 10,000 yen
I've paid before too
It's 8000 yen
A total of 8000 yen
That's so out of character for him right?
Producer Suga Kenji
But he's still doing it
His wife is so annoying
I laughed because of her before
It's a cheap trick
His wife is really something
Say, Itao...
Yes?
What are ya doing?
This is the third one
Itao continues to do shichihenge without permission
Really... go home?
But I can't just stop halfway through it can I?
Halfway through what..?---
I thought this was shichi-henge, seven changes
Well, I've actually prepared like 9 or 10 changes
The people who created Shichihenge are not accepting Shichihenge...
What's all that about?
I've never seen anybody
Refuse a shichihenge so damn hard before
What the hell?
I don't know but--
Please accept this new form...
But you see, that's how it is...
In shichihenge we
We are trusting each other, you know?
And then we get suddenly attacked by someone, out of nowhere
Take the surprise away from it and we wouldn't laugh
But everyone laughed!
No we didn't all laugh...
You all laughed!
No, none of us did
Look at him, he's laughing
Yeah but he's...
He's a *********, so...
Hey, who laughed?
This guy, this guy... !!
Everyone, right?
Everyone, everyone
That's not true
For sure
What the fuck?
Alright, 1,000 yen please!
Everyone laughed
I didn't laugh
I'm not paying up, I'm sorry
No way, you have to pay up
This is messed up, Itao
It's messed up, right?
Alright then, let's have Heipo pay for us
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7
It's 7,000 yen
Seriously, let this be your last one
Alright, see ya
Later
Fujiwara!
Send him home!
Yes, yes, sorry
What is this? Send him home!
Manager Fujiwara Hiroshi
Yes, sure
Tell him to go away
Why are you eyes red all around?
I got hay fever, sorry...
Really?
There's a lot going on here
Hay fever? What the heck
It's Heipo's fault too
You clearly laughed, man
He got after us 'cause you were laughing
Gotta stay alert
I really didn't expect that
I'm not good with that
That's no good
The Itao family prepares a shichihenge
That's not shichihenge
Oi you...
Everyone laughed didn't they
Well, not really, but...
Yeah, I won't deny it
I think that was kinda funny
I know, right?
But this... just doesn't work as a shichihenge
Alright but... you laughed, so pay me up
5,000 yen
5,000 yen each
5,000 yen for each one of us?
Look, that is worth 5,000 yen each
"That"...?
I spent some serious money on this
But you're doing this all by yourself
My kid worked hard on this
And you're not gonna give her any recognition...?
Alright, here's 1,000 yen
No, it's 5,000 yen each
It's the right price for such a big skit
Really!?
Didn't seem that big to me...
You just painted some cardboard boxes
And you said you spent money for this? I doubt it
Of course it costs money
Didn't cost money, right?
For sure!
It cost money, right?
Which is it?! Seriously which is it?!
One person didn't pay up
Ah okay, it's 10,000 yen
We all paid up
Man...
Miss wife, please don't ever show up again, won't you?
She ignored me!
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com x w--a.net/shappuri-agemasu-subs
translated by Shion & WA / typesetted and QC'd by WA / edited by Shion
Whatever, man
Sorry for the bother
See ya
Please continue
Just leave us
What's going on here?