Original French translation by Razuberii - English subs by Joel Ratman!
Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahande, 1st ever "Let's play retro games on the FAMICOM! (NES)"
Did you ever play Famicom when you were young?
Yeah, I played it before - Yamasaki played a lot too
Yeah, I played it a lot
We've brought in the old games today.
Playing them will bring back memories.
What do you think?
What game would you absolutely want to play again?
For me I think Mario Bros
I think Mario as well....
And also Donkey Kong.
I'd love to play Donkey Kong again too.
I confess, today's theme doesn't excite me that much..
A kid with a 7.3* haircut would not be motivated to play
Yeah, not motivated by games.
*The most perfect an trendy haircut, it had to have a quiff at the front with a ratio of 7:3 (?) Endo's hair would have taken priority over video games.
At the time everyone was like "Games, games", but I was always out playing baseball with my Dad.
You played baseball with your dad?
Yeah, playing baseball with dad...
What about Downtown-san?
Playing the shooting game, Space Invaders
Downtown playing on the table        game at GAME CENTER
It's scary to remember how poor it made us.
Seriously, at 100 yen per game, for us that was...
For us this was the "sum of death..."
A "lethal dose" at 100 yen!
Then we just watched others playing.
People spending money like it grew on trees...
I thought  this is  not  even  possible  -  "THESE guys are the extra-terrestrials!"
They arrive at the studio
Follow me, it's in here!
I feel really excited all of a sudden!
UWAH! LOOK AT ALL THE GAMES, THIS IS CRAZY!
In the studio there is a mountain of old game cartridges for the nostalgic Famicom.
In total there are...
743 GAMES!!!!
Hello and welcome everyone!
You waste no time!!
Already he's right here before us...
And this is?
This is Fujita-kun.
All these games belong to him.
EEH? ALL these are yours?
Yes, sir.
Fujita
The celebrity specialist in video games, Fujita.
I'll show you a photograph of my room.
-Yes, it's mine.
This is yours?
I live in this 2LDK* so I can store all my games.
*A standard apartment type in Japan with 2 bedrooms, lounge, dining and kitchen.
I collected all these games one by one, especially for this day.
What we see behind us here are all your games?
-Yes.
Fujita-kun, what were you doing when you were a kid?
What did I do? Uh, games...
He's asking what got you into it!
BagOOOOON!
Sorry, I was focused on my presentation, I misunderstood you...
No matter how many games you played, you have no strategy against this guy...
You have no defense against this "BOSS"
First they go to admire and rediscover the games.
UWAH, brings back memories!!!
Ah, I know these games!
There's Donkey Kong...
I didn't know there were so many versions of DK.
Ah, have you seen these before?
There's PAC-MAN!
And XEVIOUS as well!
And here it shows month by month the events he went to that year...
"In August 1983, I went to Koshien* for the final which pitted PL gakuen and IKEDA"
*A famous baseball stadium in Nishinomiya (Kobe pref) which hosted the annual championships.
You were there too?
Yes, I was sitting in the "Alps"*
*The name given to the benches surrounding the field
*Japan's Prime Minister from '72-'74 - In Oct '83 he was convicted of taking million dollar bribes from Lockheed.
Hamada wept when Tanaka Kakuei* was convicted at his trial.
As if I would cry for that!
I have no idea!
Why was he crying?
He must have admired him.
WTF!!!
Finally he cries bitterly...
Finally he...OW!
GOOON!!
What did I say??
Wow, there's even ELEVATOR ACTION!
AAAAHHH!
You had to use a lot of lifts and doors...
Yeah, that was a great game!
There were many TABLE machines with this game.
And there's also YOSHI'S COOKIE!
It was a very cute game.
I played it lots with my girlfriend at the time but could never beat it...
...In the end I got so tired of it I threw it out.
Anyway, it's time we should start!
Now the members will compete through the games on the Famicom!
Each member will choose a game. Then they will take turns to play.
The highest score will be declared "King of Famicom"
The battle will commence with Housei's game choice
I chose a cartridge.
I picked ARKANOID
Maybe Matsumoto-san will be good at this game.
Oh, Arkanoid...
-Year of release 1986-
ARKANOID
The game involves clearing bricks and objects with the aid of a ball
The objective is to clear every brick to complete each level
The essential skill is use of the control lever to move.
We will start with Hamada-san.
EEH with ME?
Hamada-san, we're counting on you!
The graphics shouldn't confuse you too much.
WAH, it's nostalgic!
Be careful!
What are you looking at???
What are you even doing, GO HOME!
Do your best! If you can take a capsule get it!
You want to die for a capsule!
Seriously, what are you doing?
I'm not telling!
Get that green capsule!
WAAAH!
It's scary to watch...
Result: 3100 points
tsukai ya arahende
Downtown no
gaki no
Famicom Battle: Tanaka challenges Arkanoid!
I'm sure Tanaka will be bad at this game.
I beg to differ - I think he will be gifted at this.
Focus on the bricks, you're not obliged to get capsules
Nice one! You're playing really well!
Wah, I would have done that too...
Why don't you take that capsule Tanaka?
If he takes a new capsule it will be a new item...
...And he prefers the long paddle as his item
This one has the most success right?
Gon!
GON!!!
In the end Tanaka does not succeed.
Result: 9940 points
Though we kept complimenting you.
It's Endo's turn to play.
From playing baseball, your reflexes must be good.
I should not have said that, it disrupted you.
Result: 1830 points
The joystick is harder than I thought it would be.
They struggle to master the controls
Next in the ARKANOID challenge is Matsumoto!
I see it's necessary to press hard on the joystick.
Wah, but I don't know what strength I need to move with
OYYYY!!!
BOGOON!
WHAT are you doing?!?
YOU can talk!!!
Wait, wait, I just need to find my timing...
GOGOOOOOON!!!
WTF are you doing???
What is this? That was horrible!
If you score less than me that's scary.
EEH! Watch out now!
Be careful!
He was good then
AAAGGGHH!!!
I didn't expect that at all, you got over 3000 points!
Results: 3540 points
It's not that though... I didn't think the joystick would be so sensitive
Yamasaki got us with this controller!
Now it lies with Yamasaki to show his ability with the game he has chosen...
He's good at holding it stable.
Ah, he's really keeping the paddle stable.
You're almost there! Keep it up!
Wah, it's going fast!
You're gifted! You're going to succeed!
Bravo! Just keep it going!!!!
Housei-san, hang in there!
Waaah, what just happened?
It's okay, there's no problem
He actually said something...
Nice! There's just one left!!!
OH! BRAVO!
Well played, bravo!
Youre good!
It's stability that is needed to succeed
Geez, you love saying that!
STABILITY-GUY!
He has mega "Stability-ability!!!"
Super! He succeeds with "stability shot"
All done...
Results for ARKANOID
You totally won.
Year of release: 1985
Dig dug
Next is Tanaka's game choice: DIG DUG
In this game, it is possible to kill an enemy by dropping a rock onto them
...or by bursting them with the aid of the air pump.
By eliminating all enemies, the level is clear. ACTION GAME!
First we will see how Tanaka performs!
So this is DIG DUG?
Yes, it's DIG DUG.
UWAH, how nostalgic!
Brings back memories!!!
If you go right to them it's a bad move
Ah you did it purposely to attract it?
No, not at all...
Use your pump against them!
AAAAAGGGH!
Uwaaaah!
What do you press?
We're not telling you that!
Glitch!
It went buggy...
PFF! What's going on! This ain't the time for glitches!
What's going on Fujita-kun?
Next is Matsumoto - will he give a good performance?
I feel like he's gonna win.
Are they allies on the side?
They're here! Right behind you!
I'm telling you they'll get you!
No way, I'm gonna run away.
Ah, I see, that's how to do it.
I get it, we can use the rocks against them.
What, you're kidding me!
That's bullshit!
These things are annoying!
You have to press 4 times to explode him.
Oh yeah, I totally forgot!
That's it...
EEEEEH?
Finally - you just need the right technique.
You're really good anyway.
Matsumoto fumbled a bit on his first level. Now let's see the second
Ah no no no! AAAAAGH!
Oh no!!!!!
Results: 9940 points
Housei is faring moderately.
While Endo's turn is very bad.
Finally we come to Hamada's turn!!
Here they come! They're right behind you!
What am I supposed to do?
Just try to kill one of them first!
Are you SERIOUS?
- I really tried to do it!
You got surrounded there!
Can I get some help?
You need to press the button 4 times to kill it.
Oh good, so I press 4 times?
Yes, not once but 4 times.
OK, gonna press 4 times...
What are you doing?
What are you DOING!!!!!
WTF ARE YOU DOING!!!!
You can get the carrot!
WHAT THE HELL - I can't believe you could get that carrot...
What are you doing?
AAAAARRRGHHHH!
That is too hard!
Too difficult for old man...
Are you friggin' serious?
You still managed to get 2410 points.
Results for DIG DUG
Hell yeah, I won!
Donkey kong
Endo may have a chance with a game he played before - DONKEY KONG'S HIS CHOICE!
With Mario's first appearance, this game became the centrepiece of the Famicom.
Mario must save the princess who was abducted by Donkey Kong in this ACTION GAME!
Hamada is the first one to take the challenge!
So far we can say Hamada hasn't exactly shined.
It's possible he could even die before it starts.
This is how you jump?
I was just checking that this button is jump.
That was such a stupid end, I can't even comment.
It's not even funny.
After the unthinkable but true, Hamada doesn't even get past the first level.
What did he score?
Hamada-san scored ZERO POINTS?
EEEEH? ZERO POINTS!??
ZERO POINTS!!!!????
EEEH? ZERO? NO POINTS!
Among the next 3 players, Housei gets the best score.
Now comes Matsumoto's turn!
Unlike Hamada, he seems to have the skill to bring Mario to rescue the princess.
I wanted to get that one.
How long will the hammer last?
He can't go up with the hammer.
You're good!
He already has 2200 points!
WHAT?
This is annoying, he's still only on his first life...
He totally says nothing...
YYYEEESSSS!!!!
WAH, this part brings back memories!
I remember this...
Hamada-san, do you remember this too?
Yeah, I remember too...
He's gifted!
That's so fast!
You made it!! That's awesome!
It's no real surprise that I'm so good.
It's because I remember how.
WAH, this level is evil...
It's hard to get past.
EEEH? Wait, what?
He can't jump when he is holding the hammer
He can't jump with the hammer?
You should have said it earlier Fujita-kun!
I couldn't jump with the hammer!
Matsumoto wins this round!
Released in 1985
10 yard fight
The next game is Hamada's choice: 10 YARD FIGHT
The first American football game for FAMICOM.
Using your team and collecting items to get past the opposing team...
Hamada is the first to try the game.
Let's party!
Wah, again it brings memories!
OK - I receive the ball and the team runs together...
Which is Hamada-san?
He's the team in the blue uniforms...
In blue?
Yeah, he's the team running up the field.
So he is running up the field?
That's right.
That's it, go go run faster...
I stopped to tackle so I can advance!
Hurry up you can still pass the ball!
It doesn't help to shake the controller.
Just press the buttons, the controller is old.
Yeah, ok I understand.
Don't be shaking the controller just to get laughs.
It's not even your role to be BOKE!*
*The classic Japanese comedy duo consists of "Boke" (fool) and Tsukkomi (derisive partner) - Matsumoto suggests that Hamada is reversing their roles
That wasn't my intention!
Stick to your own role!!!
So far, there is no sign of improvement from picking up items or that the game will ever end.
How do you know when this will finish?
True, how do we know?
Haha WTF there's still more!
It says "High School 2nd half"
This still isn't finished?
We can't show this shit on TV...
We seriously can't broadcast this.
You can just show his "first half"...
Your "party" is too long.
We have to be honest about your choice.
This is simply embarrassing!
Release Date: 1985
Famicom Battle! - Next up is Matsumoto's choice - 1942
This game involves destroying as many enemies as you can while avoiding their shots.
The first challenger will be Housei.
So which buttons do I need to press?
I don't know, I haven't played this game very much
So I just fire with the A button?
Yeah, that's what Fujita-kun said.
I'm firing with "A", but there was also something that allowed a "dodge" in critical moments.
UWAH! You're good Housei-san!
But you know, I haven't played this for ages so I don't remember the buttons.
The same for me...
Despite this, Housei displays a beautiful performance!
Whoa nice! Now you have 4-way shots!
Geez, I'd love to play like him...
WAAAH! Did you see what he just did?
What a dodge! WHAT A DODGE!
Yama-chan, what an epic dodge!
What a superb dodge!
Such a good dodge. Did I tell you it was a great dodge?
AAAH! OYYYYY!!!!
AAH! OYYYYYY!!!!!
What's up?
Results: 18950 points
He said "OY!" To Hamada!
Tanaka plays next.
C'mon man, you need to just press A
Not so hard like that...
That was a good dodge.
Hey BE CAREFUL!
DANGER!
BE CAREFUL!
Results: 4400 points
It's over.
Endo and Hamada didn't shine in previous games.
In this game Endo fought a good battle of courage.
The last player is Matsumoto - He's ready to take it to a whole different level!
Matsumoto challenges the game 1942!
The highest score is 18950 points.
He starts his game smoothly.
And his score increases bit by bit.
WAAAH!
I can't believe my eyes!
That was scary!
WAAHH!!!
That pisses me off!
Such a close call...
Yes, c'mon, c'mon...
There's the aircraft carrier!
That just means the end of the level.
You made it! Nice, such a good job!
Look at his score!
What were WE doing?
He's too gifted!!
You're right - it's kinda weird.
Eh? The sea?
Fujita-san, is all that the sea?
Below him?
Ah sure, yes that's the sea.
AAAAAAHH---!!
Gotta keep going - I really want to get to the big plane.
I want to see that!
AAAAAAHHHH!!!!
Ah, I'm hurting my fingers!
Anyway, you totally smashed the high score.
Results: 35350 points
That was awesome!
He made 35350 points!
FYI, here is the boss Matsumoto mentioned.
The giant bomber plane from this game...
...when reaching the end of level 7.
Now all the games have finished.
Matsumoto has become the FAMICOM KING!
Just look at those scores.
Matsumoto has finished 1st in this battle.
Indeed...
Last is.... Hamada-san.
EEH? TOTAL 9560 points?
Even MY score was over double that!
It's clear you simply cannot operate a controller.
The worst was him scoring ZERO on Donkey Kong.
Yeah, obviously...