Downtown's Hamada "Unthinkable!" trial.
The immature and arrogant acts that show business's
most sadistic man has engaged in are too numerous to mention!
People say......this man is unthinkable!
As a result, we held an emergency project!
We open the court for the Hamada Masatoshi "Unthinkable!" Trial!
Now, we open court for the 1st Hadama Masatoshi "Unthinkable" Trial.
Judge
Kobayashi Hiromichi
Will the attorney and the members of the jury please enter?
Endou Shouzo
Attorney
Juryman
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Yamasaki Housei
At last, the accused, Hamada Masatoshi, please enter.
Defendant
Hamada Masatoshi
I don't understand why I'm even here.
Shut your trap!
Your honor...
...please give him the death penalty!
We'd like you to accept a death penalty.
You haven't even proven anything yet!
You see, this time...
...we'd like to show how the defendant, Hamada, is an utterly unthinkable man
and has caused harm to all those arou....
Hey, wait! Why aren't you saying honorifics?
Hah!?
I said, "Why aren't you saying honorifics?"
HAMADA!
Mister Attorney are you all right?
I'm all right!
If you've got nothing prepared then you don't have to respond!
You see, today I'm outraged.
Because you see, everyone has been harmed by him.
Yes.
This man is an immense sadist...
...and many people have suffered harm by him.
Firstly, as you won't know how sadistic he is...
..so we have video footage of it for you to watch.
Please watch it.
jburogu-godzillaradio.blogspot.com
gaki-no-tsukai.com
Hamada Masatoshi "Unthinkable!" Trial!
"The Legend of the Super Sadist" - Compilation
The defendant - Hamada Masatoshi.
Victims of his sadistic ways continue to appear all the time.
Victim 1
Yamasaki Housei
?
Shut the hell up!
The event took place at the Yamasaki versus Moriman battle.
Please pay attention to Hamada, who goes in between the quarreling pair.
That hurts!
It hurts!
The neutralist, Hamada, grabs Yamasaki's hair and drags him around.
This was a decisive moment of the super sadist.
Please pay attention to Hamada, as he gets in between the two again.
This is a different year again.
After dragging Yamasaki out, he slams him down onto the ring.
This man is just unthinkable!
Super sadistic behaviour then explodes mercilessly on to he knocked down Yamasaki.
This is a different year again.
That's right.
....7, 8, 9.
Fight!
He doesn't easily accept a knock out!
This was a moment of tragedy tasted by Yamasaki, caused by the Super S, Hamada.
There are still many more.
Penalty's Wakki
Victim 2
What did I do?
Hello! Please come over here.
It happened when Penalty first appeared on Gaki no Tsukai.
Wakki, who prides himself in having hard abs was attacked by Hamada's Super Sadism.
What? So you got hard abs?
Yes, that's no problem.
Oh really?
I can take even harder.
That's not even his abs!
That's his liver!
Immediately after meeting Wakki, Hamada lands a serious punches on his body.
This man is unthinkable!
Since then, Penalty haven't returned to Gaki No Tsukai.
Director Onuma
Victim 3
"Super S" Hamada also shows no mercy towards those who can't fight back.
The attacked was the Frozen Mammoth, Onuma.
It's frozen so it's dead.
No, stop! stop!
Ouch!
He wasn't expecting it.
It must be pulsating badly now.
He pulled it out a bit.
The body can't take in such things.
Furthermore, to the red panda, Fuuta-kun....
Super sadist Hamada's harsh hit smacks Onuma in the face.
Extreme pain that even shocked Onuma himself, runs through his body.
Honkon
Victim 4
There'd be heaps for Honkon-san.
Start!
Tragedy struck at the imaginary audition.
Hamada, in the role as film director, assaults Honkon after this.
Acting Proficiency Test
Getting Slapped
The customers are freaked out!
Somebody stop him! This is not good!
What is his problem?
Honkon gets attacked by a storm of slaps.
What does the victim himself think about the "Super S" Hamada?
Bluntly said - I'm afraid of him.
A normal comedian would do one or two slaps but...
I don't know why, but he came back to me
and when our eyes met....
...his eyes didn't show any signs of kindness.
And at those times, if you go against him, he attacks even more.
Maybe it was eye contact telling me...
"You've got no choice but to bring your face to me, yourself"
Does even gender not matter to this man at all?
After the break, we reveal all the proof of Hamada's super sadistic actions!
Morisanchu
Victim 5
Gender doesn't matter to Hamada's sadistic ways.
Morisanchu's Oshima, who came to give him
a Valentine chocolate, was also a victim.
Ready, set...
Hit, wear, jankenpon!
One more time!
You hit her with the handle!
That must hurt!
This face is just wrong.
No holding back, whatsoever.
The shot was so powerful that it even broke the pico-pico hammer.
After that, Hamada's sadism escalates further.
But his target wasn't just Oshima.
The person targeted by Hamada, was Murakami.
Apologize!
Murakami has her breast groped.
Hamada's sexual harassment left Murakami's innocent heart in tatters.
This is what these girls have to say about Hamada.
What's his problem?
That was cruel, Hamada-san!
That was cruel! What's your problem!?
Oshima-san is still a woman you know!
I'm a woman! Was there a need to hit me so hard!?
As for me, he rubbed my breasts and...
he probably was thinking "Oh I did her good".
Don't make a mistake.
People say stuff now, like, "Murakami is Hamada's girl now".
That's such a bother.
Guys will find it hard to approach you then.
I seriously can't get a boyfriend because of that.
Hamada's Super Sadist deeds shall not be excused!
Hamada-kun....just how sadistic are you?
Well...I don't think I am a sadist.
Of course you're a sadist.
Yes, and even whilst watching the video footage -
- he was hysterically laughing "hya hya hya hya".
I heard that.
Like 8 monkeys worth of laughs.
That's quite a lot of cackling!
Hosei-san, there was a video involving you so -
- could you please step up as witness?
The death penalty is already decided at this point.
I'd firstly like to talk about the Moriman incident.
Firstly, Moriman and I did a sacred muay thai dance and -
it was decided that Morio would come to me and we'd fight.
Yes, bluntly said, that's a promised event.
I think from about three times ago, Hamada-san would get in between that and -
- as he pushed Morio and I apart
he'd definitely grab my hair and punch me
and would assault me as he separated us.
Honestly, if that got laughs, I'd have no problems!
But not a single person is laughing in regards to that!
I really wish he'd stop.
Morio doesn't know how to respond either because he's
getting beat up by Hamada before their own fight even starts!
And the guests don't laugh.
However, his engine revs harder when guests don't laugh.
The reason for that is that, by then, he's no longer a comedian anymore.
He's just simply a sadist.
Well, there were other victims aside from Yamasaki-san but...
...in the case of Morisanchu Murakami's breasts....
...do you have any counterarguments?
What was your intention?
That was my way of tsukkomi.
Tsukkomi !?
Without using words or simply hitting.
Squeezing her tits for her was the tsukkomi.
"Squeezing her tits for her" was??
Hey listen!
Hey listen.
Hey listen !
What's up with ya!?
You've got tsukkomi all wrong!
Didn't you see in the video? She wasn't playing dumb!
She was running away!
You chased after and grabbed her!
We don't know how to react either!
Same thing goes for Onuma-san!
But wasn't he acting dumb like that?
Because you'd be like "What? A frozen mammoth?", right?
Well, I suppose it was but...
Yeah see, it is right?
But Onuma isn't a cointainer to put burdock roots in so...
I'd like to ask him something.
This thing could've split his nose, right?
Because...they're clearly different sizes.
Weren't you afraid of that possibility?
Afraid of what?
Of the nose splitting.
What's the problem with that?
Well splitting his nose with a burdock root...
...isn't exactly a good deed.
Oh...well it may not be a good deed but...
I did that with the intent of it being a tsukkomi.
So if it split -
The splitting would be the tsukkomi.
Splitting it, really ?
It's his debut piece.
"Splitting is the tsukkomi"
Hamada Masatoshi "Unthinkable!" Trial!
"Overacting in Pranks" Section
On a Gaki no Tsukai prank project -
- Hamada's over excessive acting causes colleteral harm.
Tanaka Naoki
Victim 1
It's you Tanaka. We remember this well, don't we?
In this prank, Hamada snaps at Tanaka,
who is acting as foul mouthed character.
Small fry wins!
I'm the champion?
What about us?
Why did that happen?
Are we able to broadcast this on TV?
Are you unsure?
Hm.
What do you think Yama-chan?
Eh?
Yes.
"Yes"? We've done the same thing twice already!
That's really scary!
I'm sorry.
Whadd'ya mean you're sorry?
That's scary.
It was scary.
Are you taking it serious? Is this the best you can do?
A foul mouthed...
Mm?
Foul mouthed? You call that foul mouthed!?
That hit him!
Well!?
We're sorry!
What's wrong with you?
This ain't good!
An unthinkable level of overacting!
He knees Tanaka in the face, and as a result...
JUST KIDDIN'!
Hamada's over excessive acting leads Tanaka really cry.
Victim 2
Manager Fujiwara
In this prank, Matsumoto fakes an injury,
and responsibility falls to his manager, Fujiwara.
Wrong way!
Are you okay?
It hurts! Don't touch me!
As if that would happen from that.
I'll slowly roll your back over.
Can this happen even at that speed?
Hamada Appears!
The snow is soft so...
Here he comes.
Call the rescue squad!
I told you so, Fujiwara. Didn't I?
Sorry.
I said it didn't I?
Yes.
Didn't I say "What if something happens?"
Slap!
This is strictly a prank project.
Get your act together, damn it!
Yes.
It's because you guys said it would be fine, when it wasn't!
Well!?
Yes.
Thud!
His unthinkable over excessive acting even included a head butt!
As a result...
[Gaki no Tsukai Prank]
It's starting to hurt now...
Hamada's over excessive acting forced Fujiwara muster a bitter laugh.
Cocorico
Victim 3
This prank involved scaring the daylights out of young comedians as they wrestled.
However, Hamada's targets were fellow prank insiders, Cocorico.
WHO THE HELL WAS THAT!!??
Hold on a second!
Who just kicked me!?
WAS IT YOU!?
In pursuit for realism, Hamada's fist cleanly hits Endo's head!
Why are you all just standing there?
What the heck is wrong with you guys?
Why did you do that!?
Who kicked me!?
Who did it !?
Who did it?
Tanaka made a mistake in choosing to approach.
Even here, Hamada's slaps explode.
Get friggin' real!
DO IT PROPERLY, DAMN IT!
The youngsters were at a complete loss of words due to Hamada's overacting.
As a result....
I'm so relieved....
Hamda's over excessive acting caused this ugly man to cry.
Hamada's over acting, shall not be forgiven.
So, there you have it.
Tanaka, as you were a victim, could you please step up as witness?
Yes.
Yes sir.
I'm sure you have much to say.
We~ll, we were shown some horrible footage.
This is something I thought while watching it but...
...what do you mean, "It was Tanaka's mistake to approach"?
Frankly that's quite strange.
We were also insiders setting up the prank
and know what the plan is!
Was there a need to hit us? That hard!?
The effect of hitting Endo was already enough.
Right! Everyone there was already scared!
So hitting me was totally unnecessary!
And even the one before it. It was quite an old video.
The prank while playing badminton.
There was no need to hit....that hard!
If he just acted fierce then I'd be scared enough with that!
After I understood that it was a prank, it's an embarrassing story but
I broke down and cried.
Those weren't tears of relief from finding out it was a prank!
It's because I was scared!
I was being held by Suga-san.
It was the first time I cried on someones chest!
Do you have any objections to that?
You're clearly going too far, aren't you!?
Pranks are boring if you do it half-assed though, don't you agree?
Whadd'ya mean?
What do you mean?
The aim is to scare you, so if that's the goal
I've got to at least to do that much.
But, for example, with the skiing prank
we were trying to trick our manager, Fujiwara, but...
the thing I found amazing was...
...that people don't usually get angry and head butt like that.
And usually, you'd realise it's a prank as soon as you get head butted.
But since it wasn't realised even after the head butt...
...you must often be head butting in real life.
Are you a head butting man?
Well I'm annoyed.
Annoyed...?
Do you think he's mixing up words?
What do you mean by annoyed?
It's annoying that I'm being made to sit here.
To be judged on these video footages.
What are you saying?
I just try to do my best at work.
Why is he wearing a T-shirt over long sleeves?
Let's analyse this from a different angle.
Errr...you.
Can you come in here, just like the way you come to a shoot?
How do you normally come?
Reenact how you'd come in for shoots.
It's just the same way as before!
HURRY UP!
Die!
Please come in.
' morning.
'morning.
Eh?
No, it's not like that.
Was it like that?
No, and I've never heard him clearly say "Good morning".
Well hear this, defendant.
We have secretly filmed you as you enter shoots.
Oh! I'd really like you to see this!
Please watch!
The video reveals Hamada entering for shoots.
The shocking moment that the camera recorded!
Just what was filmed on there?
....we have secretly filmed you as you enter shoots.
Oh, I'd really like you to watch this!
Let us see this then. Here it is.
Good morning.
See! See!
But I did say "Good morning" then.
Did you see that?
You didn't say that at all!
You were laughing and not listening.
What!? Play it again!
Where?
You just laughed and didn't listen.
Good morning!
Good evening.
Good evening!?
What was that about?
If it's night then it'd be "Good evening" right?
No, no, no.
What's with the walk and not taking off the sunglasses and saying....
"Good evening".
That's scary.
He's totally looking down upon people.
Oh, you're right.
Is that really me?
Seriously what's with the sunglasses?
Are you a mole rat?
Are you a mole?
Take them off!
Idiot!
Die!
Just simply die!
Like this, the defendant Hamada comes to shoots with
a fierce face on purpose in order to intimidate us.
And it's not only at shoots for....Gaki no Tsukai.
He does this at various other places.
Could the witness please enter?
Shoufukutei Shouhei
Witness
Hello.
Next week! More unbelievably evil acts by Hamada are revealed!
Also, a famous actress stands at the witness box and confesses for the first time.
And what are the secrets of Hamada after a psychological analysis?
We focus on the victims within show business in the next Hamada "Unthinkable" trial!
And what will the judgment given to Hamada be!?