Matsumoto Hitoshi's 55th birthday
September the 8th
Come on, drink up
Oh, thank you!
Matsumoto ever said to us
let's talk about all the kind things
Man, it's unbelievably hot today
I'd like to make some compliments
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
About what?
About Yoshimoto-zaka
That's the birth of a new idol!
It's a group composed of selected Yoshimoto comedians,
Yoshimoto-zaka 46
produced by Yasushi Akimoto (Nogizaka46 & Keyakizaka46)
I wonder how will it go for they from now on
They're idols
Yeah, newborn idols
Chihara Junior
Kimura Yuichi
[everyone] Good evening
So that's how it looks like, huh
Good evening
How come you knew about this place?
You know, 'cause it's famous
Oh, is that so? Thank you. A place for two?
Yes
Master, did someone ever sat in here?
This thing is really...
It does... get in your way
Can I move it away?
Of course you can, do as you please
Someone must have placed this here (before)
He's already acting rude
It's stuck on his mind
Only 10 years ago he would have gone berserk about it
Just because of that?!
Now he has calmed down
I just asked if I could move it
One time he got mad just by looking at a rental k-car
For real?
"Why would I go to a car-rental if they have k-cars?!"
And his face was bright red
That's for couples
One time he got really made at some guy who was
Buying a Pocari Sweat at 22:00
Why is that?
He was like "the fuck are you buyin' that at this hour?!"
What the hell, why?!
It was saturday
It felt like that "saturday's just starting" thing
Well, you had your reasons
Yeah, it's a matter of timing
It must be a long time since you two know each other
Right?     - Yeah, it's been a long time
Me too, it's been almost 30 years
Since I got to know and work with Downtown
And I surely received lots of kind words from them
Is that so?
Yeah, really...
From who?
Well, since today's your birthday...
Oh, thank you so much, really
September 8th - Matsumoto Hitoshi is 55 y.o.
It's kinda embarrassing but I'm now 55
55 years, man...
So in this timespan...
Today Matsumoto's young colleagues, whom he knows for a long time,
will talk about all the kind words he ever said to them to this day
He said lots of kind stuff to you, right?
Yeah, he told me so many nice things
You remember the first Gaki DVD?
How many years has passed since? Like 10 years...?
You mean our first one?
Yeah the very first one
Which featured the batsu game
From that batsu game, lots of DVDs were made
15 of them, I think
And around the eight volume...
The "Yamazaki vs Moriman"
DVD too    - Yeah, yeah
Was released
Once per year, around June
I got paid for its sales income
And that sum was the same for more than once
Even around when we were
doing the "Moriman Showdown"
I got paid the same amount
And I thought "ohh, that's nice",
then I got a call from Matsumoto
And he told me by phone
"Yamazaki, how's the income
for the Moriman Showdown?"
I was like "Huh? The DVD? Same as always"
And he "What? The same as always?"
"You mean for the Moriman Showdown?" - "Yes, that"
"And it's the same? - "Yes it is"
He said "Oh, I see",
And our call ended
Then, one day
I was doing some stuff
and looked at my bankbook
And I noticed that the same sum I was
been payed through all those years
Has been payed once more the next day
I mean, for the DVD, by Yoshimoto
I thought "What?" and on our next
Gaki session I asked Matsumoto
"You know, I got the same amount payed again"
And when I was about to say
"Could it be a mistake?"
He said "That... you know"
"This is not money meant for us"
"So you have to take it instead"
- that's what he said
And so...
What's that story about?     - Huh?
What do you mean?
I have no idea...
What do I mean?!
I mean, what I'm saying is that
About the Moriman Showdown DVD, Matsumoto...
You got payed more than usual?
Was it doubled?
It was
You didn't say that
That's the unclear part
I said it
I said the same sum got payed twice
Oh? twice... just say it before!
It was doubled
Now we got it 'cause you said it
Yes, right
It's always like that
He always makes mistakes
when saying good stuff about me
It was an important part too
That was the core
It's always like this, today too
Now I get it
What are you doin' on Ochiken?
note: short nickname for "rakugo kenkyuu kai" - rakugo research club. (ochi = raku)
Don't call it "Ochiken"!!
He did it again
I hate that nickname!
He always fucks up each good talk about me he's doing
Did I make mistakes? I was careless
Now it makes sense
Sorry
So, it was doubled?     - Yeah, same sum twice
I got the same sum payed twice
And that's because Matsumoto-san
made it possible, right?
But say it, man...      - I got what you mean
You got it, right?     - Sorta
I mean, he was not the type of person to get it himself
He didn't try to understand it      - That's right
Did it really happen?
It's real     - I see
And that's because Matsumoto told you so
Yeah, he told me that
Yes, I did say that
See?
I said that wasn't money me and Hamada deserved
It was the fruit of Yamazaki's hard work alone
And so we didn't need that payment anymore
No matter how many DVDs we sold
I told that to manager Okamoto
And he said "got it", and so did our agency
But I thought "will he notice it?"
And so I got them to deposit the sum on his account
To confirm that I asked him that     - I see
On the phone, about the income
And he was like "nothing changed"
And thought "that's not good"      - I see
If that would have happened
I'd be like "Well, I'll get Hamada fired from this company"
Hamada?
Why me?
You'd place all the blame on him
Why it has to be me?
That's cause his sense of justice is half-assed
When that happened
I thought "man, he's such"
"An honest person"
And I'm not saying it as an excuse
An honest person?
I thought you'd say more
What's that?
An honest person?
His praising skills always suck when it comes to me
I mean----
Wouldn't you think he was honest on that?
Yeah but, "honest"?
I'd say "he's so kind" or something
Yeah, that would have been good
You had to
I mean like, "sincere"
Say "sincere" then!
He was "sincere"     - Yeah, not "honest"
Oh come on! It's the same thing!
Is that the mood this episode's going to have?
It's not our fault he was the first
I mean, the staff already handed me this handkerchief
It's good you're all set up
There's no right timing to use it right now
I just want to wipe off this weird sweat
Well, at least you're sweating
Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Translation & Subtitles by Shion
Want to support my translations?
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
If that's the way this is gonna continue...
Don't go away, please!
I don't like this    - Don't go
If we're talking about knowing each other...     - Yes?
Me too since I've joined Gaki no Tsukai...
It's been 22 years to this day
You all took care of me
And there were countless times
In which I've received kind words from him
I don't really remember---
I mean, I don't recall
Saying all these kind words
I think you     - You just don't remember saying them
Exactly      - But those who heard them do
For me there was something you said I can't forget
We always have this Gaki No Tsukai
new year's party episode every year
And one time, after it
There were Matsumoto, Housei
and Fujiwara from License
Together with me and the writer Takasu
note: he's talking about Takasu Mitsuyoshi
And we all decided to go have a drink
For how many years have we...?
I think it's like 6 years we're doing this
And so, we were all talking while drinking alcohol
It was about 2 years ago
And as we were normally drinking
Everyone started to talk a bit
about their job-related worries
And we all wanted to talk
to Matsumoto about them
And so we discussed freely
about them, that was the mood
And at that time
I was trying to came in contact with ZIP
note: a japanese morning news/entertainment show
And looking for movies to play in
I was kinda trying to find something else besides
comedy, like my animals picture book promotion
I just happen to be in a situation in which
I wanted to have more comedy-unrelated jobs
But I was thinking "am I cut for this?"
I mean, I thought that too about Gaki
I'm always wondering
if I'm actually cut for this
And so, in this period in which
I was shrouded in such worries
Thinking about stuff like
"can I do this job properly?" and such
I asked Matsumoto for some advice
And he told me
"Don't think too much about it, Tanaka"
"Because, Tanaka, I think that..."
"The best thing about you is that you always
do the jobs you have to do with utmost effort"
"And you're always doing jobs fit for yourself"
"You're always aware of things,
just like the size of your body"
"You can choose by yourself the clothes
you wear, and you do the same with jobs"
"So don't sweat it about genres or such"
"Wouldn't it be good just to do the jobs you think are best for you?"
That's what he said to me
And it lead me to choose the job I'm doing now
note: Tanaka is currently the host of ZIP
Yes...
I don't remember that...
That's why it's good he could say that now
Yeah, I said the same before
Right, you said it too
Didn't this story start from Endo's bad mouthing?
Did it begin with my bad mouth?
This really good story?
Was it when I said the clothes
you were wearing didn't fit you?
Well, Endo's case is different
But Tanaka was going through a lot
So I told him to do what he likes to
D-did you remem---
It's not that I clearly remember it
or I forgot about it...
It's just weak
Well, that's how it is inside you
It's surely way stronger inside Tanaka
Man, he just told you about his feelings!
Yeah, I was like "aww, man!"
I mean, there's been a lot of stuff
I think that's a good thing
He lead you, right?
- Yes, it was thanks to him
It's not like I despise it---
It's like some teaching from Buddha, right?
Right
It's a way to show how thankful you are
That's what I thought, it gave me strenght
I think it was like... 20 years ago
I've been doing lots of stuff in Osaka
And when they ended, I came to Tokyo
But there was hardly any work in Tokyo for me
The kind words Matsumoto said to Junior on their first show together
I think it was like... 20 years ago
I've been doing lots of stuff in Osaka
Junior when he was younger
And when they ended, I came to Tokyo
But there was hardly any work in Tokyo for me
And I was like "what do I do now?"
At that time
There was this show, "warai no jikan" (time for laugh)
Which Matsumoto was doing on Asahi TV
With Imada, right?     - Yes
So, at the time
On their first episode
They had gathered like 20 Yoshimoto comedians
And the plan was just to have them talk freely
That was the first time I ever worked with Matsumoto
So, when I was in Oosaka I always
relied on Itao who took care of me
So when it was my turn to talk,
I talked about an episode I had with him
While I still was very nervous
There was this one time we went to the Koushien
note: a baseball tournament
And they fired some jet balloons
from the 7th inning's bottom
So, they fired it from there
And the same goes from the other innings
Then I have no idea how, but when
they fired it from the ninth inning
Even though there were like 55 thousand people
That ballon, with a one in a 55 thousands chance
Landed straight on his head
And while I was like "Woah!" he didn't move an inch
He still had the balloon on his head
At one time the plastic tip fell and hit his forehead
And without even moving
He just swiped it off
When I said this story to them
The audience laughed at it
So, we all had a closing party after it and
we all went there to have a drink or such
And around when it was about to end,
Matsumoto went to me and told me
"I think that your story about Itao was the funniest today"
And then he got back home
Those words really had a huge impact on me
And thinking about them I thought that maybe
I could have a chance in Tokyo
I see
Looking back at it I think that those words
Are still echoing inside my head
Do you remember that?
I don't...
Either way, they're here
That's right
They're still here
They had an impact     - Yeah
See? It's good they're talking about it
You may not remember,
but they still have them here
It's just... they're faint
It was a good story, yes?
Yeah, it was
Shouzo, do you...?
Yes, I...
You know, I've remarried 3 years ago     - Yes
And I had to make lots of arrangements for it
And between them, the most important to me
Was about the daughter I had from Chiaki, my ex-wife
Which was a mid-schooler by
the time I was getting remarried
So it was a pretty emotional time for me
I've been thinking about how to told my daughter
I mean, should I told her beforehand or after it?
I didn't want her to be involved and felt
like talking to her about it wasn't good
And while I was thinking that much about
the right timing to tell my daughter about it
Some journalist out there
Was pretty quick to slam my remarrying news on paper
My current wife is now pregnant
And I know that from my daughter point of view
It's something like "daddy married another woman
plus there's a chance I'll have a brother or a sister"
And I know that if I was her age, I'd panic over this
And so when I saw that news on the Sanspo newspaper
I thought "Woah, this is the worst..."
So I talked about it with Matsumoto,
And I was like "what should I do about it?"
and felt flustered about it
And at that time Matsumoto was like
"There, there...", he tried to cheer me up
And I just keep saying "man, I'm so
pissed off about it, what should I do?"
The next day on the show Matsumoto
was taking part in, "Wide na Show"
I was really feeling down and trying
my best to let my rage fade away
I also have the DVD from back then
Can I put this on?
He got that too?     - Yes
You know, Endo from Cocorico
is going to get married again
And he has already a kid and he's been
thinking about the right timing to say it
I'm talking about the daughter
he had with Chiaki
And she knows there could be a chance
she could get a brother or sister in law
Endo is thinking a lot about this, that's
why he's feeling down about it
Because even though he wanted to tell
her by his own timing
But the Sanspo newspaper wrote it first
And his daughter was shocked by it
I mean, something like that...
It's not something you want for your kid
I'd like to know from these jerks what's
the point of writing that stuff
'Cause it really pissed me off
When I watched this
I felt really relieved, it's as if
Matsumoto put on words everything
I had in mind right in front of the public
And I thought "man, he really saved me"
And when the year ended, on the New Year's party
I thought I had to say thanks to him directly
So I went and I said "Thank you so much for
saying that, you really helped me to calm down"
And then Matsumoto at that point
Inside this whole "let's not talk about it" atmosphere,
looked at my face for few seconds and said
"Sure."
That's what you kindly told me
"Kindly" told you?     - Yes
Yes well, you already...
Said everything on that show, so your
"Sure, it's okay" was enough for me
Really, that's it
Well, just so you know...
Kimura has been crying for a while by now       - What?!
That's impressive
I mean, his sensitivity
Come on, man!
It's going on for a while by now     - For real?
I mean, he's really impressive, he's crying for a while now
I think he's worth receiving Kiyohiko Ozaki prize record
note: a japanese singer
Who decided that?!
Sorry for that
I really
Do feel you guys
Kimura will tell us about his memories with Matsumoto
His eyes are swollen by now
I've been like this since our briefing session before
Well, it is emotional
It's like when I watched Project X
note: documentary about Japan's greatest achievements
It must be since he met us
It's just like Project X
I mean, its ending
That's history
At first...
Back when I was a director in Umeda-Kagetsu and
note: aka Nanba Grand Kagetsu, a Yoshimoto-brand teather
My job was to raise and lower the curtains,
Downtown were doing their signature abduction skit
I remembered there was hardly any
applause at first, and when I was leaving
There was this thunder of applause inside
the teather because how funny it was
Like this, every day was filled with emotion for me
One time they decided to have this quiz-skit
It lasted for about ten days
What I felt about it
On the opening day
There was a problem with the intro, it should have
been about one asking what's the height of Mt. Fuji
And the other had to come up
with an answer and scold him
And then they did other stuff, but
But they kept on doing it for then days, always answering
a new question with answers from previous days
And as I kept on watching it
And I was having goosebumps
I happen to notice the mekuri
with "Downtown" written on it
note: a paper signboard displaying comedians name / manzai duo names on stage
So I took it off and went to the guy who wrote it
And told him "go make a new one, you can't
have them be on stage with such filthy mekuri"
So I had him make a new one
That was the first time I ever thought
I had to do my best myself too
The atmosphere...
And clothes too... everything was really cool there
So...
I brought some notes, may I...?
Sure
You wrote a friggin' lot
Gimme a sec
It's one of the things which echoed the most in me
As you know in the 90s Gottsu Ee Kanji ended
But we also had a special episode
around the beginning of 2000
So, after we finished airing it,
we all decided to go to the pub
You know, to wrap things up
I was there too, a bit late
There were also Matsumoto
Imada, Takasu and YOU
Even Higashino... he came later
Also Junior was there
So I saw them and said "good morning"
"It's 9"
"What? Are you 29 y.o.?"
"Nope, it's just 21:00"
And I was like "whaaaat!"
"What the heck"
So, as we kept chatting and drinking
Matsumoto went and to each one of us...
I think he was a bit drunk
While pointing his finger at us,
he started saying really nice stuff
"YOU, you're this this and this,
and so this", like that
"And Higashino, you're this"
"Imada, you..." etc.
And it was my turn
He said "Kimu..."
"You know, this guy lives on a
170'000 yen monthly rent house"
note: roughly 150$ / 130€
"But if we have to base it on his merit..."
"There's no way he'll have to live in such a cheap place"
"Kimura, I'm sure that one day..."
"You'll live in a 1'000'000 yen monthly rented mansion"
note: roughly 8900$ / 7700€
...That's what he said to me
I'm so thankful
Also, back then your mobile
phone was a two-touch dial...
Kimura will talk about another memory with Matsumoto
So, Matsumoto,you had a two-touch dial phone
Two-touch dial?
Those old ones in which
by pressing the number buttons
You'd call an assigned number
It was some time ago
I was assigned as your number 2
I thought "woah, only number 2... that's quick"
What---       - I was happy about it
"Number 2"      - What are you--
Well, it was a 1 digit code, so I could easily call him
And quickly      - I got it
Calling you was quick cause you were registered early
You said "You're Kimu, so you're going NImu"
note: "NI" means "TWO"
Why did you say that?
I don't think I ever said that
Translation & Subtitles by Shion
I have no idea what's this "Nimu" thing
"Kimu" is fine
We were in Korea...
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
And I was eating crabs
I accidentally got some shell
stuck between my teeth, and then
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
You looked right at me with a face which seemed
Really concerned about me
Want to support my translations? Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
The hell is he talkin' about
Let's just call it a day
This is a no-profit translation made by a fan for other fans, all copyrights
are reserved to their respected owners
for updates & support like my page: www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
main website (archive): www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
want to support my works?
Buy me an Oyan Fifi: www.ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai