Freeze King Grand Prix!
It's a competition to see how well you can freeze without blinking and without being noticed by your target while eating.
Three teams entered this last week.
Matsumoto will judge them on each of the five sections to see how well they did.
This Double Freeze is a Extremely Freeze, so to speak.
Tonight, the remaining three teams will take on the challenge, and the Freeze King will finally be decided.
The next challenger, come on!
Why did you take this job?
Didn't your manager freeze?
I love pranks, and I said so many times that I wanted to be in this.
I think you are insane to think this is a prank.
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]
The Freeze Girl who defies conventions.
Rola.
Here we go!
Hi!
Good evening, I'm Rola!
What's up?  I'm doing well!
Who are you talking to?
Everyone, watch me! I'm definitely going to win
I think this is the piece of cake!
Okay, bye-bye!
- She's always on the move, isn't she?
- Yeah!
Her targets are her good friends, Yoshiizaki-san, a hair stylist, and Imamura-san, a fashion stylist.
She was waiting for her target at a restaurant.
Hey, why are they using this footage?
She is so excitable even when she is alone.
How will this affect her freeze?
Hair stylist Yoshizaki-san arrived.
Next, Imamura-san, the fashion stylist, arrived.
Rola's plan is to set up immediately after the toast.
Cheers!
- What's her private life like?
- I've never seen it before.
Tasty!
- Are you sure you don't have a boyfriend, Imamura-chan?
- It's not that I don't, it's just that I can't.
How about *****-san?
He's gay.
I just found out recently that *****-san is not gay.
- He is gay.
- He's bisexual, isn't he?
- What's that?
- He can go for both.
Is that so? That's creepy.
You're just talking aimlessly.
Fifteen minutes passed without her freezing up.
More girl talk ensued.
This is delish!
I should have brought my dog today.
- I should have done the same. You can bring your dog here.
- Is that right?
Maybe.
She's always on the move.
She's so into girl talk that she never freezes up.
So the staff sent her a text to warn her.
Are you serious?
Then Rola finally started moving.
What would you like to order?
Takoyaki!
That's the first one.
You're not drinking any plum wine.
Don't do that. Have some plum wine.
You're frozen.
She didn't get caught?
Rola's nostrils are open.
Don't be ridiculous!
She should go on the offensive from here in one go.
But...
- I wonder who would be a good match for you.
- I don't know anyone among the people I know.
- How about *****-san?
- He has a girlfriend.
Is it going to end after just one time?
- Surely that's not the case.
-  I'm certain she will do many more from now on.
- He might have a lot of flaws.
- Yeah, he might be very careless.
When I met him the other day, there was a hole in his sock.
I don't care about the content of your chatter!
Rola is completely absorbed in her chatter
Hi.
Since she shows no signs of freezing, the staff hastily calls her on the phone.
She is just eating her dinner for free.
He politely explained the purpose to her again.
How will reflective Rola freeze?
Have you reflected on it?
- Then I'll introduce you to a good man.
- Really?
How about Gushiken-san?
I prefer someone a bit younger.
It finally started.
Why did you freeze at that moment?
You're completely caught!
"Why did you freeze at that moment?"
She froze as if to say, 'Please look at me.’
Is she still doing it?
She's already been ignored.
They think she is an idiot.
She tried her best in her own way, but she was already drunk and showed no signs of freezing.
Are you serious?
The staff called her, but she was completely oblivious to the phone, so they were at a loss.
Now's your chance!
She blinked.
That’s terrible!
Rola, you're terrible at this!
Was this song played on the second day of the event?
No.
You are being ignored by them.
And 'BEAST', which wasn't on the first day either.
Oh, really? I wanted to see it!
That's a lie.
Don't say weird things.
If you say that, I'll eat takoyaki.
You're bad at this!
It was Rola!!
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye.
It was difficult.
Rola, they called you and explained everything, didn't they?
But I forgot.
So I'll do better next time.
“Next time”!?
This doesn't happen frequently.
There won't be a next time.
Matsumoto-san, please evaluate her.
This is terrible.
That was terrible.
This is still on the better side.
The category in which I want to give you the highest score is 'Discomfort.'
However, there is no such evaluation category.
It was funny that you introduced Gushiken-san to her.
That has nothing to do with the freeze.
The next challenger, come on!
Why are you next, Diamond Yukai?
I know the audience didn't see it, but you tripped on the stairs, didn't you?
Yukai-san, what did you think of the VCR so far?
A rock 'n' roller like me is a terrible liar.
If possible, could you speak a little more up front?
You're always so close.
Freeze Fighter with Ultra Hardness.
Here we go!
His targets are Mori-san, the stage manager for his gigs, and Yamamoto-san, the new manager who has recently been put in charge of Yukai.
Yukai's plan is to set him up when he breaks the disposable chopsticks.
- Mori-san, please take a seat in the back of the room.
- It's been a while.
- Hi, I'm already drinking.
This time, Yukai invited the two targets, with the cooperation of manager Ogura, for a dinner meeting that doubled as a planning session for his 50 yeas old  anniversary live concert.
When he breaks the disposable chopsticks...
Huh? It's already started?
You look very tired. Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Before freezing, Yukai made sure to express to them that he was tired.
I see.
Giracci!!
(*This is a call invented by Yukai.)
"Giracci"?
[Yukai is drinking non-alcoholic beer to drive back to Sano, Tochigi Prefecture, where his home is located.]
I finally had a drink with you.
Once he breaks the chopsticks, his freeze begins.
Oh, is he going to freeze already?
He started right away.
He's a rock 'n' roller.
Yeah, that's good.
A good start.
This is unexpected.
He's hungry, but he did it at this point.
- Surprisingly long.
- Yeah, it's a good.
Are you tired? Are you okay?
- I haven't slept much lately.
- You should eat a lot of food.
The target interpreted the freeze as fatigue, because he was appealing that he was tired.
From this point on, Yucai began to freeze boldly.
My kids are cute.
Look.
Oh, twins.
- They are resemble to Yukai-san.｡
- Yeah.
No one is laughing.
They think you're a sketchy person.
You haven't been sleeping, poor thing.
It's important for the office to create artists who are too busy to sleep, right?
“You haven't been sleeping, poor thing.”
It's hard for me too because he's the father of twins.
I'll talk to my colleague about it.
I'll talk to him about your debilitating condition.
Mori-san was worried about Yukai's health and contacted an acquaintance.
But...
[Order button]
He sees Yukai-san's “symptoms”.
He has the look of someone who's into drugs.
What the hell are you saying to our talent?
- So he has managed to deceive them completely.
- That’s right.
You're not doing drugs, right?
That's not true! Come on!
In other words, his acting is convincing.
Yukai was under suspicion.
You've been told a terrible thing.
An hour had passed since the start. He went to the restroom.
He'll be worried if he leaves now.
You're really pushing yourself!
Hey, that's not good!
He'll die if he drives home.
He looks dead!
And It’s a long time!
Allow me to say, that phenomenon of his is very dangerous.
- As his friend, I have to say that his condition looks dangerous.
He is serious about it.
The suspicion towards him continues to grow.
The mood is not good.
But Yukai didn't care about their worries.
Are you all right?
He is very worried!
But it's funny.
Mori-kun, you wanna see my guitar?
(*His guitar is a Martin D-45.)
This guitar sounds great.
I'm going to pee.
Why did he go peeing at this point?
He's a rookie.
He's a newcomer, so he probably doesn't know what he should do.
“Why do I have to manage this guy?”
How on earth is he going to manage this man?
You should stay in Tokyo instead of going back to Sano.
I'll be fine.
It's dangerous.
You really shouldn't go back to Sano today.
That's funny.
He should not be allowed to leave.
Let's take a picture.
You don't get many chances to take pictures, do you?
I'll pass.
Why don't you take the picture without me?
Say cheese.
It's too long!
They're waiting for you!
They're waiting for you!!
It's so long!
Hey, are you okay?
We're going to have a meeting about Yutaka Tadokoro (Yuka's real name).
I'm telling you this as your friend, you didn't really do anything wrong, did you?
It was Diamond Yukai!
It's over.
It was pretty good.
It had a lot of power.
That was funny, Yukai-san.
But I was treated like a junkie.
You were very worried about them.
You almost got a perfect score.
The soulless feeling you had when you left the room was amazing.
I didn't expect the word "drugs" to be used so much on TV.
Now for the last challenger.
Yama-chan.
The flow is really good now.
I can show you the Extremely Freeze that Matsumoto-san mentioned earlier.
They are freezing!!
It's a double freeze!
Don't laugh!
You guys freeze too much.
Housei Yamasaki, the man who freezes laughter.
Here we go!
His targets are two guys whose careers are less than his, but who are his seniors in rakugo.
He is practicing.
He is well prepared.
He just waits for his targets to arrive.
Hi!
He has invited them for a dinner meeting to discuss the rakugo show.
Cheers!
Yamazaki's plan is to grab some hot sake and then start the freeze.
Don't you just want a drink?
This year marks the 100th anniversary of Yoshimoto.
The Great Yoshimoto Rakugo Festival?
So I want to do something with rakugo storytellers in Tokyo.
Hot sake was served to their table.
Finally, Yamazaki makes his move.
Let's be careful while drinking sake.
Cheers.
This is quite long
Suddenly, this is long.
The first freeze is long.
We don't do that in rakugo.
It's a joke to stop your body like that, isn't it?
He made the next freeze difficult because they saw the first freeze as a joke.
How many stories can you tell?
Almost 130.
I don't have as many as he does.
But you are already in the media.
I used to criticize the media.
To be honest, I used to criticize Hosei-san, too.
I didn't know anything about the TV industry at that time.
- Now?
- This is terrible.
This is the worst thing to do.
He must be testing the rakugo storyteller's reaction.
He couldn't freeze well.
As the drinks went down, the target started doing it too.
If I was going to FREEZE, I would do this.
You made him say the word “freeze.”
At this point, you've already failed.
Did he freeze you back in return?
- What is happening?
- They're just playing .
He's imitating Yamazaki.
The target, Kakitsu, also started to freeze.
The banquet turned into a messy game.
And...
How much hot sake did you drink?
About six bottles.
- This is terrible.
- This is a messy game.
This is a messy game.
- Is that okay?
- I guess you just have to make them laugh.
It was Hosei Yamasaki.
Yama-chan!
You were worse than Rola in some ways.
Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha.
Please evaluate him.
I cannot evaluate him at all.
That was just a shit.
Did I poop?
This can't be on the air.
Gaki News!
The Downtown figure is very popular and is now available for pre-order!
This is your last chance.
The deadline for ordering Hamada figures is approaching!
See the official web site for more details!
Now, Matsumoto-san, please announce the winner!
Yes!
The winner is ...
- Come on!
I wondered what would happen if I did it now.
We are waiting for you.
You don't have to stand with the comedians, Yukai-san.
The winner is ...
Come on!
Diamond Yukai!!
You will receive the Freeze Trophy!
Congratulations!
You don't have to freeze anymore!
[Thank you to those who were inconvenienced]
Hi.
This is the Freeze King Grand Prix.
I have to freeze.
I don't get it at all.
What the hell is that show?
- This is Gaki no tsukai.
- Is it serious?
I had a feeling that something was off.
This is the Freeze King Grand Prix.
Was that an act?
Of course!
I was seriously worried about you!
- What is this?
- This is Gaki no tsukai.
This is a segment that just freezes.
Do you think what I did is funny?
I don't think so at all.
I don't know what it means.
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]