Translated and subtitled by hotarubi
Gaki No Tsukai, graduation ceremony
"Goodbye Yamasaki Hosei"
Good evening dear viewers.
DOWNTOWN
Hitoshi Matsumoto
Masatoshi Hamada
Hein, Matsumoto san?
Yes.
COCORICO
Endo Shozo
Naoki Tanaka
Last year we did not care a bit,
we knew it was a joke.
But really ...
THIS DAY IS REALLY HAPPENED!
I do not remember that anger.
He participated in the show since the second episode.
But today, it's really his last appearance,
then I suggest we demand more explanation to the person concerned.
Here,
Yamasaki Hosei.
Whoever leaves the 'Gaki no Tsukai "
Yamasaki Hosei
Well, Yamasaki kun ...
... Please, sit down.
We want to hear your own lips that you stop the show.
Explain to us why.
Well, there are several.
There are several.
Yes, I see.
I participated in a special broadcast.
On my way to the backstage
Actress
I see "Private box A-1: Wakako Shimazaki.
Besides, I see "Jaru Jaru" sama.
Comedians
What are your Kohai.
The Jaru Jaru were also treated to a private suite.
Continuing to walk,
I see "Rehearsal Hall B-2".
It is a large room for 8 groups.
Comedians
I was with THE PUNCH.
So I talked with Yanaoka (staff member).
He asked: "What is funny?"
Production Manager
Yanaoka Shuichi
It pissed me off.
No, I did not say that to make him laugh.
I told him: "It's not that!"
Yanaoka san said, "Really? I see...
This is where I would reply: "Really? You see? "
What do you mean?
We want to know why you quit the program.
The official version, so to speak.
But maybe it's hard to tell ...
You may not want to talk about it.
Well ...
My wife called Aya.
I talked with her,
and it turns out we managed to save enough to enter semi-retirement.
We would like to open
a store of imported items in Meguro.
* Meguro rounding Tokyo.
A store?
My wife and myself,
we love the furniture from Guam.
That's why we want to import this kind of furniture and open a store.
The discussion is progressing in this direction.
But this is not ... a reason to stop ...
You may very well continue the program in doing this.
- "Exactly!"
You can keep your store while continuing the program.
Maybe he can not tell the reasons Matsumoto san.
His reasons can not be said on television.
His heart must be closed.
He thought maybe we would not understand them.
You talked Suga san? About your reasons?
You could answer correctly?
DOWNTOWN This \ Ngaka no Tsuki ARAHENDE YA!
Well, Matsumoto san, I think we have no choice.
We will watch a video of Yama chan
and his best moments in Gaki. Here's the best of.
yrs
YAMASAKI HOSEI
We just changed the age!
He participated in the show since the 2nd episode.
He participates in "Gaki No Tsukai" from the 2nd episode.
Hiroyuki Miyasako
Narrator
It's been 21 years with us, you have participated in numerous scenes become cults.
Cult scenes were recorded.
- Why is Miyasako?\ N "But it's true!
He has now decided he would leave the show.
He decided to leave "Gaki No Tsukai" ...
Let us review these great moments offered by this man.
BEST MOMENTS IN gaki no tsuki
YAMASAKI HOSEI
NUMBER 5
Yamasaki, pathetic! Fight face to face!
Released in October 1993
To become less pathetic, we did fight several people, he gave all his energy.
(AKA: Tsuttsun, at the time: assistant director)
Director Tsutsumimoto
He was young!
Hey, I've seen you, you!
You have become shameless, do not you think?!
You're also a cheeky, eh!
You came late, right? Hey!
Shut up!
This is nonsense!
They just shove.
Blanc
Points
Red
Verdict
What it will come up verbally to lose against a wizard?
But this was not the only confrontation with the young "Tsuttsun.
Released in May 1995
Test whether a confrontation between Yamasaki \ Net "Tsuttsun" can be funny.
What was that? It does not hurt at all.
It does not hurt?
Put more force there, you idiot!
Ouch.
It hurts, you idiot!
If it hurt, you should have-
He reacted slowly.
Hidden Camera: Nakamura is dead?
NUMBER 4
Ah yes, I remember.
Producer Nakamura
Released in November 1996
To believe that the producer Nakamura Yamasaki died in an accident. Nakamura, presumed dead, come to torment him.
A week before
After that Yamasaki has won an award, Nakamura P promises to pay next week.
It's fucking ...
Nakamura is dead ...
Really?
Yamasaki of the death of Nakamura P
Are you serious?
Immediately after, P Nakamura appears suddenly in the car
The car has been tampered with so it does not start ...
Yama chan ...
Did you see his head?
Look, your price ...
NUMBER 3
SAYONARA YAMASAKI HOSEI
That's number 3!?
Released in April 2009
For the ninth time, you managed to make viewers believe that you stopped Gaki No Tsukai.
It was one of last year.
We did not know that this day would come actually ...
Wait!
Yama chan
will not stop Gaki No Tsukai!
Tokyo Station
In your eyes transparent
"Wine Red No Kokoro"
~ Version "will not stop Yama chan ~
It is ugly!
COCORICO, DOWNTOWN, because I love you
Yama chan will not stop Gaki No Tsukai.
Highlights of High Voltage
NUMBER 2
I see...
Released in May 1998
Hosei kun, You have always shown an admirable High Voltage.
Released in June 2004
Those who saw your performance was out of breath.
Hit the boogers!
It was anything.
Marriage poignant Yamasaki Hosei
NUMBER 1
Enough.
We have already seen several times!
Released in November 2001
The man in the face of a child finally gets married.
ITÔ AYA
MARRIAGE moving
YAMASAKI HOSEI
It forced us to see that emotion.
"Katame No sakazuki" (They drink 3 sips of sake)
Looks like a video "How to" about the marriage.
It's been how many years in a row that looks right?
But it's true, what's that video?
Almost 10 years.
We saw it 10 times.
The quality is excellent as well.
Even for television, there is no such quality.
Eh! ...
He cried!
Am I dreaming?
It's fast!
I dream!?
What made you cry in there!?
You have grown up in Gaki No Tsukai, Hosei kun.
The time has come for you to put an end to this story.
However ...
The years spent with you will never wither.
I'm sure you always decorate the album in our hearts.
Yes For eternity.
He ran away!
Goodbye and thank you for the memories.
Goodbye!
Thank you for the memories
A user, there you go.
It is normal that so long,
he was in the show for almost 20 years. This has happened things.
It's time to flower distribution.
It begins with Suga san.
Please.
~ A word from the producer Suga ~
Yama chan, you really did a good job.
You too.
The world of show business is really ruthless.
It's all or nothing.
Despite all these people who have made comments to him unpleasant,
Yama chan, 20 years ... no, 21,
lived in the world of show business with no talent.
It's impressive.
For thou hast left no impression.
Among the artists with no talent, you were in third or fourth.
In "Gaki", you were the 5th.
I am really grateful to you.
Thank you, I am grateful.
thank you very much (polite)
It continues ...
The female member of staff of Gaki No Tsukai, Uchino, would have something to say.
Uchino chan.
~ A reminder of the part of Uchino ~
Thank you. - "Ah! But it ...
Hey, it's your makeup box.
It was heavy to carry!
Ouch!
So the special box of Yama chan
prepared by staff members for the program.
- "Exactly!"
- "OK... As we now say a word,
and distribute bouquets of flowers. First the COCORICO.
~ Kohai his speech, the COCORICO ~
When I started in Gaki No Tsukai,
I did not know at all how to approach DOWNTOWN.
One that was between us, and gave me advice,
Yamasaki was you, eh?
* Endo tu his senpai, Yamasaki, which is rude and disrespectful.
I am really grateful to you.
Congratulations. Good job.
"Congratulations"?
Congratulations on your graduation.
In any case, I've always hated.
thank you very much (polite)
In our turn.
~ Speech of his senpai, the Downtown ~
Personally, I really have nothing to add. Courage for the future.
That's over.
I think that Matsumoto san has something to say.
Well ...
At one time, I was often asked: "But what he did there, Yamasaki?"
I replied: "No, but Yamasaki, looks like it but ..."
"This is an artist who sees only once a week"
Starting next week, it will change Nezumi Senpai (singer, tarento).
Although I wish he remains himself. This time he will be on the viewers,
and I hope we look.
I did not know that separations with only good things existed.
- "OK... It's finally time for Yamasaki Hosei make a speech.
~ Farewell Message to the viewers, from Hosei Yamasaki ~
I ..."
"Excuse me." I ..."
COCORICO san ...
The COCORISOCO san ...
Hello, le site congres-medical.com est n cour de traduction et sera tres prochainement dispoble completement e anglais
that's how they call me.
I ... 'll leave the "Gaki no ..."
But that does not mean ... I'll leave the TV.
I will appear in several programs ... a little bit in several travel programs.
And when you see me a little bit in several travelogues,
cheer for me!
ENCOURAGE ME, EVERYBODY!
I WILL BEGIN TO KEEP A BLOG!
THEN LEAVE ME COMMENTS!
Hurry up and save me!
There's someone, right?
NO I HAVE NOT WANT!
I DO NOT WANT TO STOP!
If you do not want to stop ...
If you do not want to stop, you're not forced to leave.
I DO NOT WANT!
It is you who ...
We do not force you to go ...
I will not!
I have no choice!
Okay, it's going ...
Save me!
Black on black, we do not see well.
It is less visible than he thinks.
He decided himself that he wanted to stop, that's why we're here.
But then he says he does not want.
That may be because of downsizing ...
Anyway, nothing can be done.
Exact.
So I suggest we go away.
Let's go.
WAIT A LITTLE ~!
So I suggest we go away. Let's go.
YAMA CHAN WILL NOT STOP gaki no tsuki,
IT WILL NOT STOP!
IT WILL NOT STOP ~!
You scared?
You too have been afraid, not true, dear viewers?
The COCORICO and Gaki No Tsukai Downtown asked Yama chan
preparation of this hoax.
Yama chan Gaki No Tsukai not stop.
Why he chose Kudo Shizuka? (Singer)
Kudo Shizuka san is? - "Ah! That's true.
Causes a storm
Yama chan will not stop
Arashi no Sugao
~ Version "will not stop Yama chan ~
Yama chan is beautiful, then it can go it alone
Starting tomorrow, I am proposing new
appointment for the job
If I have the habit of running away so pathetic
It's all the fault of Gaki
I was on tiptoes
Lately, Komu is cold, it would be laughable
By pointing the finger at Komu
I want to pull the trigger
All the better if Komu collapses
Causes storm
Yama chan will not stop
I will not stop Gaki Tsuka
He just wanted to do this piece, I think.
Looks like ...
He wanted to do that too.
He had seen somewhere.
Again!
Please wait while the changes of costume and decor.
We must still wait?
It is just waiting for since earlier.
Welcome home, dear master ♥
Sorry for making you wait.
We bring the Premium Iced Coffee. ♥
A user, there you go.
Master Matsumoto, I would add gum syrup and milk in your coffee iced
do you agree?
Yes, if you please.
בסדר
I will now add the milk, when there will be enough,
Tell me, "Nyan Nyan ♥"
Tell a cute way, if you please. ♥
It must be said otherwise it will not stop.
Do you mind?
Nyan Nyan.
Nyan Nyan!
Yes thank you very much (polite)
But I said "Nyan Nyan" ...
Then, for gum syrup,
saying: "Chuki ♥"
Say it out loud, if you please.
Chuki!
I am happy, the repetition-if-you-please ♥
Oh, I'm happy! Again, if you please ♥
CHUK! I do not understand ...
I am happy, the repetition-if-you-please ♥
I said "Chuki".
A user, there you go. thank you very much (polite)
- ”Shut up!"
And now you can attend the rest ♥
Excuse us.
You should tell the others too.
No, thank you.
After:
Yamasaki in trouble in the 2nd stage!
It's 2 against 1, that is not fair.
It's not over yet ~!
A movie theater?
A 3D movie? Maybe it's "Avatar" ...
Komu (Director Komurasaki)
We're sorry for making you wait.
The film will be screened immediately.
AVATAR
I knew it.
Please bring these 3D glasses.
We can not even wear them ...
Real are much better.
Avatar
~ Version "will not stop Yama chan ~
Wow
Looks like Komu sees the film in 3D.
Ouuuaahh
There is no connection with "Yama chan will not stop."
It does not even speak.
That's true.
It does not say "Yama chan will not stop."
... Will stop ...
- "Ah! He said.
He finally said.
But he still stumbles.
... Will not stop ...
I think it is problematic if it is still long.
Oh?
He tries to tell us: "Go".
Go away !
He asks us to leave.
"Hurry up and go!"
Well, well, let's go.
It persists because it took him time to prepare.
Translated and subtitled by hotarubi \ nhttp: / / www.dailymotion.com / hotarubi
Yes, that's normal.
This is backwards.
עבודה טובה
Why you chose Kudo Shizuka?
Yeah, why?
I wanted to do this.
I knew it.