Subbed by: Mickstar813 & YamasakiGIFs
Gaki no Tsukai- Backstage
Damn, my body hurts...
What the hell are you doing!
My body really hurts...
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi         Hamada Masatoshi
Piss off you idiot.
Don't touch me
Oh don't be like that
What the hell , you always...
Cocorico
Endo Shozo        Tanaka Naoki
It's like always...
Good morning.
Pardon me.
Can... Can you listen for a minute?..
My body hurts so bad...
Yamasaki Housei
What?
Well... I kind of need to discuss something...
Um...
Lately, I've been struggling financially...
Damn, he's really...
He's so direct...
I know it's sad
But seriously, last week, when we finished recording and I jokingly looked in his wallet...
He only had thirty something yen...
For real.
Oh, was it three hundred and something?...
You're kidding!
Yeah it was
No way...
I was surprised.
No, really.
Really?
I just bought a house, you know?
Ah right, yeah.
And the loan re-payments are tough
And I have 2 kids right now
That's right
And to be honest, I want to put them in a private school...
you get me?
That costs a lot..
It does.
You have two girls right?
Yeah...
So why don't you just work really hard?
No, I mean... I am working hard...
But it never changes...
Since I was 28, it's not gone up once!
My worth!
That can't be!
Honest!
But it's not something to say here, it's something to say at the offices...
Right, yeah.
No, no, that's--
Just tell your wife
Just say it to '******* *******"
OI YOU!!
What was wrong, he should say it to his wife...
To his family, right?..
He shouted 'KORE ME-N' at me... (Note: He meant to say "Kora Omae- OI YOU"
But anyway... Seriously...
I want money...
So I heard that you can get a lot of royalties selling music...
Yeah I've heard that.
I mean yeah, I guess it is true...
Yeah, I heard that you can so...
Wait, are you a rakugouka?.. Why are you taking your jacket off whilst talking...
I was a bit hot
As if he's getting to the good part.
What the hell...
After shouting, I got a bit hot...
Right? So I heard that you can get a lot of royalties when you do stuff...
And you know I have so much talent when it comes to music?
And so...
I actually went and made some music. Seriously.
What? Four songs for us?
Just from your images...
one song each?
And so you guys sing it and burn it onto a CD...
And then.. I would get the royalties from it...
So you composed and wrote the lyrics?..
Right, yeah.
Just for this day, 4 completely original songs
Narrator: Noda Keiichi
were genuinely created from scratch by Yamazaki.
And on top of that, he only had
4 hours to create them, showing his genius.
He was not a comedian whilst working but just a creator
Whilst imagining the singers, he was serious when checking over the melodies and lyrics.
All for the mortgage and the future of his family
Will Yamazaki be able to realise his potential as a music producer
and live his life off royalties like he dreamt?
So singers royaltieswill start at 200,000 yen each
So singers royalties will start at 200,000 yen each
However many we sell, that is set.
That's the contract
I don't know, this is something I've thought from a while back...
But Yamazaki uses Gaki no Tsukai for the privatization of things...
He really does!
Yeah, he does it a lot
Just for money too...
He really does.
Honestly, he just keeps doing it time after time...
Hamada-san, let's go.
Let's go.
Right now?
M-me!?
Right now.
Wait, right now?
Listen to it, rehearse it and then shoot the real thing
Eh, seriously!?
For real.
Really?
There's no way someone wearing this kind of shirt can pull this off...
Dun-dun!
Seriously!?
Really.
You're kidding!
What the hell...
Damn, this is tough
This is really tough
4 hours later
Thanks for your work!
Alright!
This is a horrible kind of tiredness...
Was it?
It's not like a nice 'tired' feeling...
You might feel like that now...
But you're going to watch what you did now and think "I'm glad I took part in that"...
Really?
You sure?
This is new ground for everyone...
There are loads of things I want to protest about...
Right anyway...
Let's start with Hamada-san's...
Oh me?
Wait, am I actually going to sing?
Hamada's Rehearsal
Yes, you are...
Wait... Why?...
Well.. That's so...
So we make sales...
To sell CD's, you can't muck around...
Please play it then
Why does the song have such a fast tempo?
You could have made it slower...
Sung by
Yamasaki Hōsei
It explodes in the middle of the town
♫ Machi no man'naka de haretsusuru ♫-
The desire that cannot be supressed
♫ Osae kirenai yokubō to ♫
But seriously, the person who made the whole thing is really amazing, huh?
Well, I did the whole thing by myself...
Right here...
Yes...
This part is really tough, even I struggled to sing it
Right.
The crimson key that opens the door
♫ Tobira o akeru shinku no kagi to ♫
OK.
Yeah?
You ready?
I mean, I don't really know...
Okay, let's try it for real.
No, no, no, wait up!
This is impossible
Just sing it once, seriously.
You can't just say  "Sing it"...
I don't remember the words so how am I meant to sing it?..
Okay, let's go.
It explodes in the middle of the town
♫ Machi no man'naka de haretsusuru ♫
The desire that cannot be supressed.
♫ Osae kirenai yokubou to ♫
The reality which had been dictated by man too much
♫ Tsukurare sugita genjitsu o ♫
Yeah?
You really weren't paying attention at all, were you...
I'm very sorry...
You were literally so bad right from the start...
I'm sorry..
Eh, hold on,
Wait, this is going to take some time...
I mean...
I know I was singing it casually like
♫ Machi no man'naka de ♫
Right.
But sing it like
♫ MACHI no man'naka de ♫
Right?
MACHIno...
♫ Machi no ♫
♫ MACHI no man'naka de ♫
Like a bit faster.
OK, I get it.
And just the last part
OK.
Just at the last part, it's a bit hard because of the lack of characters
Then add some on...
No but, er,
'To that world that no one knows about...'
♫ Daremo shiranai sono sekai e ♫
That's how you want it?
Yes.
Oh wait, the dancing...
The dance?
Well you can't be like this...
Oh you mean pose?
Yes
So start like this...
Hold on now,
Like this...
Are you sure this is okay?
Isn't it really lame?..
No way...
OK.
In the middle of the town...
MACHI...
♫ MACHI no man'naka ♫
No way, this is going to be so lame...
It's never going to be lame...
Sorry.
#1 Hamada Masatoshi
Yamasaki Produce!
Yamazaki produce... Hamada's song...
Weirdo alert...
Lyrics & Composition by Yamasaki Housei
Sung by Hamada Masatoshi
What the hell is this?..
Eh, what was it called?
"Beach Paddy."
Woah, this is...
Like a really old idol...
It explodes in the middle of the town
♫ Machi no man'naka de haretsusuru ♫
This desire that cannot be surpressed
♫ Osae kirenai yokubou to ♫
I balance this reality which has been dictated by man too much
♫ Tsukura re sugita genjitsu o ♫
I now know what image he's going for
For real?
and continue to live my life
♫ Hakari ni kakete ikite iru ♫
How far will we go, what should I do
♫ Doko made iku no dousureba ii no ♫
Like...
It's really old, huh?
Is there an answer, who will decide
♫ Kotae ga aru no dare ga kimeru no ♫
It really is...
Like the 80's, maybe 70's?..
Shine the light on
♫ Fumouna tochi ni ♫
this barren land
♫ Hikari o ataeru ♫
And it's been done so badly...
And on to the world where there is a Messiah
♫ Meshia no iru sekai e ♫
What the fuck is 'The world where there is a Messiah'?
It violently rings
♫ Hageshiku uchi narasu ♫
Literally...
O keeper who controls time
♫ Toki o kizamitsukeru ban'nin yo ♫
I have no idea what the lyrics mean either...
along with the chosen people
♫ Erabareta monotachi to ♫
and the crimson key that opens the door
♫ Tobira o akeru shinku no kagi to ♫
O keeper who
♫ Hageshiku uchi narasu ♫
The lyrics...
The lyrics are amazing
violently writes time
♫ Toki o kizamitsukeru ban'nin yo ♫
Do you get what this is about at all?..
Let's jump out right now
♫ Ima koso tobidasou ♫
Umm..
The lyrics are just...
To that world which no one knows.
♫ Daremoshiranai sono sekai e ♫
Aww, you laughed a bit at the end...
Sorry about that.
Like it's a best 10 hit or something...
This is great
You get it right? Like who this is meant to be and all...
It's him right? I might be mistaken...
* Popular music artist Takanori Nishikawa (1989 - Present)
TM Revolution.
Without doubt...
No, no...
It's not?
Totally wrong
I've never of this 'TM'...
Oh really? I was sure it was TM...
It's got to be...
However you look at it, that was TM...
Wait, is it similar?..
TM's Nishikawa-san is very much like that.
Very similar.
Even the outfit.
Even the movements.
No no, that's just...
Actually, Hamada-san was even more
pumped to do it than I thought...
Well he might not be as bad as you but
he is someone who loves royalties...
Oh, so he was thinking about that?
Yeah, he thought about that and got into it...
To try and sell it, huh?
As if that shit will sell...
Of course it will sell!
Really?
Yes!
An by the way, this song is called「BEACH PADDY」。
Right, why?
It's Hamada (in english)
Hamada
Oh really?
That's why
What kind of a title is that?..
But he's like
not said beach paddy once...
It has nothing to do with the song...
I can get if that musician is called it...
But the title of the song shouldn't be that...
No, because Hamada-san sung it...
Did you sing it, Matsumoto-san?
No, I didn't...
You didn't, right?
That's why it's「BEACH PADDY」
Well, I guess I can smack you anytime I want to so it's okay...
Let's go to the next one!
Next is Tanaka...
What was Tanaka's like?
Was the song style different?
Yes, it was
Can we proceed?
Yep.
Right, here is Tanaka's..
This is, uh...
Tanaka's Rehearsal
This is the stage.
This is the stage for my song?
Right, so do it the way
Right.
that you want to.
Okay
Do it like that..
Ok...
he doesn't look at me when he speaks to me at all, huh?
Right, cue music!
I always think...
♫ Itsumo omou no ♫
Can you sing through your nose a little bit more?
Through my nose?..
I always
♫ Itsumo ♫
When you do the V sign, look at Camera 3...
Right by your face...
Like this?..
V sign like this?
Basically as long as it's cute, you can do whatever you want
#2 Tanaka Naoki
Yamasaki Produce!
Yamasaki produce: Tanaka's song...
Lyrics & Composition by Yamasaki Housei
Sung by Tanaka Naoki
I always think
♫ Itsumo omou no ♫
Hang on, this is Noppo-san!
When I feel you next to me
♫ Anata o soba de kanjita toki ♫
I know, right?
He's gay?..
That's right, this feeling
♫ Sou kono kanji ♫
I thought that would be the best...
This is horrible..
I felt it when I was a child...
♫ Osanai toki no mama yo ♫
I have a lot of things to say about this too...
I will come to pick you up on sunny days
♫ Hareta hi wa mukae ni kite ♫
He does sing it like...
and wait at the entrance
♫ Mae de matteru wa ♫
It's intentional, I was singing through my nose a bit
Our special sign
♫ Futari no aizu ♫
The V sign with both our hands
♫ Ryoute de buisain ♫
Ah, that's awesome.
I was doing as I was told
And the movements, right?
Yes
When I was a kid
♫ Kodomo no koro ni ♫
I heard this story
♫ Kiita ohanashi ♫
It always has a happy ending
♫ Itsumo wa happii end ♫
So what kind of ending
♫ Anata wa watashi ni ♫
will you give me
♫ Don'na ketsumatsu no ♫
for my story
♫ Ohanashi o tsukuru no ♫
This is just..
This is a song for a woman to sing, surely?
For our lovely, that's right, love story...
♫ Sutekina sou rabu sutoorii ♫
This is some lyrics...
Wow, that was just...
This was really difficult
It was hard to sing it I bet too...
It was.
I was meant to be a 15 year old girl singing
Right.
My one, I was meant to be 21...
Right? I was 15...
Oh I see...
A 15 year old girl!
Right now, there are 6 billion people on this planet...
Who benefits from this episode?..
What you mean, some people might listen to the song and it might cheer them up!
What was the title called?
This one is「Riziere Centre」
What does it mean?
It means Tanaka...
In french though...
That's Tanaka in french?
Yes, it is
Is that what it means?
* Shoumurasaki Hiroshisan (Gaki Director)
It's so obvious you made Komu or someone go and search that...
Definitely...
Shall we go with the next one?
OK!
Ok
Right, next up is Endo-kun...
Right, my one was a real problem
This one in itself...
This was really difficult...
Right, shall we proceed then?
Shall we...
Er...
Endo's Rehearsal
It's all in English isn't it?
But I don't get why...
This isn't about remembering the words...
It's just your soul shouting
Ok
That's too bad
Pardon?
When you say That's too bad, say it like...
"That's too bad!"
Yeah, that's so much better...
Okay...
The interlude is like really long...
Yeah it was..
You're like free to what you want there...
Free?
Sorry producer, can you not like tell me what to do there and stuff?..
So we'll do this like once
Like we have no time
So we're going straight to the real thing...
#3 Endo Shozo
Yamasaki Produce!
Yamasaki produce: Endo's song...
Lyrics & Composition by Yamasaki Housei
Sung by Endo Shozo
Everything is done by Hosei-san, huh?
What's that about!?
Holy shit...
This is...
Oh damn, this would be tough to do...
Woah, this is...
This is something else...
This is...
I actually think Endo's amazing for doing this..
Yeah, this was really...
You really performed for your seniors...
Your seniors would never do this...
Yeah, Matsumoto and I would never be able to do this
Yeah, we wouldn't...
Yamasaki-san chose like everything with this, including the clothes
This was really tough...
Wow...
Honestly, I applaud you Endo for doing that...
Well to put it simply, that was heavy metal...
No Death Metal, it's Death Metal.
Damn but...
Death metal?..
If you put this into one of those hexagonal graphs...
You know, measuring applause from the crowd and all
It would definitely be close to like a dot in the centre...
Seriously, it wouldn't spread out at all...
Was there a reason for mine being all english?
Well because it's death metal
Oh, so because it's death metal...
You've been like preaching 'death metal, death metal' from before
but what the hell is it?..
It's a song
It's a song from hell
I sang that?..
Then don't make your juniors sing that kind of song...
Right, lastly...
Right.
Let's check out Matsumoto-sans...
Oh man...
Right, have a look..
Matsumoto's Rehearsal
It seems
♫ Mou ♫
that we've come to a point
♫ Modorenai ♫
where we can't return anymore
♫ Tokoro made kita mitaida ♫
This is literally
the manliest
of men kind of song
I see...
So I really want you to put your heart into it and sing it...
Uh-huh, yeah.
It's fine if you cry...
Without being embarassed
That's it.
Can we try then?
It seems
♫ Mou ♫
that we've come
♫ Modorenai ♫
to a point where we cannot return anymore
♫ Tokoro made kita mitaida ♫
That's great. This is really...
It seems
♫ Mou ♫
That's fantastic, Matsumoto-san
that we've come to a point
♫ Modorenai ♫
I'm sorry, I don't feel like I'm going to cry
but I'm going to laugh instead
No, you definitely cannot laugh
Really?
Yeah.
that you have
♫ Shinjitsu o ♫
nothing to lose
♫ Tsukamu made ♫
OK! OK, OK, OK!
We can shoot the real thing
Okay, let's do the real thing
Can I
drink something quickly?
Sure.
About the change of clothes...
Please go get changed, we've prepared something for you
I have to get changed?!
Yes.
We've got everything prepared
Seriously?
Yes.
Aren't we going a bit too quick?..
Alright, if you could please.
After this, Matsumoto records his real take..
#4 Matsumoto Hitoshi
Yamasaki Produce!
Yamasaki Produce: Matsumoto's song..
Lyrics & Composition by Yamasaki Housei
Sung by Matsumoto Hitoshi
This makes you look so lame already...
♫ Mou ♫
It seems
that we've come
♫ Modorenai ♫
to a point where we can't return anymore
♫ Tokoro made kita mitaida ♫
The theme of this song makes you look so lame...
Every time
♫ Furikaeru ♫
I look back
♫ Toki wa itsumo ♫
He should let you like run around a bit more...
I see
♫ Jibun no ♫
my own shadow
♫ Kage o miru ♫
Right?
And
♫ Sou ♫
if that's the case
♫ Sorenaraba ♫
let's go to the place where we must go
♫ Iku tokoro made ikou ♫
and if we do that
♫ Sou sureba ♫
You know like
They literally forced me to wear the jumper and jacket...
we'll probably
♫ Kitto ♫
Ah, right.
So I look like so serious...
not look
♫ Furikaeru ♫
back anymore
♫ Koto mo nai ♫
This feels like I've gone to welcome drinks or something...
These precious
♫ Zutto ♫
thoughts that
♫ Shinji teta ♫
I just come to Tokyo, and need to work hard.
I believed
♫ Taisetsuna ♫
Be friendly with the people I have to work with...
in
♫ Omoi o ♫
and my heart
♫ Darenimo ♫
which I've brought up
♫ Jama sa rezu ♫
without letting anyone
♫ Sodatte kita ♫
get in my way
♫ Kono kokoro o ♫
Oh damn, this is tough!
This is SO tough!
You can probably do it
♫ Kitto yareru sa ♫
This is so bad
It's always like that
♫ Itsu demo sou sa ♫
So old!
No, please no english!
Until you grasp
♫ Nani ni mo makenai ♫
the truth that you
♫ Shinjitsu o ♫
have nothing to lose
♫ Tsukamu made ♫
He's really gone and...
This is so bad...
It really leaves its mark for sure...
Right?
This is tough...
So bad right?
That was awful
That was amazing
Like I sweat the kind of sweat that comes out only when you've broken a bone...
You could have let me muck around a bit more
That's true
I wish you'd done something for me like Endo's...
I mean, these 3 got to muck around!
I mean yeah, we didn't have to dress up like you...
You guys are like doing it as part of the joke...
It was so serious...
Yours was so serious...
No, everyones was serious!
I'm so embarassed...
Everyone's was serious
* Popular music artist Shōgo Hamada (1975 - Present)
That was definitely Hama-shou...
I don't know who Hama-shou is..
I mean Hamada Shogo...
I don't know Hamada Shogo, that much...
You used to listen to him every day...
Yeah, but like... I forgot who he is
Even though you listened to him so often?..
I don't get it...
That reply was hilarious
You just forgot him?
Yeah...
So that was original.
All music producers watching this on TV
What is with him being like this?
Out of the 4 songs, I don't care which one, I want to make them into a CD.
We're all like totally serious
Wait, what?
"We're all serious?" You mean you're serious?
Yeah...
Right!
You are
Everyone, bow your heads.
Wait, what, what?
No, what do you mean?
Please!
All 4 of them?
Yeah, that would be fine
So for example
1 song is fine, right?
Yeah, 1 song is fine
Even just Matsumoto's...
Yeah, that would be fine
After watching them, I think only Matsumoto's has a chance...
Ours are like...
Ours were a joke...
Seriously,that was the first time in my life
the words 'Let it be' came out of my mouth
My mouth is shocked
So everyone in the music industry
We will be waiting
So please consider us!
Info Text
He's serious
There it is!
And we would like to end the show this week with this song...
Whilst listening to this?
I mean, this is the only way...
Geez...
This really leaves its mark...
What is with this feeling?
♫ Hageshiku uchi narasu ♫