Gaki no Tsukai presents the 1st,
"Stake your life on this one bite for a chance to win ¥100,000"
KIKI Cheese!!
It's the 36th Kiki episode.
I noticed something amazing.
What is it?
No, what I mean is... It said this is the 36th one from the Kiki series, right.
I've won it 6 times.
That's impressive!
That means I've won 1/6 times.
Kiki Series' winning percentage of 16.7%
Ain't that one hell of a winning percentage.
How about it, guys? In this Kiki...
Holy shit, you stink!!
Yeah actually, this is pretty embarrassing.
Kiki Series' winning percentage of 8.3%
I've really lost confidence in my senses.
It's been 10 years since you've won any.
2004 was his latest win.
Last time he won was for Kiki Miso in 2004
10 years?
It's been 10 years.
Man, I can't remember...
I haven't won any since the divorce.
Last time he won was for Kiki Oolong in 2003.
It's because of the divorce.
You also failed on the Kiki marriage.
The rules are quite simple.
Out of the 12 brands of cheese, you just have to find your selected cheese.
If correct, you'll win ¥100,000. Who will walk away with the reward?
The first challenger is Tanaka.
The number of cheeses has really increased, eh?
His selection is Koiwai Dairy's Creamy Cheese 6P.
From the mellow scented fermented butter
comes a rich flavor and a smooth texture.
Will he be able to remember this taste?
I'm going to smell it first.
Don't the elementary schools serve it during lunchtime?
Yup, we ate the thin ones  at school.
Eh, no way.
Yup.
Ours was block shaped.
They served it melted.
That's right!
Nope, it was triangular.
Really?
Yes, yes, yes, it was triangular.
I wonder if I've had it...
Whoa, this is delicious but,
it's too simpley...
Huh? What did you just say?
It's like "the cheese".
...like the father of all cheese.
I suppose so.
That was dangerous.
Whoa, whoa whoa, you held out really well just now.
Hamada-san, that was dangerous just now.
You already knew it was Hamada.
Why me?
Anyways, you've gotta pick one and try it.
I'm sure you've had this before.
Yes I have.
This Yukijirushi's...
Did the package change a bit?
Seems so.
Hokkaido-
This one's the standard...
As always...
You've been saying 'standard' a lot recently.
Why do you keep saying it every time?
Aren't they all standard?
Bon Appétit!
Surprisingly, Tanaka and I've won on the same ones.
There's pudding, castella...
Looks like it.
Nope!
Nope?
I can tell.
Eh, you can?
Yeah.
Is it totally different?
Yup, it tastes totally different.
The taste?
What I had
was NOT Yukijirushi Hokkaido 100 Cheese.
Alright!
Were you sure about it?
I was.
Well come on, he always says that.
But in the end...
I reckon the milk's fragrance was much stronger.
The fragrance?
Yes.
Please continue.
I've heard quite a bit about this cheddar cheese.
Just stop!!
He's just sayin'.
What am I meant to do... Why would you say that...
Why does he need to stop?..
However, Tanaka's momentum doesn't stop there.
Ah, the flavor was much deeper, much richer.
With confidence, based on the taste...
...isn't Chedder Cheese 6P!
...isn't Baby Cheese Plain!
Making it swimmingly so far,
Tanaka clears through three in a row.
Having cleared this much, it's not the time to be praising just yet.
Family Mart
I'll give this a go.
This...
This is really gonna make us quite full.
How many...
I told them 12 is more than enough.
I'm sorry but it's 12.
What?
Well, there's 12 of them, yup.
"12 of them is more than enough", well, there's 12 of em.
My apologies.
You were trying to say that it should've been 10, right?
Yes, my apologies.
Anyone would make that mistake
Just to let you know, he's had a sudden change of expression.
I take my eyes off a second and his face turned like that.
Like he discovered something...
It's totally the same!!!
What did you sample again?
May I?!
Well, if that's the one, go for it...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
If you're so sure then I suppose you've to go for it.
That's great man!
I'm going for it, for real.
What I had was Family Mart's 6P Cheese!
Come on!..
It was totally off.
Tanaka, you totally got it wrong.
Stop moving around.
Face your punishment properly.
It's time for the punishment.
He's so pissed!
You took ages after knowing you were wrong, just go to the front you idiot!
Nibble away at the cheese you filthy rat of a comedian!!
That lasted ages!
That was so long.
Ow, ow...
That would hurt.
Your face is completely frozen over!
Ow, Ow, ow...
Looks painful.
Proofreader:
Oolong (DTR Subs)
Timer/Typesetter:
yamasakigifs.tumblr.com
Translator:
J-Hive & Mickstar
dtr-subs.tumblr.com
j-hive.weebly.com
Next up is Endo.
We have to pick a simple one for Endo,
Thank you very much.
...since he's such an idiot~
Family Mart Collection 6P Cheese.
Butter mixed in Hokkaido cheese, this rich flavor is a one of a kind.
Go for it!
Uwaa, the sme- is quite something.
The sme-?
It just blew up in my face.
Compared to the cheese I'm aware of,
it's got a smoked smell to it.
It's not smoked at all...
Smoked cheese is totally different...
That would change everything...
Yeah.
He's such an idiot~
He's talking about the wooden board probably.
Looks like it.
You're smelling the board?
He's smelling the wooden board.
Smelling the board... What an idiot...
Endo is truly an idiot.
Well then, I've already narrowed it down. I think it's between these two.
I can't eat that much cheese so I'm going with this.
I'm going to try Yukijirushi Hokkaido- 100 Cheese.
You were stressing so much on the smell earlier, seems like you gave up on it.
Ah, this feeling when I hold it...
This feeling when holding it is a bit...
You can't be serious, Endo?
Please give me a moment here.
If that's all you've got to go with, then you're in trouble.
He just wants screen time...
I wanna cut ties with him.
Because he always has short air-time in the Kiki episodes.
But this one is quite bitter.
That's the first I've heard of, cheese being bitter.
I couldn't describe it properly but I know what I meant.
Say it so we can understand...
What an idiot~
A very uniquely processed cheese that had no scent
and made sure that people of Japan would like the taste of Hokkaido...
Just stop!!
What's with you, this whole time?
Well then, excuse me but this isn't it.
What I had was not Yukijirushi Hokkaido 100% 100 Cheese!
He can't see because he's aging...
He is aging...
Alright, he withstood it.
What the- so this wasn't it.
You withstood it.
I sure did.
You were absolutely sure that was the one?
I did.
If that's the case, then it will be something I've never had before.
Well then, I'm going to try France now.
Oh!
Uwa! This is all... It's all mushy, totally not it.
Ah, uha ha ha ha ha~
He's really making a mock out of this.
...isn't White Cream.
Convinced with the correct answer, Endo is full of smiles.
Uwa~!
Correctly getting by steadily, only six more to go.
I'm now going to have a go with Mother Farm - Plain Cheese.
Damn, the smell... Seriously, they've all got the same friggin' smell.
It's really close.
What?
I didn't hear him.
Guys, the cheese I've had before is this.
This is the one I've had before but not sure about...
Just stop already!!
Of course he would shout at you...
But it's definitely gotta be among these 2... 4...
I'm going for it!
I'd really like to get this right~ Here goes!
What I had is Mother Farm - Plain Cheese.
Uwaa, that's harsh.
Seriously~
I can't do this.
Your guess was wrong!!
The spray time was shorter than Tanaka.
Endo, it's this.
This one again...
It showed up just before.
It's Family Mart, the one that I fell for.
This is tough.
Ah, this is it.
Well you obviously have to just agree with it...
Next up is Hamada and as for his selection,
Q.B.B Baby Cheese from Kansai.
Based on carefully selected cheddar cheese, it's a milky dish with the perfect amount of saltiness.
Will he find this taste?
It's got some elasticity to it.
Elasticity?
If you're going to talk about elasticity, well...
most of them have it too.
and also there's...
some texture to it, as Endo mentioned before.
Where the hell do you see the texture anyway?
It has texture?
This guy is an idiot too.
An idiot right after an idiot.
These ones are probably all soft, as seen during Endo's challenge.
No, no, but you never know.
It might be better just to make sure.
For me...
It could actually be the one to stump him once he tries it.
You can tell, right... the moment you hold it...
What the hell is this?
We should hear the 'Ba-baaaan' (Out sound)
I can really tell the difference.
What I had
isn't Sekai Cheese Shokai- President White Cream!
Alright.
Wasn't that cream cheese? Just sayin'.
You can totally tell that it's a different kind of cheese.
Please try those other two...
You're right
Right? Please try one of those two
I agree
This Family Mart's...
Ah, are you going for that one?
Was it this hard?
If you get dragged into thinking about that too much...
it might confuse you more...
Huh?
I'm still speaking here.
There's a limit to how many times you can interrupt when someone is talking.
It had a more cream-ish feel to it.
What the hell are you saying?
What I had
was not Family Mart's 6P Cheese!
Alright.
But he's confident...
Yeah.
Is that confidence for real?
Moreover, with this one being cleared,
that makes it three in a row!!!
Ain't that Itsuki Hiroshi?
(Japanese singer)
It looked like it.
It was similar.
Sounded like in "Chikuma Gawa"
*"Chikuma Gawa" is one of Itsuki Hiroshi's song.
It wasn't even close.
Damn, you really pulled "Chikuma Gawa" outta the bag.
Yeah, the song...
"Chikuma Gawa" is outta the bag.
Not really.
How about this one?
Yotsuba Hokkaido.
Well, it's got a similar texture.
What do you mean by texture. God, you're annoying.
The feel is...
You should put it against your cheek then.
Everyone starts to like....
get stuck around here...
That's right.
If you told me it was this one, I would agree...
The texture...
The feel...
Goddammit, how many time is he going to mix em up.
Just bloody stop already!!
Hamada-san!
Yeah, he said "the feel" just now...
Just stop it! You!
The elasticity...
Stop recording!
All the cameras, point towards the ceiling for a bit.
It's going to be a long one.
Point it up once and bring it back down.
Swing it up and bring it down.
The two of you went for it, right?
We did.
Alright then, I'm going up as well.
What I had was Yotsuba Dairy- Yotsuba Hokkaidō Tokachi 100 Mini Cheese.
Well, it figures.
I didn't meet the correct one yet...
This is hard.
Ah~ there he is.
Has your thick brain all melted, ya fuckin' moron!?
Has it melted!?
Take a look, Hamada-san.
Which one was it?
It was a pretty simple...
Ah, so that was it.
I hadn't tried it yet.
Yup.
Well then, why don't you have a taste.
I thought you might actually get this one to be honest...
The feel.
What happened to the texture?
I definitely won't be saying that again.
The fourth challenger is Housei.
His selection is  Family Mart Collection, where Endo also suffered.
Butter mixed in Hokkaido cheese, this rich flavor is a one of a kind.
Will he be able to remember this taste?
Alright~
Getting wrong on the ones that showed up before is pretty funny.
That just gives us more pressure.
Yeah, sure does.
I thought you'd perhaps give me
a soft one from a foreign country
He's kicking off with a complaint...
Ah, it's got a light taste to it.
I've probably had it before.
He's smothering it all over his teeth...
Are you alright?
Will it really help?
Are you kiddin' me?
Just go home if you're going to keep that up.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
It's not coming off at all.
I'm going to try and choose which one I think is right.
Go for it.
Here goes, Baby Cheese.
Totally not it.
Absolutely not.
The flavor of the taste...
The one I picked wasn't Baby Cheese Plain.
The one he picked?
Ah~ But this is...
It's totally not it.
Clearly?
Yeah, I can clearly tell it's different.
And another one I've had before is this.
Nope.
Wow, I can really tell.
What I had
was not Yukijirushi Megumiruku.
You're on a good pace.
The pace is good.
Okay, let me try this one.
The one everyone...
Nope.
Totally wrong.
Huh?
What did I eat then?..
Well that's what you're trying to figure out...
He's tried this 36 times on this show...
What I ate
was NOT Family Mart's 6P Cheese.
So quick! It beeped the moment you dropped it.
Shocked, aren't you?
Eh, no way?
Shocked, aint you?
They cut you off real quick.
Like it literally hadn't left your hand yet.
Eh~ for real?
It was totally different.
That's what I'm saying, there's no way we'll get it right.
This is going to be hard...
No, this is impossible to get right.
Your stupidity has been fermenting for too long!!!
That went for ages!
It was the previous selection.
I had it just before.
Really?
It came up on your third one...
He got to try the correct one, as well...
He tried it and still got it wrong..
Now all that's left is to try it.
Just because it showed up before...
All that's left is to try it, surely
this cannot be different.
No, it's different.
That's enough.
It's definetely this.
Just stop!!
Proofreader:
Oolong (DTR Subs)
Timer/Typesetter:
yamasakigifs.tumblr.com
Translator:
J-Hive & Mickstar
dtr-subs.tumblr.com
j-hive.weebly.com
The last challenger is Matsumoto.
and his selection is Yukijirushi Hokkaido- 100 Cheese.
Using 100% Skimmed Hokkaido milk
It has a deep taste and has been sold for a long time.
I have no idea at all which one you've chosen...
I guess...
Please try tasting it.
Ah, it's hard.
What the hell, ain't this the leftovers!?
Just hurry up and eat it...
No it's not...
It's fresh new one...
It's really, really plain.
This one's just so plain.
Even at this stage...
The smell is also important.
Ah, but this really
smells like a rubber balloon.
Right?
Don't they both have the same smell, cheese and rubber balloons?
Since he can make balloon dogs.
Ah yes, at home...
Think about it, if I had kept on making it from then,
my daughter would surely be sick of it.
It was extremely plain.
Going by that bit, this plain cheese...
since it's been titled as so.
How about I try one of the ones around here...
and proceed while observing the situation...
Would that be okay?
He's imitating Non-chan.
Smells like rubber balloon.
This'll end it!
I'm going for it.
What to do, if this isn't the one
then it'll turn into an absolutely uninteresting show.
Ah, I know what to do.
I think it's probably this.
But I won't go for it
I'll say it's wrong...
But if I do as such
and it beeps, I'll seriously beat you all down.
I don't get why...
Why would you do such thing?
I'll hit you with my moves...
All of us?
Seriously?
I'll only leave the camera assistant alone.
Why is it only him that's safe?
That man...
I'll take a pass with this,
if this turned out to be wrong, it'd really be
such a waste.
All I'll say about it is that it's extremely close.
Nope, the camera assistant is going down as well.
Just because of that, I feel so sorry for him...
I feel so bad..
Just when he was spared.
You know, I feel like
I'm the victim of this show...
if this isn't it.
What I had wasn't Mother Farm- Plain Cheese.
Holy shit, that was close!!
"kyoe~! kyoe~!"
He was all, "kyoe~!"
Well, I'm going from this side.
This is going to be a long fight.
Uwa~ the elasticity is similar too.
Seriously, who picked it?
It was him (Hamada), wasn't it?
It was really all of us.
Everyone's said it.
This has gotta be the one.
That's what we all thought
Yeah...
You can't be picking this again!!
Seriously, to think that you'd dare pull this one again.
I haven't the slightest clue.
This is extremely close.
It's just a regular cheese.
But!
It's certainly got a slight bitter taste, so to speak.
This Yukijirushi's cheese.
Maybe that's all to it, that bitterness.
I'm really going to get it right today,
so I'm going through this seriously.
What I had
was NOT Yukijirushi Hokkaido- 100 Cheese, I think.
This isn't funny at all!!
You're right...
It wasn't funny at all...
I'm so embarrassed.
I know, right?
So embarrassing.
Yaaa~ that sure was tough.
If you have time to work on your body, work on your senses, you baldy!
He's turned all white.
That was a pretty long spray.
Yes, yes, that face...
I'm really embarrassed right now.
You had no clue at all?
Absolutely none.