10th Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Can we all be on the same page?
Let's rendezvous without using your smartphones!!
Thanks!
Last time we were together the whole time.
Didn't you guys purposely avoid meeting up with us?
Come to the place properly!
You know where to go when you see a theme, right?
- Tanaka, they know you're doing it on purpose.
- What the hell!
Here are the results so far.
I'm great, after all.
I knew you were terrible.
- I know I'm terrible.
- I'd never met you on the first one.
But last time, Hamada-san gave me the advice to go to the second place I thought of, not the first.
I took that ad..Nvice and....
"Advance"?
- Did you say advance?
- That's enough.
Let's rendezvous without using your smartphones!
The rule is that each person goes to the place they imagine from the theme presented, and if everyone can meet up, it's finished.
Usually this is a five-person segment, but this time they will add a guest to the challenge.
This person is the guest!
please come here!
Hi!
- This is going to be difficult.
- Yeah!
- Is it?
- Because there will be one more person.
- Do you know about this segment?
- Of course, this is a very popular segment.
- Are you confident about it?
- I have lived in Tokyo for about 18 years.
- You are like a Tokyoite.
- I am more than happy to be invited to a decent segment.
What kind of segments are not decent?
I am always invited to Big Dog Contests and other crazy segments.
That's a decent segment!
That's crazy!
Here's the first theme!
Historical buildings.
This is a very wide range.
The definition of "historic" is difficult.
- Hamada's house is also a historic building in a sense.
- What the hell!
- Do you live in such an old building?
It's 8 bedrooms.
"8 bedrooms"!?
And there's no bathroom.
It's a strange house.
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]
At 1:00 p.m. they left Nippon TV in Minato-ku, Tokyo.
What is the strategy of the top in terms of meet-up rate?
They are idiots.
So I have to adapt to their ideas.
Otherwise, I would not be able to meet them.
Yes, the shortcut to meeting up is to adapt to the ideas of other members, not just your own.
Zojoji Temple, which I visited last time, is also a good example.
- Are train stations also historical buildings?
- Tokyo Station is a case in point.
Matsumoto reaffirmed the definition of a historical building.
Meanwhile, Hamada had something he definitely wanted to avoid.
Anyway, I don't want to meet my buddy on the first one
Hi.
Last time, Hamada met up with Matsumoto for the first theme.
He seems to have been traumatized by that.
The Tokyo Metropolitan Government selects historical buildings that have been built 50 years ago and are considered important in terms of landscape.
What do the members think is a historic building?
It's the National Diet Building, isn't it ?
Considering the distance from Shiodome, that is where they usually go.
- It is where the prime minister is.
- That's right.
Viewers would probably think that "Macchan is the most sane", everytime.
There is a possibility that about three people could meet.
- That's never happened before, right?
- Yes.
If you adapt to the thoughts of the other members, you will inevitably meet up with someone else.
- Do you have some options?
- Yeah.
I came up with two.
I know I' ve mentioned this a few times, but I used to go to the driving range at Gaien a lot.
Wasn't there something in the back there?
- The picture gallery?
- That's old, isn't it?
And,
*****.
That's old too.
The heads of state used to come there.
Where do heads of state gather?
Hamada-san likes the Diet Building, doesn't he?
Yeah, he parked his car in front of the Diet building
And stared at it, saying,
"Just you wait and see."
It's depressing when Hamada comes there, though.
Will Downtown duo meet again on the first theme?
And where will Housei, who currently lives in Kansai, go?
I came up with two. It's one of those.
Okay, let's go there.
I decided quickly.
But it's difficult.
He seems to have narrowed it down to two choices.
Tokyo Tower and Tokyo Sky Tree.
But Tokyo Sky Tree was built not long ago.
Tokyo Tower is a historical landmark.
I will go to Tokyo Tower.
He chose Tokyo Tower.
I lived in Tokyo when Tokyo Sky Tree was built.
It was built 10 years ago.
So I went to Osaka when Tokyo Sky Tree was built?
I have such memories.
The Tokyo Skytree was built because I left Tokyo.
I had that feeling at that time.
"I'll leave the rest to you."
But that's a bit ostentatious.
"Historical."
Do you think Endo understands that?
You're a bad guy.
When the theme was announced, he looked kind of complicated.
I don't think Endo knows what it's about.
Is he okay with it?
Does Endo really understand the themes?
The first is Tokyo Tower.
The second is Nippon Budokan.
There is the aspect that Tokyo Tower = Tokyo.
That one often appears in old monster movies.
The Nippon Budokan is a historical building.
Nippon TV has shot a 24-hour TV show at the Nippon Budokan.
Downtown hosted it in the past.
Endo was able to understand the theme.
Where did he choose?
Then please head to *****.
And where did the guest this time, Fujimoto, head?
I was very happy to be invited  to such a popular segment.
After the Big Dog Contest aired, a young guy came up to me and said, "Awoooooo!".
- You are completely teased.
- Yeah.
Where did Fujimoto, who has lived in Tokyo for 18 years, choose to go?
Akasaka Rikyu, the guest house, for example.
But the other one seems to draw more people.
*****.
After all, everyone uses that place.
What does Fujimoto mean by a place that everyone uses often?
*****.
Okay, we'll head there.
At this point, Matsumoto, Hamada,Housei, Endo, and Fujimoto are likely to meet someone.
The only one left is the troublemaker Tanaka.
Will he be able to clear his name of the past nine times?
The first thing that comes to mind is Tokyo Tower.
The second is the Budokan.
What a chance to meet up with Hosei or Endo, whichever he chooses!
But!
But I'd prefer something more solid.
Sorry for being vague, but I prefer something solid.
Suddenly he started saying "something solid.
What was the answer Tanaka came up with after much deliberation?
Then one came to mind.
*****.
***** has a very long history.
Please head to *****.
Where did Tanaka choose?
A great chance for all of them to meet up with someone on the first theme!
What will happen?
Let's rendezvous without using your smartphones!
Now everyone has a chance to meet up with someone!
We're in front of the Diet building right now.
If there are five of us here, we'll end up here.
There's a TV crew over there.
That's not Gaki's, isn't it?
That was close.
It's okay.
Okay, we're here.
Yanaoka, could you pretend to be an idiot once and ask the security guard if you can get into the building?
If I did that, I would be gone.
Matsumoto arrived at the Diet building.
The chances of him coming here are the highest.
Really? That would be a depressing.
At the same time, Housei arrived at Tokyo Tower.
I like the way it feels.
You still think this is awesome, don't you?
And the clouds are moving so fast!
The clouds are moving so fast!
He excitedly waited for the others.
We arrived.
Soon after, Endo arrived at his destination.
Where is that place?
Look,
It's the Nippon Budokan.
Endo went to the Nippon Budokan and did not meet up with Housei.
I don't want to be alone anymore.
Now we're here.
Where did Fujimoto come from?
Speaking of meeting up, it's Tokyo Station.
Tokyo Station.
You never know where they will appear from.
Don't leave me alone.
And Hamada, if he comes to the Diet building, he can meet up with Matsumoto.
Where did Hamada arrive?
- How old is this building?
- It's 113 years old.
Yeah, 113 years.
Akasaka Rikyu, the State Guest House.
He could not meet up with Matsumoto.
Did they go to the Diet building?
Time's up!
They confirm their respective locations on the call.
Hello.
Enough of this!
By the way, where is Matsumoto-san?
Are you guys really stupid?
You guys should have come to the National Diet building!!
Come on.
I went through there.
I knew it.
That doesn't come to mind.
I've considered this.
- Endo, this was on your list of options?
- Yes.
If you didn't go to the National Diet Building, where did you go?
I came to the Nippon Budokan.
I see.
Oh, I forgot about that one.
Where was your second choice?
It's Tokyo Tower.
Can I talk for a second?
Don't talk!!
I'm here for Tokyo Tower.
I knew it!
You came to Tokyo Tower, Housei-san.
Tokyo Tower is too new.
Fujimon, where are you?
Don't you all remember that?
It's Tokyo Station.
Tokyo Station.
I know.
That was one of my options, too.
It might be true, but...
- Where is Hamada-san?
- CHAN-HAMA!
I'm in front of the Guest House.
That doesn't sound like you.
Hamada and the guest house don't go together at all!
I used to go by this area when I went to Nippon TV in Kojimachi by myself.
- I don't care about that.
- Don't say that.
Then, where is Tanaka?
Did Tanaka come to Ueno or something?
No, I'm in Nihonbashi, that bridge.
You better take care of your bridges with us than that!
A bridge between me and all of you?
Let's go to the next one!
Not a single person came here.
They were all scattered.
I'm relieved
I'm not wrong.
I said the guest house, didn't I?
Will Tanaka be able to meet up with someone?
50 minutes have passed since the start.
They have yet to meet anyone.
What's next?
Next.
What the hell is this.
I don't get it.
"Furniture store"?
One thing comes to mind. Is that still there?
Otsuka Furniture in *****.
Please head to Otsuka Furniture in *****.
I've been to Otsuka Furniture in *****.
Can they meet up at one of the several Otsuka Furniture locations in Tokyo?
The furniture store I usually use is Nitori.
Nitori also has many different stores.
Which store do you often go to?
I often go to the store in *****.
- Ah, that store on the corner over there?
- Yes, it is.
After I got divorced, I went there to buy beds and mattresses and stuff.
And dishes, too.
Nitori took care of me.
Let's not talk about these things.
Tanaka is a crook, and I'm not sure about Fujimon either.
I wanted Alice Hirose to come.
It' s fun when an actress comes.
I don't get excited when Fujimon comes.
Meanwhile, what about Hamada?
Isn't it Otsuka Furniture?
in Shinjuku.
There is a Cassina in Aoyama.
That place stands out too, doesn't it?
And then there's Nitori.
Fujimon will definitely go to Nitori.
He is likely to go there.
Hamada's prediction was right on the mark.
Which Nitori store did Fujimoto head to?
Here is their current location.
The area is narrowed down considerably, but where will they really go?
Will they be able to meet up?
The problem is still Tanaka.
How do we get Tanaka out of the regular members?
Let's go tell him that we're ending the show.
After all, that's especially difficult in the beginning.
That is why it makes sense for us to meet up with them.
Then, let's continue with Gaki as if nothing had happened.
And Tanaka would eventually notice that.
"Hey, this isn't over yet!"
But he won't tell us that.
He won't say to me or Hamada,
"Hey, why isn't it over yet?!"
Where did Tanaka, on the verge of being fired, choose to go?
How about IKEA?
Where is that?
Harajuku?
The Harajuku store is right in front of the station, right?
Let's go to Harajuku.
The answer Tanaka gave was IKEA Harajuku.
I'm in trouble.
And where did Matsumoto arrive?
Here?
Otsuka Furniture in Shinjuku.
Tanaka doesn't have to wait for someone, which is nice.
Who will be able to meet up with the others?
1 hour and 5 minutes after the start, a great chance for the members to meet up.
Matsumoto was waiting for the other members at Otsuka Furniture in Shinjuku.
Then...
Matsumoto-san, Matsumoto-san, Matsumoto-san,
Oh, what a surprise!
This is the only place, right?!
This was the only place I could come up with.
- 'm expecting about four of us to be here.
- I think this is an easy theme for us.
Anybody come here?
Good!
This is fantastic!
This is the only place, right?
- Can you think of any other place?
- No, speaking of furniture...
it's Otsuka Furniture in Shinjuku.
The three of them were able to meet up with each other splendidly.
Where did Hamada arrive with Otsuka Furniture as an option?
This is where today's young guys would come.
Fujimoto chose Nitori, and this was his chance to meet up with Hamada.
Well, here we are.
What will happen?
Is somebody there?
Nobody's here.
Fujimoto chose at Nitori in Nakameguro.
He couldn't meet up with Hamada.
Meanwhile, what about Tanaka?
You can see the furniture from outside.
There is no doubt here.
He arrived at IKEA Harajuku.
Time's up.
Did you meet someone?
We are now the Matsumoto Team.
Yamazaki and Endo are here.
There are three of us!
We are at Otsuka Furniture in Shinjuku.
Where else but here?!
I knew it!
They're all freaked out by us.
What did you say?
I first came up with Otsuka Furniture in Shinjuku.
Then why didn't you come here?
- But in these days, everyone buys at Nitori, don't they?
- You don't have to think about the these days.
Don't think you're right because you have more people!!
I'm scared!
Where is the Nitori where you are, Hamada-san?
- I'm at Nitori in Shibuya.
- Why did you go to that store?
- It's so big!
- I know that place, but I've never been there.
Where's Fujimon?
I'm at the Nakameguro store.
Ah, I know Nakameguro store.
Nitori in Nakameguro?
Fujimon is standing on stage at Shinjuku Lumine, right?
This is your neighborhood, you know.
You're doing all those hero show skits at Lumine, aren't you?
Shut up!
Where is Tanaka?
I'm at IKEA in front of Harajuku Station.
- Huh?
- Where's that place?
That store!
A short time ago...
I can't stand in a place like this (because it is so crowded).
Hamada was passing by IKEA Harajuku.
Hamada was passing that store.
We were absolutely right.
That's right.
Are you guys all scattered?
- You three have forgotten what it feels like to be an ordinary person.
- That's right.
That has nothing to do with it.
This is not that kind of segment.
Endo, don't be cocky.
That was very scary.
Endo, it's true,
you're getting carried away.
Oh, really?
We're comrades, right?
Next week.
[Kushikatsu Tanaka]
Let's rendezvous without using your smartphones Part 2!
Will all six of them ever get to meet?
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]