The Second Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende Chiki-Chiki
Yamasaki Hosei's Ass Revenge "Ass-1 Grand Prix!!"
So that's his last wish
That is so, he absolutely wants to do it
That's his wish to end this year
Well, about that
I can understand why he wants that
He would hate not doing it so much.
Wouldn't you feel the same?
He always did what he wanted to
Anyway he wants to do it this month and year
He's very encouraged. I see.
Without further a do
Let's see Yamasaki on the stage
He's on it
Yamasaki san
Good day. Come on in
Frankly speaking, I'm so angry today!
What are you angry about?
I must be the one to do it
You see, last time I didn't fight to the fullest
Didn't you?
Honestly, I was overpowered by Moriman
I see. Honestly, in many aspects
But last time before the match with Moriman you were saying how you'll beat everyone
Before today's match he came to me and said "she's a bit mean to me, I don't understand that", isn't that hilarious?
Last time Yamasaki fought with an Ass-match champion Moriman
Where Yamasaki fought with a steel will in a match where the existence and the survival were bound together
I'm sorry for last time
I'm sorry for that.
I'm really sorry, can grab your attention for a moment?
Look at this
Who's that? That's mine
So that's you? Yes
I've injured my fourth and fifth ribs
But there's nothing at all!
I did! Look there!
But it's all white, I don't understand what you mean
How can you not see anything on it?
Wait a moment, then what do you want to say with that? You want to quit today?
If that's possible...
Then why you came?
I'd like to quit it, but I won't be fighting like last time
Last sparring was about physical condition
As we've seen. So what's your plan for today?
Today this sparring will not be about physical condition. This time, as I don't have much power, I'll be using a lot of technique
Is that so?
If I'll be doing that, I'll definitely beat Moriman
Then call your sparring partner
Hey, mister!
What a tough-looking fella
Hello, is that your friend?
Good day
Is that so? You must be joking
Heipo, are you going to fine?
I think I'll be alright
He looks quite ready
I'm looking forward for it
"Revenge" (rule-free mixed martial arts match to grab one's ass)
Looks good
He's attacking!
What's Heipo doing?
You fought like a 40 year old office worker
Yamasaki san, that was good
You did really good
You understood how to get an advantage over the opponent?
But as we've seen previously, Moriman slaps the face
Is that so?
Do some guard work
Let's go
"Assuming a champion's attack, sparring again"
Just like that, throw these punches, Heipo!
Yamasaki san, that's not how you do it
I would like to see a fight for the last bowl of rice between Moriman and Heipo
Wait there a moment!
Give me another chance! But that's not the matter!
Give me another try! Why you're asking for that?
I'll do my best
I understand. So this time, Yamasaki san do your best at this match with Moriman
"Fate deciding match - Moriman vs Yamasaki"
"The outcome will be seen at the second half of this program"
Matsumoto san, this time at the seats by the sparring ring
Are quite filled, aren't they?
Are they really going to come out from there? It was quite difficult buying tickets for that
Even if a celebrity would like to watch it, it'd be quite a task to get here
Even for Uchida Yuki
Today
So, enough of chit-chat, let's start
Yamasaki became a challenger now, didn't he?
First, the entry of the Challenger!
"Challenger Yamasaki Hosei"
You fools!
Whom are you telling this?
Fine, fine, we know you're angry
He's already undressing
Why did take that off already?
Next up in is the Champion's entry!
"Ass-match champion Moriman"
There she is
Long time no see
One point scored
There are no snots
What was that?
Are you an idiot? There's nothing coming out
What's the matter with him?
There's a flower ceremony for both parties
What a sight! Both sides should do their best today
Are you touched?
I'm very moved
So, without further ado, let's begin the match
Don't forget what you practiced before!
Don't give up!
Looks great!
That doesn't look good
"Champion Moriman victory"
This looks so pathetic
Yamasaki, that was too much
What are you going to do now?
Where are you going?
What was that?
Moriman, you idiot!
What's the meaning of this?
What are you doing?
How long have you waited for this day?
Why did I have to go through all this?
That's all because you're so damn weak
Shut up!
The hell you're talking about, you weakling
That's too harsh. That's bad.
You're 29 years old already and soon will be a 30-year-old
A 30-year-old
Shut the hell up yourself!
Stop talking about my private life!
We understood it, we understood
What are you going to do?
My privacy was exposed