Yamasaki Hosei
North Sea crusher Moriman
The two have never ever been so stubborn before, facing and fighting each other again and again, however it all ended up as failures to Yamasaki
His pants were taken off
And was brutally beaten
After that, this summer a battle was held, where Yamazasaki lost all rounds in front of everyone's eyes
In front of Moriman's astonishing power, you get to know what real life is
In the end, Yamasaki ran away from the ring
He said, that next year this match can be continued
"The biggest winter campaign of the century"
Yamazaki vs Moriman Storming Last Final Revenge Match
Yamasaki enters the venue three hours before the decisive battle
Then 30 minutes later, arrives Moriman
The venue before the decisive battle of the century was quiet
"Pre-match doctor check"
Yamasaki san
What's the matter?
Is your physical condition alright today?
It's fine
You don't need to be afraid having a body check
There's no need in that
Your zip's undone already
Is that fine? Then please...
Take that off
Everyone does that before fighting
Just check my heartbeat
Look how his arms are hanging
How raised it. You took your clothes off, as if you'll have a heart attack
Like he's going to die
His heart beats a little too fast
So he's worrying
Let's listen to him breathing
His breathing is fine. So it's alright. He just feels very nervous
He's nervous?
That's not true. I am going to do it!
Really?
Doctor and Yamazaki san have been through some stuff
The day of the match is finally here, where in the Korakuen Hall a history will be made
More and more people gather at the venue
And finally the venue is completely filled, with the audience being electrified
All that is left is to wait for the match
Why don't we have a look at how both fighters are doing now
How are they doin... Ah, here we have two assistants
Thanks for having us
I think he'll make it today
He looks good today
So he'll do it today? He will.
I really want him to do his best
That's a waiting room?
So, that's Moriman?
She looks so relaxed
She looks like she's at resort
And her partner is.. No way that's real
They act as they will never lose
They seem just like last match, that they have plenty of free time
And Yamasaki san is here
That looks weird. YOU, LISTEN HERE!!
I WILL ASK IT AGAIN! DID SOMEBODY SAID THAT I'LL LOSE?
So he beat them up? THAT'S HOW YOU END UP!!!
I didn't know this side of him before
Moriman is scary! Do it genis cumedean. Do it with your right hand!
What's that, genis cumedean?
No idea
Ah, do it genius comedian
When he kicks, it's difficult to hear
Right hand, right. Will he say that again?
Go for it, genis cumedean!
Now at least we got it
Moriman is scary!
Moriman is scary
He presses him with "Moriman is scary"
Will he say it again?
Moriman is scary!
That was hilarious
Thank you for your wait!
The biggest fight of the year is about to begin
Yamasaki vs Moriman
Storming Last Final Revenge Match
First of all, this competition's jury, Downtown's entrance
Thank you very much!
Is it really the final match?
I would also hope to think so, but he always keeps dragging that further, so that can't be helped
What if Yamasaki will suddenly lose today?
Yamasaki should definitely make it
He honestly should do win it
I think he worked enough for that
Today I the most important thing is to have an intention to do it
And finally, ladies and gentlemen, I think everyone wants to see him win
Ladies and gentlemen, I ask for our attention
Champion Moriman's entrance!
There's even a banner, saying "North Sea crusher Moriman"
You came all the way from Hokkaido
Moriman had to come to Tokyo, all the way from there
That was honestly so bothersome to come here
Today I will absolutely destroy him
Shall we greet our next challenger?
And our next challenger - Yamasaki Hosei's entrance!
I DON'T WANT TO BE A LOOSER ANYMORE!
HOLD IT! WAIT!
I'M SICK OF THIS BORING-ASS PERFORMANCE! SHUT UP!
THAT'S MY DANCE OF DETERMINATION!!!
I DON'T GET THAT CRAP!
I HAD TO COME ALL THE WAY FROM HOKKAIDO HERE!
FROM THE BEGINNING, A MAN REACHES OUT TO HIS DREAM!
The hell did you say?
TODAY, RIGHT HERE, IN THE YEAR 1998, YOU'LL SEE YOUR DEFEAT!!!
WHATEVER YOU THINK, I'LL NEVER LOSE TO YOU!
IT'LL BE YOUR DEFEAT!!!
NO, YOURS!!!
FINE,LET'S FIGHT!
Let's give him a final word
Yes. FROM THE BEGIN...
Cut that off
Now ladies and gentlemen, we will proceed to Yamasaki's friends flower ceremony
The first person to come is Yamasaki san's old pal
Fujita Senji sama
Please, do your best today
Following up, flowers from NSC (Yoshimoto New Star Creation) Morishita Yukio sama
How foolish
Without further interruption, let's commence our match
In the red corner, 210 pound
Absolutely unbeatable champion
Homicide Angel
MORIIIIMAAAN!!!!
In the blue corner, 130 pounds
The Eternal Challenger
Born in Nishinomiya, a fighter that disappears without a trace
YAMASAKIIII HOOOOOSEEEEI!!!!!
Without further interruption, please, stand up for the anthem
Right now, Endo Shozo will perform
Endo's song
Ladies and gentlemen, please look over there
Is he a fool?
He's so irritating
Childcare in Japan is number one
You're all doing great today!
Thank you very much
Let's give now a word to Downtown
Please ladies and gentlemen remain quiet
Well, our dear audience, now will have
Heipo's performance
Let's commence
I didn't really know what to expect from that
But that went OK
So, let's see now the battle menu
Over there!
From now on, fighting styles for our fighters will be chosen from this board
Well, I think for the first round will shall choose something that we haven't used before
Pantyhose removal duel
So this one? It'll be terrible
You think so? I think it will go well
Is that alright with you? Yes!
Sound good!
Pantyhose removal showdown!!!!
"Pantyhose removal showdown"
Let's begin!
First round!
Here it comes!
The movements are not that bad
I think we can give them one extra minute
He's losing it
Yamasaki saaaan!
Yamasaki san!
The hell were you doing?
Please, listen for a moment
OK
It became too intense
How can you say such words?
No, I'm serious, serious
Aren't you alright?
Alright?
LET'S MOVE TO THE NEXT MATCH!!!!
BEER SMASHING SHOWDOWN!!!!
"Beer smashing showdown"
Beer smashing showdown
Let's begin
Did you hear that?
I did very well
Can Moriman hear?
Can you hear?
Moriman can you hear? it's alright
Go, go for it!
Go for it!
Can you hear? Can you hear us?
Can you hear?
Yamasaki san
You're OUT!
As soon as it flew from the ring
I was so close!
That was such an exciting battle!
Yamasaki san, tell us your next fighting style
LONG TROUSERS SHOWDOWN!!!!
That's a new style
What a foolish match style
The hell's that?
Go for it, genis cumedean! Moriman is scary!
They gave him some advises
I think they are the most incomprehensible foreigners
"Long trousers showdown"
That's quite a...
I think no one ever saw a fight like that
Do your best!
The way he hit his head
He can't lose like that
Yamasaki
He's being knocked down
He's knocked down
That was so wrong. Why were you hitting an arm like this?
Do you want to quit?
No, you're wrong
What's that?
That's so I could go
We were so surprised, we thought that you wanted to give up
He's knocked again
He's knocked
Yamasaki san!
Stop doing like that!
No, no, that looks like a joke. Please put more effort
That's a give up gesture
I'm doing that when I'm desperate
THE NEXT MATCH!!!
Well, what do you think about Gobourebaki stick match?
Gobou stick showdown
Gobou stick showdown, that will be a brawl for real fighters
So that will be, indeed, a sight. Matsumoto san, please look over there
They look like his real mentors
I WILL DO IT!!!
BRING THAT ON!!!
WE UNDERSTAND!!!
"Gobou stick showdown"
Yamasaki san!
It hurts, it really hurts! It hurts?
Please, listen! That's no good, fighting with these sticks.
Do you mean that you want thicker sticks?
No way!
How foolish
Yamasaki san!
Is this match going to finish with Yamasaki's defeat?
That hurt, that really hurt
Yamasaki san
Gobou stick match
LET'S GET IT ON!!
Let's start!
He fought so wrong
That was such a big mistake
Yamasaki san
He gave us a spectacular reaction
We stay with the Gobou stick fight
Yamasaki san, are fine losing it this way?
I lost!
Yamasaki san, you may have lost this round, but next one you'll surely win
That's what you should tell
I really hate it
If that's so, then let's go with another style
Piping hot soup
That must be good
"Piping hot soup showdown"
That looks really hot
Matsumoto san
I think after that he'll become a disabled person
You know, it seems like it's impossible for Moriman to lose even once
Next match you will absolutely win
Please give me a real match
From what we saw before, you don't seem that you really want to win
Understood. Next match will be a K-1
K-1 SHOWDOWN!
"K-1 showdown"
This time, referee will be Hamada san
Please
We count on you!
Let's start!
This is the first time Moriman fell from Yamasaki! Will we remember this fight as his first victory?
Try to guess, until you'll find it out next week!