As the boke I'm worried for my job
Hamada Masatoshi Senility Trial
This king of comedy will turn 51 this year,
But his senility will not stop
His "old man-ness" will be exposed
Incident #1
It was an episode where they enjoyed nostalgic games
They have bang snaps too!!
Hamada found some bang snaps, that make a loud bang when you throw them
He hatched a plan to scare Endo,
He approached with the Bang Snaps
There's ice cream-
He tried to throw them to the ground,
But he misjudged the distance to the table
Indeed, an onset of senility
Incident #2
Broadcasted in April, TKO Kinoshita's Shichi Henge
Pay attention to Hamada's front teeth,
This was there the whole time
Right in the middle?
He did not notice,
There was some spring onion stuck between his front teeth
In the centre?!
Spring onion is stuck in there,
And he didn't notice it,
It's GREEN!
Incident #3
A birthday gift to his junior,
The tangerine says "Otanbi Omedetou" instead of "OtanJOUbi Omedetou" (Happy Birthday)
I didn't notice at all
His senility caused him to forget the most important character
Don't you feel relieved after writing the "TAN"?
I mean that kanji-
That's a great proverb
"One feels relieved after writing OTAN"
Incident #4
Hamada misunderstood the size and came in wearing a ladies T-shirt
Victim - Kimura Yuichi
The victim explains what happened,
In the end,
It was like a ballet dancer's practice outfit,
The shirt barely reached his belly button
It short and tight,
I was quite sad...
If that was a ladies,
It was just right
Another great proverb
And tonight, more senility incidents will be exposed!
We have a junior comedian here who looks up to Hamada,
We've collected testimonies,
and a representative is here,
What...
Is that alright?
Yes
Witness, enter please
Presiding Judge
NAKAMURA Yoshinobu   Producer
Hello,
Witness
Jinnai Tomonori
What the hell man
JInnai will be the representative,
That's correct
In order to present evidence against the defendant,
I have collected testimonies from various junior comedians
To provide a judgement,
Yes indeed,
Testimonies from junior comedians,
Jinnai will reveal some shocking senile moments!
In honesty, there are many young comedians who admire Hamada,
In fact, I WAS one of them,
WAS?
You say that in past tense?
I was dissapointed in a lot of his actions,
There's a lot there
So you've lost respect?
First off, "Incident #1 - A Meal Time Disaster"
Hamada has treated many of his juniors to dinner,
But there are many senile moments that occured at those meals
Ready? This is it,
Knocking over a transparent glass with water inside it
"Knocking over a transparent glass with water inside it"
Transparent things are invisible to him
He can't see them
Just invisible
Transparent things are invisble,
When he knocked it over,
he went " WHAT WAS THAT?!"
He was surprised?
So, moving on,
"Satisfied after 3 pieces of meat"
This story,
Hamada and his juniors,
They had dinner at a Teppenyaki place,
Being considerate of Hamada,
"Should we reduce the size of our order?" they asked him
and Hamada said,
"Don't treat me like an old man! The standard is fine!"
He was a bit angry
So they ate the meat,
But after 3 pieces of meat; "Damn I'm so full"
and then he dozed off
I've been told this happened,
What do you mean "Dozed off"?!
That's what an actual old man would do
This is what I've been told
It's a shock indeed
I wish we saw his meat loving side more there
There's other dishes, before the meat. There's other courses,
So it's not like,
Dozing off, and such
That story is something a comedian made up to be funny
You're still only 50!
You've still got a long way to go
Moving on,
"Pranking Himself Instead of His Junior By Accident"
Hamada, with his junior from Osaka,
There's a bookstore he often goes to,
Leaving his room, Hamada,
He takes his junior's shoes, and throws them really far away,
This is a signature Hamada prank,
But recently, and he does this very often,
He throws his own shoes away
Don't be ridiculous!
HEY! Stop being ridiculous!
There's no way that's true!!
There's no way that's true
I've been told this
This is too terrible!
Typeset by Shappuri Agemasu Subs
Translation by senor_wristband
"Young Comedians Confess"
The senility stories continue
But really, Hamada,
He does care a lot about his juniors' birthdays
He's a kind senpai
Is that so?
First off,
"Forgetting a Birthday #1"
There's 1 and 2
There is a 1 and 2,
There a junior named Hirai, who's birthday Hamada went to,
And 2 days after, Hamada called him up,
"When is your birthday again?"
Piss off!
There's no way that happened
Is it possible to be that dumb?
It was a kind thing to ask, but yes after 2 days
After 2 days?
If it was Monday, he asked on Wednesday
And if it was Wednesday, he asked on Friday
"Forgetting a Birthday #2"
This story,
One day one of Hamada's juniors suddenly got a call from him,
Hamada called him up
"Did you know it was Taiki's birthday yesterday?"
"If we don't do something for him he's gonna be sad,"
"Let's have a party for him"
Very kind
"I'll decide on a place and call you later"
Very kind senpai indeed
He hasn't called him back for 2 years
Terrifying!
Comedians are funny huh?
2 years, so close to 700 days?
700 days without a call back
A surprise?
Funny, very funny
As expected of comedians
So moving on,
"They're Senile As a Couple"
From one of his juniors,
At Nozowa Naoki's birthday,
When Hamada reached over to remove a rice grain stuck on his wife's face,
She thought he was gonna smack her and was very scared
You piss off!
She was like this
Knock it off I'm saying
Both of them are senile
Incidentally, Hamada is really into using LINE,
There's a stamp that Yoshimoto put out,
A stamp of himself farting, and apparently he really loves it,
Whenever he wants to reply "No" to his wife he sends it to her
Why, why does he do that?
He farts at home,
and farts on LINE,
And then his wife gets scared when she sees it
She thinks she's gonna get smacked
Next, an anti aging story
Another shocking revelation awaits
Hamada, well,
He wants to bring back the cute Hamada of the past
He wants to be cute?
Restoring his cuteness at this age?
He wants to bring back the cute Hama-chan
He's desperately trying different things, like this here,
"An Unwavering Faith In Garlic"
What the hell is that
He just straight up loves garlic
Sounds very stupid
He will order a dish with garlic in it wherever he goes
An unwavering faith
Absolutely
That is a bad way to say that
If you go out for BBQ and they have some garlic side of course you'll order it
An unwavering faith
That's all that means
That's why it says "Unwavering faith"
Stop using stuff like "Unwavering Faith"
Everyone orders garlic
I don't really believe in garlic that much
It makes you seem cute so it's OK
This is a nice thing
So the second thing,
"He Uses Face Masks for His Skin"
This one,
I get it,
This one is true
I admit this one
Have you done this anti-aging stuff recently?
If I go golfing, after I come back,
I will for sure do it then
A picture of that moment,
It's Jason
And you're sending a fart here
I don't know about that
Let's move on to the last bit,
A "Title" for Hamada
In order to cement his position,
He's asked his juniors to refer to him by a title
"Call me this"
Oh no
You're all familiar with these titles,
Yeah you guys know this
Hagimoto Kinichi is called "Colonel",
Takeshi-san is "Tono" (Lord)
Sanma-san is "Waka" (Young Lord)
So,
Hamada Masatoshi,
This is what he's told his juniors to call him,
Here we go,
"CEO"
Is he a CEO?
This is not a lie right?
This is true?!
Well, yeah,
We were talking about "Should we decide a title?"
And before that, on some TV show or something Matsumoto-san called me that
So using that I said "Call me CEO",
That's it
So this is not a lie then?
This is not a lie right?
What's with that desperate attitude?
Why is he mad?
I said "Hahaha Call me CEO!"
I said THAT!
Well you did tell us
Alright, alright,
We'll let that one go
And it makes you look cute so it's alright
Memory Related Incidents
Incident #1
An incident when Hamada and his juniors went out for Karaoke
"Mazinger, Mazinger,"
"Mazinger Z!"
"OK! I won't lose to anyone!"
"Tonight, I'm gonna drop you"
"I sang my heart out"
"As expected Hamada-san, you're good!"
"Right?"
"You guys sing your heart out too!"
"Yes, thank you very much!"
"Alright, I'll sing Mazinger-Z again and do better!"
"Okay!"
Right before the junior was about to sing,
"OI! YOU JUST SANG THAT SONG!"
"DON'T SING THE SAME SONG TWICE AT MY KARAOKE PARTY"
"SCUMBAG! I'LL KICK YOUR ASS!!"
"Sorry! I won't do it again!"
Hamada unleashed on the junior
So scary
"Whatever, can I sing now?"
"Yes, please!"
"What should I pick"
Please, please don't
"OK I got it"
Please stop
And then,
"Hmm, is this ..."
If it's not a joke, then this is unnerving
Hamada sang Hikigane once again in high spirits
Incident #2
This New Years,
What kind of house is that?
Hamada's juniors went to his house to hang out
"Hamda-san, Happy New Years!"
"Oh, you guys are here! Come in"
"Your house is huge!"
It's nothing special!
And then,
Cause he's an idiot
"Happy New Years!"
"Ah Natsumi-san, Happy New Years!"
"Make yourselves at home today!"
"OK! Thank you!"
And then,
The Hamada household's lively puppies
"Hamada-san, you have dogs?!"
"Yup, they're so cute right?"
Hamada cared for his 3 dogs like they were his own family
"I really love dogs!"
"What are their names?"
"You asked a great question!"
"I'm only gonna say this once, so pay attention,"
This big one is Kiyonu,
This one is Ribbon,
and this little guy here is De Niro
"They're so cute right?"
"That's not it at all!"
"The biggest one is De Niro!"
"And this boy is Kiyonu!"
"And the small one is Ribbon, right?"
"Just when will you remember?!"
It seems Hamada doesn't know his beloved dogs' names
Incident #3
This incident happened when Hamada and his juniors went to play golf
Golf is awesome!
"Hamada-san, you're in high spirits today!"
"That's right,"
"The ball went really far too"
Hamada on that day was feeling his best
They went through the course in high spirits,
And then,
"Okay, starting from now, English is banned"
"You have to pay a 100 yen penalty for every English word"
"Ehh, that's so hard"
"By the way, Hamada-san,"
"What should we call the driver?"
That's easy! That's the pushy thing, or the "Eldest Son"
"Amazing, Hamada-san!"
"So then, what about the Iron?"
Well,
"The Second Son"
Even idiots like you guys understand right?
So they began playing with a ban on English
Alright let's do this!
"Yes!"
"Ok then ..."
Hamada's very first word was START
"Man, the Eldest Son really hits different!"
What should we do about this
Is it alright if prosecutor Tanaka takes the stand?
Well, well,
Witness
NAOKI Tanaka
That's correct
Those three eipisodes,
You wish it was on purpose,
You wish it was a joke
Yes, a joke
You wish that was the case
Do you have anything to say about those scenes?
The Karaoke?
Hikigane
I cannot recall
Surely it is
Do you remember that you got angry at your junior?
Mazinger-Z
I mean, making people to listen to the same song again,
I see what you mean,
I might have said something about that,
The English ban,
That one at least, that could've been a joke
Uh, yeah ...
Sorry, can you elaborate on this
When starting something,
You want to get the excited,
Of course
What did you say?
He said it with his chest
This one is,
It's not just me
I mean anyone could make a mistake like that, right?
Well, it was your challenge
The first word you said!
You could've said "Hajime!"
There's more,
Last year, the defendant Hamada released a golf lesson DVD
So with a DVD,
Only people who bought it, can watch it, right?
Whoever bought it, will watch it of course
But still, Hamada at the end of the video,
"Everyone, buy it please!" he said
They're already watching it!
Do you have objections?
Nope
Right
Acts of senility that have shocked the comedy world
It's time for his sentencing
Prosecutor Matsumoto,
Announce your judgement
Judgement
The defendant, Masatoshi Hamada, is so senile that we cannot refrain from remarking on it
This is an established fact
Now that society knows about his affliction, he must redeem himself
The sentence is; "Hamada Jizo: Steal The Manju" Part 2
"Restore Hamada's Image! Hamda Jizo Part 2"
What?
What Hamada Jizo means...
HOT BLOODED
HAMADA CLASSROOM
An episode where Hamada unleashed his Spartan teaching style
Go get it
This incident occurred
So next is "Steal The Manju from Hamada Jizo"
Alright?
In this game, players have to steal a Manju being protected by a blindfolded Hamada
Hamada has a paper fan in his right hand,
And a CO2 gas burst trigger in his left
He puts his blindfold on and gets ready
Principal, you forgot about the button
You need to take the blindfold off first
What're you laughing at?!
Very sorry
Then Koumoto tries to steal the Manju
He swings the fan to protect his manju, however,
You can do it!
He clears the challenge with ease
However Hamada doesn't realise this, and frantically swings the fan
ENOUGH! Enough
What are you doing Principal?
And just when exactly are you gonna use that switch?
A depressing senile moment
He will redeem himself in this moment
Is this necessary?
If you can do this, we will no longer doubt that you are not senile
But still, if I'm blindfolded,
I can't see
Yes?
You need to sense it
Sense it? Alright fine
Last time, we were outside
It was pretty blustery that day
Stay quiet, so I can hear
Focus on us then please
We want to help you as much as we can
We want you to succeed
Yes, I understand, OK
He forgot to pick it up again
Let's begin
You're ready?
Ready,
What, asshole?