First ever, Episode 7 Absolutely Tasty Takoyaki
Now is Takoyaki
Rice, Pizza, Taiyaki, Chawanmushi, Mochi, Tempura
Today is Takoyaki
It's true
This corner
DOWNTOWN
Matsumoto Hitoshi              Hamada Masatoshi
I don't wish to fill myself with these food
Cocorico
Endo Shozo             Tanaka Naoki
Thats right
That's right
After eating i feel sick
Yamazaki Hosei
Returning water
Term for feeling unwell
Remember the previous episode, angel mark appear
Is that true?
It is truly delicious
My recipe is bread and corn soup
Angel mark
Truly delicious
Delicious
If you do this well, will there be prize for it?
That is genius creation
Genius right?
Top-batter is Tanaka, what did he bring for ingredient?
First dish
It's this
Big potato, instead of squid
Big potato
This is sweet
Sweet
Wait, i want to try something sweet
Are you including the sauce?
This is sweetened
Sweetened
This is possible
That's right
Like snack
Yes, like snack
Second ingredient
It's this
Crab pincer
Crab, Pincer
Children will like it
Adult will also like it
Normally, children also like Takoyaki
Children will definitely like it
Seafood replacement will still be good
Firstly
Hot steel plate is ready to cook the takoyaki
Put the potato?
I am
For real?
First dish will go well?
I heard it before Takoyaki Potato
This is enough right?
In between is okay
It's huge
That's right
Instead of squid
I put it like this
Put the whole
This is definitely good
Like that
My grandpa know how to make Takoyaki
For real?
He did it once
He just did once
What the hell
There is salty Takoyaki
Salty one
There is pork meat takoyaki
There is whale Takoyaki too
Terribly disgusting
Never heard of it
Finally everything is inside
Never heard of Whale Takoyaki though
Big potato Takoyaki, the sweetness trait material will receive what point?
Crab meat
Second dish Crab Pincer
The end of pincer is out
This is a never seen Takoyaki
I've never see this before
Ain't that right? This is new creation
For the enjoyment of Children and Adult
2nd dish comes out as a beauty
Tanaka first dish is Big Potato Takoyaki
How does it taste like?
Ain't this looks good?
Well-made
You are amazing
First look and it's well-made
This also smell nice
Tanaka, distribute it
Why are you first?
I took the bad one
Distribute it now
Look at the potato
Don't judge by smell please, scary
The potato itself have sweetness, firstly
Itadakimas
The smell is
Taste of sweetness
Sweet
Too sweet
Delicious
Sweet but delicious
During festival
When you buy it, you will be happy
On the other hand it's not something fun
No.. this is .. Tasty!
The black sesame
It's strong
Tanaka's dish is not bad
I think 7
It's around there
How is it?
It is just the first dish
Then it's 7
It's high
This is high
How is the next going to be
How what?
Confident?
Why you didn't eat what you make?
That's right
What the hell
What the hell is this
This is too sad
6!
It is delicious!
Why? why? why?
I used my hand directly
5, 5 , 5
Tell us beforehand
No, no, 7 is okay right?
The potato takoyaki Tanaka afraid of, 5 point
Next is Tanaka 2nd dish, crab pincer
How success is it?
It looks nice
How is it?
This is very nice
Doesn't it looks fun?
Ain't it?
Made for children
That's right, see
It's scary because the pincer become muscular
What is it?
Kids enjoyment is fulfilled
Itadakimas
The flavor is in
Hoi, delicious
Whatever Yamazaki eat, he always say tasty
It's not bad
That's right
Ah, tasty
The flavor is distinct
If you try to improve the sauce, the flavor will be better
Right, the volume is enough
What happen if it's tartar?
It's wrong right?
Need improvement on the sauce for CrabYaki, 7 point
Next challenger is Endo
The ingredient Endo recommended is?
The first ingredient
This it is
Go,go
Salted kelp, this is
This is..
Eh, just now i was hit
It's a trend
This is definitely will go well
Tasty
You are going with this?
It's also cheap
This come from Celecrity Endo
Celebrity Endo will..
You are famous
For real, being a celebrity
The fame for being a celebrity
I don't know but there is 6 million yen spent on my wedding
The bride's Father
Is a chairman of a company
He literally spent 6 million yen on this
He have celebrity friends too
Now is royalty
This is request from the Father right?
I don't really think much about it but i am shocked
I see
Next dish is this
What's this
Yes, it's tea bag
Tea?
Tea, i don't really drink it but i will explain later
Well, this is a try
Where is frisk?
This time i think i must stop it
It looks so cheap
You still a celebrity?
I am ~~~
The poor man style, dried kelp flavor, how will it fare?
Tea bag is not edible, just like this
Round it and round it
The entire thing?
For real?
The entire thing
What the hell
You are an idiot
The taste will spread in the takoyaki and then we will eat it
Imagining takoyaki with the taste of tea, how will it fare?
Endo first dish salted kelp, how will it taste?
It's something interesting
Eat just like usual?
Just like usual
The taste is all over
The plate?
Bring it
Faster
Don't show your chest
Faster, faster we don't have enough time
Downtown must be first
The first is Tanaka
Honestly you look awesome
He is getting proud
This is good
Itadakimas
It smells nice
Tasty
Delicious
How is it?
Tasty
This go well with beer
Yeah
It does go well
Delicious
This is a delight for 40 years above
It suits us all
8 point
This is seriously angel mark
For real?
First is the economical cost, then
The taste blend well, really well
It is angel for me
Despite Yamazaki judgment, the dried kelp takoyaki receive 8 point
Next is Endo 2nd ingredient, tea bag
Don't show your chest
don't show it
The appearance is not bad
You did it
This situation fit the kid's enjoyment
That's right, eat like this
Eating like this is not my style
Hot
It is difficult to eat
What the heck is this
Right
The taste?
There is no taste
There is no taste ... Bitter
The tea flavor didn't come out
There is no taste
How many point, yama-chan
This one...
6 point
So high!
Too high!
1 point
It's 6 though
But the taste
Thats right
Based on what we eat is 1 point
There is no taste
So close, i think it's not 1 too
It's not ~~~
Because it's Endo
Why so lenient
Previous episode he also keep on saying Endo, Endo
That's right
Hard to eat and tasteless tea bag Takoyaki, 1 Point
Next is the sweets lover Yamazaki
First
First is this
Please Yama-chan
What's this
Peanut butter
I hate it
I decline this
I hate it, It's sweet I don't understand
Don't understand? It's peanut butter
I can't take this
You are saying you hate it before i make it
It's like child saying cannot play at my house
It's tasty though
Foreigner like it though
Yamazaki first ingredient peanut butter
2nd dish vegetable juice, turmeric tea, tomato juice
For finishing touch i will put it on a stick and it will look like dango
Why do i feel he is speaking impolitely to me?
Looks like 3 color dango
You are putting that much?
This much
Fifth episode using peanut butter
So it's like that
Cool
Just that?
The flavor is there
This is all
He is impolite again
You must stop it
Yamazaki 2nd dish is no filling, varied color and healthy dish
Yamazaki 1st ingredient peanut butter
Peanut butter
Matsumoto, this is delicious right?
First glance it's just usual takoyaki
Toughness is just right
Let's eat
It smells nice
Hot
Tasty
Don't keep on saying delicious
There is no sweetness
He is right, no hint at all
Because it's too warm, the sweetness just fade
Because of the heat the sweetness disappear.
That's right
*10 to the power of -9  or the value 0.000000001
This one didn't even worth 1 nano*
Nano? That's all my effort worth?
1 nano peanut butter, obviously 1 point
Next is Yamazaki, first glance healthy 3 color food
This
I see
First..
Appearance
Look at it
Never seen this before
Never right?
Vegetable juice, turmeric..
Tomato juice
Vegetable juice
Horrible
The turmeric
The turmeric is amazing
Seriously?
Last is tomato juice
I ate 2
It's 3 times as bad
This is very
Eat all your food
This guy really
Even Suga is laughing
Black-faced wagyu
First look at the edge of betrayal, 3 healthy diet, 1 point
Next is the highly anticipated Hamada turn
First ingredient
What the heck!
What?
Let it not be black-faced wagyu
Don't say that
Squid ink
I mix in the body
Squid is already in takoyaki, so..
Takoyaki is squid ball, so Hamada improvise with squid ink
2nd dish
This is the usual octopus
There is seaweed and rice, why?
Hamada 2nd recipe, Normal takoyaki is made into rolled sushi
Put this in
This is again..
Daring
It's black
If this is sell at a stall, the reaction will be what the heck
That's true
The squid too
Then squid ring too
Takoyaki is also using rice powder
That's true
I see
Each person get one
First is squid ink, how will it fare?
Here it is
This is evil
The shape of evil
It's bomb, bomb
It's grotesque
When i saw it,
I am shocked
So it turn out like this
Let's eat
Tasty
Again
This is very tasty
Squid ink taste like this
Anyone seen this before?
The squid is nice too
The squid is big
Even though it's good
Not bad
If there is crunchy taste it will be better
It's 6
The top is 8 so 6 is okay
Seriously?
Then 6, thanks
Taste not bad, squid ink takoyaki 6
Next is Kansai-nara combination takoyaki rolled
It looks good
Looks good
It's setsubun
I see
Rolled yaki
From any angle
Done it during setsubun?
Never..
Let's do it
It's like something mother will do
True
Let's eat
Nothing special
I get the feeling if there is something to dip with
I see
It's close but..
Do this with the sauce
Mayonnaise
Absolutely
It's hard
That is good
How is it?
It's better
For real?
Seriously?
There is a taste
How many point?
With or without sauce 4 or 5
Seriously?
What?
I think it's higher
What point?
I think it's 5 or 6
True, Hamada being senior need to receive better treatment
Is it because of the Nakayama muscles? It's 2 right?
The betrayal rolled sushi, 4 point
Last challenger Matsumoto
What is his wanted to try
This creative, first time ever appear now
First is this
Fruits takoyaki
After making the takoyaki
Then dip it into the chocolate
Then we freeze it
Freezed takoyaki
Freezed?!
I always have 3rd ingredient
I need to stop those, i can't play with food
They are not edible
Next is my 2nd dish, it's this
It's seal testicle
Testicle?
The whole thing?
Yes?
I am thinking of using this part
That part is good for health
This is from the same water family
Amazing
First is Strawberry, banana, orange made into takoyaki
And then
Put it in here
Until the last part it's delicious
Cover it with chocolate
Then put this in freezer
For 2 hour
That's quite long
Let's break up first
It's bad
Gaki staff is not afraid of that
They are
The seal testicle have a special way to prepare
The piece is amazing
The pieces are amazing
This is a delicacy
Never heard that before
Shut up
This looks extremely delicious
Looks like pino*
Guessing it's a choco ball
Yeah looks like pino*
I put in different fruit, so i don't know which is what
Let's eat
This is not takoyaki
It's not
It's dessert
Orange
Orange is bad
It's still edible
Evil?
Evil is common now, skull is not
What's with the evil
Labeled with skull, the takoyaki 1 point
Next is the scary one, the testicle takoyaki
Normal jumbo takoyaki
First look to it
I see
Disgusting
Imagine what is inside
The testicle and another one cost 20,000 yen
So it is something to try
This is amazing
The thing inside is impossible
Oh, sorry
The smell
Impossible
The smell of ammonia make my nose run away
Heipo
Heipo~
Master Heipo
He save us during these time
Please eat it
Takoyaki is delicious
Eat the main
Everything
What happen master
It stink