Gaki no Tsukai's famous series: Shichi Henge
In this series we see how a true comedian behaves
In a harsh situation in which they cannot fail
Last time we had Bananaman's Himura, who made everyone laugh
Bananaman Himura's Shichi Henge is already subbed and online @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com!
He got fifth on the Shichi-henge ranking
And today is time for Himura's partner, Shitara!
First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai!
Bananaman Shitara's Shichi-Henge!
Is it our first time?
We have Shitara today, Matsumoto
You know, I wanted Himura to be the first between them
I mean, that's how I think it's supposed to be with them
Is that so?
Also I happened to see him before, he looked like a member of the Blue Man Group
Not his best face
Here's our protagonist
- Yes
Let's bring him in
Thanks for having us
He's not showing his best face here
I'm feeling tense
You did great last time
Yeah, he is in 5th place
That's right
46'000 yen
I remember how happy I was when I got home that day
We got lots of positive feedback too
I thought you were just a human billboard promoting bobcuts
Guess you're not just that
He's gonna be great too
He's our brain, you know
We can say he himself is Bananaman
Yeah, I'm not as much as Bananaman as him
I have nothing to do with that
The hell are you sayin'?
Let's start by asking you which place are you aiming for
I'm guessing higher than him
I think I'm aiming for 10'000 yen
Gimme a break, man!
You can't aim that low
Yamasaki only made 10'000 yen?!
You never cease to surprise me
Impressive, right?
Don't talk shit about me, hey!
Such potential!
I didn't mean to target you
Anyway, anyway...
How are you feeling today?
How? Pretty shitty
Shitty, huh...
- Why?
It's true, you can tell
Look at his dead eyes
He has no sparkle in his eyes
- Yeah
Before entering this building, I walked around it for minutes
BANANAMAN HIMURA'S SHICHI-HENGE
Translation & editing by: Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Typesetting & QC by: GakiDave
find more at: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
haven't watched
like my page: facebook.com/shionnotsukai
support my content on:
tinyurl.com/bananamanhimura
yet? go here:
・ ko-fi:  ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
・ patreon:  patreon.com/shionnotsukai
What should we do?
There's a lot of stuff on the whiteboard
"Matsumoto Zombie goes to New York!!"
Can I say something about the first one, "Matsumoto Zombie"?
We did that, yeah?
It was terrifying
What?
Being buried under the ground
Tell us about it
It was incredibly scary
I mean you're completely in the dark and you can only hear voices
Maybe zombies are more scared than we are
I think they're the scared ones
You endured it pretty good
I was freaking out, really
It was around 25 minutes
Really?
- Yeah, around that
ADs too told me to get out
Really?
Around 10-15 minutes
Incredible
Why bother enduring it, then?
You have a point
Long story short, I'm done with zombies
What if we do it in New York?
- No way
He'd still be buried underground, you know
I'm never doing it again, for real
You know
When you arrived you were like "we're here"
I heard it through my in-ears and I wanted to get out in that moment
That only makes the whole situation more hilarious
I'm scarred for life now
I wanted to see your live reactions
What should we do...
We can use Endo's obsession with Frisk...
Yeah, that---
I bought a large bowl today
Man, I love seaweed with vinegar
Is there anything to do?
Put 'em in
Not so many laughs, huh?
Wasn't that funny? It was to me
Yes, it was
Hurry up and pay
Did you feel that smell?
- It was something
Alright then
Real talk now, what are we doing next?
Which one?
Yama-chan performs "Annie - the musical"
This one?
Have you done it before?
- No, I haven't
I used to have an hairstyle like Annie's before, though
I remember that
The fluffy one, right? It was more than 10 years ago
I remember that pic with your surprised face, hilarious
And you always wore that suit
I'm glad you managed to get over that phase
You opened your eyes and realized your mistakes
Was it that bad?
The fact I only wore that?
I'm sorry, hold on
Hello?
Hi, it's mom
Doing well?
Yes I'm fine, listen...
I'm working right now, so...
Oh? Yes? Are you working? What are you doing?
I'm working with Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai, so I'm quite busy now...
Are they here? Can you let me talk to them?
No way I can't, I shouldn't even be on the phone...
Come on, let me talk to them
I'll call you later, ok?
No wait, wait, don't hang up
I can't, really
Who's there?
There's Downtown, Cocorico, Yamazaki and others...
Eh? Who's that?
Who's that?
Tanaka from Cocorico...
And...?
And Yamazaki
Hm? Who's that?
You know, Hosei
Who's that?
Hosei Yamazaki
Come on mom, I'll call you again later...
You know, you said there's Downtown here...
I don't really like Matsumoto, be careful, ok?
Don't say that, mom... really, not now
Please it's my only wish, let me talk to them
Are you kidding me?
Just few seconds, would you?
Alright, but don't be rude, ok?
It's my mom, she just wants to say hello, can you talk to her?
Please, sorry about this... please
Hello?
Oh, hello, I'm Shitara's mom
Oh, nice to meet you, I'm Matsumoto from Downtown...
Thanks for taking care of my son
We're in the middle of a meeting, so maybe later...
I'm glad I got to talk with you
Same here, I'm glad
Thank you so much for everything
Satisfied now?
Don't you think he changed?
He's becoming more gentle, you know
How can you tell?
I think that having a child made him become more gentle
You think so?
Do you think he was nice?
Can I talk to Hamada too?
Mom, please... Give me a break
Come on, just a little...
For real?
Hamada, sorry... it's my mom, she wants to say hi
Hello?
Ah, hello, Hamada?
Thanks for always taking care of my Shitara
Thanks to you, ma'am
You have such a wonderful voice
I think you're really my type, Hamada
You're flattering me
Best regards for what's coming next
Thanks, same here
Hello?
Hello
Hey, I think I got a little w▀t down here...
The hell are you saying, mom? That's embarrassing
This is ridiculous
Wait-- w-- excuse me...
I want to talk some more
You just did it, mom, isn't this enough? Come on
Let me talk to them some more
We're done here, mom
What the hell
She had no idea who you are
Yeah, I wonder why...
Even though he's appearing so frequently on "Drive A Go! Go!"
Yeah, he's spending a lot of time in that show
He's always there
- Is he?
You won't believe how many times I saw him there
I remember
When I saw him on the preview for next episode, I laughed so much
I laughed aloud in front of my tv
That much?
- Yes, I swear
Like "It's him again!"
"There he is!"
[idle chat] Yes, it doesn't match up with his character
[idle chat] Always doing crazy stuff...
He really enjoys making a mess
That was hard to bear, man
I have no idea how to explain that
That's the main issue
It's hard
We have to hurry up and choose something
Excuse me, are you Mr. Shitara?
Yes
I'm a huge fan of yours
Oh, thank you
I have a request if you don't mind...
Can you show me your d▀ck?
Eh?
I'd like to take a look at your d▀ck...
My d▀ck?
Yes, I want you to show me your d▀ck
I'm so happy!
Ohh, amazing! Thank you very much!
Pardon me?
I'm a fan too
Oh, thank you
Can you please draw me your d▀ck?
You don't want my sign?
No, your d▀ck
Do I have to draw my d▀ck?
Yes please
I mean, no big deal...
Amazing!
Thank you so much!
I'm really a big fan, can you please take a photo with me?
A photo?
If you please
A picture with your d▀ck
Yes please
With my d▀ck?
How should we--- can I do this?
Here I go!
Ohhhhh, amazing! Thank you so much!
Don't put that on your blog, please
That was so random
You gotta be kidding me
Made it  - He's the worst
That was really something
- Incredible
He did really good, those girls were amazing too
He got me so quickly, even before the pants
- It's the angle
Yeah, you had him right in front of you
Himura, would you please stop laughing so nonchalantly?
You're making us laugh too
- You can tell he's genuinely having a blast
But it's like my first time ever in 17 years watching him going all-out like this alone, I'm having so much fun
Is it?
You're really enjoying this
I won't deny it
Pay up
That frickin' mouse!
That guy is a huge sadist, isn't he?
I don't get him, doing that thing all over again, it got on my nerves
He just couldn't stop
Hamada is the same type
Sadists are so insistent
He's so insistent
- He is
We still have no idea what to do
How do you like this one, sir?
Sure
Sorry to have kept you waiting
Here's your Martini
He's the worst
He's really the worst
That was disgusting
Heipo made us all laugh
'Cause the girl almost hit the trumpet
Yeah, I laughed at that too...
I hated it
Is this the last one?
- Yep
What's this? "Producer Oonuma's office is a ghost mansion!?"
What's that place like?
Akira Onuma
Producer
You know the company's office
It's 40 years old and its walls are so thin
It's... it's not a ghost mansion, I wonder what that means...
Nothing special about it?
- Not really
But it's really something
- That guy is such a mood killer
I mean, the place is great and all, but his office alone has this weird aura around it
Heipo
Why is he so excited about it?
He wants to work on that
"Producer Nakamura's secret midnight girls meeting"?
That's not true, am I right?
Are you kidding me? That's all he ever does
Don't say it
How do you know that?
Oh, sorry
Senpai, please give me some clothes
Why are you always asking that?
That's not true
No way my clothes will fit you
Killer Khan
But I've lost so much weight
Really?
- Yes
I have some clothes here... but will they fit you?
I really like this one
Isn't that too small for you?
I've lost some weight, it should be ok
Maybe it fits
See? It fits
It looks tight to me
Small clothes are this year's fashion
Is that true?
Seriously? If you're ok with that I'll give it to you, but...
That's trendy
Is it?
- Really?
Thank you
You can have it, then
Alright!
I also have this one if you want it
I'm worried about its size too
This... yeah it's fine, thanks!
But you're so big
Can you wear it?
I can, don't worry
You sure you're ok?
That's its back
That's how I do it
See?
Is it going to fit?
It's creaking... is it really ok to you? Looks small...
You sure you're ok?
I'm fine
Is it ok?
It's so hip
If you like em they're yours, man
Thank you so much
Yeah, don't worry about it
Wanna go grab a bite?
Is there anything you wanna eat?
Jingisukan
Jingisus--kan?
Jinjs--- Jingisukan
Jingisukan? Let's go
Can't wait to eat it!
Incredible
That's a nice sum there
One, two, three...
Alright, let's see...
37'000 yen!
- He scored 13th place
You scored as much as hip-shaking Obasan
Thank you very much!
You did pretty great, you know?
- You think so?
I thought "man, he's such a bad guy" more than once, you know
Me? A bad guy?
You also got others involved
Oh, you mean Killer Khan?
- Him too, yeah
You went all out on dirty jokes too...
You mean my d▀ck?
Yep
Wasn't that hilarious, though?
It was
- Yeah, it was
This guy is an asshole too, he couldn't stop laughing!
Translation & editing by: Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
'Cause I thought he had such a nice d▀ck
Typesetting & QC by: GakiDave
No one asked you that
find more at: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
I also thought about forcing Matsumoto to touch it
I thought about that too
like my page: facebook.com/shionnotsukai
I've touched some big d▀cks before, ya know
Sorry, uh...
But your d▀ck is way better, am I right?
support my content on: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Yeah, that's a really good d▀ck, I swear
Shut up!
I swear
- What the--
The hell?
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
SPECIAL THANKS TO GAKIDAVE FOR TYPESETTING THIS EPISODE!!
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FAN-TRANSLATION MADE BY A FAN FOR OTHER FANS. ALL COPYRIGHT ARE RESERVED TO THEIR RESPECTIVE OWNERS.
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES