People who lose control of their emotions
This, is that complete documentary.
subbed by jesper (www.jesperong.com)
thanks to kengho for helping out
Endou
Everyone Else
Hamada
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Yamazaki
color coding:
Here, the members assemble.
By the look on their faces, they're still carrying smiles.
Well then, guys
There's a sign there
(sign: wait here)
As always, the bags have no relation whatsoever.
This is irritating!
You can actually see him from where the bus was can't you?
Fujiwara Hiroshi
Hey you guys!
You're not being very cautious at all.
But we already saw you from the bus
The stupid look on your faces is completely exposed.
Well we can see you from here too.
It's.... completely exposed.
Do you know why...
...I'm on a stakeout, Yamazaki?
Me?
You're supposed to be a woman right?
Well, I can't say I know why
Why are you such an idiot?
If a celebrity,
acts like an idiot it won't do you know.
It becomes an unthinkable scoop
Sorry, who the hell are you supposed to be?
It's been decided that we're news reporters
As newbie reporters,
everyday, various...
no, not everyd..... Sorry.
How can you not laugh at this?
Act out your character properly!
As newbie reporters,
You have to take the various scoops as they come.
Speaking of "news reporters",
what's up with your appearances?
Well, we've only just heard about this.
Can't be helped
There're boxes(changing rooms) over there,
Go get changed quickly.
(Getting changed to the appropriate attire)
We'd like to at least decide on our own costumes yea?
Please step out in sequence.
Firstly, Hamada
- Oh fits you rather nicely.   - Oh yea? Thanks
(Competent old reporter Hamada)
Matsumoto
(Bald hoodlum reporter Matsumoto)
The cap sorta suits him
Doesn't this look right for hunting?
Why here....
I look like a caddy don't I?
Yea you're right
Endou
(Fresh, handsome reporter Endou)
Tanaka
(Skinny, lanky reporter Tanaka)
Yamazaki
What the hell?
(Oldboy reporter Yamazaki)
What's the meaning of this?
"What's the meaning"?.. This was there
You again...
If a celebrity acts like an idiot it won't do no?
This is a huge scoop!
If you keep that look, then it's enough
Ok guys gather round here
Let me explain the rules.
First of all
From now, you'll be working as news reporters for a day
Next,
Once we board the bus, you're not to laugh no matter what happens.
*cough*
Suppose you do laugh
You will receive a harsh punishment
Well I don't really understand what that means
But somehow I don't think it's a good thing either
That's all.
Well then, shall we head to the bus-stop?
Is it time?
Is it starting already?
Matsumoto-sempai, this is ridiculous isn't it?
I heard it was supposed to be paradise
For real
Ah, it's here.
Kurobikari News Company
Ga-su- Kurobikari..
Ah! To "Ga-su- Kurobikari News Company"
This is the name of company you'll be working for from now on
For celebrities, your reactions are pretty weak
No well, we don't really know what's going on.
It starts once we get on right?
We're a little nervous you see
Ok, let's get on.
It'll start once you get on
Ahh crunch time!
Here I go
Arrange yourselves -
Yamazaki, Matsumoto, Hamada, Endou, Tanaka
(Several passengers on board)
1st seat Yamazaki
Scary~
I don't wanna go to this so-called news company
Is it far?
I don't...
...think it'll take long.
It's bad talking to that guy
He fumbles on his own words
Yea you're right
Fujiwara-san, what kind of character are you playing?
I can't really tell
I'm a beautiful reporter!
It's a first for me
(Bus-stop Arrival)
(Office Lady boards)
(Another Office Lady boards)
(Matsuko Deluxe boards)
That's dirty!
That face is bad! It appeared all of a sudden!
(Receive ass-beating from Black Tights Corps)
My ass is crying!
(Corporate OL - Matsuko Deluxe)
What's up for today?
What should we do?
She came in with a face full of confidence
Deluxe, you're really popular with men aren't you
I'm so jealous~
I attract the weird ones, can't help it though
Rumor has it that Yamashita-san from the sales department
is also interested in Deluxe
It's totally hopeless!
Hey look
Those 5 guys have been staring at Deluxe since just now
Deluxe is too popular~
Say about the first guy on this side,
(Deluxe evaluates the 5 guys)
Welllll... not bad...
What about the second guy with the shaved head?
Somehow it's difficult to say
Ahhh... I seeee....
What about the third guy?
That guy, even though he doesn't look very sharp
doesn't he look honest?
Doesn't he look respectable?
Then then, the next g...
That one looks extremely good!
(Endou is extremely good-looking ?)
(Since they have already begun laughing, please enjoy until the next bus-stop)
What about the last guy?
...Impossible...
Isn't that pubic hair on his head?
It's pubic hair!
(Not completely taken in - Tanaka)
Eeww.. Disgusting~
It's sorta making me angry
Eh? What's wrong?
Hold on, I'm going over there
(Deluxe draws near)
Oi, step outside
You! Step outside!
That's cheap!
She's still looking, still scowling.
She's humongous..
What made her flip like that?
Let's quickly leave! Let's go!
Why were you so detestable?
I have absolutely no idea.
She's staring really hard
Totally staring.
If Deluxe was thin, he'd be a handsome guy no?
Seriously, why do you say so?
Why? "If he was thin, he'd be a handsome guy"?
Huge eh?
Another bus-stop?
(Bus-stop arrival)
Wah!
Here it comes
Wah.. here we go
Somehow somewhat that's what I thought
If you're nervous it won't succeed
But we practiced alot
(Chinese - Gekidan Hitori & Yamauchi Kenji "Kamaitachi")
Good thing we did yea?
Really anxious yea?
You're nervous aren't you?
Look, how about trying them?
How about having them
look at our magic?
Excuse me!
We're magicians from China
Now, would you mind having a look at our magic?
Ah. ok.
- Thanks   - Please look
This trick has no set-up
This here is just a long cotton swab
It'll be stuffed into the nose
It'll then disappear altogether
(Original Magic - Cotton swab disappears in the nose)
It won't disappear you know
Do it
It's long you know
Just do it
I can't do it
It doesn't matter
Nono, Impossible impossible
YOU CAN DO IT!!
i can do it
I don't know how to do this
Please look here
EHAHgrhh~ ENDOU-SAN
ENDOU-SAN
Stop saying Endou-san will you
This is absolutely impossible to withstand
Now, this time you'll do it
A hot boiled egg will be placed in the mouth and then disappear
(Original Magic 2 - Boiling egg disappears in the mouth)
I can't do this
It's really hot!
It'll disappear in your mouth
I can't do it
I can't do it..
YOU CAN DO IT IDIOT
WHY DO YOU JUST ASSUME YOU CAN'T?!
i can do it
Here I go!
*cough cough*
Why you...!
Throats are supposed to be narrow right?!
Throats are narrow?
What're you doing?
Because your throat is narrow
I thought expanding it would be good
What the hell
There's no magic here at all!
Are you idiots?!
What are you trying to do?
If you're gonna die from doing magic, then this is enough
Stop... OK?
Pull your act together will you
Guys, fix those faces
We didn't come to Japan for the sake of this
We came from China, just the two of us
hoping to become stars
We wanted to show the people back home...
our radiant appearance
Remember?
The song that was on the radio when we left China?
Long-winded!
Stop whining and shut up!
Oi, let's go!
What're you doing!?
These guys are extreme!
Ah.. It's amazing..
Can we just hurry to the news company?
(Just 15 minutes into work, there is already a "punishment" rush)
(But there's still a long way before reaching the news company)
(They're wary of the senior high student in front of them)
Hello
(Violation of manners - Having a conversation in a vehicle)
Eh? What? Are you an idiot?
Really? That's weird of you
Oi oi
That's awful of you - on the phone in a bus!
(From the back, a middle-aged salaryman appears)
(Oowada Shin'ya)
You're bothering everyone can't you see
Hand it over
Hold on, what're you doing?
When you're in the bus,
you shouldn't use your mobile, it's common knowledge
(Oowada's preaching begins)
You know don't you?
Are you in junior or senior high?
- Senior high   - Senior high?
Which year?
Senior 1st year
Well, that means your exams are soon right?
Ehh?!
If you can, try to understand alright?
(Bus-stop arrival)
If you understand then respond!
Yes.
Oh Akira!
Takeshi!
Somehow I've been caught up with some weird geezer
Oi, old man!
What business you got wit Akira?
(Oowada in a pinch!!)
I'm just trying to educate him about not using the mobile in the bus
Who here saw a phone bein' used?
Nobody oi!
In a train, a mobile...
It's a bus yes?
Stop beating around the bush oi!
Can't we discuss about this huh
Geezer, alight at the next stop
I can't, I'm going to work
(Bus-stop arrival)
- Get off!       - What is this!
Alright! Tell you what.
So you wanna have a go at it huh?
Then...
...Follow me!
(Oowada escapes!!)
His leg went limp!
It did! It did!
His leg went limp didn't it?
It must really hurt
His leg went limp c'mon!
I guess it wouldn't just end with that
His leg went limp..
That was an amazing combination
Yea
I didn't even know he was sitting there
Was he there since the beginning?
I guess so
This is really taxing
Oh. Something's there
(Bus-stop arrival)
More people coming on board?
You're kidding!
(Foreigner with baggage boards)
(Ishikura Saburou in bag)
Sorry.. I'm really sorry
Really. Sorry
This is messed up!
This is really scary!
What's the purpose of this?
He's always staring at me or Matsumoto
(Ishikura left on the floor)
What're you gonna do about this?
(Bus-stop arrival)
His face turned sour when it met his feet!
Woah! He's still looking
He's still looking!
Woah scary!
Like an occult
Why did you have to go look a second time?
Let's go already
Yea
Are we reaching?
Yea just a little more
That's what you've always been saying!!
Could you not speak with such Tsukkomi-like timing?
The art of timing Tsukkomi lines..
is what makes it funny
That's true
Everyone look
This is the company you'll be going to
Wow~
(Ga- Su- Kurobikari News)
Woah.. extravagant
this news company
This place is huge
Alright everyone it's time
(Arrived at news company)
Shall we?
(Company entrance)
Guys can you see this?
This youngster here is
Ga- Su Kurobikari News Company's
founder, Suga Kenji
(News Company founder - Suga Kenji "youth")
Cute huh?
Because of this youngster's...
...passion for journalism...
This company, from his passion
This comp...
This news comp... huhu... company has come to exist
What do you think?
How many times do you need to repeat yourself
Their brandishing hurts
(Entrance - Lobby)
Our company is also active in cultural exchanges globally
We received this during a partnership agreement
with a Chinese news company - a stuffed panda.
It's name is Mun Mun
Ah... It's Nun Nun
Wait, Hamada-san laughed too!
Just now at the front gate, Hamada did laugh though
Read properly, it's Nun Nun
It'd be bad if they really did kill it
(This is not a real stuffed animal)
Hamada-san laughed
This is a pretty messed up company
This is a picture taken from that time
("I'm really black" Shiny News Company Friendship Remembrance Signing Day)
(The founder then - Suga Kenji)
(20 years ago - then 33 years old)
Ok alright sorry we're done
Please no more Suga-san
20 years ago, during the partnership
agreement signing,
partnership agreem...
the agreement meeting for the partnership...
He kept repeating "agreement"
Well then, let me introduce you to the receptionist
Yes. Suga-san - Clear.
Huh? The reception lady isn't here.
(Reception area)
(The reception lady comes to work on a bike)
Whew! Made it just in time again today
(Receptionist - Katahira Nagisa)
This development is too unpredictable!
Fujiwara-san, good morning
These gentlemen are?
From today, they'll be under training to become reporters
Ahh.. so that's how it is
The truth is I did think you looked inexperienced
You.
Your name is?
I'm called Hamada
Hamada-san? And your given name is?
Ah. Masatoshi.
Ah... by the way, your father's name is...
It's Kengorou..
Eh? Kengorou?!
What's up with that sound effect
This one's dangerous, really dangerous
Suspense-zone?
Let's see...
You. What's your name?
It's Yamazaki
Yamazaki-san, have you settled down yet?
I see...
So, when you get home,
a meal prepared by your wife should be waiting for you right?
Yes.
What's the best dish from the Yamazaki household?
I guess that would be our Pork Cutlet
PORK CUTLET!?
Shit! Anything you say can be used
There're still some of you I've yet to know...
This gentleman here, your name is?
I'm called Endou
Um.. During your school years, what was your best subject?
Sports. I liked baseball very much
Then shall we have a little test?
Can you recite the alphabets for me?
You're terrible!
Anyway, please do your best for this first day
It really hurts..
It's really amazing this time round huh...
I don't get it.. I should know the 26 alphabets
"I should know the 26 alphabets" he says
(Coincidental Office Lady - Maeda Bibari)
It's "one incident, one laugh" for me
Ah. Hello.
Maeda Bibari speaking
Eh? 6:4?!
Well.. I...
...thought it was 8:2 you see...
(A confirmed blunder in the insurance company's ratio)
That was harsh.
Let's get off
100%
I was laughing 100% of the time
Ah here they come
This way
I can't endure this at all
Over here is the editorial office
(Editorial office)
Sports Department. Entertainment. Politics. Many various departments are here
Huge
Over there we have the 'captain' of the editorial board
A very competent person, so I'll introduce you
He's giving out an intense aura
The aura is radiating
Over here
Captain, I've brought the five trainees that'll join us
Ooh.. they're here?
(Editorial Board Captain - Takada Junji)
He's on the verge of laughter himself!
Ehh.. I am...
the editorial board's captain, Rhinoceros Beetle.
I can't control myself..
So you guys are the newbie reporters
Oo I have quite a few questions
This joke is going too far!
First off, you.
The taste of shit from shit and the taste of curry from curry
Which do you prefer?
The taste of curry from curry...
Oh the taste of curry from curry?
Pretty ordinary huh~
You.
Large-spirited and...
Small asshole...Which do you prefer?
Large-spirited I gue...
So you like large ones huh~
Captain!
That's me!
How about this news story? Please advice
What noise was that?
Oh.. That person...
That was unexpected huh...
Captain!
It's almost time for the meeting
All reporters, please work hard
Ai~ So the meeting's over here?
What the hell, that was irritating
Let's go. This way.
That captain's bottom half was something wasn't it
No it wasn't
This way
Damn, I've been laughing a hell lot
(Newcomers Training Room)
This here are the trainee reporter desks
At last!
At long last! Finally
So guys, sit at your desks
Just to get here, we had to go through many terrible things
It was long
Its gonna be a long day today
Ahh... this is tiring
"Maeda Bibari speaking" she said
Those kinds of things should be said only once
There's no need to repeat it
In my opinion, Endou has been laughing at everything
Yea
Laughing Endou
Hold on, I have a "laughing" face
No you don't
You're laughing right now too
Yamazaki and I are relatively more disciplined right
That's not true!
No but umm
When Fujiwara-san made a mistake back there about the panda's name?
You laughed at that didn't you?
Noo~pe
Didn't you laugh and get away with it?
Stop being so rough!
You should stop destroying yourself
Yea you should stop it
Do you think there's anything planted in our desks?
(Everyone's cautious about what's in their desk drawers)
If I'm not wrong there should be
(CO2 gas from the drawer)
I didn't think there'd be an accident!
Eh? it's this kind of system?
EhHhH~
You're kidding!
I thought I was gonna die.. really..
I was really frightened
That really scared the hell outta me!
Wah.. Now its scary to open them
This is the first time in my life
to really slip and fall off a chair
That was inevitable
Matsumoto-san couldn't have seen anything, except for pure-white
Ah. I remember, somehow really
It was instant right?
Yea, in that instant, I was thinking -
"An accident! An accident is happening!"... Somehow
This conversation is long huh
Well I understand
It can't be helped, if the cause of it is like that
Yea, you regret opening it
If it's your own, open it yourself
Endou, open yours
(Taking turns to open the drawers)
Woah this is really scary!
Here I go
Open it normally
Empty
I see, so this means there won't be anything
There's nothing
Empty
Why did you have to pull it so hard?
Why did you have to pull it so hard just now?
We would've been happier if you did it gently
Here I go
WAAAHHH
Empty
I'm sorry
Tanaka you're noisy
Tanaka!
Tanaka being scared like this isn't a good thing
It'll be better if you do it fast
NgAaaaah
Sports Newspaper
What the hell!
Why was I the very the first one to open this drawer this time round?
It's as if everything the staff planned will happen
You got that right
There're signs that this third table was tampered with
Matsumoto-san, please open the drawers
Well why don't you stick that up my ass
(I'm very unsure about this)
Why don't you....
...stick that up my ass
That's harsh isn't it?
It's been a long time since things are happening to my pace
There should be something, everyone else doesn't have it
I think we should deal with what's already at hand first
Woah, you're gonna open them all?
There it is!
(Suspicious button found!!)
Not this again!
Because you had to open it, Yamazaki-san
But I had to
Isn't it abit too early for us to have found this?
Well if we don't press it everything will be fine no?
There's no need to push it on purpose
That's true
It's found from Yamazaki's desk anyway
But I'm afraid I'd anger someone if I have to press it
What's there to get angry about?
Who'd get angry?
Someone will
(1 hour passed)
(It is still undecided on what to do with the dubious button)
Hey, there's a clock here this time
(First clock in the Batsu Series)
Yea because of it, you can actually feel time moving
I was surprised too
I'm sorry for this, it seems I have no choice
Eh? Now?
Eh for real?
But I really have no choice
It's alright if you press it though
Since it's from your place
But if I laugh or something because of that
By some big explosion, I'm gonna get really pissed
Please don't say that
It's really ridiculous
that it's gonna 'hurt pretty bad'
Here, look at the face he's making
You're breaking the rules there
Then shall I press it
Well if you feel like it
(Roulette START!)
You're kidding me!
This button is dangerous!
Nobody could have expected this
It's like a manga
Amazing
This is a really impressive system huh
Alright now there's no reason to push the button
Yea you're right
I was in a dangerous position too
Hold on, when is it gonna close?
I won't be able to tell the time like this
That incident wasn't funny at all right?
Yea
There's nothing in this one
Matsumoto-san, could you open your drawers?
Nothing
So if I open this one, it's considered that my area's cleared right?
Ah, thankfully nothing
Alright! With this I've done my part
Me too
Shall we?
Yea, just do it at your own pace
Ah it's ok
Something's inside
Waaahh..
(This time a yellow button appears)
Ah "Endou" is in yellow, and the button's also yellow
But Yamazaki's button is blue!
No when I pushed the button, the blue "Hamada" got an out
But there wasn't a red button for Matsumoto-san
But it wasn't in Matsumoto's desk
(Red button appears)
So this is Matsumoto's button
Nothing inside
Nothing inside?
So what does this mean?
I think there's no relation what-so-ever
Wait look here
Pressing the red could be Matsumoto-san or it could mean something else altogether
Let's be certain
(Sweets fall from the ceiling)
Wait a minute
So the outcome was sweets huh
Should we try the yellow button?
What's up with this...
What an amazing device
Is this a reward? Sweets?
I don't get it
What's up with the sound it made when it came out
Like a "Buu"
He's laughing, he's laughing
That wasn't necessary!
I think an absolutely different thing will happen for Endou's
Yea maybe. I'm gonna do it OK?
Here I go
(Roulette START!)
Matsumoto was laughing
So what's the meaning of all this?
This means...
When Endou pushes the yellow button, thinking
"It's Endou, it's Endou"
it turned out to be Hamada-san
We've pushed them all, Hamada-san's was different
These two buttons yea?
This one was special(Red)
Then shall we press the red one again?
Shall I?
(Roulette START!)
What is this?
I don't really get what's going on here
It's better to put these away
I'm putting them here
(Switch on)
You pushed it
You pushed it just then
I saw it too
(A photo drops from the ceiling)
This(photo) came out?
I didn't see it at all
(Yonesuke 22years old)
You...
I haven't a clue who that is
Who is that?
Yonesuke-san
When he was young
A good-looking chap huh
How come?
Ouch
Enough of this too
Put it away
Pretty merciless huh
Man... the worst has yet to come
It was pretty tough in the bus
Matsuko Deluxe yea?
And it wasn't just the pressure she gives alone
She was huge huh
Huuuge
Takada-san
Yamazaki-san also feels that it was a well-suited role right?
Yea
Everyone should work hard too, to achieve that standard
Work for dear life, body and soul
to achieve that standard
His legs went limp when he got off the bus
That Oowada-san
It wasn't an act right?
I was really surprised!
There's still more to come from here on
(Matsumoto-san,
-Cue Card)
please present the next video segment
Can't you stop this?
Nobody is looking forward to it
See, it was a bad response
This time there was a photo inside huh
It all started from this (CO2 gas)
I agree...
(Sudden outburst - Matsumoto)
This was something
I laughed because I remembered
This time it really hurts
Umm, can I have a little of your time
Uh... I forgot everyone...
Aah... I forgot to tell everyone something
There's a smoking area over there
Shall we have a look
Also, the scenery is beautiful
(Smoking area)
(Oowada, who got hunted down by the juveniles)
Oh, really pretty
(The members are oblivious to the existence of Oowada)
There's a Japanese martial arts hall!
(Discovery of Oowada)
Seconds
Dangerous dangerous dangerous
Man... I'm falling I'm falling!
Of all places to do this!
Careful careful careful
Shit! It's dangerous!
I'll fall getting it from here!
Ah! OW!
So he was caught after that incident huh
As I thought, he really did sprain his leg
He's dragging his feet
He's dragging them because of the strain
Yea doing it here's dangerous
We survived that huh, we could take it
This is frustrating~
Hamada, wanna go for a smoke?
This is tiring me out
Until now, there has been no form of release for the members
With this, a sigh of relief
It's peaceful here eh?
This time
I think it's strange that my ass doesn't hurt that much
Instead my thighs, for one
Did they miss?
Sorry?
They did
Aaahn?
They missed totally, they got my thighs, or my back
Careful careful
Yea I'm going I'm going
Again, Hamada-san with his "AaaHn?"..
Couldn't catch what I said?
No, it wasn't that I couldn't understand
(Sudden crashing noise)
Guys, bad news!
There was a loud noise coming from the rooftop
Like a huge roar, shall we go see?
(A scoop on the roof? What in the world...)
(UFO crash on the rooftop)
This is certainly amazing
(UFO Open!)
An alien is coming out!
(Alien? - Itao Itsuji)
Excuse me, are you an alien?
Haar?
The hell are ya sayin' huh!?
His ears are super evolved
But because you came out from a UFO...
I can't hear you at all
But you came out from a UFO didn't you?
Yea so I did
You saw me come out so why da hell ya asking
"You came out didn't you?"
Sorry, could we have a look at your teeth?
Why do you need to look at my teeth?
Well they're sharp aren't they?
It doesn't matter, particularly if they're sharp or not
Wait, isn't it difficult for you to talk?
His face doesn't look right too huh?
Are you really not an alien?
FAR FROM IT!
There it is! Over there!
(Entrance of Earth Defense Corps)
Is everyone ok?
Nobody hurt?
That was without a doubt, a human possessed by an alien
As I thought, it really was an alien
Let's go shall we
This is a first
The crows are crying
Why I wonder
In symphony
"Course"
There was a Japanese martial arts hall right?
Did you say "course"?
I was thinking about the crows' "course"
Because crows have a "course"
No they don't
Isn't "course" used for airplanes?
No, there were many reasons why I laughed
Hamada-san kept looking at me
Who's this guy!?
Full of energy huh
The guy's young
He joined NSC around last year or the year before
If he went to Volks(steak-house), he'd always be eating instead
So far, Yamazaki's in the lead yea? (Number of Outs)
To get whooped? That may be the case
From the start, it was "straight"
I faltered at every single joke, how do I describe that?
"Straight" right?
Ah, It's "perfect"
Isn't making funny faces prohibited?
Isn't humor(amongst ourselves) prohibited?
Yama-chan, that was cheap just then
It was cheap and not just then
So why should funny faces be prohibited?
I have two evil reasons for that
People who are smiling, can trap others unknowingly, and 1 more reason
Accordingly, if you keep making funny faces
When you smile, it's as if you were trying to deceive
These double evils, are for me, latent
At... at least that's what I think
You should have said so directly
Absolutely no response yea?
If you're gonna lecture Yama-chan, then you shouldn't do it yourself
That's how I am when I'm in pain
When in pain, people can't make the correct decisions
But you just...
This is in fairness
Everytime, as always, there's no reason to strike at each other right?
My motivation now, is to get through this and say, "Aah... It's done"
But this is just my personal opinion
It's just an individual's opinion
In our newspapers
There's a popular corner for dinner recipes
Incidentally, the chef is in the vicinity
Let's go collect some data on the recipes
(Cooking Studio)
Sit accordingly - Tanaka, Endou, Hamada, Matsumoto, Yamazaki
First seat at the end - Tanaka
So then, sensei, if you would please..
Ehm, Gwood day~
(Culinary Lecturer - Sekine Tsutomu as Wajima Kouichi)
(Wajima Kouichi was a former boxing world champion known for his peculiar 'frog jump' uppercut)
For real?
Riiiight, that was a good punch but off a little eh?
I, Wajima,
Yes~, will be preparing the dish for today
Recipes yes?
Jot this down eh?
Why do you need to take this down?
???
Right, this is my assistant, Megumi-chan
She's the traditional round-girl with
? ? ?
Eh?
Just listening to him is hard
You can't tell what he's trying to say right?
Sensei, what were you trying to say just then? 'Round-girl'...
Sorry eh.. I'll stop
Sensei, so what are we preparing this time?
This time, it's a man's dish yea
(Today's Menu - Pork and Tomato flavored stew)
Right, here's the frying pan
(Spread oil over frying pan)
Putting the oil is dangerous eh?
When the oil splashes, you gotta defend yourself
You gotta defend yourself
???
(Tenderize the pork)
Right, hold this for me
You gotta snap, snap!
You can't do it slow
If you do that, it'll be like...
This cooking lecture...
Could you please talk about the cooking itself?
This here...
You can't pull your punches yea?
Will you please stop it
This IS cooking right?
You can stop now, I get it already
The pork's tenderized already
(Place the lid, so that it cooks well)
Oh, the gong(bell) has gone
It's done like this right?
You have to do it standing no?
This is how I thought up of the frog jump uppercut
I'll first make the opponent think I've disappeared
See, he can't get to me right?
Not even here
So what now? I jump up and "Biing~"
Ahh, thank you very much
(Wajima Kouichi dinner recipe complete)
How many blows was that?
We were being force-fed
Itadakimasu
This is bad, my ass seriously hurts
Seriously?
The watchman...
...are not paying attention at all
(Sudden judgment on the programme)
It's because of what you said
Eh?! For real?
You shouldn't have done that you know
It was an act of rebellion that's why
Wait, someone try saying something
I don't think so...
Can we stop this?
And I was enjoying my meal...
I've already been hit
You gotta stop it!
This chair isn't stable to begin with!
Well I wasn't the one who knocked it over
It was dangerous you know
Even that kind of expression counts?!
It's cuz you keep saying awful things
You've made the watchman angry
You brought this on yourself
This chair is really scary
Wasn't it really dangerous?
He almost knocked the back of his head
Please just let me have my meal. Please let me have my meal
This guy's totally laughing!!
Hamada-san's laughing!
Uwaah... It's just the crows crying..
Oh he's laughing
Yes he just did
Can you guys not do that? You were mistaken about earlier
Hamada-san, you started it first
No that's not it!
Doesn't it feel good doing that?
Les' juz eat properly
"Les' juz eat" he says
I think the watchman is kinda offended
Isn't the tempura a little bad? Sometimes
Right?
Man, do you only know how to complain?
That was the worst
??
If even this is also a "Matsumoto OUT"
How do you expect me to escape huh?
Somewhat, I,
Naa!
Right, listen here
Noone...
.... can be bothered about this and just continues eating
"Playing it safe at any cost"... Kinda right, kinda wrong
Ahh it hurts it hurts it hurts
This time round, finally you get to see Hamada go "Ah, it hurts it hurts"
No matter how painful it is, I never utter a word
But probably...
In the end it doesn't matter
Sort of a cause for anxiety isn't it
(Looking for something in Hamada's desk)
(Yonesuke 22years old)
(Placed atop the seat cushion - standby)
Who did this?
Wasn't it supposed to be left here?
(Hamada goes to the smoking area)
(Placed atop the seat cushion - standby)
(Yonesuke 22years old)
(Placed under the seat cushion - standby)
There's a press release at another location
Let's go collect some data
He didn't even say whose press release it is huh
We'll be going by car. The car up front - Hamada, Matsumoto
Behind - Endou, Tanaka, Yamazaki
We're in the middle of a war eh
Eh!?
I'm in the middle?
You should be in the middle
Sorry
Why do I have to sit where the bulge is? It's not right ya know
This guy's laughing
You keep pushing and hogging space eh
Why are YOU pushing and hogging space!?
WHAT THE HELL
You're taking up all the space!
What the hell is this....
Oh it's taking place here huh
(Huge numbers of press members packed together - attention levels are high)
(Staged press release public interview)
Over here
(Press release - Hall)
This place is huge huh
Taking time off your busy schedules to come here,
Everyone, really, thank you very much
Putting that aside, the great national theater will present to you this play,
in celebration of its 25th anniversary.
The theme for the play is this -
Stage Version - Star Wars: The Empire Strikes Back
They had to do a Star Wars play...
Now, let me introduce the main cast of this version of Star Wars
Playing as Luke Skywalker -
(Kawasaki Mayo)
Playing as Princess Leia, her debut performance on a stage
(Umemiya Claudia)
(Umemiya Claudia is the mother of Umemiya Anna, a model)
Playing the evil ruler, Darth Vader
(Satou Gajirou)
And lastly, specially featuring..
Playing two roles, as C3PO & R2D2
is this gentleman
(Meguro Yuuki)
MEGURO YUUKI
Wasn't the speed of which he came out just strange?
So, members of the press, please feel free to ask any questions
(Question & Answer Session)
I have a question for Claudia-san
Where is the one place that you would like to visit the most?
Because I have alot to say...
I'll try to bring across my message properly
My heart is racing
Ah, it's ok, I'll help you in every way I can
Ah.. I wonder if doing so might anger Umemiya-san
Thank you very much
That is all for the question & answer session
Still to come,
we would like you to watch a special segment from the play
Please kindly wait
They unveiled something really shameless eh
He's really close
Five minutes later
Ten minutes later
Eh wait this guy here's sorta laughing also
Ah, he's going back
That sort of gag is just terrible
A long time ago, in a galaxy far away
Under the reign of the dictator, Darth Vader,
Princess Leia has been held captive
At that time, Luke...
? I am Luke Skywalker ?
? Protector of peace in space ?
Master Luke!
What's wrong? C3PO?
I've learned the whereabouts of Princess Leia
Let's save her at once
Let's go C3PO!
Wait for me Master Luke!
They're kidding right....
Meanwhile...
Princess Leia is being held captive by Darth Vader
Everything is going according to plan
Release me. Release me.
Absolutely no emotions at all
(Reading from script)
I knew it, this was all your doing
I... Aldar...
She's just reading
Planet Alderaan's Princess Leia, descendant of Breha Organa
This is a war
A galactic war
In other words, star wars.
Luke Skywalker, C3PO & R2D2
will surely come to save me
And then, by the hands of Luke Skywalker, C3PO & R2D2
I will be saved
Because Luke Skywalker, C3PO & R2D2
are my best partners
Miss Leia
With that, are ya done?
That's in Osaka dialect
Take her inside!
Save me Luke Skywalker, C3PO & R2D2
That was awful..
It's supposed to be their 25th anniversary right?
Meanwhile..
An intense mid-air battle unfolds
as Luke and R2D2 linked up to fight enemy forces
What is this
Man.. What the hell is this
Let me go, you rude people
Eh you're pretty noisy aren't you
Wait!
You're finally here, Luke
Let's battle with our sabers
What an awful play
They're actually using toys for this
Look at Claudia, look at Claudia
She's just plain standing there
And so begun their grand struggle
And then manifested Luke's master, Yoda, who then pulverized Darth Vader
Thank you Luke
Where has C3PO & R2D2
gone to I wonder
You're right! Where could they have gone to?
Where I wonder
Where exactly, they were around earlier
(Finally, R2D2 enters the scene)
R2D2, are you alright?
EH? Weren't you with C3PO earlier?
pipopa i don't know pipopapipo
Let's just leave C3PO be
Oh what the heck
? I was born for the sake of protecting the galaxy's peace ?
My stomach hurts my stomach hurts my stomach hurts
It's gonna be a big hit, no doubt about it
Awful
All of them were just awful
(Level 4 Lobby)
(Matsumoto goes to the toilet by himself)
Ouch!
(Collision with a boy holding soft cream)
Are you ok?
Ryo-kun~
MAMA!
What happened?
A boy was running,
then he bumped into me and got soft cream on me
His name was Ryo-kun right?
For a moment I thought
his father would appear
That father is Chouno-san, the guy who slaps your face
Wait a minute
Yamazaki, if you wish
You can go to the dressing room to get a change of clothes,
since yours are dirty
Why are these here?
This time it's gonna be really harsh
The buttons huh
Yama-chan is getting changed now right
(Dressing room)
While Yamazaki is changing
the respective members spend their time freely
(Smoking area)
And Matsumoto is lonely all by himself
Those buttons are detestable
Is Yama-chan done changing?
May I?
You should just come out if you're done
You're a newspaper reporter right?
You shouldn't say things like "You're a newspaper reporter right?"
Nobody asked you to wear something like this
It's like you're just trying to make us laugh
I'm not trying to be funny here,
I'm not trying to be funny here, I'm really gonna catch a cold
Then I guess it can't be helped
Do you mind...?
What do you mean by "Do you mind?"
I don't know
Oh no.. This big guy
I have no idea what you're trying to say Yama-chan
There's no specific meaning to it
Do you mind.. This?
Do you mind...?
Do you mind...? For real..
What the hell...
Why are you so persistent?
What's the meaning of all this?
Just stop it
What do you want? Can you just say it?
Yea
You want me to hold it?
Heavy
Then you could've just said so in the first place
But you have to feel it for yourself to know
But if you just said so in the first place...
It's not something you'd expect you know
No need for this, it's heavy I know
Just a little, feel it for yourself
The weight isn't something you'd expect right?
There's reason to be seriously alarmed by this yea?
Heavy..
??
I'll drink something hot
The buttons
I'm gonna press it
Seriously?
Why am I the only one who's ok with it?
(Roulette START!!)
Wait! Wait! This will hurt!
This definitely hurts!
Ah pain..
Kintaro-han, are you for real?
You'll be fine!
This is awful
But I'm just wearing a rag
The hit is direct on my ass
Eh? Guys, come here and have a look
Eh? Is it bad?
Nono, this underwear...
He didn't actually choose to wear this himself right?
Why are you wearing that kind of underwear?
C'mon please spare us!
Why are you wearing a T-back!? (G-string)
Why are you wearing a T-back?
All of a sudden...
So why are you wearing a T-back?
...Why not?...
What if I've always been wearing them?
You're kidding!
What's wrong with you!?
See!
That's bad, really
It's bad, it's turned pink
This is definitely no laughing matter
I'm gonna get chewed out for this...
Who?
That was Tanaka!
Who's gonna scold you?
Yama-chan, was this whooping as terrible as yours?
Mine was worse
Who's gonna get angry at you? Just curious
If...
Blood or something gets out..
And stains the underwear, I'm gonna get scolded
Who's going to?
Everyone...
Everyone?....
Zaki-san, just be more careful
Shall we try the blue button?
Waitwaitwaitwaitwait
You wanna press it?
This one's done, I'll put it away
Yea that one's taken care of
Ah, Endou should push it
Here I go
(Itao Itsuji's license)
This did it! This button sure did it!
That was pretty awful yea?
This is the worst...
It's cold you know
You're gonna catch a cold
Maybe we could make a hot bath?
Nonono... I don't want that
??
I wonder if there's a dropper
Wait.. Hamada-san
Really.. really.. I..
I think Yamazaki is probably thinking..
that Hamada is up to no good
Yes that's right, it's written all over his face
Wait wait wait.. no no no please
Yama-chan, that movement of yours is disturbing
Nono, you're mistaken, I'm just getting a drink
??
Ah there it is
Nonono, please wait a moment
This is crazy isn't it?
Wait guys, please just calm down
This is really ridiculous
Why??
You're mistaken, we were just thinking of
putting the stove sideways so it'd warm the place up
Ohh I see
I'm sorry
You.. don't need this do you? You only need one cup right?
What's up with you?
Please stop..
Oh no...
I can't trust anyone anymore
You're gonna drop the stove on my head aren't you?
What's the point of dropping the stove on your head?
Yama-chan are you cold?
No I'm not
I'm fine
It's not a bad substitute for a pocket warmer
Nah, I'm absolutely fine
Endou, the tea-bag(T-bakku) over there...
Isn't the T-back with you?
It's tea-pack(teii-pakku)
(Stove)
I hate this
Attending a party celebrating the establishment of a new office
Why is it like this?
Why do you always naturally end up getting in first?
Because I got here earlier
And you were behind...
...taking your own sweet time weren't you
That's sadly true
(Party Hall)
Ladies and gentlemen, for taking time off your busy schedules
to attend this event, I honestly thank you
Now, an entertainment production, "Field of Butterfly",
Let the party begin
Firstly, let's get this started with a ceremonial sake barrel breaking
You should remember this man, when celebrating the establishment of new offices
may we invite on stage, the barrel breaking expert!
(Barrel breaking expert enters)
(Egashira 2:50)
(the expert who's not breaking the barrel)
It's my honor to split open the barrel
How's he gonna do it?
(Breaking the barrel by head-butting)
Allow me, to split open the barrel
But you already did...
It's already open!
Oh no oh no oh no oh no!
Th...thank you very much
Let's move on
(Debut of a member of the company)
Presenting this gentleman, with his comical 'BIG 3' on stage!
(Koji Tomita as Tamori)
In this world, there're many people with different bad habits right?
For example, Tunnels' Ishibashi-kun...
When he's trying hard to read off a message during filming
(Trying hard to read off a message - Ishibashi Takaaki)
Ooh this is good, extremely good
Thank you very much
This here is...
Yokohama's...
???
Speaking of which, Bandou-san's Kansai dialect's intonation...
...is kinda wrong right?
(Weird intonation - Bandou Eiji)
Next we have this year's runner-ups for "King of skits"
Presenting, Banana-man
(Fukki as Shitara Osamu)
Ah this is my partner, Himura
(Nobu as Himura Yuuki)
Looks like the real thing!
They were too similar. I mean I've watched them perform before
Ladies & gentlemen, thank you for waiting
This cute, 'elder sister' character who captivated many in no time at all
Getting her huge break from this year's Air Ayaya(Matsuura Aya)
Please get to know her, presenting..
(Nakamura P as Haruna Ai)
The clothes are awful
I've had enough of laughing
He(Nakamura P) sure practiced hard for this
Next, let's invite our next performer
More!?
Scouted from Europe,
Presenting, this street dancer...
(Morisanchuu's Kurosawa Kazuko)
What's up with that body!?
That's some body..
(Longevity)
That's the nastiest
Go die!
You're the worst!
It's to the extent that I would've rather laughed
Moving on,
The Field of Butterfly president's address
(President's address)
(Chouno Masahiro is a professional wrestler)
(Chouno Masahiro)
OI!
The two officials over there, come up here!
Why was today's performances so weak?
Is that kind of standard OK for you?
Who was the one who gave you the instructions?
(Punished by a slap in the face)
The truth is that, there is an announcement for everyone here
President Chouno's most treasured notebook has gone missing
(What crossed Yamazaki's mind - "Where has he seen this similar turn of events")
Have some spirit!
(No Laughing in Hospital)
(Recollection of exactly one year ago)
Dr. Chouno's most treasured handkerchief has been stolen
It's design is something like this
Everyone here please check your pockets
(Culprit found!)
("Chouno's Slap" punching punishment)
(Is Yamazaki the leading actor for this tragedy once again?)
President Chouno's most treasured notebook has gone missing
(President Chouno's notebook stolen!!)
The stolen notebook looks identical to the one I'm holding
The culprit should be here in this room
(Escaped after much difficulty - Yamazaki)
This isn't true right?
(Culprit found!!)
Hurry on up here!
Thank God~
A journalist from where?
Which company are you from?
Ga-Su- Kurobikari News...
I didn't steal the notebook you know
Did you look at what's inside?
Are you trying to use that to blackmail me?
Well I've only been using it to collect data
Field...
...of House
Field of Butterfly...
I've had enough
Stand over here
(Culprit gets punished by a slap in the face!!)
But I'm really scared
It's fine just stand there
Here I go
President!
Bad news!
(President's secretary appears)
Ryo-chan suffered serious injuries!? What the hell happened!
Ryo-chan? Ah! AH! AH!
The kid with the soft cream!
(The kid with the soft cream appears)
Do you remember how this person looks like?
Yea
The guy might be in here for all we know
Ryo-chan, see if you can find him here
(Search for the culprit!)
Changing the look on your face might save you
It's him Papa!
(Culprit found!!)
Oi! Get up here!
(Culprit gets punished by a slap in the face!!)
Are you trying to oppose me!?
Please wait
Please Wait
Chouno-san..
I am truly very scared already
I'm really very scared
But you were the one who bumped into the kid earlier
How the hell did you knock into my kid for him to sustain such injuries!?
Wait wait! WAIT WAIT REALLY PLEASE
Your son....
He fell....
So I asked him if he was alright
Why didn't you help him!?
I DID!
How? Show me
I said "Are you ok?"...
Then I sympathized with him
Come up here!
Wait, I really don't want this...
But we weren't the ones who knocked into the kid...
Then you should have made me the lead right from the start...
Wouldn't it be better if I was holding the notebook instead!?
Are you trying to insult me!?
I'm sorry! Wait!
Is this the only way? Please say it isn't true
These are your circumstances
What do you mean?
If you can explain to me clearly, then...
OK I'll explain everything to you in detail
OK get started
I was walking normally
Then your child...
....came running and knocked into me
It's because you didn't give way that it happened
I DID give way
But even then, he came knocking into me
I was like, "Are you OK? Are you OK?"
Then how did my child sustain such injuries?
I have no idea
It seems you won't be persuaded huh....
Then let's do this oi!
What's up with you
What's wrong?
I'm scared....
Now you know how I feel don't you!!
You know I was really ecstatic when it turned out to be Tanaka
It can't be helped Zaki-san..
OK OK OK we'll do it we'll do it
OK we'll do it
Could you do it with a little bit of a warning..? A warning
What do you mean?
Well, that way, it won't hurt as much
But I haven't even moved yet..
Please, a little warning...
Wait wait
My ass feels weird...
I don't feel so good...
Save me Tanaka
I don't feel so good anymore
Alright, let's get this over with
Say, "I am a bad person."
Say, "I'm sorry, I've been a bad person!"
Forgive me!!
(Moment of execution)
Amazing huh!
Yea! Stars were flying!
I've never experienced a slap like this before!
Show's over! Get out of here!
Get the hell out!
All of you get out!!
Ah... I just got it...
Field of Butterfly...
is Chouno
Ah excuse me
Ah hello
(Unforseen visitor - Murakami Shoji)
Wah!!
I've been studying comedy inside a tiger's cave..
And I was picked up by the news
(Island)     .     (Roast pork)     .     (Everybody)
Kyushu   .   Charshu   .   Minnanoshu    Ha Ha
Can you stop going "Wahh"..
How did udon...
...gradually become popular
Udon is actually a product of China
How was udon discovered?
I'm sure everyone is familiar with Marco Polo
Though in Kanji, it's written as Wantan
(Or rather, it's Y Tun)
But in Chinese, it's read Undon
So after going through different dialects and accents..
it gradually became udon
So in Kanagawa Prefecture..
it appeared there, I don't know if you know this...
the truth is that, there was one time, Marco Polo...
...took it from China...
Then brought it back to Italy with him
Then presented it to the King
And he ate it
Uh.... uh...
Can you stop doing that with your hand?
Thank you very much
I knew it would go like that..
Guys
Now there's a wedding conference for a big celebrity.
Let's go collect data
Wow... one after another
Seriously?
News agencies sure are busy huh
It smells like winter huh
It doesn't matter, does it?
I'm just saying this...
Why? (being in the centre)
(On the way to a wedding conference in hired cars)
(Successive attacks from funny set-ups)
(Who could this big celebrity be?)
(The conference will turn into a comedic hell)
(A certain hotel, hall entrance)
Who is it?
This is the husband huh
Oh it's not a fellow big celebrity huh..
Ladies and gentlemen, we apologize for the delay
Please welcome the blessed wife onto stage
You're getting married?
(Chiaki is Endou's ex-wife, I believe they divorced in late 2007)
(Shocking wedding - Chiaki)
Is this for real!?
Thank you for having me
I'm Chiaki
PuU~
Now we have the Q&A segment. To the journalists here, please feel free to ask questions
Yes, that gentleman over there
Chiaki-san, what do you usually call your husband?
Ummm..
(Affectionate name which means something like "Big brother")
For my ex-husband, I called him "Onii"
For my current husband, it's "New Onii"
I feel like my ass is swelling
How did he propose to you?
For my ex-husband..
"I want to be with you even as you grow old"
For example, when it comes to death
To illustrate with soft cream...
"You would be pink strawberry cream..
and I would be chocolate cream,
so that when they mix,
they would also disappear together when they melt
similarly, if you die, I'll die with you."
...was what he said
For my current husband, it's the regular
"Would you marry me?"
This is amazing stuff, everything is exposed
Chiaki-san, what made you decide that he was the one for you?
Compared to my ex-husband,
he is absolutely unique
Sir, if you will, can you show us something interesting?
(New Onii showcasing something interesting)
I'm really receiving every blow eh?
So gentle... patting his cheeks..
Actually I've heard that..
..you husband is exceptional at impersonations
Chiaki-san, is this true?
Yes, that's right
His impersonation of Beat Takeshi is rather good
("Beat Takeshi" Takeshi Kitano is a prominent Japanese celebrity)
Wow, then let's have a look
(Impersonation of Beat Takeshi)
Endou, you bastard!
You were made to say that weren't you?
Chiaki-san, does he have anything else in stall for us?
His impersonation of Mori Shin'ichi-san is also excellent
(Mori Shin'ichi is an old Enka singer)
Mori Shin'ichi-san huh?
Then let's have a look
(Impersonation of Mori Shin'ichi)
..Mum..
That wasn't good at all!
What was he spouting?
He said 'mum'
(Mori Shin'ichi had a dispute with the late composer, Kohan Kawauchi, over the song "Ofukuro-san", or "Dear Mother", for changing the lyrics. It has since been settled)
It's supposed to be 'dear mother' right?
So next, to the journalists seated in the front row..
whose impersonation would you like to see?
Please make a request with the celebrity's name
So, could we have Yamazaki-san make a request?
Lessee.. how about Kobayashi Akira-san
(Impersonation of Kobayashi Akira)
(Kobayashi Akira is an actor)
Hey what're ya doing?
Ya better do it properly!
Who the hell is that!?
With this, the conference will come to a closing
Chiaki-san, do you have anything to add?
Onii! Please be happy!
PuU~
Please be happy too..
It's over right?
You know, i forgot about all that stuff
(Foreign Correspondents Club for Prime Minister, Japan)
(Prime Minister Oonishi)
(From the hairdo, I believe it's a parody of ex-Prime Minister Koizumi Jun'ichirou)
I'm Thomas Jarod from New York Times
Thank you for having me
Could you please tell us about the economic situation
There are many places...
whereby... uh.. money..
should not be taken from
Even if you have to..
You can't.. is what I think
What kind of places are you referring to?
Like loan companies...
..where money...
is borrowed from
Getting too engrossed to Jimmy-san is dangerous eh?
I'm Anna Kaiser from Frankfurt News
How much do you know about Germany's situation?
Germany?
I know about Germany
Beer...
Is there nothing from the political aspect?
Ah from the political viewpoint...
Frankfurt's policemen...
What was that?
Frankfurt police
Germany's policemen
What about it?
together...
we will form close relations
We will form close relations
I'm Anne Smith from Boston News
I've heard that the Prime Minister's English is excellent
Could you please sing us 'Twinkle twinkle little star' in English please?
(In Japanese)   ? Twinkle twinkle ?
? Twinkle twinkle ?
? Glitteryyy ?
That wasn't in English was it?
That 'glittery' part was weird
There's still more to come huh..
(12 hours have passed since)
(It's about time they've reached their limits)
(More assassins to come bare their fangs at the five)
I'm tired...
What's up with that slap?
It was as fast as a bear catching salmon
The wedding conference huh
That was surprising huh
I really do hope Chiaki-chan attains happiness.. those two..
(Matsumoto-san,
-Cue card)
please present the next video segment
- It's the last one      - Oh the last one?
Do a good one
That's enough please!
(this was what the guy with the guitar was singing before the Star Wars play, in case you forgot)
Pretty cold (lame) isn't it
(Going to the Wrestling Division to get data)
Here we go
(W Joyman)
Takaaki    Nakamura P
Exercise is important
"Band" is an English word
Nakamura is Yoshinobu
Ootake is Shinobu
It came out all of a sudden, SOrry~
Honestly SOwwy~
Bae Yongjun . Peruvian
(As you can see, they're mostly celebrity names)
Won Bin . Beer bottle
Yoshinobu . Pork shabu
Takagi Buu . Piggyback
Oda Mudou . Sewers
Ikkokudou . Gangsterism
Amura....
(Girls who imitate the style of Amuro Namie, singer)
Odagiri Joe . Abnormal
Shibasaki Kou . Tailing
Producer . Bulldozer
...
Don't tell me you can't remember your own stuff
THEY should be out!
This is our company's wrestling division
(Wrestling hall)
It's OK to step up here with your shoes on
(Company's outstanding champions!!)
(Kurobikari Wrestling Division)
("Secret extreme training" data collecting)
(Cloaked in secrecy)
They're about to finish practice, so they're coming here to meet you guys
What kinda data should we be collecting?
1, 2!
(Ga-su- Kurobikari News Company)
(Wrestling Division)
We will make critical wins
Achieve the results with much difficulty
Is that clear?
(Wrestling Division special training commence)
Alright everyone!
Now we'll have the stocking tire pull
There'll be a stocking attached to this tire
Which you'd also wear over your head
This is training for your neck
(Pulling a 40kg tire with just the strength of a stocking over the head)
Keep going forward
- OK?     -OK!
So who's gonna go?
Iwao!
(Iwao Nozomu)
(Dodge the balls and grab the flag)
It hit his face
His face must hurt
It must've really hurt just now
(Nukumizu Youichi)
This is terrible!
In the wrestling ring, balance is of utmost importance
So we're gonna train our balance
Bring it out!
(Coffee Balance)
(A cup of hot coffee will be placed on a certain part of the body, balance must be maintained)
Fujimoto!
(Fujimoto Toshifumi)
Where do you want it placed?
On my stomach please
Alright next!
Hiroaki!
(Ogi Hiroaki)
Wanna go for double?
Double?
Is that even possible?
There's no way this can be done right?
This is definitely impossible
Don't move!
His balance is bad!
Alright who wants to try this big cup?
Leader please do it
Please!
(Shoufukutei Shouhei)
It's shaky
The captain's balance is awful!
(The extreme heroics of the wrestling division)
(Time for sparring)
Alright next!
We have 1-on-1 sparring
(Haranishi Takayuki)
(Kosugi Ryuuichi)
Kill! Kill!
That was dirty
(Himura Yuuki)
(Yahagi Ken)
No! No! No!
There was no need to do that right?
There was really no need to do that right?
(Iwao Nozomu)
(Ogi Hiroaki)
That's good taking him from the back
That's right that's right!
Eh? What's going on?
This isn't right!
That was mortifying
In the end, it was nothing but his anus
He was totally nude huh?
Why are they going back as if they've accomplished something?
I would like to begin the "Regular Report" Meeting
(The journalists will exchange their inside stories/reports)
Firstly Yoshimoto Kogyo's talent,
(I apologize, I believe most of this segment is translated wrongly)
Yamazaki Housei... any stories on him?
Umm.. About that guy..
Something disastrous happened
He was staying over at an inn in the countryside
For a TV program
- Right, TV Tokyo.        -Ah, that's right.
So one morning...
I wanted to go meet him
But it's like Yamazaki just refused to.
So Yamazaki kept rejecting
One of the reasons he gave was
"He was sleeping at a stranger's place"
From one's knowledge you'd know he wasn't at a stranger's place and yet...
But then the next morning came..
"That's no reason to cry"
So then after, he did leave the place
For some time, I discussed the matter with the staff
You'd get disoriented due to the time-difference
The regular guests cried twice as much
That's mean
Every time I greet him my heart goes...
He supposedly causes miracles to happen doesn't he?
With Ameagari-san,
(Ameagari Kesshitai is a comedy duo)
they went for the written oracles (fortune-telling)
Miyasako-san got slightly good luck
Hotohara-san got moderate good luck
But Yamazaki-san got a blank piece of paper
So everyone was like, "Wow that's amazing!"
Then later with a friend, I messaged Yamazaki-san
to ask where he was
And later proceeded to the get written oracles too
I got slightly good luck
the friend got moderate good luck
When Yamazaki-san drew his lot...
there was no need for a second look
on it was written "Plain"
Recently, Yamazaki-san got into the iPod
There were various things you could do with it
Editing sceneries, photos or even music... it's all in
So he was showing some juniors his pictures
He was showing this photo to Kobayashi
So holding his iPod like so...
Caught in the nail of his pinky was a strand of pubic hair
Was that true?
Pubic hair huh...
Regarding the boom of his shophouse home
He wanted to turn it into...
A shop specializing in Yakisoba
-
He then hired a chinese guy from the mahjong club
He wanted to a start a store specializing in fried rice.
He wanted me to teach him how to headhunt for people
The guy likes to blow his nose alot doesn't he?
(Haven't the slightest what this joke is, sorry.)
He rips off from Koike Eikoe
Saying, "Chan is 'clip-clop'".
For real?
Are all these stories real you guys?
Any other news?
Something like scandals?
I just got this news though
Just recently at the wrestling club..
Shoufukutei Shouhei was there wasn't he?
I helped him with his costumes yes?
So when I did, I noticed his pubes were all white.
What kind of conversation is this?!
This is about Miyasko Hiroyuki during his lowest
He claimed "I'm as interesting as Downtown".
(This is Miyasako Hiroyuki)
And despite saying that....
Now even though he's actually earning quite a sum of money,
He admitted, "My honeymoon was on the sandy beaches of Wakayama".
There's nothing wrong with that really.
Furthermore, he went by express train.
But its suitable for working class people
But its suitable for working class people right?
This is about Downtown's Hamada Masatoshi
He doesn't just do comedy does he
There are dramas and movies too
Also as a voice actor yes?
Like in Shrek...
So he casted as Shrek, which was suitable with his Kansai dialect
And Fujiwara Norika...
Though was quite compatible, casting as his female companion,
and they've co-starred quite a number of times before.
I daresay that at least once...
He carried her in his arms
Who's earning from all this!?
-
Jinnai was worried about his physical condition
(This is Jinnai Tomonori)
It was said he had problems with his stomach, according to reports
In the dressing room, he was eating pastries
And all of a sudden, he vomited.
When asked "what's wrong?"
He said, "Oh no, I forgot I'm already full."
Why do I have to get my ass whooped from your lying!?
-
Some time back...
During that time, there was an event late in the night.
Everyone was sharing scary stories
Then all of sudden, Jinnai turned pale...
and broke into cold sweat.
saying, "It's cold, it's cold.."
As if he was in his final moments.
And then Tamura Keiji (another celebrity)...
when he saw this, he started hitting Jinnai's back
(looks like an exorcism ritual)
Jinnai was healed.
There are some reports associating Jinnai with Kobayashi Kendo right?
From my info, it's known that Kendo Kobayashi was quite the prankster.
(This is Kendo Kobayashi)
There were pranks done to Jinnai's glasses
???
So what happened was that the glasses were stir-fried in a fry pan
He said, "Don't just use the gas as you please!"
Normally you'd say, "What are you doing to my glasses!" and get angry
But he reacted to the gas being used instead huh
What about the rest?
This is from Mimata Matazou the celebrity
About Takeshi and Hitoshi, both of whom he's acquainted with
At Matsumoto Hitoshi's household,
The paparazzi was constantly snooping around.
This is something I heard from others who saw it.
As mentioned earlier, Matsumoto was having a meal with his other Yoshimoto colleagues
Then Matsumoto Hitoshi-san...
he went to Dyson the next day, with the intention of buying a vacuum cleaner
The person there said, "I have a Dyson cleaner that's been used only twice."
So Matsumoto said, "I'll take it".
From what I know, he then had it delivered to his Yoshimoto junior.
It was well-received.
"Thanks for the vacuum cleaner"
Text messages as well.
He even received calls like, "Thank you so much."
Then he was like, "What good manners he has, he must be a good person"
As was said earlier, what did the "twice" stand for?
-The times it was used
Right, just twice. Doesn't it concern you? What those 2 times were used for?
According to investigations..
it was used to suck the anus
But the person in question doesn't seem to know about it does he?
So you're saying he didn't know what it was being used for?
Right he just thought that the cleaner being used only twice was a good thing
Any more?
Last week there was a report on Matsumura Kunihiro..
(I believe it's masturbation)
about his ****** incident.
He fell in love with someone in the sports club
A 64 year old woman that he met
Every Monday and Friday
Twice a week, in the locker rooms, he'd ******.
(Someone asking Mimata Matazou...)
...asked him if he had any interesting stories to tell
Then he said, "I'm going out with Idol A's mother".
(This is Mimata Matazou)
That Mimata,
at 4am in Roppongi Sushi,
was having a lover's quarrel with Actress A
After thorough investigations
the 4th date he had was with someone new
Even though until now he still has prostitute's panties, I believe... (not sure about this)
Later it was found out there was a third party involved.
When **** introduced them to each other,
it turned out to be Yamashiro Shingo-san
(Yamashiro Shingo is an old actor. Around 70 years of age.)
This is the best story
So shall we go with this?
Big actress A introduces Yamashiro Shingo to him
Morning paper headlines - Mimata's 4th date!!
Dismiss~
I can't take in anymore
In our news agency, we have horror department duties.
The duties start at this time
Would you guys like to help out?
Aww maan....
The room is in basement 1.
But I'm not going, because I'm scared.
What the hell?
In any case, from here on, it's OK to laugh,
But it's an 'out' if you get scared.
Here we go..
Excuse me,
I don't wanna be with Tanaka in this case
Anything strange would be enough to scare him
(Late night special rule)
(No getting frightened news agency)
(Illumination within the building has changed)
Tanaka, it's scarier at the back.
Right, you should stay in front, it's definitely better
OK, please walk behind me then.
(Toaster)
Tanaka with his reaction...
Stop that will you
I think he landed on his knee
Keep it together will ya
(Heipo scream)
What the hell
What the hell are ya doing?
Tanaka are you dead?
If a person's voice is your limit then there's something wrong with you
(Carefully sweeping across the basement towards their destination)
(What will the horror dept. have them do?)
Ah here we are! The horror dept.
Endou, you're a little too loud
(Farewell letter)
Sit and wait
Absolutely no manners huh...
(Horror department member)
Hello
I'm looking for someone from the horror department
Endou-san
Endou speaking
Hello, I have a request.
In the archives on the 3rd floor
There are 3 portraits on display
Please take photos of these portraits
so that the spirit will be caught
Endou-san and Yamazaki-san
would you be so kind as take the spirit photographs?
The archives on the 3rd floor
There are 3 portraits
If their photos are taken, we'll have ourselves spirit photos.
This was requested of Yamazaki-san and myself
You're kidding!
Portrait photos and Shouzou ... complicatedly related.
('Portrait' and Endou's given name are pronounced the same = Shouzou)
(Discharging of CO2 gas)
This would definitely scare anyone
(2 meter tall Kitarou)
That's really scary
Huge
Excuse us..
Don't worry~
(Nishino Lion)
You're really scary
That head...
Don't worry~
This IS worrisome
(The echoes of the 2 screaming men)
They're really noisy
You can hear them all the time
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry
(Bombardment of firebombs)
(Sign before entering)
You guys were lame
(Electric Pen)
What's wrong?
Housei-san (Yamazaki), please sign.
It'll be OK if you use your sleeves
It's really painful and scary you know
It's fine even if we don't write anything
Are those it?
Zetto Zetto Zetto
(Vocalist Mizuki Ichirou constantly shouts "Zetto" as his gag)
ZETTO!
(Mizuki Ichirou emerges from portrait)
Did you get it?
Got it got it
(Nishikino Akira on a Segway)
(Balloon Man)
DOWN! DOWN! DOWN!
I took it I took it
OI! ENDOU!
This is bad this is bad
This is bad
You guys sure were noisy
The last time was nothing compared to this
(Snakes from the ceiling)
That scared me!
Were there instances like this one?
This is nothing.
Purifying the 3rd floor archives with salt
Hamada & Matsumoto
It's not 3 people?
No just 2
Be careful
Oh we will be cuz we're scared
Man this is depressing
Stop it with this pattern!
(OL Matsuko Deluxe)
(Sento-kun is Nara's 1300th anniversary mascot)
(Sento-kun)
It's Sento-kun
Why did Sento-kun enter all of a sudden?
Is this the 3rd floor?
(TKO's Kinoshita Takayuki as Sento-kun)
You.. really... always screaming
What the hell
DON'T WORRY~
You scared the hell outta me!
You were really loud
This is messed up, really messed up
They're screaming like us, Downtown-san
Two 45 year olds.. that adds up to 90
Shut up will you
Oh there's something there
This is the kind of thing I hate the most
Mysterious Cleaner
Contortionist
What was that just then?
(Sign before entering)
It's these kinds of doors that are the scariest
Sign before entering..
No you do it
What is it?
I got zapped
Open the door then
YOU open it
You're really harsh you know
There was a running current just then
WuD tHe hELL?
This is enough, seriously enough
(Yuutarou emerges from portrait)
Can I have some salt?
Please do
Mmm goood
Let's go back
What is "Nya~"?
Wouldn't it be good if nothing happened on the way back?
(Nishikino + pillars of fire)
Really scary really scary
What is he doing seriously
Is he an idiot!?
He's here he's here he's here!
(Nun Nun in elevator)
This is really tiresome eh
This time's much more taxing than the last right?
(Tanaka alone remains)
Hello, may I speak to Tanaka-san please
Hello
May I request that you take spirit photos at the mountain nearby
Eh?
A car has been prepared for you at the entrance of the building
I have to bring back spirit photos from a mountain nearby
Where where?
There's a car waiting for me by the entrance
Eh? You're kidding
There will be a coordinator dressed in a red hood waiting for you there
What's wrong? You looked like a sardine can
Your legs are bad so be careful
Doing this alone is just impossible
Tanaka: The mountain nearby... which vicinity is it in?
Driver: ...
Tanaka: Ah there
Coordinator: Eh?
Tanaka: WOah!
Coordinator: What?
Coordinator: You're late! You should have hurried here!
Coordinator: Cuz I'm really scared, I hate this
Coordinator: Hurry up I'm really scared, hurry
Tanaka: Eh? What's going on here?
Coordinator: I don't know, they just told me to stay here
Tanaka: You're Heipo-san aren't you?
Heipo: Right it's Heipo
Tanaka: Is it OK if you get in?
Heipo: Woah the driver!
Tanaka: Har?
Heipo: Give this letter(map) to the driver
Heipo: I don't know, I was given this for company
Tanaka: Right, so it's OK if you get on right?
Heipo: Right and give that to the driver
Heipo: With that we should be OK
Heipo: Ahh.. Scary
Heipo: Excuse me Mr. Driver, but on it is written where our destination is right?
Heipo: Could you get us there?
Heipo: Eh? Please say something
Heipo: Eh? This guy's scary...
This video tape recording is recorded by Tanaka & Heipo themselves, and unmanned cameras.
The staff was not involved with anything that happened on scene
Heipo: This is pretty amazing, it's pitch-black outside
Tanaka: Yea it's pitch-black
Tanaka: Just calm down OK? Heipo-san
Heipo: OK, I understand
Tanaka: We've entered one heck of a place
Heipo: Eh~ Noo
Heipo: No good Tanaka-kun, I'm scared
Heipo: I've had enough
Heipo: Ah ow ow ow ow ow
Heipo: Is the red light on? (Video recording)
Tanaka: Ah yes yes
Heipo: Look at this, this is somewhat incredible
Heipo: There's something, something over there
Heipo: Looks like we're here
Tanaka: Eh? We've arrived?
Heipo: Uwaahh.. I don't wanna go out there
Heipo: EHH~!
Heipo: ah...
Heipo: ...my bad
Tanaka: Eh? What is it?
Heipo: I don't know, I thought I saw something move
Tanaka: Does this mean we have to get off?
Heipo: I don't know...uWOOAAHH  DRIVER
Tanaka: What's the matter?
Heipo: I just saw a shadow over there! A red one
Tanaka: Eh? What kind of shadow is it?
Heipo: See? A red one!
Tanaka: Isn't that your reflection Heipo-san!?
Heipo: UwaAAhh!
Tanaka: What's the matter?
Heipo: I.. don't know
Tanaka: Could you stop saying "I don't know"?
Heipo: WaAAh~ No more!
Tanaka: This is just terrible
Heipo: A torchlight this weak is just no good! Aaah
Tanaka: Eh? What's wrong?
Heipo: Ah.... I don't know
Tanaka: This is that right? A tent
Tanaka: Are we supposed to get inside it?
Heipo: I guess so
Tanaka: We have no other choice but to enter
Heipo: The car's gone...
Tanaka you're talented,
Heipo: Eh?
with the camera
Heipo: Alright! This is fine
Tanaka: Right
Heipo: Ahh.. I'm scared
Heipo: Tanaka-kun, let's close this, it's scary
Heipo: Scary~ scary
Heipo: Man.. Pull yourself together
Heipo: Oh I don't know
Heipo: Tanaka-kun please stop it
Addressed to Tanaka and Heipo
You'll spend this short period of time
in this tent
When the alarm rings
Open the envelope and you'll find a map
On it you'll find the location of the spirit spot and
how to get there
PS: Heipo should also appear in the photograph that's taken
Be safe
Stay in the tent temporarily
When the alarm rings, head for the spirit spot
Heipo should be in the photograph that's taken
Heipo: So what does this mean?
Heipo: Is there really a map or something?
Heipo: "When the alarm rings, the map in the envelope..."
Heipo: It's that!
Heipo: I'm scared...
Heipo: I'm already worn out.. coming out here
Heipo: No more...
Heipo: No more~~
Tanaka: Cold~
Heipo: It's because it rang so suddenly
Heipo: So what now? Do we look at it (the map)?
These two are really something huh
Heipo: What does this mean?
The worst duo
Heipo: Mizunomi...
Take the photo in front of Mizunomi
Tanaka: Look at the map carefully
Heipo: Now we're outside aren't we?
Heipo: It's like plaza isn't it?
Heipo: We need to go straight and then make a right
Tanaka: So we go straight huh
Heipo: So firstly we go straight right?
Heipo: I can't see anything with the camera's light on!
Tanaka: Are we still to go straight?
Tanaka: Wait wait
Tanaka: Wait calm down calm down!
Tanaka: It's alright! Heipo-san calm down
Heipo: I don't know...
Heipo: EH~!
Tanaka: Can you please shine the light to the front?
Heipo: Tanaka-kun, do you know where we are?
Tanaka: No I don't but...
Tanaka: Man... isn't it just pitched black?
Heipo: NoO!!
Tanaka: Wait wait wait
Tanaka: Let's stop let's stop
Tanaka: Let's stop, stop a sec, really
Heipo: A tree...
Heipo: I hate this, I can't see at all
Heipo: I hate this... let's just end it here
Heipo: There's something here
Heipo: Ah! Moths moths!
Heipo: Wait a minute! No no no no! Moths moths moths!
Heipo: Is it because of the lights?
Heipo: Enough is enough, Moth-chan
Heipo: Stop it!
Heipo: I can't turn off the lights you know
Tanaka: Let's get closer
Tanaka: Feel my hand.. Feel my body
Heipo: Wait....
Tanaka: Feel my body.. No I mean..
Tanaka: When we snap the photo,
Tanaka: in order to stay close, we'll feel each other's bodies like now
Heipo: Ah I'm at ease.. at ease at ease
Heipo: Is it a right from here?
Tanaka: When the ground goes left, we'll make a right
Heipo: Ah the ground!
Tanaka: Eh? How can you tell?
Heipo: Well I don't know, but look
Heipo: Isn't it wide?
Heipo: Isn't it somehow wide?
Heipo: Ahh~ I can't see!
Heipo: I don't know!
Tanaka: Let's take a look at the surrounding area
Tanaka: Find a place to rest and the route we should take
Heipo: ooh.. no...
Heipo: no more...
Heipo: Ah!
Heipo: Is that it?
Tanaka: Could it be?
Heipo: Huh?..
Heipo: No....
Tanaka: Uwaaa... This is somewhat scary
Heipo: I'm scared
Heipo: So what do we do here? Should my back be facing you?
Tanaka: It's supposed to be a photo with you facing the front right?
Heipo: Let's be in the photo together
Tanaka: Then who's gonna take the photo?
Heipo: Oh right..
Heipo: Is this OK?
Tanaka: Please just stand there properly
Heipo: Where're you going! Where're you going!
Heipo: No no no no no no
Tanaka: I'm too close to take a shot
Heipo: Ah I see
Tanaka: Say cheese!
Tanaka: Ahh.. This is scary!
Heipo: Scary!
Tanaka: Let's get back, seriously
Tanaka: Shouldn't we hurry back?
Heipo: Hurry?
Heipo: What is this!
(The duo, frightened by orange peels)
Tanaka: Stop this already
Tanaka: Wait it's dangerous it's dangerous
Heipo: What's the matter~
Heipo: Are you alright?
Tanaka: It was tiring wasn't it
Heipo: Let's rest
Tanaka: Yea let's
Heipo: I can't take this
Tanaka: I really have the urge to go pee
Heipo: Are you going to?
Heipo: What will you do? Will you be OK? Can you hold it in?
Tanaka: I think I'll go
Heipo: Eh? By yourself?
Tanaka: I'll be back as soon as I can
Toilet
Heipo: Can I close this?
Tanaka: Sure
Tanaka: If anything happens I'll be back immediately
Tanaka: Is it over there?
Tanaka: Ah I'm scared
Heipo: Huh what?
Tanaka: Ah it's me
Heipo: Oh..
Tanaka: Ah I'm scared...
Tanaka: Uwaaa.. I'm really scared now
Tanaka: This is really scary
Tanaka: This is where I'll have to pee huh
(The camera's light dies suddenly)
Heipo: What's the matter~
(Heipo - startled by Tanaka's voice)
Tanaka: Wait a minute! The batteries!
Tanaka: Ah I dropped it! (Camera)
Tanaka: I dropped it...
Heipo: What what?
Heipo: Hurry! I'm scared!
Heipo: No no no no!
Tanaka: The zip! The zip!
Heipo: Stop it .. no more..!
Heipo: Where did you go?
Tanaka: I went to pee
THE TOILET!!
Tanaka: When I was about to open the door (toilet)
Tanaka: The batteries died out ya know
Tanaka: The camera's batteries
Heipo: Seriously?
Heipo: Uwaaa scary
Tanaka: It was sudden you know
Heipo: You were really shouting, I thought something had happened
What's the matter~
Spirit photography completed
When did you get back?
Just now.
Your eyes have really sunken in you know
It was the worst
Who was the person in the red hood?
Well I don't wanna see that person ever again
What happened?
He was really annoying
You look really irritated
Guys, today's data collecting ends here
The newspaper will be completed shortly
So rest easy while it's being done
Shall we go?
Go back.
So it's finally over?
(The journalists' hard day's work)
(Welcoming the results that come instantly)
Wooh I'm tired out!
Please line yourselves up here
Then descend the stairs
The newspaper should already be out right?
Well then, let's go down
Congratulations~
Everyone, Happy New Year!
Founder
Suga Kenji - Youth
Here's Ga- Su- Sports New Year's Issue!
Yamazaki-san
Uncle Matsumoto
Uncle Hamada
You were definitely sleeping
Uncle Endou. thank you..
He looked like he just woke up!
...Uncle
Everyone, I look forward to working with you again this year
Incredible!
Incredible, they really made a newspaper
Well then shall we?
No. of ass-whoopings
The asses of five reporters
The more you beat them, the sadder they get
The more you spank them, the sadder they get
Because it makes me laugh
Because it makes me excited
Because it makes me scared
Its inevitable that youll be beaten
Blue bruises on the ass of a 40-ish year old man.
Surprise visitors attacked without a break
And I cant resist a smile
By those big onions
My heart breaks for the first time
I got off the train at Kudanshita station
and walked up the hill
As I pass the stream of people
My buttocks swell up red in the twilight
With Fujiwara laughing behind me
Annas mother, the woman from Kayo, they both
leapt out
Oowada twisted his ankle
Junjis ass, Bibaris neck, turning around
Nakamuras anxiety at the growing appearance fees
When the joke is revealed, he laughs and gets beaten
It happens over and over again
Only the buttocks swell without a word
I dont care, Im gonna scream says Heipo
Song TL: /u/BratscheTLW
I think in your case, you should be the most tired one
Heipo-san right?
When he gets frightened, I'd ask "What happened?"
He'd go "I don't know!"
That was the extent of his intelligence
It's always "I don't know"
There are quite a bit of articles in the paper yea?
Yea there's even a segment on Umezu-san's funeral
???
Looks like Johnny Depp
His haircut eh
They don't look alike at all
There's the funeral too
'A lovey-dovey interview right in front of ex-husband' huh?
The 'New' Onii
You haven't tried it yet have you?
Me!?
Hamada-san too!
He's unwillingly to that's why
You already know what it does, so you should be OK
Yea it's because I've seen it already right?
Yea it shouldn't be a problem
What what? What're you doing?
What were you doing!
What's the point of holding it there?
Just feeling a little of it is enough
So letting go was OK?
You were holding it forever!
Everyone else let go!