Tonight, made public at last:
The comedian with the most outrageous snoring makes his appearance.
His snoring is something to behold.
It sure is hot, right?
Hot indeed!
People are usually on the edge when it's hot.
A lot of annoying things have been happening lately.
Not just because it's hot right?
Have you gone there?
Where?
I heard you've visited this place.
A golf bar...
I still visit that place.
You're still going?
I mean, I play golf so...
Miyasako said: "A golf bar is pretty interesting, shall we go?"
So we ended up going together.
It's a bar, but it's also golf.
They've got this screen and you hit the ball on it...
...so it's kind of like you're playing golf.
They have several rooms and you have to wait.
Then when one is finally available...
"Please come this way."
This shit is really expensive too!
There's a caddy as well, and he goes like...
..."would you like to hit some balls for practice?"
Yes yes, so I hit a few balls.
About 250... feet? Not feet right?
Yards.
Yards!
"You're actually pretty good!"
Yeah, I can kinda do this stuff.
"Alright, should we get started then?"
Okay let's go!
So I hit and...
And the next one...
Do your best!
The caddy and his half-assed cheering.
"Should we hit one more?"
So I hit again...
"Nice... shot..."
HOW WAS THAT NICE!?
I'LL NEVER COME TO THIS SHOP AGAIN!
AND I'LL NEVER WALK NEAR THIS SHOP AGAIN EITHER, IDIOT!
I went home after 10 minutes.
You see...
Is this really something to sweat this much about?
Why are you getting mad because you can't hit properly?
NO I WAS HITTING IT!
Even when I hit a good ball it was like...
...it didn't seem to have registered the ball.
The screen didn't register.
HOW USELESS TO NOT REGISTER!
Obviously something hit the screen!
"Sorry, it seems to not have registered, could you hit it again please?"
Alright...
So the next shit ball I hit, why does that one register?
I don't know about that but...
I was so annoyed.
Also, I don't know why you are giving me such a cold response when I'm talking about a golf bar.
I mean, it's not a shop to get that mad about.
The other day as well, at my place...
...I thought about going to sleep.
I opened up my fridge...
...you usually have these jars in there, right?
Something about them was bothering me.
So I decided to rearrange them a bit.
And out of nowhere, BANG. Completely shattered.
Super thick soumen sauce, everywhere.
In the middle of the night, in my kitchen.
Super thick soumen sauce and some other stuff, everywhere.
I just... I just... I couldn't move.
I'm mostly surprised that you eat soumen at home.
Of course, I have it just in case.
In that kind of situation, what would you do?
What do you mean?
I can't vacuum that stuff.
Oh, right.
But shards went all over the place, right?
You can't really move because you'll pierce your feet.
So I had no idea what to even begin with.
I just wanted to sleep, really sleep.
But this super thick soumen sauce is everywhere!
Okay dude.
Very carefully I moved backwards.
I grabbed a cloth and carefully wiped it up.
But it was super sticky.
And why was that?
Because it was super thick soumen sauce.
I see.
Before I knew it, two hours had already passed.
I want to get it all cleaned up.
And when think you got all the pieces, you look at it like this...
...you see another piece of glass.
All I could smell was soy sauce.
I thought to myself, how am I gonna eat all this sauce now?
That doesn't really matter.
And I'm also sweating like crazy.
I mean, that stuff is unavoidable.
I brought out the Quickle wiper.
Yes, yes...
The thing that's like, like this, you know?
The one where your finger gets stuck.
So I bring it out and it goes like "Quickle".
After one wipe you have to change it already.
It's all sticky!
Oww oww oww!
Learn from that will ya?
No matter how many wipes I used, it wasn't enough.
That stuff got me so irritated.
It was all sticky?
Completely sticky.
And why was that?
Because of the super thick soumen sauce.
Today actually...
...we have a special program.
That's right.
But before that, go ahead!
Yama-chan isn't the type to scream this much about.
That's not true!
Good evening!
During the talk from 2 weeks prior...
So I took a little summer break.
I decided to go to Okinawa.
You probably don't know but...
...do you know a kouhai named Onigiri?
First time I've heard of that.
Never heard of, right?
Everyone here probably doesn't know him, either.
So I went with Yamasaki and Miyasako.
And Miyasako has a kouhai who he really likes, called Onigiri.
This guy is about two meters tall.
No, for real!
If you tell him, "you're sweating like crazy"...
...he's like, "this is not sweat, it's rice water".
Nobody was laughing.
He seemed to be good to have
around as a bodyguard...
...so we brought him with us.
Apparently, he used to be a volleyball player.
He shows up with glasses on...
...and a suit that nobody told him to bring.
So the whole time he was talking into a radio like this, with an earpiece in.
He'd be like "No no no!" if someone came close.
"No picture!"
This guy's snoring is astonishing.
You can't even call this snoring.
What do you mean by that?
You're not allowed to call it snoring.
I see now.
Are you for real?
That's just screaming!
THIS IS REAL!
Onigiri, the crazy snoring comedian.
That's the gist of it.
You don't know him, right?
No idea.
It seems the three of us don't know him.
Never seen him either?
The first time I heard about him was during our Okinawa trip.
We don't really know this guy after all...
I guess I don't know either.
Stop making it look like I'm gonna introduce him to you all!
He's more or less Matsumoto's favorite child.
There's no way he's my favorite!
Here's Onigiri!
No picture!
No pictures!
Is he able to manage this on his own?
My apologies. *fumbles over his words*
What the hell!
I work under Yoshimoto and I'm part of the comedy group New Romance. *more stumbling*
Yoshimoto Industry Tokyo NSC 8th Year Manzai Combi New Romance Onigiri
To be honest...
...to stand on a big stage like this on your 5th year is amazing.
You're sweating like crazy already, right?
This is not sweat!
It's rice water!
See, this is what he's like.
Over time you get used to it.
This guy compares everything with rice.
Why don't ask him some questions?
How tall are you in centimeters?
193 grains!
See what I'm talking about?
I mean, he did compare it to rice after all.
How big is your shoe size?
27.5 hectare!
Is this compared to a rice field?
Yes, a rice field.
So this guy...
Ending already?!
It's been more than enough already!
This guy's snoring is so amazing.
We shared a room with five people.
But the first two days, we had him sleep on the balcony.
It was that loud?
That is what we want *everybody to see today.
You're messing up today!
That one was really bad Zaki-san.
Next up: Footage of the most impactful snoring made public!!
Does snoring like this really exist in this world!?
The person in question: the young comedian, Onigiri.
Good morning!
The truth about Onigiri's snoring.
Onigiri, born in Hokkaido, July 1977.
From here?!
With his 185 cm father...
...and his 175 cm mother...
...Onigiri was always a tall kid, who kept on growing.
After graduating middle school, he was already 188cm tall.
With his physique, he worked hard to become like a certain person.
I wanted to become a volleyball player like Nakagaichi.
Yes, volleyball!
With dreams of becoming a pro, he gave it his all during his youth.
He entered Nippon Steel, famous for the volleyball team.
Working and playing volleyball....
...he achieved his dream and was able to meet his hero shoulder to shoulder.
So why did he quit volleyball to instead become a comedian?
Nakagaichi's payslip had fallen in the gym.
I ended up looking at it and the pay wasn't that great so I decided to quit.
You can't do that!
I'm terribly sorry.
Doubts of Onigiri's snoring started to surface.
That's why this time, we decided to record his sleeping at home.
With four cameras set up, we'll wait for Onigiri to come home.
What's up with
that tiny futon?
Thank you for your hard work! Thank you!
I'll be sleeping now. Sorry and good night!
You don't have
to apologize.
Late night, a bit past 1 am.
After a day of work, Onigiri goes to sleep like usual.
What will see from here on out!?
*5 minutes later*
Is this the first
time you've seen
yourself sleep?
Yes, this is
the first time.
*10 minutes later*
Onigiri starts snoring little by little.
*20 minutes later*
This still seems
fairly normal.
*30 minutes later*
What's this?
What the hell
is this?
It's not like he's
sleep-talking.
Paired with a peculiar voice, he starts to make small shaking movements.
*45 minutes later*
He's laughing!
For real,
what is this?
He's a monster,
right?!
We found a reason for his peculiar snoring.
You're screaming!
1: First it starts with sleep apnea.
I can't help but
look at the earplug
2: Gasping for air.
What the hell
is this?!
3: Followed by peculiar snoring.
This is bad.
What is the volume of the strange snoring?
I told you it
was for real!
The highest snoring measured was a whopping 94.0 dB.
This same volume occurs when a train crosses a steel bridge.
Just before dawn, the snoring still continues.
This is crazy!
How long do
you keep going?
For real, how
long do you
keep going for?
Onigiri-san, good morning.
We'll be heading out now.
May I sleep like I usually do now?
Onigiri's strange snoring continues...
That was amazing.
That wasn't really snoring.
You're screaming!
You've never seen something like this before right?
Never!
You started moving like this as well.
That was gross!
See! Going on a trip with this guy can't be fun right?
I had a lot of fun!
Probably, yeah.
During that, are you having dreams?
Not in particular.
You don't sleep bad either?
Not really...
You sleep very well?
Yes, I do.
Aren't you tired when you wake up?
No, I feel super refreshed.
You feel refreshed?
If you were his girlfriend, you'd probably be scared.
Don't you have one?
I'm currently taking applications!
I shouldn't have asked...
I'll say this: he's very bad at this kinda stuff.
So this footage has been submitted to a specialist.
Let's hear what they say about this.
Onigiri's snoring sounds like an animal.
What does a specialist have to say about this?
He's laughing!
When a specialist
is laughing you
know it's bad!
This is the first time I've seen a video of someone sleeping this poorly.
It's scary,
honestly!
From what I can see, due to his corpulent physique...
...it makes him unable to breath, causing sleep apnea.
Over the long term, this will have negative effects on his heart, brain and blood vessels...
...as well as the dangers of arteriosclerosis, heart attacks and strokes.
I would highly recommend seeking professional help...
...to find the causes and to treat the issue.
Go to the hospital and get an examination done quick!
What the hell?!
No way you're sleeping!
But it seems like you were telling the truth after all.
I was!
That was abnormal.
That was the end, but could we please see it one more time?
I want to see it again too.
Because of the laughing I couldn't hear all of it.
This is very precious footage.
More precious than footage of eels laying eggs.
Let's watch this precious footage again.
This is on the
verge of still
being acceptable.
You'd almost think
he's doing this
on purpose.
This is kinda
gross, I don't
like it!
It's like an engine
starting up.
This is way
too long.
He's saying something.
What do you think after seeing this?
I'm sorry for any trouble I have caused.
Such a normal response!
The normalest of the normal!
Didn't you compare everything to rice?
Stop crying!
I'm not crying!
Oh really?
I got rice in my eyes.
Aren't you an onigiri?
Now it looks like I bombed too.
After all of this you'll be a grilled onigiri.
Next up: Onigiri's special move!!
Would it be okay if I told you about his special move?
He used to play volleyball so...
...his backslap is nothing to joke about.
Sorry, then I would like...
You're crazy, absolutely crazy!
I really don't want that!
That's just crazy!
Yama-chan hurry up already...
No, please wait!
Sorry!
Angela Aki should go!
I'm not Angela Aki!
Wait, this is impossible!
Hold on, you're the one who told us about it!
He's your favorite child after all!
He's not my favorite!
Could you do it on this chair then?
A slap from this height coming down...
You're sitting?
Here I go!
That was very underwhelming!
What the hell.
It barely moved.
It was kinda cute.