Are scary stories from around the world really scary?
What's this voice?
Welcome to World Ghost Stories Summit 2015
Are scary ghost stories from around the world really scary!?
World Ghost Stories Summit
That's not a face I know
Really
Have you switched your inner channel?
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
We're talking about scary stories, I can't shout as usual
Amazing...
The way you said "World Ghost Stories" was something
Amazing
What are we doing today?
You know we're in that time of year
Where we hear a lot of Japanese ghost stories, right?
That's right
Yes
Yeah
How about other countries?
Now that I think about it...
Never heard them
I mean, I don't know much about it
Is there any to begin with?
That's what I want to know
Yeah...
We've gathered TV stars from 6 different countries
Foreign TV stars are going to present scary stories from their own country
Our members will pick the scariest one
World Ghost Stories Summit 2015
To find out if scary stories from around the world are actually scary
Our first guest is Hong Kong's representative, please come in
Who is it gonna be?
Our first guest is Agnes-chan
Her face...
I mean
With that face?
Is she trying to make us laugh?
Really
Is that it?
No way
She'll tell us a scary story
That's too much
Translation by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Typeset & QC by Kedomas
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com | fb.com/shionnotsukai
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai | patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai Ya Arahende!!
World Ghost Stories Summit begins!
Foreign TV stars are going to tell us scary stories!
Our representative from Hong Kong is Agnes-chan
Agnes-chan
China ・ Hong Kong Representative
China, Hong Kong
A well-know country and one of the leading economic powers
But which scary story hides within it?
Which scary story...?
A scary story from Hong Kong?
Yes, whenever you're ready
This is a real story happened in a region of Hong Kong
One night, there was a phone call in a
tearoom which was about to close
It went "ring ring ring",
and as the store manager answered
"I'd like to have... coffee... and sandwich... 3 of each, please"
Huh?
The manager thought
"Who the hell makes calls this late?"
and set out to make the delivery
When he got to the house, he angrily knocked the door
Tearoom catering
And then, the door opened a bit
And a voice from inside
Told him "place them inside"
It was a ghastly voice
He then put the food through the small gap on the door
And after he did it, the door slammed shut by itself
He then realized the customer didn't actually
pay him and started to shout "pay me up!"
And then, money came out from under the door
He got so scared he immediately rode his bicycle back home
The next night, at the same exact time, he got the same call
Asking for 3 coffees and 3 sandwiches
Just like the day before
He slid the food down the door and got
his money without showing his face
He thought "could this guy be involved in some crime?"
So he decided to bring the police with him
The police came and the officer said
"it's strange, this should be a vacant house"
"No way!"
"It can't be true"
Then the two of them entered the room
And when they did, what they found...
Were the rotting corpses of three men
The policeman stated they must have been dead for at least 2-3 months
"It can't be" - said the shop owner, "I got some
deliveries from here the past few days"
But no one believed him
Some days later, the police called him
"We performed the autopsy..."
"And we've found something like a sandwich in the corpses' stomach"
Ohh...
The shop owner thought again about the money he received
And when he looked at it, he realized it had turned into
Few gold-colored coins, which in Hong Kong
Are buried together with dead people for their afterlife
The money he got that day turned into these
And that's it
What do you think?
You said this really happened, right?
It's a famous story
"Golden coins" are something I've heard before
That's right, when he got them at first they were normal money
But when he looked back at them later,
they've turned into golden coins
They've changed
It's a scary story, you know
Quit laughing around
You're giggling like crazy
You too, Hamada
Not true
It was you
Agnes... she was laughing, wasn't she?
No doubt about it
What am I supposed to do?
Why was she laughing?
Yama-chan made her laugh
We started at the same time
See?
She said at the same time
Heard her?
I think that's because when she entered
she tried so hard to strike a scary look
It makes sense
The whole thing has become unbalanced since
You're right
She did too much
Next up is a scary story from the U.S.A.
Our U.S.A. representative is a comedian from Nabe Pro
Ike Nwala
U.S.A. Representative
Mr. Ike Nwala
Please tell us your scary story
This story is from the state of Wisconsin
And it's about a little girl
So, there was this girl called Jane
She used to wear a yellow ribbon around her neck everyday
She knew a guy named Johnny, he was her best friend
Yellow ribbon
Everyday Johnny asked Jane:
"why do you wear that yellow ribbon?"
But Jane would never reply to that
When they grew up and became adults, they eventually got married
Jane gave birth to a baby, and he always asked her
"Mama, why do you always wear that
yellow ribbon around your neck?"
But his mom never replied to that
As time went by, Jane and Johnny became old
And one day Jane became ill
Johnny went to the hospital everyday to check her
And he asked her again
"Please, Jane, tell me"
"Why do you always wear that yellow ribbon?"
Jane replied "you can have it"
"Take it away"
As Johnny unfastened the ribbon from her neck
Jane's head fell off
That's the story
What a dynamic punch line!!
Really
That was sudden
The ending is so dynamic
Incredible
I see...
I don't think there are stories like this one in Japan
Nope
I mean, they don't usually
You're right
End with a black humor feeling
It was easy to follow, I liked that
Was it effective for you?
Yeah
You can tell it's from the U.S.A.
Yes
And that makes me wonder
Maybe we didn't need Agnes to join us
No way
She's from Hong Kong, it's different
Of course we needed her
But her face...
That's just for show
Our next scary story is from Egypt
Our representative from Egypt is miss Fifi
Egypt Representative
Fifi
Egypt is the home of countless myths about pharaohs and curses
Egypt
Which scary story are we going to listen to?
Which scary story...?
I think you all already know this...
But if we talk about Egypt you can easily picture stories of pharaohs such as Tutankhamon
Such as myths about cobras attacking you if you get close to a pharaoh's tomb
There are lots of stories like this one
I wanna tell you about a scary story I personally experienced
Since when I was a little girl, I used to see white dwarfs all around
White dwarfs
Dwarfs?
I don't think I was the only one
But since I was little, whenever I saw a white dwarf, something good would happen
White dwarf
It was a long time ago, from when I was a high schooler
That day I thought "it's been a while since I last saw one"
And then
The doorbell rang
When I opened it there were around 50 men carrying vegetables
I recently moved in, so they were bringing me presents
So something good did happen
Whenever I happened to see another white dwarf, the doorbell rang
And people brought me sweets
But one day I was busy making a phone call and the doorbell rang
I was too bothered to go open the door
That night I had a dream in which I was in the same room I was in during the day
There was a door on the other side, and from its gap
I could see a black dwarf behind it
Its eyes were gleaming and it was staring at me blankly
Then I suddenly opened my eyes
I stared at that same door in my dream
And one of my neighbors was spying on me from that gap
I got frightened, but before I realized that man got closer
And he started choking me with a really menacing look
He kept on pressing until I passed out
The next day I woke up, it was a dream
I was talking to the landlord and told him I had this weird dream
I told him that nice man from that house which often comes over was choking me
He replied "no one lives in that house"
"You're kidding me, aren't you?"
He told me "no, it's true", and took me there
He opened up the front door
And there really was nothing inside
It was still morning and I had no idea
what I just saw the night before
I got near the washstand and when I glanced at the mirror, I noticed I had a mark around my neck
The end
What do you think about it?
More than "white dwarf", I'd say "small dwarf"
You know
I thought you said shiroi koibito at first
That sweet from Hokkaido?
It's a traditional Hokkaido biscuit
Next up is a scary story from Guinea, Africa
Our representative from Guinea is mr. Sankhon Ousmane
Guinea Representative
Sankhon Ousmane
Guinea
Guinea occupies the western edge of Africa
And lots of different tribes live in its vast pristine nature: which story are we going to listen to?
Which scary story...?
This story...
It's a fairly popular scary story in Guinea,
which is in western Africa
It's about a funeral
In Guinea, when someone dies
We bury them
You burn your dead in Japan, we bury ours in Guinea
In Guinea, they usually bury their dead
As a tradition, from when the dead is placed inside the coffin
until the burial is completed, you must not turn around
Don't turn around
That's because it will disturb its ghost.
So, one day an eminent man died
And after his burial
Everyone thought it was time to go home, but one man
Was being pulled by something from behind
Something kept on pulling him
But no one could turn around to see it
And for half a day
He stood still, quibering
Hm?
Quivering
"Half a day"...?
Half day
And then he-- all time---
When he turned around, no one was there
There was just a cat
Which was pulling his dress
This is not a story to laugh about
When he got back home, all the houses in the village were burnt in a violent fire
It's over
It was kinda scary...
It had a sort of double turn
Yeah, kinda
But in a way it has a happy end, didn't it?
H-happy...?
It's not a happy story, is it?
What the-?
Matsumoto?
Is him our most non-responding guest or what?
Next up is a scary story from Nigeria, Africa
Nice dress
Our representative from Nigeria is Mr. Bobby Ologon
Bobby Ologon
Nigeria Representative
Nigeria is the most populated country in Africa
Nigeria
Which scary story is from this country of repeated civil wars?
Which scary story...?
Thank you for having me
This is a real scary story which is
still happening in Nigeria nowadays
Its name is "elbowrun granny"
The elbowrun granny is really fast
It's said to be faster than a Ferrari
It's a granny who could run up to 300km/h
This granny's story started a long time ago,
when she married a king
300kmh fast granny
This king
He was kind to her
And still, he eventually got a second wife
But after he got married
He grew distant from his first wife
And told her "just focus on the task I give you"
So she went for a 20km walk
In order to get some water
One day, on her road to get water
She slipped
And fell down a cliff
When she fell down
Her body was cut in half
But no one couldn't find her for three whole days
And so she disappeared
And became tainted with rage
As she became angrier and angrier
She started to kill everyone from the village
Who came to the river to get water
Her speed was over 300 km/h
And if she goes lock-on on you, you couldn't escape from her
One after another
She started to kill every young men from the village
And so young men started disappearing from the village
And people thought "this is bad, the King has to do something"
So they decided to go see the fortune-teller old lady
The old fortune-teller
Said "your previous wife is filled with rage"
"If you don't do anything about it"
"The village is going to be destroyed"
He's not in the role at all
"But what should I do?"
And so it was decided
That each year, 7 young male virgins
Would be offered to her as sacrifices to ease her anger
Anyway
For now let's offer these 7 virgins
And so she can kill them and have her anger eased
This was the elbowrun granny's tale
I have no idea what he's
been talking about all the time
Sorry about this, Bobby
First of all...
First of all, what granny did he say?
Was it red-row granny?
It's elbowrun granny
Come again?
It's a granny who runs using her elbows
Ah, she ran with her elbows?!
Elbow-running, I see
And she's 300km/h fast, right?
Yes, yes
It's supposed to be a scary story
But you said "if she goes lock-on on you" and stuff
You can't just go and use english there
He's right, that's no good
He realized halfway through it that we weren't following
And just gave up trying
Eh? Really?
That's not true
He started talking like "yeah, whatever"
It's not true
Coming up
The last storyteller narrates something absurd
Our sixth guest will be our last one
Our staff held an audition for foreigners living in Japan
Last Storyteller
They chose a foreigner living in Japan whose scary story
best represents the country from where they come from
And chose the one whose story best represents their home country
Ah, so it's not a famous person?
That's right
Please
Mr. Alif is our representative from Bangladesh
Alif
Bangladesh Representative
It's a pleasure to have you here
Bangladesh, a symbol of India
Bangladesh
Which scary story is born in this land?
Which scary story...?
You can start telling your scary story
This is a very famous story in Bangladesh
I first heard it when I got back to my country during Summer break
And since then I still think it's really scary
In Bangladesh we have two types of ghosts: male and female
Male ghosts are called "Jin"
And female ghosts are called "Pori"
And because such ghosts are known as "Pori"
They appear as beautiful girls
And they are always trying to lure men
So she went where this guy was
And she was beautiful and then she got closer and closer
And then he ran out
And she run and run and run after him into a paddy field
And then smack, smack and she got him from his neck down
And then
His friends are like "huh? He was sleeping, wasn't he? We gotta get him away", you know, from the ghost
They all went together all of them, they were all afraid
They all went out to search for him
"Oh! He's there and look!
His body disappeared there's only his head!"
He's--- he's been pushed till there and look,
that's all you can see
So they all went there
And ouuuuughhhh
They all lifted him up together
Some of those who lifted him then died
On the same day this story was already well known
And the same people, pretty much the same, the same guys
Were followed by the ghost
She was still a beautiful pretty lady and during their sleep
Those guys were forced to do different stuff,
so no one would know
In Bangladesh we have huge trees,
like 5 to 6 meters tall
And their branches, they're like extra big
They're big trees
They say if you get tangled in all those small and big
branches you can't get out from them by yourself
They were looking around there and they're like "hey where is he? Is he in the fields?"
"Look up that tree, look at it!"
They were like "Aaaah we're all gonna die"
"All our parents, all our kids, are gonna die! Quick!"
And lots of people here and there in the village,
they died, they were dying
It was Summer break and I really
wanted to spend time outside
But I didn't want to be alone outside
If I only happened to see a shadow on the ground
Like, if I walk I'd be like "woah, am I gonna get attacked?"
Like, I felt it in my heart and even if my feet would feel itchy
I felt like someone has always been
stare-stare-stare-starin' at me
I was so scared, that town--- mama told me
"Get back home as soon as possible, get safe inside"
The end
What the--!?
The hell was that story about?!
"The end" was so sudden
Really unexpected
Lots of people saw that too
I'm speechless
Listen to me, Hamada
Yes?
If you ask some
They would reply that they did see it for real.
You know? On the countryside we have these trees
They're like
Big horse heads shining like diamonds
So I got back home and was like "woah, uhg! I can't ohhhh"
Once again: what the hell are you sayin'?
We don't have much time left, mr. Alif
It's time to go
Yeah, right
This can't even count as a spin-off
We barely got anything out of his story
Here are the scary stories told by our six guests
300kmh fast granny
Bangladesh
China - Hong Kong
Don't turn around
Egypt
Ghost Lady Pori
Guinea
Nigeria
Tearoom Catering
U.S.A.
White Dwarf
Yellow Ribbon
Now they'll decide which one told the scariest one
Lastly
Keep in mind that the winner
we pick, the one with the scariest story
Will tell us the same story in their mother tongue
Mother tongue?
Mother tongue? Why?
Are we in hell?
I'm sorry for Ike, I really liked his story
But he's from the U.S.A., so in english...
Yeah, I know
We would sorta understand, more or less
Yeah, that's it
What do you think?
How about our last guest then?
It has to be him
What do you think about Mr. Alif?
But we barely understood anything
An incredible original language scary story!
Coming up
True
INTERMISSION // CREDITS
TRANSLATION BY SHION (FGRNDNOISES)
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FANSUB MADE BY FANS FOR OTHER FANS. NO COPYRIGHT INFRINGMENT INTENDED. ALL COPYRIGHTS ARE RESERVED TO ORIGINAL OWNERS.
USEFUL LINKS:
twitter: @FGRNDNoises
FB (info / updates): fb.com/shionnotsukai
more episodes: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
donations: patreon.com/shionnotsukai & ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
PLEASE DONT CALL THE COPS lol
Alif, our representative from Bangladesh
"Ghost Lady Pori" in his mother tongue
Alif, Bangladesh Representative, will now tell us his story
Will now narrate us his scary story in his mother tongue
His voice comes from his throat
You can tell
kou yatte... [in bangladesh]
like this...
[in Japanese] people died like this
Japanese...?
He switched into Japanese
Oh, my bad
I'm sorry, I've been living here in Japan for so long...
I know I'm talking about my country
Just hold it down!
I even end up speaking it when talking to my mother, I'm sorry
You should have wrote it down beforehand, come on
I'm sorry about that
Does your mind switches to Japanese when you think?
It does!
It's a real story, so of course I'm gonna switch
It's so obvious
I've been in Japan more than in my home country
I'm here since the Showa period
Showa?!
That long?!
That's a long ago
That's why I didn't get some words he said
That's right