Ya know, I heard Endo's having trouble
- Really?
Gaki no Tsukai's dressing room
That's not true, I've never been so happy at home as I'm now
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
It's too early for that
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
How can you say that in front of Tanaka, huh?
It's fine, it's fine
Cocorico
He's right  - I'm fine with it
Tanaka Naoki
Have you seen the poster for ZIP!?
"Your morning laughs", it says
Inside the balloon behind him  - The speech balloon, right?
Makin' my debut on ZIP!
Your morning laughs
every thursday!
Poster for ZIP!
Stop it! Please stop  - Are you ok?
Maybe you should wear more colored shirts
- Right, he's always so bright and stuff
What's your deal?
- Excuse me
Huh? What now?  - Can I...?
Komurasaki Kozo
Producer
Hosei told me he wants to do a rehearsal and asked me to call you there
Ah...
I hate him so much!!
After all these years of friendship?  - I've hated him for years
Do you hate him?  - Yes, no doubt about it
Is that so?
Why, you like him?
Well, it's our senpai...  - Well...
Do you?
It's their senior, after all
- That's right
Do you like him?
Me?
I feel nothing
I see
What I mean is that you know him better
- It's different, it's cause they don't hang out much together
And you, Komu? You like him?
Yeah, it's been decades
Me too, I don't think much of him...
It's settled then, this is pointless
- He's right
You should like him to be here
- Whatever, for now just come with me
That's natural
Come with me, please
- Let's talk about this issue
Ehh? Really?
- But I hate him...
Sorry
- Even Komu...
He doesn't like him either
- I thought he did
He should have said that at least
- Yeah, I'm kind of shocked about it
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
MORE EPISODES: SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FOR UPDATES: FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
FOR DONATIONS: KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
EARLY ACCESS TO SUBBED CONTENT & SOFTSUBS, UPLOAD SCHEDULE
AND MORE TO COME BY BECOMING A PATRON ON PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
Downtown's
Gaki no Tsukai
ya Arahende!
What's behind this?
- Please, get in
Here
He looks pissed
- Oh my
Oh boy oh boy
Look at his pissed off face
Is he angry or something?
God, you're right
This looks shady
Really
'Morning
Morning...
- 'Morning
Good morning
What a soft voice!
What's wrong?
It's not a matter of what's wrong or not  - Yes?
It's been 5 years, you know!
As you know, "genius producer" is what I've been called
I'm talking about music
Music?  - Yes, music
Oh, is that so...
- Well, it's true that now and then he worked on it
One way or another
- Yeah, that's true
Countless masterpieces
were given birth to by him!
Tsukitei Hosei: our talented self-taught genius producer who composed several masterpieces!
Genius music producer
Tsukitei Hosei
Clanging so violently ♪
It's the watchman of time ♪
Alongside the chosen ones ♪
Holding the door-opening crimson key ♪
Let it be, let it be ♪
I'm not giving up until I'll grasp the truth  ♪
The sparkling stars are way beyond the reach of our hands ♪
But regardless, they'll eventually enshroud our weak selves ♪
After 5 years, he's working on a new song!
And after 5 years, today he's blessing us with a new song!
CDs aren't sold as much anymore in this era, Yama-chan
So you've noticed it, huh? Good point
You're aiming at making a CD out of this?
Of course
This a graph covering the last 10 years
Of CnD sales...
Did he stutter?
Cindy Lauper?
Did you say "Cindy"?
Cindy Lauper...?
You mean Cindy Lauper's CDs?
I meant to say "C-D"
"CD", ok?
Sure, got it
As you can see it's been sinking down on the last 10 years
Well, that's true
A lot, really
Why do you think they don't sell?
It's 'cuz no one's makin' good songs anymore!!
Eh? But that's not true...  - You think so?
- One you can enjoy with your family
My idea of a good song
A song which anyone can enjoy, they're no more!!
Alright then, let's do this!!
- Come on
I surely didn't expect that
Please, hate on me!!
Don't treat me well, how can we joke about this?!
But I told you I want to do it!
That's not it-- joke around some more!
Shove more jokes on my face, guys
- Yeah but... yes
A change of pace is nice too sometimes, right?
Whatever man, let's set that aside
What I want to say is...
Yes?
It was such a nice answer, right?
It was
We're five, ok?
- Yes
There are 5 member on Gaki no Tsukai
- Yeah, 5 Gaki members
What's another team made of 5 incredible comedians you know?
Is there anyone else?  - Yes, who?
5 people...?
- Mhh...
It's the Drifters, you silly!!
Ohh, right, right  - Right?
And I think that we're all
We're the same as them, really
It's a coincidence
Are we?
We are, yes, that too
Even as characters?
You think so? We and them...
- I think we do
Matsumoto is Shimura, no doubt
Shimura Ken
Then we have Tanaka, he's Nakamoto
Nakamoto Kouji? I see
Nakamoto Kouji
Yes, Nakamoto Kouji
Yeah, like a slim version of him
I thought I was gonna be him
Yeah, me too
Endo is Kato, his face even looks like his
Katou Cha
Wait a sec, hey
- Yes?
Are ya sayin' I'm Buu?
Takagi Buu
It doesn't really fit him
Well, I'm Ikariya, so...
Ikariya Choukai
I thought you were picking the leader, so...
- Of course
But why should I be Buu?
- But
That's how it went, it's one for each one
- What's wrong with that?
Buu doesn't do shit!
That's not true
- No way
He's cool, he did a lot of stuff
- That's not true, he did "Almighty Thunder"
You shouldn't say that
He's right
That's true
He's good at ukulele too
He's doing it on purpose!
He's a great ukulele player
Oh, right, I remember that
I knew you were picking the leader!
Of course I'm Ikariya, that's out of the question
Now that we're good with each character...
Don't you think we should consider not doing "No Laughing" at the end of the year?
I agree
Right?
That---
I really think so
If you don't deny that too, I'm...
- I don't know what to say
But it's true, I'm saying I agree
What should I--- I mean, now
We have to make our way to NHK
Ah, you mean Kohaku?
KOHAKU: NHK's New Year's Even singing contest
Kohaku? We should take part in it, that's the best plan!!
Ahh! Nice!
If we can manage to sell the CD, that is  - True
That's the best reason to do it, isn't it?
It is
It's what we should aim for
Yeah--
- We don't want to be backstage, right?
That's right, that's why we gotta do something about it
It figures...
Sure, sure
What's going on here?
Now, let's try to get a clearer picture
Listen to a song by The Drifters, to get the idea
- It's like this
There are a whole bunch of them
I don't think young people know much about them
I think I know them
I know some of them
I think you know this one
Drift's Zundoko-bushi
Here it goes
Zun zun zun zun zun zun zun zun ♪
Yes, I know this one
It's famous
In the forest shadow on the way home from school...
This is Katou Cha  - Yep, it's Katou
She ran after me and gave me a smooch
It's Katou
It was a precocious girl wearing an uniform
I've never really listened to it that well
How could I ever forget her sweet kiss?
You hear them go "SORE!", right?
We're doing it all together, of course
Well, it's just one chorus
Did you get the picture, more or less?
Yeah but, it's confined to its own era...
Is this ok?
No way
Did you make a song based off this song's vibe?
Actually yes, I did!
I also wrote the lyrics
- Oh, nice
Haven't they-- worked on them together?
And here they are
- Whoa, that's something!
Alright, Tanaka! Read the title on top for everyone
Oh, ok
"Heisei Era Pa-Pi-Pu-Pe-Po Folk Song", by "The GakistarZ"
That's right!
Is that our band name?
Yes, "The GakistarZ"
The GakistarZ...
Are you for real?
I'm not kidding
Listen, ok?
- Yeah
As you can see, it's all split up
Yes, it's made of few parts
- Not only that
Is the first one a sushi chef's line?
Oh, he's right  - That's right
Gettin' all my clients with the rotation sushi
Aimin' for the mature-sushi boom
I've matured my dishes, and even my rice
And yet you got food poisoning? (pa-pa)
And a tear rolled down my cheek (pa-pa)
The hell?! You only got wasabi in your eye!
m 0 0 l -30 0 l -30 15 l 30 15 l 30 0 l 0 0
"Catchin' clients with rotating sushi, aimin' for a the freshness boom"
"Improved my rice & dishes, but you still got food poisoning!"
Pa-pa!
- We're all doing this "pa-pa" together
Are you kidding me...
And then "and a tear rolled down my cheek, pa-pa!"
He's explaining too much stuff
"A tear rolled down" comes in every part
A tear rolled down my cheek (pa-pa)
On this part, make it sound sorrowful
And then "The hell?!"
"You only got wasabi in your eye!" - like this
The hell?! You only got wasabi in your eye!
Do we have to shout here?
- Yes, "The hell?!"
This is embarrassing
- "You only got wasabi in your eye!"
"You imbecil!!" - like this
I don't see that anywhere
Me neither
"You imbecil!!" is something I came up with, but same tone
Pa-pa!
- We have to shout "pa-pa" together
What's the deal with this "pa-pa!!" thing?
I've been wondering the same
You've been repeating it but it's not clear
- What's the meaning of this?
It's important to have it
Oh, but it's pi-pi later on
Oh, you're right  - It's pi-pi
The next line is about a school kid
Elementary
schooler
Kids my age are always criticized
I got more lessons to attend,
it's such a burden
Stress at school is so horrible
And now my tummy aches (pi-pi)
And a tear rolled down my cheek
(pi-pi)
Mom! I got a 100 on math's test!
- That's what Miyo-chan said!
pi-pi
m 0 0 l -30 0 l -30 15 l 30 15 l 30 0 l 0 0
"The test gives me stress, my tummy aches"
And then it goes "pi-pi", it's connected
- Ok, got it
And again, "a tear rolled down", "pi-pi"
And then "Mom! I got a 100 on math's test!"
"That's what Miyo-chan said...!"
Do we have to say it like that?
This is no fun at all!
May I ask something?
Do we really have to say it like that?
Alright, moving on...
He ignored you
Now
In this part we have a buddhist monk
A monk, ok
This one's a bit tricky
Buddhist monk
The number of old people is
increasing, but funerals are not
And I'm getting older by the day
My sight is getting worse,
can't even read sutras
And I have a congestion (pe-pe)
And a tear rolled down my cheek
(pe-pe)
This is the real... grandparanoia!!
pe-pe
m 0 0 l -30 0 l -30 15 l 30 15 l 30 0 l 0 0
"Old people are increasing,
but funerals are not", it's quick
Too many words
"And I'm getting older myself,
can't see well, can't ever read sutras"
Is this a song?
Yeah, where's the music?
Hey, should you really be singing?
"I have a congestion and..."
You're not supposed to--
Are you sure?
There's no music
No music you say...
Yeah, yeah, whatever
No way, man
- Can't we just read it?
Pay attention to this part
- I think we kind of get it
It goes like this in here, and then "pe-pe"
"Congestion?"
Again, "A tear roled down, pe-pe"
Buddhist monk
The number of old people is
increasing, but funerals are not
And I'm getting older by the day
My sight is getting worse,
can't even read sutras
And I have a congestion (pe-pe)
And a tear rolled down my cheek
(pe-pe)
This is the real... grandparanoia!!
pe-pe
m 0 0 l -30 0 l -30 15 l 30 15 l 30 0 l 0 0
"This is... the real... grandparanoia?!"
You're laughing so much!
What's the meaning of "the real"?!
Is this the real deal?
- That's right, the grandparanoia
'Cause he's like a grandpa now
And this is the final hook
"But we'll live,
and the Sun will rise again"
But we'll live, and the
sun will rise again
No matter how many tears
ovverflow
Let's keep on smilin' and walkin'
pa-pa
Final hook
m 0 0 l -30 0 l -30 15 l 30 15 l 30 0 l 0 0
"No matter how many tears ovverflow"
Ovver...?
- "Ovverflow"?
"Let's keep on smilin' and walkin', pa-pa"
- "...and walkin', pa-pa"...
This is frightening
Yeah, I agree...
Alright then...
How are we...
I shouldn't have come today
How are we splitting this up? I mean, the parts
He's right
I've kept you waiting enough, your parts:
Sushi chef: Hamada
First we have the sushi chef
And that's Hamada, we're counting on you
Sushi chef: Hamada
Nice
Matsumoto will be the monk
Whaaat?
Buddhist monk: Matsumoto
Yes, so make sure to focus on that "grandparanoia"
No way...
It's gonna crack everyone up
That part?
The "grandparanoia" thing?
- If no one's gonna laugh at that...
If no one's gonna laugh at that, it means it's your fault
Buddhist monk
Elementary
schooler
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Housewife
Matsumoto
Sushi chef
Tanaka
Taxi driver
Hosei will be the elementary schooler,
Endo the taxi driver, and Tanaka the housewife.
Alright, let's listen to the music first, come on!
Listen now, here comes the orchestra
Sounds like a parade
- True
It's a fanfare
- Yes
And now what?
I'm confused
- Which genre is this...?
The intro is pretty long
- Yeah...
Gettin' all my clients with the rotation sushi
Huh?
Ah, it started
Aimin' for the mature-sushi boom
I've matured my dishes, and even my rice
And yet you got food poisoning?! (pa-pa)
Pa-pa! Alll together
Ah, this part
And a tear rolled down my cheek (pa-pa)
"The Hell?! You only got wasabi in your eye"
LINE
Pa-pa!
Was there a pa-pa in here?
Pa-pa
Yes  - Ah, here it is
Yeah it's--
It's not immediate
That's right
If I say that too early...  - That's not ok
Song practice: full immersion
The 5 members immediately start to practice
But we'll live, and the Sun will rise again ♪
No matter how many tears overflow
let's keep on smilin' and walkin' pa-pa ♪
Let's keep on smilin' and walkin' pa-pa ♪
Alright, I'm done with this!
- This sucks
Wait, we can't --
This is enough
Good job guys
No need for that
Call me a cab, would you?
A taxi, please!  - Can we go now?
I'm done here
- Please, I beg you
What the hell is this?
Come on
What is this?!
It's hard to sing and even harder to listen to!!
That's 'cause you have to feel it
You think so?
- It takes some time, you'll get it
Shocking! Hamada's secret wig!!
This is seriously scary  - This isn't ok
Buddhist monk
Elementary kid
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Housewife
Matsumoto
Sushi chef
Tanaka
Taxi driver
Housei's original song is aiming to take over Kohaku!!
With Hosei's song, they'll aim to take part in Kohaku
MV filming prep:
various costumes ready to be used
Now, they'll choose the outfit for the music video's filming
Hamada!
What?
Here
These aren't wigs for a sushi chef
Sushi Chef Clothes
Yeah, they usually have shorter hair
Right
Well, there are many types in there
But they're all long!
- No way
Stop complaining, come on
Think about the housewife and the taxi driver inside your head
Too many hairs, it's filthy
Counting on you guys
I'm done here
Alright then, Matsumoto come out please!
Buddhist Monk
Matsumoto's part
You've done it
I've done what?
You caught its essence
What are you talking about?
- Feels like you're the real deal
No way
It's perfect on you!
It's really good, I swear
You look like a monk of high virtue
You think so?
What about the wig? Do we really need it?
Can you take that wig off for a second?
Ah
Not bad even without it
It's not bad, but...
Doesn't this...
Seem a little bit like Townwork to you?
Nah, that's not true  - You think?
Next up is Endo's Taxi Driver
Endo's part
Taxi Driver
Housewife
Tanaka's part
Tanaka shows up dressed as an housewife
And last but not least...
Hamada!! Please come out!!
Hamada's part
Sushi Chef
I told you...
Is there any sushi chef like this?
That's one of a kind
- He's got a point
Going like "Welcome!" or such
- Not really
I'm tired of looking at that wig, but it's still hilarious
Right
We still laugh at it every New Year  - Really, it's a classic
But I don't think it's really a good choice...
What?
Is it not?  - To be blunt
Sorry but, huh...
But... look, they're all too long
I'm a sushi chef you know
He's right  - Not very clean
Bring me that
This is too much
This one
Try this one  - Ah, Kenji Sawada style...
That classic wig is so natural on Hamada now
You think so?
Well, that's--
I've never seen a sushi chef like this
We've got to see it so many times
That's true
Holy cow
I swear...
Every wig looks incredible on him
That's right, it makes me jealous  - That's a talent
This doesn't feel right
I personally like it  - Maybe if you go to the countryside...
It feels dirty!!
Maybe that's how they look
On the countryside? Like this?!
I bet there are
Making sushi like this?
It's not impossible, you know
This can't be good, come on
I don't think it's the best choice, though...
I mean
Bring me a crew-cut wig, please!!
Try this one on, first
One more
Different wigs, same shit
Make sure to wear it
The staff gathered them all for you...
What the fuck is this?!
Definitely not this one
Terrifying
However you put it, this feels strange
It is, actually
So filthy...
Yeah, feels dirty  - Maybe, with the hat...
Try to put the hat on
Doesn't feel clean at all  - Maybe it's gonna make things better
I don't think it's gonna change anything
Isn't it good?
How about a small ponytail on the back?
Ah! Nice idea
It's gonna change a lot like this
- Like that, yes
Why not give me a short-haired wig to begin with?!
This isn't bad, let's keep it
What's the point of having them long?!
You mean like this?
Yes, like that
It's not bad  - It's the best we can get, I think
It's finally time to film the music video!!
Give me a break...  - Let's go with that
Alright, guys
- Yes?
We're doing a choreography
First off, take a look at this set
Yes
I spent 20 million yen on this!
Really?!  - Yes
20 million?
- That's right, 20 million
I can think of many other ways to spend that amount
Yeah...  - Unbelievable
Alright, follow me
Watch your step
I'm wearing a kimono and everything...
Right, that's no easy task
Ok
I've already decided the order
Tanaka is on the left side
Sure
It's Tanaka...
- Ok
Then, it's Endo...
I see, it's the colors...
Oh, right
- It's our colors
And I'm here, in the middle
Why do you have to take the best spot, huh?
The center  - He's the leader, so...
That's right, he's the boss
But he's the least popular one here
So, we'll draw back here
We have to be here first
- He completely ignored you
Huh? What? Why?
For the entrance?
That's right
Please start the music so we can practice
Here goes
Look, we got a huge audience in front of us
Thank you for coming
Thank you so muuuuuch!
Thanks, everyone!
Thanks for being here!
Yes!
Make sure to smile to our audience
Stop right there!!
- Here!
We'll stop here, on the 4th step
That's right
- You didn't tell us
Ok, now let's move down
He never said that before
There are a lot of people in front of us
People...?
Even over there, you see them?
Are they?
- Alright!
Just start singing already!!
Can you explain us...?
What are we doing?
I have no clue
I don't know what we're doing
Which part of this is a song?!
I have no idea  - Yeah, the music already started...
And I have no idea why he keeps on
talking about the audience
I have no idea!
Housei shows the choreography to the others
Hosei displays his choreography so the others can follow it
This is completely absurd
- Everything is absurd at this point
And then...
Alright, time for the real deal!!
The real deal?!
Really?
- The real deal already?
Ok
Let's keep on smilin' and walkin' pa-pa ♪
Filming the real deal
Ok, good
staff
Aw man...
Time to take a look at the complete music video!!
Enough is enough
Genius music producer
Tsukitei Hosei
Tsukitei Hosei, the genius who gave birth
to countless musical masterpieces
text
I would have laughed at it, if it was a dream ♪
Facing my enemies, only those who block my way ♪
Carrying my cross, with my sword of glass ♪
Aimin' at his heart, lock in down, hi!! ♪
Now I can honestly say it ♪
"Thank you"
Your smile is everything I need ♪
Thank you ♪
A gum is holding us all together ♪
"Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende!!"
A 5-colored fresh chewing gum ♪
Matsumoto ♪ Hamada ♪ Yamazaki ♪
Cocorico ♪ Tanaka ♪ Endo ♪
And now it's finally time for a new music video! Will it be even better than the previous ones?
And now a new music video will be revealed!!
Alright, we've completed "Heisei Era Pa-Pi-Pu-Pe-Po Folk Song" 's MV
That was quick!!
Really, too quick
- Yeah
It's a record
But I don't feel any sense of accomplishment
I agree
None at all  - Doesn't feel like it
So, are we watching it?
- You sure it's ok?
I think it's fine, yes
Alright, roll the tape, please!
Pa-Pi-Pu-Pe-Po
Oh, is that how it looked?
The set isn't bad-- what the?
Oh please...
Here we are
Heisei Era's Pa-Pi-Pu-Pe-Po Folk Song
The GakistarZ
We all look dirty
And I'm the dirtiest
All of us?
Gettin' all my clients with the rotation sushi ♪
Aimin' for the mature-sushi boom ♪
I've matured my dishes, and even my rice ♪
And yet you got food poisoning?! (pa-pa) ♪
And a tear rolled down my cheek (pa-pa) ♪
The hell?! You only got wasabi in your eye!
Pa-pa ♪
The pa-pa is nice
Kids my age are always criticized ♪
You were almost late!
He's right
- Producer!
I got more lessons to attend, it's such a burden ♪
- You were kinda late
This isn't ok
Stress at school is so horrible ♪
No no, that was part
of the character
And now my tummy aches (pi-pi) ♪
And a tear rolled down my cheek (pi-pi) ♪
"Mom! I got a 100 on math's test!" - that's what Miyo-chan said!!
Pi-pi ♪
Everyone's following
My base fare has been lowered ♪
We're all fighting to get our clients ♪
So I started giving away candies for free ♪
And everyone start thinking I'm a weirdo (pu-pu) ♪
And a tear rolled down my cheek (pu-pu) ♪
Don't chew me out! Chew on the candy instead!
Pu-pu ♪
I don't get this
This is embarrassing...
- What is this?
- It's embarrassing
This is... a plane?
- Of course you're not
I wasn't even smiling
The number of old people is increasing, but funerals are not ♪
And I'm getting older by the day ♪
My sight is getting worse, can't even read sutras ♪
And I have a congestion (pe-pe) ♪
And a tear rolled down my cheek (pe-pe) ♪
This is the real... grandparanoia!!
Pe-pe ♪
- I don't get it
He had to do it
I love seeing all these love affairs on TV shows ♪
And so I went to a class reunion ♪
And then this fat bald guy tried to hit on me ♪
What's this?!
Seriously...
I felt my body burning up inside (po-po) ♪
And a tear rolled down my cheek (po-po) ♪
Darling? Tonight you're getting a special treat ♥
Po-po ♪
But we'll live, and the sun will rise again ♪
This sounds awful
What the hell is this...
No matter how many tears ovverflow ♪
Let's keep on smilin' and walkin'... pa-pa ♪
Seriously...
What was that?
This is the stupidest
thing in so long
It was so good!
Was it?
- It was really good
Are you sure?
- Yeah, aside from the song
You put a great effort in it, well done
Are we, like, uploading this on Youtube?
We'll have a nationwide release for it
Nationwide?
- Yes
Only Japan..? Not the whole world?
- Well, can't blame him
On Youtube just for us?
- Japan only?
Why Japan-only if it's on Youtube?
- Not worldwide?
No, nationwide
- Nationwide? Japan only?
The world will never see it
Oh my
The entire world could see it on Youtube...
- Now that I've seen it I don't know anymore
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
MORE EPISODES: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
FACEBOOK: fb.com/shionnotsukai
TWITTER: twitter.com/shionnotsukai
KO-FI: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
PATREON: patreon.com/shionnotsukai
get early access to subs by subscribing to my patreon!
or donate on ko-fi to support / motivate me to do more