The First Annual Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende, Chiki Chiki
So loud...
Let's Shoot a Music Video with a Drone!!
So about today-
Today's Plan
Use a drone to shoot a music video in a single take
m 87 915 l 1836 915 1836 1024.5 87 1024.5
So apparently, we're going to use a drone and shoot a music video in one take
That's correct
Inamoto
Takafumi
Endo
Shozo
Fujiwara
Kazuhiro
Hamada
Masatoshi
Matsumoto
Hitoshi
So, License's Fujiwara has...
Tanaka
Naoki
Tsukitei
Hosei
m 1 833 l 1917 833 1917 1053 1 1053
awakened as a drone
He awakened?
I guess, yes, I have
Fujiwara is going to operate the drone to shoot the video in
one take
Just one take?
Yes
2 weeks before the shoot
Damn, that's small!
This?
That's right
Narrator:
Yamada Shinichi
Micro-Drone
Fujiwara will use one of the smallest drones around: a micro-drone
-
A small camera inside
WEIGHT - 70 Grams
m 78 873 l 1201.5 873 1201.5 1030.5 78 1030.5
Weighing only 70 grams, it has a small embedded camera
Fujiwara will be able to see what the drone is seeing via a headset
Control without the use of the headset
First, he will practice without the use of a headset
I barely moved my finger at all just now
Drone Racer
Erinnu
It's a really sensitive machine
that will respond to the slightest push
So I have to get used to
how sensitive the controls are
It really just hit me that I'm going to have practice a lot
To control the Drone for the shoot, his training begins!
From this day, in order to control the drone, he began training
Third day of training
Yoshimoto HQ
To practice, he used locations with plenty of open space, like Yoshimoto's HQ...
Fifth day of training
Takatsu Dojo
and even a karate dojo where Fujiwara trains in his free time
He committed to his training
7th day of training
From the seventh day, when he got the hang of operating the drone,
he started training with the headset on
Are you getting the hang of it?
STAFF
m 324 843 l 550.5 843 550.5 901.5 324 901.5
I think I've mastered the basics
10th day of training
When he wasn't working, he spent all his time training
His control of the drone improved
Yep, nice!
Fujiwara's first time using a drone
Will he succeed in shooting a one-take music video?
TL - mickstar813
TS - Bipedal
So, what song are we using?
Yes, about that...
'Okuru Kotoba'
Kaitentai's
And since the song is actually quite long,
if it were just you guys, we'd be lacking in numbers...
so we've invited some special guests today
Big time guests?
Of course they are, so if the big-time guests would like to come out now, please!
Shinagawa Shoji
Bobby Ologun
Football Hour
Fujiwara
Haranishi
Takayuki
Iwao
Nozomu
Shoji
Tomoharu
m 0 859.5 l 1920 859.5 1920 1050 0 1050
They aren't shit!!
I thought he was going to joke like: "They're not big!" but then he shouted:
"They aren't shit!"
Right then, now we're going to go around so you understand the course the drone is going to take
so please follow me inside
1st
Floor
2nd
Classroom
Entrance
Grounds
Library
Staff Room
Stairs
Toilet
m 109.5 265.5 l 312 265.5 312 331.5 109.5 331.5
m 1203 546 l 1330.5 546 1330.5 594 1203 594
m 1504.5 420 l 1629 420 1629 469.5 1504.5 469.5
m 1504.5 573 l 1663.5 573 1663.5 627 1504.5 627
m 1756.5 877.5 l 1846.5 877.5 1846.5 937.5 1756.5 937.5
m 592.5 703.5 l 685.5 703.5 685.5 753 592.5 753
m 696 873 l 789 873 789 937.5 696 937.5
m 940.5 634.5 l 1054.5 634.5 1054.5 682.5 940.5 682.5
HAMADA
m 978 688.5 l 1113 688.5 1113 741 978 741
SHOJI
m 1212 660 l 1294.5 660 1294.5 706.5 1212 706.5
First, the individual parts they will sing
HARANISHI
m 1398 612 l 1449 612 1449 772.5 1398 772.5
IWAO
m 1542 477 l 1624.5 477 1624.5 522 1542 522
MATSUMOTO
m 456 532.5 l 642 532.5 642 583.5 456 583.5
ENDO
m 693 633 l 774 633 774 675 693 675
TANAKA
m 424.5 735 l 553.5 735 553.5 786 424.5 786
BOBBY
m 1504.5 702 l 1620 702 1620 750 1504.5 750
HOSEI
m 312 672 l 396 672 396 718.5 312 718.5
We start on the second floor classroom, where Hamada will be
INOMOTO
m 189 475.5 l 325.5 475.5 325.5 528 189 528
Hamada-san,
this is the classroom
You will be inside here
I will?
Yes, and then
the drone will enter from this door over here
The drone will come through here like this
You'll be dressed up as Kinpachi-sensei, and behind you
there is the character for "human"
HAMADA
Teaching in Class
So you're teaching the students about what that character means
And please look directly at the drone whilst you sing
It's okay to look directly at the drone?
Yes, that's fine
And I sing "Okuru Kotoba~?"
Around that point,
the drone will move again
I see, so that will just go off on it's own
This door here will be closed
The drone will pass through here
Don't try that!
Isn't this a really tight space?
There's no lesson where the door is open
If you're going to say that,
there's no lesson where drones are flying through the classroom!!
Shoji
Telling off student in corridor
Next the drone passes Shoji, who is telling off a student in the corridor
Haranishi
Sticking a piece of paper on his back
Then it films a scene where Haranishi is getting pranked by another student
"Gorilla"
Grading a test in the staff room
Iwao
It comes into the staff room
and goes past Iwao, who is grading a test
Name:
Hamada Masatoshi
The drone goes to the first floor, where Matsumoto is
Then the drone leaves the staff room
and goes to the first floor, where Matsumoto awaits
So here it comes, it's coming down...
Yes, it will come right down here
And it will come here in front of you
I see
It will go around you,
Matsumoto
sings by the shoe lockers
so if you could turn with the drone
"Owari madde kiitte~"
As he sings, right?
And keep singing whilst you turn
"Okuru Kotoba~"
Just like that
About one full turn
Yep, around one turn
So wait, what am I meant to be doing here?
Everyone so far has been doing something
What on earth am I doing here?
You're just overseeing things
Like the shoe lockers...
Just overseeing everything-
Isn't there a better role for me?
I'm just standing here, overseeing things?
But this is where things get really exciting
It's a great role, right?
It's coming from above and all
Endo
Finds a love letter in his shoe locker
The drone then films Endo discovering a love letter in his shoe locker,
Dancing on the stairs
Tanaka
and goes past Tanaka dancing on the stairs to the second floor
Bobby
Bobby getting kancho'd
It films Bobby getting kancho'd by a student,
then back to the first floor
And in the interlude...
It's now coming back down again
and right here, using this line here:
Matsumoto-san, Hamada-san,
Shoji-san, Haranishi-san
you will be jumping rope here
Interlude
Matsumoto, Hamada, Haranishi, and Shoji skipping
Downtown will be in between here and you will both be jumping
You're just jumping rope
So when the drone comes, we are just jumping rope here?
That's correct, this is the interlude
If the rope catches my leg,
that's not going to affect anything, right?
No, then we re-do the whole thing...
Come on, let's not do that
This is serious, suddenly
Do we really need to do this?
Before, I was just overseeing things here
Now I'm here jumping rope?
What kind of person am I?
I don't get my character!
Coming out of the toilet
Hosei
The drone passes Hosei coming out of the toilet
Inomoto
Kicks the soccer ball
and films Inomoto kicking the soccer ball away
And then the music video is done
Right then, let's do it!!
Good luck all!
Right then everyone, I'm going to start now
so please be ready
Right, got you!
Yup!
Good luck guys!
Shut up!
Of course you'd react like that
I'm starting up the drone now
Fail, and they must restart. The one shot music video
Will they succeed?!
I'm starting up the drone now
Fail, and they must restart. The one shot music video
Finally, the shoot begins!
Here we go then, counting down from five:
four,
three,
two...
Okuru Kotoba
In the light and shadows of the town at sunset
I give you these words as you go away
Instead of hiding your sadness and faking a smile
It’s better to cry until your tears dry up
The more sadness a person experiences
The more they're able to be kind to others
It’s too sad to just say goodbye
So I give these words to you, my love
They’re interrupted by the twilight breeze
But please listen to the end, these words I give to you
Instead of being upset that you can’t trust anyone
It’s better to take a chance and get hurt
Don’t ask for kindness
That’s a cowards excuse
For you, my first love
I give you these unembellished words
The rope, the rope, the rope!
Shit, it's coming, it's already here, we're way too late!
We're way too late, shit!
We were way too late!
In this new life you are about to begin
Someone will probably love you
But there is no one who will
Love you as deeply as I do
Your receding shadow disappears into the crowd
No longer do they reach you, my words to you
Success on the first attempt!
Amazingly, he manages to complete it on his first go
Hello, sir!
Kinpachi-sensei, hello sir
He was dressed as the janitor
Takeda Tetsuya
And as a surprise guest: Takeda Tetsuya himself!
Man, you get really nervous doing this, eh?
I wish you would have gone a bit higher at the end, though!
It ran out of battery, right?
Right? It fell at the end
Yes, there was no more battery left
Oh I see
How was it?
I was watching until just before
the skipping and it was pretty good
The skipping part was a bit...
Didn't you go past Shoji-san a bit too quick?
You literally got no screen time at all there
Seriously?!
I tried to look into the camera and sing but it just
flew off!
Can we watch this now?
Shall we have a look?
I think Takeda-san should also come and have a look
They watch the recorded footage from the drone
That's nice
I like the angle
That's good
It's really good
He's made Hamada
look really good
Right?
He looks good
Yeah he doesn't
look bad, eh?
This is
Shoji-san's part
He hasn't started
singing yet...
It's way too fast!
It flew past so quick!!
It flew past way too quick!
You've screwed up a little here...
I still don't get
what I'm doing
What the hell
am I doing?
Why are you
standing there?
I mean...
You know...
Not bad
Here, right?
See, the rope
isn't there
The jump rope!
It's still not there!
Oh damn, so close!
We finally start here
You didn't jump
over it at all!
You haven't
managed that at all
Hamada-san didn't even try to jump
I think we should all
be here with him
Look at us walking
out slowly
Right?
We're just coming out, relaxed
We should run to where he is
Damn, I wish the
camera stayed
for a bit longer there
Come on
you can do it!
Come on, a bit more!
It's too low,
it's way too low
We need to start skipping quicker
Rather than worry about getting the rope out quickly
You should focus on learning how to jump rope
Who cares about that part!
What should we do about Kimura-sensei's part?
Shall we run to get there quicker?
I think you should run, and then we can sing it together
If you have any other comments, say them now
To Fujiwara...
Could you make sure the drone
focuses on me for a bit longer?
I'm sorry, I was panicking a little bit
I was just thinking about Haranishi-san after that
And what was going on with Hosei's part?
The fact he came out a bit late pissed me off
Like a "master performer"
Don't build it up
What you mean by that?
I was just doing it when the staff told me to
Right then, shall we
do it again?
I think we can do this
Amazing
You can get this good just practicing for 2 weeks, huh?
You know
If he properly masters this
we're going to be doing a B'z song next
"Ultra Soul" for sure
Sorry, everybody
I will correct
the mish-
the mistakes I made
No way...
I wonder if he'll be okay,
this is going to start eating him up
He needs to get it right here
2nd Challenge
To try and get a perfect take, this is the second challenge, but...
FAILURE
Hey man...
I'm sorry
When it entered the classroom, it banged as well
It's no good if it hits something like that though, right?
No
No, it's no good
It properly crashed before
How is it going?
How are you feeling about this?
Just as I calculated
That's no good
What kind of calculations were you making?
Don't use those calculations
3rd Challenge
They try a third time
FAILURE
We are stopping there!
Is the window open?
STAFF
Was the wind strong?
m 82.5 688.5 l 295.5 688.5 295.5 741 82.5 741
Apparently, there's a window open on the second floor
STAFF
m 88.5 195 l 298.5 195 298.5 249 88.5 249
Could you please close it?
Oh I see, the wind?
Here come Fujiwara's excuses
Right? He wasn't saying that earlier...
All of a sudden, he's starting to moan
4th Challenge
And then, the fourth challenge
We're getting it all-
Okay, that was good!
However, even though they made it to the staff room,
The drone didn't hover in front of Iwao
Sorry, but we're stopping here
With that, 3 failures in a row!
Now, he has failed three times in a row
So, was that first take
just a miracle?
Maybe we're not going to be able to do this again
During the rehearsal, he didn't make
Staff
m 363 729 l 595.5 729 595.5 786 363 786
this many mistakes
Oh really?!
He sucks under pressure
I know
What's he doing?
He sucked in the M1 final too
He's so up and down
5th Challenge up next! Will he succeed?!
He really is
All over the place, right?
License's Fujiwara
Using a drone, shoot "Okuru Kotoba" in one take
5th Challenge
Good!
He got through
Good
He's good
The drone goes to the staff room, where things went wrong before...
...then it gets to the part which Fujiwara says is the most important:
Matsumoto's part
The Drone gets to the last part
With no major mistakes, the drone gets to the last part
As he completes the course, Fujiwara smiles!
Finally completing the course, Fujiwara smiles
I'm okay with it if you are!
Okuru Kotoba - One take music video - SUCCESS!!
I'm so happy!
Great work!
The One Take Drone Challenge, filmed by Fujiwara
All of them watch the recorded footage
Everyone watches the footage they just shot
I think this is the one?
From what I watched, there were no screw-ups
Without further ado, please enjoy Fujiwara's music video
Okuru Kotoba
In the light and shadows of the town at sunset
I give you these words as you go away
Instead of hiding your sadness and faking a smile
It’s better to cry until your tears dry up
The more sadness a person experiences
The more they're able to be kind to others
It’s too sad to just say goodbye
So I give these words to you, my love
They’re interrupted by the twilight breeze
But please listen to the end, these words I give to you
Instead of being upset that you can’t trust anyone
It’s better to take a chance and get hurt
Don’t ask for kindness
That’s a cowards excuse
For you, my first love
I give you these unembellished words
In this new life you are about to begin
Someone will probably love you
But there is no one who will
Love you as deeply as I do
Your receding shadow disappears into the crowd
No longer do they reach you, my words to you
I think it's great!
It was definitely the best out of all of them!
Fujiwara, what do you think?
I'm happy with it, if you are
You're good, right?
We all agree then
Thank you all so much
Great work everyone!
Thank you!
TL - mickstar813
TS - Bipedal