Murakami Shoji's classroom series started without anyone wanting it
It started with a ninja class
You're just an old fart!
You're not a ninja or anything!
and continued a green beret class
And today's class is...
Get yourself together!
Thanks for helping me
Matsumoto san. Yes?
The hell's that?
Well...
How shall I put it
I think we're pirates now
You're right
We're all pirates now
Our dear viewers, you've probably noticed that
Shoji already summoned us a few times
He wants us to dress up like this
Is this our fourth time?
But didn't he tell us about it?
It's officially the third one
I've heard from staff
That the most exciting part about it, is our meeting day
So far, our gathering is the most exciting
Our group arrives at a park
Are we supposed to walk like that around the city?
Right in front of the highway
I think, I saw it from the highway
Really?
This ship?
Right away...
Blackbeard?
"Put a stick through this hole"
Hamada san, please do it
Good morning!
What was that for?
Well, were you surprised?
The man who jumped out with a bang, was Murakami Shoji
Are you all fired up?
Big brother, what are we doing today?
What?
Repeat that
What are we doing today, big brother?
Today your brother...
WHO THE FUCK DO YOU CALL BROTHER?
WHO THE FUCK IS BROTHER HERE?
I'm Captain!
I may be a captain, but I'm not your average club captain
Do you get it?
I'M FREAKING CAPTAIN KIDD!!
I think, you're a bit too loud
A policeman may come here
Because of the screams
We're pirates
Understand?
Well, we are now
You're just like Captain Hook
Like Captain Hook
That's a hook right there
You're wrong
That one's from a fishery cooperative
This one
You've already mentioned that you're a pirate
CAPTAIN MATSUMOTO!
Yes, excuse me!
COME OVER HERE!
Come to me
Aren't you a bit fat?
No, I don't think so
Then, alright for now
You see, today
is the third installment in our series
We're pirates!
Yes. Understand?
"Please don't expect much from this episode. Nothing much will happen right through to the end."
Don't you think we can avoid doing it?
I'm so tired of listening to your whining
Is that so?
And shall we always be eager to do it?
That's right!
As a matter of fact, I was born here...
So, have some compassion!
How many years ago did that happen?
Do you see the nuance
All of it? Yes
Listen up
First of all the pirates are...
Excuse us
It flies over here again
What have we done wrong?
HALT!
Listen
Do you want to sail on ship?
But it's still too early for ya
Look over here!
That's our pirate frigate!
What are you laughing at?
You're messed up
He must be retarded
He's out of his mind
Only you could have said such thing
The pirate class starts immediately
Starting with the most important training exercises
You still have to train enough on land
Wait for a moment
Cars are so noisy!
I guess it's hard for him to see
Ah, I see...
Starting with a navigation training!
Yes!
He really glares at you (Yamasaki)
What's your name?
Yamasaki!
Yes
Fine
Can you please seat on a bench?
Alright
Just seat there
Wait a moment!
He really hates him...
But I hadn't done anything!
YOUR FATHER
BULLIED ME A LOT!
Always getting on my nerves
I was called Captain Seasickness
I had a mental breakdown!
Get lost!
You'd better apologize, Yama chan
If I apologize, will you forgive me?
Please, forgive him!
Please, we ask you!
Show me your consistency
Show me better your consistency
He just showed him hands...
Are you a boke?
What was that?
I am sorry for that
What did you hear?
"Show me your hands"
Why would I need your hands?
I am sorry for mishearing you
But, I want to do it with everyone!
Please, forgive me!
Please forgive him!
What shall I do?
Forgive him, please!
Don't even dream about it
Shall we train on land?
Yes, please... Get lost
Place your ass on the bench and watch us
Endo
Can you push me from behind?
Yes
Just push it a little bit. I see...
Let's go. Be careful...
Alright
Raise anchor!
Full starboard!
I said full starboard
Why did he jump out so sudden?
Didn't I say full starboard?
I am not very sure...
which side is it...
Starboard means right side!
I see, right side
Starboard means right side
Correct. Yes, I'm sorry
He switched so suddenly...
Raise anchor!
Roger
Full starboard!
Full port!
You're good!
I see...
It sounds in Japanese like a vessel's direction
Full of memories
I said "full of memories"
Didn't I?
Tell it
Last year, I had much fun with my family in Okinawa
What's that?
Is that a chocolate? That's a biscuit. He really likes him a lot
That's for your family
Thank you very much! Good job
Is it 'cause he's young?
Let's continue
Endo!
Endo is right in front of you! Captain, what's the matter?
What's the matter with you, captain? We don't understand you!
Let's go
All together now
What a relief! Thank you so much!
Life on frigate is impossible for a pirate
without a superhuman sense of balance
We're going to do some highly difficult training
What's that?
That thing...
That thing?
Fall in!
Yes! What's that? Listen carefully
The sea
is calm sometimes
but usually it is choppy
Because of it
During a battle
you must be stable
We are going to train it here
Got it?
Delivery
from a soba restaurant
Let's give it a try
Tanaka!
Get on the bike
Good luck!
That's tough...
That's very difficult
That's scary!
And drive it over there. Wait a moment!
Captain!
What's up?
The balance...
What's the matter? It's fine, just that angle...
What's that?
My shoulder...
No way... Are you joking?
No way, you're serious
Really?
Are you for real?
Maybe you're not fit to be a pirate?
When you'll be climbing the mast ropes, are you gonna be like this?
Some would need to save you
He's right
That would be quite...
It still looks very tough...
Will it really help for the battle? Hold it tight!
Just go ahead at once
Go for it!
What was it?
Wait a moment
My shoulder...
What?!
And you, Hamada san?
What's that?
How can you even move like that?
Is your leg alright, captain?
No way you'll be a pirate like that!
Captain...
Captain, perhaps...
You could show us how to do it?
Please, show us
That's right
Please, show us once
Oh, captain, look good
Oh, great!
Go for it!
You were so disjointed...
Wait...
What was that?
It's dangerous to be on the sea
You can't do that much on land!
You have no right being on a ship!
You look like you never wanted to be pirates!
Listen up
WE'RE NOT PLAYING GAMES HERE!
We're sorry
You should be all salarymen
with a bonus twice a year!
How often do pirates get that much money?
Let's move on...
You're hopeless...
Training on land is the same
We're sorry
Let's get on a ship
On ship?
Can we?
Get on it?
Thank you very much!
Isn't it better to teach practice on boat?
Thank you ver much!
Am I right?
Come aboard
It's so easy to enter
That's too easy
It's very impressive
It's so cool, captain!
Listen up, this is our vessel now
It's totally different, being on board
We've been on top and on the bottom
Right?
Listen up
What's the best thrill of being a pirate?
I guess...
Getting rich very quick?
You're spot on
Thank you very much!
Treasure hunt!
We see...
Pirates are pirates only if they repeatedly pillage and hunt for treasure
What's the essence of it?
Turn around
Over there
We have a treasure chest
Inside it
There's a treasure trove in there
so everyone has ten seconds
to get one treasure for yourself
Go and snatch things that are not gold
Yes
Okay
You have ten seconds, go
Get set!
Go!
Alright, bring it all here!
10 seconds are up
Why did you take it?
To be fair...
I had no intention to take it
I'm sorry
Did I do well?
What 'bout you?
I took a log...
This could be rented, compared to his
Who would buy it?
Excuse me
You're definitely not a connoisseur
Me...
I got a gold bar
I don't want it!
But don't pirates have lots of these?
Take it off
TAKE IT OFF!!!
I'm sorry
I took it off
He did it...
He was envious
They definitely don't fit him
How to survive after a long period
adrift in the ocean
due to an unforeseen disaster?
When you're in the sea
You're in an open space
Then a ship sinks, or something
Or get attacked by a dinosaur
Yes
What's the most important thing for a man at that time?
What is tit?
Water, I guess... You're right
Thank you very much!
But
When you're adrift, there's no rainwater
There's no fresh water
You're in the sea
It's sea water everywhere
We understand
Here it comes...
Ah, I see
So much...
Sea of Japan has 3,5% of salinity
That was so much, captain...
So much...
So, it should be like this
Sea of Japan has 3,5% of salinity
When you go to the south
It gets 0.5% thicker
Just like hatcho miso
Hamada!
Yes?
Please
Don't you want to survive?
I will drink it!
It's like, it can't melt
It's just sinking down there
Captain
That's no good...
You're so useless...
Captain, won't you?
Please
Please, so it
Please, captain!
As can be expected from you, captain!
What's the matter, captain?
Captain?
That was fast...
He just spat it
Captain, what have you done?
Anyway...
Let's move on
You drink so much!
Listen, captain
That's unfair, you can't do that
Wait for me under the slide
Yes
If you want to be a captain, you have to be able to pull of these kinds of tricks
On this slide, to the bottom
This thing
I'll bring it down with me
I see...
Please be careful, captain!
I'm fine
That's very spectacular
He's fabulous!
Captain, that's great!
Alright, let's move on
Let's move
Captain, you're drenched...
Let's comtinue
What was that, captain?
A pirate must never give up the fight to the last
even when his weapons run out
The set up is
You've driven into a tomato field
Are you sure, that relates to pirates? Shouldn't we deal with ships?
Of course, there are such situations!
Alright
You've driven into a tomato field
So, what are you going to use as a weapon?
I don't really know...
You only have tomatoes!
You will use tomatoes
You'll tear them off
You'll aim at your enemy's vital point
and throw it
Hence...
We have to choose one target
Let's get serious
Captain, will you also take part?
Yep
Will decide turns with rock-paper-scissors
And we'll decide it
through the Pop-up Pirate!
That's dangerous...
We'll play it
This ordering determines the fate of the six people
Let's start!
I'm going first?
My heart is pounding!
I absolutely hate it!
I'm starting!
That thing...
Alright, alright
You can do it
Don't pop!
Who's turn now?
Captain
I don't wanna do it...
Put it!
Now, Tanaka
Do it carefully
This looks bad...
It's so scary... How are you supposed to choose it...
Hamada, you should be fine!
Hamada, that's fine
And, now my turn
I can't help but feel like it's going to pop
Please, pop up!
It's horrifying!
That's so bad, so bad...
I think there are ten left...
Go for that one
I beg you...
Don't... Yes!
I'm done if it pops...
Captain, I don't think that's your turn now...
You've messed up
I don't think that's good...
Indeed
Yes, but I already did it...
But you've messed up our order
I don't think such behavior is good from a pirate
Please, stab it once more
We're sorry captain...
Please, pop up!
Please, captain!
"Captain is the target"
"What will be the captain's fate after this!?"
Alright
Look at my eyes and throw at me!
Yes, that can't be helped
We're sorry!
Fine... Ready?
Look out!
He's trying to say something
What's that?
Why am I zoning out?
What?
CAPTAIN!?
CAPTAIN!
These are the tomatoes for Kagome juice...
What's that?
Let's go home...
"These tomatoes were later washed and eaten by the staff"
It wasn't worth it
COME BACK!!!
"These tomatoes were later washed and eaten by the staff"
HEY!
PUT SOME KETCHUP ON ME!!!
WAIT!
WAIT FOR A MOMENT!
I'm going to announce a championship for that!