So good!
Eat from all the 32 shops in the 23 wards of Tokyo!
Eat from all the 32 shops in the 23 wards of Tokyo
Gyoza's King Sarae Marathon
They'll have to eat in a relay-style
6 gyoza from every shop in Tokyo's wards
m 0 0 l -30 0 l -30 15 l 30 15 l 30 0 l 0 0
The individual quota is 6 shops each
The challenge starts at 11:30 A.M.
m 0 0 l -30 0 l -30 15 l 30 15 l 30 0 l 0 0
The challenge started with Yamazaki, each one of them aiming for 6 shops
The sash has been passed from Tanaka to Hamada,
and they've cleared 15 shops
Adachi
Arakawa
Bunkyo
Chiyoda
Chuou
Edogawa
Itabashi
Katsushika
Kita
Koto
Meguro
Minato
Nakano
Nerima
Oota
Setagaya
Shibuya
Shinagawa
Shinjuku
Suginami
Sumida
Taito
Toshima
Hamada: in progress /
currently completed shops: 15
And tonight, it's time for this marathon's emotional finale!
An emotional finale!!
m 0 0 l -30 0 l -30 15 l 30 15 l 30 0 l 0 0
THIS EPISODE IS PART TWO OF A TWO-PARTS EPISODE.
PART ONE IS @ SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
MAKE SURE TO WATCH PART ONE FIRST!
(SUCH AN OBVIOUS THING TO SAY...)
TYPESETTED AND QC'D BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATED BY SHION
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
(7 hours 12min since start)
32 total shops
Nishidai station's shop (Itabashi Ward)
shop no.15
Hamada is at his 3rd shop, and he's still feeling at ease
I can do this, I can keep on until shop no.22
Hamada Masatoshi
Third runner
That means 60 gyoza
You're gonna take part of Endo's quota too
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
At the same time, our next runner Endo
arrives at South Otsuka
19th shop
4th runner
Endo
arrives at South Otsuka's shop
I'm really hungry
I'm ready for this
Itabashi
Kita
Nakano
Nerima
Toshima
Travel distance: 2,8km
Travel time: 13min.
from Nishidai station
to Ukima-Funado
How's your stomach?
I'm still good, no big deal
I don't want to be irresolute here
If I don't want to eat anymore, I'll just say it
(7 hours 32min since start)
32 total shops:
Ukima-Funado (Kita Ward)
shop no.16
Dusk has fallen and Hamada is going
to challenge Ukima-Funado's shop
Are we going?
After you, Hamada
'Evening
Please
Welcome
Oh, that's a first one here
Alright alright alright alright
I'm ready
Nice
Ok then, let's order
Excuse me?
Yes?
One serving of gyoza, please
Coming right up
Thank you
Please wait few minutes
- Thanks
This is Hamada's fourth dish
But Hamada is feeling uneasy...
But Hamada is starting to feel worried...
This is the cursed 4th dish
That's right
You're right
I have no idea what's so cursed about it
Middle-aged men's stomach killer:
The cursed fourth dish
It's time for the most feared enemy of
our old dudes' stomachs
But on their 4th dish, suffering came along
Yamazaki and Tanaka were both fine
Even Yamazaki and Tanaka were fine
until this fourth serving came
It's the stumble no one has been expecting
Thank you for waiting
How's the cursed 4th dish gonna affect him?
Here it is. Ukima-Funado's shop's challenge starts now
Don't make me rush, geez
Start!
It's time
- Let's go
This is a crucial point
- Is he gonna be fine?
Good!
You did really well up until now, so...
- Yeah
So what?
Enjoy it at your pace
He just scolded you
- Let's eat slowly
(License)
Fujiwara Kazuhiro
Inomoto Takafumi
Special reporters
He said "so what?" right at your face
I guess his usual pace slowed down a bit, huh
But it's fine, really
- No need to worry
It's fine, take your time
The nightmarish 4th dish visited Hamada
Hamada is experiencing the nightmare of the 4th dish
His pace has slowed down significantly
He's not speaking as much as before
- Right
Where's Endo now?
Endo is waiting at South Otsuka's shop
- Nice
He's done eating
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
I'm going to pay and then we're leaving
What now...?
Hamada's tragic play for Endo!!
coming up...
Is he sleeping?
Hamada, don't forget there's a time limit for this...
Shut up...
Is he full?
4th runner - Endo
Currently waiting at South Otsuka's shop
At the same time, Endo is expecting to see Hamada soon
Hamada is gonna come here, right?
Yeah, he's on his way   Good to hear
- It's him!
Ohh! Hamada!
Woah!
As the other costumers cheer him on,
he moves to the next shop
Give it your best!
- Thank you!
Haven't I done enough already?
Huh? Excuse me?
I think I understand what they meant by "it comes suddenly"
Yeah...
Let's go, Hamada
- Come on
Let's move on
Ok
They're waiting for you
(8 hours 2min since start)
32 total shops
Akabane station, south exit (Kita Ward)
shop no.17
A destroyed Hamada arrives at his 5th shop
We're getting in
Welcome!
Good evening
Here?
Welcome
Thank you
How many dishes do you think I've eaten, huh?
Five with this
30 total gyoza!
You gotta do it
Hey, do you remember if I ever, like...
Wrote that gyoza are my favorite food in my profile?
I don't remember reading it before
- I don't think so
Let's go, Hamada
Oh boy, that's the spirit
Nice done
I don't need any more gyoza...
You don't need them?
You all have to give the best to pass that sash
Gyoza won't fall down his throat
He can't swallow any gyoza
Let's flush them down with some water
So he drinks to forcibly let them go down
Deli~cious!
A completely different Hamada
from what we've seen before
Hamada became a different person
Last one for this shop
Hamada
Yanaoka (staff), lend me the phone
The phone?
I wanna talk to Endo, pass me the phone
Ah, that-- I mean... you can do it, ok
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
Oh, he's done here
Incredible
I'm calling
Do I have to?
Please
Hello?
Endo?
Akabane Station
Call
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
South Ootsuka
Oh, good evening
Sure
Are you ok?
Come to Oji's shop
What?!
Endo's opinion didn't matter...
Eh?
Hello---
Let's go to Oji!
Got it
Let's just go, hurry up
I think
I smell trouble
Let's go to Oji
Hamada heads to Oji's shop (no.18) too
Moving on the next level
I'm the youngest one here, I have to be fast and resolute
That's right
I agree
"Let's eat everything up!"
(7 hours 32min since start)
32 total shops
Ouji's shop (Kita Ward)
shop no.18
Should we just wait?
- Sure
Alright then, let's wait
This is Ouji's shop
Where is he?
Welcome!
He's here
Sorry I'm late
'Evening
- 'Evening
Good evening
Are you ok? How are you?
What's up?
I mean, you told me to come here, so...
Yes, I know
I was at the next one...
Right, South Otsuka
I was waiting at South Otsuka's shop
I thought so
We figured so
Here
Endo Shozo
Fourth runner
And with this, you've received the sash
from our third runner Hamada
Are you done for?
Now you're the fourth runner
Alright I guess
Yes
Just so you know, we had a little problem at Takadanobaba's shop
And it's this thing here...
Ok
Oh, you have something?
That's right
This is--
It's a lil' take-out
We had a take-out
The gyoza Tanaka asked a take-out for
Tanaka asked a take-out for the gyoza he couldn't eat
But it's Yamazaki's fault, since he couldn't reach his quota
Yamazaki is responsible for this!!
You can just drag 'em along your way
We're giving them to Yamazaki at the end
I see, it makes sense to give him these
How many shops do you think you can go through?
Well, we have our at-least-6-shops quote, right?
And there's Hamada's shop, so it's 7 now
I think I can aim for 8 or 9 shops
Really? That would be great
Really?!
I came to a Gyoza's King 3 days ago and practiced, you know
Now that's dumb
I swear, I'm serious
You think you can go through this?
Yeah
Will we see the results of his training?
How is Endo's performance going to be?!
Let's start
I'm eating
Come on, dig in
Look, that's a double
- We can count on him
Completely different approach
His technique is completely different
I've never seen this before
So unique
Isn't this going to affect him later on?
Maybe this way his digestion is gonna be slower
What a wonderful performance
That was really good
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
Wonderful
Alright then Hamada, we part ways here
Thanks for today
See ya
Countin' on you, Endo
Itabashi
Kita
Nakano
Nerima
Toshima
Ouji's shop
South Otsuka's shop
travel distance: 3.9km
travel time: 7min.
It's not recent but
I think it was like 10 years ago
Yes?
But I had this eating competition
You took part in it?
Yeah, I did
I see...
I know for sure you shouldn't rely on water
Oh, I see...
Have you noticed I didn't drink a single drop now?
You're right
Not a drop
I didn't drink
- Yeah...
Water is your enemy
Myogadani station
South Otsuka
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza
Fast-eater Endo easily clears 2 shops without touching water
We're done here
4 shops remains to reach his quota
He still has 4 shops to reach his quota
25th shop
Fifth runner
Matsumoto
arrives at Kameido's shop
At the same time, Matsumoto arrives at the 25th shop
You may think he's too early, but...
This one?
'Evening
(clerk) One person only?
Yes
They're 1 and a half hours late to their schedule
They're already 1 and a half hours late
Closing time for the remaining shops is drawing near...
And the closing time is drawing near
The 4th shop is hard
(9 hours 26min since start)
32 total shops
Waseda Natsumezaka (Shinjuku Ward)
shop no.21
But Endo's pace is raising
Here we are
You can start
His pace is not changing at all, huh
He gets rid of the cursed 4th dish as well
He gets rid of the cursed 4th dish with ease
And we're done
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza
We're done with this shop too
Alright
Thank you
Suidobashi's shop (Chiyoda Ward)
The 5th dish too is not a problem for Endo
And his expression shows no signs of suffering
Let's just go, quick
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza
He's so quick
(10 hours 5min since start)
32 total shops
Kanda East exit's shop (Chiyoda Ward)
shop no.23
For how long can he keep up this fast pace?
Here I go
I wonder how hot these are
They're hot
- I see
Are they?
Now he knows how to deal with them
Can you keep up the pace?
Huh? You forgot how to pick it up?
Have you become unable to hold a gyoza?
Nope, I'm fine
It's coming, huh?
We can totally tell it's coming
Here it comes
Endo's pace is finally slowing down
Huh?
What's wrong?
No way
I'm completely fine
You're almost ther--
Huh?!
Gulping down a lot of water
Here it is
No way
The reason for why he wants to keep on eating gyoza is...
But there's a reason for why he doesn't want to give up yet
I want to pass my sash onto Matsumoto with a good feeling
I see
I'm trying my best to do so
- Got it
Man, I'm so hungry...
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza
He's done with his quota
All 36 gyoza are done
Do you have any stomach medicine?
He takes some stomach medicine to trick
his stomach and continue his battle
Gimme some
Here
(10 hours 25min since start)
32 total shops
Asakusabashi's station (Taito Ward)
shop no.24
Endo will now face his 7th shop - an unprecedented resolution
Here we are
Pray for Endo
Down goes the first one
He's at his limit
Hang in there
Do your best!
Gyoza no.4!
And it's down
He got 'em both!
He really made it
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza
Alright
Thank god he got 'em both down
That was impressive
Oh shit I can't anymore... I've reached my limit
Oh boy
This is terrible
It is
This is impossible-- I thought I could go for like 10 dishes, but...
I think 7 shops is incredible enough
(10 hours 52min since start)
32 total shops
Kameido's station (Koto Ward)
shop no.25
And finally, Endo's efforts will be shared with Matsumoto
Welcome!
You're so late~
You're really late, man
I'm here
We don't have time left--
Here's your sash, take it
Please, have it
5th runner
Matsumoto Hitoshi
We made it, it's Matsumoto's time to shine
I'm so hungry you won't believe it
The sash has been passed
At last
We have this one here too
What?
take-out gyoza from Takadanobaba's shop (no.12)
How old are these?
Let's see...
It's from here, so it should be from 4 P.M.
This isn't "Gyoza's King" anymore, it's "Gyoza's Pawn" by now
Let's deal with the other shops first
So Tanaka is gonna eat those later?
Yes, I mean, it's Yamazaki actually
How did this happen?
They should have eaten more
They all tried their best here
'Scuse me
Excuse me?
I'll have some tenshinmen!
No--- it's gyoza!
I know you're hungry but please
I felt like eating that...
I wanted to try, you never know
Yeah but... yeah
I see
One serving of gyoza, please
Please
I wanna go all the way through this
Let's do this
We're counting on you
Hang in there
I get what you're saying
Sorry to have kept you waiting
So fast!
Yeah, the King is pretty fast
Want some vinegar?
Yeah, fine, I'm gonna eat 'em all anyway
The hell? These are so good
Their taste is making me laugh
So good they make you laugh?
It was the same for me too
I felt the same at first
I'm craving some white rice
I'm fast, right? Right?
I think I was even quicker on my first dish
Alright! I'm done
Last one to go
I'm gonna pay, you get ready ok?
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza:
Meal finished!
- Alright!
Give it your best, Matsumoto!
Let's move on
Here we go  Bye!
I'll wait for you at the goal
Adachi
Arakawa
Edogawa
Katsushika
Sumida
Taito
from Kameido
to Hirai station
travel distance: 2.5km
travel time: 5 min.
It was a piece of cake just now
Yes
I think I'm a big eater
Between Yoshimoto's comedians
A glutton?
Yes, that's right
Inside Yoshimoto I think I'm like the 400th in rank
- That sucks
- That's pretty low!
But the other guys are way worse than me
Don't you think it's strange they
can't eat up 6 gyoza servings?
Are they gay?
Even if you say so---
They're hermaphrodites
That's the way a hermaphrodite eats
Scrap that, a hermaphrodite would eat more than that
- What
- You're talking so much!
- Do they eat so much?
(11 hours 11min since start)
32 total shops
Hirai station - North exit (Edogawa Ward)
shop no.26
Matsumoto enters the 26th shop in a good shape
It took us forever
Let's get in
We expect a lot from you
Can I just get in?
Of course, let's go
'Evening
Welcome!
Good evening, thanks
Let's do this
We're ready
Place your order
Have you decided already?
Yes, I'll have...
Tenshinmen, please!
How was that? Lame?
One serving of gyoza, please
Coming right up
I'm completely fine
He easily finish up his 2nd dish of gyoza
His chopsticks movements are smooth,
and gyoza goes down one after another
I wanna eat even more of these
It's going to take you around 3 minutes per shop
You're fine, it's just half empty
I can do this
Counting on you
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza
Alright!
Nicely done
Let's move on
I get it now!
Nice speed
Really good
- You're doing great
You're fast
That was fast
"I get it now..."
A sentence got us worried
Matsumoto uttered some words of worry without thinking
Do you think you can keep up your
fast pace from the 3rd shop?
Yeah, sure
Let's keep it then
I mean, yeah, sorry
- It's good
We'll pay while you eat
Of course
So we can go faster
But you know, if I'd stop now I'd be fine
Excuse me?
- What was that?
W-what was that just now?
(11 hours 28min since start)
32 total shops
Shinkoiwa's Lumiere shop (Edogawa Ward)
shop no.27
Matsumoto is already showing weakness,
but it's now or never for the Gyoza's King
This is also a battle against heat
- That's right
He's keeping a good pace  - It's good
A nice fast pace, it's what we want
chewing gyoza without speaking
- He's fast
He's doing good, isn't he?
- He is
Want us to go pay?  - Should we go?
Matsumoto?
You're going?
Yeah, we're doing it now
Alright then
We're done here
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza
Another meal finished
Just like before
Oh my
Uhhh...
This is tiresome
Ohh～ now I get it...
- Well...
(11 hours 54min since start)
32 total shops
Mizue station, North exit (Edogawa Ward)
shop no.28
A nervous Matsumoto challenges the cursed 4th dish
How is it going to affect Matsumoto?
How is he going to overcome it?
We're happy to see such a good senpai eating all these gyoza
- It's so rare
Feast your eyes on this scene, folks
Next up is Koiwa's north exit shop
- That's right
Right
One after another
- Yeah
Matsumoto?
- Matsumoto?
Matsumoto...?
I don't wanna eat anymore
He's giving up!
What?! Giving up?!
A new tragedy awaits Matsumoto!!
coming up
Are you kidding me?
- What?!
3½ shops?!
Now I get it...
You ok?
- Just focus on their taste
It's the last one
- Come on
Let's do this
Let's get rid of the 4th dish
- Yes
- Oh crap!
Let's go, Matsumoto
He's starting to gulp down a lot of water
This is the first sign of surrender
- That's an "I give up"
We know this by now
But man, I'm impressed I made it this far to be honest
This is the cursed 4th dish
And he's done, let's go pay for this
Meal finished
total amount of eaten gyoza
Let's go, Matsumoto
- Come on
We don't have time
We're running out of time
Let's go
Come on
Hang in there, Matsumoto
Adachi
Arakawa
Edogawa
Katsushika
Sumida
Taito
from Mizue station
to Koiwa station
travel distance: 5.8km
travel time: 12min.
Here we are
- Next shop
Until now as you can see...
For example, Hosei got help by Tanaka
when he couldn't make it
I see
In your case, everyone will help you
We thought you wouldn't need this,
you said they're all gay and stuff
Well, yeah, I still think they're all gay
- I see
But by now, I've become a full-fledged little girl
What?!
4 shops left to conquer
Everyone will take part on the last two
4 shops left - everyone will help for the last two
The other 4 believe in him and wait...
He has to do it for the other 4, waiting and trusting him...
Matsumoto is going to strain his stomach!!
He's going to strain his stomach for them
- Here we are
Koiwa's station, north exit
Yes
Oh boy
Huh?
- What the-
Oh!
Oh shit
We're fucked
They're closed
This sucks
current time:
Are we done now?
They're closed already  - It's over
Thank god...
Wait, what?!
No, I meant-- that's not it
Did you say "thank god"?
I mean, I'm sure it's on me too, it took me too long
Ugh...
I don't like half-assed things like this...
I wanted to go all the way through to the end, man...
This--
Really
So uncool～
Status report for the other 4
I can't believe this is the end
Is no one gonna answer?  Yeah?
Hello?
Yes?
Call
Hamada Masatoshi
Koiwa station
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Waiting room
Koiwa's shop is closed
Closed?!
It's past business hours
The shop is?
It took you guys too long
He's scolding us sayin' we were slow
You gotta be kidding me
I figured he would say that
Is he for real?
He says the shop is closed
What?!
Please, come to Koiwa station's north exit
Koiwa?!
Koiwa north exit? Now?
Call
Hamada Masatoshi
Koiwa station
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Waiting room
How about you end this by yourself?
No way, that'd be awkward
Please come here, please
Did they tell you they're going home?
Let's finish this properly
Tanaka?
Call
Koiwa station
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Waiting room
Yes?
I'll wait for you at Koiwa's north exit
He says he'll wait at Koiwa's north exit
I can't--- I don't want to
Call
Koiwa station
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Waiting room
I mean--
Let's just gather here
It's like that, you know
Yes?
Just like the first time we went to a brothel, let's gather first
He says to gather like we did when we first hit a brothel
We're coming
We're coming for you
Sure
I'm gonna bother the neighbors...
Our members' challenge
ends on their 28th shop out of a total of 32 shops
Start!!
He's so fast!
Alright!
DEAL WITH IT YOURSELF!!
No way
Let's just head to Takadanobaba
Deli~cious!
Thanks!
Good!
I don't wanna eat anymore
I think I wanna go home
They'll meet up for the review meeting!!
coming up
Oh, they're here
It's really closed
He's right
Oh no
You're late
I've been waiting for minutes
What?
Well, it took us some time since the phone call to get here
Actually...
You haven't completed Takadanobaba's shop no.12 yet...
There's nothing there
- It's blank
What do you mean?
You haven't completed Takadanobaba's shop no.12 yet...
You're right
It's here
We have the five left gyoza here with us
This is Yamazaki's part, right?
- It's Hamada's
It's yours
No
Endo took care of mine
You can eat those, right? It was morning back then
We're counting on you
Well
I don't think I can eat those
What?!
I can't
You gotta do this
It's yours, man
How about we split this, Hamada?
Why am I getting involved in this? Endo took care of me
Me and Endo aren't involved
For crying out loud...
So you can still eat
You just said you couldn't!
He can
This is a closure for the five us, see?
- I'm doing this
I think so too, yeah
For you guys
Don't speak while you suck on those, it's really sick
TRANSLATION BY SHION | TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
MORE EPISODES @ SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
He's done
He ate 'em all, wow
FOLLOW ME ON SOCIAL MEDIAS: FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI &TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
Now we're done
28 shops done
We're all done
How many shops are left?
Only four of them
WANT TO SUPPORT MY CONTENT? CONSIDER DONATING ON KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
Four?
Only four, huh...
What do you think? It sucks, huh?
It sucks, doesn't it?
Right?
OR BECOME A PATRON ON PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
Let's try this thing again
When?
Next week
What the hell
Next week would be impossible--
That wasn't funny at all, man
No one laughed
Yeah, you're right
Director
Matsumoto Hitoshi
GAKI NO TSUKAI NEWS  - MOVIE: SYMBOL (2009)
Excuse me?!
After a good meal, it's time for the arts!
Symbol, a new movie directed by Matsumoto
Is now available in every theater!
I wanna go home!
Symbol
In every cinema
TYPESET & QUALITY CHECK BY KEDOMAS || TRANSLATION BY
SHION || MORE EPISODES: SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
LIKE MY FB PAGE: FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | FOLLOW ME ON
TWITTER @SHIONNOTSUKAI | WANT TO SUPPORT MY CONTENT?
YOU CAN DONATE FEW BUCKS ON KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
OR ON PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
THIS IS PART TWO OF A TWO-PART EPISODE | PART ONE IS AVAILABLE ON MY WORDP
RESS @SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM | I MEAN THIS INFO IS USELESS, IF YOU'R
E READING THIS IT MEANS YOU HAVE WATCHED PART TWO ALREADY, DID YOU MISS P
ART ONE AND YOU'RE REALIZING THAT ONLY NOW? ARE YOU DUMB?! JK, IT HAPPENS.
IT'S OK. | | |  THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FANMADE TRANSLATION MADE BY FANS FOR OTHER
FANS | NO COPYRIGHT INFRINGMENT INTENDED, NO ADFLY, NO MONEY INVOLVED EXC
EPT DONATIONS WHICH ARE NOT EVEN REMOTELY MANDATORY I'M LITERALLY DOING
THIS JUST BECAUSE I LIKE DOING THIS | THANKS FOR WATCHING <3