0 0 m -300 -65.625 b -310.75 -67 -339.875 -65.625 -336.875 -41.25 b -338.375 -27.75 -309.25 -1 -301.5 0 b -289.25 7.625 -284.625 -1 -277 -2.5 b -267.75 -11.625 -258.625 -14.625 -249.375 -37.125 b -246.25 -58 -266.25 -59.625 -267.75 -61.375 b -280 -67 -290.75 -65.625 -300 -65.625 m -292.375 -58 b -278.5 -61.375 -260.125 -52.375 -263.125 -43.125 b -273.875 -54.875 -283.125 -54.875 -292.375 -58 m -370.625 -189.875 b -364.375 -189.875 -312.25 -179.5 -320 -110.625 b -330.625 -67 -359.875 -46 -369 -41.25 b -373.625 -39.875 -398.125 -20.625 -431.875 -52.375 b -439.625 -67 -455 -83.875 -444.25 -121 b -439.625 -136 -431.875 -164.875 -404.375 -181 b -396.625 -185.25 -384.375 -193 -370.625 -189.875 m -232.5 -193 b -229.375 -193 -192.625 -203.5 -160.375 -148 b -155.75 -134.5 -143.5 -117.75 -151.25 -76 b -160.375 -41.25 -175.75 -39.875 -185 -37.125 b -192.625 -37.125 -203.375 -27.75 -240.125 -53.5 b -252.5 -63.75 -270.875 -70 -278.5 -112 b -277 -112 -295.375 -139.25 -257 -181 b -249.375 -187.375 -241.75 -193 -232.5 -193 m -373.625 -143.5 b -416.625 -136 -392 -89.5 -372.125 -94.25 b -366 -94.25 -352.125 -97.375 -349.125 -117.75 b -353.75 -142.375 -362.875 -140.25 -373.625 -143.5 m -373.625 -129.875 b -364.375 -133.125 -359.875 -121 -361.375 -117.75 b -361.375 -106.375 -370.625 -106.375 -375.125 -106.375 b -381.25 -107.375 -384.375 -113.5 -382.875 -121 b -382.875 -124.125 -379.75 -129.875 -373.625 -129.875 m -370.625 -124.125 b -375.125 -122.375 -373.625 -116.75 -370.625 -116.75 b -367.5 -116.75 -364.375 -122.375 -370.625 -124.125 m -221.75 -143.5 b -255.5 -137.5 -240.125 -91 -221.75 -95.25 b -215.625 -94.25 -200.25 -97.375 -200.25 -124.125 b -204.875 -142.375 -217.125 -143.5 -221.75 -143.5 m -221.75 -129.875 b -201.875 -129.875 -208 -106.375 -218.75 -106.375 b -221.75 -104.625 -234 -107.375 -231 -121 b -231 -124.125 -229.375 -129.875 -221.75 -129.875 m -218.75 -124.125 b -223.25 -121 -220.25 -115 -217.125 -116.75 b -212.5 -117.75 -215.625 -124.125 -218.75 -124.125 m -376.75 -116.75 b -379.75 -116.75 -378.25 -112 -376.75 -112 b -375.125 -112 -373.625 -116.75 -376.75 -116.75 m -223.25 -115 b -226.375 -115 -224.875 -110.625 -223.25 -110.625 b -221.75 -110.625 -220.25 -115 -223.25 -115
0 0 m -455 -217.125 l -142 -217.125 l -142 86.875 l -455 86.875 m -145 -214.125 l -451.875 -214.125 l -451.875 84.25 l -145 84.25
Backstage- Pre recording
So you guys tell them what you bring...
Yeah like straps quite often...
Oh really?
Cocorico
Downtown
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Yamasaki Hosei
What the hell are you reminiscing about?
I know...
No, I wasn't like that, was I?
You were...
You really were...
Otomo
What the hell?
Producer
Suga Kenji
Otomo..
Umm, yes?
Tachi?
Who's going to play Tachi?
I'm talking about Tachi Hiroshi!
It's stupid just doing this all by myself
So Tachi...
Tachi from Seibu Keisatsu?
That's right
Naoki...*
*Suga is addressing Tanaka by
his first name to be intimidating
Tachi Hiroshi...
Decide with that!
For some reason, Suga producer hands
Tanaka a bouncy ball
r
Decide who's going to be
Tachi Hiroshi, Naoki, you sort it out and decide...
Got it?!
He's so pissed off!
That was so scary!
What the hell was that?
And why is he ordering you like that?
Otomo, what's going on?
Well umm...
He's a huge fan of Seibu Keisatsu
Director
Ootomo Yuichi
He's a huge fan of Seibu Keisatsu
And as you saw, he's Daimon, right?
Yeah, I got that
Daimon Keisuke
Producer
Seibu Police
Suga Kenji
And he's been saying for a while he wanted to do this...
Producer Suga wanted to
do Seibu Police kind of things
r
But this isn't really the program for it...
So if someone could
play Tachi Hiroshi
Just do it
among the staff...
The talent shouldn't have to...
Exactly
I'm above that...
Oh no~ we can't be the only ones to...
right Ootomo~?
Let's all do it...
Are you gay?
Heipo
Heipo-san?
So decide with the Bouncy ball...
They must use the bouncy ball and
decide who will play Tachi Hiroshi
r
who will play Tachi Hiroshi...
Wait, I don't get what we have to do...
So we have to decide who is going to do it?
One of us...
Ok then...
We'll go around the table
For example, throw the ball against the wall
and then when it bounces back, we
catch it one handed
and whoever can't do it
plays Tachi Hiroshi
okay?
I don't want to man..
No no, that's like the only thing I can think of...
They take goes throwing the ball
Throw the ball against the wall and catch it
Whoever is the last one able to
against the wall and catch it with one hand
catch the ball plays Tachi Hiroshi
r
text
We go one by one around the table and they throw the Bouncy ball against the wall and catch it one handed
Whoever is the last one to do it has to play Tachi Hiroshi
Here I go then
Bouncy ball
Don't catch it and
become Tachi Hiroshi
Gold
White
This is...
Yeah, it's fine
That was fine
He did it so softly
Wow, amazing
That was dangerous
That was close
So close
He threw it so softly...
So I can do it as soft as I want, right?
They're getting nervous
No one has failed...
Because of everyone's sweat, the ball is so slippy...
This is...
He'll be fine, no?
Surely...
That was awful!
Your eyes couldn't keep up at all!
That was so bad!
That really was!
Tsutsun, you're up
That was dangerous
It was...
To be honest, the slower you do it, the harder it is...
Yeah
Because it bounces weirdly
Yeah, if you do it too soft
it goes weird
Oh this is bad!
No good...
Out
Okay, here we go
These guys suck so bad!
That's awful!
The talents are just amazing though...
I guess it's our youth!
Heipo now
Here I go
He was skipping there...
He like hit it
You got to catch it...
Second round
I think he's in trouble...
He is
We told you not to throw it softly!
He got it though
You smug piece of shit...
Right then...
What are you on about?
You're an idiot
If your kids were watching...
He's so bad!
So bad!
Surely you're not feeling pressured here?
Oh, he caught it!
So if Heipo catches this
If Heipo catches this, Nakamura
becomes Tachi Hiroshi!
r
This is the one
Here I go...
So that means Tachi Hiroshi...
is going to be Nakamura-san!
Nakamura Producer- Decided
Tachi Hiroshi
(Tachi Hiroshi)
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Producer
Seibu Police
Tatsumi Sotaro detective
Daimon Keisuke detective
Producer
Seibu Police
Suga Kenji
Watari Tetsuya
Let's play golf sometime...
You always say that and never play
Otomo
Yes?
Have you decided who'll play Akira?
Akira?
Tachi just went to you...
Akira I said, Akira... Tera Akira!
(Tera Akira)
Matsuda Takeshi
Seibu Police
Choose someone
We can't do anything, just the two of us
Naoki
Naoki, you decide using that, who will play him
Suga hands Tanaka a deck of cards this time
r
Tera?
That's right, Tera Akira.
I have to?
Yeah, Naoki decides...
Damn, he's rough
So rough...
What's that about?
He has no delicacy...
And what's with the 'Naoki' thing?
I have no idea...
It's the first time I've ever heard him say that
Yeah
So what shall we do with this deck?
I don't know man...
What should we do...
Just make it simple
You're right
Like we all take a card and flip it over at the same time
and whoever has the lowest number...
Oh yeah, I do like that idea
Oh man, so scary
This is quite scary...
So the lowest number...
Oh, wait!
So, If before I draw
I say "hearts"
And then I flip over the card
and it's hearts then I'm safe
Oh, that's a good idea.
Wait, you'd be safe?
Should I be out?
Because it's a 1/4 chance.
If we do that,
It'd be better if you were out.
If you were safe no one would...
That might be better.
I think so too.
Continue this until there is only
Guess the Card Suit
If the suit of the card is the suit
Pick a card and guess the suit,
and then flip it over.
called out, the player is out.
one person left. Loser becomes Tera.
text
Flip a card over, and if it is the same suit as the one the player called out, he is out.
The last person to be out will perform Tera Akira.
If you guess it right, you're out.
Gold
Guess the Suit,
Tera Akita
Playing Cards
White
If you're right, out.
If you say hearts and the card is hearts, you're out.
Hearts
Safe!
Are we putting it back in the pile?
Nah, just leave it out.
Ah, okay.
Say it out loud.
Hearts
That was close
Thank God
Spades
Wow, nice
There's a 1/4 chance so...
It's over with just a flip.
Endo's the 4th turn, so...
Clovers
No way, I don't wanna...
Right, right
There's still a chance.
Go ahead, Tanaka.
Diamonds
Yes, okay.
It's lookin' like Endo...
Right?
Say it!!!
Hearts
If you don't call it first, you're automatically out.
Diamonds
Just two people left.
It's gonna be Endo!
Just two left, Endo.
Three-Leaf
Three-leaf?
What the hell is "three-leaf"?
If Heipo Guesses Wrong
Endo Will Perform Tera Akira!
Text
I've never heard of that suit.
So it's all on Heipo now.
It's gonna be Endo.
It's already Endo, though.
Spades!
Which means,
Tera Akira is...
Endo!
Endo To
Perform Tera!
Thank God...
(Tera Akira)
Endo Shozo
Matsuda Takeshi
Western Division Police
(Watari Tetsuya)
Daimon Keisuke
Producer
Suga Kenji
Western Division Police
(Tachi Hiroshi)
Detective Tatsumi Soutarou
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Producer
So we...
Otomo
Yes.
Who's gonna be Gen-san?
Gen-san?
I'm talking about Kariya Shunsuke!
(Kariya Shunsuke)
Detective Genda Kouji
Western Division Police
Kariya Shunsuke...
Naoki
You pick.
It's up to you.
This Time Producer Suga Gives
Tanaka a Recorder
text
Decide with this...
pick Gen-san.
Alright...
Understood?!
Y...Yes.
He really had trouble closing that door.
How should we do it?
What do you mean, we already know how.
Explain the rules already.
Every one will pick
their own recorder...
And only one of these recorders
doesn't make any noise.
will be Kariya Shunsuke
The person who gets that recorder
If sound comes out, safe! The person who
Pick one of the recorders from the
Recorder Playing
bucket and blow into it
picks the broken recorder becomes Kariya
text
Pick a recorder and try playing in order.
The person who picks the silent recorder becomes Kariya Shunsuke.
Should we all pick at the same time?
It's a 1/8 chance, so...
If I'm gonna get picked after all this time,
I would have preferred Tachi Hiroshi.
Let's all pick at the same time.
Box
Gold
Recorders
Whoever picks the
silent recorder is Kariya
Alright.
I'm begging you...
We just have to blow togeth...
Oh right, One by one.
Let's start blowing.
Alright, starting with Yama-chan.
It's you!
See?!
Try playing.
See?
It's Yama-chan!
Perform Kariya Shunsuke!
Yamasaki To
That's so unfortunate.
I almost shed a tear.
(Kariya Shunsuke)
Detective Genda Kouji
Western Division Police
Yamasaki Hosei
(Tachi Hiroshi)
Detective Tatsumi Soutarou
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Producer
Western Division Police
(Watari Tetsuya)
Detective Daimon Keisuke
Producer
Suga Kenji
Western Division Police
(Tera Akira)
Detective Matsuda Takeshi
Endo Shozo
Western Division Police
We should be good now
We're good.
It's enough already.
We're definitely good.
He's so...
Otomo
Yes.
gonna make me tell you?
How many times are you
Tani-san. You know, Tani-san.
Tani-san?
I'm talkin' about Fujioka Juukei.
(Fujioka Juukei)
Detective Tani Daisaku
Western Division Police
Tani-san!
Who's it gonna be?
Naoki
Pick Tani-san, with that.
This Time Producer Suga
Gives Tanaka a Towel
text
Pick Tani-san.
It's Kuroiwa. Just kidding, it's Daimon.
Alright, got it. I'll head right there.
Yup, got it. No problem.
But Kuroiwa is from Daitokai*
*Daitokai is another popular detective/police drama
Understood?!
Decide already.
He has no idea what he's doing.
I thought he loved that show.
That way of playing it off,
"Just kidding..."
His face is probably so red right now.
Bright red!
He said "Just kidding"...!
Such a stupid way to cover it up
So what's this?
This is a towel for each of us.
And with these...
There's only one towel
which has ink on it.
Each person will choose a prepared towel and wipe their face with it,
Each person picks a towel from the
Ink Towel Face Wipe
The person that wipes their face
bucket, and everyone wipes their face at the same time.
text
with the ink towel will play Fujioka Juukei.
and the person who chose the ink towel will play Fujioka Juukei.
Ah, I can see it.
Let's pick.
After we choose...
It's ready, right?
I could see the ink towel.
He could see it.
Oh really?
Yea.
You can just take off your glasses
if you're gonna accidentally see it.
Oh yea!
Face Turns Black
=Fujioka Juukei
Gold
Ink Towel
White
Alright, here it is.
I don't wanna do this anymore.
Let's just pick for now.
Let's all wipe at the same time.
3, 2, 1...
We were spared...
But I just saw...why me?!
Which means,
Fujioka Juukei will be played by Heipo!
Heipo To
Perform Fujioka Juukei!
Fantastic.
(Fujioka Juukei)
Detective Tani Daisaku
Heipo
Western Division Police
(Tera Akira)
Detective Matsuda Takeshi
Endo Shozo
Western Division Police
(Watari Tetsuya)
Detective Daimon Keisuke
Producer
Suga Kenji
Western Division Police
(Tachi Hiroshi)
Detective Tatsumi Soutarou
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Producer
Western Division Police
(Kariya Shunsuke)
Detective Genda Kouji
Western Division Police
Yamasaki Hosei
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Otviss
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
Mickstar (Team Gaki) & Callanse
Translators:
Typesetter: