The man incredibly gifted by god
Reiwa's most remarkable genius
He's back after 4 years!
The music producer Tsukitei Hosei
The 7th time to make an impact on the music industry!!
You're saying this yourself?
Thank you very much
Your voice sound hoarse, huh?   -He lost his voice
It surely is hoarse
I was very surprised too
The members have recorded the music already
I lost my voice after singing
Yeah, you completely lost your voice
But we've been doing this for so many times
And yet, the music companies never contacted us, not even once!
This is absolutely unbelievable
We're under the condition of corona now, so...
It's so complicated to say "condition of corona"
But I did say it clearly, right?
We are in a tough situation now, so I hope to make waves and cheer people up
We actually talked about this during the meeting
"It has been a while, shall we do this again?"
And this dude replied with two "Yes(es)"
He can't wait to do it
I was like "are you serious?"
This is the 7th time now
Hosei will create 3 songs with all his might
But before that...
Let's watch the songs produced up till now together
No thanks   -Please don't say "no thanks"
Super no thanks
No one was interested, so what's the point of watching it again?
No, no, these are truly masterpieces
And among all of the songs that I've produced
This one is my favorite
Hosei produce! The fascinating masterpieces
I remember
this one
Endo loves
I won't say
I love this one
But I do
remember this
Ah, Yamasaki-san, the starry sky that we looked upon
I remember
this scene
What the heck
is that face?
It's staying in my mind as if it just happened yesterday
His face is
pissing me off
-He's into it
-He really is
Ah, Matsumoto-san, the promise that we made that day
I've enshrined it in the drawer of my heart, because it's so precious
Good facial
expression,
Matsumoto-san!
I didn't know
what face to
make here
We can't reach it with our hands
The shining stars high in the sky
I just have
to say this
You're just
copying SMAP!
So please embrace us forever and a day
Completely
copying
No way,
that's not true
As we are weaker than you thought
This is
my original
So please embrace us forever and a day
Look at this,
I was so embarrassed
No, I like Hamada's voice,
it's deep and tender
As we can easily fall into despair
Just fall into despair,
who cares
Look at Tanaka
during the end
-At Tanaka?
-Yes
What the heck
are you doing?
Was that improvised?
How could that be improvised
I seriously dislike Tanaka now
I'm such a pathetic person if that's improvised
Many people talked about this with you right, Endo?
Nope, no one said anything about this to me...
Did something happened?   -Yes, of course, Endo
Well, anyway, please explain it with narration afterwards
With narration?
That's so troublesome
I don't understand this line
The masterpiece is sometimes ruined by the singer
This happens
I've worked so hard to create a masterpiece, and yet...
The vocal ability and abnormal thinking of the singer ruins it
We're just doing what you told us to do
You mean it should be an amazing song if we did it right?
Yes, exactly!
Hosei produce! The regrettable songs collection
Why is it the photo of him wearing the Rakugo costume?
This one was awful too
I don't remember a thing
Eh? You must be kidding
Look who's the singer
Yeah, I remembered this
It's Yashiro-san
I'm wearing this wig
at that time already?
This was the first time
I'll put this cup of diluted whiskey here on the table
Aki-san is the best!
And let the ice melt at your own pace
If that's what you're thinking about, then shall we dance?
Please pay attention to here
The position of the bangs were
higher than at the beginning
He moved it up himself!
Are you trying to flirt with someone like me?
I see
He thought he
looks better this way
So he moved it
while he's still singing!
Stop it! I'm not that kind of person
No, no, I'm just...
He's trying hard
to get a laugh
Please smile like how you used to smile
That cooled me down
Please don't mention that
Look! It's completely different
Don't remind me of the old days, it just makes me feel miserable
We two are the same kind of flower
Please try to touch it, the flower of love
Standing in the storm, face the reality now
I remember this,
I was terribly teased
What happened?
Diamond Yukai-san teased me
Environmental destruction! We have to stop it now!
We are the destroyers! We have to stop now!
Why are you even doing this...
Here comes the main point
The disappointing scene
starts from here
How come?
Please keep watching
Yukai-san probably got hyped
and did this for the show
But then, look!
Endo ran away!
He knew he'll be destroyed
Look, look, I'm standing right here
What the heck is happening?
This was awful
-This is worse than the worst
-Yes, this is terrible
This is frightening!
Since a long time ago, I've been standing right here
It looks so good on Matsumoto!
I felt sorry for asking this senior
to mess around with us
The ocean, the sky, and the love of yours
They are all the same as the unchanging earth
What kind of world is this?
Ru Ru Ru-ru-ru...
Good question
Ru Ru Ru-ru Ru-ru-ru...
Seriously, what the
heck is going on?
Ru-ru ru-ru-ru Ru-ru ru-ru-ru...
Are these 3 people crazy?
We're just doing
what he told us to do
Yes, exactly
You said your masterpiece is ruined because of the singer, right?
No way...
You moved the wig without permission
Well, I did move the wig, but...
What's even going on with Matsumoto and Tanaka's song?
Honestly, what was that?
I thought you guys will look like fairies, but I turned out to be completely wrong!
How the heck is that a fairy!
We won't look like fairies by any chance
I was terrified that day
I even thought I may get hit by a car on the way home
I actually thought the same thing...
This time, I honestly created it with all my might
Let's start with Cocorico
He forced us to do all kinds of things again...
We haven't watch this yet, of course
This is the most difficult one of all time
We had no idea how to express the mood of the song...
Endo, what happened? You went to a hot spring?
No, well...I didn't
The title of the song for Cocorico, is purposely chosen to be Cocorico, the name of your duo
Oh, that's the title?
Yes, so I hope you'll treasure it
I believe you two will be doing stage performances in the future
So I hope this could be the theme song of your performances
Oh, seriously?   -Yes
My impression of you two...
From a global perspective...
Is India
This is a country that is on the rise
But the rise has stopped recently, right?
-Just like how you guys have stopped
-No, we stopped a long time ago
Well, yes...   -We stopped ages ago
So I hope Cocorico can be on the rise again, just like India
Just like India?
Just do it like fury and go like "Bang!"   -Got it
You guys are lacking momentum!
Momentum...that doesn't sound good, but fine...
And this is the song for Cocorico, created with all his heart
So this song
is called Cocorico..
Yes, that's the title
Hey hey hey, Women
This is terrible!
Love you, love you, love you, love you
Hey hey hey, Man
Absolutely awful!
Love you, love you, love you, love you
What the heck is this?
So cold, so cold...
My heart was captured by your lips
Learn to refuse, you guys
Love you, forever
My heart was captured by your eyes
Is this really
Indian language?
Where should I take you out?
Yes, it is
Hey hey hey, Women
Where will you take me out?
Hey hey hey, Man
It's even somehow frightening
Hey hey hey, Women
Love you, love you, love you, love you
It's not frightening, right?
No way, it is frightening
Hey hey hey, Man
Love you, love you, love you, love you
Hey hey hey, Women
He screwed you guys up
Hey hey hey, Man
Love you, love you, love you, love you
What is the concept of this song?
Firstly, this is India music
I really like this style
I feel energetic whenever I watch India movies
And since Cocorico are both not energetic recently
No, that's not true
He always says we're not energetic
You're interrupting their business!
He asked us to use this as the theme song...
At the Lumine theatre?
He kept asking us to show the India side in us
But I found it really difficult to do so
And both of us...
Actually just me, was asked to retake for many times
Yeah, he retook his scenes quite a few times
What did he do wrong?
He's crap at it
Well, that's understandable   -Right?
He's simply crap at it
The song has also been recorded during the rehearsal
Hey hey hey, Man
Hey hey hey, Man   -Wait a second! Wait!
Wait a second, stop, stop!
For real!?
What do you mean?
Endo okay   -Thank you very much
You, for real?   -Eh? Really?
What was that horribly off-key singing!
Hey hey hey, Man
Hey hey hey...
Stop laughing dude!
I've put in so much effort to make this song!
Yes, you're right
If possible...
I want you to sing in female voice
Female voice?   -Female voice
Hey hey hey, Man
Just like this   -Sounds good
Well, the song do stick in one's head though
Oh, thank you very much
Yes, it was really catchy
The next song is for this duo
Downtown-san!
I know nothing about this song too
I completed the songs and gave it to the staff three or four days ago
And the female assistant producer of Gaki no Tsukai said...
"Your song for Downtown really made me cry"
She really said this
For real
But I think that girl just quit her job though
No, she didn't!
We can't get a hold of her   -Of course we can!
We've been left on read
Why would she leave us on read?!
No idea why...   -Good morning
Good morning
It's insane, huh?
Yes, very insane
Right?   -I heard it from the staffs
And I thought I don't want to do this   -Exactly
No, no, please...
This is something that we mustn't do   -Exactly
No, no, give me a break
The lyrics...to be honest...
I didn't think about it at all
What do you mean?
I didn't think about it at all, and...
Excuse me
Is this being recorded?
Of course it is being recorded!
Just look at the number of cameras
It's completely being recorded
I thought this is not being recorded   -No way, it is
This don't need to be recorded though
Please record it, from the start to the end
I didn't think about the lyrics at all
Then I wrote it all at once promptly and smoothly
Eh? I see
Therefore, it sounds very natural
So we don't need to add any twists and turns, right?   -Yes, exactly!
Excuse me
Are there batteries in it (mic)?   -Yes, there are
The highlight of this song is the slow rap   -I see
I've never sang anything like this before
Please give it a try
We like the same type of girl
We have the same sense of Owarai
Phew...this is terrible
We like the same type of girl
We have the same sense of Owarai
When we're happy, when we're sad, when we're brightened, when we're frustrated
Who made us feel like that?   -Wait, wait, wait!
What's going on with you?
I was scared too, what happened?
I understand it, I know you're getting hyped, but...
He sang it so well, so of course I'm hyped
I know, I understand, but...
Please be patient, it's not your turn yet
You have your slow rap section later too   -Fine...
Tie me up, please tie me up!
I can't control myself
Please enjoy Downtown's song with slow rap parts
Look at the costume,
doesn't it look familiar?
We saw it just now!
These two are
from the video we
watched just now!
-I don't get it
-A hand on the shoulder
We've been together since we were kids, me and you, we've always been together
No, no, hell no
How long will it last? This precious time with you
All I can say is hell no
We like the same type of girl
You call that rap?
We have the same sense of Owarai
I was laughing already...
When we're happy, when we're sad, when we're brightened, when we're frustrated
Both of you are
laughing already
Who made us feel like that?
I bet God decided it
Very good
If that's so, then I have to tell God something
The Kansai accent
is so strong
We like the same food
No way, it's different
We hate the same food
I told you it's different
When we're happy, when we're sad, when we're brightened, when we're frustrated
Who made us feel like that?
Very good
I bet God decided it
If that's so, then I have to tell God something
Thank you for letting us meet each other
(They're holding hands)
(What are they trying to express?)
I see, I see
This is really worth watching
No way, it's not worth watching   -It surely is
I don't really get the music
But this is so funny
This is so interesting
Hamada's shoulder became hotter and hotter
It became hotter and hotter
Of course it'll become hotter   -Yeah, right?
The title of this song is Downtown
Yeah, it is
Is this also Hosei-san's impression of Downtown-san?
Yeah, the lyrics came to my mind promptly and smoothly
How long did it take you to write this?
So I created all three songs in one day
Then I wrote the lyrics the next day
Did you create it in your own room?
Well, I have my own music studio, outside
Outside?   -Outside?
You mean you rented another room?   -Yes
You scared me...
Come on, I'm not doing it in the wild
I thought you treat the wild as your own room
I thought like "this dude is finally becoming insane!"
We're talking to God in Kansai dialect, huh?
Incredible
Yes, you're right, and that symbolizes innocence
No matter who you're talking to...
I honestly almost punch you in the face just now
"Bang!"
Please don't, that's too dangerous
Please don't do that
Please don't do that, it's such a brilliant song
Okay, so here comes the climax
This song is for the five of us, and the title is Gaki no Tsukai
I just have to say that everyone is so hyped
And I almost got crushed by the enthusiasm from you guys
Were we even hyped?   -I don't think so
By the way...
I feel like I drew a bad lot...
There's no such thing as a bad lot
None of it is a bad lot
What do you guys think after listening to the song?
Well, it's definitely Hosei-san's kind of style
Hosei-san loves this kind of songs
I listened to it in my car
And I almost wanted to hit-and-run
No way, please don't do that
This is such a troublesome song!
Eh, really?
I'm in love with this song
Yeah, I knew you like this kind of songs
A loud and explosive song
Nah...
Hey Boy, inside your mind, with bare hands, pour everything out
Hey Girl, inside your heart, with bare hands, pour everything out
Hosei is in charge of demonstrating and teaching the members
What does it mean?
There's many things that I want to talk about, but...
We really need to get hyped, huh?
Yes, it's much better if you're hyped
Yeah, it is, on the whole
For the first line "On your head, pull every hair out with bare hands"
Who's gonna sing that line?
No? I got it wrong?
There's no such line
Ah, sorry
"Inside your mind, with bare hands, pour everything out", that's right
I thought it's a self-deprecating song
Formation practice
...inside your heart, with bare hands, pour everything out
Hey boy!
Is this only broadcasted on TVer?
Nope, it's broadcasted on Nippon TV, and across Japan
As usual
Is it possible to only broadcast it online?
This is will be broadcasted across Japan
Hosei has been very fastidious about the costume as well
Matsumoto-san, please come to the front
Come on...
At the moment that it was flipped, this didn't even get a laugh
I want to get a laugh
I want to get a laugh if I have to do this
Hosei produce finale
This is a song for the five members, with fastidiously chosen costumes
Hey Boy, inside your mind, with bare hands, pour everything out
What the heck is
this look, honestly
Hey Girl, inside your heart, with bare hands, pour everything out
Hey yo, I'm gonna defeat this, I'm gonna defeat the world
Shout against the world, wow wow wow wow
It didn't get a laugh at all
Let's change it with our power, change the world with our power
Turn the world upside down, wow wow wow wow
Then we will finally be free, and we can fulfill our wishes
I'll definitely make it come true, wow wow wow wow
We're gonna do it together, we're gonna fight against the world together
Shout against the world, wow wow wow wow
Hey Boy, inside your mind, with bare hands, pour everything out
Hey Girl, inside your heart, with bare hands, pour everything out
You're the only
one that's hyped
What the heck
was this, honestly
This was awkward
This was so
awkward
What was he
wearing on his head?
-Is that the thing in rugby?
-Yes, it's from rugby
What is he thinking?
Hey Boy, inside your mind, with bare hands, pour everything out
Hey Girl, inside your heart, with bare hands, pour everything out
This is awful
How dare you make that face, dude?
What do you think about this as a producer, Yama-chan?
I think this is a masterpiece   -Oh, really?
In regard to the costumes...   -You were very fastidious, huh?
I was super fastidious about it
And each of them costed a lot of money
And there's no money left for the set today
So that's why it's so plain
It's completely empty
I see, so that's why
It's the set for NHK's gymnastic shows
To be honest, I really don't want this to be aired
No, no, no...
This needs to be aired multiple times
Dear people related to the music industry
I would like to sell these 3 songs
You're stuttering like crazy
This is Downtown-san's greatest wish
He's still continuing...
Please, Downtown-san really wants to release their CD
No, no...   -They want to release CD for Gaki no Tsuakai!
Everybody, please do them a favor!
I'm saying this for real, and Cocorico agrees with me too, right?
Hell no, he's going crazy