I didn't think there'd be a second episode of this
11 months ago, I gave those bastards a heavenly punishment
I thought that would be enough to set them straight,
But those bastards haven't learned their lesson
Do you know who I mean by "bastards"?
The same 4 idiots from Gaki no Tsukai
Those bastards...
ARE WORTH LESS THAN TRASH
Today... I shall bring the wrath of the heavens upon them again
Timed & Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
Starting with this moron, the idiot Hamada
11 months ago I gave him a good lesson...He didn't learn a thing!
The theme is, an impression in the style of Furutachi Ichiro
Oh no!
So this is Jiji-nuki, it's a game like Baba-nuki where you pair up cards,
And near the end,
You were looking at my cards the whole time right?
Stop doing that Tanaka!
When I said "This one" you were just straight up looking at them like this
Did you see that?
The Idiot Hamada says "You were peeking right" straight away
Stop peeking!!
He kept repeating it! See he said it again
You were peeking so hard
Stop glancing at them
There again!
So while I was playing Jiji-nuki that bastard beside me kept repeating that
He's like a small dog that loves to bark
He's a Chihuahua! A Yorkshire Terrier! A Pomeranian!
THIS IS WHAT HE REALLY LOOKS LIKE THOUGH!
So starting from Hosei-san, pick a card
From Matsumoto-san right? Ok
Hmm? Oh right
Oh I got one! Right away
BB Queen - Dancing Ponpokurin
BB Queen right?
Matsumoto-san just needs to get this one right?
Yes, exactly, yes...
That's the order...
That's not right...
Eh?
Hosei-san just took one now right?
Endo will take from Hosei-san now
Oh right, I got the order wrong is all
It's Tanaka's fault right?!
Furthermore, during a different theme...
Tanaka you better get this one
No no , that's too difficult
Yes, I had this card
That's wrong! You messed up!
EH?!
Give that back to Yama-chan, and then Tanaka take it from Hamada-san
Who the hell is this guy?
This was Tanaka's fault
*clicks tongue*
He said it very clearly. He said it clearly just now
What the hell man
The game itself is complicated to keep up with
So hearing them
Nag & Nag & Nag & Nag & Nag & Nag
It just confuses me! Who the fuck was that guy from the staff? Holding things up
The staff are scared of Hamada, they just go along with him
They're corrupted by Hamada
Today, I shall make a clear declaration,
I SHALL NEVER PLAY JIJI NUKI AGAIN
This is "Easy to Win Beach Volleyball",
The aim is to win by 100 points
Alright!
What's with that sloppy attitude?! YOU'RE SLOPPY!
Are you gonna play or not? Which is it? ARE YOU GONNA PLAY?!
I'll play!
I'll play, I-i'll...
The guy on the other team's bench is angry... Is everything alright?
They could just all get along...This is like power hasrassment
OI!!
Fifi was worried for me right? She said it was "like power harassment"
When his switch flips,
He just becomes un-understandable, he just won't stop
You know what?
Like...Um...Get Yoshimoto to fire him
DISMISS DISMISS DISMISS
DISMISS HIM
He's too backwards for In age where TV has to adhere to compliance
He can't understand this era
I heard...that guy came out with a song?
WOW WAR TONIGHT ~ Sometimes we create a Movement
"Sometimes like this" - Shut the fuck up!
"Just a little bit-" Shut the fuck up!
Impossible Impossible Impossible Impossible!
How are you gonna create a movement?!
You're corrupted by movement
And his partner is a piece of work too...
The next battle - Wake up! World Record! Slimy Climbing!
This was an episode where everything was slimy, well just watch,
And the point was to get over that height
Poof
He just farted
(Everyone) That's so embarassing!
OI! You just farted now right?!
(Background) No farting!
That guy loves farts
He loves farts, asses, and shit!
So he will always notice right away
He'll immediately turn to face the fart
Even though he's almost 60!
He loves farts!
(Narrator) Which Gaki member does Toru Muranishi think is the filthiest?
So this was the 100 Quiz for Toru Muranishi
Tanaka-kun seems like he has a lot of stuff to clean off his di
Ahh, he has a dirty dick?
He did
So he's talking about dick cheese?
Ahh I see. That's a proper insult.
Yeah for real!
Which Gaki member does Toru want to swap places with?
This question, he answers who
Tanaka-san
He said me
He has a normal personality, he's a normal person
A normal guy with too much dick cheese?
No need to bring it up again
A guy with a normal personality
And because of that you don't clean your smegma
That guys loves dick cheese too
Farts, asses, shit, dick cheese
That guy loooves dirty jokes
Even though he knows they have to bleep it out, he kept saying it!
He might have big muscles,
But his brain is all shrivled up
Which Gaki member does Toru think is filthiest?
This question comes up everytime, and I'm not satisified with this happening everytime
Endo and I didn't back down
Yes, I just has to be Tanaka I think
This bastard...Whenever this question comes up he always writes my name
He never once thought about something different
He alwaaaays writes the same thing
That's why all he can ever do is Ho-Ho-Hoi
What the hell is Ho-Ho-Hoi
It's not funny at all...
There was one other guy,
I forgot about that useless guy
That Rakugka from Naniwa
That guy, for the "I think you like this item" series,
For an accessory for Shiraku-shisho,
This is what he chose
Yup it's funny that's it get rid of it
get rid of it
The Fuji Soba incident...
Is that a Fuji Soba? The place near Bancho
On NTV Road
Yeah NTV road
This is NTV road right?
That right?
Yes, either down the hill or on the way down I think, right around there,
Almost there
Here?
Here! That one!
It's a Yudetaro...
I've messed up...
Tanaka where are you?
I thought of everyone so I went to the one near the studio in Kojimachi,
Kojimachi?
Yes
But I ended up at a Yudetaro...
I see we should have changed the card and gone to Yudetaro
Just as Matsumoto said.
Just come to Yudetaro
Those guys never shut up about this either
"You went to Yudetaro!" ... "You went to Yudetaro that time!"
So many so many so often so often they never shut up about it
It's a Soba store, it's a standing soba store
Just think of it as the same!
Come ... to Yudetaro
This time too,
Time time too ... Those 4 idiots ... I want to give them a heavenly punishment!
First Ever on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arrahende Chiki Chiki
Bet your life on this one sip, KIKI Canned Coffee!!
Alright!
This is the 44th one
Fourty four this time
You don't drink this stuff?
I don't really drink it that often, it's too sweet
You don't like sweet drinks? Tanaka you don't drink it?
Yeah I wonder
I've never really seen him drinking it
But I think he might drink it the most out of all of us
Canned coffee?
I think now I shall bring down heavenly punishment on these 4 idiots
Who's going first? Shozo will you go?
Can I? Alright
Go to the front
It's canned coffee...
Oh no
This seems like a tricky one
The one chosen for Endo is a smooth tasting canned coffee
Alright then
I've drunk this one before
Really?
Eh?
Are you done now?
Yes, I should be good
Alright then
Damn, I think i've drunk this one before
Alright excuse me, I'll get started with this then
"Beat Black"?
I feel like it's not the one
It's not?
Well the smell is just as important as the taste
Yeah
I can tell
For real?
It's different?
It's totally different!
Totally different?
Really?
The one I drank was not Beat Black
Wow!
I think we can tell - Well it's only been 1
Well well well yes
Ehh? Hold on what should I do
You start to lose your sense of taste
If I touch it I have to drink it right?
Yes if you touch it
Yeah if you touch it
It's canned coffee, so the smell might be hard to discern
Alright here I go
Matsumoto-san, I can tell.
Hosei-san, I can tell
Oh really?
It's wrong! This is totally different!
The one I drank...
This one, was not Beat
Alright alright alright
You can really tell?
If I get this I win 100,000 yen...
Actually they're all Beat aren't they? Beat Black...
Yeah they chose a lot of Beat ones
This is a Beat special
Here I go
Are you starting to lose confidence?
You're starting to lose confidence right?
Yeah he might be
Ah but this one is dangerous!
This is where you gotta decide!
Indeed!
Hold on! Is this it?
It's not it right?...
Can you really do this?
What do you wanna do?
Do your best!
What should I do
You can do it!
This is so hard!
No way, this is only the 3rd one
Yeah, you don't want to take too much time
Alright, excuse me
The one I drank, was not Beat special
You're doing pretty well
Yes, I am
4, 6, I've cleared 7
Alright
Anytime now I should get
Damn really?
Now that you've come that far you gotta win
Yeah
Yes
C'mon clear them Endo
Do your best
Yes indeed
The one I drank was not Black Morning
Wow!
Alrighty
That was close!
Too close!
Hot!
C'mon hurry up Endo
OK
Endo!
Don't waste time like that, you have that habit
I've never drank these ones before
Go ahead
Do your best
Thank you
Here I go
Alright go!
Ahhhh...
The one I drank was,
Do it!
Endo!
"Time Premium"
Endo! Hurry!
Hurry!
Was not it!
ENDO!!!
ALRIGHT!
ENDO
ENDOOOOO
Alright! Thank you!
OK!
Thank you!
Alright, I'm kinda happy about this
The one I drank was not Cafe Choice Coffee...
Seriously?
It was that one?
Damn, what the hell is this?
Hold on hold on
This is scary...
Don't just do Ho-Ho-Hoi!
What is this?! I'm scared!
That hurt!
The next one... Can you go please?
Yeah, c'mon clear this one
Oh yeah
This feels kinda wet...well whatever
We've decided
Hamada-san here you go
The smell first
The smell comes first
First remember the smell...
The smell is pretty important
Hamada...
Oh? Is it that bad?
The smell is important
What's this fancy one?
Sorry?
It's probably one of the expensive ones
Yeah the most expensive one
How is it?
Hamada?
Hamada-san cut it out
Keep going Hamada
I-
this-
What'd you say?
I-
You know this whole time,
I've had like, a head, a head-
This is way closer than the last one
Damn this is a tough one!
dAmN tHiS iS a toUgh OnE!
Is it this one?
iS iT thIs ONe
"is it this one"
Should I bet on this?
Oh will you?
I think even If I think about it...
Do your best. Alright!
The one I drank was this canned coffee!
That sucks...
I got it wrong huh...
You'll never get another advertisement for canned coffee!
Ow!
Alright
This one is too hard
Now they should behave
Alright let's go
That's a wrap!
I'm very sorry!
The Bazooka was terrifying
I was saying "Ow"
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. You told me that last time too.
You said that last time too
I had no idea what to do
Yeah, I'm sorry about that
How was it Tanaka-san?
Just...So unfortunate
This is so unfortunate
You slipped on the stand
I slipped
That was dangerous
Matsumoto-san was there, so I grabbed his shoulders
He was soooo stable. Like a rock.
I thought "What a reliable guy"
Timed & Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband