Today is that man's birthday
I came all the way from NTV here in these clothes,
Nobody laughed at it
Nobody laughed?
I came in these clothes on my 54th birthday,
Literally nobody laughed
You'd think it would get a few laughs
Yeah
Well, we have a cake as well. It's a birthday after all.
Thank you. I'm really pleased.
Let's celebrate together!
Hold on, sorry, hold on
It went out...
Sorry, we were singing too loud...
It went out from our singing?
Our breath put it out?
This is an awful age
It blew out right?
Oh it's all melted now
You can't even read the number
The 5 is gone now!
Are candles this hard to light?
They both went out
That's not even a 5 anymore
Is there a plate?
This is...
A bad impression
It is!
It really is
They have one, behind you
Is there a 4?
There's no 4?
Just the 5 is fine
Just the 5?
This will work
How many times have we done this with these members?
That's true
Like 30 times?
Is this the 29th year of this show?
So at 55, it'll be 30 years
30 years is amazing isn't it?
It is, yeah
The cast hasn't really changed that much either huh
We had a lot of backroom talks about replacing some of the cast though
You guys don't talk about that right?
The company told us too
Yoshimoto tells us, and so does NTV
"you guys should change the cast soon"
They thought that Yamasaki would finally quit the show when he moved to Osaka
I would "finally quit"?
Cause, you know, coming just for this
Yeah getting on the bullet train every time
The conductor of the bullet train was saying it too
Even an employee of Japan Railway?
"Do we really need to let this guy on" he said
"Where the hell do you need to go?"
Tokyo of course
"Is there any fuckin point in him going there?" is what the conductor said
"fuckin point"?
What a foul mouth
A foul mouth, seriously...
The girl with the J-Diner was saying it too
The trolley thing
The trolley girl?
That's called a J-Diner?
"Why does this person show up sometimes?"
Since I got my start on Gaki,
It's been 21 years
Always,
You were so kind to me
The hard work of making comedy,
The brilliance of creating comedy,
Those two things, always,
I learned up close from you
Matsumoto-san, Matsumoto-san,
Thank you for everyday
When I'm feeling and don't know what to do,
Matsumoto-san, Matsumoto-san,
Thank you for everything,
Those times, always,
You turn it into laughter
Thank you for being born
Well, yeah,
How was that?
No not, "yeah", it's your birthday
It was nice, thank you
Thanks
A nice surprise
I didn't mean to startle you
The words "thank you"...
They seem like simple words but they're really,
Hard to say
They're hard to say
This was a special opportunity
Right, this was a good celebration
What do you think?
What do you mean?
That he did this for you
I already said I was glad,
Songs are nice aren't they
You can say the things you can't normally say
I see. What about the lyrics?
Did you like them?
I did yeah. Tanaka's,
Well he's not a professional of course, he has his own ability,
That's true, of course,
But still struggling hard despite the lack of talent,
He still managed to sing the song
That's what I felt
Who cares about the singing
Was he able to convey his feelings to you?
Yes, I said
I said YES already
Let's just get along
This is a birthday party after all
Since it's a special day
It's fine if Matsumoto-san gets a little happy
That's enough for me
There's no reason I wouldn't be happy
I'm glad! That makes me happy
You wrote these lyrics Tanaka?
Of course, yes
How old were you when you joined Gaki?
It was in the 4th year
4th year
You joined in the fourth year?
Around the 4th year
Around 25
That's fast
So in another sense, there were only 4 years of Gaki without you
I'm so grateful
From the warmups
You guys were called Cocorico Bombers right?
And part way through you got rid of Bombers
I introduced Tanaka to you right Matsumoto-san?
Yamasaki came to get me
It was during the Bubble Era,
When I get to Tokyo on the first bullet train,
There's a massive line of taxis,
So I asked Yamasaki, "sorry, could you please line up for me?"
Like 30 minutes before I arrive
And I think maybe Tanaka was lonely by himself,
It was the very first time I met you
Me and Yamasaki were in the back, and Tanaka was next to the driver
He didn't say a single word the entire drive
Of course you don't get nervous now
It was your first time meeting him
Of course yes
We saw from behind, his face was like mud coloured
His face was like earthenware
Honestly, and he wouldn't move either
He wouldn't move or talk at all
It wasn't an issue of whether he was funny or not
I was nervous, yeah
I was introduced to him after that
I wanted to say this
Do you remember, the first time
The first time
As a Gaki member,
I hit on a girl and picked her up
And brought her with me
I was a pain in the ass
At the Nakameguro Video Rental Store "Dan"
I had no money,
"Use my card,
"Just rent it", is what you said to me
To me, who can't see a future
You gave me a light
The person who gave me my comedian passport,
Matsumoto-san, it was you
Let's go stay on this road,
And run as hard as we can
I am grateful to you
Brillaint
He sang for you
How nice. How was it?
It was great, yeah
What was?
Like "Oh yeah that happened"
I see
A video store called Dan?
Yes, in Nakameguro. It's gone now.
It's gone now, I saw it when I passed by it after a long time
After shooting Gaki, he let me ride in the Jaguar he had
I didn't have any money, so Matsumoto-san said "rent it with this"
What kind of video?
A perverted one
Just you two? Didn't even pick one movie?
We didn't, we just got dirty videos
How many? How many did you rent?
We got about 7, and with Matsumoto-san in the car,
Matsumoto-san was going through them like,
"This was yours right Endo?" "This one was mine"
That's what I remembered, it was so nostalgic
They don't have DVDs like now,
You can't tell by looking at it, you need to remember the title
We messed that up sometimes right?
But yeah, after Gaki, we'd do things like that
I learned a lot from you
Like massages
"I know a good place"
What kind of massages?
Like they massage your shoulder and neck?
...A perverted one
A perverted? What do you mean?
I had no idea. The name of the place was "Magic Hand"
I can't tell what it's supposed to be
"What kind of magic is it"
They used some amazing magic on us right?
A very petite woman, with a mysterious bag
I tried to look, but they said I absolutlely couldn't
Then she dimmed the lights, and after that...
To the point I have no memory of it, she did a lot of things to me
Her name was Eri-san by the way
TN: "Tsuru no Ongaeshi" is a story about a man who saves a crane from hunters, and that crane later secretly becomes his wife, and has to transform in a room while he's not looking.
I've heard that name before!
It wasn't exaclty "Tsuru no Ongaeshi",
But she was like "Please don't look at all"
Inside?
What did she do to you, in the end?
I, became a little girl,
You did? Shozo you became a girl?
Yes, in that moment I became a girl
And she had me in this position,
She did so many things. SO many things.
I don't think it's that strange
Became a girl right?
I'm gonna record this episode
Today's broadcast?
Something like Hamada Shogo would be good now
Thank you,
For using me Matsumoto-san
And in the future too,
Please Matsumoto-san
Thank you,
for laughing, Matsumoto-san
And in the future too,
Please, Matsumoto-san
Stoic when it comes to comedy,
Ability that I can't match
He's super witty,
I really admire that
The pinnacle of comedy,
The most creative ideas,
The front line in the comedy world,
Can't imagine someone who won't laugh
Can't imagine someone who doesn't admire
People aspire to you,
You bring light to a dark world
Thank you,
For laughing Matsumoto-san
And in the future too,
Please, Matsumoto-san
Please
Happy Birthday!
This one was unusual
There was some rap
They're youngsters
We are the youngest ones here yeah
We though we should do something new
Something different from you guys
I couldn't do it I don't think
I turned everything I wanted to convey into rap lyrics
I thought it was just gonna be Imoto
Matsumto-san I've been on Gaki for 18 years
Do you still think my name is Imoto?
Matsumoto-san said it without thinking
He called you Imoto?
It's Inomoto
I thought it be just him singing
txt267
txt268
txt269
txt270
txt271
Oh really?
Do you remeber?
After the recording
You treated me with dinner
Always, on the way back
"I'll shop at the store near your house on my home"
You muttered, dropped me off,
And disappeared into the store
"Good work today!" I bowed my head
And then went home
And the days since then,
You told me,
"Back then,
"I never needed to buy anything"
But for your sake,
I dropped you home
The beginning though was...it was kind of...
It got better and better near the end
In the start he was,
Were you trying to do an impression?
No not at all. I'm scolded about this a lot.
By who?
What?
It was kind of like Hamada Shogo
Sorry, it's just that our singing voices are similar
Do you remember what he talked about?
Yeah, I think we all do things like that
I think Hamada-san has done it too.
Seniors actually look out a lot for their juniors
Like if I pay for his taxi,
That's kind of bothersome to the senior having to hand over 1000s of yen
Yeah, so, it's fine to just drop him off nearby
Often, yeah, I didn't need to buy anything but I'd go there
I see
This is not that big a deal
He did it for me every time
I think anyone would do it
But still, I'm thankful for it
Back then, we were together 4-5 times a week
I also had nobody really,
He's actually the first one to come to Tokyo
And then half a year later DownTown-san came right?
Matsumoto-san was really all alone
I was also alone
I was also alone, so it was us two together everyday
Did anything happen like Endo's story, like some place you went to
Often at the video store in Nakano Sakaue
Back then I used Matsumoto-san's card to rent a video,
We got a bunch, we got around 6,
And I've completely forgotten to return them
Back then Yamasaki wasn't married yet,
And he doesn't really tidy up, his room was all cluttered
It got lost?
It got mixed up and lost
He genuinely snapped at me for that
They didn't let me rent when I went there
I said all sorts of things to him in that hour. All sorts of abuse.
I didn't think he would've been so angry at me not returning the videos,
But it was my fault
Since then when I would yell at him,
Yamasaki would start drawing Doraemon
Not to run away,
He wants it to save him
If I draw Doraemon it'll save me
I'm not doing it conciously,
You're not drawing it while he's yelling at you right?
I am
It's a habit
That would make him more pissed
No way, for real?
If he sees me doing that he doesn't get mad
It's like I'm Gian
Oh really
After this, a super unexpected guest!
We hung out with girls too
We would hang out together,
And then became friends,
And then us and the girls would meet again, us 4
And there, a girl I met for the first time,
"Hey, do you wanna drink something, Jiin?"
She called him "Jiin"
Jiin?
She took it from Hitoshi
TN: Hito (人) can also be read as Jin
She took the Hito from Hitsohi and got Jiin
"Jiin, you're not drinking anything?"
It was the first time you met her right?
It was the first time
You're fine with that?
Well yeah, it's probably cause, that girl was really,
When we were alone together...I embraced it I guess
Like "I guess Jiin is fine"
Closed the distance quickly
And Yama-chan was like "What is she saying"?
Yeah. I thought oh crap, calling him Jiin,
It was back when he was angry and rambunctious,
I thought he would go like \n"WHO YOU CALLING JIIN?"
But no he was all smiley
"He can accept that" I thought
He can accept it
That must've been amazing, Jiin
There a lot of different memories
It's a long history
Matsumoto-san happy birthday!
Thank you !
Oh, thank you very much!
Next Week
Matsumoto Birthday Party - Part 2
Unexpected guests!
And his partner Hamada too...