TG
Note: Oogui is a thing in Japan where people consume a shitload of food in one sitting. There are genuine competitions where people compete against one another, seeing who can eat more of various dishes.
The 7 Gaki Members do the Oogui challenge
Tonight, the 7 Gaki members take on the Oogui challenge!
English Checker:
James
Mickstar
Sacro
Team Gaki Presents
Translators:
Typesetter:
The first annual Gaki no Tsukai Chiki Chiki
Work together and defeat Gal Sone
Oogui Competition!
We're going to defeat Gal Sone?
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Apparently so...
Surely we can't do it?
But if we all try our best,
maybe we can beat her
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Yamasaki Hosei
We can do it!
No no no no!
But you know, just with the regulars
it would be a bit too tough
Yeah
I see
So we
get Vacuum Fujiwara today...
Thank you very much
Fujiwara Kazuhiro
Inomoto Takafumi
The Charanporan
Vacuum Fujiwara
Vacuum-san!
The Vacuum!
Hello Vacuum-san!
What is the reason he is called Vacuum Fujiwara!?
The man who just sucks up his meals, Vacuum Fujiwara
Narrator Chihiro Tago
On the episode "Eat snacks with rice", Fujiwara...
Aired 5th November 2006
Last year in November, in an episode where they had to eat loads of rice
Fujiwara dominated
This is good
I bet
It might taste good, but seriously, how many bowls do you want to eat?
shoved 9 bowls of rice into his stomach
Everyone suffered,
but this man shoved 9 bowls of rice into his stomach
And this is how Vacuum Fujiwara was born
Whatever happens, I always eat my meals
Whatever happens...
Obviously...
He got dressed up for this occasion today to look special but...
he just looks like Tamori-san from the old times
NOTE: TAMORI IS A FAMOUS JAPANESE TARENTO
Oh yeah!
That's true
And the person they will go against this time, Gal Sone appears.
Food Fighter
Gal Sone
m 0 0 l 600 0 l 600 210 l 0 210 l 0 0
The fact this girl here eats loads
I know
I just don't see it
Thank you
On a live broadcast this morning, she was eating loads of okonomiyaki as well...
she ate 3kg of Okonomiyaki
On this morning's "Radical" (TV program)
My stomach is a bit out at the moment; please touch it
See, her stomach is out
Holy shit, that's so scary!
She's like a mermaid
Like "Let me come out already"
Gaki Team
Gal Sone
Oogui Battle
This battle
is a 7 vs 1 battle
7 meals of 7kg
Whoever eats it all first wins!
Whoever eats all 7 meals, weighing around 7kg, first wins!
Cake
Curry
Gyoza
Hamburger
Okonomiyaki
Sushi
Yakisoba
Gal Sone will eat all 7 meals by herself
Gal Sone will eat all of this by herself
The 7 members of Gaki
will aim to eat 1 dish each
Gaki will eat in a relay style, eating one dish each
If one of them cannot eat it all
Vacuum Button
press the button and Vacuum Fujiwara will suck it up for you!
However, if you really cannot eat anymore, Vacuum Fujiwara will suck it up right for you
Vacuum Fujiwara is the key
to the outcome of this battle!
So, Fujiwara holds the key to the outcome of this battle!
But Matsumoto-san is awful
Why?
2 hours ago, he ate a meal!
No way!
I know...
Take this seriously, man!
Hamada-san had pilaf an hour ago...
Are you serious?!
What the hell is wrong with Downtown?!
Downtown!
What is wrong with you!?
Seriously!
Do you have 0 kindness!?
You'd think that!
Right?
This isn't a show where we really give it our all...
Don't say that!
We need to decide our order
Gaki Team decide their order of eating
So we can only really eat 1 dish each
Am I over here?
That's right
Yes
Hamada-san loves yakisoba though
That's true
If it's something you love, you can probably eat more than usual...
Don't you guys underestimate us
Don't underestimate the over 40's!
Yeah, seriously!
Cake
Curry
Endo Shozo
Gyoza
Hamada Masatoshi
Hamburger
Inomoto Takafumi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Okonomiyaki
Sushi
Tanaka Naoki
Vacuum Fujiwara
Yakisoba
Yamasaki Hosei
Will they be able to eat all 7 meals?!
And lastly..
On our side
Yup
If we can't go any further
Uh huh
We can surrender
If either team cannot eat anymore,
White flag button
they can surrender and end the battle
I see
Surrender
But the only person to press that button should be Vacuum-san, right?
That's right
And Gal Sone, I'm sure you'll be fine but...
That's right, you can press it too if you can't eat anymore.
Okay
But you know
I see
Oogui battle
It looks delicious though, when you look from here
Oogui Battle: Start!
Go, Inomoto!
First dish: 35 nigiri pieces
The Oogui battle that 7 men challenged the 1 woman...
Starts with 35 pieces of sushi
But damn, this...
It's SO good!
There's a lot...
Yeah?
It's so delicious
You got this...
Yeah?
This one likes to taste her food and eat it.
She's not a super quick eater then.
I kind of lied to you, Matsumoto-san, I said I could eat a fair bit...
I eat about as much as a rabbit...
Are you going to be okay?
Do your best, man!
We're counting on you, man; you're the first one up!
Why the hell did you get cocky and go for the sushi then!?
This probably is the biggest plate out of the lot!
Yeah, definitely, it has rice too
Why would you choose this one?
She's already eaten all of the Toro (Medium Fatty Tuna)
Oh I see...
It's so good!
You said before she doesn't eat that fast
But she's not that slow at all...
I know, right?!
Yeah...
Her tempo is good...
And that is true
When Gal Sone shoves one of the nigiri into her mouth,
she tastes and enjoys it, but breaks it down quickly,
and in 10 seconds, she moves onto the next piece...
She should be feared!
She's so fast!
1 piece is like...
Oi Inamoto. It's not decreasing at all!
Oi Inomoto. It's not decreasing at all!
Come on man
We're counting on you!
Inomoto!
Are you screwed in the head?
You're first up, come on man
Yeah
Have you come with your family?
Eat some of the white fish too!
Eat it!
Yeah
Look, she's nearly finished!
Eat the squid, the squid
Really?!
Holy shit, she's quick
Eat the salmon roe and squid
We're counting on you
And she's not drunk any water or anything
He's probably thinking, "You fuckers try this then!"
I'm sorry but this is awful
This is
He should be quicker than this
Inomoto, hurry up and eat!
Inomoto!
He's biting so slowly...
Are you at your girlfriend's place?!
He'll eat even slower than this...
Are you worried what her parents might think?
Excuse me
Shit!
Wow
Can I get some ice cream please?
It's a chaser
It's just filling her up more so it's not against the rules
That's right
About 25
Try eating 25 at least
please
She's about to eat a chaser
Amazing...
What does that do?
She's totally taking the piss out of us
It's so nice!
Yeah
If you eat a dessert mid-meal, the taste changes and it becomes easier to eat
If you eat a dessert mid-meal, the taste changes and it becomes easier to eat.
Excuse me, please get me some ice cream
No!
Think about this
Why!?
You're first up!
You going to be able to eat that?
But the gari (pickled ginger) will be good!
Oh yeah
Yeah, good idea
Instead of ice cream
It will change the taste
It might help with digestion
Don't bring the ice cream please
If you order ice cream and don't eat it, Vacuum-san will have to suck that up too
Please don't eat ice cream then!
Gaki Team: Inomoto: 11 pieces
5 minutes since they've started
Inomoto has eaten 11 pieces
Gal Sone has already shoved 25 in her stomach
Gal Cone: 25 pieces
The gap between the two keeps increasing
But you're full already, right?
Come on, she's going to finish soon
And she moves onto the next dish?
Yeah
So we need to catch up... big time.
What?!
HELP ME, VACUUM-SAN!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
Go!
You're kidding me?!
Is it okay to use him so early?
Hurry, hurry!
I can't believe this...
Go for 2
Earlier than anticipated, Vacuum Fujiwara appears!
After this
See for yourself: Vacuum Fujiwara's eating abilities!
This man's appetite is...
Vacuum-san
Vacuum-san...
You eat 2 pieces in one go, huh?
He's definitely going to break his body...
Will you be okay?
You're going to get a fever again...
He definitely will...
You're working tomorrow, right?
2 at a time, you sure?
She has what, 3... 2 pieces?
Can she not eat a bit slower?
Yes
On the other hand, Vacuum-san here is...
He's last anyway
35 sushi pieces: 6 minutes 38 seconds
Gal Sone
Hold a minute, what the hell is with this?
It's not even competitive in the slightest...
We're like barely halfway
Not a battle at all...
Come on man!
I told you this would happen...
This is bad man
But if you get through this, Hamada-san will destroy the yakisoba
Hamada-san will...
Gal Sone 2nd plate: 4 people's worth of Yakisoba
Yeah, let's get through this
He will get us right back on track
Let's count on Hamada-san
But you know
I love ginger too
Vacuum-san...
Give me a second
What's wrong?
Hold on a minute...
When we looked away for a second...
Are you a fucking idiot?
No
You are...
We should be winning, at least on speed...
Definitely, we should
This is so delicious!
Easy to say!
Hurry up, man!
Yakisoba is delicious!
Oh really?
We might give up without even finishing the sushi...
What should we do...
Be the first time ever...
Vacuum-san
Come on, man
All the two of you have done is eat the sushi
I know!
10 minutes since the start
Gaki Team Sushi
Gal Sone Yakisoba
Gal Sone is already halfway through the yakisoba
The Gaki Team just has to finish the heavy on the jaw, squid sushi...
Can you not just swallow it down?
CAN YOU DO IT?!
Note: Since he is Hosei's junior, shouldn't say omae as it isn't polite
Don't say "Omae"
He's your senpai, man!
Vacuum decides to separate the squid
And plans on only eating the rice
You're not Vacuum-san at all!
You're not Vaccum-san at all!
This is just normal...
He's not sucking up anything!
He's just the everyday
old guy chilling with a hostess
Just a normal bloke
He's going to finish the sushi about the same time she finishes her dish...
She's nearly done with the yakisoba
Who the hell gave you the nickname "Vacuum-san"
YOU FUCKERS DID!
Coro-coro, Coro-coro
Note: Talking about how he can't suck anything up
Coro-coro, Coro-coro.
Yeah he's right
You really are...
Why do you have to be such a disappointment?
Just the squid left now
She easily finishes the yakisoba
4 people's worth of yakisoba: 12 minutes 58 seconds
Gal Sone
In just under 13 minutes, she flushed 2kg worth of food into her stomach
Vacuum!
Here comes the next one!
Gal Sone 3rd dish: 5 servings of hamburger
This looks delicious!
Damn, it's huge!
How is it in the centre? It better have been cooked right through.
It's fine, absolutely fine
It's so thick
I know...
Do I have to finish this?
There she goes...
Of course you do!
So delicious!
Obviously you idiot!
Hurry up and eat the squid, stop eating it 1 at a time!
Come on man!
Just go for it!
Eat them both at once
Come on
I can't eat as much squid as I thought!
What the hell man..?
Gal Sone tastes and eats the food...
You don't sense she is struggling at all with all this food...
You're putting on way too much soy sauce!
If there were legs, you wouldn't be able to eat that
The taste would be too strong
35 pieces of sushi: 14 minutes 23 seconds
Gaki Team
Hamada-san, we are counting on you!
We are counting on you!
Gaki Team 2nd dish: 4 people's worth of yakisoba
They finally finish the sushi, and now Hamada takes on the yakisoba
Will he be able to close the gap?
Go for it
Great!
This is what I am talking about
This right here!
Amazing, just as we expected
And... he's stopped...
Hang on, you had one mouthful!
He ate a bit too much on his first bite...
Come on!
Are you serious?!
That was a bit quick
At least this part!
He just took a bit too big a bite on the first one, give him a second...
That was a bit quick...
A bit quick to be drinking water...
Yeah, isn't it?
You shouldn't drink too much water
Just before, I had a beef pilaf with Suga-chan...
What the hell...
Why did you eat a beef pilaf?
Suga-san, why didn't you stop him? You knew we were going to do this today...
I know...
It's not going down that slowly...
It's good
Oh dear...
He put his chopsticks down...
He put it down...
He looks like he's in hell...
You cannot press the button whatever happens...
That's right
You already ate that much?!
That's amazing...
Your lips are so  fucking shiny...
Your lips are so fucking shiny...
Honestly, it's quite disgusting to look at...
You guys eat this then! You'll get shiny lips too!
Naa...
20 minutes in
Something happens to Gal Sone's body
Here, something strange happens to Gal Sone's body
You're going to undo your belt?
Yes, just loosen it a bit
Just take your pants off
Maybe it IS tough for Gal Sone-chan too...
Maybe, yeah.
I wonder, let's just observe for a while longer.
Yeah, let's do that
He's got the weird sweats...
Holy shit
I totally feel you
He's sweating so much
Yeah...
The weird sweats...
This hamburger is so nice!
He said, "I can't"
Don't look him in the eye...
Yeah, don't
Don't look at him
Don't look at him, Inomoto!
Don't look him in the eyes.
Don't do it!
He was saying something.
Don't!
He touched me!
Something touched me right here...
No no...
Shit, it stinks!
Just your imagination
Maybe put some mayonnaise on.
It won't do anything!
You've only eaten one person's worth...
Yeah
You really are...
That's good, if I ate one person's worth
That's not enough
What the hell is wrong with this? It's not coming out that well!
What the hell is this?!
But if you put too much on...
She's nearly finished the hamburger, just the carrots left
Don't you ever say you love yakisoba again...
He was saying "I'm going for it" at the beginning..
What happened to the pace at the start?
5 servings of hamburger: 21 minutes 19 seconds
Gal Sone
Gal Sone eats 3kg worth of food in less than 22 minutes.
This...
There's no way we can win
This is bad
HELP ME, VACUUM-SAN!
HE'S PUSHED IT!
Okay!
Here's where it really begins, Vacuum!
Go get it!
His second appearance, Vacuum Fujiwara reappears!
Gal Sone 4th dish: 3 people's worth of curry
Gal Sone tackles the 4th dish, 3 people's worth of curry.
Uh oh...
The image of Vacuum I've become accustomed to seeing
This freezing part right?
I see him like this often
But Vacuum-san, isn't the yakisoba really easy to eat?
Is it?
Your answer isn't "Yes, you're right"?
Damn, this is amazing
Look at the pace she is going at!
This is seriously bad!
She's getting into it
Yeah...
The curry has lots of meat and veg in it, so it's delicious
For real?
Is she serious?
Amazing...
Vacuum-san!
He's like seriously...
Vacuum!
Vacuum-san!
Vacuum Fujiwara not functioning at all
Vacuum!
Vacuum-san
he's just scooping it up and putting it back
This is it
I got it, let's just keep rotating then
Yeah
Eat a bit, and then
Then rotate
Gaki Team
Change the rules so they can keep rotating
Gaki Team changes the rules so they can keep rotating so the battle goes on.
After this
Matsumoto makes a miracle happen!!
And finally, Matsumoto appears. Will a miracle happen?!
Get out, Vacuum-san. Matsumoto-san, go
Let's have Vacuum rest.
They change the rules, and Matsumoto goes for his first attack
Will they be able to make a miracle happen here!?
Just as expected...
Here we go
Amazing
We need to hurry up, she's already done with her hamburger
I know
Should we eat till we're full?
We just keep rotating
Rotate?
Yeah, otherwise we can't win
Yeah, let's do that
You're not that fucking fast!
He got SO angry at him!
OI
Do you have to get that angry?
Apparently so...
You're lips are fucking shiny too!
It &£(*£(*...
What?
It won't go down...
She's finished the curry!
The curry!
She's basically done
Shit
Yama-chan, swap in
Zaki-san!
Let's just keep rotating
It's hard.
I see...
You're just moving your hands!
Come on...
There's no point in gathering it all to the centre
You got to eat all of that!
Is there a point in doing this?
He's trying to show he's doing something
He's trying to make it look like...
That was delicious
She's already done
3 people's worth of curry: 24 minutes 50 seconds
Gal Sone
Can we not just eat the next dish together?
Didn't the curry disappear like really quickly?!
To counter the super speed Gal Sone ate the curry
Rule change- they can all eat together!
Gaki Team changes the rules and eat the food together!
Gal Sone seems comfortable and starts on the 10 people worth of cake
Gal Sone 5th dish: 10 pieces of cake
Good
You're doing well
Cocorico are doing well
Okay, great.
We're done
4 people's worth of yakisoba: 25 minutes 49 seconds
Gaki Team
Good
Endo, sit and keep eating!
There it is
Go, Endo!
His mask slips...
Come on, cut it up
Cut it up, okay.
Yeah, cut, cut
Gaki Team 3rd Dish: 5 servings of hamburger
Go go.
It's huge!
Cut it so it's easier to eat
This is really big!
Make sure it's easy to eat
Let's go one piece per person
Yeah?
Please?
Gaki Team - Hamburger
Gal Sone - Cake
Still..
That isn't the last dish right?
We've still got curry
Go for that one.
Why is Vacuum-san not eating at all?
Vacuum!
What the hell?
Yama-chan, don't take the small pieces, take one of the huge ones
I've got a small mouth...
I'm eating so much of this...
What the hell...
Let's go
Damn, they're fast
Really?
Half each then
I'm getting really full now...
You finish up
You can do this
Endo, keep going
Me?
Go
We're done
5 servings of hamburger: 27 minutes 30 seconds
Gaki Team
Gaki Team, finally finish their 3rd dish
Here we go
Shozo, go alone for now
Let us rest up for a second.
Gaki Team 4th dish: 3 people's worth of curry
I feel like I'm doing Vacuum's job
No no...
That's true
Come on, man
Come on Endo
He's taken over
Endo-san, you eat a lot, huh?
You know,
I actually did this 8 years ago (Oogui)
Just eat.
Jesus, man, who cares if I just explain it quickly?
Endo-san, come on
30 minutes since the start
Gal Sone's pace hasn't slowed down
Gal Sone's pace still hasn't decreased, and she's eating the cake very quickly
She really does eat a shitload...
Does this woman's stomach not have a limit?
Vacuum, swap in for me.
HELP ME, VACUUM-SAN!
You should still be okay to go
You can just eat this real quick
Yeah
It should all just go in real quickly
You need to show us your worth here
I was so full before...
Like literally
Hey, if you leave that much rice, is the balance going to be okay? (between rice and sauce)
Right?
You do love your rice
Come on
She's really something else though...
I know
It's nice to watch.
Yeah, it really is
That all goes in her...
He stopped again...
Not again...
Vacuum-san stopped again...
Just some random boy now.
Keep going, man
You look like one of theold men outside...
You look like one of the old men outside...
He's completely ignoring the potatoes
What are you planning on doing, leaving all those potatoes to the side?
He threw it to the side...
You're never going to be able to  escape from the reality of potatoes
You're never going to be able to escape from the reality of potatoes
It's bad our pace has gone down now
Who?
You're Vacuum-san!
You're giving the sunglasses?
Vacuum-san!
You don't become Vacuum-san if you wear the sunglasses you know?!
Come on, finish it
He started eating again...
Of course
Of course, this is awful
That whole cake...
Let's go
Hold on?
What?
Next is Okonomiyaki
Just okonomiyaki and gyoza...
Just them
She really eats so much
Yeah
Amazing
This isn't fake like at all as well...
Nope
Amazing
It's delicious
Yeah?
Delicious?
Still at this point?
It's amazing she can still say that
She can still say that...
Gal Sone eats the 10 people's worth of cake with no problem
10 people's worth of cake: 33 minutes 42 seconds
Gal Sone
Meanwhile, Vacuum, who is not responding...
What are you going to do?
Are you serious?
Vacuum-san?
Are you serious right now?
Amazing..
Gal Sone 6th plate: 5 people's worth of okonomiyaki
Oh yeah
She's killing us
Put whatever you want on
Good good
Oh here we go
He's just moving his hands about loads
I know
So true
He's just trying to show he's eating a lot...
He just looks fast...
So many unnecessary movements...
Yeah
That's no good!
Don't muck around!
Don't!
We can't have that!
Yama-chan, you won't hold out like that
You've only had 3 mouthfuls...
I'll eat all the rice
All the rice?
Wow, good stuff
Man, whilst we were talking, she's like nearly halfway through hers...
Damn
Amazing
Right, here we go
Good
Damn, the cake will be tough
I don't like cake...
Good stuff
Finished?
3 people's worth of curry: 36 minutes 43 seconds
Gaki Team
Yamasaki does well and finishes the curry
Gaki Team 5th plate: 10 people's worth of cake
Tanaka loves cake
Oh really?
Yep
You're just moving your hands and not eating that much!
Oh yeah
You're just eating the cream
Come on, eat up
40 minutes from the start
Gaki Team's "altogether" tactic is working and, even though only a bit, the gap is starting to decrease
Cake 1/5
Cake DONE
Curry DONE
Gaki Team
Gal Sone
Gyoza
Hamburger  DONE
Okonomiyaki
Okonomiyaki  3/4
Sushi  DONE
Sushi DONE
Yakisoba DONE
However...
Gal Sone's pace has not dropped, even now
You've only eaten like 2 or 3 pieces at this point...
Inomoto, you go
Inomoto, go
Damn
After that, Yama-chan will go
Inomoto, eat it all
You can do this
You can do it all!
Vacuum-san hasn't said a word in about 20 minutes
Are you okay?
Vacuum-san?
She's only one mouthful away...
Wow!!
Shall we eat altogether?
Yeah, let's
5 people's worth of okonomiyaki: 42 minutes 6 seconds
Gal Sone
Gal Sone, in just over 40 minutes, has eaten 6kg worth of food
Amazing
Yeah
One mouthful is so nice
Gal Sone 7th plate: 7 servings of Gyoza
Gal Sone moves onto her final dish
Jumbo Gyoza!
However, here...  A problem arises.
It's a bit too hot, I can't eat it yet
Right?
It's really hot
They've found her weakness!
A strange weakness is found on the final dish!
This is the final chance for the Gaki Team
Gaki Team's final chance!!
Oi oi!
Hold on...
What's this?
Seriously, what's with him?
Yeah man
After this
Can the Gaki Team produce a miracle?
He was doing some show in the other studio, no?
Whilst Gal Sone is waiting for the Gyoza to cool down
10 people's worth of cake: 44 minutes 49 seconds
Gaki Team
The Gaki Team finish their 5th plate
Damn, this gyoza is amazing
This is amazing, filled right up
Damn
This is amazing
That is tough
This is really amazing
Damn that looks tough
This is amazing
And now, Gal Sone
has started eating the final dish
Gaki Team 6th plate: 5 people's worth of okonomiyaki
Fujiwara reappears for Gaki Team's 6th plate, okonomiyaki.
Go, Vacuum!
Go go!
Vacuum-san?
What the hell are you doing?!
You definitely haven't eaten like 9 bowls worth of food today...
I have...
He's angry again...
Are you angry again?
But you know, I am done now...
Me too
All that's left is if he pushes this button or not
I see
Oh yeah
Either that, or she finishes
Or the white flag
I see
I wonder if she'll finish
BATTLE OVER
GAL SONE WINS!
Wow wow wow wow...
What??
What about our feelings?
Yeah
I don't give a shit about your feelings...
Were you at your limit much earlier on?
I was pretty damn full after the sushi...
After the sushi?!
That's the first one!
The first one?!
Seriously, don't you EVER say you're a vacuum to me again
Yeah man!
Give us a break!
Quit now on that stupid dream of yours!
It ends here!