Aired last week, Fujiwara's Heipo Baby Raising Lifestyle - 1 night and 2 days
This will become a "sensation"
In order to make it up to Hamada, Fujiwara will take care of a helpless Heipo baby
A harsh purification! He will need to feed him, change his diaper, and more
Well I guess you had no choice Fujiwara
This is shocking
It's a purification after all
Furthermore, when Fujiwara had to take Heipo for a stroll in Ometesando (A "high class" neighbourhood)
Uwahh
No no no no
This is too much!
This is hard isn't it?
They'll think I'm a pervert!
Heipo ignores his baby role and starts talking normally
Can we stop for a second here?
I've had enough!
I need to go to the bathroom, for real
Yes.
I get sick from drinking milk
The fed up Heipo unleashes his anger!
If you could just pee first,
I CAN'T CONTROL IT LIKE THAT!!
I can't do just one thing at a time
Stop taking the piss!
Ahh! It's coming out already
Ahh I can't hold it in!
My stomach hurts~!
So, will Fujiwara be able to make it through this purification?
Typeset by portnoyd
Translation by senor_wristband
It's been 8 hours since the start.
Tired from all his talking, Po-chan falls asleep
Is he really sleeping?
He's snoring for real
Amazing
What a Tokyo-ite
It's just shocking footage after shocking footage
Sleep apnea
That's sleep apnea right?
Makes sense Fujiwara is scared
Yeah I was a bit scared
Po-chan's breathing can't be heard
So scary
He hasn't breathed yet
Yeah he hasn't
Fujiwara films Heipo with the camera
This guy is really something
He's sleeping with glasses and a pacifier
What happened?
Heipo waking up maybe?
His sleep apnea again
He might be having problems
Are his eyes opening?
He's smiling
He's smiling isn't he?
He was smiling
He's smiling
Ehh for that long?
He stopped breathing for 26 seconds
26 seconds seems too long
Too long
Po-chan ...
Sometimes you stop breathing
You stop breathing sometimes
I stopped breathing? For 1 minute?
Well it wasn't 1 minute...
Po-chan starts to ignore the no talking rule
Yeah why is he ignoring the rules?
Yeah, he's been talking normally since they came back
Sleep apnea is ...
He slept again!
No way!
This is too much
This is too much!
Heipo has fallen back asleep.
This guy is actually no good
I hate this guy!
It's been 10 hours since the start.
Fujiwara starts to look tired
However there is no rest. Time for a new activity,
Let's put Po-chan in the bath!
Oh yeah, of course
This is an essential one
Alright Po-chan shall we enter the bath?
In order to wash off today's tiredness, he puts Po-chan in the bath
Po-chan just sit down real quick
This honestly sensational!
Just sit down nice and easy-
I also-
Hot! Wait it's hot!
The water was too hot for baby Heipo
I hate this! I hate this!
What are we gonna do about this!
Wait I can't do this - I'm scared!
This is tiring
I'm gonna slip
I'm scared
Since Po-chan is scared, Fujiwara joins him
He's saying "I'm scared"!
We need to tell him off
Okay okay, it's alright
Po-chan, it's alright it's alright
It's overflowing!
Yeah that would overflow
Since it's just 2 adults after all
Po-chan I'm gonna clean your ears, come here a second
Yeah, he doesn't have any kids
This was my first time
Welll I guess you can learn from this
Alright alright
Are you wearing a ring?
Let's get out
Okay Po-chan sit down sit down OK
Fujiwara gently cleans Po-chan's body
Yeah this part is not good. Wow right?
Alright, this part!
No way
Alright Po-chan
Alright
Alright, alrighty, alright
Fujiwara's never given a bath before
Fujiwara manages to get the bathing done
After this, Fujiwara will get Po-chan's body nice and dry
This guy is actually no good
This is just scary man
What the hell are they doing?
Just stop this already!
What the hell!
You're getting dressed first?
That's not right
I didn't wanna catch a cold
Alright Po-chan
Hmm, Fujiwara seems to be getting good at this
I think so
What are you idiots doing?
Fujiwara's exhausted breathing continues
He's huffing a lot
Are you OK?
I guess you learned what parenting is all about
To keep Po-chan warm, he dresses him and dries his hair with a blowdryer
Hot!
Really Hot!
It's ok.
It's too hot!
Are you warmed up?
Alright turn over, just a bit more
So warm
Let's suck out Po-chan's nose mucus with that nasal aspirator over there
This one sounds really gross
Suck out your nose mucus?
Put the tube inside the baby's nostril, and suck out the mucus with your moth
Eh what is this? Eh suck out with this?
He's never done this before after all
Seriously?
Keep going! It's a purification, so keep going!
This is not good!
This sucks
ohh this sucks!
I can't do this...
Let's use an earpick to clean his ears
I have to pick his ears too?...
Ear pick...
Yeah it's scary kind of
Po-chan
That's not safe
Ow!
Sorry, sorry Po-chan
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Owowowowowow
Look at that face...
Look we got a lot out-
You shouldn't wretch like that
What the hell!
After the break - Heipo's anger is unleashed!
Spare me! I'm not a man in his 20s or 30s!
He's the lowest of the low
It's been 11 hours since the start.
9:30PM
He sure sleeps a lot!
Po-chan falls asleep again
Po-chan farts in his sleep
This guy...
He's the lowest of the low
It's time to go to the bedroom and go to sleep
Let's go to the bedroom
Have a good night.
Yes.
Don't say "yes"!
The horn makes Po-chan panic
I'm lonely...
Lonely?
What emotion?
Time Until Lights Off
Will he be alright? I'm the one who's scared
Waaah!
Aaa Mouuu
Aaa!
Wawawawa!
There were more setups planned for Po-chan, but they were put on pause because of an incident
What am I supposed to do, there's not enough room
Can't sleep Po-chan?
You were screaming
In order to fix the problem, Po-chan is moved to the living room for now
He's just walking now
Can I start talking already?
I'm tired!
He's decided that's spot is where he belongs
More complaining I guess.
Yeah, he returned to the same spot
I think we're almost done though
Give me a break!
That's cause you're in your 20s-30s. A young man has more stamina!
Po-chan snaps at Fujiwara
I'm sorry but,
I'm sorry you had to put up with that
How does this end? That's what I don't know
Just endlessley stumbling
This is not going on until the morning. What should we do?
No idea what to do!
Po-chan complains in order to be heard by the staff
My head is spinning right now
I said my head is spinning and still the staff won't help me
Yes
They just say "do it do it" I'm sick of it
I absolutely don't trust staff like that
He's really mad
I wonder when Gaki No Tsukai became like this
Now he's got a claim against the show
This is nonsense
In order to relieve Fujiwara from this responsibility, a young director enters the room and conveys Director Komurasaki's instructions
Enough alright
I'm so damn tired
He's the focus of this,
I'm not really that relevant
This is the first time I think, like seriously I'm going faint
I'm not like a young man
I need breaks sometimes
We really are almost done, I'm sorry, almost finished
I said I don't wanna do this anymore
The young director leaves to consult with Komurasaki
He just told you it's the end
This guy can't move?
3 Minutes Go By
What the hell is this?
It's time for the unsatisfied Heipo to resume filming
So just enter the bedroom for now,
We just need you to scream once after the power cut. After that we'll be done.
Just don't lie to me anymore
Seriously!
Ok thanks.
You've pushed me this far even though I'm so tired
I'm worried there's still more left
What the hell is this
He's bringing up a lot of stuff
What does he even mean
Good work today
I'm so tired
Should we go to sleep again? It's almost over
With the incident resolved, Heipo is brought into the bedroom again
When we return, Heipo flips out!!
Should we go to sleep again? It's almost over
With the incident resolved, Heipo is brought into the bedroom again
Ow Ow Ow
It hurts?
Po-chan I'm leaving the light on
I wonder what hurt
Well I guess a lot happened
He has a bad shoulder right?
Heipo's "50 year old shoulder" hurts
50 year old shoulder?
Time to Prank
AHHHHHHHHHHHH!
AHHHHHHH!!
Heipo overreacts in order to finish early
Time to Prank.
Heipo is quite scared.
AHH!
Alright I get it! I knew you were lying!
Listen!
No!
Please!
I'm actually done!
The Complex (2013)
Heipo panics to open the door
STOP MESSING AROUND
I said please didn't I?!
Komu! (Director)
I don't want to be friends with you anymore!
This is gonna raise my blood pressure isn't it?
Please spare me
We're done aren't we!
Amazing ...
Please
This has been a long one hasn't it?
Good, it's good that it's too long
Please...
It's funnier if it's too long
Who is it? Ah I head something
Time until smoke comes out
Enough of this stuff, it's not my batsu game!
AHHHH!
What?! What?! What is this?!
You're going overboard
Just end this, please just-
That's gotta be enough
I hurt my shoulder
Everything about this old man is hilarious
Why did you lock it?!
Fujiwara?
That's it
Yes, rest please
That was too much, I said-
He's going back to that spot?
It's not funny, please
Just wrap up filming, that was a lot just now
That just now,
Just spare me, that's it!
I can't do this anymore
Yes?
You're just a liar! You said that wasn't a setup!
I don't know if it'll make it on air, but that shit is [!@$!@$]
Do you agree?
I've got "50 year old shoulder"
It just snapped and fixed itself, just now
What the hell is wrong with this guy!
With that, Fujiwara's baby raising day was over
It's not Fujiwara, but Heipo that pisses me off
What's with that guy
He turns into Takeda Tetsuya sometimes
"I don't wanna be friends with you!"
It's like that one line of his.
What's with that?
We've still got that individual left, lets bring him in
Come in!
Sekai no Heipo (The Global Heipo)
What'd you think of the video?
What'd you think?
It was supposed to be Fujiwara-kun's batsu game right?
Why did I have to be subjected to this?
I do think that is a bit unfortunate,
But, I guess, it's cause it's funny, isn't it?
Every single thing was hilarious
You came up with some great quotes too
All: Yes.
You did
I hated it,
Ghosts have been working on Gaki for 25 years right?
Ghosts!
I don't understand. Ghosts have been working for 25 years?
I want to stop the Ghosts!
I think we better stop then
No more ghosts.
It was hilarious, really
Oh, yes ... Ah ... oh yes.
What happened?
Sorry I sort of peed just now
Heipo continues his explanation
You peed now? You peed just now?
Just a little bit
I was a bit nervous
You were nervous? But normally you can't pee when you're nervous, you've got it backwards