Hello everybody
Matsumoto-san, why are we here today?
Well, we visited Murakami Joji's home last time   -Yes
And that episode received many bad reviews
Don't do it again then
However, doing it again disregard of bad reviews, is the style of this show
Today, we invited someone that we thought it's impossible for him to accept the offer
Maybe he wants to advertise his drama, I think?
So that's why he accepted, or else it would be impossible
But then we thought, having big guests
is not the style of this show too, so...
Today's guest will be Jimmy Onishi instead
That dude is always available!!
Not always though, it can't be always
So it's the same as last time, right?   -Yes
The Gaki members prepared many items in the home to be visited
The guests need to introduce the items as if they own that item
We'll see how he reacts to the items that we've prepared
And of course, he has no idea what's inside
So it will be improvised
Which heavily depends on your sense of humor
So let's start the home visit   -Let's go
Subbed by Appieopie, more episodes at
www.laughseejapan.com/user/18797
There he is
Wearing clothes that are far from colorful
That's too monotone
Good morning   -Good morning
Your home is so big   -Looks really good
Well...actually...someone gave it to me
Gave it to you?
Is it possible to give out homes?
Umm...from my uncle
So big
You gained weight, huh?!
Max 20 kg
You look so big   -Yeah, he looks fat
He definitely gained a lot of weight
You look completely black now, everything
His skin is so dry too
And your face is so dirty too, dude!!
You're so loud
Ma..ma..ma...
This kind of face should never appear on tv!!
It's because of wearing masks   -His skin looks so dry
-Oh, because we're always wearing masks
-But still, his skin looks too dry
Look, the house name plate says Onishi
Yeah, that's his real name
Gimmick (1)
Graffiti on house name plate
He stinks
Retarded
This dude is so stupid (ww)
You boring piece of shit! Move away!!
But something else is written on it
Yeah, they always play pranks on me
You're not angry about this?
Well, even if I erase it, they'll just write it again
It goes on forever, so just leave it like that
-Can we enter your home now?   -Yeah sure, welcome to my home
First time ever
There's even a little garden here   -Incredible
Your dog is not here?
Oh...my dog is...umm...
Gimmick (2)
Empty dog house
My dog is at the pet shop now
How come?
Well, guests are coming today, and it's inappropriate if the mic pick up it's voice
What breed is your dog?
Well...the breed is...umm...pit bull   -Pit bull?
It looks like this...   -Oh, really?
It looks more like a frog though
I see, so it's called a pit bull
Is it a large dog?
Well, probably medium sized dog
Can we go inside now?
Yeah sure, let's go inside
I really want to meet pit bull   -Yeah, exactly
Wow, it can even open on this side?   -This is amazing
Excuse me   -Welcome to my home
Wow, these shoes are neatly arranged...huh?
What's written on it?
It says "right" and "left"
Gimmick (3)
Shoes with "left" and "right written on it
Well, right, left, right, left, right, left
It's kind of like one, two, one, two
Eh? What do you mean?
Because I want to wear those shoes properly
Or else, it's gonna be embarrassing, right?
So I have to wear it properly
-Or else, it looks awkward if I wear it like this, right?
-Oh, so wearing the shoes on the wrong feet
Or maybe wearing right shoes on both legs, or the other way round
So these things happen if you don't label it clearly?
Sometimes, I trip on my own feet
And I wonder why these things happen
Then I found out I confused left and right
So these things really happen...
So you won't get it wrong if you label it?
Yeah, I can walk steadily now
What happened?   -What are you laughing at?
It's all Hamada-kun's fault   -Huh?
What the heck are you talking about?
He's breathing heavily   -What are you talking about?
He's breathing so heavily   -It's all Hamada-kun's fault
Anyway, so you won't get it wrong anymore with these labels
This is something unique about Jimmy-chan
Wait a moment, this is unacceptable!
Come on, Jimmy-chan
Gimmick (4)
Pushpins on Hamada's face
This is completely unacceptable
Why are there pushpins on my face?
-Because that's the only place to put those pushpins
-No way, dude, that's not true
There's pushpins at the four corners already
Why did you do this?
Because I can't help but to laugh whenever I see Hamada-kun's face
What are you talking about?
He's pissing me out   -Because...
Because only Hamada is wearing the Kappa wig
I'm so sorry for doing this   -It's okay
-He's probably bearing a grudge though
-Yeah, there's many other solutions
Anyway, please show us around your home
Excuse me   -Which room is this?
This is the kitchen   -Kitchen?
There's a home altar   -Yes
You're very devout   -Yes
*Manma-chan is the mascot in Sanma's show
Gimmick (5)
A home altar with Manma-chan
But why did you put Manma-chan there?
The Amaterasu-Mikonokami   -Mikonokami?
*Should be Amaterasu Omikami, the god of the Sun, however Jimmy said Amaterasu Mikonokami instead, which means the god of the son
Mikonokami?   -Yes, the Amaterasu-Mikonokami...
It's the sa...sa...sacred tree
*Sacred tree (Goshin-boku) and body of governing god (Goshin-tai) have similar pronunciations
-A Tree? That's not a tree!
-Do you mean the body of governing god?
I'm asking you, why did you put the Manma doll over there?
Well...umm...
Either way, it's definitely not a sacred tree
But why?   -Why did you put Manma-chan there?
Because I like Manma-chan so much
As a God
You like it as a God?
Amaterasu?   -Amaterasu-Mikonokami...
-And worshiping it as a sacred tree?
-Yes, as a sacred tree
I told you it's not a tree
What about the poster behind Yama-chan?
Gimmick (6)
Poster of Hayami Yu
Oh, she's my favorite girl, Hayami Yu
We saw the same thing in Jouji-san home   -Yeah
Not the same poster though. Are you two of the same generation?
Yes, we are   -You still like her now?
Yes, she's still my favourite girl
I've entered the entertainment industry, just to become Hayami Yu's disciple
You want to become her disciple?
She's younger than you though
Yes, I want to become Hayami Yu's disciple, that's why I've entered the entertainment industry
No way, dude, I said you're older than her
You want become her disciple?
Yes, when I first saw her singing "kore janai" during high school
I've decided to become this girl's disciple
Why would you want to become her disciple?
I understand that you want to get closer with her, but...
You want to become her disciple?
Hey, what's this?
Gimmick (7)
A whole lot of fireworks
Eh? That's so scary
This is for...you know...
Yakitori (grilled chicken skewers)
Thread the chicken onto skewers, and eat it like this
So it's a skewer?   -Yes, skewer
No way, those are fireworks, right?
Jimmy-san, those are fireworks
Umm...well...these are actually fireworks
Umm...
But the fireworks are facing this way, how come?
Yeah, it's facing the house on the other side
This is because...sometimes...intruder enters from here
No way, the fireworks are definitely aiming at the house over there
Well...actually...whenever I beat the futon, they're always complaining
So there's a neighborhood dispute
But he's being mean too
This is inappropriate too
Well, these things just happen
What's this? Look at this, Matsumoto-san
What the heck is this?
Sake?   -But the thing inside, it has to be bra
Gimmick (8)
Bra soaked in sake
Well...bra...
You're soaking bra in Sake?
Well...yeah...I'm soaking girl's bra in Sake
Why?   -That's ridiculous
Why are you soaking it?
Well...umm...
The smelly fluid of girls   -Fluid?
Body odor
Of girls?
What are you soaking it in though?
It's Umeshu (Sake with plums)
Umeshu?   -I see
It tastes really good
Eh? You drink it?
Of course I drink it
It's delicious
So it's a Bra-Sake
Yes, Bra-Sake, with the good smell of girls
Who's bra is it for the one at the rightmost side?
Yeah, who's bra is it? Do you remember?
This is Saeko-chan
Who's that?
We did...a play
An underwear play, and she gave me her bra
You got her bra during the play?
She bit the shoulder strap like this
Bit it?
Bit the shoulder strap?
Yes, she bit the should strap and dragged it like this
Oh, I see, so that's the play   -Yes
What about this one?
This is Hurukawa Ruri-san
And what about this one?
This one is Hujimoto Rumi-chan
Eh...this is Shizuka-chan
You omitted her last name*
*Matsumoto mentioned last name (Ue) and Jimmy made up the name Ue-kawa
Uekawa Hujika-chan
You're just inspired by my "Ue"
Then what about the last one?
It's a black one
Umm...Meisa-chan
*Black is pronounced as Kuro, so Jimmy just think of Kuro-ki Meisa, a famous actress
You're definitely just inspired by "black"
Okay, I see
Let's take a look at other places   -Yes, sure
The bathroom
Huh?
Can this be aired?
Gimmick (9)
Konjacs with a hole in the middle
Look at this   -What have you been doing?
There's a hole in the middle of the konjac
You're still doing this in this age?
Yeah, sometimes...3 times per week
That's unbelievable   -3 times per week
If you don't use it frequently, you'll lose your sexiness
Is it relevant to sexiness?   -Absolutely
Tanaka, look at those things on the floor
Wait a second...this is...eh?
This is for that, right?   -Yes
Gimmick (10)
A whole lot of paper underwear
You wear it when you get a massage, right?   -Yes
There's so many of them
For example, when you go on a date with a girl
I'll wear this and show it to the girl
What are you talking about?   -I have no idea
Show it to girls? What do you mean?
Well, this is my tactic to approach a girl
You're using this tactic to approach girls?   -Yes
Why are you storing so many of them at your home though?
Because I sometimes ask them to come over to my place
Oh, to your home?   -Yes
So you're using it at home too
What about inside the shower room, Tanaka?
Huh? What's going on here?
Someone is sitting inside
Gimmick (10)
The body scrub aunties
The body scrub auntie...
Yeah, she's always here to give me a body scrub
She's always here?
The body scrub auntie is always stationed here?
Yes, always stationed here...
Therefore my back has almost been destroyed
-That's going too far   -Let her go!!
So you're wearing this underwear when she scrubs your back?   -Yes, exactly
Of course, that's my tactic to approach the auntie
Okay, I see
You're trying to approach the auntie with these tactics at home?
Yes, only approach, it's not allowed to touch her
You're not allowed to touch someone who is always stationed here?
No way, this is my rules, my system
That kind of behavior is intolerable
What about here?
Oh, it's the toilet
Yama-chan   -Yes
There's so many difficult idioms   -Yeah
Gimmick (11)
Posters with idioms
What are these for?
These are, well, Classical Chinese
Classical Chinese?
How do you read this?
*The correct pronunciation is "Gaden Insui", but Jimmy pronounced it as "Hikita Tenko", who is a famous is a Japanese pop singer turned magician
This is "Hikita Tenko"
You're living here alone, right?   -Yes
*Sound Princess (Otohime) emits the noise of a flushing toilet to spare a woman's blushes
Why would you need to use the Sound Princess?
Gimmick (12)
Toilet with Sound Princess
*The Sound Princess is playing Bonch Osamu's gag, who is Jimmy's master
You're using your master's gag to mask the noise of your poop?
I've been listening to his gags for 30 years
So my poop won't come out smoothly without listening to this
I'll end up having constipation
Can we enter this room?   -Yes, sure
This is just...
What the heck is going on?
Everybody, come in   -Okay
There's so many guitars   -Yeah
Why do you have so many guitars?
Gimmick (12)
A whole lot of guitars
Well...umm...
I was actually a folk "songer" before...
You mean a folk singer?
Yes, I mean folk singer
He said folk "songer"
-You know how to play guitar?   -You were a singer before?
Yes, I can   -We wanna hear you play guitar
Please play the guitar for us
This is the one that I used during middle school
Your tiptoe went stiff   -You're gonna sprain your leg
Sing "Yesterday" for us   -Good choice
Nice, very nice
Fireworks?
Oh my city?
Oh yesterday
Oh my city...
Nice, very nice voice
That was superb
You can even join the "Singing gag contest"
With oh my city, yesterday?
Look at this, Hamada-san
That's the Demae-can uniform
*Demae-can is a home delivery service, endorsed by Hamada
Yes, this is from Demae-can
You work part-time at Demae-can?
"Yes, I do! Yes, I do!"
*"Yes, I do! Yes, I do!" is a one of Jimmy's most famous gags
No, that's not what I'm asking for
"Yes, I do! Yes, I do!"
I told you we don't need this
Are you working part-time at Demae-can?
"Yes, I do! Yes, I do!"
Are you trying to redeem something?
Because you can see how this is going to end
So you're making a full effort to redeem
I can even feel your anxiety
So you're working part time while being a comedian?
"Yes, I do! Yes, I do!"
Can this be aired? This needs to be censored...
What is this for?
"Poop is the absolute truth" (words on the hanging scroll)
Whenever I brew tea
I'll sit formally (Seiza) in front of this
And read this phrase out loud
What does it mean? Is there any special meaning to it?
I'm learning how to brew tea now
You're learning tea ceremony?   -Yes
Why didn't you reply "Yes, I do! Yes, I do!", dude
He didn't think of it
Get your act together!
Please explain this to us
Is that Jimmy-san's poop?
I usually harvest it when I need it
Harvest it?
Is that how you use the word "harvest"?
So you're harvesting the freshest one everyday?
Okay, I see
The freshest one   -Steaming hot
That's quite disgusting though   -Sure it is
This is the living room, it's always nice to relax here
Good to have a room like this   -You're right
You like Leah Dizon so much
Yinling of Joytoy as well
Yinling...Leah Dizon compilation
You made a compilation?
It says edited on it
Yeah, cut out the best part of the videos
What made you like Leoh Dizon so much?
Because Leah Dizon solves many riddles
Solve riddles? What do you mean?
She was actually a lawyer before
However...
He don't know her
Why are you shivering all of a sudden?
-He's shivering all of a sudden
-Did you collect these, Jimmy-san?
Please tell us the story behind it
She lost her lawyer license one day
What happened next?
Thinking "where is it?" and finding her license, that's what the story is all about
Eh? You must be kidding me? What the heck is this story?
Leah Dizon
Where is my lawyer license...and keeps finding it...
-That's so lame
-So she's finding her license from start to finish
How many episodes are there?   -10 episodes
That's quite a lot   -What happened in the end?
Of course she found her license in the end
What a lame drama   -No way, not lame at all
She spent 10 hours to find her license?
That's all she did in the drama?   -Yes
This sounds interesting in another way
You like Kyojin no Hoshi, huh?
It's a baseball manga, and you play baseball, right?
Yeah, of course   -This is the memory of our generation
But it's all chapter one...
It's all chapter one   -Yes, only chapter one
If you don't read chapter one, how can you read chapter two?
You definitely read it already!!
Just go for chapter 2!
He's starting to scratch his head
You haven't read chapter 2 yet?
I finished all of the chapter ones
And I then read chapter one again
You're reading it many times?   -Yes, many times
Is this chapter one different from this chapter one?
Exactly the same
I bet they are   -Sure it is
I just read it again and again
You really like it, huh?
The calendar...November...
23rd is circled and "Definitely!" is written below it
What does it mean?
These are the days that I'm not allowed to move
Not allowed to move?
So you can't move on the 13rd and 30th?
Definitely can't, or else I'll have an accident
Who told you about this?
It's a book called Des...Destini-ni
Destini-ni?
Not Destiny, but Destini-ni?
Yes, a book called Destini-ni
I read it and made these notes
What about on 23rd?
It means I definitely can't go out
No, no way   -It's circled, so it should be fine, right?
You can't move if the day is crossed out
What about the days being circled?
Well, for 23th, I shall make a big leap forward
Leap?   -What the heck is going on?
Destini-ni told you to "make a big leap forward"?
It's difficult to make a big leap though
Thanks for coming today   -Thanks for having us
Let's leave from here
Thank you very much   -You're welcome
Please come again
Huh? Which way did we come in?
That way
Huh?
That way, no, no, it's that way
Jimmy-san...
What the heck is this, Jimmy-san?
1000 penis per day?
You're working out?
At home?   -Yes
What is this machine for?
You're aiming so high   -Yeah
1000 times per day?   -Yes, 1000 times, everyday
Why though?
To build up my muscles
1000 times per day...
Elbows on the floor...yes, just like that
With your elbows on the floor...
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch...
My balls hurt, my balls hurt....
The tip is...the tip is...
I won't be able to use it anymore today...
Let's go   -Thank you very much
Goodbye, thank you very much
It's enough, right? It's enough
It actually doesn't hurt right?   -It does
Because I'm wearing jeans...
Oh, not jeans...