[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
The First Gaki No Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
The First Gaki No Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
Oh, he's so quiet today.
The First Gaki No Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
What's with him? His voice is so quiet today.
The First Gaki No Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
Kumazawa Edition!
You were so quiet!
I could only hear the part about 'strolling'.
I couldn't hear anything else.
I can't yell at a place like this.
So, where are we? What park is this?
It's Kumazawa Park!
Ah, right...
Matsumoto look.
Daikanyama, Nakameguro, Jiyugaoka, Sangenjaya, and this is our fifth time.
Ah, right...
Matsumoto look.
Daikanyama, Nakameguro, Jiyugaoka, Sangenjaya, and this is our fifth time.
-Yes!
-Our fifth time!
This program was filmed at Sangenjaya last time.
They had had many tip offs so the guys thought it would be very easy...
But the search proved harder than expected.
However, 1 hour 52 minutes after the start...
They finally found Kato from Zabungle returning from a grocery run!
They immediately barged in at his home!
And now, the guys have arrived at Setagaya Ward's Komazawa district!
With places such as the Komazawa University and the Komazawa Olympic Park,
this commuter town is full of greenery and is extremely popular with the celebrities.
They have received plenty of tip offs this time too, and they cannot go home until they run into a celebrity.
The hellish challenge starts now!
This one's gonna be a tough one, I think...
-You're totally right.
-It's gonna be hard...
We're not in the city center, you know?
Right.
It's just a residential area.
We're not in the city center, you know?
I have to say this, but Endo is running a fever again...
He's got a weak body!
I'm so sorry.
It happens pretty often, doesn't it?
But I must say, I haven't gotten a fever since Takeshi Endo's Extreme Challenge.
For real.
Well, you did have to go down those water slides over and over again.
And you were in tighty-whities.
It's been 4 years!
Well, you did have to go down those water slides over and over again.
And you were in tighty-whities.
4 years since then.
I can't believe you had a cold and you still did that!
It's gonna be a long one today.
We have to try really hard today!
So, do any of you know the area?
No, not at all.
This area is mostly filled with homes.
Well, yeah...
But I do hear some rumors of famous people running in this area.
Oh, right, right.
Arthur Kuroda must be running around here somewhere.
That would be awesome!
Meeting Arthur Kuroda would be perfect.
It would be awesome!
It would be perfect.
Yes, perfect.
We have to find Arthur Kuroda.
Perfect?
Let's stroll around until we find a celebrity!
Komazawa Edition!
These are the rules:
The shoot won't end until we meet a celebrity.
However, all members must know the celebrity's name.
And naturally, we also need filming consent from their respective agencies.
Now, will the guys find any celebrities in Komazawa?!
Ah!
Eh?
Doesn't she look like someone?
It's Sachiyo Nomura!
Sachiyo Nomura?
It's Sacchi!
Her home is not that far away from here.
It's definitely not her.
Yeah.
She would even give us a glance.
That's amazing.
Alright, let's get going!
Let's go!
Let's walk to the center of the park.
To the center?
We have to check out all the walkers.
It's time for a little stroll.
-Endo!
-Yes?
-Ah, should I put it on?
-Oh, a mask.
I should.
But there's not a lot of pollen around.
It's not for that, it's for your fever!
We don't want your bugs!
Endo has a weak body...
And Hamada is no good either. He gets sick all the time.
This guy is also out.
You think so?
I'm actually pretty resilient.
Right, surprisingly so.
Tanaka and I are pretty resilient.
I almost never get sick, do I?
But what about the other day..?
I get sick, but I always hide it!!
-He's shouting again...
-Even I can't be healthy all the time!!
Too loud...
You're too loud, we don't know what you're saying.
But you've already skipped one episode of this series!
That's right.
It's true!
It's only natural!!
The guys have decided to explore Komazawa Park first.
Why are we taking a stroll inside the park?
Well, we wanted to see if anyone famous was taking a stroll or on a run.
Personally, I think it would have been better if we went straight to the shops...
Actually I might be better if we went that way.
That way?
I mean, it doesn't really matter which way.
There's no right answer here.
Right...
Guided by the crew, the guys head towards the racetrack within the park.
We can't be going this way.
We can't go this way, for real!
Then, the guys spot a bunch of students after their training session.
Nothing good ever comes out of Komu's mouth.
You can do it!
Komurasaki...
We'll be at Komazawa street if we head down this street.
Komazawa street?
This is where you get mobbed and thrown into the air.
No way...
There's no way.
But you know, I have been thrown into the air way back then.
That's scary!
I was at a Karaoke place, so I went to the bathroom and ran into some students in the hallway.
And they just lifted me up, in the middle of the hall.
That's the worst.
Yeah, but all I could do was laugh.
You can't do anything, right?
Have you guys seen any celebs around?
Someone running around? No?
I guess it's useless to ask as a celebrity myself.
They're high school students.
I bet these guys must have the hardest morning wood.
Hard?
You think so?
These guys are rock hard every morning.
Do you get morning wood?
Don't actually ask them!!
They're shy.
-They're still teenagers!
-What the hell are you asking?!
That boy's ears turned beet red.
They were super red.
Why would you ever ask something like that?
For real...
Whoa this park is huge.
Oh, a Chow Chow!
It's a Chow Chow!
They get along so well.
Have you seen any famous people on your walk today?
Are you guys looking for celebrities?
Unfortunately not today.
-By the way, who have you seen around here?
-Yes, in the past.
We always see the Eita and his wife.
(Eita Nagayama & Kaela Kimura)
Eita and his wife?
Kaela?
Yes, yes, yes.
-Right...
-They are always with their children.
I've also seen Shinji Yamashita walking around.
-That's great!
-Meeting Shinji Yamashita would be amazing!
I've also seen Shinji Yamashita walking around.
-That's great!
-Meeting Shinji Yamashita would be amazing!
He would be perfect!
-That's great!
-Meeting Shinji Yamashita would be amazing!
He would be perfect!
-Thank you!
Thanks!
Shinji Yamashita, huh?
Shinji Yamashita would be perfect.
He's just the right fit for us.
It's only been 20 minutes since the start of the challenge.
The guys are heading towards the big stairs leading up to Komazawa Park.
There's nothing around here.
Geez!
There's really no one around.
We're getting farther and farther away from the station so there's less and less people.
Right, they just scatter.
I see...
These are the big stairs, right?
Yes, this is the spot.
We're here.
But what now?
I don't think we'll find anything here.
There's no one around!
This is bad.
This is really bad.
That girl looks like she could be a celebrity.
We have to keep a good eye out.
Isn't she an actress?
That must be a script in her bag.
The script for episode 4 or something must be in there.
Episode 4?
-That's a late appearance if you ask me.
-Well, she gets introduced in episode 4.
No, no...
But episode 4 is still a bit too late.
You're right.
Is she gonna be alright?
Will she make the cut?
At this point, the guys give up on the search at the empty park and head towards Komazawa Street.
Once we leave the park, there's nothing around.
This side is also full of apartments.
No one's walking around here.
You're right.
I have a feeling we won't find anything.
Let's cross this street and go to that Ramen Shop and the Lawson.
(Lawson is one of the big convenience store chains)
Let's visit some of those stores.
Let's cross this street and go to that Ramen Shop and the Lawson.
(Lawson is one of the big convenience store chains)
Let's visit some of those stores.
Let's look into all 3 of those stores.
The guys cross Komazawa Street to peek into the stores.
Go and have a look.
Oh, Endo you go look over there!
Go ahead.
Following Hamada's orders Endo and Tanaka search for celebrities inside the restaurants.
Oh, that's nice.
It was pretty empty.
This place has a line.
Let's have a look at Jojoen.
(High-end Japanese-style BBQ restaurant)
But there is not a trace of celebrity anywhere.
They've just opened, so there were no customers inside.
But they told me they get about 3 groups of celebrities a week.
That's a lot.
-They go into the private rooms, right?
-Yeah, that's why.
Who the hell suggested we come here?
Who was it?
I'll ride him like a pig and beat the crap out of him.
-Who was it?
-Really, who was it?
There's nobody around.
-Who was it?
-Really, who was it?
There's nobody around.
Who's idea was it?
I really want to know who it was.
For real, who suggested we come here?
It wasn't a single person, we all decided as a group.
The guys wander around Komazawa with no clear location in mind.
-There's another BBQ place here.
These guys must be Jojoen's competitors.
But this place is much more reasonable.
-Oh, really?
-Yes.
But this place is much more reasonable.
-Oh, really?
-Yes.
-It's a different concept.
-Right.
Whoa, that's amazing.
-You're right, it's so cheap.
-Yeah, look.
They even have half off for elementary school students.
-You're right, it's so cheap.
-Yeah, look.
They even have half off for elementary school students.
Whoa, it's free for old people too.
So, you guys can't afford Jojoen?
It's a bit too expensive?
Is that so? This one's better?
-Are you guys in high school?
-Is it all-you-can-eat?
-Oh, I see...
-It's an all-you-can-eat!
'The kings of BBQ'.
Whoa, amazing.
I bet those kids would be so happy if Hamada treated them to some Jojoen.
Of course they would.
Go ahead.
Tons of good rumors would start spreading about you.
You're the one that approached them!
You're the one that went: "Let's go".
You should have said something like: "Instead of waiting in line, I'll treat you to some Jojoen."
But saying something like that is pretty hard.
I mean, yeah.
Then why didn't you say it then?
You had the perfect opportunity right there.
Right?
I mean, I have no personal attachment to those guys.
And there he goes.
He said it.
At that moment, Hosei spots something!
There's a masked girl running towards us.
That could be it.
We won't let you run away.
This time we won't let you run away.
A girl hiding her face with a mask has appeared!
Hello.
Have they finally found their celebrity?
You're a celebrity, are you not?
There's a masked girl running towards us.
We won't let you run away.
This time we won't let you run away.
We won't let you get away.
She looked a bit suspicious.
Hello.
Excuse me, you're a celebrity...
You're a celebrity, right?
You're not?
You're not a celebrity?
I just don't want to get sunburn, that's why I'm wearing a mask.
-Oh, she doesn't want to get sunburned.
-I see.
-Sorry to bother you.
-Sorry about that.
What'd she say?
She's wearing a mask because she doesn't want to get sunburnt.
I thought we'd definitely found someone.
-Right?
She had the right vibe.
Are you a celebrity?
No?
Tanaka, you're embarrassing us.
It's already been 45 minutes and there is no trace of a celebrity around.
Our path has been cut.
Which way should we go?
What are we gonna do?
Let's go that way then.
Sure.
Ehm... Can we go to where people are?
I don't think we should listen to anything Komu has to say.
It's all his fault.
The guys stave off the main street and walk down an empty street towards Komazawa Park.
What time do celebrities go to dinner?
I'd guess around 7.
7?
Yeah.
That's the same as a normal family!
At 7?
Most people have dinner at 7.
Where are we?
-It'll be even earlier if they have kids.
-You're right.
That person's a genius!
This is amazing.
That's really good parking.
Eh? How in the world did they fit that in?
I'm always amazed by people like this.
That's amazing.
but I don't think they've moved it in a while.
This must always be parked here.
Whoa! But look at it! It's crazy!
This one's a tough one.
I really wanna know how they did it.
Looks so hard.
Do they go back and forth?
That's crazy.
It's really amazing.
It's 5 o'clock.
Now?
Yes.
Just now.
Once again, the guys head to Komazawa Street.
There's no one around!
Look, we might find someone at that dog boutique.
Yukina could be there.
(Yukina Fujimoto, Fujimoto Toshifumi's ex-wife)
It looks like a place a celebrity would visit.
I've got a strong feeling.
-Do you have a feeling?
-Yeah.
I've got a strong feeling.
-Do you have a feeling?
-Yeah.
Really?
-Do you have a feeling?
-Yeah.
-Alright, Yama go and have a look.
-Sure.
Chasing a hunch, Hosei enters the dog boutique.
Will there be a celebrity waiting for them?
I think the time frame was not right.
I think they usually come out a bit later.
But it's already 5 o'clock.
Maybe that's just Komazawa.
What do you think?
I just wonder who would pick a place like this.
Really?
I don't know if celebrities actually hand around here.
Hosei comes back after finishing up his search.
No?
No.
There was no one inside.
And they even told me that they've never had a famous customer.
Did they ask, "What is a celebrity?".
They don't go there.
And the dogs were barking at me.
Endo, I think you get sick more because you're always naked.
That's why.
Eh?!
This is it.
-W-Where?
-Alright, let's record it.
-This is it.
-Let's get some evidence.
He tripped on this.
It's about a 4 cm high step.
-What time is it?
-It's 15:05.
It's about a 4 cm high step.
-What time is it?
-It's 15:05.
15:05!
-Understood.
-Alright, the incident happened at 15:05.
And he even tried to play it off.
He tried to act like it never happened.
That's the lamest part.
He tried to play it cool, and I think that's super lame.
I mean, it happens to everyone.
-Right.
-It does, it does.
"Ah!" or something like that.
Or, "Uh... I almost tripped".
But he went like this.
With his poker face.
That's lame.
We have to record this time for posterity!
Not the time he tripped!
But the time he tried to play it cool.
It happened at 17:05.
What?
At 17:05.
17:05!
He tried to play it cool!
You can apparently come here with your dog.
This looks great.
Let's have some tea here.
I didn't get enough rest before coming here.
Really?
Let's see...
We've only been going for an hour though...
Hamada is also tripping over some 4 cm tall steps.
Let's take a break.
Let's go in.
The boys head into the cafe to have a small break and plan their next steps.
But we have to keep a lookout.
Excuse us!
Let's go into surveillance mode.
It would be great if we found a comedian.
Yeah, a comedian would be great.
-Right.
-That would be the easiest.
Right, right.
But there's nobody around.
I'll go take a pee!
What the heck?
It's just as we predicted, isn't it?
Yeah.
It's empty.
Right.
-Who suggested we come here?
-I'm super curious too.
Right.
-Who suggested we come here?
-I'm super curious too.
Wasn't it Matsumoto?
Once again, the guys have started to search for the one who chose Kumazawa as today's location.
We all decided.
So?
I was just asking.
There's a theory that says fancy cafes often don't have washlets on the toilets.
(On Wednesday's Downtown they test trivial theories)
Oh...
I see...
We were talking about Komazawa being a bit empty...
And wondering who came up with the idea to come here.
Yama was also talking about it.
So, who had the idea?
Wasn't it you?
Hold on!
It was that old man right there, wasn't it?
H-H-Hold on.
I have never suggested a location in all my time at Gaki No Tsukai.
Stop lying!
That's such a big lie!
Stop lying already.
I would never suggest anything like this.
Stop lying!
I mean, it happens...
Even a rookie would know this stuff.
Everyone knows you're the one making the decisions.
No, no, hold on.
I really... Ehm...
Alright, should I be honest?
We had some work at Shimokitazawa, right?
Right, right.
We went to Shimokitazawa to film Downtown.
So going to a completely new place in such a short time would have been weird.
I mean, I get that...
Right?
That's why we did the other show first.
And we can't just go home from there, right?
So we finished the show there.
And we couldn't just keep filming at Shimokitazawa for day on end.
So they asked us to suggest another place, and this location came up.
I see...
And we couldn't just keep filming at Shimokitazawa for day on end.
So they asked us to suggest another place, and this location came up.
I see...
Right?
But why here?
And you know, I'm always suggesting Ikebukuro.
Yeah, you did suggest going to Ikebukuro.
Ikeburuo would have been so nice.
But whenever I suggest Ikebukuro, the staff all go like this...
All these guys...
They make that face like, "This guy’s saying some crazy stuff again"...
As if they were dealing with a bomb or something...
Just like that.
A bomb?
Like they don't want to work with Yoshimoto again...
That far?
That's the vibe I get.
I mean, Ikebukuro does sound kind of bothersome.
You're right.
I mean, but this is bad.
Do you get a lot of famous customers?
A lot, actually.
A lot?
Yes, plenty.
We get about 1 famous person a day.
1 a day?!
Are you in the industry?
No, I'm just an employee here.
An employee?
You look like Keiko Fuji.
(Junko Utada (stage name Keiko Fuji) was a Japanese enka singer and actress.)
I don't know her.
She was super famous back then.
She doesn't know Keiko Fuji...
She was Hikaru Utada's mom.
Right, right, you look like Keiko Fuji at her debut.
Are we still looking?
We can't really stay here?
Right, we have to get moving!
Nothing will come out of sitting here!
Let's just go back to the main street.
Right, let's go.
Alright.
The sun has set and the boys resume their search in the darkness of the Komazawa town.
I can't see people's faces!
It's so dark!
Maybe we'll find someone over there.
Or they'll just sneak past us.
At that moment!
That's our AD.
What's wrong?
Oh my god! I was so shocked!
They finally found a celebrity!
But you can't be on our show!
You're a free agent, right?
-Is this Fuji TV?
-Yes, yes!
It's Fuji TV, we're recording Gaki.
Gaki? Oh, sorry, I don't think I can then.
Ah!
That sucks!
This person is a TV announcer for another station, he cannot appear on the program!
Therefore, the task is not clear!
Where do you think we'll meet the most celebrities around here?
You know, there's a very good chance you run into Brother Tom around here.
Alright!
Is that so?
Let's go.
Sorry about that.
I'll excuse myself then.
I was so happy.
But he's not a free agent...
But I'm happy we met him.
For a moment there I was also like,
"Huh? Is he a free agent?".
But he wasn't...
But he said Brother Tom is also around.
That was amazing.
But I just got a good dose of adrenaline.
You know, back then...
...I'm sure they used to have a picture of Brother Tom here.
-For real?
-Really?
He must be big around this area.
Yeah, I'm sure of it.
-I always wondered why.
-This must be his hometown.
He's filming a Drama right now, isn't he?
With Nippon TV.
And now, did they find another celebrity?!
Finally, the time has come!
Whoa! It's that guy!
-Mr. Gajiro!
Amazing!
They have found Gajiro Sato!
It's Gajiro Sato...
We got it! We got it!
We did it! We did it! We did it!
Amazing! Amazing! Amazing!
He played my dad once!
-Whoa, that's amazing!
Is that your store?
Could you lend us a bit of your time?
Sorry about that.
Could you come out for a bit?
We're so sorry.
That's amazing!
Please park the car before.
It's been a while.
Yes!
That's amazing!
Close the door!
Ah, sorry.
Mr. Gojiro, please come over here.
Good evening.
You know, we were strolling around the area looking for celebrities.
My shop is around the corner.
Really?!
We couldn't go home until we found a celebrity!
Am I a celebrity?
Wait, Mr. Gajiro, can you be on our show?
Yeah, sure.
Thank you!
We did it!
And everyone knows his name, right?
Yes!
Should we say it properly one more time?
Alright.
One, two...
Mr. Gajiro Sato!
Thank you.
I'm so relieved!
1 hour and 32 minutes after starting, the task is cleared!
Where were you coming from?
My store, my store.
Oh really?
I have a store in Ginza.
In Ginza?
I'm going there.
You were about to head there?
That's my wife.
Oh, I see.
Yes, yes.
How in the world did you spot him in his car?
Right?
I was wondering what was going on here.
For real.
I'm heading out now.
Thank you so much.
No, it's no problem.
Keep working hard.
I'm so glad.
Well then, I'll be taking my leave now.
Thank you!
Excuse me.
-Please drive safely.
-Excuse me.
Excuse me.
-Please drive safely.
-Excuse me.
Have a great evening!
Keep up the good work!
Thank you!
This was perfect!
-It was...
-Too perfect!
I had no clue what you were all yelling for.
Yeah.
But this timing...
That was crazy.
We wouldn't have met him if we didn't take it easy at the coffee shop back there!
That was perfect timing!
So true!
It's a miracle!
Awesome!
That's amazing!
It's Gajiro Sato!
That's crazy!
I'm so happy!
Komu, we have no problems here, do we?
Yes!
But that felt so good.
We just got the 'okay' from his agency.
Really?
Alright, the end!
We did it!
Thank you, everyone!
That was very satisfying.
I almost kissed Mr. Gojiro.
You were that happy?
I was.
Bamyu Bamyu News!
With Sebastian Asuda!
And Yasutake Nakata!
The final version of Hamada Bamyu Bamyu is finally complete!
And its title is...
Nandeyanenen!
On sale December 16!