First Ever Gaki No Tsukai - CHIKI CHIKI
Calbee Potato Chips Competition!
All that aside,
Isn't it amazing we all showed up in the same outfit?
These are your private clothes?
We didn't show up in these!
You guys did the same thing!
These aren't our private clothes
Oh really?
Nobody would wear these outdated clothes!
So everyone in today's competition you will try and guess the chip flavour
There's this many?
Yes exactly
There are 72 different flavours
You will try these
Some of these flavours have been discontinued
Do you eat chips normally?
I love them, I eat them often
Oh you eat them?
What about Endo-san?
Well I uhhh,
The lightly salted, consome, the seaweed and salt
So about 3 or 4 of them
I really friggin love 'em
You really like them yeah
I've been eating like 3 bags everyday since they sold them
Seriously!
I couldn't understand you through that nasally voice
Today's Gaki No Tsukai: Calbee Chips Taste Comparasion Challenge!
They will decide between 72 specially provided Calbee varieties
Subtitle attempt by /u/Senor_Wristband
Normally in the Kiki games it's a personal effort,
this time all 5 of you will try the chips
Then all 5 of you will announce one choice
If the guess is really terrible, there is a batsu game
There's definitely some we know
The ones we know are just the ones up there
That's true
Like look at sixty...
Like 67 right?
Shimane
Akaten
What is Shimane Akaten flavour?
It's a tempura
What is it?
I don't know what Akaten is, what the hell is it?
It's a spicy fish paste...
...Tempura
Yes exactly
This is the first I've heard of it
So if you think "This is a spicy fish taste!" then it's Akaten
How the hell would I know
I wouldn't know that
You 5 will decide that together
Ah I see
OK let's go
First off we have these potato chips, OPEN
They look familiar
The colour looks a bit different
These look pretty normal
Woah, it feels very basic
They're not plain
Not plain?
Smell them please
They give off a plain vibe though
Is it different?
The chips touched his nose
Hamada-san's -
A little sour smell
Acidic, acidic,
There's some acidity
I got it!!!!
Could it be that one?
You're allowed to eat them, you know
Oh is that so?
It's not a smell guess competition
I got it, I got it too. I understand now too.
Right?
What, really?
I got it
Oh! Eating this much is OK?
If you eat too many- It's bad too eat too many
I've got it
Hmmm?
I've totally got it
Oh?
Is it an obvious one?
Looking at the title; "Isn't it this one?"
Same for me
I think I got it
I've got it
Did you get it Endo?
Let's try saying the number together once
Just the number then
Just the number? OK
OK
Ready, steady,
French Salad
Seitouchi Lemon
Soy Sauce & Mayo
All over the place
Number 12
Ah, but
Matsumoto-san, Housei-san, & Tanaka-san, all 5
Woah woah, what's that?
Endo San?
Six
Soy Sauce & Mayo?!
No way, so scary, scary!
There's not a goddamn hint of soy sauce! Or Mayo!
There's no way
Neither of those
That's why Chiaki left you!
Who gives a shit about Chiaki right now?
Nobody gives a shit?
Even if nobody gives a shit,
Soy Sauce & Mayo?
Let's do number 5
What about number 12?
Hamada-san?
Twelve
Setouchi Lemon
Cause if you think about sourness,
Ah I understand,
It's not as off as Soy Sauce & Mayo
It could be that one
Right?
Could be either
But this sourness, it's the French Salad
I see
It's definitely not the Soy Sauce & Mayo
Everyone mentioned the sourness,
Yes, yes
Soy & Mayo has no sourness
It's definitely wrong
It's definitely #6 to me...
I think I really can't get it
12 is also ...
Right?
Number 12 is certainly ...
But you know,
I've tried Setouchi Lemon before,
There's more of a lemon fragrence
More citrusy?
I've tried it once before
There's no others?
No more sour ones, right?
Since you're all undecided now,
Eliminate the choices, and choose one answer
So the Soy & Mayo is definitely out
Yeah it's out
If it was that, I'd do literally anything
Seriously?
If it was Soy & Mayo?
How about that Endo-san?
OK I'll withdraw my choice
So between 5 and 12?
It looks that way
Then if we consider our 4 choices,
3/4 of us said number 5,
OK then, I understand
It's definitely this one, right?
Yup
You've decided on an answer, all together now,
please say the answer
The one we ate was French Salad
Incorrect
Totally incorrect
Totally?!
He said totally incorrect!
Hold on!
Is it twelve?!
What about six?!
No!
But it's "totally incorrect"!
There's no way it's six
The flavour you all ate, was,
Number 71, Oita's Soy Sauce & Kabosu!
How the hell would we know that?
What is this?
it was Soy Sauce scented Kabosu flavour
Soy sauce huh?
Soy sauce!
RIGHT?!
It's soy sauce!
It was soy sauce!
We really doubted you
Seriously smell it, it's soy sauce!
Honestly I thought you guys were talking too much shit about me
The smell was soy sauce
It's soy sauce right?
We had to smell it more
The smell is really important
Let's move onto the next one
Hmmm?!
These might be easy to guess
I think I see something here
This is like mentai or something right?
Mentai is red yeah
Then it could also be Osaka Pickled Ginger
Number 64
Yeah
Or Shimane's Akaten
Yes, yes
Oh yeah
There's also Sakura Shrimp
Sakura Shrimp?
Number 61?
That's also red
So the colour first right?
Yeah yeah the colour is important
How about the smell?
Not really ...
The redness could also be from plums
Plums ...
We won't know until we try them
Yes taste them
The hell is this? ...
This is-
Hmm
Hold on
I got this one
Tanaka-san you also-
Mostly- I think I got it
Hold on this is a hard one
I got it
Housei-san?
I got it-
Surely you are too surprised
Was it really that scary?
What did you think it was?
As soon as I said "I got it",
It was like "You're wrong!"
I thought the Calbee mascot was angry or something...
How hated are you?
Let's go, let's say our guesses
Wait, wait, hold on
I think it's definitely that one
I also think it's that one
Me too
I'm confident
I see
Hamada-san is still...
Hamada-san, say something
There's a spiciness at the end
So it's not one of those flavours
It's not?
That is not possible
Then, then even though I'm not one to say,
Isn't it 64? Osaka Pickled Ginger?
Exactly, it's like that's the only possible choice
Same for you Matsumoto-san?
I thought that at first too, but the aftertaste,
It's reminiscent of shrimp
Yes exactly!
So if I had to choose, number 61
It's possibly Sakura Shrimp
I see
Then I say number 61 too
Endo-san?
Number 64 for me
No doubt
You didn't change it to 64 after everyone else?
No, no I thought this from the beginning
Is that the truth?
Cause you genuinely thought it was Soy & Mayo
But, three of us said it was 64
That's true
With that said, everyone, your answer please
The one we ate,
was Osaka Pickled Ginger flavour!
Unfortunately, incorrect!
I've no idea...
Incorrect!
Seriously? It's totally that...
Incorrect
If you say "That one", it's that one
61?!
It was Shimane's Akaten flavour!
Don't know what that is!
I've never eaten Akaten before!
Exactly!
We told you, it's a spicy fish paste
You did
That was the spiciness?
That was the spiciness we told you about
Fujiwara gave you a hint at the start
When Matsumoto-san said "What is Akaten?!"
I explained what Akaten is to you...
I don't listen to anything you say
I'm shocked
Let's continue, next up is this
YES!
We can narrow this down
The appearance right?
It's the ruffled type
One of those two
Ruffled - Chicken Consome
Ruffled- Salted
Either one
Oh yeah
Either one right?
This is a freebie right?
Ah this is a freebie question
Yeah at this point they should
It's gonna suck if we get this wrong
Let's try 'em
Only two-
Hmm?
The ruffled makes it taste different
I'm getting hints of butter
Yeah
This isn't consome right?
I got it
I was deceived by the ruffles
The ruffles are irrelevant
Irrelevant?
Yeah
But it's,
It's honestly, spicy
Spicy?
It's spicy
Spicy??
It's a bit
a bit tangy
OK I got it, can I say it?
Really?
#39, Luxury Potato - Potato Butter
Yes, yes, yes
Right?
There's definitely a butter taste
It's definitely butter
Tanaka-san?
39 for me too
The same?
What about #23?
23?
Could be that one
Rich Potato - Butter & Soy Sauce
Yeah could be
There's a feeling of "rich"ness
This spiciness is not in those
It's spicy?
It is
The spiciness-
There isn't any
You're told us it's spicy right?
Yeah, it's definitely spicy
You guys aren't getting it
It's not spicy, it's a rich flavour
Yes it's rich, one of those
Rich Butter, it's 23!
It's either 39 or 23
Right?
It's definitely butter
By the way, what is your guess Housei-san?
Can I say it seriously?
The one I really got was 13
Mentaiko Butter
There's no hints of mentaiko!
The hints of mentaiko,
Look carefully please,
There's bits of mentaiko
The red bits right
The red bits
This is mentaiko?
This is mentaiko
Oh!
Right?
What if it is!
It could be!
Right?!
Once you tell me, it tastes like it
This is a good hint
It's a bit frustrating, but let's listen to Yamasaki
It could be that one
Let's get this correct
Yes, let's get this right
Everyone, your answer please!
The one we ate, was, Mentaiko Butter Flavour
Fantastic!
Fantastic, well done!
Housei-san is amazing!
He really told us!
Well done!
You were the only one banging on about the spiciness
Hakata's special "Spicy Mentaiko", crisp spiciness, and a rich butter flavour
You skillfully distinguished the taste
Thank you
That was fantastic
That felt good
I'm very happy
Like I carried everyone
The ruffles decieved us huh?
We have to change the way we think
Moving on, the next chips are these
I think I've eaten these before
Oh, really?
I've eaten these before
Is it that flavour?
I think it's that one
Right?
That was quick
I think it's that-
It's either of those
It's either one yeah
Right?
It's rich
It's rich?
It's rich? Huh?
It could be one of those plain ones
Consome Double Punch
Yeah exactly
I guess I'm lame after all...
You're cool!
What the hell?
This part is repeated
You! What the hell?
Endo and I think it's either one. 2 or-
Consome Soup                     Consome Double Punch
2 or 7
2 or 7?
or 7
Absolutely not
There's no way
Consome punch isn't like this
But the amateurs would think so
They'll think it's consome punch
Amateurs
You're a professional?
I think Housei-san is taking a very different approach
Eh seriously?
I really understand that amateurs would think this is consome
Understand their feelings?
Yes
But amateurs don't understand
The smell is totally different, completely different
From consome?
Consome is more brown
Oh really?
Yes
More brown
It's more delicate
Yeah
Yes exactly
I don't have a friggin clue
Not a friggin clue?
That is shocking
It's somewhere between 21 and 56
Not a friggin clue
Is it like-
No FRIGGIN idea!
Not even if it's consome LOL
So loud
You ate it too
Yama-chan which is it?!
There's two of them
Which ones?
So the taste right, for example
Like Kyushu Soy Sauce
Say the friggin number!
He got so mad
He got really angry
So hostile
If you don't say the number I can't find it
He's unleashing his anger again
I was trying to build up to the answer...
You need to say the number
I was building up my justification
Say the number
Like 34 for example
It feels like that sort of taste
Kettle Cooked - Kansai Dashi Soy Sauce
But it's not kettle cooked right?
Yeah it's not kettle cooked, so #4 or #8
Happiness Butter
Hokkaido Butter
So 4 or 8
Is there butter taste?
This is butter, this is butter taste
But the last one was butter,
Would we get butter twice in a row?
I have no idea ...
Genuinely no idea
So could all of you-
This is the hardest one so far
Honestly yeah
Could you all say an answer together?
He got it before, so let's rely on Fonto-chan
Counting on you Yama-chan!
Really?
#4!
Happiness Butter
Understood
The answer please!
The one we ate, was, Happiness Butter Flavour!
Unfortunately incorrect!
There's no helping it, this was impossible
Why say it like that?
Impossible?
What the hell?
I was not convinced that it was butter
It's unbelievable you all did not get this
#50 - Yamagata's Simmered Curry Udon!
Seriously?
It's curry
Curry?!
It was a total miss!
There's no way!
There's no way, no way
Can't be curry
It's curry flavour, right?
Curry?!
It's curry!
Oh yeah,
Really?
It's curry!
After you hear it's curry?
After you tell me...
It's curry!
it's curry ...
After you tell me and I eat it...
After you tell me, it becomes curry!
So now you can taste the curry flavour
Certainly
It's a mild taste
Next up are these chips
Oh these are ...
Hold on...
You just gotta smell it before anyone else huh?
He smells them immediately
Like "I am the one who smells"
You can smell it too!
Just smelling the shit out of them
Ah but ... the smell
The appearance is...
I see I see, I understand
You understand?
What is this smell?
What is this?
They're tasty tho
Tasty?
Tasty
We should be able to get this one
There's a distinct flavour
There's something there
Yeah
It's a distinct taste?
Yeah yeah
A kombu taste maybe?
Hmm yeah
Say what you think it is
Ready, steady,
Chicken Salt
Iwate Hitsumi Soup
Kansai Dashi Soy Sauce
Sweet & Salty
White Soy Sauce
It's all over the place. Housei-san?
#40
Sweet & Salty
Springtime potato     - Matsumoto-san?
11, it's 11
Kansai Dashi Soy Sauce?
Like a weak dashi taste
Oh yeah I get that
"This tastes like a weak dashi"
Hamada-san?
I said #10
White Soy Sauce
Ah I see, yeah exactly
Endo-san?
I said #47,
Hitsumi Soup
I don't know what that it is, but it might as well be this
I said #43, Chicken Salt
Chicken Salt?
Yeah like a salty chicken umami flavour
Chicken?
It's chicken yeah
It became chicken for you?
After you hear that it tastes like it right?
This could be good
The smell is chicken!
Really?
Yeah
The chicken-ness is pouring down on me
Can we get this?
We can, we can
We did it?
We did it yeah
Everyone, the answer please!
The one we ate, was, Chicken Salt flavour!
Unfortunately incorrect!
Totally missed the mark!
The one you all ate was #49, Iburi-Gakko (Smoked Pickled Daikon)
Like I said-
Like you said, now that you know it's Iburi-Gakko,
Please try them again
I had no idea
I thought it was octopus
They should taste like pickled vegetables
Oh yeah!
It's ibburi-gakko!
Once you tell me yeah
After we tell you yeah
They really do
A smoky taste?
It's definitely ibburi-gakko
It literally can't be anything else
Honestly yeah
Our sense of taste is so weird!
Yeah exactly
It's ibburi-gakko right?
Can you say the names first from now on?
Next up are these chips
That's nori!
What is this...
There would be more green flecks, and there's red stuff here too
I see maybe the nori is irrelevant
It's a distinct flavour
Yeah, the hell is this?
The hell is this...
I kinda like this one
I got it
I've no idea...
I got this
Can I say it?
It's #37
Cheese & Herbs?
*Chews in Japanese*
I see
Nobody is saying anything
We don't really know
The staff are like;
You'll give away the answer reacting like that!
Yeah but the herbs,
Isn't this a herb taste?
Hamada-san is really smelling these chips
He's really smelling them
I have no idea, what is this?
Potato Chips - Taste Guess
TN: His mouth is full of chips so not sure about this line
There's a mayo taste too
It's a mysterious taste huh?
It's refreshing, very refreshing
It's kind of a salad taste
Yeah it tastes like salad
Endo-san?
Because I taste salad,
French Salad
I say #5
I think I've eaten french salad before,
Is there a sourness?
Yes
There is
What smell is this?...
There's a lot more choices this time
Like afterwards "Ah it was that flavour"
Like the curry?
Yeah
I couldn't taste the curry
Housei-san?
I think, cause it's a mysterious taste,
For example #46,
Aomori's Shellfish Miso
Or could be 16 too
Pizza Potato
Wait hold on everyone, what is this green stuff?
What a slump
What a big slump
Can you all come to a conclusion?
Hold on, hold on
It could be something simple like French Salad right?
That's what I thought at first
Can I pass this one?
No, you can't
I can't
You can't pass
Really?
There's no pass
Should we go with #5?
French Salad?
Is it really not this one?
There's no way
Really?
It's not between 1 & 5
Seriously?
I see, you've probably eaten those before?
Really?
Can we go for Cheese & Herbs?
Let's go
I see
Cheese & Herb right?
It will feel great if we get this
Yes that would be great
With that said, the answer please!
The one we ate, was, Cheese & Herb flavour!
Unfortunately, not right!
Wrong again?
This is difficult
But, you did guess this correctly before
Really?!
You were so close!
It was French Salad!
You said it wasn't
You said there's no way!
You're a liability!
Blocking our path!
You said there's no way!
You said it with your chest!
Housei-san, Batsu Game!
WHY THE HELL?!
HOLD ON!
This part is repeated
I got it correct before!
That is scary!
What should I do?
Just stand there
Where will he hit?
YOU TASTE GUESS POTATO THINGS!
What?
BLOOJI BAJTARD!
The hell was he saying?
What language was that?
What kind of insult?
"BLOOJI BAJTARD"
I see, "Bloody Bastard"
We could have got this one
We guessed this one
Endo-san said it was French Salad
This guy ruined it for us
You said it was #5 too right?
"Could it be number 5?" "No there's no way"
He clearly said it
It was like a sneeze "Theres no way"
"I ate all of them, there's no way"
You really remember it huh?