Alex
DC Subs
English Checker
Hinnerk
James
Lei
Mickstar
Oolong
Otviss
Rich
Sacro
Solari
Team Gaki Presents
Team Leader
Translators
Typesetters
Typesoshee
hachihajeo
sythy
veliem
TG
It all started 10 years ago
It all started
10 years ago
This year is...
New Year's Eve special
Do Not Laugh for 24 Hours: Detective!
Downtown's
Gaki no
Absolutely No Laughing
Tsukai ya Arahende
Detective 24 hours
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Great to see you all!
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
There are so many people here...
Tsukitei Housei
Amazing...
This day has come again...
This one is the final one we do...
Whaaaatttt!?
Is that so?
Is it really the final one?
The audience is saying "Whaaat" and all.
But you 4 weren't really saying anything...
That's true...
Let's keep doing it from here on...
Who's the youngest out of us 4 again?
That's us
And how old are you two again?
We are 44 years old
So young...
Are we really?
You still have ages to go
You're at the age where we started this whole thing...
Oh, you mean yourselves...
What was this year's theme again?
Do Not Laugh: Detective
Right then, Matsumoto-san...
Why the hell do I have to do this?
Check if the plug hasn't been unplugged
ON!!
Do Not Laugh: Detective
The beginning
The beginning of it all...
Welcomes the men
The same kind of morning weather...
kindly welcomes the members...
Oh man, it's started raining
Oh, for crying out loud...
It's started to rain just as we're about to start...
Oh man, how's it going to turn out this year?
Oh man, that's really annoying
Why is the weather suddenly so bad?
It's starting to pour down
Heeeeey!!
Shut the fuck up, you idiot!
You idiot!
You're so fucking noisy!!
From so far away...
You're all complaining so much
You're the worst, Matsumoto-san...
Yeah...
Why is he walking so fast?
He's just rushed off ahead
He's just such a  forward guy
Really?
What are you dressed as?
Morning, guys
I've seen this character somewhere before though
Over here...
That's fine and all
But can't we do anything about this rain?
Morning, guys...
Downtown's Former Manager
Fujiwara Hiroshi
You got to be kidding me!?
You guys have no aura at all
Well I mean...
We've never been told to have  an aura really...
If you had told us a bit sooner to have an aura,  maybe we could have...
Yeah, we would have...
At this rate, we can't get  any F1 Sous...
F1 Sou...
F1 Sou: A 20-34 year old woman who works in the broadcast industry
How many times you going to say that...?
Do you actually know what a F1 Sou is?
Like what kind of people from which generation they're from...
They're them women...
That's so him...
And because I knew this would happen,
I've invited a special guest
with some serious aura
A guest with aura who even F1 Sous would know!
He's a guest
That's right... A guest!
This has never happened before...
Are you serious?
This is a first...
Right, so look over there
Heeeey!!
Straight from the start?
Special Guest Incoming!!
Already?
Someone with aura...
Yeah.....
Who is it?
I wonder who it is...
We can laugh now, right?
Since we haven't started...
He was so far away...
Multiple guests?
We had no idea
What!?
WHAT!?
It's Nakai!!
What the hell is he doing here?
Is it the real one?
Oh shit, it's the real one
Oh shit, it's the real  one
It is...
Wait, why???
Our surroundings are kind of shitty and a bloody train's just gone past
Your timing was just...
Damn,  your timing sucks
Damn, your timing  sucks
Damn, your timing sucks
Your timing really sucked there...
Even though he's a superstar...
His entry collides with a train going past
That was just...
The train in the back...
Wait...
I didn't know about these guys behind me until now...
So this is the super guest with aura...
It's SMAP!
Special Guest: Super Idol
But the guys in the back...
The guys in the back aren't...
Wait...
I didn't know anything about these guys...
Kusanagi-kun is really  pissing me off
Yeah...
Hey, Kusanagi-kun...
Where is he looking?
What is he doing?
They just came out of nowhere...
Amazing...
Kusanagi-kun is so funny...
The way Gorou-chan  made his entry  was amazing
So funny
It was amazing
Damn...
You're right...
Aren't you guys meant to be at the Kouhaku?
That's right
Oh yeah!
Am I okay to be here?
Am I okayto be here?
I haven't heard anything about the dealings between the two companies...
Yeah...
You're meant to be on Kouhaku, right?
You're fine!!
What are you doing here...
SMAP has five members,
so it's fine if Nakai isn't there
But all 5 aren't here...
Kusanagi-kun, where the  hell are you looking?
I know...
I want to ask a lot of things
First of all, where are you looking, Kusanagi-kun?
Where?
Seriously...
Please tell us...
Yeah, please...
I have no idea what he is looking at...
Nakai
It was your dream to go on Gaki, right?
Just go, man!
He is...
Nakai-kun, go on the show
and make sure you don't get your butt slapped, okay?
That was good...
He's quite similar...
Kusanagi-kun,
what should I do?
Do your best, Nakai-kun
He does not have a voice like that..
He definitely doesn't sound like that...
Not at all...
It's fine for me to go on Gaki and all,
but I wish there was a script or something...
We wish that as well!
So at least we're on the same page about certain things...
Wait, when he said you've been invited...
Wait, are you actually coming  with us?
Yeah, I am, right?
This year,Nakai is  taking part too.
You're kidding me!
This year, Nakai is taking part too.
What, for real?
But seriously, you have to go to Kouhaku, right?
Obviously...
But these 4  have nothing to do with the show...
I presume...
Enter Nakai Masahiro!!
The First Ever Guest Player:
Enter Nakai Masahiro, this series' first ever guest player.
Before the start,
a troublesome feeling...
Wait, are these guys coming as well?
No, no, um...
Everyone but Nakai can just go home now
Oh, they're going home?
Hey, Kusanagi!
They've left...
Kusanagi!!
He didn't say anything...
What is wrong with that Kusanagi?
Yeah...
This is amazing
Are you sure this clash with Kouhaku is not a problem?
It's fine
You keep saying it's fine,
but why are you so confident about that?
and all
He's been saying he wants to come on  Gaki
So since he's managed to get onto his dream show,
let's get Nakai to say a  few words  to us
For 24 hours, as long as it's allowed, I would like to join forces with you guys
Our pleasure! Great to be working with you.
That was shit!!
Can you introduce yourself without any chopsticks or sticks?
Oh just forget it;  just line up, will ya?
It's fine..?
I thought he was heading somewhere...
What a weird feeling...
Okay, guys?
Not really...
Today's weather is perfect for a detective
How?!
These are the times when  investigations really take off
Hey Hosei!!
I'm wearing  these  glasses
and dressed as a boy  in a blue suit
And 100 per ce... oh shit, it's not 100 percent
Sorry...
No, I'm sorry, but...
you really are shit at this
Oh, I see...
He actually said sorry  there,
didn't he?
So this part really has no cuts or anything, huh?
Yeah
There's loads of this to deal with...
You don't edit  it at all or anything
Nope...
You shouldn't really be apologising to us...
In the end, there is only truth.
This year's theme is Detective
I am the one who will look after you from here on
My body is  chubby;  my brain is loyal to the job
My body is  chubby; my brain is loyal  to the job
My body is  chubby;  my brain is loyal  to the job
and my name is Detective  Fujiwara
and my name is  Detective Fujiwara
Okay?
What are you on about?
It's just as we thought...
This year's theme is detective
How many fucking times are you going to say that?!
and take part in harsh tasks for 24 hours
The 6 will become detectives
And the 6 will become detectives...
and participate in various activites...
That photo of me is awful...
I said you guys were going to be detectives, so why are you dressed like that?
Well obviously, we had no idea about this...
There are some clothes prepared  for you in the boxes
So go and get changed now, will ya?
They get changed into appropriate clothing
As they are going
to become detectives
The first step:
They must
change into suitable clothes
Are you guys all ready?
I'm going to get you to come  out in order
You're so cool... you're really fit, huh?
Man, Matsumoto...
You're going to become Japan's most macho detective
Oh, thank you very much...
Super muscular macho detective
You look really awesome
Thanks a lot
What are you so happy about?
Fearless Tsukkomi Detective
Yeah...
Why do you look so happy?
Because it's been a few years since they gave me normal clothes...
That's right
Oh I see...
They tampered with his clothes the last couple of years
Yeah, it does make it harder...
Damn, as usual you're looking handsome.
Thank you very much
Handsome re-married detective
You're the handsome detective
I'll do my best...
As usual, you just look skinny as ever...
Skinny, lanky detective
But I guess you'll be a good lanky detective
...Thank you very much...
Oh, aren't you cute
Oh, they gave you normal clothes...
Baby faced detective
It's okay.
I thought Yama-chan was in trouble since he was last
That's what you'd think
That's true
Yeah, because  he was 5th
Yeah me too, but it was all okay...
Which means...
Damn man, it's so tight on you!
Nakai's clothing size is too small
The size of the clothes...
It's definitely not the right size...
It's definitely not...
It's a bit weird...
It's far too small
What is that?
Umm... to be honest
I actually really like it
You're actually  pulling it off
They probably wanted me to say, "What the hell, guys? Why is this so tight?!"
But to be honest, it's really not that bad
Do Not Laugh: The Rules
The rules are very simple
Be a detective for 24 hours
During this time,they cannot laugh
If they laugh,they will be severely punished
For the next 24 hours, they cannot laugh, no matter what
That is all
In a minute, the bus to the detective agency will arrive.
Prepare a fucking taxi, man!
The nervousness starts to build
But seriously...
Guys, can you just line up over here?
There's a bus stop here, of all places?
Seriously man, enough with the buses...
Hey, the bus is here
You guys really are going to start at this time in the morning?
Yeah..
I am shocked...
There were pictures of that bus all over Twitter, you know?
Already??
Even before we get onto the bus ourselves?
Here it is, guys.
This is the bus to Gaasu Kurobikari Detective Agency
This is the detective agency you're all about to go to
As soon as you take a step onto the bus you're not allowed to laugh
As usual...
Seriously, why aren't we allowed to laugh?
You really do have a point
Can you just tell us what the reason is?
Yeah, explain that to us
You just can't laugh...
It's a rule!
BUS TO
The bus to Gaasuu Kurobikari Detective Agency
On the bus designed for the detective Suga-lock Holmes,
They will go to the agency
they will make their way to the detective agency
Shall we?
Shall we go?
This must be stressful, every single year...
Since it's a special occasion, Nakai should go first
Me?
The first step...
But you're all coming too...
Of course
Yes
He's on!
As soon as you get on...
Detectives
Do not laugh
His butt
looks so tight in that...
It's so tight
Let's go on then...
Damn, we've started this again...
I know...
2015...
There are already others on board
Ah~~~, it's begun!!
It's come again this year, huh?
I mean I'm new here, so I'm really looking forward to it
But this is tougher than you think
Are the days before
really horrible?
Oh yeah, I hate it
Like the day before, when we are on our way here and all,
don't you just hate it?
I hate it so much
In my head,
"Donna Donna" starts playing
I feel like I'm getting sold...
The bus leaves. What lies ahead?
Finally, the bus leaves for the Detective Agency
What lies ahead?
It's still so weird that Nakai-kun is here
Yama-chan, it's been so long huh?
It really has been...
How many years has it been?
Haven't met since Hosei went on a program hosted by Nakai 17 years ago
Like... 15 years?
That long?
What?
Do you still have that rabbit?
No, he's not with us anymore
Because... When we last met he...
Rabbits live for like 7 to 8 years
What was his name again?
Ninjin (means carrot in Japanese)
Please stop that
Trying to frame each other and stuff
Here comes the first one...
If you laugh, the black army
smack your butt
Can I take this off? Isn't it boiling in here?
They're just trying to get each other
You're right
Nakai-kun, that's no good
Nakai-kun, your butt
Show us your butt
Oh, shall we stop the cameras once?
Trousers around the butt area tore
Don't say things like "shall we stop the camera".
We're not going to stop the camera for something like that!
Why would we stop it?
Wait, I had nothing to do with that
That rip is seriously quite big though...
We're just going to carry on though...
Yeah, the whole way
Shit, it's really torn
Don't say things like "Let's pause once".
The vehicle where the guys try to get each other...
The laughter assassins lie ahead
and finally reveal themselves
Now finally, the laughter assassins reveal themselves.
Man, seriously I am so nervous
Arrived at bus stop
Dokonjo Gaeru Theme song
Goriraimo
Himura Yuuki
Kyouko-chan
Ocarina
Have you spoken to Hiroshi about "that thing"?
I haven't got the courage to tell Hiroshi-kun...
Because he would definitely be upset...
If he finds out I only have a month to live...
That might be true, but you have to tell him
Dokonjo Gaeru Story
Kyouko-chan has only 1 month left to live
But I've actually invited Hiroshi out here...
So you have to tell him when he comes
Hiroshi will be here any minute...
Hiroshi
Yoshikazu Ebisu
Kyouko-chan, it's been a while.
What a face...
Reading the script
Learn it, for God's sake...
What a great face...
You have to learn your lines...
Hiroshi, sit here...
Please don't be surprised and just listen to me...
The truth is I...
I only have 1 month left to live...
What, is that true?
Well, Hiroshi? Listen up.
Kyouko-chan was thinking about you and didn't tell you about her illness
I had no idea that Kyouko-chan was ill
What should I do...Pyon kichi?
What should I do... Pyon kichi?
Hehehehehehe
Awful
Seriously... What the hell?
Come on, let's do our best
What's wrong, Hiroshi?
Hehehehehe
Umm I...
What is it?
Kyouko-chan, the truth is
I reallylike you
I really like you,
Kyouko-chan
You said it, well done!
Hehehehehehehe
What the hell is going on?
What's going on?
What the hell?
Please do it properly...
I don't know what's going on... What's wrong with him?
He's not serious at all
Hug her tight, Hiroshi!
Gyuu!
Hehehe
Oh no, Kyouko-chan's condition has...
Kyouko-chan's condition has worsened!
Hiroshi-kun...
Dokonjo Gaeru Story
Kyouko-chan's condition has drastically changed
I don't want to die!
Kyouko-chan!
Kyouko-channnnn!
This is not the time to be crying, guys!
Gorou
Wakabayashi Masayasu
It's too early to give up
Kyouko-chan
is on the verge of life and death.
Let's make Kyouko-chan's wishes come true
and give her will to carry on living
Dokonjo Gaeru Story
Make Kyouko-chan's wishes come true
and give her will to carry on living
Let's make a miracle happen!
I want to have my first kiss!
Your first kiss?
Kyouko-chan's wish
She wants to have her first kiss
Her wish is to have her first kiss...
There are 6 guys right in front of us
So out of these 6
Choose who you want to have your first kiss with
Go in front of the guy you want to kiss and close your eyes
And since your life depends on it
Method of getting her first kiss
Stand in front of the guy she wants to kiss and close her eyes
The guy who you stand in front of with your eyes closed will want to kiss you anyway.
Kyouko-chan, choose your guy
It's your first kiss, so take your time in choosing
Really look at them...
Take your time choosing...
She's looking at him...
She just tipped his hat to the side..
Oh...
She closed her eyes!!
Her first kiss will be with Hamada
It's probably because of his lips
This guy with the lips will kiss you, I'm sure
I'm sure he will
She smiled a little bit there...
That was great, huh?
Why me?
That's great, huh?
Ouch, that looked bad
I'm so happy for you
Kyouko-chan, you will never get another chance like this
Why don't you kiss one more guy?
But get one with
some real passion
Might as well kiss one more
Close your eyes in front of them again
You're kidding me...
She really does like him...
You got thrown away...
Hey, she's gone over there
Hold on, you don't think...
Hold on...
Has she closed her...
She's locked on...
It is her second time...
That's right
She's closed her eyes!!
2nd kiss will be with Nakai
Her eyes are closed!
Yeah they are
Go for it, bro
Yeah
Kiss her for us, please
Her life depends on it
Deeper than the one before
She wants another one, huh?
That's right
Give her a deep kiss
Go for it
That's deep
Give her a deep kiss
That was amazing
You must be so happy
That was something...
Kyouko-chan...
That was amazing
You really did it...
That was amazing, huh?
We received a bit of hope
With this, Kyouko-chan...
Is that enough?
You must have gotten the will to live
I...
Kyouko-chan's still saying something...
I want to hear SMAP perform live...
Kyouko-chan's wish
To hear SMAP sing live
You want to hear them live?
But we need SMAP to be here to do that..
We haven't arranged that though...
That's true
What should we do?
Hey guys...
He's here...
He's sitting right in front of us!
SMAP is here!!
SMAP is here!
And it's SMAP's leader who's here!
Oh wow, the leader?!
Please, Kyouko-chan's life de...
Kyouko-chan's life depends on it
Please sit here
And sit next to her
Sit right next to her
And please hug her for us
Please sit right next to her and sing for her...
Please
Music Start!!
Lion Heart - SMAP
Fujiwara suddenly cut in
What the hell
You're going to fucking sing it?
This is like a "You're going to sing it?" series...
I knew Fujiwara-san stood up and all...
When the hell did you get there?
Okay, here we go
Lion Heart - SMAP
God, she's annoying
You can hear everything...
I will sing now...
You are always my medicine box
SMAP Leader - No volume at all
You heal any pain
That I am in
What can I do with
ordinary love?
To protect you, that's what I was born for
It's not good at all
It's their song as well
Singing it in such a weird way the whole time
I'll be by your side even when you get sick of me
God, he's so shitty
As I watch you sleep, my heart shakes, Lion Heart
He's so shit...
This is the worst
This is just ridiculous
Again?
If we ever
Goriraimo now cuts in
have a kid together
He's quite good...
I will tell the kid that it
You're kidding me, right?
What world is this?
is the 2nd most precious thing to me in the world
You will also at some point
Gorou now cuts in...
meet someone you love
God, he's shit as well
Just like I did
This is awful...
When I met your mother
This really was bad
A past full of lies
Now Hiroshi cuts in
and false love
I'll bury everything
Awful
all those things we lost
A SMAP group has been made!!
This is the worst
I'll be by your side even if you get sick of me
It's just a party
As I watch you sleep, my heart shakes, Lion Heart
Kyouko-chan's life has...
KYOUKO-CHAN!!
KYOUKO-CHAN!
You've gone and done it!
Why the hell is he laughing?
Why is he laughing?
Someone's just died!
Yeah, someone died
She just died...
Why did he laugh?
He couldn't hold it in...
If you were the real SMAP,
there's no way Kyouko-chan would have died!
You're a fake idol, aren't you!?
They're going to leave Kyouko-chan?
What's he going to do?
She's not dead at all...
What the hell...
This really is tough...
Yeah this is...
This really is hard...
1 hour since the start
Only 1 hour since the start
The smacks keep coming
Due to the number of smacks, the 6 do not crack a smile
However, the traps which lie ahead of them
The traps which lie ahead
will not go easy on them
Well, I guess you had no choice but to sing before
Arrived at a bus stop
But I'm not sure why the others started to sing...
YOU GUYS, DON'T MOVE
Don't move
Tokyo Metropolitan 1st division: Shiroda Gorou
Kinoshita Takayuki
You're all here, yeah?
The other day, there was a murder case around here...
There was a murder nearby
According to witnesses,
there was a man between 40 and 50 years old,
dressed as a detective...
The 6 match the criminal's description
They were dressed like you
Come to the police station please
Hang on a minute please
Who the hell are you?
I'm Superintendent Ito of the 7th Division
Takanashi Rin
Tokyo Metropolitan 7th Division- Superintendent Ito Rin
The 7th division will also be taking part in this investigation
The 7th division has nothing to do with this
This is an investigation for the 1st division, so go home! Go home!
And we're saying we don't trust the 1st division!!
Who the hell are you?
Horikita Maki
Tokyo Metropolitan 7th division: Kinomiya Nagisa
I'm like her, from the 7th division; my name is Kinomiya Nagisa
For real?
They got a serious actress...
Seriously?
This is amazing
I'm scared, I'm scared
Kinomiya? I've heard that name before
The female detective who uses some special ability to find the culprit, right?
When Kinomiya-san takes her headphones off and syncs with a person, she can read your mind.
What the hell are you on about?
Detective Kinomiya's special ability
She can read people's minds
Anyway, enough about that
I'm going to take these guys to the station, so move out of my way.
I got to go
Shiroda-san...
What?
You really think these guys are the ones who did it?
Of course they are, however you look at it.
That guy with the blonde hair
He's definitely the one who did it
Well, this would scare anyone...
I have synced...
Wait, what?
"Make it the exact same, will ya?"
What the hell you on about?
This guy... This October...
He bought a specially made cake from a store in Shimokitazawa
You're right, there are witness statements backing that up
This October, at a cute cake shop in Shimokitazawa,
an out of place macho man was seen entering and leaving it
And the cake this man ordered...
No no no...
It was a full of love:
Please hold on a minute...
a birthday cake with a portrait of himself on it,  which was to be sent to his wife
Please...
Please hold on a minute...
Whaaaat?
It's not how it sounds!!!
Wow!!
She figured out about how Matsumoto is a loving husband
It's not what it sounds like!!!
That's amazing!
Wow...
Oh, that's why she said at the beginning, "Make it the exact same, will ya?"
Oh right, I get it now
Oh right, that was what it was about
I did not see that happening
That is a shock
I don't want her to look at me
That was unbelievable
Where did they get that information?
The information! Where did you get it from?
And on top of that,
He's been making appearances at Nakano.
You're right
You're right, there are witness statements backing that up
He was at Nakano Broadway
looking for a "Unagiinu" costume for his daughter
It took him a while, but when he did find it,
there was a huge macho man jumping with joy
I'm hot
I'm so hot
Seriously, enough now...
No, no, no...
I see...
She is really amazing
She figured out how much he loves his child
Yeah, she is
She's amazing
This is not good...
Are you okay?
No no, it's not like that...
What was it about?
I'm so hot...
Okay then...
How about this guy?
Isn't this guy the one?
I have synced.
"Living in Japan is actually not bad at all."
Haha
This guy's preferred location is the African forest.
That's right, I have it here.
The western lowland gorilla.
Scientific name Gorilla gorilla gorilla
A mammal categorized in the primates order, hominidae family, and gorilla genus,
It is a specially-designated dangerous animal that inhabits wetlands of lower altitude areas.
That's what she meant by, "Living in Japan is actually not bad at all."
Reads the mind of a wild gorilla
What the hell...
This is a false arrest, right?
If you actually took us in, it'd be a false arrest, right?
That's true.
What about this man, in the middle..?
Is this man the perpetrator?
You're gonna get synced.
She's staring like crazy.
I have synced.
Good, good.
"Gee, I'm really fashionable."
What do you mean?
This man's private clothes...
He himself thinks they look good,  but it's just
a shameless display of him being an ex-delinquent.
That's right, I have it here.
Despite being a super idol,
his private clothes are like those of
an unbelievably lame delinquent.
On top of that,
his junior who comes from the same hometown, SU of RIP SLYME,
is dissing the lameness of his clothes behind his back.
I wouldn't want...
I wouldn't want this to be revealed at a place like this.
Sees through an ex-delinquent's fashion sense
The worst problem is the hat.
Miss Kinomiya, this is serious.
This man wraps a bandana around his head and then wears a hat,
a style that's been seen only on
Chage of CHAGE and ASKA.
Even on the internet, it's a hot topic
that he looks just like Chage.
He looks so similar, seriously.
She synced.
Reads his mind and sees through the Chage style
It's not that similar.
I see. In that case,
you have nothing to do with the murder case, but
come to the station with us for a Chage crime!!
Let's go!!
Come to the station with us. We're gonna question you.
Nakai Masahiro to be questioned by the police for a Chage crime
Let's go.
Wait...
What?
He's gone?
What's going on?
He's already gone?
Everyone, we'll be arriving at the detective agency soon.
What!?
Seriously?
The bus holding the 5 shows itself.
This, however, is not the finish line.
A New Battleground
It is a new battleground.
We're here!!
We're finally here.
The Do Not Laugh venue:
Gaasuu Kurobikari Detective Agency.
An epic battle with the laughter assassins begins
The detective agency whose foundation is mystery-solving and laughter
At this detective agency, whose foundation is mystery-solving and laughter,
an epic battle with the laughter assassins begins.
It's your wife's birthday?
Yeah.
Arriving at the detective agency
We're here, everyone.
Then why didn't she...
She was syncing with you.
And you were yelling about...
"This is embarrassing."
"Stop it," you were saying.
There is no birthday though.
There is "no birthday?"
How can there be no birthday?
What I meant was I was feeling sorry for people who might be tricked into believing that whole thing.
The loving husband completely plays dumb
Let's go.
A loving husband.
That's a good thing.
That's a good thing, though, really.
This way.
This is the detective agency. Take a look at this.
This is the symbol of this detective agency.
It's impressive, isn't it?
Detective Agency Founder:
Suga-lock Holmes
This bronze sculpture has
a really profound legend to it.
Can you wait there?
He's not doing an explanation like he always does.
Sorry about that.
Transformed into a mini detective
Sorry to keep you waiting.  I'll be explaining this statue, so make sure you're all listening, alright?
Who are you?
It's Fujiwara.
Come on.
Fujiwara, you've gotten smaller.
Yeah, he's a smaller size now.
For some reason, Hamada gets smacked twice
You hit my hand! What the hell, you fool!?
This is the sshhhh...
sshhhh...
Gaasuu Kurobikari Detective Agency's
bronze sculpture of Suga-lock Holmes the First.
Hol... Director Holmes was
an American bus... businessman and... I'm sorry
He's really similar to him.
He's just like Fujiwara.
The mini detective is faithful to the original
Don't do the "I'm sorry."
You can do it, you know it.
You're saying it, you got it.
You're doing fine, you're doing fine.
Okay, bye.
It looked like he changed...
Transformed back to Fujiwara
All right, let's go, everyone.
He's totally different.
Let's go.
Their sizes are just...
Gaasuu Kurobikari Detective Agency.
Agency Entrance
It's large.
It's impressive, isn't it?
Isn't this really large for a detective agency?
This is the foyer.
Wow.
It's spacious.
You're right. Wow.
1F Entrance
A detective agency...
A detective agency within an immense building
More traps await in the direction they are heading
A detective agency with an unbelievably large property.
Of course, more traps await them in the direction they are heading.
This will be your waiting room.
Let's go in.
Let's go in, everyone.
Whoa.
It's started.
Rookies' Training Room
Take a look.
This is
the world famous masterpiece,
the Hama Lisa.
Masterpiece: The Hama Lisa
This painting has a market value in the billions of Yen.
There are times when his face looks like that.
He's not laughing that much.
Uh huh. This is... right.
He's not laughing.
He's not laughing that much.
Everyone, can you take a look at this?
This is a bronze sculpture of the first Great Thief X.
The first Great Thief X was
The First Great Thief X
the riv... eternal rival of the first director of Gaasuu Kurobikari Detective Agency,
A master thief who was active worldwide
The First Great Thief X
The eternal rival of Detective Suga-lock Holmes
Suga-lock Holmes.
Director Suga-lock Holmes
made this bronze sculpture of the first Great Thief X,
so that no one would never forget the passion of being a detective.
He's an enemy, right?
Right.
He's wearing a mask, but don't take it off, no matter what.
What?
Don't take off this mask.
Really?
Will everyone take a seat?
I'm gonna quickly go to the bathroom.
Yeah, me too.
I wanna go too, and it's hot.
Also, somehow,
before I knew it, my top has become
really small...
We don't really need that.
His coat was secretly switched with Nakai's
They gave him the wrong one.
That's Nakai's.
They got mixed up.
That was the one Nakai was wearing.
Since Nakai was taken to the police station
for a Chage crime...
Why didn't you notice?
During that part, when I took it off, they switched it?
Detective Duty 2nd Hour
10 AM. Material that is a yearly tradition begins.
So these are the drawers, right?
Ggff
Well, according to the usual pattern, yeah.
You were totally laughing just now.
No, I wasn't laughing.
Yes, you were laughing.
I wasn't laughing.
It's the drawers, the time for them.
There's a DVD player there, Tanaka, so there's a good chance there'll be a DVD inside.
Airport
DVD Thai kick for 6 years straight
Defense Force
Great Prison Escape
Hotel
Spy
Teachers
Not this year again. There's been enough of that, come on.
But I'm actually in pants this year.
That's right. It breaks from the previous ones...
Maybe something's different, you know?
That's right.
On the 10th year...
I'm opening it now.
See?
It's right from the get-go.
Mystery DVD 2
Right from the get-go.
And it says "2."
They will just not waver on this one.
It says "2."
Nothing.
Is there a "1?"
Huh?  Another one?
There it is: 1, 2.
Mystery DVD 1
1.
And a letter.
It looks like a letter. What is this?
What is that?
There's  money inside.
5000 Yen?
One 5000 Yen bill
He gets to receive money, then.
I get to receive money?
This is a first, getting to receive money...
He simply gets to receive it?
Aaaah!
I've been saying to do it gently!
He simply gets to receive pocket money?
I simply get to receive pocket money?
That's what I think.
5000 Yen is realistic, too.
It seems like average allowance money
It might be an allowance
There might be a time to use it
Then Matsumoto-san, please go ahead
Nothing's there
Oh, you're right
"only the owner..."
envelope that says "only the owner can look inside"
It says "only the owner can look inside"
So we can't look at it
What does it mean by "owner"?
Only Matsumoto-san can look inside
Ahh it's one pattern
Hey, don't look!!
Challenge letter from Kaijin Nijuu Mensou
Translator's note: Kaijin Nijuu Mensou is a recurring villain in Edogawa Rampo's books
Starting now, a top secret mission will be assigned to you only.
Do not leak what is written here to the other members!
Oh wow...
In under 10 minutes, led by your own words, make Tanaka-
You're not allowed to tell us, right?
Matsumoto, who talked about the top-secret mission?
How confusing!
What is the mission?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
No no no no
It's all just plainly written there
If only they
wrote the mission in red or something
Yes yes yes
Well I heard about doing something to me...
Top secret mission's "make Tanaka..." is exposed
You already heard it
Right
That's just
No it said "make Tanaka..."
We heard "make Tanaka...", and then you stopped
"Make Tanaka...", yes
So what happens to Tanaka?
Yes, yes.
We also heard something about "10 minutes"
10 minutes, yes
Don't worry about it,
Matsumoto's own
top-secret mission
a "big science shock punishment" will be enforced on you.
Challenge letter from Kaijin Nijuu Mensou
If you're unable to do it,
The clock behind you has already started ticking.
Within the next 10 minutes,
make Tanaka cry using your own words.
clock behind him starts to count down
but Tanaka is... but...
Tanaka is really working hard...
Do you think so?
You're so insincere
with your animal book
Oh yes, I released that
Published by Shougakukan, or...
Actually it was Gakken
Translator's note: Gakken and Shougakukan are two publishers in Japan.
Oh, Gakken
Such attitude!
They seem like nice orders
I agree
Yes
If I have any idea, I think that
he wants to compromise
If Matsumoto hadn't said "make Tanaka...",
he would pull everybody in different directions to make his target unclear
This is written poorly too
but, about that encyclopedia with Gakken...
presented by Tanaka
Did you show it? To your kid
Yes, I showed them
Oh, what did they think?
They said that their perspective on living things is different
You don't usually realize that, so
It seemed like that, yes
They thought everyone had the same point of view as them
Sure, and when your kids saw your book,
I think it instead changed the way that they look at you
You mean with that book?
Seeing your perspective on animals,
and releasing a book that shows them, "Our dad sees things like this",
changes the way that your kids
see their dad, I think
You figured it out by now, Tanaka
No I really didn't!
You definitely knew!
You knew!
You found out!
No no no
It seems like a difficult challenge
Your face is just telling him to cry
What a difficult challenge...
7 minutes have passed....
7 minutes later
Things like, "Dad works really hard"
They won't say that to you directly, but I think they're definitely thinking it
Doesn't have an effect on Tanaka's feelings at all
Matsumoto's words don't affect Tanaka at all
Only time passes with such cruelty
Time is passing mercilessly
9 minutes passed
but the Tanaka that's here today...
you owe some of it to Endo
Definitely, that's very true,
because Endo told me, "Hey let's do comedy."
I was able to become part of this world
I see, so Endo is remarkable too
10 seconds, 9, 8, 7....
Endo, say something
Endo, say something to Tanaka
Tell him what you're usually thinking!
You work really hard, thank you!
I failed the challenge, idiot!!!
Challenge Failed
No, I don't know what's going to happen.
There's some punishment
He's here
Wait, what is it?
"Big science shock"
"Big science shock"?
I'm scared
How scary
*If you're not drinking it, absolutely do not touch the cup
Big Science Shock procedure
Slowly take a drink
You must hold the silver part of the cup.
Oh wow, it seems scary
How scary!!
It says he has to drink it
I would hate to do this
Am I gonna die?
It says "shock"
I wouldn't wanna do this
Please don't die
Please, we're asking you
This is scary...
I don't know what will happen
*If you're not drinking it, absolutely do not touch the cup
Big Science Shock procedure
Slowly take a drink.
You must hold the silver part of the cup.
What does it mean by "science shock"?
So first, hold the silver part - wait are you drinking both or just one?
Anybody who is not drinking it can absolutely not touch the cup
It doesn't specify if you drink one or two cups
The silver part, right
how scary...
I'm REALLY scared right now
The color bothers me...
The scent is very minty
Yes
It's very strong
"Drink it slowly"
OWWWW!
OUUUUUUCH!!
MY LIPS HURT!!
MY LIPS HURT! OUCH
This is the worst!
My lips hurt! My lips hurt!
Science Shock
very powerful static electricity
MY LIPS HURT!!
They're tingling! My lips really hurt!!
OW OW OW MY LIPS HURT
Are they swollen?
They're swollen, aren't they!?
My lips are swollen right now, aren't they!?
OUCH
They look really swollen!!
What is this?
So it shocked you?
Like "BANG"
Yes
My lips are swollen aren't they?
No seriously, my lips are swollen, aren't they?
No, they're not swollen
Is it naturally like that?
Right there?
No, they're just shaped like that
My lips are super swollen
Then why are there two cups?
In case you mess up
Try it then
Absolutely not
After seeing that,
Definitely not!
there's no way we would do it
He was plainly laughing
It spilled everywhere
How many years have you been doing this?
No, so listen
What exactly was your mission?
What was it?
In 10 minutes,
In 10 minutes, make Tanaka cry
Top-secret mission:
using your own words
using your own words,
Yes...
make Tanaka cry
Make him cry?
Make me cry!?
That is very difficult
I thought I got pretty far
No, I wasn't close at all
Excuse me, but you weren't close at all
AAAAHHH!!!
I TOLD YOU TO DO IT GENTLYYYY!!!
They've been on duty for 2 hours and 30 minutes
On duty for 2 hours and 30 minutes
They are still experiencing surprises from the drawers
I really felt like
it felt like my lips got smashed by a piano lid
Shozo, open yours up
It's here
What!?
Again, this pattern
We know everything...
envelope that says "we know everything"
Look in the other ones
Every single year, it's this pattern
Especially since we're detectives this year
Ahh, these ones, right?
"We know everything" pattern?
Oh yeah, we are detectives
Yes
They've investigated for a year...
Again...
What is this again?
Endo's drawer
Weekly Photo Magazine
Um, not Monday...
What was it again?
Monday is M-O-...
M-O-N-....oh, that's "Mon"
This is just ridiculous
Seriously though?
M-O-N is pronounced, "m-oh-n" right?
Say it properly
That's not how you say it
Properly
Say it properly
In Endo's Drawer
MONDAY
Weekly Photo Magazine
That's not how you say it
Like the word "massage"*...
*Note: The particular word he uses (momu) with his hand movement suggests a groping-like action
Massaging...
Hamada-san is laughing too, you know
How... How did you get that?
Oh come on... Stop it
Don't make that face, Endo
I mean, wouldn't you just read it phonetically?
M-O-N is how it's spelled, so isn't it "MOH-nday*"?
*Note: In Japanese, they imitate the Western pronunciation of "Monday", so in the Japanese alphabet, it's actually spelled and pronounced "Mah-n-deh"
This title, what does it say?
MONDAY
Weekly Photo Magazine
In Endo's Drawer
In the folded page is the big scoop
The full story of Cocorico's Endo's "Joyful Night"
What?
What??
Full story?
Oh, it said "full story"
Huh? What could it be?
Well, we should just do it like last year
Indeed, if no one remembers it...
But for me...
But see, right there
Your anxious behavior isn't good
The folded page right?
Oh, it's this
At the location of "The Legend of Momotaro",
Big scoop!
4 pages in the fold
You can't believe who Cocorico's Endo has targeted!
the Demon of Affairs has appeared!
At the location of "The Legend of Momotaro"...
The Demon of Affairs has appeared...
You can't believe who Cocorico's Endo has targeted...
The Legend of Momotaro?
Notes: Momotaro is a Japanese folktale from Okayama about a boy defeating demons with his animal friends
Okayama?
Must be Okayama
In Endo's Drawer
Weekly Photo Magazine
A certain local broadcast station's
super gorgeous feature announcer!!
Big Scoop!
Cocorico's Endo seduces!
MONDAY
Who is this person?
Oh right, it's the announcer person, right?
You're in the picture together
Local broadcast station's...
Feature announcer...
Oh, an announcer...
You exchanged contact info?
Yes
It was normal, just after work
At an unexciting dinner meeting,
The Demon of Affairs falls in love
Pfft...
This guy's plainly laughing here
Hey now
What?
What is this referring to?
You were seducing her?
No, I wasn't seducing her
I wasn't seducing her
A certain local broadcast station's
super gorgeous feature announcer!!
Big Scoop!
Cocorico's Endo seduces!
Weekly Photo Magazine
In Endo's Drawer
MONDAY
Who is this?
You know, I think this is something I shouldn't really say
It says here, "Constantly text messages..."
"But according to Ms. A, she only felt dread towards having dinner with Endo alone."
"Only felt dread"? It says "dread," but who...
"Only felt dread"...
It's because you laughed! I only read it!
No no no
But me too, I only... I didn't...
What? What is going on?
I wasn't being persistent...
Tell us what happened!
What are you saying? You know what you did.
You were seducing her?
I was not seducing her
So annoying
You were texting them
Indoor Announcement
I wasn't, I wasn't texting
This is an emergency broadcast
Please look at the monitor
Greetings everyone
Hakata Daikichi
On-site reporter
Emergency broadcast
Monday Scoop!!
I am your on-site reporter, Hakata Daikichi*
Note: Hakata Daikichi is a famous Japanese comedian
Actually, at this time
the staff decided to try and reach out to her to make an appearance, when
she gathered her courage
come here on site for us.
to hastenly
Without further ado
Ms. A, who Endo tried to seduce
Thank you for coming
Thank you for having me
Firstly, we'd like to ask you why you agreed to making an appearance.
Well...
I have my own position in society
I was very unsure of what to do
For myself, I thought
that I need to reveal the truth
I decided to make an appearance
I see
This person seems like a petite and cute lady from this impression
Endo, do you prefer petite ladies after all?
That is indeed my type
Thought so
And now, including Endo, the five of them look at the lady on the screen...
They think she's a local broadcasting announcer
But her identity is...
Endo's ex-wife, Chiaki
Assuming a female announcer
Answering questions normally
Ex-husband
Ex-wife
Ex-couple's exchange
And now, we have the panicking ex-husband who thinks she's the female announcer,
and we have the ex-wife, who is answering questions as if everything's fine
Please enjoy as this former couple have a conversational exchange
If you'd please, I'd like to go ahead and have a discussion
What, I didn't hear about this, what is going on?
First of all
Endo Getting Pranked
Thinks female announcer but actually Chiaki
What was your first impression of Endo?
Well...
I apologize, but
at first
I thought of him as
the guy in Cocorico
who isn't Tanaka
In terms of impression
I'd say it was going well
This person says horrible things
My impression was that he's
a comedian who is actively
shown on TV
She says some awful things
Through work, huh?
It seems that you exchanged contact details, but...
And that...
Not by text message
It was a LINE* group actually
Note: LINE is Japan's most popular chatting app
Even now, do you still
Endo Getting Pranked
Thinks female announcer but actually Chiaki
Even now, do you still
converse over text?
I think that Endo is
is more of a sensible person
Even now, I get
quite a few texts from him
Exchanges texts with ex-wife every week
Eh~~?
I don't, I don't, I don't at all
Would it be possible to share with us any of your conversations?
Yes, um...
Endo Getting Pranked
Thinks female announcer but actually Chiaki
I haven't texted her at all, it's on
Socially, well...
LINE, it's all on there
As a member of society
In terms of our personal conversations,
Endo's permission is...
Sharing with you without
not good, I think
Then
Isn't it okay?
If it's no big deal
if it's not something you're ashamed about
It's not something I'm ashamed of...
It's not really...
How about Daikichi-san looks at it once?
Yes, alright then, then if you could just show me...
Can you promise that
you definitely won't show
this to the public?
Endo Getting Pranked
Thinks female announcer but actually Chiaki
Yes
I definitely will not show this to the public
She's so concerned that she doesn't want it shown to the public
Then let's see
But I don't think I really...
Daikichi is being shown a text that Endo sent to his daughter
But you haven't sent those kinds of texts, right?
No way, I did not
Are you sure you're not writing things like, "let me train you..."?
No no no, I don't do that anymore, I've matured since then
Hahaha...
Daikichi-san?
Yes
"I love you" with lots of hearts
Text to his daughter
What happened? Is it funny?
No, it's uhhh...
I wouldn't say it's "funny" per say...
It's a bit... um...
There is more or less a
conflict with the evidence...
What do you mean by "conflict with the evidence"?
Well, even so, yes
This is not something to
show to the public for
the sake of both of you
What a good dad!! It's a favorable impression so we will not show it.
No, no no, no
If it's like that, then...
This isn't in a group, you guys are texting directly, right?
I was seriously being deceived here
It was in a group, but...
But, um, at first it was just between us
It started just texting with her and it turned into getting dinner and then it became a group chat
Sounding like a real idiot
So desperate
For example, "Let's get dinner" was something that
in the female announcer's perspective
"I wonder if he sees me as a woman and is inviting me out"
There's nothing I can do about that
Directly, it's...
Well, yeah, that's true
By seeing Daikichi's reaction
True
It doesn't seem like that's it though
And so
Would you like to talk directly?
With you, Endo and her
Oh yes
Endo Getting Pranked
Thinks female announcer but actually Chiaki
Ummm
It's been a while
Ah hello
Ah, hello
Hello
It has been quite a while
Thanks for before, with um... You know
Ex-couple's unnatural conversation
I have my own position to consider
Yes, of course
So I can't really say much
For myself
I must speak the truth...
Yes, that's understandable
"The truth"? What exactly is that?
The truth is... Um, what kind of truth?
That is how she is, so Endo and everyone else
This time around
With the staff's
earnest persuasion
We have been given permission
to show her face
Wait, but this... No no no
This is pretty bad, isn't it?
Actually the truth is,
she composed a letter
in regards to your feelings
Endo Getting Pranked
Thinks female announcer but actually Chiaki
It will be read for us in just a moment
So Endo, please listen carefully
And so, if you could please read the letter
There's no way, I mean...
This series of events is not right...
What the hell are you saying?!
What are you doing looking so serious?
I apologize for deciding to
make an appearance with solely my own judgement
But there is something I want you to hear
so I have come here to do so
Why are you texting and inviting other
women out when you have a girlfriend?
This isn't a personal conversation we had...
In general, in society, you should be more settled down
You are a 44-year-old divorc.
"I've reflected on myself since the divorce and I'm more serious"
Before, you had said
"I'm a changed man"
You've told me
But in the end, in current conditions
even though you hate being seen as a stupid person
What you are doing is completely stupid
From now on, the strength of your
completely exposed heart of stupidity will never change
Because of your carelessness
I got called out to be on "Gaki no Tsukai" this year too
I'm Chiaki
Puu
What the hell is this?!
No way no way, what the hell is this
No no no, come on now
Gimme a break
But you know, I was kind of relieved
What the hell is this?
What the hell is this?!
And now
Chiaki-san has something to say to you
Endo Getting Pranked
Ex-wife Chiaki with an emergency broadcast
You cannot leave the
Demon of Ahairs...
You can't leave the...
Chiaki!
Chiaki
Chiaki, you gotta keep it together
Oh come on...
Huh, wait, what is it that, what are you trying to say?
Got to bring closure
Bring closure please
You cannot leave the
You cannot leave
the Demon of Affairs to fix itself!!
Endo Getting Pranked
Ex-wife Chiaki with an emergency broadcast
Defeat the Demon
please!
Defeat the Demon of Affairs, Enforce Punishment
What, what is happening?
Dog & Pheasant Arrive*
Note: In the story of Momotaro, his animal companions include a dog, pheasant, and monkey.
What what what??
Wait, in the end, I didn't actually have an affair!
In the end...
What?!? What?!?
Enforcer of the punishment is the Monkey
Whoa whoa whoa, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!! No please, stop!
Ow Ow Ow!
Ow Ow ow!
A monkey's Palm Strike
Punishment for getting rid of the infidelity demon
A Palm Strike, huh?
A Palm Strike....
A Palm Strike from a Monkey really does hurt...
What the hell was that..?
This really hurt...
They've been Detectives for 3 hours now
The drawer pranks are still not over!
Oh yeah! Tanaka still has his!
2 DVD's & A 5000 Yen Note
Tanaka's drawer
Go for it Tanaka. You're the only one left
Tanaka's punishment has to be something original
It seems that way now
Well, it's a DVD again
ACHOOO!!
What's wrong?
He's way too jumpy
You're way too jumpy!
Why are you so jumpy, Tanaka?
Way too jumpy!
It was just a sneeze
How many times have you heard it before?
Hamada's sneeze
It surprised me
I laughed from looking at his face
Really?
It's because I was focused on this
Why'd you have to jump like that?
I've seen enough already
Anyways, I'm putting it in now
Alright
Please don't be too bad!
Ga
su
Thank you for calling
Direct
TV Shopping
This is Gasu Direct!
This time we're following up on a bunch of requests
And finally that ground-breaking item will be on the market!!
A ground-breaking item on the market!
This is it!
They look like just some fashionable pants from a quick glance
Pants made by a high-class brand with a special feature!
But actually they have something to them!
To the viewers watching, have you ever been in town when suddenly...
When Suddenly...
A Thai Kickboxer comes out and kicks your butt?
Have you ever been Thai Kicked in the butt?
This product is perfect for just that occasion!
A fantastic product to protect you from unexpectedly running into
a Thai Kick boxer
When you're in town or at the office or at a ceremony,
Mamoru-kun will protect your butt from any Thai Kick Boxer that you run into
Mamoru-kun
Thai Kick support as pants
Using Mamoru-kun is totally simple!
All you have to do is secure Mamoru-kun over any pants!
And with just a pull of the red cord on the side of it
The airbag inflates in an instant!
The airbag
cushions the Thai Kick boxer's attack
Can just the power of air really protect you from a devastating Thai Kick?
Can just the air really protect you?
If there are people watching this thinking that
You don't need to worry about it!
An airbag made with special material
The truth is that Mamoru-kun is made with a special material!
This is terrible
Mamoru-kun's airbag uses the same materials as a firefighter's protective jacket!
Manufactured Country: China
Material: 210 denier nylon
Because it uses 210-denier nylon
You'll be safe, no matter how strong the Thai Kick is!
This is a personal opinion
When I put on Mamoru-kun,
the feeling of being safe from a Thai Kick boxer
relieves my stress and lowers my blood pressure.
I boldly...
picked the denim type Mamoru-kun.
With my heart and my mind at ease
I've been able to go out more and more,
And so the price including delivery and taxes is...
4,980 yen!
4980 Yen
Installation Payments OK!
Mamoru-kun
Special delievery cost
for Hokkaido and Okinawa
Thai Kick Support as Pants
Once more, 4,980 Yen!
You can also pay through installations!
Black
Blue
Choose from 5 different types!
Crocodile
Denim
White
You can choose from the 5 different types available!
4,980 Yen
Gasu Direct
Installation Payments OK!
Mamoru-kun
Special delievery cost for Hokkaido and Okinawa
Television Shopping
Thai Kick Supporter as Pants
We're waiting~
Didn't you get 5000 yen earlier?
Ah!!
I get it now!
He can buy it with the 5000 yen from the drawer
So that's what it was for!
So this is what I need to use it on!
Seems that way!
If you don't call, it'll be bad
You should really call them
Speaking of calling, where's the phone?
Is there really no phone in here?
Ah over there!
Ah! There is one!!
So this is what it's for!
It has to be
You're definitely gonna get Thai Kicked
Because you're gonna get kicked in the ass from this video
Won't this thing protect you?
You know this is really good for you!
So you should really do it...
Gasu Direct...
Alright, I'm calling them
Operator
Hello, This is Gasu Direct!
Ah!
Uh...
I'd like to have one Mamoru-kun please!
Yes?
Thank you very much for your interest!
Operator
What kind of type would you like?
Uhhh...
The denim-type!
I'm really sorry about this but
Operator
At the minute we have only the blue ones in stock
At the minute we have only the Blue ones in stock
If you'd like the Blue we can deliver it to you right away!
I'll take the Blue then
Thank you very much!
Because we have someone from the store delivering it right away
Operator
Please just wait there for a bit!
Alright
It's good you didn't make a fuss over the denim one
So why'd they ask you what color you wanted?
I was wondering why they asked
But you know, this is really...
That was quick
The speedy delivery of Gasu Direct!
Is there a Tanaka here?
That's me!
It's Gasu Direct...
That was quick!
Here you are
Thanks!
Amazing
They delivered it properly
That'll be 4980 Yen
Ah, Here's 5000 Yen
Why'd only Tanaka get it?
You're getting some favorable treatment!
Amazing...
How reliable
Mamoru-kun
Mamoru-kun...
Ah! It's really Mamoru-kun!
The pants Thai Kick support Mamoru-kun
Amazing!
It's just as it was on TV
I guess it's alright if I put them on now
It'd be good to do it in advance!
Aren't you glad you got blue?
These are a lot better than the denim ones surprsingly
Yeah
It's an exact fit
This is good!
Amazing...
Man these are really amazing!
So when something happens you pull the cord right?
If I think he's coming
Ah there's a note
If a Thai Kick boxer shows up, pull the cord
Mamoru-kun handling explanation
If a Thai Kick boxer shows up, please pull the cord
If it was always blown up you wouldn't be able to sit
So then
Won't watching the next video be alright?
With this it will
Mystery DVD (2)
I wonder what this video's gonna be
But I'm really happy with this!
Mamoru-kun...
My name is Tanaka Naoki
I'm just an uninteresting man that works at a detective agency
Today, I'll tell you about a famous detective case
"The Murder of Don Kong"
Animation: Studio House
Character Design: Yuuki Nara
The Famous Detective Animated Series
YEAH!!
Huh?
Where on earth is my teacher?
The match is just about to start!
OUT THE WAY!
With the face of a mountain gorilla
This man is the famous detective I respect
Hamadaichi Kousuke!
Carrying in his hand his trademarked blue pillow
As proof that he has severe hemorrhoids
Sorry, were you waiting?
Thank you all for waiting for this big event!
From now on
The World Heavyweight title match will begin!
Let me introduce you to the reigning champion!
In the red corner!
A real Black Japanese man born in Kyushu!
The Wild Tonkotsu Engine!
He came from hell like Jason Voorhees!
Sugapro Creed!
Sugapro!!
Get him!
And now for his challenger!
In the blue corner!
The Japanese Chuck Wilson!
A man that will only drink room temperature water!
He came from the planet Jintan
The blonde hair prince!
Muscly Matsumoto!
Get him Muscly!
This is ridiculous
This is already too much
Tanaka's chin is also a little too much
It's a little much
Muscly Matsumoto!
Get him, Muscly!
And the promoter for this match is
Don Kong!
DON KONG!!
OY DON KONG!!!
HURRY UP AND START IT ALREADY!
Eh? What happened?
Everything went black all of a sudden! Is it a power outage!?
H-He's dead!
For some reason Don Kong had blood coming from his head and had collapsed on the stage!
Master Hamada!
Can I ask you something?
Huh?
The cause of death seemed to be by blunt force
It appears that he was smashed in the head
If I were to guess from the circumstances,
I'd say the suspects would be the two people in the ring as well
The champion and the challenger!
Champion
Changing Room
And so they went to get some information out of the two
Starting with the world champion gleaming with a black luster of energy
Sugapro Creed!
Why would I do that?
Wouldn't it be-
Those wet tissues...
Suga-san really loves them, huh?
Why would I do that?
Wouldn't it be dumb if I did it?
I was at the corner post when it happened
It would be bad for me if the match was held off!
Challenger
Changing Room
Next was the man with a suspicious mask and hat
together with a tight white tanktop,
Muscly Matsumoto
[note: from mukimuki, which means muscular or brawny; or from muki ni naru,
which means to get angry or worked up over something]
Why?
Why would I have a motive for killing Kong?
Tomorrow,
my favourite program in the world,
"Tagawa Ebisu Casual Travelling" will be airing
Yousuke Tagawa and Yoshikazu Ebisu travelling all over Japan via buses within a certain time limit]
[note: ref to Local Bus Transit Journey, a program which feature
There's no way I'd do such a sinister thing!
By the way, if Muscly,
does not use nose drop medicine, his nasal passage will be bad, and it seems, so will his mood.
does not use nose drop medicine, his nasal passage will be bad,  and it seems, so will his mood.
They really look at the small details
That's detailed!
Really detailed.
Super detailed
Hmm...the both of them don't seem to be murderers.
Who the hell's the culprit?
It appeared!
Hamadaichi-sensei's dirty dandruff!
To have produced so much dirty dandruff means
the start of great Detective Hamadaichi Kousuke's
renowned reasoning!
Footage of the crime scene!
We should just replay the footage from the scene of the crime!
That's right, we do have that option.
Thus,like sensei had suggested,
Thus, like sensei had suggested,
we replayed the footage of the crime scene during the blackout
And so,
the decisive moment
when the crime was committed was shown in the footage!
The culprit is Tanaka!
We are the police. Move aside!
Police Chief, if you please.
Tanaka Naoki, for being a murder suspect, you are sentenced to receive a Thai Kick!
But now...
But now you can use it
Please wait a moment.
Let me pull the cord
okay?
Oh~ it's here
it's here
Small, it's small
Mamoru-kun is so small
The airbag is smaller than expected.
Wait a bit.
What happened?
It hurts! Arghhh!!
What's wrong?
What happened?
Are you okay?
It reached the front
Are you okay? Tanaka?
It really hurt
The kick reverberated to the front
It hurts the most when a little time has passed
It hurts a lot
What the hell?
Don't open your thighs so widely!
Don't be so dramatic, you!
That's...
That's also no good, right?
This...
What happened?
Mamoru-kun is really small
It's super small
It's different from the one they were selling..showing in the video
Whaat!?
Matsumoto-san was the one who laughed the most...
Yeah!
This is no good...
That's a defective product
This is  no good!
Even though the airbag they showed in the video was so big
Why not call them up again?
A complaint
Definitely a  complaint
That's...
I should tell them right.
Yes, it's better to tell them
This is a little...
I had better tell them about this
tell them to  shape up
Right.
It's better if you use Osaka dialect. Really.
This is terrible.
Oh, they've picked up
Operator
Hello, this is Gaasuu Direct Sales.
I just boughtyour company's product,  but...
I just bought your company's product, but...
Yes.
This is awful. It was a defective product
Mamoru-kun
I see.
It's completely  defective.I wasn't protected at all.
It's completely defective. I wasn't protected at all.
It's completely defective.  I wasn't protected at all.
Air... The airbag did not inflate completely.
Yes
Please excuse us, would you tell us your name, please?
Operator
I am Tanaka Naoki of Cocorico
Mr. Tanaka you ordered "Mamoru-kun Mini", right?
Operator
No no...Not "Mamoru-kun Mini"
Gaasuu Direct Sales' excuse
Tanaka's order was for  "Mamoru-kun Mini"
No no no...
He did not say that
He ordered a normal one...
Not the Mini, not the Mini
What's she talking about?
A normal sized one...the regular size.
I see.
Our deep apologies.A new one will be sent to you shortly. Please wait a moment
Operator
Our deep apologies. A new one will be sent to you shortly. Please wait a moment
so there was also a Mini
Yes, yes, yes
Isn't this good?
Well, well
We did not think there even was a Mini
We were not informed of the Mini
They've absolved themselves of responsibility
Yeah, we were not informed
Good!!
It's being delivered anyway, right?
That's right. Yes, it's here
Mr. Tanaka
Well, I don't think it's the deliveryman's fault
As for money...ah
It's an exchange
An exchange will do?
Yes, that's right
So a Mini and a normal one costs the same
Then, there would be hardly anyone buying the Mini, huh?
The Thai kick's already over though
Yeah, that's true
I think there'll be no more...well, the appearance...
The "Mamoru-kun" this time
We can't confirm...
I can't see the difference between the regular and the Mini from just the appearances
No, but...
I wonder why blue's the only colour left...
Will the airbag
Will the airbag really work...?
Probably...
If it works, will it feel totally different?
I think so.
Oh... that's good.
It's just,  the Thai Kick...
It's just, the Thai Kick...
Yes, there are no more DVDs though.
Yeah
Mr. Tanaka...
What is it?
Delivery;  presenting a gift of apology from Gaasuu Direct Sales
No, no, I didn't...
Delivery; presenting a gift of apology from Gaasuu Direct Sales
A gift of apology from Gaasuu Direct Sales
Well,
that's to be expected
Thank you.
They've made a mistake after all
A gift of apology?
Isn't that good?
Yeah
Hmm?
What's with this mini fan?
Fan?
A letter came with it.
Portable fan "Tsumujimaru"
[tsumuji means a whorl or a swirl]
Tsumujimaru?
That's nice
Seems like it's okay to sit here and
just  push the red button
well, it's a gift, it's like that
I'm going to push the button.
Wow! Cool!
Awesome!
Tanaka, Tanaka...this, this
Mamoru-kun, Mamoru-kun
Ah!  It came out from the front
Ah! It came out from the front
No no no
It's the other way around.
The airbag inflated in front
What happened? You put it on the wrong way around
Mamoru-kun's not supposed to be protecting that area
Why did you put it on the other way around?
Arggghhhh it hurts!!
Too much
That's gotta hurt
We can see your crotch
The place to protect is wrong
Why!?
Plus this too?
And  now you're hitting me?
you're all worn-out
Now it's inflated in front
It's now a version for the front
I did not put it on wrongly, right?
Yeah
After all, the placement of the cord's the same
Was it?
It's in the same place as the previous one
Then. it's a defective product  too
Defective product?
Yup, a defective product
Even if you call,  there's no point
Enough. I won't call.
Isn't it better to call them up?
No, I won't call them again.
You should at least tell them that it blew up in the front
How terrible
This is terrible
I wonder why...
Operator
Hello, this is Gaasuu Direct Sales
Um...The product and gift of apology arrived
Ah. Might you be Mr. Tanaka?
Operator
Well, it's okay...
Ah. Might you be Mr. Tanaka?
Ah, yes, that's right.
Our deepest apologies.
The regular size "Mamoru-kun" was delivered
The airbag activated in the front instead
Can we confirm if you are Mr. Tanaka?
Operator
Yes, this is Tanaka
You ordered the "Mamoru-kun Front" right?
Gaasuu Direct Sales' excuse
Tanaka's order was for "Mamoru-kun Front"
Was there such a thing?
I didn't even know there was such a version of the product in the first place.
I really thought it was a regular one, because of the Thai Kicks
Our apologies.
Operator
We will now review your order again, so
would you please hold and wait for a moment?
They'll deliver again
Wait
No no, what does she mean by "review"?
How the hell do you use the Front version?
yeah, since Thai Kicks are always from the back
Click
She hung up
She ran away.
We got fooled
This is terrible
We totally got fooled
This is awful
Awful.
Gaasuu Direct Sales is awful.
5000yen got taken
Yeah, they totally took that 5000yen
Messing around like this...
What is this? Seriously?
It has been 4 hours of detective work since the start.
Detective work 4th hour
The newbies have no time to rest.
Okay, everyone?
Now, in order to deepen friendships between fellow detectives,
a recreation convention will be held so
Change into these jerseys  I'm handing out
and we'll go
Recreation?
Recreation participation
To deepen the friendship between fellow detectives
Recreation among fellow detectives
What is the meaning behindhaving jerseys of different colours?
What is the meaning behind having jerseys of different colours?
This is somewhat  scary.
Meeting Hall
This is somewhat scary.
What's this? I don't have a good feeling about this
Um... from now on, it's okay to laugh so please
Um... from now on, it's okay to laugh  so please
During Recreation, it's OK to laugh!!
Special Rule
A lot?
Yes.
So please enjoy yourselves a lot.
We've waited for you!!
We've waited for you, everyone.
Here, come over here.
Come over here
So that's what the colour of jerseys meant!?
Come over here!
Oh
I don't think that team is much better than ours...
We won't lose!
Matsumoto HItoshi
Okada Keisuke
Bobby Ologun
Dewi Sukarno
Endo Shozo
Fujimoto Toshifumi
Hamada Masatoshi
Miyasako Hiroyuki
Ogi Naoki
Sekine Tsutomu
Tanaka Naoki
Team Miyasako
Team Okada
Tsukitei Housei
The newcomers will play split up into two teams
From now,
the curtains will rise to the challenge of an earnest game battle
Captain, are you feeling okay?
The captain is here!
Exceptional promotion!!
Thank you very much
Exceptional promotion!
Are you a detective?
He is a detective
A few years ago, you were over there (as MC)
Yes I was
Don't mention my obvious demotion!!
You couldn't prove yourself
Yes, and
There is also no HAPPY BOY this year
Probably next year I won't be here!!
The first event is
Assistant
Chihara Junior
Gaasuu Kurobikari Detective's Office
MC
Nihon TV Announcer
Nihon TV announcer
Sasazaki Rina
Changing Faces: 20 Looks
Train your disguising ability
Changing Faces: 20 Looks!!
Good!!
I'm good at this!
Yes!!
In order to protect their identities, detectives must be good at disguising themselves
You will participate in a game that will challenge your ability to disguise yourselves
The chosen representative from each team will have
to make 20 faces, with 2 seconds between each face
Rules
The representative from each team will,
along with the sound of the shutter every 2 seconds,
have to make 20 different faces
They will not be allowed to look sideways or use their hands
You cannot use your hands or look sideways
Junior-san will compare the photos and judge which representative
Junior will decide which representative
had the most variation
had the most variation between their faces
It's up to me to judge, right?
Yes
Understood
With that, let the battle begin!
Winning team gets 10 points!
CAPTAIN BATTLE!
Miyasako Hiroyuki
Okada Keisuke
Thank you
Miyasako can go first
You can definitely beat Okada
He (Miyasako) is pretty skilled
I have 2000 patterns
He's saying he has "2000 patterns"
How many patterns do you have?!
I heard it as "2000 rocks"
Matsumoto heard "ishi" instead of "ichi", making "patterns" into "rocks"
First up
Miyasako Hiroyuki
Changing Faces 20 Looks
First up is Miyasako
Miyasako-san is very strong!!
Practice Room
Yeah, he is pretty strong
I agree!
They're all funny
Our captain isn't gonna lose though
I can do it too, right?
I don't really see you doing different facial expressions
I do do it!
For example, like what?
For example,
for example
Oooh wow!
you can't use your hands!
Don't mess around!!
That's a move!
It's only your face! You can't use hands!
So strict!!
Do it like this!
Actually I need my hands
What's wrong with him?
Miyasako-san, how are you?
Okay, perfect!!
Do your best!
Once again, here is Miyasako-san!
How's your confidence?
I am confident!
Oh, he has it!
What if you have to look like a certain celebrity?
Yes, I have it
And if you had to guess who that would be?
I would say Jurie
Sawada Kenji-san
With that, let's get started. Changing Faces 20 Looks starts...
Gaasuu Kurobikari Detective Office
What about Jurie?
Did he revert?
You don't have many looks
He had some
There are 4000
Oh, again again
It's (Antonio) Inoki
Inoki was a pro-wrestler
Not enough faces!
No no no no
They're starting to look the same!
This guy is terrible!
We've seen these!
Finally!
Thank you very much!
He made too many gorilla faces
They're all different
If you look at them you'll see
What about Jurie??
You used Jurie so quickly
For Jurie, I wanted to use him later but it was impossible
Just now, there weren't even 8 faces
Please look at the photos
They're completely different
Let's take a look then, shall we?
This way!
Okay, good
Completely different
We already saw these
Gorilla!
That one was good!
Very good
Good good!
Amazing development
See, look at this one!
There's barely any difference
1 and 5 are exactly the same
Please look at 1 and 5
No, no
5 is Kitamura Lawyer
This deserves 0 points
4 and 12 are also very similar
The tongue!!
They're different!
That is a Okinawan Lion (statue),
whether or not you're opening your mouth
These are COMPLETELY different
That's Horiemon
And, with that
chance
Captain Okada!
Okada Keisuke
Second up
Don't mess this up!
He's our leader!
His face isn't that interesting
Please do your best
Go practise
Go-
What the hell?
That's our leader!!
Are you okay? Leader?
What is it?
Does he have something?
That's just the guy next door
Did he think that first one was funny?
You can't hide the ones that aren't funny
Are you ready, Captain Okada?
He can do it!
No, he definitely can't
Hey Okada-kun,
what approach will you take?
The expressions are based on four emotions
I just need to express those emotions
What is there besides those emotions?
Okay, with that...
FOCUS!!
Changing Faces 20 Looks... ready...
The timing is completely off
That's his normal face
Can he even do this?
Oh that one's good!
That one is good
CHANGE IT!!
PLEASE CHANGE IT!!
I seriously wanna beat him up
You can't turn your face
I'm seriously gonna hit him
Is this a joke?
Are you kidding
You already used that!!
No no you're kidding!
I'm scared I'm scared
That's 3 patterns
Only the direction of his neck changed
I got really nervous
But you know, right?
Thank you for everything this year
But you tried
You're definitely not going to get paid
So let's check his faces
This way
This is his normal face
It's his normal face
Around 6 they're all the same
He already did this
You had this
We saw ALL of these
You did this
So normal
This is so bad
You had ALL of these
You did this, you did this
You didn't change your face at all
You're only moving from left to right
Even early on, 2 and 3 are the same
I'm so shocked
17 and 18 too
You didn't do anything between them
He didn't do anything for 4 seconds
Do you have a gag along with this face?
YOU...
You don't have one!
You're REALLY not going to get paid
Now, Junior-san, please announce the winner
the winner is Miyasako-san!!
Winner Team Miyasako gets 10 points
Team Miyasako will now receive 10 points
Let's put a limit
I bet Junior is also pretty bad
The second challenge is...
Please demonstrate for us
J-san, please show us an example
I bet it's gonna be funny
Watch Junior-san
No no, that's not-
He can do anything
I can't explain enough how much talent I've been saving up to today
Up until now, it's just been the introduction
He is a star from the same era, after all
Right
He's making one more anyway
I agree
He's into it
Changing Faces 20 Looks, Junior version... ready... start!
They're all the same!
Scary scary!!
BLEHH!!
Open your mouth!!
This is-
Why don't you change your face!?
He was making kissing faces
This is a game of changing your face
Did you know the rules?
Okada-kun, you're pretty good
He even said that hands don't matter but he's doing this...
I was about to throw up
He tried to be cute
He wanted to be cute
Who were you doing that for?
Yeah, what's with the trying to be cute?
And who were you doing it for?
Who was I doing it for?
My wife!!
Right, let's check the pictures now, here they are!
I don't really even want to see them...
Wow...
They're all the same!
All of them!
Shit, that's scary!
Damn, that's scary
Damn!
It's not changing!
This is not good...
It's all the same...
Yeah you're right...
It just looks like a curtain design
4 and 5 are amazing
And 2 and 3...
This is a commemorative photo
It's so bad!
It's actually amazing though
It is right?
Yeah, he literally has not moved positions...
I did move!
Please hold on a second...
4, 5 and 7 please!!
It's the exact same!
It's the 3 brothers!
Their numbers increased by one!
They're triplets!
I don't understand the "expression" of that face...
Next up is...
Try and find out who is talking under the sweater!
Find the man
speaking under
the sweater!
Everyone on one team hides their mouth with a turtleneck sweater.
One person speaks the prompt doing an impression.
Rules
One team hides their mouths
and one of them has to say the word that is given to them
If they are correct, they earn 10 points. If they are incorrect, 10 points go to the prompted team.
The opposing team guesses who was speaking.
The other team then has to guess who said it
and if they get it right, they get 10 points.
If they get it wrong, the other team gets 10 points
OK then, first up is Team Okada!
Decide who is going to say the word...
First up: Team Okada
First up:Team Okada
We will decide now then...
This will be so easy...
Bobby will be too easy to guess...
So we can take two of them out of the equation...
Captain Okada?
Have you decided,
You have? Okay, if the other team could turn around for a second.
Now then
The person who will talk, please reveal yourself
Person to speak: Bobby Ologon
Team Okada
OK guys, turn around.
Right then, Team Okada's subject will be this...
It's Sakana-kun.
Sakana-kun
Subject
Right then, let's get on with it...
3..2..1 go!
*&*&^&*$&...
Damn their voice is small!!
I couldn't really hear...
It's got to be Hosei-san or Matsumoto-san...
Please can you say it louder..?
Yeah it's got to be
Please say "Arigatou Gyo-zaimasu"!
Here we go
Arigyato gyozaimasu!
Bobby?
We all have different opinions
That's great, they're not sure at all!
One more time
OK, please do it once more!
Arigyato gozaimasu.
Right, please decide and answer
Please give us your answer!
Hosei-San
Team Miyasako FAIL
Right
Who was the one speaking then?
And it was...
BOBBY!!
Answer
Bobby Ologon
Bobby, you were awesome!
It was Bobby...
He did so well
Yeah he was really good.
I was so nervous!!
He was good, wasn't he?
WASN'T HE!?
What is he on about?..
Right, Team Miyasako, please decide who will speak for you
Medama Oyaji
Subject:
The person to speak for Team Miyasako: Sekine Tsutomu
Person to speak: Sekine Tsutomu
Team Miyasako
He will speak as Medama Oyaji from Gegege no Kitaro.
Medama Oyaji
Subject
Right then, the subject is Medama Oyaji
You can't cheat and speak together, okay?
Yeah
Right then, Medama Oyaji in
3...2...1... Go!
You're meant to be Medama Oyaji...
The 2nd guy looks...
Medama Oyaji please
We have to be able to hear what you're saying..
...rou
Only one person is meant to speak, you know?..
More than one person just spoke!!
HEY!!
That's not right!!
Hey, you!
What the hell are you doing!?
This guy...
This guy wasn't the person who was meant to talk
and he just accidentally spoke...
Damn...
Hamada-san!
Please get yourself together!!
Damn, that was a shock!
He wasn't meant to say anything
And they knew it was you speaking...
Yeah, I thought straight away "It's Hamada"...
He just said  "rou"..
Funashii
Subject:
The guys get themselves together, Fujimoto will now speak
Person to speak : Fujimoto Toshifumi
Team Miyasako
His subject is funashii
Funashii
Subject
OK then, let's hear Funashii then...
I think it was Fujimon...
Can you speak a little bit more...
Yeah okay
Please say "Nashijiru Bushaa"
Okay, go ahead!
Hamada-san just
don't bother trying...
No one thinks at all that you're doing it!!
We don't need your little tricks...
Yeah, it's never going to be him...
Right then, are we good?
You've decided?
Fujimon
Team Okada get 10 points!
Team Okada get 10 points
I mean...
Because of Hamada-san's slip up...
I don't think anything we would have done would have worked...
12:30pm- 4 hours 30 minutes since the start
Guys
Our chief inspector
who was on a business trip has just returned
So let's all go and say hello to him
The chief, huh?
The legendary detective
They will now go and greet him
They now go to see the legendary detective
Who is this person?
This is the chief's room right here.
Don't be rude to him, okay?
Here we go then...
Excuse us
Can you guys just go and line up over there..?
Chief's room
Oh, over here?
Hmm, it seems he hasn't returned yet...
Ishizaka Kouji
Kindaichi Kosuke
Sorry for
making you wait...
No way...
I mean yeah, he's meant to be a legendary detective...
Yeah of course...
Damn
He's a legendary detective...
I mean I guess yeah...
He's the legendary detective...
Yup...
Since you came here...
I don't want to say it's my speciality or anything...
I would like to do a bit of Reasoning
Chief Kindaichi's speciality: Reasoning
First up is Endo-san...
You are a comedian but in March this year...
Just to make a profit, you made a songand released it on CD, right?
Just to make a profit, you made a song and released it onCD, right?
Right?
I believe the title was "Someday of Stardom"
Someday of Stardom
That was the film Tanaka was in
and they asked me to sing a song...
I see, so you took part in that
Yes I did...
And that song got downloaded once on iTunes
And got 1 download on a smartphone...
And got 1 download on a mobile phone
So in the 9 months since March, it's been downloaded 3 times...
I felt awful there...
3 downloads in 9 months?
Damn, I really do need to do better...
When we think of Matsumoto-san, excuse me here...
What magnificent blond hair you have...
But in the past, when a comedian dyed his hair blond
did you not label him as scum?
and I've also heard this story from one of your juniors
That you went to Sanrio Land
with your daughter this one time
And you were in the car, trying to get your daughter all excited
Every time you saw a factory, you'd say
Hey, is that Sanrio Land?
And when you saw some laundry, you'd say
"Are those Kitty's clothes?"
You are the person they call "The God of Laughter", right?
I do understand you were trying to get her excited but
your performance is just so...
This is really horrible...
And here we have...
Let's see
This is actually a story I heard from your son
Your wife said, "I made meat stir fry, so heat it up and eat it"
So then you heated up the meat stir fry
Eventually, as you wandered around here and there...
you got hungry
"Why isn't there a side dish for the rice!?" you say
*Note: Egg over rice is just raw egg on rice, usually with soy sauce. It's known for being a poor or lazy meal
And then you ate egg over rice*
You had meat stir fry, didn't you?
You even heated it
I beg of you...
You even microwaved it
What happened, Hamada-san?
It's because you were tired
That's exactly right
How disappointing...
"How disappointing"???
Thank you very much
Five hours into their detective duties
Detective Duties: 5 hours
It's time for lunch and everyone's been looking forward to it, but
Well, with that, I think I can keep saying it
Is that so
Alright everyone
I'm sure you're getting hungry right about now...
Here it is
At this detective's agency
Ah, this again
For those that can do it, a gourmet meal
I hate this one the most
For any deadbeats, a shabby meal
We've had enough...
I suck at this
This is what I hate the MOST
The food you get will be based on how well you do
I really suck at this
This is the one I forgot to mention
It's that time, huh?
This person will be in charge
Come in please!
It's that person, right?
It's that one guy with the same name as the bullet train stop, right?
Here he is
Good job everyone
Seriously, stop coming every single year
Shinagawa Hiroshi
Shinagawa Shoji
Note: "Shinagawa" is one of the stops that the bullet train makes in Tokyo, thus Matsumoto's joke
Your face doesn't change at all
Seriously
Always the same, every year
It's the bullet train station guy
I always get a weird sweat because of your damn segment
And so, in this challenge, you will be betting your wunch... Lunch for...!!
Huh?
You can't even speak right
Really, what's wrong with you?
Hamada-san, please...
We aren't in a normal place!!
What a pain in the ass
We aren't in a normal place
He's become someone who laughs so easily
Is this fun for him maybe?
Are you having fun?
No no no
Are you just plainly having fun?
He fumbled his words so...
Well, at that time, I...
Go over to Lumine the Yoshimoto!!
Note: Lumine the Yoshimoto is a comedy theater in Tokyo where an audience can watch live performances
Eh?
Me?
Me too?!
What is going on?
You can't help but laugh...
Really, you, the limit...
Downtown, what's going on with you guys?
Gently, alright?!
Do it gently, okay?
Then let's get going
As of now, in this challenge, you will be betting your lunch for this...
I don't want to do this...
Praise it!
Praise it! Sing it! Culinary Improv Idol Parody Song!
Sing it!
Culinary Improv
Idol Parody Song
From the Showa era*
Note: The Showa era spans from 1926 to 1989
Idol... Song...?
This year is idol songs!
Shinagawa will designate one of the five and
a card with a name of a dish will be presented
Praise By Improv Idol Song
The rules are
Hamada-san!
Shinagawa will designate one out of the five guys and
Ramen
a card with a name of a dish will be presented
The designated person, with the melody of a certain idol song,
must praise that dish by improvisational performance
must give praise to that dish through a song performance
As an example, Fujiwara will perform
The theme song will be Tahara Toshihiko's hit song,
Dakishimete Tonight is the melody for the song of praise
Theme Song
"Dakishimete Tonight" (Hold Me Tonight)
If you would!
Dakishimete Tonight
Subject
Broiled eel over rice!
Broiled eel over rice
Ahh I become so energetic, when I eat eel, in an instant
The sauce with the secret formula... Uh... Um, goes well with rice... Errr... I'm sorry...
You suck, you really suck
That was awful; can't you do it properly?
Please do it properly
That's just cruel!!
How could you forget how to do the example?
There is no damn reason to get hit because of this!!
This year's is terrible!!
This is terrible!
Why do I gotta suffer for this?
Apologies
This goes to show how difficult it is
Do it properly!!
Nagisa no Balcony
(Matsuda Seiko - 1982)
Praising to the melody of
Theme Song
I love you so love you don't let go of me, mmm... I love you
Waiting on the balcony by the shore, before long, the morning wraps the two of us with a veil of mist
The first theme song is "Nagisa no Balcony" (Balcony by the Shore)
Let's first listen to the original
This is fairly long
So damn long!
This is pretty long
We don't need this part
Wow, so long
Too long!
Starting with Tanaka!! If you would please
Here it is!
Go, Tanaka
Here I go!!
Let's do it perfectly
Music start!!
Nagisa no Balcony
Subject
Tsukemen! (Dipping ramen noodles)
Tsukemen
With all my heart, I want to dip, smoothly scooping, want to use my left hand smoothly too, both hands smoothly scooping
This is good
This is pretty good
Tomorrow, today, day after tomorrow I'll eat mmm... I love you
He's completely...
Terrible at singing, isn't he?
Yes!
What the hell is that?
The last... The last... You didn't change the last bit at all
The last bit didn't change
It was good, right?
This passes
No way!
It passes!!
"I love you"?!
Doing it like this is okay?!
But wait!
But wait, it was fine, right?!
Gently, okay?
The lyrics didn't stick to me
There's an issue with your singing capabilities!!
That's right
Singing capabilities are a different matter!!
This is the level of quality that we're maintaining this year, right?
Well, this was very...
Right?!
The feeling from "Tomorrow and the day after tomorrow, I want to eat"
It was good, wasn't it?
When you say, "you," just who are you talking to?
Tsukemen!!
You completely talked casually just now!!
No! That was not what it was...
No, not at all
You said, "Tsukemen! Tsukemen!"
You're way too excited!!
Why is it just me?
You're really excited
You were laughing...
My junior talks to me casually and I get the out
GENTLY!!
I SAID GENTLY, DIDN'T I?!
Matsuda Seiko - 1982
Nagisa no Balcony
Theme Song
Tsukitei Hosei
Next up is Hosei to take on the song of praise!
Nagisa no Balcony
Subject
Cold tofu!
Cold tofu
Please grill my tofu, just for me, grill my cold tofu, I beg of y...
Why the hell
Grilled cold tofu...
No no no
That's not right
I don't get it
You and I, with soy sauce mmm... Let's eat cold tofu
What does that even mean?
Don't understand it from the beginning
That is an out
That's an out!
What the hell is he even saying?
Grilled cold tofu?
What do you mean by "Grilled"?
You don't heat it
From the opening, it completely became a song about grilled tofu
Yeah, seriously
What are you saying?
Matsuda Seiko - 1982
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Nagisa no Balcony
Theme Song
Next up for the challenge is Matsumoto
But before that
I say this every year, but
Putting the name of the dish in the song is pretty lame!!
Yes, I agree
What do you mean by "pretty lame"?
By that logic,
Even if you say that
You make it so that you know what dish it is without the dish name in the song
Yes, just like that
Logically, okay?
I'd like it done like that
Even in famous songs, there are times when the title isn't in it
So then
Matsumoto-san, you must feel very confident about this
And now, Matsumoto-san
That's right, huh?
Let's not include the title
Such confidence
Nagisa no Balcony
Subject
Crab omelette on rice
Shower me with that endless thick gravy, dripping from my shoulder, drip drip from the back of my neck, you should shower in it too, shower
That's not right
What the hell are you saying?
Crab omelette on rice, crab omelette on rice, crab omelette on rice, crab omelette on rice... Drink up the gravy til it's gone
He said it, he just said it
Crab omelette on rice?!
He said it 3 times
Said it 3 times
PERFECTION
Perfection, thank you!!
That is an OUT
That was no good, right, Shinagawa-san?
What do you mean by, "Perfection, thank you!!"...?
Well... You know
"Crab omelette on rice" was said four times!!
That's right!
I wonder if you were singing from the perspective of the crab omelette on rice...
Exactly
For crab omelette on rice, the eggs are poured over...
That's a good point
And then becomes the omelette...
Why are you showering yourself with the crab omelette gravy?
Because I couldn't think of a damn thing!
It wasn't bad
Let's not make it tense here...
This heated battle for lunch gets even more fierce in the second half
Detective Duties: 5 hours 15 minutes
Praising to the melody of
TOKIO
Sawada Kenji - 1980
Theme Song
Fan the flames, tear through the darkness, the super city comes soaring in
Flying in the sky, the city is flying, pierce through the clouds becoming a star
TOKIO TOKIO while embracing the two of us, TOKIO TOKIO is flying in the sky
The theme song is
Sawada Kenji's hit
It's TOKIO
It's so fast
So fast
The song itself is difficult too
It's long
It really was
This part, here
This part's so good
This part, it'd be great if you could make your song really good here
This is damn hard
The tempo's gone up
Hamada Masatoshi
Sawada Kenji - 1980
TOKIO
Theme Song
First is Hamada
Can he keep up with the faster tempo?
Subject
Pork cutlet rice bowl!
Pork cutlet rice bowl
There is pork cutlet, the coating is sealed with the egg, the pot is... Uh... It's there
What's it, what's it, whaaat is this? What... What is this? Pork cutlet rice bowl, this is pork cutlet rice bowl bowl
Come on, hurry
Open the door, open it
Get the hell out, get out
This is an out, right?
Yes!
What are you doing??
That was just... Amazing...
What is this movement?
What are you trying to do?
That was amazing
I don't know what the hell is going on!
That was terrible
What the hell was with the "I'm doing it"..?
I was going from the perspective of a server
A server?
"W~hat is this"
W~hat is this?
A server!?
That's really weird!
A server would make something and say "What is this"?
A server would never say "What is this"
This is bad!
W~hat is this
How many times are you gonna say it!?
A server
makes the food
then says "What is this"?
Don't get sucked in
There's no server on earth that's like that!!
W~hat is this~
Whose line is that?
The manager!
A manger would say that?
Even though he made it?
Isn't that fucked up?
Him in the store going "W~hat is this~"
Even though he made it
He suddenly forgot what he made
Just in the store
Enough already!
Loitering around
The first part was just...
I know...
What an amazingly
stupid server!
He was saying "What is this" and then
at the end says "It's this"...
I know...
He just suddenly got his sanity back
His memory just went a bit...
Oh, so he remembered it at the end?
That's it!
Damn, age is scary...
But that does happen I guess...
He remembers the recipe!
Put bread crumbs on the pork
Then dips it in the egg.. Then "Wait, what is this"
Please stop!
I can't do this
He was doing so well...
That sound has just been going off nonstop!!
My stomach hurts!!
My brain's taking serious damage here...
He just forgot the name
And as he danced, he started to remember more and more...
And hence remembered...
And you're just like "I never asked for you"...
Yeah I guess
So he's dancing and comes out
and you're just like "I never asked for you"...
I can't do this...
What the hell should I do?
I'm in serious trouble
I'm getting sucked into trouble...
HELP ME
I'm getting sucked in
Please help me!
Man that was amazing
Damn, that was
Sawada Kenji - 1980
Next up is Endo! Can he cut through the bad streak?
Topic
Music Start!
Cabbage Roll!
Cabbage Roll
Rolling Ruerarkl Cabbage
Wrap it Wrap it What is this
You do the buy
the sauce's...
Wait a second! Wait a second!
OUT!
Endo!!
Don't you fucking try and steal my partner's killer punchline "What is this"!!
THAT'S MY PARTNER'S KILLER PUNCHLINE!
Seriously...
Hold on, It really makes you panic!
Sawada Kenji - 1980
Next up, Tanaka will try to praise the food to TOKIO
We're getting hit so much
Okay, I'll do my best
Music Start!
Cucumber Roll
Roll it up Put it in Yellow uhh.. Roll it up
Roll it up Roll it up Put in good things Roll it up
Cucumber
Obviously though...
What's he on about..?
Just Cucumber is fine
You can't just roll the cucumber...
Cucumber
It's fine if you roll it!
The cucumber...
Obviously you're OUT...
Obviously...
Are you guys okay this year..?
You just said "Roll it up"...
I'm OUT?
Obviously...
Oh, I was?
In a Kappa Maki,
Yeah..
the only think you can roll is the cucumber...
So you can't roll the Kappa maki..
You only really said "roll it" too...
So bad...
Damn...
Sawada Kenji - 1980
Next up is Hosei, Can he praise the food?
MUSIC START
PAELLA
Paella
Pae-tte  Put a lot of macaroni in it and Roll it up
Pae-tte   Pae-tte   Pae-tte   Pae-tte  and Roll it up
Poemo
Whilst the Poemo hugs me
Roll the paella!
He's out right, Shinagawa?!
Obviously...
Of course he is
He's out, right?
What's poemo?
What is poemo?
You said it so many times...
Did he say "Wrap the paella"?
It was so bad
What is "Roll the Pae"?
Did you mistaken it with something else?..
He got dragged into saying "Roll it"
That's true
Sawada Kenji - 1980
And then it's Matsumoto's challenge! How will he fare?
MUSIC START
Fox Udon!
Fox Udon
I haven't eaten it!
Last week too!
Last week Tuesday I didn't eat it!
Fox
What is he doing..?
The fox's... wife I will go to the town they live in
The town
the wife and the fox will live in
Let's live with foxes!!!!
It's so bad...
OUT
That's what happens, right?
So embarassing...
Wait, Let's take a photo together!!
Together?
This is so hard to do...
Next is Yamaguchi Momoe's 1977 hit song!
Ah, Ah, Ah Imitation Gold, Ah, Ah, Ah my bare skin burns
Ah, Ah, Ah, Imitation Gold, the people this year who think you're young
I'm sorry, I'm comparing you to people of last year
Imitation Gold
Sing to the melody!
The voice is different, The years are different, The dreams are different
Yamaguchi Momoe - 1977
This is the next song
This is too hard
This is so long!
Man, this is long!
Damn, this is going to be hard!
Yeah it is...
There's like 3 parts to it...
Hamada will now try to praise to this song
Right, Hamada!
MUSIC START
I'm counting on you, man, I'm counting on you!
SARA UDON!
Note that the noodles in this dish are hard and covered in a hot gooey sauce
Sara Udon
This is
AH my mouth hurts
It stabs me The udon stabs me
Even though it's udon, it's not soft
Amazing!
I don't know why but
the noodles are deep-frying!
AH It hurts! AH It hurts AH It's stabbing! AH It's stabbing!
Sorry~ It's thick Mmm Mmmm
"It stabs me"
The noodles?
The hard noodles, right?
Do they really stab you in the mouth like that though?
There's no way they can stab you that hard...
He said it hurt when it stabs his mouth...
It's amazing that a dish
like that still exists in this day and age...
To sum it all up these are the final results!
Shinagawa deemed that Hosei came last...
Thank you very much!
They get their lunchbox according to their ranking
And now they get a bento depending on their results
1st Place
Three stage lunchbox + Boatload of Sashimi
2nd Place
Lunchbox
I guess we are of age...
3rd Place
Seaweed Bento Box
Yeah...
4th Place
Endo Family portrait print Bento Box
Damn, this bentobox pisses me off...
Dried Potato
Last place
Damn, that was tiring
My tooth came out
Apparently whilst eating his dried potato,
his tooth fell out...
WHAT!?
You're kidding me
No...
But dried potatoes are soft though!
Which tooth?
This....
The back tooth
has a filling in there but
But now
There's a dried potato in there instead
Give me a break...
You say OUT but
obviously we are going to laugh...
His filling came out and instead
There's dried potato in there!!
It's 1:30 in the afternoon and something is bothering the 5 members
5 and a half hours since the start
He said "Don't take that mask off whatever happens", right?...
Yeah I know, It's been bugging me for ages...
First Generation
Phantom Thief X statue
Yeah, he did say that
But wait, it is what I think it is, right?
What do you mean?
Isn't it Hamada?
Really?
It's probably Hamada...
First generation Phantom Thief
Look's like Hamada?
Take it off, Tanaka...
What, if we're going to do that, you take it off, Hosei...
Shall we do Rock Paper Scissors?
Shall we?
Let's do it
"1 loser" Rock Paper Scissors?
Yeah?
Yup...
Wait, hold on... What is "1 loser" Rock Paper Scissors?
So whoever is alone as rock, paper or scissors loses...
So we're not doing it until the last person loses but
"1 loser" rock paper scissors
The 5 do rock papers scissors and whoever has different choice to everyone else loses.
we do rock, paper or scissors, and whoever is by themselves...
Yeah, yeah
That way, It'll probably be decided after 3 or 4 times
Rock, Paper, Scissors...
Ah, this...
Two...
we have two people, Hamada and Endo
Hamada put out scissors so it's Hamada's loss
Thanks
Shouldn't this mean we'd have to play again?
This is Rock-Paper-Scissors, after all.
In the end, we're playing rock-paper-scissors so
it's good that it's fair
Yes, we completed it in one round
It's Hamada-san
Let's do this the next time,
then we'll forgive it just that one time
It's this sort of rule
Why?
We'll do it according to the rule
How gentle
We're playing again?
Gentlemanly
This is a gentle order
Macchan you said it well!!
"1-loser" Rock-Paper-Scissors
Once 2 people are left,
we can then  move to play normal Rock-Paper-Scissors
"1-loser" Rock-Paper-Scissors
No, this is different...
It becomes 1 person win
No, no, this is 1-loser...
Yes, 1-loser
Not 1-winner
No, no
That's strange!
I put out Scissors, and you guys put out Paper
Normally, it'd be my win
But Matsumoto-san was the one who said it
That it's over when 1 person is left
It's a loss if one person's left
Please!!
Yes, please!
You were the only one left
This...
This year too, we're watching this in the studio, right?
Yes, we'll all watch together
The guests will draw back, I believe
Why?
I put out scissors,
you guys put out paper;
why am I the loser?
The meaning, "only 1 person using a particular sign",
was hidden in the rule we decided
Endo, decide for us
The rule
Shall we go with naming it 1-person-left Rock-Paper-Scissors
instead?
1-person-left Rock Paper Scissors
We played 1-person-left Rock-Paper-Scissors
What did you think we played?
1-loser Rock-Paper-Scissors
1-loser Rock-Paper-Scissors?
So shall we make the previous game invalid?
Yeah
1-loser Rock-Paper-Scissors?
I said "1-loser Rock-Paper-Scissors" just now
we'll move to "1-person-left Rock-Paper-Scissors"
He said it
so...
Do over with "1-person-left Rock-Paper-Scissors"
1-person-left Rock-Paper-Scissors!
What to do in this situation...
It's you
Is it okay for me?
It was a pretty pattern
where only 1 person was left
It has been decided that Endo will be the one to remove the mask
Shall I remove it?
Yes, take it off
Why do I have to be the one to take it off when I'm the one who does not want to do it the most..?
You have to do it gently
I'm scared
As expected...
It's Hamada-san
This is clearly Hamada-san!!
How old is this, Hamada-san?
Just so clear that it's  Hamada-san
Just so clear that it's Hamada-san
Phantom Thief X the First
As expected, it was like that
With the eyes uncovered,  it suddenly became Hamada-san
That's right
I thought it was Hamada-san
For an instant, I wondered
but once the eyes were revealed...
Look,
if you do this,
no one will know who this is
Yeah, seriously.
Really?
Yes
It's the eyes
Fujiwara
This, do you know who this is?
It's me! No matter how you look...
Say something...
At least say something
A Hamada lookalike statue of Phantom Thief X the First
The 5 did not know, but this statue will later create a great storm of trouble
will later cause a great storm of trouble!!
Everyone, okay?
From now, um... our
Black...Gaasuu Kurobikari Detective
Black... Gaasuu Kurobikari Detective
Handed down the generations in Gaasuu Kurobikari Detective Agency
Is training of the basic physical ability needed by detectives
So put on your outer coats and let's go
Special training ...we're going
Basic physical ability needed by Detectives
Special training to build that up
Basic physical ability?
Everyone, board the bus
They board the bus and head towards the training center
What awaits them..?
They board the bus and start their journey. What awaits at their destination?
the five's new battle
curtain rises
The five's new
The curtain rises on the five's new battle
After a journey of 15 minutes
Everyone, we're almost at the special training facility
Gaasuu Kurobikari Physical Training Center
The Detective Agency's pride, the physical center
Certainly,
in their minds,
unpleasant memories surface
We're here, let's go
Everyone, let's go
Over here
we're here...
This, huh..?
Countdown to Hell
The special training's full particulars will be made clear
Everyone, over here
The training room's suddenly so old
Here
Training Center waiting room
Over here
You can't move around easily in those clothes so
Change into these training clothes here
there's no time so hurry up and change
What do you mean there's no time!?
Before physical training,
They clad themselves in training clothes and prepare for the special training. Then...
they change into clothes which are easier to move around in
A
alarm
goes
off
sudden
Black Oni intrudes
What is it?
Really, what the hell!?
So many came in
Your mouth's open
What's this?
So many?
Your mouth's open
The Black Oni squad
carried Matsumoto away
Feels like we'd bang into the wall the way you're carrying me
The Black Oni squad
carried Matsumoto away
At that time, if we had stopped them,
we wouldn't need to do this tag game?
To save that guy,
we have to run around, right?
Let's go
Finally...
Okay
Shouldn't there be an age limit or something
for this?
Something like a Senior class
Until 45 years old
Until 45 years old...
The stage where they will be using for basic physical training is...
Wah!
It's vast!!
Yeah, it's spacious
Really spacious place
Spacious
Wow, spacious
We don't need such a vast space
It's a baseball field !!
94m by 94m Baseball field
This large and spacious 94m by 94m baseball field tells of the harshness of the training
tells of the harshness
Can you guys line up here?
How spacious!
Now, the special training you will undergo is this!!
You sure never get sick of this segment, huh!?
Yeah, every year, every year
From now, it's okay to laugh but
chasing after you,
if you get caught by the Oni
a harsh punishment  will be meted out
We know that already
Why?!
Several Oni will enter play at the start
Together with the start, several will enter play
The number will continue to increase every 20 minutes
Absolutely No Getting Caught
Detectives
The curtains rise on Absolutely No Getting Caught: Detectives
And so
If it's only you guys who are
old men, it can't be considered training
Then just don't conduct this training
Yeah, we know we're old
so we called in a special guest
Special guest?
It's this person!!
Please enter!!
Helper
Yagira Yuuya
It's Yagira!
I'm Yagira Yuuya. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you
Why are you here?
An awesome person has appeared
I'm a big fan of Gaki no Tsukai
Though I'm feeling nervous, please take care of me
No, no, no
Yeah
You're not a person who should participate in this sort of program
Do you know what it is we're doing here?
Yes, I know. I watch every year.
Seriously?
No, no, no
Seriously? An amazing person has arrived...
Actor Yagira Yuuya is taking part. He will later get to know the scariness of variety shows.
First appearance on a variety program
Yagira Yuuya participates!!
Thus,
I will now explain the specifics of the Special Training
Firstly, look over there
There!
Ah, he's already there
Matsumoto-san
While running from the Oni, they need to find the key to the confinement room
While running from the appearing Oni, they need to find the key to the confinement room, and rescue Matsumoto
Matsumoto will get punished if the wrong key is used.
Explanation's finished?
Ready?
Yagira-kun
Please say a few words of enthusiasm
I'll find the key!!
I'll find the
Oh~ good.
Let's find the key!
Let's end this quick
Training... start!
It's coming! What will be the first one?
Start of the Physical Training
Wah! Run!
Slipper
Wait a bit...
Wait wait
I said wait
Okay okay Hamada-san got caught
You said "Okay okay", you...
This was a serious blow
Definitely
It was a serious blow this time as well.
It hurts!
This year too,
Matsumoto is relaxing alone
No such thing as "relaxing"
Again...I can't take it?
How was it, Hamada-san?
Really, this is super painful
This'll cause a concussion
Seriously?
The second Oni enters
Harisen (Paper fan) is coming!
Harisen
Run!!
It'd be really painful, really painful
Hard to escape from that...
Hard to escape
Harisen
No
Hosei-san!
Your hat!
That's going to hurt... That is going to hurt.
That really hurts...
Damn, that hurts...
It really hurts!
Yagira-kun, be careful, okay, because they're going to come out, one after another
What shall we do, if we don't go forward?
We will only be able to run around this area
That's true
Uh-oh, here comes a Harisen
Harisen
Right, he's locked on!
Locked on Yagira
He's seen him
Yagira-kun has been targeted!
Damn he's fast
Damn, he's not like us...
So different to us...
Oh wow, he's fast...
Wow, he's fast...
Uh-oh, but he's in trouble!
He got caught
It's going to hurt!
Poor thing...
He's like Japan's upcoming actor...
Let's go about this with good teamwork...
I saw before, like you...
Can I say this?
shoved Tanaka towards them...
Hosei sold Tanaka out
When the Harisen came out just now...
Hosei shoved me so hard towards them...
towards the Harisen...
Did you push him?
Yes
He admitted it straight away
I thought if he got hit, I would be safe
Let's not do that kind of thing...
Can I do it though when it's something I really don't want to do?
What an amazing face...
Just amazing...
But if we start thinking like that, we all don't want certain things...
That's what I hate about being in a group, personally...
But seriously, we need to find a place to hide
That's true
Sorry guys, I'm splitting up from you guys.
Okay, let's find the key
Look at him by himself, trying so desperately,
Hosei goes to hide himself
because he doesn't want to get caught, I really want people like him to get caught...
I do not want to become a senpai like him...
So true, I hate Hosei-san when he's like this...
Go run in different directions!!
Hamada-san, a Oni has just come...
Oni is going from behind to get Hosei
Harisen
Go and scatter yourselves!
Please try and find the key yourself too!
Yeah...
Yes yes yes...
Good good good...
But seriously...
Are you going to be okay by yourself?
There's one coming, isn't there!?
I could tell by your eyes!
Damn, he found out!
I could tell by your eyes!!
There was one coming just now, wasn't there!?
I got it!!
How the hell did he find out!?
I figured it out
from your line of sight!
It's coming over here
It's coming here
Please, man...
Uh-oh...
They're in trouble
They're in big trouble
They're in serious trouble
The Harisen guy looks quite tired...
Oh, he's been caught
He gets caught because he does that kind of shit
Exactly
That's karma...
like what comes around goes around...
Hamada-san suddenly started talking...
Unnaturally...
Really..?
Hamada-san...
He was trying to speak to take my mind off it
and trick me
Yeah, Endo was next to me going:
"There's one coming... There's one coming..."
I was like "Oh right"
But seriously, I think we need to improve our teamwork...
That was a bit crap of all of us...
What's wrong with your ear?
Umm, I... I'm really sorry but
I don't think I can carry on...
My ear got whacked by the Harisen...
He used the same shit excuse 16 or 17 years ago...
That was also the Oni Gokko in the Gymnasium...
He said the EXACT same thing!
But this could be serious...
What? When he hit it?
Nothing's wrong with it...
Yeah, it hit my ear
and my ear is ringing right now...
Maybe your ear drum just went...
Oh definitely...
I seriously can't hear anything, nothing at all
I seriously can't hear anything, nothing at all...
For real..?
Yeah yeah...
But you're replying really well...
Hosei's lie quickly gets figured out
What a crap trick...
What are you on about..?
to get figured out with
The Skating Princess appears!!
The terrifying Oni Gokko...
But we need to get over there
and find the treasure chest...
Tanaka, go to the stands
and see if the treasure chest is there
Tanaka goes to the stands alone
Go, we'll let you know if a Oni comes...
Please do!
It might take a while by himself
So Yuuya, can you go from the other side?
That's true
Yagira goes to the other side of the stands
Go check the other side of the stands for the treasure chest
Matsumoto is confused by the sudden greetings
Okay, Hamada-san
It is weird though, right?
I'm going to go over there...
Like it wasn't really the time or place...
Endo goes to see the outer stands
Yeah, you never know
Man, I'm quite hot...
I'm going to leave it here...
I'm going to leave it with you
Coincidentally sees a Oni on his break
Baseball bat
You're kidding me!!
Is this seriously happening!?
Surely this isn't happening!
There was one over there?
I guess it was hiding...
It was hiding...
The Oni was also like "what?"...
Damn, that hurts...
Damn that made such a loud sound!
Oh shit, that hurts!
Guys!!
I have found a treasure chest!!
They find a key
Finally, they find a key
There it is
They make their way to Matsumoto
Matsumoto-san
We've found the key
This is this year's guest...
The guest..
Nice to meet you, my name is Yagira Yuuya
Oh, hello there...
I'm counting on you...
Open it up for him
Go for it...
You hadn't met up close yet...
Let's get this over with quickly...
If this just opens, we're done with it...
Yeah, it'll be the end
Oh dear... It's the wrong one
You're saying it like it's no big deal: "Oh, it was the wrong one"...
Matsumoto to receive punishment
Yuuya, just come down
He's going to receive his punishment now
Again this year...
Oh man, this sucks...
Obachan
It's tough to even look back
There she is...
Hip-shaking Obachan...
I don't want to
look behind me...
There she goes. She's shaking it...
She's still got it
Still on active duty
She's a grandma, you know..?
Amazing...
An actor who's participated in the Cannes Film Festival gets excited
by the live Obachan
What the hell is with this moment..?
This is harsh...
So gentle...
Punishment is a nose lick
The nose...
She's started with the nose...
He got his nose licked pretty hard...
It's warm though...
Still on active duty
How's the nose?
She licked my nose...
Um...
She really does smell of someone who has lived a long time
He won't say it clearly... But I bet it stinks
Guys, seriously
This is weird...
Like let's finish this in the next one or two goes...
Of course, that's what we are aiming for...
Of course...
Of course
As soon as you guys found that key...
I could hear noise from behind there
The Obachan was getting ready...
Yeah...
We get it...
20 minutes since the start...
We are increasing the number of Oni...
More Oni come out
They search outside the baseball field...
Shall we go over there?
Where are you, treasure chest?
This went on for ages...
It wouldn't be in the bus, would it..?
Check it, just in case...
I will go ahead
Okay...
That's freaky...
You're kidding me...
You would react like that...
What the hell..?
What the hell is this..?
He got caught inside the bus!
Hosei-san did...
Hosei-san got...
Wait...
What was it?
Hamada-san!
Balloon festival..?
Balloon festival
Balloon festival?
Yeah, it says balloon festival
For real?
Yeah...
Wait...
But it's a "festival" so it might be something fun
Oh yeah, you never know, it might be something fun...
What is that?
Holy shit, what a fatty...
Balloon festival...
300 balloons...
What is this?
He's going to float away..?
What?
Wait, this is actually scary...
Oh, I get it...
It's, like, his thing, something he has to take with him as he runs
Oh, I get it!
They'll know where you are straight away
Oh damn, man...
Balloons make him easier to find
This is so annoying...
Please don't come near us
Otherwise they'll know where we are!
What is this?!
They'll find out our location too!
Please wait for me!
No, otherwise they'll know where we are
Hosei-san!
This is to make sure they know where you are...
Yeah, that's right
The branches, the branches...
It's going to hit
They caught onto the branches...
This is the worst!
It really is
It is
It's seriously the worst
Oh, but seriously...
Shall we head back to the grounds?
Hosei hides himself among the balloons
That's not a bad idea...
and you're going to try and trick them?
What the hell is Hosei-san doing..?
It's impossible though I guess, while Hosei-san has that on
I see, you're going to hide among the balloons?
Secret move: Hiding among balloons
He's hiding himself among the balloons
I can use this to my advantage...
I'm going to hide...
Oh shit...
There's something there
Worst case scenario, when I can't run away...
But if you do it too much...
It'll just explode...
Loads will just burst and then...
Who is it?
What does it say?
Who is this?
Who?
Who, what is it?
Panda
It says panda...
Wait what, what is panda?
There's another panda which has just arrived
Oh I see, panda...
Oh, this is quite tough...
Tanaka always has this done to him...
Yeah, again this year...
Yeah...
I would hate this so much...
What a pain in the ass...
That is awful...
This face thing has become...
This face thing has become literally like my thing
Every single year...
Your balloons are useless!
You didn't hide...
I did hide!!
I did hide!
Let's not fight...
Sorry...
He gets angry so quickly, like this year, you have been...
No no no...
Yeah, what's wrong, man?
You're so grumpy!
That's not true; I'm sorry!
Yeah, seriously...
I'm so sorry
Please go find it, the treasure box
Okay, let's seriously look for it
We probably need to go around and over there
Okay, let's go
That's true, I guess...
They resume their search
Let's go over there
It's really not anywhere we have looked for it...
How's it going?
Nope...
Not here, nope
Harisen
Nothing here
Holy shit, they're really coming after us
They're really running towards us
It looks like they're coming, they're coming
They're coming
There's still more of them..?
Harisen and slipper!
Slipper
This is bad
Secret move: Balloon hiding jutsu!
It's not something to go "Ohhh" about...
What the hell, you guys..?
Definitely not something to "Ohhh" about...
The Oni is bewildered
Wow, amazing
What is Hosei-san doing?
What the hell is he doing..?
He's fighting him...
He's properly fighting him...
He's fighting him so he doesn't get smacked...
He's using the balloons to desperately try and save himself...
He's using the balloons..?
Man he's really fighting...
He got away!!
It's a rare animal...
Of course he will get caught again...
Damn that's amazing...
He's doing well
He's serious
Hosei-san is serious...
Balloons are popping one after another...
And his face!!
His face...
His face is really something!
His face!
Slipper
His face...
His face is so funny
He's got the string wrapped around himself
The look of desperation
Damn, that's scary
Wow, this is really amazing
It really is amazing
Come on!!
Come on, Hosei-san!
Great fight, great fight!
Come on, come on!
Do your best!
One after another popping...
And here comes the backup...
Here comes the backup...
Hosei-san, another one has arrived
Baseball bat
This is awful
They really are popping one after another
They're popping one after another!
This is amazing
What the hell is this..?
It's like a gun fight...
Wow...
What the hell is this?
They're double-teaming you!
I literally have no idea
I don't know what to look at right now...
It's like a fireworks display...
It's just fireworks...
He's...
It's a fireworks display
He's dead
That was amazing
Hosei-san...
Damn, that's scary...
What an ugly sight...
That is scary...
Great fight, it was a great fight
Yeah it was...
Damn, you were fighting so hard, huh?
We were supporting you from the bottoms of our hearts
I nearly got away...
Yeah that's right
If it was just against the slipper guy...
Shall we split up once...
and find the treasure box?
Okay, then we will also...
Some of you go over there...
Okay, here I go...
Okay I will go this way...
It really was like that anime DVD from before...
So you do actually do that...
Just as the anime said...
I feel a bit of spite about this...
Where could it be..?
Yeah, we really can't find it...
What the hell is that?
What?
Why?
Time Bomb
It said "Time Bomb"
Hang on a second...
What the hell is "Time Bomb"?
Seriously, what the hell!?
Oh, he's taking the balloons off him
Maybe he's a good guy
It says "Time Bomb" though...
Here comes another one...
Oh shit...
That's scary, man...
That is...
WHAT THE FUCK!?
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE
Now THIS, I cannot do! I can't do this!
This is seriously bad...
I don't want a time bomb!!
This is really bad...
Wait!
They're setting it up...
Guys, please...
Be by my side...
Die with me...
This is bad, they're setting the time bomb
Please die with me!
Please be next to me at the end,
I beg you!
No way...
you're going to explode...
You're definitely going to blow up!
Hosei-san, I'm sorry!
Please!
You've only got one minute!
Oh yeah!
Hosei-san, I'm so sorry!
Hey!
No way.
No way!
Hey
Please!
Help me!
Help me!!
Endo!
I'm sorry!
This is my once-in-a-lifetime wish!
Please!
Come here!
I'm so sorry, Hosei-san, but...
Please!
I'm sorry!!
You'll end up getting blown up too...
Wait...
You don't know what's going to happen
so damn, that would be scary...
Only 25 seconds left!
25 seconds left!
25 seconds?!
Another 25 seconds?
No, I can't!
They got me!
Go over there!
My foot!
My foot!!
Don't come towards me!
My foot!
How many more seconds?!
My foot!!
How many more seconds??
You're walking fine
What the hell is wrong with you..?
He's definitely lying...
It's going to explode...
Stop shouting "my foot"!
Damn that's scary
Like 10 seconds or so
No no no, that's so scary
That's so scary...
How many more seconds?!
Oh shit!
What the hell..?
What is this..?
It would be scary though...
That pisses me off...
You would be scared...
That's so annoying!
Time since the beginning of the training
40 minutes
More Oni appear
Increasing the number of Oni
Hamada-san, please come here...
Endo's Mom
Oh, them again...
Hamada-san, please come here...
Here we go again...
I don't know what they actually did to you...
Please come and relax...
You just went with them...
Yeah, you just went with her...
Hamada-san just...
Got kidnapped..?
Hamada-san just got caught
Yeah, he got kidnapped
He just went in though with no fight...
Maybe he wasn't kidnapped then...
They took me in!!
There was a woman
It might have been a female
Oh, hello there!
Endo Family
Welcome!
You're here again!?
Yes we are...
How are you..?
First things first, greetings after 1 year apart
Hello...
Hello there...
You've really been great to us and all...
No no no, not at all...
You must be tired today...
I mean, yes of course...
Please... Sit down here...
Please...
Please do
Your legs are so tense...
Well I have just been running around...
Have you gotten thinner?
Umm, no I don't think so...
I know you're relaxing and all and it is a bit rude but...
I want to talk to you about something...
Shozo really isn't getting along
with Hirunandesu's
Nanchan at all...
She really doesn't like him apparently...
What the hell is this..?
Mother worries about her 44-year-old son
Really?
Why is she always so worried about me..?
You know, Tanaka Na-chan is on that program LIFE...
with Uh-chan...
I believe that's with Uh-chan...
Yes...
and since he's good friends with Uh-chan...
I was thinking maybe she should work with Uh-chan instead of Nanchan...
This is ridiculous!
So ridiculous...
I think he's fine, being on Hirunandesu...
Do you think so?
Thank you so much...
YOSHA!!
YOSHA!
Hamada-san! To End...
I will massage
between your legs!!
OW OW OW OW!!!!!
GYA-GYA-GYA-GYA-GYA!!
What the hell..?
What the hell was that..?
He's getting beaten the shit out of...
GYA-GYA-GYA-GYA-GYA!!
YOSHA!!!
What the hell is with your family?
ONE DOWN!!
Seriously...
They really are something...
Here he comes...
Great job...
They appeared...
They appeared..?
They appeared again...
They appeared again..?
Your...
Again?!
Tell them, man!
Seriously...
I'm scared of my family...
Meanwhile...
Matsumoto waits...
The oldie gets sick of waiting...
So this is how it is...
Damn, that's scary!!
Front of the locker rooms
So that's how it is in there...
Damn, that was scary...
Yagira searches the locker room
Damn, this looks scary
Yeah it is...
I've found it!!
I've found it, awesome!
Awesome!!
Slipper
AHHHHH!!!
Damn that's scary!
AAHHHH!!
AAAAHHH!!
Of course you would be shocked...
AAAAAHHHH!!!
Damn, that would've hurt
AAAHHHH!!
Someone just got...
Who was that??
That was...
Damn, that hurt!
So that's the kind of noise he makes
He's going like AAAAA-N!
I've found it!
They found a key!
Right then...
They found a second key
And run back to Matsumoto...
Matsumoto-san...
We found it
Here I go!
Oh, it fits
It fits!
It should open
Shouldn't it?
DAMN IT!
It didn't work
Matsumoto remains
in punishment
You know what...
That didn't work either
Hasn't it been enough!?
Isn't this the worst?
This is going to mess you up
Okada Ijiri
This is going to mess with you
His movements are incredible
Rapid Licking
Isn't this the WORST?
Even the footage is disgusting
It's really amazing
It's seriously been enough
It's seriously, really...
They aren't covering that with music, are they?
No, we understand
We're also doing our best
No, it's definitely much easier on your part
Why is he saying it like that?
Why does he have to say it like that?
Oh it doesn't work
Egashira
Oh no no no no
Are you kidding me?!
You're kidding!
What what what?
Why?
Egashira-san got you
Egashira-san is here!
What is it, Egashira-san?
I did it, I did it, I did it!
What what what what
This is gonna be bad!
This is bad this is bad
It's terrible
IT'S THE ANNUAL
EGA-CHAN FESTIVAAALLL!!!
HERE IT GOOOOES
Devil's Descent
Seriously the devil descended
It's the devil
I can't watch
The Devil's Nose-Licking Hell
This is really bad!
This was really painful
Wow... Unbelievable
Are you okay?
It stinks!
Did you see the annual Egashira festival?
It stinks!!
WHY DIDN'T HE DO THAT TO HIM (MATSUMOTO)?
WHY DID IT HAPPEN TO ME!?
That must be horrible
For some reason,
the devil returned
Egashira
Are you serious!?
You're kidding!
What is this? What is this?
Yuuya-kun!!
Yagira is Targeted
Get away get away get away!!
Watch out!
Run quick!
Ega-chan is getting tired...
He tripped
He got him
This is harsh...
Ah he caught him
It's here
This is the worst
It's truly the worst
He's seriously the devil
It's the festival
He's doing it
His first variety debut is...
This is a terrible first variety experience
Oh, it's time for work
How was it?
Yagira-kun
Yuuya, this is what Gaki is like
Once it dries, it's going to smell really bad
Are you crying?
He's crying
Oh man he's crying
A Taste of Hell
Variety       33 years
Variety       new
It would make you cry
Were you scared?
If that kind of thing happened to you...
Wow
60 minutes since
the start of the training
Onis Increase
The onis will increase
Oh something's coming
Queen of Ice
What?
Queen of Ginza
Queen of Ice
Ginza...
It's Queen of Ice
If it was Queen of Ginza, it'd be a good thing
What...
Is it related to ice skating?
So you mean there's something past this?
This is a first
Covered it so we wouldn't go in
What?
Seriously...
Amazing
What should I do?
Ando Miki
Queen of Ice
Wow
Whoa
I didn't know about this
In such a slippery place
Is this part of a pattern of rewards?
She's just circling around him
Amazing
Oh?
No, this isn't a reward
That fan doesn't suit her
Unexpected Hit
I bet that really hurt
He couldn't escape, so
That was pretty powerful
That hurt
She was laughing a lot
She's an S (sadist)
She was laughing?
Laughing a lot
She was peeking through the eye area
Ice Queen is
Highly Visible
Seriously?
So that's what you meant
That's incredible
Damn... Is there still more?
Damn it
There's too much space
Please let this be over
Outline
Definitely not
You've got to be kidding
He's been targeted
You can't run away
This is scary
This thing... wow
Wait a minute
This is terrifying
What the hell?
You can't do this
Outline
They're gonna use that shovel to get you
What the hell?
Isn't the bottom going to go through the machine?
You're full of lies
You're kidding!
Since it's "outline"
Shovel will outline the two of them
No way!
This isn't right!
Don't say things like that!
Wait, what's going to happen?
We don't really know, but
Don't raise your face!!
It's okay if it's lowered?
So I can't raise my head?
Do NOT raise your face
I'm safe if my face is lowered?
If it gets really bad, I'll raise my hand
We can't help you though
No, it's dangerous if he does that
Don't raise your hand, don't move!
Scary scary scary
This is so wrong!
Don't raise your head!
Wooww this is really scary
Wow wow wow
Look! This
terrified face!
Of course you'd be scared
Look! This
hideous face!
AAAAHH!!
AAAAAAAHHHH!!!
You barely made it
It was really close
Oh my God
Oh my God...
Bad bad this is bad
That explosion was unnecessary
If they got this wrong..
Thank you
Is this something you do to someone who's never properly taken part in variety before?
Like you said before, I think it requires a lot of guts
I think it takes too much guts
This is so unusual
You did it
He probably hates Gaki now
Oh, he's here
This is about that real key you're looking for
I thought about it but I had a spare the whole time
Every year...
With this, let's go rescue Matsumoto
At last, they get the real key in their hands,
Training is Over
and their training is over
What kind of training is this?
7 hours 30 minutes since starting
It's been 7 hours and 30 minutes since the start of their duty
The five men return to detective's office
The five men who will rest soon
return to the detective's office
Wow, we're back
Ahh we're back
Wow "all of the drawers' contents have been reset"
They've been reset!
Seriously?
They don't need to reset it
Alright let's go!!
The drawers'...
contents
It doesn't matter where we start
Let's start with mine?
So opposite direction
Go ahead
First up is Endo
"All of the drawers' contents have been reset", here we go
Envelope with Puzzle
A secret?
I don't know, let me check
Isn't it another secret?
Wait, something's in there?
Wait wait wait but
the previous
I saw something familiar in there
one was about my secrets
Look,
it's a Wii
Nintendo "Wii U" and Puzzle Game
Wow, what is this?
Should we read it?
Why the hell!?
Work together to clear one stage: WHAAAT?
Challenge Letter from Kaijin Nijuu Mensou
Work together to clear one stage
First me, then Hamada-san,
Tanaka, Hosei-san, then Matsumoto-san
It's getting more and more-
Wait a minute though
For me and Hosei, this can get stressful, right?
That's true.
These 3 are just
crazy ba at video games.
Crazy ba?
Crazy ba.
Don't you say crazy ba?
It's a dialect.
Crazy ba.
Crazy bad, sure.
I don't know "crazy ba."
Aaah!!
Gently, ok?
It's an expression from the rural area my mom's from.
Challenge Sent from Kaijin Nijiuu Mensou
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
Work as a team and clear 1 stage
The order of challengers is as seen here.
A line-up where the experienced gamers, Hosei and Matsumoto, are reserved for the end.
And
the game that the five will play is...
Will it connect from here?
It's Mario.
Challenge Sent from Kaijin Nijiuu Mensou
Clear a course from "Super Mario Maker"
Oh, it's Mario.
Oh, so we just have to clear one stage, so...
You can do this.
Nice.
You can totally do this.
You're good.
You can go slowly, Endo.
Is it my turn?
Yeah, Endo is awful.
Stop
Stop.
It's my turn.
Nice pause.
Okay, then...
We do this until we clear it?
Yes, so, now,
Hamada, clear this stage.
It's in the middle, um... I've done ku...
It's because you repeated it.
Your words are messed up.
You don't need to repeat it.
It's to clear 1 stage with everyone.
Since you failed in the middle of it, I go next, and then...
Yeah, you're right.
Yes please, Hamada.
Challenge Sent from Kaijin Nijiuu Mensou
Clear a course from "Super Mario Maker"
Kill yourself!
Have you ever stopped to think about what it's like for Mario!?
You, how was I supposed to know that you stopped it there?
All right already.
Didn't you see it? The mushroom moving towards you.
I didn't see it.
I thought I was all the way on the side.
Why would Mario just stand still there?
You're up, Tanaka. Hurry up.
This... Yamazaki and I are gonna have to do this.
It's just 1 stage. That's all.
Just 1 stage. Have you played this, Tanaka?
Forget 1 stage.
Nothing has even started yet!!
Challenge Sent from Kaijin Nijiuu Mensou
Clear a course from "Super Mario Maker"
You're just in the garden area, here.
Avoid them.
Why are you running away?
You can just bypass it.
The turtle, the turtle!
Right, right.
You don't need to run away.  That won't come back at you.
What if you hit it?
The question mark.
Wait, wait.
Whoa. You get bigger.
What was I supposed to do here?
Go up here. Jump, jump.
If you don't do it while you're right up against it...
Watch out there, the valley.
Don't go backwards.
Why were you looking at the pipe?
I don't know if I can do this.
You can.
Go all out and you can do it.
Tanaka's smiling a little bit.
What about the coin, Tanaka?
You can't get that, right?
Don't need it.
Forget the coins.
The squid!
There's a squid.
You can make it.
Were there squids in this?
Why are you going back?
No, then, what am I supposed to do?
Forward, go forward.
Go this way.
Go under the squid.
Were there squids in this, back then?
I don't think there were
squids this early on.
This might've been made just for this.
It's "Super Mario Maker",
so it's a game that has all the previous things in it.
It came out recently.
It's one of those where you create a course, right?
Isn't that going to be really hard?
Challenge Sent from Kaijin Nijiuu Mensou
Clear a course from "Super Mario Maker"
Watch out!
Why do you look at the pipe?
Watch out for the squi-squids.
Watch out for them.
I got it.
Good, nice.
Nice.
Where are you supposed to go?
Can't do anything about that now.  Wow, this is tough.
What is this?
This is really tough.
Whoa.
Hold on, wait.
This is quite brutal.
We're gonna need Hosei and Matsumoto to do this.
There was nothing like this.
Hold on, no, no...
But, I mean,
If we don't clear this, something bad's going to happen.
This means this is going to be a really hard stage.
If you get over there,
right?  Then, there's that pole and it goes "beep."
Yeah, like a "beep."
Challenge Sent from Kaijin Nijiuu Mensou
Clear a course from "Super Mario Maker"
It's back to here.
What!?
He hit it from the other side of the Goomba.
What are you doing?
No, no...
Aren't the controls kinda hard?
This is
totally impossible.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, let me do it for real.
This distance is no good, too.
That's true.
It's far away.
Try it in front, Endo.
In front?
A fresh start: they move in front of the screen.  However...
And so, as if to get a fresh start, they move to in front of the screen and restart.
However...
Challenge Sent from Kaijin Nijiuu Mensou
Clear a course from "Super Mario Maker"
Come on, let's go. You don't need to look at the pipe.
Endo quickly strikes out
Endo quickly strikes out.
Challenge Sent from Kaijin Nijiuu Mensou
Clear a course from "Super Mario Maker"
Next, Hamada.
You're kidding me.
And then, Tanaka.
Why do you go back?
Watch out!
What are you doing?
You're too bad at this.
Beginner-level failures one after another
Basic-level failures one after another.
Hope rests on experienced gamer, Hosei
Will there be a comeback? Hope rests on the experienced gamer, Hosei.
Challenge Sent from Kaijin Nijiuu Mensou
Clear a course from "Super Mario Maker"
This part is all easy.
Right, you should just go up, quickly.
I see.
Can you break those blocks?
Nice.
Nice, nice.
That was nice.
There are, like, those question marks. Whoa.
A squid came out! What?
You fell so far!
You nose-dived really far.
Come on.
I feel sorry for Mario.
Mario was big and he just...
What was that..?
I've never seen a stage like that.
Do you wanna take a break here for now?
Let's stop for a bit.
Cool down for a bit.
The game is put on hold. To the desk drawers.
Yes.
Do something different first.
Yes. Do these in order.
Come back to these now.
Let's cool down.
Yes.
Then...
Oh, I have nothing.
What?
What... What is this?
There's no way there's nothing.
It's big.
What is this?
It's duralumin.
This is scary.
A mysterious duralumin case.
Is it heavy?
Well, it's not that heavy.
The electric shock that startles you is awful.
I'm gonna open it.
They're eyeglasses.
Eyeglasses.
What's this?
Could you try them on
just once?
These are amazing.
Amazing.
Super realistic novelty eyeglasses
Wow, amazing.
These are crazy.
He hasn't changed that much, but...
These are eyeglasses for Hamada, right?
No way.
If you...
wore those and went home,
that would freak out everyone.
They're really funny.
Amazing.
These are amazing.
Such a sketchy face.
The color of the skin is the same.
Right, it's the color of Hamada's skin.
They actually matched the colors.
You don't know that.  Someone try them on.
5 kinds of novelty eyeglasses
Endo, try one.
I don't think it's for us.
Try them on.
I don't think it'll match.
Whoa, that's scary.
Endo makes that face sometimes.
It's Endo.
The difference is so subtle.
It's not that different?
It's so subtle, I'm telling you.
There's no difference.
My face is like this sometimes?
Yeah, like that.
Ow, man, my leg.
That's really subtle.
It's really subtle.
Will it work for everyone?
Try one of them, Hosei.
Hello.
This is actually like Yama.
That's amazing.
It's not weird to see him with a face like that.
Amazing.
There are times when Hosei's face is like that.
Right?
It matches you.
It's funnier when it's subtler.
Is each one matched for a specific person?
It totally matched you.
Tanaka, you haven't put one on yet.
I'm kinda scared of this one.
Hello.
It's Tanaka.
It doesn't feel out of place at all.
Tanaka, those aren't funny at all.
That's the worst outcome.
We had a good flow of laughs going one after another, right?
You're right, everyone was laughing so much, yeah.
Yeah, everyone was laughing.
Even though you guys laughed that much for me
Maybe these are each of our eyes
"Oh, it's Tanaka" and that's it
Wait, are you serious?
No no no, it's not even...
That's definitely Tanaka
It didn't change at all
There's a mirror here, a mirror
When Tanaka put them on...
Why do only Tanaka's not look any different at all?
This isn't any different
Tanaka, look this way
Are you serious?
That's Tanaka
That is Tanaka
Try this
Pardon me
If it's this one, I think it'd be different
Yes
You think so?
Greetings
Good morning
This right here...
So scary
This one
This one's the one
This is just...
So amazing...
This is the very bad Tanaka
Very bad
Is it?
That's our Tanaka
"Tanaka's such a bad guy!" is what people would say
Really?
Oh, so it's this one
I'm this one
This one is Hamada-san's
Oh so that's why there's five of them
That's mine?
This is Hamada-san's
They may each be ours respectively
Each of ours
Just perhaps!
Matching
Since there's five of them
They'd probably all suit Hamada pretty well
Here, Matsumoto-san's
Hamada-san would probably look the best by a mile
This one... I don't know whose
This is the best selection, I believe
Best for the each of us
You serious?
See, Endo's doesn't look very different
It really doesn't
This is the best
This is the best selection
Hello
This is...
Tanaka's...
That's no good
Tanaka's is too funny
This is pretty amazing
This is amazing
Tanaka's is just...
Tanaka, really though, you look like a really bad dude
If you go home like that,
"This year's 'No Laughing' must've been really stressful" is what they'll think
It'd be like...
You're right
"What happened at this year's gathering?"
Amazing
They'd ask, "Did something happen?"
This is amazing, seriously
Take that home with you
Are you serious?
What's going on..?
They'll think that you were deceived
Because you're bringing home that negative feeling from work
Tanaka, that's a good one for you
But... Oh, so it's this kind of pattern
You should take this with you
Oh, it's that powerful?
Yeah, because...
When you're scolding your kid
Like, "Come over here for a moment"
Yeah, when you scold your kid or something
At those moments when you're like, "Knock it off!"
When you tell them to stop it and they do it anyway
I heard from your mother
What do you think you're doing?
Is this okay?
This is definitely good
They'll definitely start crying
It's so good
Tanaka, that's really good
That is amazing
But I'm so jealous of Hamada-san!
So good
Well, yeah
Yes, this is a very fun item
Right because all of them were Hamada-san's
Alright then, Matsumoto-san
Nothing
Something's there
There's something
A DVD for Matsumoto-san?
No...
No, it's paper
It's a paper envelope
Mysterious Envelope
Again, it's...
That's probably it
Nothing else
A pattern of one item
One-item pattern
Then I'm going to take a look
I wonder what it is
Is it the Science Shock?
It looks like it's a command
Really?
Is it big?
Isn't it...
I wonder if this follows the pattern where only Matsumoto-san can look at it
10 Minute Joint Liability Card
10 minute
Joint Liability Card
Is it so difficult that you have to read it that carefully?
Your understanding will suffer...
Yes, that's right
It's really um... Yeah
Are we not allowed to look at it?
Should be okay for you guys to look, shouldn't it?
10 Minute Joint Liability Card
Explanation of the Rules
The item that came from Matsumoto's drawer
is the 10 Minute Joint Liability Card
Let us explain the rules
10 Minute Joint Liability Card Rules
Matsumoto
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Tanaka
Card User
If this card is used
If any of the members except Matsumoto
LOL
Even if one person laughs
Punishment
As part of a joint liability, all four of them will receive punishment
For example, let's say Matsumoto-san uses this...
If Hamada-san laughs by himself, we also get the punishment
So therefore, none of us should laugh. However,
If Matsumoto himself laughs,
Supplemental Rule
he receives a punishment, as usual
Oh, I see
So I'm just the stand-alone
Yes, you're the stand-alone
Yes, but this...
In terms of probability, this isn't good
Then this card, I'll
use this when I please for the 10-minute duration
A certain man will experience hell
The use of the card causes
Later on, when the card is triggered
A certain man
will experience hell
4:30 PM
Detective Duties: 8 hours and 30 minutes
Right when everyone feels anxious about when that card will be used
Maybe I should use it
10 Minute
10 Minute Joint Liability Card
Joint Liability Card
So no matter who laughs, all of you get... Right?
Maybe right around now is the time to use it...
Huh?
Alright now
A new mission just came in
Truth is, from now, we're going to investigate a certain facility, but
Within the group, only the most superior person
Special Mission
Superior Detective Alone Will Do an Infiltration Investigation
may enter
So...
Only one person...?
Only one person
Even if you say "superior", I think everyone...
Hosei, that means you!!
You have to prepare, so could you come over here?
Wait a minute please
Why is it me?
You're the most superior one, so you're going to the next mission
I am?
Yep
What kind of investigation is it?
Yes, that's right
Whatever, just come. Let's go
No, I can't
It's okay, Hosei
Let's go
Good luck...
Hurry up, let's go
I'm only getting a bad feeling about this
Well, it's not like...
What is...
He's got a point there
Getting called out alone
What the hell
Didn't he just laugh?
He definitely did
Yes, he did laugh just then
Tanaka, you laughed too
No no, I should be safe
Tanaka laughed too
No, I'm safe, but Hosei-san laughed just then...
There's no way he'll be like, "I'm glad I went!"
Yes, that's absolutely right
In the past...
Just what the hell?
The Superior Detective's Infiltration Investigation Entails...
What is it that makes me "superior"?
The superior detective Hosei's infiltration investigation entails...
What is this?
Once you change, go back to the room
On the other hand, right at this moment
The 4 of them are resuming their game
In the room, they are resuming their game
21st Attempt
Clear one course on "Super Mario Maker"
Kaijin Nijuu Mensou's Written Challenge
Tanaka Naoki
Aghhh
Get up there
Right now, you can go
Ahh!
Good good
Wait a minute... Okay okay
Go now
JUMP!!
If you get to the next part...
Not that way, just keep going down, oh look at what you did
Land... Jump!
There's land down there, land
Whoa, looking good
Surprisingly, the newbie Tanaka establishes a new record
This part is what scares me
Just ignore them, ignore
Get up, get up!
There's still more to it
That looked like the end
What are you supposed to do here?
Oh man!!
Fire!!
Now...
Ah, you should've went
Where... What is the timing?
Now!
Oh, I'm sorry
One more time, one more time...
Now!!
Oh, that thing!
Get on that thing and go up!
What's this? Ah!!
That's dangerous! Watch out, they're coming!
Jump, big jump!
Just like that
The bullets are there!
Big jump!
Yes yes... The bullet!
JUMP!!
What do I do?!
Over there, you go...
Bullet, bullet, BULLET!!
Go that way, that way!!
You can jump on the bullet too, whichever
Go down
Bullet!!
You can jump on the bullet too
Why don't you go down there?
Hold on, down there?
Down... Below there
Hurry and get it...
What are you doing?!
That was so important
My bad
You were so close
I think I might've laughed
Yes, I made it pretty far
No, but really, I can see what you have to do now
How did everyone get so good?
Just, like, give me a little break...
Yeah well, just now
I think I got too fired up
Alright then you're up, Hamada
Please, I think that was the homestretch
So, just like how he did before
22nd Attempt
Clear one course on "Super Mario Maker"
Hamada Masatoshi
Kaijin Nijuu Mensou's Written Challenge
I wonder why...
You didn't do anything!!
You didn't do anything at all!!
Never play this again
You're kidding, right?
Never touch the damn game again!!
For reals, never play this again, damnit
Is it still gonna take a while?
But gradually...
But I think we made it through a lot of it, I think
Oh, yes, I agree
About 80% of it?
We should've got there...
I definitely got 80% of it
Infiltration Investigation as Kekko Kamen
Notes: Kekko Kamen was originally a manga serialized in Shonen Jump in 1974. This hero is actually a girl who wears nothing but a mask, gloves, and boots and fights the teachers at her school who torture students for sexual pleasure
He's laughing
They made you look horrible
Why do you look like you're crying?
That's just cruel
If you don't mind me asking, what happened to you?
What happened to me? This happened to me
I was told that I'm the superior one so go in this room
You're superior so please get changed
We are detectives so...
I don't get it either, you know
I don't understand the concept at all
Aren't you cold?
I feel very cold
If you laugh now, it's going to be a terrible situation for you
Yeah, definitely
How does your backside look?
Just completely naked
But this time
Even if you laugh, no one will know
If you wear
those glasses from earlier,
you'll be hidden
I guess you're right
Wait... What glasses?
Won't it be bad if you talk with them?
Hiding his eyes with funny glasses
It'll be fine if I don't say anything!
But is it really alright to be hide both his eyes and mouth?
I think it'll be great if he can hide his mouth and his eyes
SCARY!!
Damn that's scary!
Scary!
This is way too scary!
BAD!
This is bad!
That's so scary!
Alright quit it for a bit, Hosei!
Let's stop this, Hosei!
What was that?
Let's stop that!
Let's stop with that!
Well... Honestly....
What if we make him a different person?
Yeah, let's change him
The compatibility just isn't there
This character is no good!
This is
honestly so scary
But one of these has to match
His pervert level
really has increased
You've got that right
Japan is finished
Enough, Yamazaki!
There's no reason for this
Endo is laughing again
Damn this pisses me off!
Please stop it, Hosei!
Please stop it!
I couldn't handle it anymore
What the hell is the deal with
that figure?
This is no good!
We're supposed to be
detectives
Isn't this guy a little hopeless?
Yeah just a bit
Shit, this is bad!
ALRIGHT!!
This is terrible!
I'm going to use my 10-minute Joint Liability card!
This is bad!
Room Announcer
Please wait a second!
For the next 10 minutes, the Joint Liability Card will be active
For the 10 minutes you will all have Joint Liability
Wait a sec!
From now on, if any of us laugh...
Wait wait wait! It's fine!
From now on, whenever Hamada, Hosei, Endo, or
Joint Liability Rule
Tanaka laugh, all 4 of them are punished
Why are you trying to make me laugh!?
It's really not that funny
It'll be fine!
This one laughs all the time though!
Honestly, it wasn't
that funny
Please just wait a second!
Won't the glasses be really bad?
It'll be fine!
W-Wait...
He's already laughing like it's nothing!
WHY!?
W-WAIT A SECOND!
So this is what it does!!
I'M NOT LAUGHING!
NO ONE WAS LAUGHING!
W-WAIT!
AHHHHHHH!!
AHHHHH!!
I can't do this!
I can't deal with this!
Stop it!
If you yell it that loud!
We can't handle it if you yell!
PLEASE JUST TRY TO HOLD THROUGH!
AHHH!!
AHHHH!!
AHHHHHH!!
T-This is terrible!
My ass is gonna be destroyed!!
If you keep yelling,
we won't be able to hold it in!
My ass...
AHHH!!
It must hurt!
That joint liability card is amazing
I can't do this!
This is just evil!
Give me a break...
Honestly,
my ass is gonna be destroyed!
Don't look anymore!
Let's just all calm down
with your violin!
Enough!
Make sure you don't look!
Wait a second!
This is bad!
Seriously!
impossible!
This is
This is seriously impossible!
This is impossible!
AAHHH!!
This is...
This is terrible!
This is bad!
It's hell...
Hell!
This is honestly impossible!
Why?
My ass is seriously....
Well, I don't know but it hasn't been 10 minutes yet!
It'd be a waste...
Wait a sec!
Rather than that one use this one!
Let's all calm down now!
This is the time to play your violin!
I just want to see you play it!
You'd better not laugh!
If you guys laugh,
I'll be really pissed!
Got it!
Promise me!
I promise!
What the hell is this?
It's no good
Wait, really!?
Stop it already!
Stop!
AHHHH!!
I can't do this! I can't do this anymore!
This is impossible!
He keeps yelling
When he yells, I can't hold it in anymore!
Ouch!
It would be nice if we could put this to rest
Pufufuu
WHO LAUGHED!?
It was Endo!
WHY THE HELL DID YOU LAUGH!?
AHHH
HAHAHA
Wait!
This is really bad!
I'm honestly sorry!
His ass is really
not that well liked!
Endo, you have to hold it together!
I'm honestly sorry!
Speaking of that, I don't think you're doing too well
Attention
It's been quite a while...
Has 10 minutes passed yet?
How much time is left?
WHO LAUGHED!?
It was Tanaka!
It was because of this!
WHY WERE YOU LAUGHING!?
Because he was wearing the glasses
How many minutes are left?
I'm sorry!
Sorry!
AHHHHH
HAHAHA
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Hosei!
I'm sorry too!
Enough! This is honestly impossible!
I'm sorry!
Sorry!
I don't need the 10 minutes anymore!
So you can stop it now!
Can you tell me how many minutes are left?
Wait a second....
How many minutes..?
This was pretty tough huh?
Who laughed?
No!
Who was it?
IT WAS MATSUMOTO!?
W-Wait a second!
AHHHH!!
Wait! This is honestly impossible!
This is honestly impossible!
Wait!
People from Nippon TV
Wait...
This is honestly impossible!
Don't pull it!
Definitely don't pull it!
This is bad
This is bad!
Wait a second!
So pitiful!
This is...
Ahhh...
Uehh....
That face.
That damn face!
I think you should probably cool your ass off
This is impossible...
Alright!
That's not what I had in mind...
What are you doing to the fridge?
Just by
sticking your ass to the fridge
won't cool it off
My ass..
Put some cold water on this
Wait... Seriously...
Just wait a second!
Has your 10 minutes been up yet?
Has it been up yet, huh?
It doesn't feel like it has
I'm being serious
Lie down with your face on the ground
Alright!
Let me move your cloak first
AHHH!!
It's a little cold but...
No more laughing, alright?
We've already climbed over the difficult part
Is there no ice in there?
Ice...
I can use this...
The fridge's shelf is cold
This is cold... Hosei, I'm gonna put it on
Here we go!
Ah, it hurts!
It's sticking on me a bit!
It hurts!
It stuck on it, huh?
AH IT HURTS~~!!
Room Announcer
There are 5 seconds left for the 10-minute Joint Liability Card
Finally!
It's ending
There are 4 seconds left for the 10-minute Joint Liability Card
It's over!
It's ending, it's ending
There are 3 seconds left for the 10-minute Joint Liability Card
It's over!
There are 2 seconds left for the 10-minute Joint Liability Card
It's ending
There are 1 seconds left for the 10-minute Joint Liability Card
There are 0 seconds left for the 10-minute Joint Liability Card
End
Ah good
You don't need this?
It's painful, painful
It hurts?
It's sticking to my skin
It's scary to excel
Because he was excellent, he was forced to dress like that...
The stake which sticks out gets hammered in was what happened
[note: a Japanese proverb; someone who sticks out excessively will get brought back into line]
Detective work 9th hour
It's 5 in the evening, and Hosei's hellish infiltration investigation has ended
Only the game is left
Tanaka shows remarkable progress while struggling with the game
I was able to get to a good place
35th try
Challenge from Kaijin Nijuu Mensou
Clear 1 course in "Super Mario Maker"
Tanaka Naoki
This is really long
You went far in the previous round
You awakened
Hosei-san
That was an amazing expression
Yeah, Tanaka's...
Look look look
Tanaka's really awakened.
Almost...
Eh, seriously?
Awesome
35th try
Challenge from Kaijin Nijuu Mensou
Clear 1 course in "Super Mario Maker"
Tanaka Naoki
Oh! It's going well
Ah! Hammers!
Here.
The problem is this point
What happens after entering?
Need to enter
There are probably Koopas
Okay, jump
Go go go
Yes, yes, yes
There's fire coming
Tragedy of clearing the game himself and getting a Thai Kick
I was quite surprised by this
This is...
Tanaka here, come here
Moreover, Tanaka...
I got goosebumps!!
Even though he cleared it himself...
Even though he worked that hard on it
This is the 3rd kick
This is really...
This is super ridiculous
I don't know what to say to Tanaka about this...
This is too sad, this ending
Really sad
Detective work 10th hour
It is 6pm and a murder has occurred in the Agency!
In order to study how to infer a criminal, they head to the scene of the crime
Within the Agency, a murder has happened!!
Shouldn't that be handed over to the police already?
Over here
We're going to investigate the scene now
Investigate the scene...
Party Room
This is a murder case
Tatsumi Takuro
Police Detective
Can you guys line up here?
Wakabayashi Go
Hamada, Hosei...
Everyone, work hard and do some inference
Inference...
Wakabayashi-san
Were there fingerprints?
Fingerprints were hard to find
Azuma Chizuru
Victim's wife
Ma'am!
Ma'am, please calm down
It was amazing
Overdoing it
Ma'am, calm down...
Who is this person?
The victim's wife, Chizuru-san
Furuhata Ninzaburo enters the scene on a bicycle
[note: "Furuhata Ninzaburo" is a police detective drama which aired periodically from '94 to '06]
You are... Furuhata-san?
Furuhata Ninzaburo
Rola
Tatsumi-kun,
could you help me put this bicycle
away somewhere?
Right.
Super
lousy
Lousy
This is bad...
This is no good
Impression not at all complete
This is...
We need to get psyched
I will explain the situation here
Receives a report from police detective Tatsumi
Victim is male, in his 50s. Time of death is 15:10.
The perp
used a knife to stab the victim in the abdomen...
As a dying message,
the victim left the letter "W"
At the scene,
one of the victim's leather gloves
came off and...
The serious acting hits Furuhata's sense of humour
Your laughter made us laugh!
This is a terrible incident...
At the scene,there's a leather glove
That lea...
That leather glove has blood on it?
fuhehehe
That's no good
That leather gl... text
That leather glove has blood on it
Hahahahaha
If you're doing an impression,
do it properly
With this, the case has been solved.
Huh?
Solved?
The perp has made 1 huge mistake.
Here at the scene, one big clue left behind
pointed to evidence of the perp's guilt
The theme of the keywords are a single leather glove and "M"
hehe... a bloody "W"left behind
This was Furuhata Ninzaburo
[note: Rola was doing a parody impression of Furuhata's reasoning]
No idea what you're talking about
You only did a self-introduction
So it's not solved yet, right?
These rookie detectives... Their faces have turned pale.
Everyone's changed
I heard Furuhata-san is good at doing impressions...
Furuhata's hidden talent
Good at doing impressions
So, does anyone have any requests?
How about Bruce Lee?
Bruce Lee impression
Ah I can do it!!
Acho--
I might not be able to do it...
If you can't do it, then don't do it...
She couldn't do it
You said you "could do it"
Because you said you could do it...
Everyone, ensure that this type of thing won't happen to you,
so please live well
[note: Rola is using a casual type of speech here]
Using such a tone to speak to us?
As expected of Furuhata-san
Please hurry and find the culprit
Hurry!
Calm down, madam
He's touching her a lot
Yeah
It's troubling to us if you just come in like that
Who are you ?
Famous detective Poirot
I'm Nishioka "Poirot" Tokuma
Nishioka Tokuma
[note: Poirot is a detective character in Agatha Christie's Poirot book series]
Excuse me
Wait, wait, what are you touching?
Nishioka starts his inference
The stab wound in the back,
a knife which has been wiped clean of fingerprints,
and a dying message, the letter "W"
A single glove
What's so funny?
The problem is this
The bits of skin left behind in the victim's nails
Inferring the culprit important point #1
Skin left behind in the nails of the victim
The perp's neck will
definitely have scratch wounds left behind
Hmm... I see.
Someone!
Send this skin to forensics!!
No, no, no need for that
I have always have had a good nose
This room has something of a certain smell
That smell is this
Ointment
Inferring the culprit important point #2
Smell of ointment wafting around the scene
I'm certain the perp used this ointment
to dress his wounds
Isn't that so, Wakabayashi-san?
The dying message, "W",
is from Wakabayashi's "W"
What nonsense are you talking about?
Then,
your throat, show it to everyone
Wakabayashi-san...
Definite proof that he is the culprit
You are...?
I married when I was young
I only focused on my job as police detective so
I did not pay attention to my family
She escaped
Years later, I
met a lady who looked like my wife
That lady was you
Me?
Then,
your husband became an obstacle so I killed him
It's all over
With this, I will end everything
Azuma-san...
Let us meet in heaven
Come, now sleep. Lay down
saa nemuri nasai tsukarekitta
*Note: The song is (Madonna-tachi no Lullaby) Lullaby of the Virgin Mary, released by Iwasaki Hiromi in 1982
karada wo nagedashite
your tired body.
Let my lips gently
aoi sono mabuta wo
kuchibiru de sotto fusagimashou
seal your pale eyelids.
Ah, if it's possible,
ah dekirunonara
She dodged really well
She dodges the knife by a hair's breadth
I would want to be reincarnated as your mother
umarekawari anata no haha ni natte
She dodged this too
What is he (Nishioka) doing?
That guy's irrelevant!!
From the start, he's irrelevant
Why is he just circling around so much?
How many times are you going to dodge?
She really can dodge
She keeps getting away from him
Maybe he'll get her next time
Nope, she dodged it
She can really dodge!
She's just barely dodging these hits
What is he (Nishioka) doing?
Ahh, it's dangerous
Ahh be careful
That's dangerous
Oh, this is bad
It's impossible
This time he'll definitely get her
Ahh he's gonna get her
She dodged it
She dodged again!
He can't get her at all!
He keeps missing
Wow
What is Tokuma
even doing!?
What could he be doing?
Oh she's a goner
Ahh her face!
She got the knife!
Instead...
The knife is stabbed into Wakabayashi's stomach...
No no no
Of course we're out...
That's fine, but...
Please watch for us
She was really dodging
11th hour of detective duty
Good news for the 5 men who have been working hard since morning...
What is it?
I'm sure you guys are getting tired.
Um,
you guys really need a breather
Seriously!
You need a breather, so
let's go see something nice
Something nice?
We're watching something?
Is it really something nice?
Auditorium
He calls it a breather, but,
if it makes us laugh, it's really gonna wear me out
Okay, we enter through here
What!?
Whoa?
Downtown Deluxe Set
What is this?
It's the Downtown Deluxe set
It's exactly the same
It's just like Deluxe
Wait, what is this really?
Are we supposed to watch?
This means that somebody will replace Downtown?
We're supposed to watch?
You're kidding...
This is a first, isn't it?
Amazing
How refreshing
Who's gonna do it?
I'm getting a weird feeling
The sound is the same... what is this!?
Be quiet!
Quiet!
Matsumoto-san!
No!!
Is this even allowed?
What?
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Well, Matsumoto-san,
in the blink of an eye,
a year has passed
I agree
No no no... Anyway, Hamada is-
What kind of year was it?
You have a necktie just like that
It was bad
Your voice is so small, Matsumoto-san
What are you gonna do next year?
Oh next year, well
I'm gonna take a bath,
take a bath,
eat some food,
and do some laundry.
Yes, that's right!
ALRIGHT, let's get on with it
Not funny at all, Downtown-san
They are not funny at all, Downtown-san
Wait a minute
Wait wait I'm exhausted
This isn't funny at all
Wow, this-
What part of this is a breather?
I don't understand
We have to do our best
This is tough
Welcome tonight's guest!
Who?
Tonight's guests
Wow, amazing
Natsuki Yoko
Mikihisa Azuma
Kaiya
Tomonori
Jinnai
Umemiya
Tatsuo
Demon Kakka
Kikuchi Ami
What is this?
Animal
Hamaguchi
No no no
This is incredible
What the hell is this?
What are they trying to do?
This is as good as the original Deluxe
So, today, we have many luxurious guests
So, let's get into it
He's proceeding very well
Firstly,
Star
peaking rankings!
Star peaking rankings!
Oh we do that
We have that
*Matsumoto doesn't speak at all*
Yes, Matsumoto-san doesn't
Jinnai,
So quiet
I'm not speaking at all
Not a word
He doesn't say anything
Maybe from here he will
Star peaking rankings!
I changed a lot...
I, who won't even kill flies...
Umemiya
Tatsuo
So, let's move on
You changed a lot
I, who won't even kill a fly...
2nd is
Demon
Kakka
Devil dash at the school festival!
Frantic!
Demon Kakka
Frantic! Devil Dash at the school festival!
1st place is
A prescription from his mother!
A puzzle!
Tomonori
Jinnai
Jinnai, puzzle!
A prescription from his mother!
So, let's continue
1st place Tomonori Jinnai Puzzle! Prescription from his mother!
so he told Twitter
Recently, he's been unable to sleep,
Lately, you've been busy, and you said on
Twitter that you can't sleep well
Yes, that's right
and when you did,
your mother became very concerned
His mother, who was concerned,
sent him some medicine,
and sent you some medicine
Yes, correct
but that medicine was
but that medicine is
one meant to increase your appetite
meant to increase appetite
Yes that's correct
Because lately I've been unable to sleep-
1st place Tomonori Jinnai Puzzle! Prescrption from his mother!
but that medicine is
meant to increase appetite
Unfortunately your time is up!!
No no please let me talk
Hamada-san, please let me speak
We just started!
All he (Matsumoto) does is laugh
Please let me speak!
That old man only laughs
It makes me mad
A puzzle! A prescription for his mother!
First place
Tomonori Jinnai
Jinnai, why,
even though you have a wife,
your mother had to- did- needed to watch over you
Oh, Matsumoto-san
No, Matsumoto-san
I got divorced
Whaaaat?
You already knew that!
This is bad!!
This is hard
This is very bad
How many times are you gonna say that!?
Sorry
My bad
I knew that
By the way, Animal-san is-
Yes?
"I knew that"?
My secret to good health is
a collaboration between strength and will.
Until 200 years...
I can live to be 200 years old
Are you serious?
First up,
recently,
I invented this
What is it?
Here goes
I don't believe it
Are you serious?
Yes
Let's move on!
This is like a very broken Matsumoto
His wig is-
His wig!
His face is getting red
The next segment is...
Celebrity World!
Let me speak!!
This time, let me ask!!
This time let me ask, let me speak!
Come on!!
First up is this person!
Mikihisa Azuma's
Question!!
Who is Mikihisa's question for?
Kikuchi Ami
Let me ask
For Kikuchi Ami!
Oh? Me?
How can I get on better terms with Hamada-san?
Kikuchi Ami
Mikihisa Azuma
How can I get on better terms with Hamada-san?
Yes, that's right. I've been part of the celebrity world for a while,
and I've been working with Hamada-san for over 10 years,
How do I get on better terms with Hamada-san?
Kikuchi Ami
Mikihisa Azuma
Question!
That's right
but no matter what, I still get nervous around him
Yes that's right,
but Ami-chan is on pretty good terms with him,
Yes that's correct
even though she's so young
Oh, yes
Not technique, but
I wanted to get her advice
Not a technique...
When speaking to Hamada-san, I get very nervous
But I befriended him naturally
Like on the last show, there were many female celebrities,
but Hamada-san came up to me
and said, "it's okay to come up front!"
Really?
Seriously! He said that
to me!
Don't mess around!
It's true!
I don't know
the right way to watch
So, let's move on to the next segment!
Don't scare me
Celebrities' Personal Style!
Yes!
Let's see the celebrities' personal styles!
4th place is Jinnai!
Tomonori Jinnai
Yes!
His usual waiting room wardrobe
Usual Waiting Room Wardrobe\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nUsual Waiting Room Wardrobe\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nUsual Waiting Room Wardrobe
Yes
costs around
46,852 yen (~$500 US)!
Personal Style
Tomonori Jinnai's
Usual Waiting Room Wardrobe
It looks something like this
It looks similar to Endo's style
and usually I add glasses
Interesting!
Yes, but I wear this often!
So cool!
Is that so?
Nice nice!
The sneakers!
The heart sneakers are cute, right?
Limited Edition Valentino Sneakers that he received as a gift
Very nice!
Wow!!
Look look look!
I got these from a friend
Limited Edition Valentino Sneakers
How cute!
So youthful!
You think?
Fashionable!
Nicely done!
Very fashionable!
3rd place is
Demon Kakka!
Demon Kakka
Devil's Holiday\n\n\n\n\n\n\nDevil's Holiday\n\n\n\n\n\n\nDevil's Holiday\n\n\n\n\n\n\nDevil's Holiday
Devil's Holiday
Demon-san
costs around...
100,053 yen (~$855 US)!
Wow!!
Demon Kakka's
Devil's Holiday
Personal Style
Oh yes this
is a casual daily look
He dresses like this?
Is this true?
His shoes are very worn out
Very worn out
New Balance Sneakers     7890 yen (~$67 US)
He wears them a lot
He must wear them a lot
They're very normal
Even this-
His face is still weird
It's nothing
It doesn't matter if you take it off
Golden Bear polo shirt     7,452 Yen
10,053 Yen
3rd Place
Demon Kakka's
Private Clothes
The Devil's Holiday
It's good for when you go golfing.
Oh, golfing in this?
Right?
Oh, we're doing it here.
That was...
That was unexpected.
Next, in 2nd place, is
Umemiya Tatsuo
Big brother Tatsu.
I'm a Star
Oh, Umemiya?
"I'm a Star."  The price is...
Oh, a star.
I'm a Star
"I'm a Star." The price is...
238,560 Yen
238,560 Yen.
I'm a Star
Wow, there it is.
Pshh...
I'm a Star
238,560 Yen
2nd Place
I'm a Star
Private Clothes
Umemiya Tatsuo's
Come on.
He's tottering.
He put... he put his hand on the wall there.
Roller Skates    58,000 Yen
Yeah, he couldn't do it smoothly on his own.
Yeah.
You're shining. You're shining like a star.
Is he really like that in private?
I see.
Wouldn't he be cold? Like, in the winter?
Finally, we present 1st place.
1st place is this person:
Natsuki Youko
Natsuki Youko.
Party Until the Morning
Wow.
Party Until the Morning.
I'm excited to see what it'll be.
Party Until the Morning
And the price is...
Priceless
priceless!
Party Until the Morning
No surprise.
Natsuki Youko's
Party Until the Morning
Priceless
Private Clothes
1st Place
Isn't something wrong with this?
This is Egashira, right?
Very handsome.
She's out of breath.
That was cute.
That was cute! Right?
Cute!
That was really cute.
Really cute.
Is that cute?
We have now
run out of time.
See you again next week!
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
8 pm.
Detective Duties  12 Hours
Detective duties have crossed the 12-hour mark.
It's probably that.
Gone undercover in various locations
Participate in the detectives' reporting session
The newcomers participate in a detectives' reporting session.
Oh, this.
Now, I would like to start the
reporting session for Gaasuu Kurobikari Detective Agency.
Just in case, to confirm the purpose of this session,
we go undercover in various locations,
Detective Agency Reporting Session
Reporting session for  actions and statements
made by suspicious entertainers
observe the actions and statements made by suspicious people,
and report on their tendencies.
Note: On the right is Nishikawa Kiyoshi, a very senior and respected comedian.
Huh?
There's a veteran of comedy here.
You're kidding me.
Are we good?
Whoever has information to share may begin.
Yes.
Please.
On Tsukitei Hosei,
On-location Shoot for His Main TV Show
Tsukitei Hosei's Secret Info
this is about a show called
"Drive-A-Go! Go!",
a show that he considers to be very important to him.
It's always that, isn't it?
That day, he with the other talents and staff were heading towards the shooting location.
On-location Shoot for His Main TV Show
Tsukitei Hosei's Secret Info
A female talent was appearing on the show that day
and it was her first time working with Hosei.
So on the way, the director wanted to break the ice
and asked her, "What's your impression of Hosei?"
I'm told Hosei was listening with anticipation.
The girl said, "He's an idiot."
"He's the idiot of idiots.
All he is, is an idiot, is what I think."
That did happen.
On-location Shoot for His Main TV Show
Tsukitei Hosei's Secret Info
Hosei laughed at the time
but inside, he was pissed,
so he planned
to get revenge during the shoot.
I'm told that when Hosei got back to the cast and crew bus;
she was there eating lunch.
"This is my only chance," he thought,
and he quietly sat near her
and in such a way that she wouldn't notice,
he began to fart.
He expelled all the
gas in his body without making any noise.
Hosei thought to himself,
"This girl right now
is eating her lunch together with my fart."
Then Hoshuu... Hosei...
Come on...
Mixed up with "revenge (fukushuu)."
Got it mixed up with "revenge (fukushuu)."
Come on, Katsu.
Come on, Katsumata.
That's not like you.
He mixed up "revenge (fukushuu)" and "Hosei," I suppose.
Anyone else?
Could I?
Um, on Hamada,
these few years, his absent-mindedness
has gotten worse and worse.
This happened when he went on a location shoot to Hokkaido.
Hamada's Secret Info
On location in Hokkaido
The original purpose of the shoot
was to feature desserts.
But on a previous trip that Hamada had made there privately,
he found a ramen place that he liked
so he said he wanted to go there...
and suddenly changed the content of the shoot.
He remembered two pieces of information.
"It's a ramen place in Otaru, and
the name is 'Orange.'  Go find it," he tells the staff.
With this much information, using the internet these days,
you should be able to find the place, right?
So they search and search but they can't find it.
And after asking the locals many different things, what they found in the end was
a ramen place in East Otaru
called "Mikan."*
*Note: "Mikan" is a type of mandarin orange that is common in Japan.
That is...
That is just...
Hamada, please.
Hamada, on this issue, if you could please...
Hamada, if you could please...
That's awful.
I heard another awful story about his aging.
Hamada made a call to one of his juniors.
To Iwahashi of Plus Minus,
he made a call and got his answering machine.
Informant
Plus Minus' Iwahashi
Hamada's Secret Info
The Answering Machine
Hamada left a message, but
in the middle of it, he thinks he's talking
to the person instead.
I had Iwahashi play the message for me.
"You have 1 new message."
"Beep."
"Hello, it's Hamada."
"How are you for next Thursday?"
"Wondering if you want to get a meal or something."
"Next Thursday... How are you?"
"Hey, are you listening!?"
"Hey,  are you listening!?"
What the hell are you talking about?
How could that happen?
He forgot what was going on.
Jin, what the hell is that?
It got all mixed up in his head.
He got it mixed up.
That's awful.
Yeah, that's awful.
Oh, YOU, go ahead.
On Hamada's aging...
it seems that, from the stairs in his house,
Hamada's Secret Info
The Stairs in His House
twice a week is the frequency at which he falls down from them.
He falls down...
Twice a week?
In his house, right?
He falls down from them?
He should be the most used to them.
Even with your eyes closed, you should be able to climb them.
Twice a week?
This happened just a few days ago.  He finished shooting,
After Shooting...
Hamada's Secret Info
and Hamada kept going like this,
so I was wondering what he was doing.
Turns out he was looking for his
lapel mic that he had aleady taken off a while ago.
That guy, seriously.
That's crazy.
Really.
Oh, on the left.
This is a story about Endo.
When he was young and still getting started, performing at the Ginza Lot 7 Theatre,
Crowd Warming at the Ginza Lot 7 Theatre
Endo's Secret Info
he was a warm-up comedian there.
And the director had told him,
from a while ago, when you call the performer on stage,
say a catchphrase or something for them
right before you introduce them.
After thinking on it for a while,
*Note: Katsura Bunchin is a comedian who is much more senior than Endo and was much more accomplished than Endo at that time.
for Katsura Bunchin's* introduction, he said,
"He's recently been improving by leaps and bounds.
Here's Katsura Bunchin."
What?
No way.
What an idiot.
A veteran comedian who has been in the business for over 40 years
Katsura Bunchin
Seriously?
Endo was called into his dressing room and he said to Endo, "Who do you think you are?"
Who do you think you are?
That's to be expected.
Ballsy.
Of course he'd be scolded.
My apologies.
Go ahead, anyone.
This is about Kiyoshi.
Kiyoshi?
Um, in the Tokai region...
About me?
Yes.  In the Tokai region...
Hello.
he was doing a location shoot...
Excuse us.
Sorry about that.
He's been acting weird over there.
Everyone was too scared to do him in the first round.
Sorry about
greeting you there...
Let's calm down for a second here.
He was doing a location shoot in the Tokai region,
At a Shoot in the Tokai Region...
Nishikawa Kiyoshi's Secret Info
and I was on the same program,
and we always take a cast and crew bus
to go from Nagoya Station to the location.
Every time we get on the bus,
he immediately says, "Let's have a preparatory meeting."
"Let's have a meeting," he'll say. "Let's have it when we get on the highway," he'll say.
Every time when we get on the highway
*snore* - he's sleeping.
Then are you guys fine without doing the meeting?
We just have the meeting when we get to the location.
So he does mean to do it. He has the motivation.
The mornings are early, so, you know.
I also have something on Kiyoshi.
Recently, we did a live duo performance.
Backstage at a Duo Performance...
Nishikawa Kiyoshi's Secret Info
We had invited
Kiyoshi to appear as a guest,
and he had agreed to come on.
For that performance, we had written three new stand-up routines.
But we got them done just the day before or so, so on the day of,
two hours before we go on stage, Nobu and I
planned to just rehearse in that time.
Just hole ourselves in our dressing room.
So right when we had holed ourselves in our dressing room and started to rehearse
in front of the mirror, there was a knock on the door.
"It's Nishikawa," we heard, and he came in.
Backstage at a Duo Performance...
Nishikawa Kiyoshi's Secret Info
"Are you guys in the middle of a manzai rehearsal?
This is the most important moment."
As he says that,
He came in, sat down,
and just kept talking
I thought, "Oh? You're gonna have a seat?"
This is the most important moment
And the person who knows this best
is sitting here with us, is what I thought
"It's important to rehearse your routine"
"Yasushi-kun and I, when we had new comedic material,
we had to rehearse it at least 20 times!"
I wanted him to let me do exactly that...
You were going to do exactly that...
Yeah, you would've done exactly that
And...
Backstage at a Duo Performance...
Nishikawa Kiyoshi's Secret Info
Sorry about that
Not at all, so then
I thought, "What do I do?!" There was only 20 minutes
until the live performance and that's when I knew we were in trouble
Seriously speaking here
He goes "ALRIGHT!!" and then stood up
He says to me and Nobu,
"Let's go get some ramen!!"
That is ridiculous
That's ridiculous
At the location of the duo performance
20 minutes before it starts, no one would go to get ramen
So I said to the master (Kiyoshi)
Backstage at a Duo Performance...
Nishikawa Kiyoshi's Secret Info
"We'll pass on the ramen..." And then Master replied,
"That so? If it's just me, I'll go eat soba,"
and he just left us with that weird statement
And it was about 5 minutes before the performance
We went to the back of the lobby and said, "I look forward to working with you"
"Looking forward to it!!" he says
while eating a tempura rice bowl
He didn't eat soba??
Ramen, then soba!!
This is ridiculous
Did you change your mind?
You keep changing it, ramen, soba...
Is that what it's about?
If it's about food
I think it'll be a hit
A series about food?
Well...
Nishikawa Kiyoshi's Secret Info
Okonomiyaki Topping
Kiyoshi says, "Let's go get okonomiyaki*"
*Notes: Okonomiyaki is a savory Japanese pancake
The two of us went together and he says, "This time, I want to try something unusual."
"Can we get kimchi as a topping?"
So the restaurant staff put kimchi on top
Master just uses his spatula
and flings it right off
No way... He flings the kimchi??
"I can't eat it like this"
Even though he asked for it?
Give us a break
We've all heard of stage taboos, right?
Master Kiyoshi was
Nishikawa Kiyoshi's Secret Info
Stage Taboo
the chief judge of the Osaka Manzai Contest
Note: Denis is a comedy duo
While Denis was in the middle of their routine,
Kiyoshi suddenly stood up and said, "SOOO FUNNY!!"
And then Denis didn't become popular at all
In the middle of preparations!
I've also been
told that (while onstage)
In the middle of it!
Nishikawa Kiyoshi's Secret Info
Stage Taboo
There is a place called the Okinawa Theater
It was first my turn and then Master Kiyoshi's turn
We were doing our manzai and my line was
I know this one
"For a manzai comedian, someone unprecedented, like Master Yokoyama Yasushi, is awesome."
I say to Paradise, "Say what your great ambition is!"
Paradise exclaims, "My dream is to become the greatest manzai comedian
and get rich!" And right after that,
Master says from the side of the stage, "WELL SAID!"
From the side of the stage, "WELL SAID!"
That was just the set-up of the joke...
I remember it well
Nakagawa Reiji, go ahead
Nishikawa Kiyoshi's Secret Info
Stage Taboo
A long time ago, on a comedy show, Kiyoshi was the host
"Here's Nakagawa-Ke! If you'd please!"
Note: Nakagawa-Ke is a brother manzai duo, which means Nakagawa Family
And after that, he was getting off the stage, but
at the same time, we're getting on the stage
Right as we pass each other, he says "GO GET 'EM!!"
He sure shouts a lot
It was live and he got to make a joke before we had a chance
Were you surprised?
I was surprised
"GO GET 'EM!! GO!!" he says
Wow, that's amazing
Oh, Nishikawa-kun, do you have something to say?
Um...
May I speak about Sakata Toshio?
Note: Sakata Toshio is a long-time comedian, currently 74 years old. He is commonly referred to as Master Sakata or Aho-no-Sakata (That-Idiot-Sakata)
Sakata Toshio's Secret Info?
Should we have him say it?
Yes, I think that's fine
You guys
You all know so much
You guys listen up too, you hear?
We're all listening
Is this a funeral?
A funeral...
Why would you say funeral, of all things?
I can do this...
It was like, "Let's prank call Sakata Toshio's house"
Prank Call
Sakata Toshi's Secret Info
When I call his place...
Sakata and his wife always sleep together, so
Sakata wakes up and his wife is wondering what it is
"Excuse me, this is Asahi Broadcasting"
"Tomorrow, Sakata Toshio will be making an appearance so...
This is for a mic check so I apologize, but..."
It was about 11:30 or 12:30. "I'm sorry, but
2 pot lids?"
do you have
"I'm sorry, but with the 2 lids, could you...
I apologize for asking for this in the middle of the night, but..."
"It's for a mic check so
could you bang the lids together?"
Sakata then... Haha...
He puts down the phone and starts banging the pot lids together in front of the phone, when...
His wife says, as she's in bed
"Dear... What's happened?"
"Dear... Dear... You've gone crazy..."
Nishikawa-kun
Yes?
I hate to do this in the middle of your story, but
this ain't funny at all
Hey now!!
Bad...
He's such a bad guy!
Such a bad guy
Oh, sorry 'bout that...
It's 9PM
Detective Duties: 13 Hours
Going back to where the new detectives are
A strange request comes in unexpectedly
Everyone, listen up
That famous Inugami family relatives are
having a dispute over the inheritance
Right now, the relatives are gathered
They're all gathered so
They want you guys to mediate
Going in Circles Over Inheritance, Family Gathering
They Head Out as Detectives to Resolve the Issue!!
Inugami family...
Relatives?
Having a dispute... Over the inheritance?
A dispute over the inheritance, it seems
Inugami Family Room
Notes: "The Inugami Family" is a mystery/suspense movie directed by Ichikawa Kon. A detective carries out an investigation about a murder and learns about the Inugami family secret.
Pardon us
We're from the Detective Agency; would it be okay for us to sit here?
Thank you very much for going out of your way for us.
Please, have a seat.
Excuse us, thank you for having us
Sir,
would you please hurry and read the will for us?
Inugami Takeko
Second Daughter
Madam Takeko, please wait a moment
While Sahei-san was alive, he instructed,
"The will is to be read when all members of the Inugami family are gathered."
Lawyer Furudate
What did you say?
Takeko-san... I apologize, everyone
Eldest Daughter
Inugami Matsuko
My son should be here shortly
Eldest Daughter Matsuko's Son's Arrival
Now, hurry and come sit here
What the hell is this?
Now sir, please begin
Before we begin
Madam Matsuko, I have a favor to ask...
What could it be?
The person there, is that truly your son,
Itao or not..?
What did you say?
I don't mean to doubt you, but...
If you could just let us see your face
Then sir
are you saying that this Itao is an imposter?
No, that is not what I'm saying at all, but...
How troublesome
Just once, you must remove your hood
and let us see your face
If you must insist...
Itao, take off your hood!!
Fufu...
It's Sukekiyo
Note: Sukekiyo is the name of the character that Itao is based on
(from Yoshimoto Creative Agency)
Itao Itsuji
That is unnecessary
So unnecessary
He's definitely messing around
Well then,
this Itao over there, you can't tell if he's the real person or not
Isn't that right, Umeko-san?
Indeed
Itao is such a troublesome person
Itao... Itao is...
My my...
How dare you!!
You detectives over there, what is with your expression?
"This is not Itao," is that it?
We don't know if he's truly Itao or not!!
How dare you
Itao!
Don't just sit there silently, say something!!
It's Itao!!
In Osaka dialect...
"It's"...
All of you members
It's me, Itao
Tanaka
Yes?
You know it's me, right?
Why me?
Endo
Do you feel the same way that Tanaka does?
What kind of way of talking is that?
What a roundabout way to talk
What the hell?
Hama-n
He's never said that
He hasn't said "Hama-n" before?
Never
Hama-n, you believe me, right?
Hama-n, you feel the same way that Tanaka feels?
I don't know what that means
What does "the same way" even mean?
Tanaka, how do you feel?
We're forced to agree
We don't know what Tanaka feels
Exactly
Why is he basing everything off of how Tanaka feels?
O-Matsu
Am I a girl!?
That's a girl's name!!
O-Matsu
O-Matsu, do you feel the same way Tanaka feels?
That's what we don't understand!!
"Tanaka's feeling"
is what we don't know
in that case we can only have the same opinion-
Agree or disagree-
We could make it clear if we agree or disagree
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU!?
I'm Hosei
You're not popular enough
It seems you're not popular enough
I'm done with you guys
You agree with the statement,
"you are not the real Itao"?
You don't believe that
he is the real Itao!!
Itao, take off that mask!!
Itao Finally Reveals himself
Isn't this too surreal?
Itao
let's go
They're leaving?
Just because they didn't recognize he was the real Itao
Alright let's go
That was really too surreal
Yes, that was well done
10:00 PM
14 hours of duty
When the 5 men who were pushed around by Itao return to their room,
a new development...
Hey!! Guys!!
The Hama-Lisa is gone!!
Oh wow!!
Phantom Thief X III
Phantom Thief X is this statue, so it's this third generation
Thief is Phantom Thief X the Third
So whatever looks like this
His grandson...
If that's-
It could only be Hamada-san
No it's not me
Isn't this Hamada-san?
They look alike
Emergency Alert!! Emergency Alert!!
Internal Announcement
The Masterpiece Hama Lisa was stolen by Phantom Thief X III
All officers please report to the auditorium
To the auditorium!
Okay
Case of the Stolen Masterpiece Hama Lisa
Thief is Phantom Thief X III Everybody to Auditorium!!
We got really busy
We're busy
Auditorum
So everyone, can you come sit over here?
All officers are present
A very serious atmosphere
Hamada, you're on the very edge
He didn't use honorifics though
Why am I over here?
Usually Hosei's spot
Something is off
The seating is different
Chief Detective Explains Situation
As you all know,
the masterpiece worth 10 million yen,
the Hama Lisa, was stolen!!
In order to catch the thief as soon as possible,
we asked for the help of the police department
With that, please go ahead
GOD
DAMN!!
Masahiro Chono jumps in!!
Police Department Investigator
Metropolitan Police Department's...
CHONO!!
The thief is Phantom Thief X THE THIRD
Hey,
Bring it here!
The first...
Phantom Thief...
The first Kaito (Phantom Thief) X Statue
X
The perpetrator
looks similar to this
Looks similar to Phantom Thief X
Theft Perpetrator
You understand?
Hey
It's different from usual
The perpetrator should be among us
He has a distinct feature... His LIPS!!
They're cod roe
Nobody is gonna turn themselves in?
Phantom Thief X Lookalike Search!!
Point is Cod Roe Lips
Turn yourself in honestly
Yama-chan's face is so annoying
Got it!?
First you, stand up
It's different...
Okay you can sit down
Okay, stand up
You can sit down
It's you
You don't match either...
Good for you
Series First! Hosei is off the hook!!
You, stand up
Yes
It's like lapping
It's not you either
Do you have any hints for me?
A mole...
He has a mole on his chin...
Cod Roe lips + Mole on chin
Theft Perpetrator
Alright
Okay!
Get up!
Look straight!!
He's changing his face
Can you remove your hat?
Raise your chin; LOOK STRAIGHT!!
Hey!
LOOK STRAIGHT!
Quite the development
Amazing!!
This year's "No Laughing..." is a bit different
Can you get up (on the stage)?
What?
Could you stand next to the statue?
I'd hate to go up there...
Hm?
Yes...
Alright, please go up
To the stage to be compared to Phantom Thief X!!
HEY!! GET UP HERE!!
This usually happens to Hosei-san
It's different
No matter how or where you see it... You did it
Well I mean
You could say I look like him...
That might be the case...
This year it's your turn
He said it directly
I would hate to be told that
The thief receives a punishment slap!!
You know,
there are a lot of complaints against you!!
On your damage report...
Does anyone have any complaints against him?
He used violence against me
Pff..
Pf-
Pff-
You rat out your friends too much
No, no...
It's the same
No matter what you do, there's no escaping
Come here
Okay, okay
This is...
This feeling...
Seriously?
No, no, wait...
Speak!
Really, you...
You! Cut it out already! Seriously...
No, really...
Really
Hey!!
No, no
That's bad
That's bad!!
Take off the coat!
Listen here
Yes
You! Come here!!
No, it's scary
It's not scary at all
No, no
You were always laughing, right!?
Right, you bastard?
In order to avoid the slap, Hamada closes the distance
What are you doing?
This is...
It is, isn't it?
This is scary!
We know
Enough, enough
It's scary, huh?
It's impossible, Hamada-san!!
Really, I can't...
Enough with this!
I really can't...
It's you this year!!
Prepare yourself
He's already said it
Yeah, he's already said it
We know
I know the feeling
It's really the same
I really don't like this
There's no helping it
Yeah, no helping it
There's no...
There's no escaping
Look here!
No, no... wait..!
Why, you...
No wait wait!
No, no, no...
Scary!
I'm really scared
Hosei-san looked really happy
Yeah no helping it
No helping it
Double... double happy.
You really don't know when to give up
He looks like he's having double the fun
Hamada!
I'm doing it! Come here!
Good that you're not getting slapped
I said come here!
It's better not to dodge in a strange way
It's dangerous, stay still!!
Close your eyes!!
That's impossible! I can't close my eyes!!
Stay still
Hamada-san, do your best
Do your best
It's dangerous
Come here!
Wait, really...
Enough is enough, you fucking bastard!!
No
Fucker!
Already filmed
Quite funny
as expected
This is funny
I've never seen Hamada-san like this
I'm sorry
Really funny
This is...
Shit, this is funny
Prepare yourself for it
Hey Hosei!!
No helping it
Good for you
It's occasionally bad for you, that sound.
I'm slapping with all my might!!
Right!!
You, remember this...
Finally time for the slap of punishment
You were really serious...
Don't run away
I'll send you flying!!
Countdown!!
That was a great expression on his face
Wait!!
That person is not the culprit who stole the Hama Lisa!!
Inspector Chono
Young Detective arrives
You are making a big mistake.
Please release that person.
Huh?
You're not the thief?
From the start, I've been saying "it wasn't me"
Wasn't it you who stole the painting?
I did not steal it!!
No way...then return to your seat
Hamada just barely escapes the slap!!
Yama-chan's expression...
it was such a thunderclap
Inspector Chono!
Phantom Thief X the first's best specialty skill:
Disguises!!
Phantom Thief X the first...
His real face, no one has ever seen it before
In other words, the face of this statue is also
Phantom Thief X the first's
A pro at disguises, no one has seen his real face
The First Phantom Thief X the statue
disguise!
What do you mean?
Well, where could his real face be hidden?
Hehe, that expression...
Please bring that in!!
Inspector Chono
Please
Use this hammer on the statue and smash it!!
Smash it?
When the statue gets smashed, the mystery will become clear!!
It's a statue, y'know
Smash it?
That was the worst for Yamasaki
It's smashed open
This is harsh
It was uncovered
Uncovered!
The statue sure has a great expression too
We've returned to the same person as always
This is the real face of Phantom Thief X the First
His descendant, it should be clear now who it is!!
The culprit who stole the famous painting, the Hama Lisa, is...
Tsukitei Hosei! It's you!!
So it's you!?
Wrong!!
Thanks
Wait...what's with this?
Case of the stolen famous painting "Hama Lisa"
The real culprit was Tsukitei Hosei !!
You sure did some complex things
No, I don't know anything
This year too... it's you!!
Seriously...
No way...
Isn't it fine with Hamada-san!?
What's your name?
I'm Tsukitei Hosei
You are the Third. The First, what Hosei was he?
The First?
Yeah, the First.
Gets brought on stage for questioning!!
What was his name?
Phantom Thief X the First?
What are you saying, you fucker?
This guy's name is...
Is that his angry face?
Yamasaki Hosei, right?
No,
Now this is starting again
It's written "X the First" here however
Bring your face to the side of the statue. From the back.
Do it properly
It's courage
Come here
Slap of punishment for the criminal
Please wait
I was hoping...
What?
Don't push
Please...
For what?
Please wait a little before you're going to slap, right?
It's you!
Hurts!
It's started!
It's started...
It's started, huh?
Alright, now get ready
I know you'll do various things
Ouch! My armpit!!
What's with that, huh!?
Coincidentally headbutted Chono's nose
I'm sorry!
You!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
This is...
My heart was pounding
Really sorry...
At the time, he was
What are you doing?
Ah, I'm sorry!
I'll pay you back double!!
This is
I didn't do it on purpose!!
You're going to slap me, right?
Of course!!
Enough
"Of course"
I'm gonna do a countdown!!
Alright?
GUWAAA!! WAIT!!
He's scared
Please wait
Really scary
Argh, scary!
Yeah, we know
We know
Do it
5 seconds too...
Then, how many seconds do you wanna go with?
3 seconds
Then...
This is really long
Yeah, it's long
That it's long...
Hey, stand straight!
Well, he said that he's paying it back double
I'm doing it!
Paying it back double...
Slap of punishment explodes!!
Really looks like it hurt!
This has got to be painful
Super painful
God
What's with that?
damn!!
What's this?
Yeah
Urgh
Ah, it was funny
What a relief...
Yama-chan was so happy; how pitiful
In the midst of the lingering excitement,
Detective work 16th hour
there has been trouble...
Guys, it's terrible!
You always say that
A businessman has come here beat up a senior detective who revealed his affair
I don't get it!
So you mean ordinary people and the detectives are fighting?
Exactly!
The senior detective said deal- he can't deal with this so
Let's go together
Well it's a senior detective we've never met, so...
A Client has come to beat up a detective
The 5 of them head out to solve the problem!!
Alright!
You don't need your jacket?
Oh you don't- you don't need your jackets
Okay
It's a separate branch so it's close by but still kind of far
So the senior detective- what did you say?
I don't get it at all
A businessman who had his affair figured out has come to beat him up?
So he's causing trouble?
He definitely is
The five men travel by bus
toward a nearby detective firm branch
The bus with the 5 of them in it will head to a nearby detective firm
What's waiting for them is...
Ah, you can hear them
You can hear them from outside
They're causing trouble
This way
It's fine!
That's supposed to be private!
It's your fault for having an affair!!
What do you mean affair!? That's a private matter!
Fuck you, how are you a detective?!
You had an affair; you're in the wrong!
Wait a minute!
Don't just stand there and stare at us!!
Can we just get along?
Just shut up and sit down!!
Hurry up and sit!!
Don't we have to fix the problem?
Yeah, right?
We don't have to fix the problem?
Just observe
What are you gonna do!?
Can you just watch?
OKAY Listen up guys
Let's fight to see who is stronger!!
Let's try it then, I accept your challenge!!
Negotiating has failed
Alright let's go!
Let's go!
Team Degawa
Team Ueshima
Celebrities whose average age is 44 years old
With their pride on the line, the Fighting Festival has begun
Shut up
What the hell
Kobayashi Kendo
Team Ueshima Staff
Just deal with it, face to face
It's called...
Tickling Showdown!!
What?
We don't understand what you're saying!!
IT'S A TICKLING SHOWDOWN!!
Kuro-chan, have at it!!
Okay I'll go!!
You can do it!
Kuro-chan
Team Degawa
I definitely won't lose!
Don't lose, don't lose!
First up: Kuro-chan
For 30 seconds the player will tickle the opponent;
whoever can make his opponent make a sound wins
Tickling Showdown
For 30 seconds, the player will tickle his opponent, and whoever gets his opponent to make a sound will win
Got it?
This will be too easy!
Oh, yeah? Let's see what you got.
So it's first batter then second batter
Get set... START!
What the hell is going on?
What the hell?
It's between two old men...
What the heck?
His opponent hasn't a made a sound though
What is this?
Ah, that's the spot
What is he doing?
What the hell is this!?
He didn't make any noise at all!
No he did, he did!
What you did to me, I'm gonna do the exact same thing to you!!
Changing Positions
Bring it on, whatever you got!
Go on, Kuro-chan!
Come come come come!
Get ready...
Already?
What the hell!
What is this scene!?
What the hell is this!?
He was making a lot of noise...
He definitely was!
I did it!!
What are this pig and this plump man even doing?
Your turn!
Tickling Showdown Round 2
Iwao Nozomu
Tanaka Takushi
One more round of the Tickling Showdown...
This time it's a fight between Team Ueshima's Iwao and Team Degawa's Tanaka
Here we go!
Get ready!
This again?
START!
START with Iwao up first
Come on
Come on, come on
His touch is so soft
I can't watch!
I said I can't watch this!
There's nothing good about this
You're doing great!
Don't look at his face, Iwao!
Good job!
What the hell
He was going "Hee hee"!!
Changing Positions
Go, Tanaka!
Can you beat him, Tanaka?
Yes I will
Set, START!
What a soft round...
Good face, Iwao!
How disgusting!!
That's not tickling!
So gross!!
What the hell is this!?
He already laughed!
Hey, hey!
What the hell is this!?
What the hell?
That wasn't a tickling showdown!
He didn't say anything, this guy!!
It's a victorious smile!!
Do you know the difference between strength and will?
Bring in THAT THING!!
What is it!?
What is it, damn it!?
What is this!?
Show them all!
Show them!
Hoshida Hidetoshi
Team Degawa Staff
This is a Blindfolded Kendo Showdown!
Whoa!
Sense your opponent by sound, then hit!!
Space with no escape
Go on, Yoshinobu!
Blindfolded Kendo Showdown
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Tonikaku Akarui Yasumura
With that, Team Degawa's kendo expert, Yoshinobu and Team Ueshima's Yasumura will compete
So put on your eyemasks, spin around 3 times, then start!
2 minute sudden-death match: put on eyemask, spin around 3 times, then start
Blindfolded Kendo Showdown
Oh I see
Okay, now spin around 3 times! Ready...
set,
one,
two,
three, START!
Go get him!!
START!!
Your stance is a bit off!!
Ahh no no no no
Watch out!
Why does he do that!?
They can only use sound to sense their surroundings.
Right
The next strike will determine their fate!!
He really gets beat up a lot
You won!
Nice counter!
Let's decide this with a daring feat!
Get THAT THING ready!!
What's this sound?
What is it?
Very flashy car enters
Whoa, what is this?
Alright, so
This car,
the back is made to be REALLY REALLY bouncy
Kenkoba will try to eat all of his very very hot ramen while sitting in the bouncy trunk of this car
Sit in very bouncy trunk
Try to finish all of very very hot ramen
Hydraulics Hopping Ramen Challenge
You guys definitely can't do this, so...
JUST WATCH!!
Who's gonna do it?
YOU'RE gonna do it?
Can you even do it?
I'll show you a report like it's from a normal gourmet channel!
You won't get a gourmut-
You won't get an offer from a gour-gourmet channel
He really got his tongue twisted
Can you do it?
Eat more!
Give us a report!!
Give us a report!
Shut up!
Drink the soup.
Drink it!
You didn't eat it!
He ate a lot of it!! What, you can't see it?
You didn't eat it at all!
You didn't give us a food report at all!!
A French maid costume set
Prepared next is a French maid costume.
After soaking it in hot water, put it on within 1 minute!!
The challenge is, for some reason, to soak all of these in hot water and wear them.
Let's do this!
The challenger is
Haranishi of the Ueshima Corps.
Haranishi Takayuki
Ueshima Corps
This guy's strong against hot temperatures.
All right, let's go!
Putting the costume in the hot water
This one, too. I'm gonna do this one, too.
You can't do it. This is really hot.
Just wait and see. This is gonna be great!!
Ready,
START!
No way. There's no way you can do it.
No way. No way.
Hot! Hot!
What the hell are you doing?
Hot!
Too slow!
He got it on.
Don't shake it this way.
Come on, come on.
You only get one chance for that.
Hot!
You still got a lot more left!
Haranishi is invulnerable to high temperatures!!
You can do all of it, come on.
Go, go.
What are you doing?
Only one chance. You took it off, gotta go to the next one.
You can do it, come on.
The bottom!
Trying to at least get a top and bottom on....
Just put the bottom on!
Just put the bottom on and you're done.
Three more seconds left.
Top and bottom!
Aahh!!
You didn't put them on!
Sloppy!
You gotta put all of them on!
That was cheap.
Looks like we beat you at your own game!!
Get out of here!
Play time is over now.
That's right.
Let's end this with the usual.
All right.
Get it ready!!
There it is...
What are you guys, scared?
For the last one we battle it out with arm wrestling.
He's gonna say that again.
He's gonna say the rules again.
Fill your asshole to the brim with air,
battle it out with arm wrestling
and whoever farts loses.
Alright already!!
Stop that.
We understand the rules of the usual.
Every year...
Every year, seriously.
And the match never gets a result, every time.
Gotta explain it, or they won't understand what's going on.
Yeah, they won't.
There are some first-timers here, so if you could repeat it again for them.
What are you talking about, here?
We're gonna arm wrestle!!  But first,
we fill your asshole to the brim with air and then arm wrestle
and whoever farts loses.
Enough already. Seriously, enough of that.
We, of course, have our invincible captain, Ueshima.
No one among you can beat Ueshima!
The legend of fart arm wrestling, Ueshima Ryuuhei
Degawa, sir, please!
Degawa Corps Captain
Degawa Tetsurou
Let's do this!
No Farting Arm Wrestling: Battle of The Captains
Ueshima Ryuuhei
Every time, you wouldn't come up. What? Were you scared?
Give me a break.
I'm totally innulverable to farts.
That's invulnerable to farts.
Let's do this, then.
Invulnerable to farts, okay.
What are you talking about? "Invulnerable to farts."
And in any case, Ueshima!
What is it?
Because you have blisters on your asshole,
the air never gets in!!
Don't say that!! You idiot.
It's gross.
Don't say that I have blisters on my ass!!
You win only because the air doesn't go in!!
Don't say that, you idiot. Don't say it.
Alright!!
Thank you, let's go.
Hosshan,
lotion on the heavy side, please
Going with that.
Air is injected into both simultaneously
This is the first time for Degawa...
Let's go.
Is it gonna go in or what?
Oh no no, that's not the anus.
Right, yes, yes, thank you.
Ow
Put the anus on.
Oh no no, not the anus.
Put the lotion on...
No, seriously.
What the hell?
I'm scared.
I'm getting hit like crazy.
He tried to say "lotion" and he said "anus (koumon)"...
What the hell?
That guy is just...
I'm scared because it's thick.
Hurry the hell up.
Hold on, geez.
Go "Hahhh."
No, no.
No, Hosshan...
The air's coming out!!
Why is it going out?
It just keeps going out!!
It won't stop. What is this?
What the hell is this?
What the hell are you doing?
It won't stop. Why is this?
Why does it come out?
It keeps going out, even though I'm holding it.
Our captain is waiting for you!
You idiot, it's in.
Here it goes!
Air is injected into both simultaneously
It's going. Okay, let's go.
Is it alright?
Alright.
It already came out.
Ueshima runs backstage
What the hell?
Stop leaking, Ueshimaa!!
Stop making Ueshima wait!
I had it just now!!
Just getting it to this point is fun.
The moment he took it out, you could hear the air coming out.
I had it, man.
Ueshima returns
How are you doing, captain?
It's coming out.
Ryuu, you should also get in that position and be ready
from the start.
I'm putting it in.
Air is injected while in stand-by mode
It's going in.
It's coming out.
Get set, get set.
All right!
Okay, good!
Ready...
Go!
Can't even tell who that sound came from.
Both run backstage
What the hell is he doing?
What is over there?
1:30AM: Returning to the office, but there are still many more trials to go through.
Detective Duty: 17 hours 30 minutes
That scared me.
Whoa, okay.
What... what is this?
Who is that?
They were saying something. A shamisen?
Isn't it simply an old lady?
Mistress Utsumi Keiko (93 years old)
I'm ninety-three.
Note: 1 "go" is about 180 milliliters
One go* of wine, two bowls of rice.
(La-di-da-di-da.)
In the middle of the night,
I go to the bathrrom 5 times.
I go to the bathroom 5 times.
In the middle of the night,
7 more years until a hundred, no way.
To everyone, I ask for
your support.
Ugghhh.
You rookie detective bastards,
I've taken a friend of you bastards, Hiroshi.
Let them hear you.
Sorry, you guys.
I'm sorry the situation has come to this.
Muahahaha!
But
I'll give you bastards a chance.
Hiroshi is captured
somewhere within the building that you are all in.
First, Hamada and Tanaka,
you bastards go first!!
From this point on, you're allowed to laugh
I don't want Tanaka!
but if you get scared, you're OUT.
This guy falls over in fear.
Lastly, it's cold outside,
so wear your jackets when you go.
Wear your jackets when you go, alright?
No way, I hate this!!
What I'm scared of is you always do this,
That's right, that's right.
and your elbow will just come up here and hit me really hard.
And your elbow will just come up here and hit me really hard.
I won't do that. It won't happen.
Your nose will bleed thick!!
Really dark blood!!
Special Midnight Rules
Absolutely No Getting Scared
Detectives
Rescue the kidnapped Fujiwara!!
First, the two are to go rescue Fujiwara.  But the concerns about Tanaka remain.
They had to pick that photo?
Every year, I know what's going to happen.
(With the elbow,) bang!!
The elbow?
Yeah, the elbow...
"Ahhh," he'll go,
and then, bang!!
I'm seriously afraid of that.
If I'm about to go like this, could you just hold me like this, then?
No, no...
That would be dangerous.
I'll be careful, though.
You mean, wrap you up?
Oh, then what about
you hold on tightly to Hamada and walk?
Instead, yeah, since you're big.
Right, right.
Like this? Like this, right?
So if you get scared, you can go like this.
Don't let go here.
We're seriously gonna walk like this?
I think it's good.
Good luck.
Sorry. I'm sorry about this, Hamada.
If only you could be more dependable, that's all this is about.
Hamada has a weak back, though.
Damn, so many things...
Arrgghhh!!
You're right
See?
What should I do..?
I can't walk...
You really can't...
You're probably taking too much time even now...
It is dark already...
Seriously though man, I'm counting on you
The elbow, man, the elbow.
The elbow, man, the elbow...
Aaaaaaaaah
Baaang
like that...
Only Hamada laughed...
Okay, I'm sorry...
We're off... We're going.
2nd Floor: in front of the waiting room
It's the scariest with you
Until the hidden prank
Where are we going, are we meant to go down these stairs?
Yeah, I presume so...
There's no other way...
Nebaaru-kun is outside the window
[Note: Nebaaru-kun is a mascot character based on natto(fermented soybeans). "Nebaaru" means sticky. He ends sentences with "nebaa".]
I'm Nebaaru-kun
Hold on!
He's already on
the floor!!!
Sticky sheets
The floor...
W-W-Wow!
Nebaa, nebaa
Dolls of Nebaaru-kun fall from the ceiling
1 for 800yen
Buy it, nebaa
That shocked me
Wait
Can you please
do something about this sticky sheet?
My hand...
Timi-...
That's shouting from hell!!
That's shouting from hell!
They're screaming right outside the door...
Tanaka, this (sticky sheet)
what do I do about it!?
It's completely stuck on you!
Take it off for me!!
1st Floor Corridor
Okay...
Man, that scared me...
Until the hidden prank
This way...
Seriously Tanaka...
Hayashiya Pe-Pako husband&wife couple appear!
Damn, that scared me.
He fell over again...
Great work on this huge shoot
Oh no, not at all... Thank you so much...
I've never been on such an amazing program...
Just for them, they're going to tell a joke
Okay...
Will you listen to our jokes would that be okay?
Even when the weather is really bad
Where's the place to dry laundry?
It's Arakawa-ku in fact...
[note: pun based on fact Ara means 'oh dear' and 'kawaku' means 'to get dry'
Ara-kawaku
Pa-ko's Picture
Seriously though, great work!
Oh, thanks...
Do your best!
Thank you so much...
Sorry about this...
Yes, sorry...
Thank you!
Great job, guys!
Damn, that shocked me!
Yeah, it did...
Haha! Oh no...
Damn, I don't want to do this...
Damn...
It was just me farting for fuck's sakes...
Huh, what was that?
If you get shocked at something like that...
Could you please not fart
here?
They quietly wait for news from the 2
Meanwhile, the other 3 wait for further instructions...
1st Floor: in front of the Disguises Room
It says something there...
From a treasure box in the room,
Hiroshi's location!!
find and get a map clue of
From a treasure box in the room
find and get a map clue of Hiroshi's location...
Oh wait...
What?
Cautious of the shock from door knob
Please, you open it...
Wait, why?
Why do I have to do it?
Oy you, don't mess with me!!
It'll be fine!!
Hurry up and open it!!
As expected, the door knob gives off a shock
You seriously are just...
1st Floor Disguises Room
What now...
There it is
Open it...
You must open this treasure box!!
Hamada-san, you open it!
Must push...
Must push!
It says "Must push"!
Must push?
Please push it...
I see...
Connected to the waiting room where carbon dioxide gas gets blasted
This is really bad
for our health
From over there...
So annoying...
Seriously, what the hell...
Nothing happened!
Current location
Map clue
Search continues! Aiming for annex's 2nd floor
The two resume their search for Fujiwara.
They head for the second floor of the annex
1st Floor Corridor
Those stairs, huh?
I get it...
Oh damn...
Until secret prank
That's right, right?
Yes, I think so...
and this goes...
Oh damn!
I'm sorry!
What the hell!?
Danson
Oh what the hell!?
3 deer and Bambino Ishiyama enters
Danson!
What...
You want us to dance?
Inviting them to dance?
Ni-bura!
[note: this is a comedy routine by duo 'Bambino'. The chants mostly  don't really have any particular meanings. Although 'Danson' means 'dance' in French]
Wait, they're coming here...
Ni-bura
You're really
doing it...
Ni-bura
Success in catching the 3 deer
Damn you're
good friends
You did it.
What the hell!?
That scared me...
Why was I forced to do
a junior's routine  like that?
2nd Floor: Photo-taking Room
Wow, damn it...
Follow the instructions of the machine
and take a buddy-buddy photo!!
Wait...
Follow the instructions of the machine...
and take a buddy-buddy photo...
What's it like in there?
HOLY SHIT!
King of Cont 2015 Lotti's comedy
[note: King of Cont is an annual comedy skit competition]
Damn, that scared me
This guy's so irritating!!
Did you see?
Ye-sh...
Are you decent now?
What the hell are you doing?
You're not decent at all!
Is it okay now? Are you decent?
"Ye-sh" he said that right?
Ye-sh
I'm opening it...
Okay...
Stop taking the piss!!
What the hell, man..?
What the-...
Wear properly, you said "Yeesh"!!
What the hell..?
The 2 take a buddy-buddy photo
The previous customer leaves
The two can take a photo now...
3...
2...
1...
The picture will come out of the side of this machine
Announce
Oh great...
Please wait outside
I was so scared...
I thought something was going to happen...
Yeah...
The picture taking ends...
Here it is...
It's already come out...
Hamada got switched with Sato Gajiro
[note; Sato Gajiro is a veteran actor]
They love using
him...
They really think
highly of him, huh?
This isn't me...
Masked squad takes the 2 away
Because the 2 did not take a good picture,
they were taken away to another location
That was a dirty trick
It was strange
Prefab small room
What?
What's with this?
What? What?
Wait a little!!
Eh? Seriously?
I wonder if the others have started out?
Tied
Up
Oh what the hell, man..?
Newbie waiting room
So tired...
I have taken Hamada and Tanaka as well
You're the only ones left!
Now go!!
Don't you guys forget to wear your jackets though too, okay?
Wear your jackets and go, okay?
You guys
Whatever happens, don't forget it!!
Here it is...
So those 2 also got caught, huh?
Before rescuing Fujiwara, they will go to save the captured two
Before rescuing Fujiwara, the 3 will
go and save Hamada and Tanaka
Damn, I'm so scared...
2nd Floor: in front of the waiting room
Please don't scream...
Let's do our very best
Carbon dioxide gas suddenly comes out
Damn it...
Right from the start...
I don't want to do this...
There's some debris here...
Sticky sheets
This is where Hamada-san
was screaming like "Ugyaaa"
The 2 in the prefab...
Meanwhile, the captured two...
Until pitch black
Help us!!
This is...
They can't hear us...
You're right
The prefab room suddenly becomes pitch black
That's scary...
What is this?
Give me a break...
Please stop this...
Wait, what what...
Filming with a special camera. Visibility for the 2 is zero
Please brighten the room up...
This would be
scary
Way more...
What the?
Filming on night vision camera
With visibility at zero, Barbie enters
What the hell, seriously..?
I had no idea...
I literally have no idea...
But Barbie can't
see either, right?
I'm scared...
What the hell is going on..?
Barbie uses night vision scope to see
Seriously...
Oh of course...
This is so so so scary...
Wait, what what??
My dick got touched
You're kidding me
Something touched my dick...
You're kidding me...
Serious...
What happened?
Mydick got touched too
My dick got touched too
What is this?..
What is going on here?
1st Floor Corridor
This is seriously annoying...
Wait here!!
It says wait here...
And it's telling us to stand in line...
Huh?
You people!!
Ufufu
The Kano sisters are waiting in the yard with machine guns
Wait right there!
What a ridiculous
outfit
The Kano sisters shoot wildly with their machine guns
I'm Sexy Rambo Kyouko!!
I'm the same, Mika!!
I don't get it
Mika...
That is one crazy outfit
Night vision recording
Barbie playing pranks in the prefabricated room in complete darkness
Please no...
Tickling armpit with brush
What the hell is this..?
Help!!
I don't think I could handle this
Come on...
What what what?
Oh God, I'd hate this
Augh!! Hey hey, wait!
Something's hitting my face!!
Hitting your face?!
What is it, what is it??
Gross!! What is it? Stop stop stop!!
Stop please, stop!!
What is this?!
Something's hitting your face, right?
Yes, something is
So gross... Who is it?
I can't get my vision adjusted at all
Time until
secret prank
seconds
Yes, it just won't adjust!
That's enough, right?
I'm telling you, I can't see anything at all
That's enough, isn't it?
What's going on? What's going on? What's going on? What's going on?!
In complete darkness, Hamada's wall revolves
Wait, what? What's happening??
What's going on? What's going on? What's going on? What's going on?!
What's wrong? What's wrong? Hamada-san??
Hamada gets switched with Sato Gajiro
Note: Sato Gajiro is a Japanese actor who has made several appearances on previous batsu games
Time until
light turns on
seconds
Come on, gimme a break
Really though... Please give me a break
This is enough, isn't it?
Uwahh!!
Haaamada-san...
I was so shocked
Gajiro-saaan...
Front of prefabricated room
Hamada-saaan!!
That shrieking is Tanaka, isn't it?
Tanaka's shrieking... You think so?
Hamada's entrance
In just a moment,
In just a moment... Hamada's entrance...
I wonder what this means
Hamada's entrance?
"Hamada's entrance"? What does that mean?
Hamada-san, this way please
Hamada's Manager, Nagai
It's Nagai-kun
Oh
It's the manager, Nagai-kun
Yeah, the manager...
This way, if you would please
Hamada entering the scene
M-Ichigo
Note: M-Ichigo is a monster that originally appears in Ultraman. He's also appeared in EDF batsu and was described as a Hamada lookalike.
Hello!
You're so cheery
Greetings
It's playing the
sound of my laughter?!
He's so very cheery
That's just amazing
He's so cheery
This this, I think this is it
Hamada and Tanaka are in here!!
That was amazing just now
Oh, there, they're there, th... Huh?
Help... Please help me!
Where's Hamada-san?
Ha...  Hamada?
Ha... Hamada?
Hamada-san, you've gotten a bit smaller
There's too many Hamadas...
No no no, that's not right
Wait...
Hamada returns with a map with a clue
We'll release you, we'll release you
Thanks
Ow ow ow ow ow...
Wow, today has just been amazing
Just now, Nagai went out for Hamada's entrance together with you
You were in such  a good mood!
You were in such a good mood!
Hamada-san... Yes, I heard him
You guys, that's ridiculous, don't you think?
It's clear that it wasn't me!!
Your eyes shine at night occasionally
You idiot...
I'm not really sure what that was...
But really, I'm so glad
I'm so glad
So glad!
With that map, do you know where we have to go last?
Grounds
Map with Clue #2
Prefabricated Room
You Are Here
With all 5 gathered, Fujiwara's rescue is on the way!!
The 5 of them head to the grounds as indicated on the last map
Isn't this insane? How far does it go?
Escape the thicket of the forest, to the grounds where Fujiwara awaits
We've come to a big forest; are we going to be okay?
This is dangerous if we're not careful
That's so true
Watch your feet
So true
Let's go slowly
Grounds
My head hurts...
Your head hurts?
Continuing on the path to Fujiwara's location of confinement
What the hell..? So scary...
These crosses...
On the grounds is a grave
So long!
Why do we...
It's Hiroshi
We have to save Fujiwara-san
Are you serious, Hamada?
There he is!
There he is!!
Where?
Huh, where?
Oh, you're right
You're right
He's been captured
There he is
Will you rescue me?!
Yes, let's rescue him!
You sure do get captured a lot. You have no sense of danger do you?
Can't you just do this yourself?
Tanaka?
Yes yes, I understand
I was about to become a sacrifice for the titan!!
Titan?
A sacrifice?
What the hell is that?
It's clearly justvelcro
It's clearly just velcro
Finally...
Hey, what's this?
What the hell is wrong?
What's wrong with your leg?
My leg won't move
Could you put me in this?
No way, we can't do that
Fujiwara's leg is injured; escape by a hand-pushed cart
This has nothing to do with it
Here, hold this yourself
Sorry about this
You're going to be a live sacrifice for the titan?
Everyone hurry, we have to go
Let's go then?
As if I'd let you leave! Go!!
I'm going to become the titan's live sacrifice!!
You're fine, you're fine
Time until
secret prank
seconds
Straighten it out
There we go
Everyone, hurry...
Please hurry, let's hurry
You're fine
Sudden alarms
Here we go
I don't like this...
I don't like this
There it comes
Here it comes!!
Colossal Titan from Attack on Titan
There it is!! There it is!!
It's Attack on Titan!!
So heavy!!
It's muddy
You're so damn heavy!!
Watch out, watch out!!
It's Attack on Titan!!
Hot hot hot hot hot
So hot
Danger!!
Watch out!
Hurry up!!
Hurry...
Ahh... I laughed quite a lot today
What the hell!
You did a great job rescuing me
Is your leg better now?
Thank you, guys
Is your leg better?
My leg is all better!
Your leg is all better...
That was really fast
Detective Duties: 19 hours
It's 3 in the morning...
Detectives
This time, as rookie detectives...
The five men serve their time...
The five men serve their time for their 10th New Year's Eve Duties
For their 10th New Year's Eve duties
They've overcome the numerous hardships...
And now...
They will greet this moment of great joy
Everyone, be delighted
Your mission for this year is now OVER!!
YES!!
It's over!
It's over
You guys did a good job
Good job everyone
Everyone, let's go!!
Wow, that was pretty intense
This is the end
This is the last
You're right
Now it's over...
Office Entrance
Over this way
Now, it's like...
Congratulations!!
Oh, already?
Here he is
Hello everyone!
Agency Grand Chief Gaasuu
Suga Kenji
He's here all of a sudden, isn't he?
Everyone, thank you for your hard work
Thanks for your hard work
This year is the year of the monkey
So, if you could lead us, master, for the year of the monkey acrostic poem
Acrostic Poem Topic
Year of the Monkey
So, if you could lead us, master, for the year of the monkey acrosticpoem
So, if you could lead us, master, for the year of the monkey acrostic poem
If you would please
For "year of the monkey" (sarudoshi), "SA"!
Sa
With awesome comrades
Ru
"RU"!
Rules that are unnecessary
Do
"DO"!
Keep continuing, come hell or high water
Shi
"SHI"!
Shigemi Satomi and I living together is my desire!!
Hand in hand with her
What the hell?
You want to live together with her?
What the hell!
I hope we work together this year as well
I hope so as well
Thank you
What the hell!
That was something
What the hell is he saying?
Living together... That's crazy
He says that nonsense for the last line...
He said "living together is my desire"...
Everyone, if you pass that gate, it'll be the end!!
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you!
Happy New Year!
Lots of things happened this year too
Hope we work together this year as well
It's finally over!
End Shz
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Number of punishments to their asses
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hsei
I'm so glad, so glad
It's finally over
I'm second
You sure got hit
That's quite the difference
Note: This song debuted in 2001 and topped the Japanese Oricon charts as their second biggest hit. Guitarist Ito has appeared in many batsu games as well.
This is the first time that it's a female
Ah, it's Ito. Normally...
Finally, he makes a
normal appearance
Guitarist: Ito Ichiro
Right?
He looks normal here
This is his normal primary occupation
Vocals: Mochida Kaori
As always, just simply
This is a song from a very long time ago!
So true
For a cause without flair
Ah right, Nakai appeared here
Spent money to call Nakai
Budget getting drained, it's so agonizing
The live singing was so awkward
Kissing so many times
Horikita, reading your heart
This feeling is so miserable
Being "repulsive" is not something I recall
Your forehead is the target for the monkey's punch
If you're not going to protect my butt
I won't be able to take any more Thai kicks
So pointless
Even if you desperately try to change, all the faces are the same
Although a hurt Junior is there too
"I want to try it at least once" is what Yagira said
Connected by punishments unknown
So scary
With all their strength
standing on their toes
Disguised
as hosts
Plain Clothes
with no fashion sense
Umemiya
staggered around
A terrible
Furuhata impression
Attack the 5 of them
From Laughter
it becomes insistent
Being forced to see this bad drama
It all started
from a costume change
There was also
some painful asses but
Believe in the young ones
and you'll be exposed, Kiyoshi
In order to not be destroyed
They'll want to watch their backs
They pushed their bodies
as far as this
Even if they run away from the oxygen
It's a lot of fun
Even though Hamada was caught
someone was overjoyed
You can't escape
from the promised slap
All of this
started 10 years ago
There are days
filled with pain too but
Let's all grab
the things we think are painful
And move towards another fun tomorrow!
"Let's take a picture"
"Take a picture"
filled with laughter once more....
Let's make this year
Thank you very much.
We've already crossed into the new year.
Oh!
Happy new year!
What did you guys think?  Did you think they might actually go with Hamada?
I really did.
I did.
Me too;
I kept thinking, "No way, no way," but it felt like they really were going to do it.
I thought they would do it.
Watching that and seeing your joywhat the hell?
We'll keep that footage, I think.
That was crazy.
Even in this new year, that won't be forgotten.
Even in this Year of the Monkey, that will have an effect.
He was going like this the whole time.
I wasn't feeling joy at all.
"Why would you do that to Hamada!?" I was thinking.
That was crazy.
No way.  How in the...?
You were slapping the ground at the end.
"Stop it!  Stop it!  Get your hands off of Hamada!" is what I meant.
You were going like this.
On the infrared camera, you look like Sakai Masaaki.
What in the world?
Why didn't you say it at that part?
I thought it might be getting in the way if I said it there.
It's getting in the way saying it now, too, though.
No, no.
And so, to everyone, please continue to watch Gaki No Tsukai in the year 2016.
This is a work of fiction
and all organization names that appear in it are fictional.