On Gaki no Tsukai,
Matsumoto's 54th Birthday
Some unexpected guests take part
And his partner Hamada will sing too
Excuse me
Oh welcome
Welcome
Happy Birthday!
Yamamura Momiji
Thank you very much Momiji-san
Momiji-san thank you very much
Beautiful today as always
It's Kitty-chan
I remembered,
Congratulations!
You came all the way here
I'm happy to be here
Matsumoto-san,
During meetngs for segments,
He brings you up Momiji-san quite often
"I want to include Momiji-san"
Oh really? That makes me so happy
Matsumoto-san is always on TV when I turn it on
And you said "You're so boring. Go get Momiji-san,
"Wearing a pink Kimono" It made me so happy
That my name came up on a show that I had nothing to do with
What do you like about Momiji-san?
I think Momiji-san has an exquisite balance, as an actress,
She can also do standup. She can switch into comedy with ease.
I see. Such high praises
I'm extremely happy
She lets me use her as a theme for Oogiri (improv)
Like "What is Momiji's body count"
Momiji-san you don't mind that?
Using me like that,
It makes me very happy
Oh really?
Even though it would not be strange for her to tell me to stop
Because you were born, because you're here,
I am also here now
If you weren't there, I,
I wouldn't be here
Is he your father?
The reason I'm on so many variety shows,
Matsumoto-san, it's thanks to you
She's talking now
An uninteresting actress like me,
Thank you for tsukomi-ing me, truly
Although, saying I have a body count of 70 is a bit too much
When I went to greet him back stage,
Even if he's taking a nap, he wakes up
You came right up to me,
And said "You didn't have to get anything!"
And you accepted my silly souvenir
That Matsumoto-san, I like him so much I don't know what to do
The sweet girl you talk about,
When I hear the happy stories
I realise, I realised
I'm jealous of her
I want to become your daughter,
Matsumoto-san's daughter,
Happy Birthday!
She even wrote the song
This is the song, please accept it
She properly wrote everything
When I heard the first chorus, I thought she was singing about her dad
If it wasn't for Matsumoto-san, you wouldn't be here
You allowed me to be born, into the world of variety shows
That's what you mean, he is your parent in that sense
I think of him as a father in that way
You weren't on as many variety shows back then
When I did, I got nervous,
And one time I made a joke, and it fell silent,
And people didn't whether or not to tsukkomi to an actress,
TN: tsukkomi is similar to a retort
But after Matsumoto-san reacted to my joke, everyone realised "Oh it's ok to react to her"
And everyone did,
And for that I'm very grateful
In that sense he's your parent, he brought you to variety
Papa!
Though today you're Mama, Mama
You want to become his daughter right?
He has such a wonderful smile when he talks about his daughter,
"Must be nice" I thought
Maybe I shouldn't talk about her so much anymore
But I enjoy hearing about her. I love his radiant smile when he's talking about her
Did her feelings reach you?
They did, I mean,
She even wrote the notes
For the piano
So nice, you came all the way here for us
It's great for us too
We have you on Gaki sometimes, like at the new years right?
She does a lot
I was able to play Akemi-chan
Oh right, Akemi-chan
Oh! Good evening!
Kyoko-chan, you made it for us?
Kyoko Hamaguchi
Take the flowers, take the flowers
Matsumoto-san, happy birthday!
Thank you very much
Thank you for having me
I never imagined you'd be here
I'm always, I'm totally, a huge fan
Thank you, I'm always cheering for you
I'm very happy, congratulations
Your lipstick is wonderful, it's glossy over here
Yes, I'm not used to it
But speaking of, you've gotten better at makeup recently
Thank you very much
You're becoming more and more feminine
But I'm very glad, thank you for inviting me to this celebration
Thank you for taking the time to come
I'm very nervous!
Oh really?
I'm glad you're here
Do you hang out outside of work?
No, not really
No, not in private
The first I saw,
Matsumoto 54th Birthday
I'm happy
Do you hang out outside of work?
No, not really
No, not in private
The first time,
When we met in a dream,
I was still 10 years old,
You made me smile
20 years since then,
Meeting you for the first time, like I dreamed,
From happiness,
I was nervous,
My heart was beating
I like your hairstyle and your fashion too
Laughing loudly, laughing shyly,
I love all of your shy gestures
And in the future, forever,
Stay the way you are Matsumoto-san
Forever, Forever,
I will love you forever
Brilliant
Amazing
Her range was great
She hit the high notes
You're good at singing
I was super nervous
Kyoko-san, Matsumoto has a nice body now don't you think?
What do you think about that?
There was someone I always train with in my gym
Matsumoto-san kept working on his chest,
We were like
"I wonder how much he can bench"
We had a conversation about that
I'm glad to hear you guys were talking about that
Yes
Thank you very much
It was nice and simple
Her feelings were directly conveyed
Yeah the people who aren't regulars on this show,
I'm glad to be surprised by them
That sort of thing makes you nervous normally
And it's natural to get nervous when singing
Yes
With wrestling, moving around gets rid of the nervousness, but,
You can't really move around, holding the mic
But I'm glad I was able to do my best for this celebration
You hate shiny things
You love to say "Don't call me papa"
Matsumoto 54th Birthday Party
Lastly, his partner Hamada will sing
You hate shiny things
You love to say "Don't call me papa"
You hate small change (coins)
You love working out twice a week
You hate chilled water
You love comedy more than anything
We met at 6 years old
And now I realise you're 54
Go get your physical check-up done
Together we are DownTown
It's hard to sing for your partner
You know everything he likes and dislikes
txt181
And he's at that age now, he should take care of himself
You guys have been together since age 6 after all
48 years!
Half a century in just 2 years
Longer than anyone
Yeah longer than anyone probably
He often tells me to get my physical done
What do you guys think? He should go right?
It makes me nervous
That's the reason?!
You'll be more anxious if you don't go
"A question for Matsumoto-san who knows everything about his partner"
"If you took all of Hamada's adult DVD's what would happen?"
TN (from wikipedia): Oogiri is a form of comedy that focuses on improvisation by providing a funny answer on the spot for a question or thematic topic
You know they should really stop with these Oogiri style questions
All of the questions are on the homepage
You really do love them
Not as much I used to I think
Of course
That's true for you too
Yeah that goes for me too
You would always leave a stack this high at the counter
Not that many, but 2-3
I would buy like 3-4 in the past. Not now though.
Right, not anymore
If I look back, I did throw away a lot of them
Before I threw them away, remember those CD cases?
They were like photo albums, with DVDs
Damn you took this seriously
I did
If I was thinking of throwing one away I would put it back in backwards
Like "under consideration"?
It could've been I was just in the wrong mood at the moment
This guy is an idiot!
Sometimes, you know you go back and look at them
And I would try out the ones I put in backwards
If it's bad then I throw it away,
Yes of course
But sometimes, I really hit the jackpot
A close call
I would go "THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL!" alone at night
I get that
While wanking, while wanking
I would say it while wanking
This guy is an idiot!
This guy is an idiot
If I gathered all of yours my arms would be shaking trying to hold them
That's not true
I think it is
But for you Hamada-san, you don't buy the commerical ones right?
Like I actually buy the ones at the store,
I also go to the store
There you go again. Enough of that.
Are there DVDs they don't sell at the store?
Your collection is like that right? It's all self-produced
It's true!
It's true though!
Is your head alright?
But it's true
What the hell do you mean self-produced?
You make them yourself right?
I don't do that
Really?
Then I guess I was mixed-up
What kind of mix up...
I heard that you did
What did you mix up
The question says take all of them, but I can't
Cause they're self-produced
Self-produced-
You come out with a new one every month
New ones
Hamada-san, your house has a huge screen right?
I don't I don't
I heard you have an A/V room
A/V and AV is confusing though
TN: A/V = Audio Video
AV = Adult Video
Like a real A/V
I don't have anything like that
It's a normal TV
That's what I've heard
Someone just made that up and told you
Then how many do you have in your collection?
How many?
Honestly I think you have 200,000
It's not exactly 200,000...
Then how many?
I don't really know...
No no no there's some I'll throw away, I'll throw them away
Then hurry up and get rid of them. Where do you get rid of them?
Anywhere
Stop speaking like a corpse
Does your wife know about this?
I'm pretty sure she does
Oh, that's like a grey area?
If she sees them, she's not gonna go "What the hell"?
She's not going to look at them. They're in my room.
We don't look at them together like
"Wow this one looks great!"
That's weird
One time I,
I got a phone call during work from my wife,
"Sorry" - My wife is that type, she goes "Sorry",
"The player in the living room was broken, and there was a DVD I wanted to watch"
She decided to use the player in my room,
And on the tray the comes out, there was an erotic one there and she saw it
And these days they print the picture on the DVD
Yeah like the pictures
Like the pictures
So I got a call during work
Those scenarios are tricky
Should I get mad,
Or should I be like "Oh that's fine"
What did you do?
Nothing more or less than that
You're not gonna say "Don't use mine without asking!" of course
I never thought it would pop out
It is a tricky situation
That's all it was
Should we leave?
Let's leave
I'm, kind of sorry
Was that...alright for the ending?
We didn't really say anything bad
That's just how wholesome I am now
I don't even go to brothels
TN: Lotion also means Lube
You used to talk about lotion a lot
Lotion? What about lotion?
Moisturizer?
You used to talk a lot about how you use lube on yourself and stuff.
You don't use it anymore?
Ah, I do use lube
You use it?!
So you do use it
I do
I would put it in my bag when traveling
In the past right?
In the past
I put the whole bottle once in my second bag,
And after work when I got back to the hotel to do the business,
It spilled everywhere inside
My second bag was all slimy
What did you do? I guess throw it out
I stuck my hand inside and got some
You still used it?!
For a moment I thought about sticking it in the bag...
Shut up idiot. Let's go
Together, we are DownTown