1st Time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arrahende
"I'm the One Who Understands you Best!"
"Anyways, You'd Look Great in this Thing" First Summer Uika Edition!!
What did you guys think about this time?
I can't think of what she'd wear normally
It is pretty tough
Her costume image is pretty strong
This time was the only one that's felt difficult
Only this time?
You guys are just the absolute worst at this
Don't include me in this
Ok, just leave him by himself
Tanaka: 11 of the past 13 items were last place
Go to Jinrikisha!!
Production Jinrikisha is a comedian talent agency
You want us to go?
No, no we're part of Yoshimoto
Yoshimoto Creative Agency is the members' agency
A special series on Gaki, where the members buy gifts for guests based on their interests!!
We've not really done too badly
I think you know beforehand who the guest is
No way
As if that's true
Hamada gets this tingling feeling before recording
He figures out who the guest is
That's not true
Let's all be on an even playing field
Anyway, without further ado
Let's welcome today's guest
Please treat me well
First Summer Uika
The Yankii character from Osaka, all over variety shows, The Naniwa Talking Queen, First Summer Uika
Yankii = Rebellious and wild
The Gaki members will choose a top and an accessory to present to her
Matsumoto-san, what did you think?
Was it difficult?
Hmm, I don't know...
I was thinking of that Yankii style, but surprisingly you dress a bit differently
I think we've seen each other about twice outside of work
Yes, once i think
Ah, so you've seen her in casual clothes
At that time, it was kinda like
Is this always how she dresses casually?
Yama-chan, what do you think?
I was quite confident at the start but
Now that I've seen her in person, I'm even more confident
Really?
After seeing how she's dressed today?
Not the clothes, but seeing the person herself, has given me confidence
I have no idea what you're talking about
No idea?
Absolutely no idea
Timed, Typeset & Translated by Inepped
Before the show started, the Gaki members went shopping for First Summer Uika
I don't think she wears Osaka style ladies clothes, like dresses
Harajuku
I think she goes for something more rough, American style
With a cap or something
There's a bunch of Sukajan
Sukajan = A type of souvenir jacket
Haven't you worn one lately?
Lately it's just like, oh I remember when I wore those
I hate that kinda style
I just can't wear it anymore
How about this?
The off the shoulder kind of look
I dunno
Is it too much
She normally has that Kansai, strong woman image
Daikanyama
I think this time I'll try something a little different
That's cute
This looks good but...
I know we're shopping for the show but
Maybe I should buy this for my daughter
I think that Uika-chan is quite fashionable
Kagurazaka
I think she likes flashy and bright colours
This is cute
Last time with Riki Choshu, both of your items were bottom
That was a misjudgment on my part
I feel truly bad about that
There's so much stuff which would suit First Summer Uika-chan
Ikebukuro
This is cute! These pumpkin shorts, this is so First Summer Uika
This would definitely suit her
She'd be so happy wearing this
This would suit her perfectly!!
No way
I'm super confident with this
This is so cute!
I wish my daughter liked stuff like this
This is super cute
I'm a 53 year old man though
Finding an accessory is gonna be difficult
Shibuya
This wouldn't work, right?
Nah
This is pretty good
What's written on it?
With the sparkles and glitter, I can't tell at all
Its a bow and a tie and a tail?
It's an elephant
Shop Manager
You can press the button on here and
It sounds like a pig
Shop Manager
Its pretty good
It's 1,000 Yen (approx. £6/$7)
Shop Manager
The best items will be taken home by First Summer Uika. The worst will have to pay
We really have to pay out of pocket
We have to pay out of pocket
How much have I had to pay already?
Which of their tops will First Summer Uika like.
First up is Matsumoto
Go ahead
To be honest
This time I did the opposite to usual
I didn't worry too much about it
When I spotted this
I thought this was it
So it didn't take long
To pick this out
See
What?
My eyes hurt
16,280 Yen (approx. £100/$115)
My eyes hurt!
It's a long cardigan
This?
Hamada is mimicking Kuidaore Taro, a famous mascot in Osaka who has stripy clothes.
Kuidaore means “to ruin oneself by extravagance in food.”
No!
Who's trying to ruin himself?
It's Kuidaore
How's this Kuidaore, shut up idiot!
You can say
I'm fine being Kuidaore!!
Can we see it on?
Look
It's nice and colourful
It looks super nice!!
What is it made of?
It's like a towel material
You can put this on after a hot bath
You can also wash the dishes with it
Wash it with the dishes
This is bad Matsumoto-san!!
Uika-san please put it over there
She doesn't seem too pleased with that
She's just holding back
When they open the bag
When a lady opens a bag, you can tell by the look on her face
I don't think that happened
They let out a "wow"
That sounds a little dirty
Next up is Hamada
I pictured her wearing
American style clothes
Maybe a sukajan but a little different than mine
That kind of feeling
Was he talking about the sukajan or himself?
I was saying a different sukajan style than mine
Well, it's not that flashy
4,990 Yen (approx. £30/$35)
Do you not think this colour suits her?
A little oversized
Well, it does suit her
Nice and casual
You'd want one of these in the autumn
A more male style jacket
Ah, leave it open
I don't like it that much
It's not about you guys
The Osakan lady yankii's would like this
It looks good like that
What are you on about?
Next to show off his top, Endo
You have that Osaka kind of image
That strong Kansai image
But that's not all you are
I understand that you have a more cute side
As if!!
I expressed that with these clothes
There it is
8,910 Yen (approx. £54/$62)
Rather than the style of your image
This shows off a more childish side
Gap
Gap = Gap Moe is when one does something contradictory to their usual character
Looks like it's time for the Osaka Expo
With a dress
It's easier to see what it's like once it's on
I'll try it on
When presenting clothes
Gap is what I hate the most
I get it but this one is ok
Everything ok?
Then please show us
Cute!
That's a stormy face
It looks pretty uncomfortable
I really like it
I think her face betrays it
Next up is the confident Hosei
Uika-chan
Her skin is beautiful
That makes me happy
She has this doll like image
He's just fishing for points
A doll?
So you're shooting for a doll like image?
Look at the face she's pulling!!
That face!
9,999 Yen (approx. £60/$70)
That's worse than what she's wearing!
Here it is, here it is!
I've already won
It's pretty
Leave it for a doll
You've really done it this time Hosei-san
Let's see it please
Looking good, looking good!!
What era do you think we're in?
This isn't about era
You look like @#@#!
Last to present his top is Tanaka
If it's Uika-chan, she will definitely say this:
"Ah, Tanaka-san, you've opened a new door for me"
Ah, scary, stop saying weird things
It's men's style clothing
What?
Once again
Scary Scary Scary
6,030 Yen (approx. £36/$42)
This is bad! This is bad! This is bad!
Enough already
Uika-chan
Looks good in men's clothing
A face for the Takarazuka Revue
Takarazuka Revue is a Japanese all-female musical theatre troupe
With this you can attack it head on
See
It looks great!
It looks like she's ready for battle!
When's this for?
Halloween
If that's the case, anything would've been ok!!
Among these, which will First Summer Uika choose as her favourite?
Let's start then Uika-san, which of these is your favourite?
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
It's this one!
And there it is!
Really?!
Of course it is
Can you tell us the reason?
In truth
I'm Hamada, in plain clothes
Hamada isn't even Hamada anymore
I wear a lot of American style casual clothes
Ah, is that so
Really?
She has surprisingly poor taste
Endo
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
In 2nd place is?
This one!
I went quite aggressive
and agressive was 2nd place!!
You guys were guessing right?
Downtown were guessing right?
Of course
When I was young, I would always wear something like this
I knew it would suit her
I like it so much I will buy it later
I'M SO HAPPY!!
Let's move on to 3rd place
Please
Please!  Please!  Please!
Endo
Hosei
Tanaka
This one!
Really?!
Really?
You gotta be kidding me!!
Well
Out of the three, it's the most usual
I like the form and feel of it
Nobody has suggested anything like it before right?
No not really
See, I've opened a new door
So, which of these two is the worst!?
The worst is...?
Choose properly
Endo
Hosei
It's this!
I thought so
It's just creepy
This one's impossible
After wearing it yourself?
I'd never want to wear it again
What's the difference between them?
Not that much really
Don't you think that's cute?!
I think I'd rather...
not comment
See it's that bad!!
It's definitely the worst!!
I think this one suits me more
The other doesn't suit you, right?
In this case, the one in last is better
It's hard to explain but
This one's not even worth last place
It's so ugly it's sad
That's the worst praise
Are you serious?
Endo's is definitely worse
Regardless of the reason, Hosei has to pay a hefty price
Next, First Summer Uika sees their accessories.
To start is the winner of the tops, Hamada
This is like a mini sukajan
They kind of go together
It was in the same store
Sukajan?
I think this is the perfect accessory, I'm confident in that
It's pretty small
A mask?
Yes, considering the current situation
What's on it?
1,540 Yen (approx. £9/$11)
A dragon
A mask wasn't a bad idea
You look the dangerous type
No she doesn't, it suits her
It's too big
It's hard to breathe in right?
It's hot right?
It's suprisingly not
Rather it's quite nice and warm
It's too big right?
You're fixated on this aren't you
The loser of the first round, Hosei
Excuse me
It's big
It is quite large
It is an accessory, right?
It is, please have a look
Her face kind of clouded over
6,490 Yen (approx. £39/$46)
What's that?
There's some sort of picture on it
Bears?
Is this to go together with the dress?
Is it a matching accessory?
But the dress was last!!
He was confident when he was buying it though
Of course
Were there other patterns?
There were different colours
But they all had bears on them
I think you went to the wrong store
Next up is Matsumoto's accessory
This one was more of a challenge than the top
The top was definitely a enough big challenge
You'll definitely like this
That looks bad
What is it?
It's a beetle!
8,580 Yen (approx. £51/$60)
It's not!
DJ Koo or Koo Jun-yup is a South Korean DJ
Even DJ Koo wouldn't wear that
This is more...
Furuta Arata
Furuta Aruta is a Japanese actor
The glitter and sparkles suit Uika
It'll make her shine
Looks good
LAME!!
It looks great!
Stop pulling that face!!
How about wearing it slightly tilted?
That's it, cute cute cute!
It looks great!
It's Yattāman
Yattāman is an anime from the 70s
Next up, the in form Tanaka
I'm really confident in this accessory
Really?
I'm grateful you liked the earlier item, I think this will work alongside it
What is it?
It's a frontal covering
Take this seriously
3,632 Yen (approx. £22/$25)
Wait, wait, it's not like that!
You wear it over a skirt as an accessory
Move it to the side
It looks like the same pattern as my hat
See!
I can see it now
You can wear it with a flashy skirt
and it gives a contrast in colours
You can also wear it up here
Here
On the front?
That looks really weird
When are you gonna wear this?
Bikkuri Donkey is a Japanese steak house
It looks like a bib from Bikkuri Donkey
Last up is Endo
I also thought
a mask was perfect
But a normal mask with a dragon on doesn't have much impact
I thought
With this mask you can really make an impact
Look at her face, it's clouding over
3,632 Yen (approx. £22/$26)
I think this really has a great impact
This is just... no
Can you turn this way?
It's not like any other mask
Who would want to wear this?!
It's easy to breathe in right?
It keeps poking me in the eye
I think we should swap out Cocorico next time
They're just messing around
How will First Summer Uika rank these accessories?
Your favourite accessory is...?
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
This one!
Thank you!
There he goes again!
It's obvious why, mine's normal
C'mon, really?
I think the whole country
will agree that this is the right conclusion this time
What about earlier?
Earlier, the tops were a lot closer
It was closer
Yeah it was a harder decision
Mine's normal, that's why
None of the others are normal
Really? No way!
Regardless, I'm happy to take this home
It's a cute accessory
It's still too big though
I can just tighten it
So, let's move on to 2nd place
In 2nd is?
This one!
Endo
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Why?!
I told you so
You're really flying high Tanaka-san
I didn't expect anything from you at all
Sorry about that
That's ok
Finding an accessory to wear over a skirt
and one that's really cute
and especially good for the summer
It'll be sweaty
The recipient herself likes it
It'll be super sweaty
The receiver herself likes it
You can just dry it like this
Right?!
The smell of that being half-dried, "wow"
It'll be fine
Endo
Hosei
Matsumoto
Next, in 3rd place...
This one!
I'm saved!
Bears, really?
You're definitely lying!!
The bears are quite cute
Yama-chan finally
Thank you
I'm in a PANIC!!
PANIC! PANIC!!
I didn't think it'd be this hard
This is bad!
Breathe
I'm panicking too
Which of these will First Summer Uika consider the worst!?
The worst is...?
Please I'm begging you
Imagine putting that on, "Good morning"
Endo
Matsumoto
This one!
You're that happy?
Really?
Of course
You gotta stop being in the bottom places
Can you imagine showing up somewhere wearing that
Who are you!?
This one was a bit closer to what I'd want
Like an American style hat, but...
The time will come!!
What about the mask?
I don't really get what the thinking is
You think we're living in Mad Max?!
With that said, Endo has to pay out
So, how was today?
I'm really touched with how you were thinking of me
Everyone thought quite hard
I now think a bit better of Tanaka-san
This time you were pretty close
We were all suprised
On the other hand I'm quite worried about you Endo-san
You didn't want it personally
I don't think anyone would ever want it
Really?
I thought it was cool