Murakami Shoji's classroom series started without anyone wanting it
He comes in and does whatever he wants
And when the ratings are so low, it's too much to handle
What on Earth did he prepare now?
What was it?
That guy...
It's Matador Class
That's right... By Shoji
When the DX was over the other day
During a break he told me "Hama chan, I'm counting on you"
What the...?
I don't want to say this...
But I want to complain to Sanma san (famous comedian)
Via Suga san
What do you think?
But I think nobody can help us
Let's just quit, then?
What about raitings?
They are awful
We need Sanma san to watch edited versions of our previous classrooms
It's getting sunny, though
Something's written!
"Bullfighter class is here"
This cardboard is so wet
It must have been out here for some time
It's getting cold, too...
With the wind blowing...
No one expected it to be this cold...
First thing in the morning comes this guy, dressed up like for parade...
Wait do you hear him?
His voice is so loud!
That's so lame... Is that a kick scooter?
I'M SORRY!
They wouldn't let me on the motorway
I have no idea why they didn't let me drive there
Well that's unfortunate
I've made myself get here, that's why I'm a bit late
It's alright
The annoying man who came by kick scooter, was no other than Murakami Shoji
The weather's bad today, so it might be a bit of a bad day location-wise
What are talking about? today's weather is great
You sure?
I always pick days with the best weather
We're not so sure about this...
Today is the ninth installment in our series
The ninth one?
That's right. You haven't achieved anything, none of you
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THIS?
Is there anything funny, Matsumoto? I'm sorry
Your voice is especially strong today
I developed it
Is that so?
Listen up
This time call me Master
Master, okay
Hamada! Yes!
Are you trying to die?
Why's that?
THE HELL'S THAT RED THING?
Do you know that bull's most hated color is red?
The voice is so loud...
Fine, I'll talk in a quite voice
No, that's alright, please excuse us
You'll be the first one to be killed!
That's dangerous!
What were you thinking?
I'm sorry
Do you understand? You'll be dead in a bullfight
Did you come empty-handed, 'cause you didn't know anything?
Go ahead and put in 2 or 3 extra pieces of intellect
Came here with nothing
"Thank you teacher! I became a great bullfighter!"
Why at least one of you can't get involved?
Get involved?
Listen, you
Do you guys only care about viewer raitings?
I see
Do you want to make me disappear with your "great power"?
What do you mean?
Do you mean that I need to tell you about it?
We don't have much time, so remember
Stand in line right here
Here
Our first training is
When we think of bullfighting, we think about red things
I see
Besides...
the bullfighter...
that man...
he'll get excited
And bulls think
"Which one of us is going to stab you?"
So, that's what we're supposed to sense
Do you understand?
Do I really need
to explain you all the elementary basics?
Don't you get excited about the red stuff?
Check your qualities as a bullfighter first
You may be wondering why are we doing it
But that's to control bullfighter's excitement
Put your hands behind your back
And hold them behind your back
Firstly
Are you alright?
"Touch the crotch. Excitement inspection"
Are you all fine there?
What are you doing?
Ma-chan?
Is Tanaka alright?
Hey, you
That was your teacher's **** inspection
SO, DON'T QUESTION IT!!!
It's all under my control!
But how can we get excited from that?
Let's continue. It will get worse
Get worse?
I tried to use more suitable words
I want you to feel it
You really have hard time understanding the basics... I'm sorry...
STAY STILL!
I'LL BE BACK!
It's so difficult to understand what he wants...
Let's wait and see...
I still don't get it...
Here!
Sports shorts
It's definitely different from the last one. These red shorts...
Alright, let's commence
Are you alright?
I'm counting on you! What is she doing!?
LOOK!!!
Look closely! I see no point in doing this...
I understand that they are red, but...
Are you all good?
You won't see this often on TV these days
Alright, that's enough, thank you
Are you alright?
She did her best
Are you okay?
What's that?
I feel a bit sticky...
Sticky? He means his hands
I mean sweat
Let's head for next training
We don't have much time
Time? I think you woory about it too much
Bullfighting unions are on strike now
Then, don't we have plenty of time?
As a bullfighter, you have to dodge the rampaging bulls
And fascinate the spectators
This is the bull
On average
It weights 560 kg
Endo, try it
Do your best
Listen
Use blanket for now
Alright?
It's still early to use the red one
Hold it like that
Go for it!
Do it splendidly
I'm ready
I see
Just like a bull
That's dangerous...
He really did it with all his might
These bullfighters are really desperate
That's right...
Matsumoto went next
Do it with more passion
I don't really understand what you mean...
Endo did really well
I think the bull might get exhausted...
Again with full force...
Here it comes!
That's hilarious
Is he done already?
Matsumoto...
Come here...
Look out, he's not finished yet
It's dangerous. He'll go out with full force, be careful!
'Cause he's a bull
Here it comes
He breathes so much...
He's definitely out of breath
Are you fine?
What?
Master?
I'll do it next. Please!
Do it with style!
I'll do it now. I'm ready. That's a bit scary...
Hamada, it's alright
You're fine
We thought that everyone will do it
We still didn't practice it
We've had enough
Are you sure?
We all want to go through full training
I'll show an example
Because it's dangerous, I don't want...
Your family to feel sad
Me...
Yamasaki
Do the bull
But I have no experience...
Do it
I actually want to see it
Yamasaki, do the bull
Grab it
Freeze and become a bull
Everyone, give me a hand
Here
What shall we do?
We're loading it?
Wait a moment!
Please, wait!
That's right, bull's actual weight is around 500 kg
We need to make it realistic
Please, wait!
Master, but you didn't have this weight
You didn't have this...
This weight
It's not a weight
It's called real bull
That face...
Do it
But... It's not a weight
CAN YOU EVEN DO ANYTHING?
For 9 episodes, can't you do at least something?
You only complain and ask to be forgiven
DO IT!
Here he comes!
Go for it!
What is he doing?
The hell's he doing?
What's that?
What on Earth?
You can't do anything
Good grief...
For those who cannot become bullfighters
There will be a training for a different profession
That's no good
I'm disappointed
To climb that hill...
Was quite difficult
for a matador
If you can't do anything Matador-related, you're out from this
You
Come here
Let's go down the other way?
What do you mean?
You have only this way
What's that? Let's do Carmen
Take it
I'll do Matador. IMPOSSIBLE!
I SEE AND JUDGE. CAN I BE WRONG???
I've been doing it for 32 years, so I can tell when one is no good
Who do you think you are?
Big brother, sorry
He said nothing
Anyway, put this on
Put it on from below
For your hands
Does anyone know the proper way to hold these?
No idea
Really no clue
I wear a costume, please...
Fine, take these off
Do your best!
Music, start!
Do you know it?
No idea...
I am!
Ah, me!
(he just says "Spanish-sounding" words in Japanese)
Cafe!
Me!
SAY CAFE AND ME!
OVER HERE! ME!
Say "me over here"!
Say that
But, I couldn't think of it...
WELL THINK!
Think?
TURN YOUR BRAIN TO FULL SPEED AND SAY
Anyway, let's have a break
Let's have a break. Can I take this off, Master? Fine
That was fast...
Is that alright?
That was quite funny
Really? We never had a break on this level... Thank you very much!
Take a seat
Yes, we chose our seats
Today
We'll have a bull, that I've defeated earlier
Really?
It's very expensive
All the bulls that I defeat are prepared that way, so my friends can cut their slices and take them home
I never heard that
That's how it's done in Spain
We'll behave today, okay?
This is the one I got today
Really?
Thank you
Looks delicious
This is the really tasty stuff
Here
It's 100 grams
Yes..
From super...
Here
Thank you very much!
That's impressive
Master!
MASTER!!!
Thank you
That's enough...
Master?
Enjoy your meal
Eat well
Master!
Shut up
But I don't have anything...
Just as soon you gave me the plate...
You want some? Yes!
Is it tasty?
It is
It's very good
Master!
But that's pig feet...
You're 10 years too young to eat beef
Why?
Your "why" will be the end for you
"Announce - We're informing customers coming to the Seaside Park"
"The Seaside Park will soon be closed"
You heard that?
We'll be doing maneuvering section
Ma-chan
What?
I heard you had
a party the other night?
That's right
Only with my juniors
Ma-chan, you've gotten distant
I also wanted to congratulate you
Thank you very much, really
I wasn't able to give you anything
That's alright
Ma-chan. Yes?
He's calling you
I don't really need anything...
I'm totally fine
Actually... Yes?
I don't want Hama chan or Tanaka to know about this
Here, actually
These are by my wife's relatives, organically grown vegetables
Can you take it home for your wife?
Today? Yes
Thanks a lot
Actually
frankly speaking
today...
I prepared some fried rice
Eat it
with your wife
I will
He made some fried rice?
That's so dirty...
I have nothing else
So...
One moment
Actually, look
I'm releasing a DVD!!!
Is this for real?
Yes, my manager said that I have to wait a bit longer, but I'm just dying to get it out already
Well, didn't Hama chan release one?
Pretty much everyone released one
That's why
it's like a good opportunity to ride this wave
And one more
Here it is!
Gag bottles for soy sauce
80,000 yen per one with diamonds scattered on them
Is it true? Here
I've sold 4 already!
That's great!
The president of the company I know bought them all
Buy one
Buy one?
But he canceled one, so I've sold three for now
To tell the truth
Learn how to collect the flying bouquet
After a spectacular defeat of the bull
The bull's already fallen
Once he's down
Hundreds of thousands in the audience
Will shout "stunning!" And then...
Will throw donations down to matador
Offerings? Ah, yes
I have too many things on my mind, that's why I made a mistake
I'm sorry
I meant offerings
Let's go, have some practice
It's quite hold...
That's true
What a great weather!
That's so tasty!
Let's just eat it
It's grilled very well!
It's hot
Delicious...
HEY!?
They're all eating
And a sausage...
Tasty!
Hey!
I was the only one who went there
What are you doing?
Oh, thanks a lot!
HEY!!!
Look, Matsumoto
That's not a tray
I'm sorry
What shall we do?
I knew it
It's only me who wants to do everything properly
With this, you'll get less than 0.1% of the viewership rating
I don't know if I can do it with you guys anymore...
I want to exceed 10% at least once!
That's still too low...
You're really are
Once you catch what's thrown at you, you'd want to take it back to your family
That's why it's the last training
Hamada, why don't you try?
What shall I do?
Catch what I'll be throwing at you
What is going to be thrown?
Let's have a look at it
Are you throwing these?
Yes. Because you're the most experienced here, wouldn't you show us how it's done?
I won't play along with that trick anymore
No, no, no
We can't even think of doing anything bad
No matter how many times you say it, Hamada, you'll do it
Because I'm in a bit of a dispute with Yoshimoto (agency)
Which concerns my goods
And the percentages that I've told seem to be different
I want you to tell me
You think if all of you will ask me, I'll change my mind?
Really, please, show us!
Fine, if you're sincere
This time
Throw it high from above
High, right?
Hamada, try it
From above?
Okay
Awesome!
That's great!
Great!
What are you doing?
Don't throw them all like that
That's money
That's money, hey!
Ouch!
That's impressive
It hurts!
So, great
Stop that! I see...
That's how it goes
Stop that
Don't ever come back!
That's a single man...
You've done him?
Absolutely
At time like this, a bull can only say
Mooo
That's enough!