(This is a recap of part 1. Skip to 2:10 for the start of this one)
I'm hungry!
You okay?
Oh shit, I'm starving!
I wonder why
I really did it now
Should've ordered more!
"Even after three stores, there's no end to their hunger!"
They've got lots of stuff!
"Next restaurant, with over 1000 locations in Japan,"
"ice cream specialist, 31 ice cream"
"With lots of variety,"
"and whatever size you would like"
"What awaits these hungry five?"
Would you like to try these samples?
The senpai should try them first
What are you waiting for?
You can have this one
No sorry I'm the kouhai (junior)
No no no take it, take it
This is our recommendation
Senpai
"The hungry five devour their samples"
"Hamada raises concerns"
Hold on, what will we do here?
There's lot's of variety
For one person, this is a lot of volume
excuse me a second
What, what do you mean?
It's just,
you wanna eat this by yourself?
If you wanna eat i-
I really do wanna eat it but,
I have too many cavities
Yeah tha-
Stop lying!
"Hungry Drive, Restaurant #4"
So what? We share it?
We can't really split this
We can't split this,
Matsumoto-san you like this right?
Yeah I uh yeah
I could eat 1
Is that so?
Of course, go ahead
There's no way,
you guys don't want some?
Well I'm having some
I am-
Of course, of course
"Nobody here agrees that they don't want any"
OK then order some, order some
Alright
Order this
I uhhh
Which has the most volume?
This Banana-Browny royal does
That seems good
Hell yeah!
I asked which has the most volume!
No, no
That's all you did?
All you did was ask?
You have to eat that one
No no I uhhh
Berry Berry Strawbery
Ok order confirmed
What size would you like?
King size
King?!
King size is-
King size?
King is uhh
I don't wanna get too cocky
the regular size
What container would you like?
The paper cup please
the paper cup?
Let's go!
"Everyone ordered their favourite ice cream"
"This is what these 4 ordered"
"They all got the regular size in a cup"
"Tanaka's order remains"
Tanaka you're tall so get a big one
Yeah you're the tallest one so,
Tallest?
Get at least the double scoop
Get that one with 6!
If anything you should get the cake!
Yeah the cake
"Minnie the Mouse Heart"-
Hmmmmmmm
I could get the cake huh?
You're tallest
Get them to write "TANAKA" on it
But, it's not my birthday right?
April
When is it?
26th of April
That's close
Since it's passed by,
the strawberry cheese cake
What size, sir?
King size
King size, OK
The cone cup or waffle cone-
The waffle cone
The double right?
Double?!
King size
Double of King?
King size waffle
Can I stick my face in this?
No, sorry
"Looking at all this ice cream, Matsumoto is at the limit!"
I wanna eat it!
"The ice cream is ready!"
"You're large ice cream is ready!"
You're so lucky dude
The King size
That was mine?
Yes
Cause you're the tallest
Please enjoy!
You're the tallest in many ways
That's sweet!
Here I go!
I could eat so many
Are you hiring part-timers?
We are
You are?!
I'll talk to my wife about it
I could just keep eating!
Right?
Should you order more?
I'm honestly thinking about it
Oh really?
Endo should get more
You're finishing that quickly
I could totally go for seconds
You should get a double or something
No uhh-
Or a king waffle
I'm being serious here
Is he actually being serious?
Yeah I think so
Not just for TV or anything
He said not just for TV
What if you order a double, I'm saying
Not just for TV
Endo?
You should hurry up and order
Oh boy, can I?!
Wow really?
You're really getting it?
Well done, Endo
What should I get?
Would you like to sample our most popular item?
Endo!
Shozo!
SHOZO!
Look up Endo, look up!
Woah what's this?
Our most popular item
This is?
Yes
Wooah!
Eat it man!
I can have this?
Yes please
Really?
You're lucky man, you're confident!
"Endo confidently acquires the sample"
"He enjoys his ice cream"
Tasty
Thank you!
" 'I want some too!', "
"Matsumoto can't stop licking!"
Would you like to try some too?
She's talking to Matsumoto-san
Matsumoto-san?
Who are you waving to?
You're waving to Tsu-tsun? (staff member)
He's a staff member!
Me and him are like,
Me and him are like, best friends
Cause you called him handsome! (Episode 1104)
You're barely...
I like it when it's melted a bit
I see
Yeah I'm really loving this
I see you're just making it tastier
It's already finished!
Damn it, I'm done!
No more
"Only Tanaka is left"
You don't wanna eat that?
You don't wa-
What the hell did you say?
You're eating slowly
If you wanted to eat it, you'd be faster
This is so damn good
Really?
Yeah
You wanna try some?
No no that's ok
"It seems they got hungry while waiting for him"
"Then, finally"
You're done eating?
Yay!
Yes!
That was great!
Matsumoto eat it already
There's a lot on there
Wow, you're lucky!
So lucky!
Thank you
Here I go!
"They head towards their next restaurant"
"After the 4th restaurant, they should not be as hungry ..."
I'm STARVING!
Hungry!
Yeaaah I'm kinda hungry
If I don't eat something now...
"All they can talk about is their hunger"
(idle chatting)
Now that I think about, Baskin Robbins is great huh?
Yeah it is
We should go back and do it again
There's gonna be traffic now
Really?!
Yeah I uhh
I looked it up, earlier
Ah just in case we tried again right?
If 100% means you're really full, Endo what would say you are?
2%
Same for me
2%?
Matsumoto-san?
I don't really have that sort of conception
"The eternally hungry 5 drive to their next destination"
Tanaka you're pretty full after that ice cream right?
No no, uhh, not at all
You were having a great conversation,
and I'm just so hungry, right?
I didn't know you're hungry
So I didn't wanna interrupt
Didn't hear anything about your hunger
I was just hungry that whole conversation
What would you eat if you could have anything?
A large katsu curry
Seriously?
Yes
large katsu curry
large?
An extra-large if possible
What is your full percentage?
Honestly ...
0%
Really?
Yes
"Up ahead,
Even after all that-
"Up ahead, there is a GO GO Curry"
There you go Tanaka
So goddamn lucky!
You said katsu curry LOL!
I wish I was that lucky!
Katsu Curry!
Do they have it?
They do yeah
They do, they do
An extra-large
"Tanaka does a 'guts pose' at the sound of curry:
"Will their hunger finally end?"
"And then"
There it is
I hope they can do it (extra large)
yeah hopefully
Thank you for the food!
Let's fill our stomachs!
"Too much for a man" Katsu curry?
Let's go!
"The next restaurant, with 41 locations"
"With plenty of volume, the roast katsu curry"
"A surprise scene when they enter the store ..."
Oi!
Tanaka!
They have an extra large!
Wow they have it!
You're so goddamn lucky!
It's 5 dishes in one!
They might not have it anymore
Yeah they might not have it
Do you still have this?
Yes we do
"Tanaka can't help but smile"
Alright then you're getting that
"Major Katsu"
Tanaka!
C'mon select it
Just check it out man
Yeah it's this item here
We all wanna eat too
You said you wanted this
You really did say you wanted this
Give this to them
I might challenge myself too
OK yeah let's go!
It's sold out!
Sold out
I'm not satisfied with this!
I can't believe it sold out just that moment!
You got the last one
So lucky!
Snatched last one!
I snatched it!
"The 4 order from the healthy class, instead of the world champion class"
I want sushi next
I could go for 100 pieces
That sounds good
Could go for 300
That's great
"The hungry five get their curry"
This looks delicious!
"The 4 enjoy the rich taste of their healthy class curry, though lacking in volume"
We can get extra cabbage?
I'm grateful for that!
Tasty
Yeah, delicious
"They enjoy their curry like no other two syllable word exists"
"Tanaka's world champion class curry arrives"
"Major Curry - World Champion Class"
"Volume fit for a champion - 2.5kg of food"
"Five times the volume of the healthy class"
Oi
Face your reality!
Tanaka it's here!
Face your reality
It's here Tanaka
It's great isn't it? You said you wanted this
Yeah I didn't expect this
His dreams came true
Yeah
I'm so hungry
OK let's go!
Tanaka...
He's not touching it at all
What happened?
Thank you for the meal!
Is it OK I get to have all this?
Of course man
You said you wanted it, so eat it
yeah honestly
That's delicious
Delicious
Tasty?
Tasty! Yup, tasty...
Damn it I'm still not full
Forget the cabage, eat the curry!
Eat the cutlets
You're not hungry?
I am, super hungry
Then eat it
I saying eat the cutlets
The curry
I'm telling you eat the cutlets!
What happened, Tanaka?
What happened?
I like to leave the best parts for last
Just try the cutlets though
Yeah, yeah you're right
What happened, Tanaka?
What do you mean?
It's just, your fork isn't moving
Dude you should just eat the weiners all at once, with your fork
That's the easiest way to eat them
Take the weiner first, for now
Like this?
Take more, more
Could you go for another?
If you can, get another
Can you?
Can you or not?
He can
OK yeah just eat that
Eat it hurry
You're hungry right?
Eat it, eat them all
Put it in your mouth
This in my mou-
The people outside got scared
I will eat this
Delicious!
Right?
See!
Delicious
Eat the cutlets Tanaka
There's no point if you don't
Cause you ate the weiners
Cause I wanted Katsu curry
Yeah exactly
Eat the cutlets
C'mon you can eat them
What are you gonna do man, quit?
What do you mean quit?
You gonna quit?
You can't eat anymore?
No of course not
Really?
I'm gonna really dig into this
"The four eat at a good pace, just waiting for Tanaka"
I want us to take our last bite at the same time
That's why we're watching you
We have to match your pace
Yeah I wanna eat faster!
C'mon man
Yeah
Eat it faster
He's just doing that same thing
You've been digging in that same place!
Seriously Tanaka, what's with you?
You're full aren't you?
Stop making a fuss, I'm trying to eat here!
We're all waiting for you man
What are you doing? Eat it
He's not eating the roux
I don't like that one weiner by itself, just eat it
I refuse
"I refuse"?!
"I refuse"?
He said "I refuse"
"I refuse"?!
Ask him Hamada-san,
ask him what he means
Just eat the weiner man!
Tanaka what's with you?
Eat that weiner!
I will not!
Why not?
Cause I'm so damn full!
I'm so goddamn full!
Please forgive me, I am full!
I won't eat anymore!
Thank god!
This sucked!
So tough!
Thank god, I drank so much water
Thank god!
The weiner ... what the hell was this guy saying?!
"What the hell is he saying" I thought
I had that episode, didn't I?
(Tanaka's Breakdown)
Our family had a small incident cause of that
What happened?
It wasn't anything too bad
That really showcased your acting right?
Mitani Kouki called you after that right?
"A fantastic performance" he said
After that,
I always watch this show of course,
But I was away for that broadcast, so I didn't watch it real time
I was planning on watching it next evening,
It was during the spring break,
My oldest son, 7 years old, recorded it,
"Tanaka's Breakdown"
He watched it by himself
And I do a lot in that episode right?
Like I said I was gonna fuck that girl after leaving Don Quijote
And he said that and thought,
"Dad is having an affair!"
Cause he's just 7 right?
Yeah exactly right?
He doesn't understand it's a skit
Right?
Exactly
He thought it was like a documentary
He thought it would make mom depressed if he told her,
He just held it in, "Dad is having an affair!"
But it got too much for him,
He didn't know how to tell his mom about this without hurting her
But his mom explained, this is a Gaki no Tsukai skit
This is a skit
Explained its a comedy show?
Explained it's a comedy show
Dad is not having a breakdown, so calm down please
So he calmed down, but,
I had that bit where I yelled at that guy right?
Like I really laid into him
And, he understood that it's just a skit,
Kids leave their toys around right?
Normally he doesn't listen when I tell him to tidy up,
But recently, when I tell him.
he starts cleaning up so fast!
He thinks you're gonna have a breakdown right?
He thinks I might start yelling
You should go all out
Go in the washroom, blacken your teeth, blacken your nails,