The first in the series on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende! Chiki Chiki, who is the true leader of Morisanchu? Rubik's Cube in a sauna battle!
Matsumoto, what do you think of this?
Well
T/N: Morisanchu is an all female comedy trio.
Thing is, it seems with Morisanchu...
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
It seems that they don't even know who is the leader anymore
Yamasaki Hosei
Who cares who it is
Originally
It seems they decided that the fat one is the leader
"The fat one"?
Recently though, they've all become fat
That's right
Then they decided the ugly and fat one will be the leader
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
But all of them are, so...
All of them?
All of them
Yes, I agree
Let's get started then with the introduction!
Yeah!
Morisanchu, welcome!
Come on in!
Oh, but wait...
The atmosphere is so gloomy...
The hell is up with all of you?!
Current leader
Kazuko Kurosawa
Miyuki Oshima
Morisanchu
Recently unable to restrain from fighting
Tomoko Murakami
m 68 404 l 578 404 578 442 68 442
Hard to look at you guys
Seriously though, I can't follow such a leader
I don't even think of you as a leader, you know
In terms of age, she's only 1 year older
Oh really?
Excuse me for a moment
Do you need a leader?
Of course we do
If I'm the leader,
then I think everything would be sorted out!
No way!
If I'm the leader,
then I think everything would be sorted out!
It's not sorted out at all
It ain't sorted out at all
It's almost as if...
Tensions are really high right now, aren't they?
I'm just saying that I can't accept it
I won't accept it if one of these two becomes the leader
Why the hell not? I refuse to accept you
You just happened to get married by chance, right?
My marriage has nothing to do with this!
Oi oi oi!!
Ahhh!
What is with this strength?!
Stop!
What the hell are you doing, you bastard?!
Oh no, oh no!!
The hell you doing?!!
I was helping you!
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
Hey!!
What the hell are you doing?!
Hamada!!
What were you doing?
And you, you should oppose him!
It's okay to not be okay with that!
I'd like to settle this, once and for all since you coincidentally got married
My marriage has nothing to do with this!
All because your husband is filthy rich, ain't he?!
You shouldn't say things like that...
Stop it!
Kurosawa!
Morisanchu in a destructive crisis!
Gaki no Tsukai to the rescue with a game!!
Morisanchu, after reaching their ninth year since debut, Gaki no Tsukai will save them from their destructive crisis!
Credits
Typesetter: Nigel
Translator: Oolong (https://clippy.moe)
QC: Bipedal
Downtown's
Gaki no
Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Downtown's
Gaki no
Tsukai ya Arahende!!
ヽ(´ー｀)ノ https://thesilentlibrary.xyz ヽ(´ー｀)ノ
No way!!
I WANT TO BE THE LEADER!!
So, Matsumoto
Yes!
To start it off, let's explain the rules
Yes yes yes
Over there to the right is a sauna
Ah, a sauna, yes
All three will enter the sauna together
Rules
Whoever finishes their Rubik's Cube the fastest
will become Morisanchu's true leader! (Time limit one hour)
The person who finishes their Rubik's Cube the fastest is the winner
I see!
I understand
Escape Button
If this button is pressed during the battle, that person may
take a break from the sauna as many times as they want!
Narrator: Noda Keiichi
During the battle, there is an Escape Button inside the sauna
If pressed, they may take a break from the sauna as many times as they want
When that happens, we'll support them with all of our might!
In the Case of an Escape
Gaki no Tsukai members will support with all their might!
We will support them!
We will support them
Do your best!
Thank you
Please give it your all
Let's do it
Oshima, are you okay?
You're not okay
Oshima, what happened?
What happened?
We're going to start soon
Come on
It's okay
Kurosawa
Murakami
Oshima
Those who leave the sauna while holding the white flag
will immediately drop out of the competition!
In addition, those who leave the sauna with a white flag
they will immediately be dropped out of the competition!
You never know!
Let's do this!
Yes, let's go!
Rubik's Cube in a Sauna challenge!
I want to be the leader...
Ready...
Rubik's Cube in a Sauna Challenge
LET'S DO THIS
Yeah!
Who will win this scorching hellish catfight and become the leader?!
A battle to become the leader in this scorching hell,
Who will be victorious in this catfight?!
Sauna temperature: 98° Celsius
T/N: Approximately 208° Fahrenheit.
So damn hot!
It's too hot for even the camera to be in the sauna
This is bad
It doesn't look like they can do it
Right?
They're all sitting a little differently
True
Murakami is the only one sitting on her knees
Oh you're right
Murakami's makeup is thick, isn't it?
Today's makeup is, yes
That is right
Perhaps she thinks a leader should...
Maybe she's expressing her feelings
about wanting to become the leader
I see
Hm?
Gotta quickly line it up
People who are good at it can do it so quickly
She's lost all her focus
She's already drenched in sweat!
What the hell are they doing...
I mean, it seems like they're surprised it's so hot
No no no, it's way too quick to call it, it's too soon!
Oh already...
With every second, she's losing
about three points on her looks
Although she originally doesn't have much...
Isn't she going into the negatives then?
Right
Oshima is also
starting to lose steam
If you entered a sauna and saw these three, what would you do?
Well, you know, we don't know who will escape the sauna, so we must indiscriminantly help
In the Case of an Escape
Gaki no Tsukai members will support with all their might!
Yes, let's help them!
Yes, let's help with all of our strength!
Here, Murakami isn't looking so good
Her eyes hurt from all the sweat
It got in her eyes, oh dear...
That's gotta hurt
So much sweat!
It's only been about three minutes and a half...
There's still so much time left...
What the hell is this
They look like old ladies from the crappy apartments
Because there's no air conditioning
Hey!
What is this?!
You guys!!
It'll never end this way so come on!
Come on, do the puzzle!
It's like...
This is uh
T/N: The Ueno Zoo is a zoo in Tokyo. It's known for being pretty rundown.
The Ueno Zoo
Hippos!
They look like hippos!
5 minutes since the start
These three, who don't even normally go to saunas,
are immediately showing expressions of anguish...
are immediately showing expressions of anguish
What the hell is this
Murakami escapes!!
Over here
Come here, Miss Murakami
Come on in
Here you go, here you go
Yeah
How do you feel? Better, right?
Here you go
See, it feels nice
Do you feel refreshed?
How are you?
Are you okay?
There you go
You feel good right?
Okay, back in you go
Alright
Come on!
Back in you go
Looking good
Do your best!
Finish the puzzle!
Murakami all refreshed
Come on!
Let's do it!
Oshima vs Kurosawa
After this, an outburst from the sauna!
Oshima vs Kurosawa, another destined altercation!!
Another destined outburst!
Morisanchu's true leader to be decided!
Rubik's Cube in a Sauna Battle!!
Morisanchu, nine years after their debut
Their true leader will be decided tonight!
You know, they shouldn't push themselves
When they want to get out, they should get out
Of course
Her expression is completely different!
Very true
Ah yes, she's looking good
She looks refreshed
Her looks went up five points!
You serious?!
Kurosawa escapes!!
Okay, Kurosawa
Open wide and say, "ah"
Come on, drink up
There you go, there you go
Kurosawa all refreshed
How much do you have done? How many rows?
Not even one row
Ah, not much progress at all
Why the hell won't you say anything?
Yeah
You're looking real pretty
She didn't get prettier at all
10 minutes since the start
We have just passed the 10 minute mark since the start
The three don't look to have any intention of giving up
No one looks even close to retiring
They silently look towards finishing the Rubik's Cube!
Oi oi oi
Murakami's really looking like
a teddy bear
You're right!
A teddy bear! So cute!
Cute!
Let's support them
Kurosawa is looking a bit...
That side wall is also incredibly hot!
The sides are hot!
The side wall is hot too!
Murakami isn't looking too good...
Murakami escapes!!
Here she comes! What do you want?
Water! Water!!
Water
We got water over here
Here you go
You can lay down
Go on and eat
-----------------------------
--------------------------------
Support Item
Cold Somen
T/N: Somen is a thin wheat noodle which is often eaten in the summer with a cold dipping sauce.
We won't tell anyone else!
Don't tell anyone else about this!
You should eat
You're looking so gorgeous!
It's delicious, right?
What's wrong?
You're gorgeous
Is it good?
Even the inside of your body will cool off
It's good right?
Good, right?
How's it looking?
Oshima escapes!!
All at once! Come over here
Oshima!
Don't look, don't look
Oshima goes here
You guys are rivals
Hurry up
Hurry and get in
Feels good, huh?
Nice!
Here, have some somen
Good
You're so pretty
How is it, Oshima?
Oh wait, this isn't good!
Huh?!
What's wrong?
Not looking good
Kurosawa's not looking good!
Murakami, come on
Murakami is taking her time
Oshima all refreshed
All good, Murakami?
Murakami all refreshed
Looking good
Why are you walking like that?
Why?
Did something happen?
Come on
T/N: I'm not sure what the censored word is, but it's most likely something vulgar.
Why are you looking like a ***?
All of them look like that
Excuse me, but it looks like all three of them aren't moving...
How's it look?
Oh, well actually, I guess they are moving
Even still, Kurosawa isn't really...
This is okay, right?
Sitting in the same place, just fiddling with the cube... So scary!
Oshima altogether just dropped her cube
Really?
Oh??
Oh?
What's going on?
Is she gonna come out?
Oshima escapes!!
Hurry up over here
You okay?
Good job
Your face, Oshima... Your face is looking real funny
Just imagine yourself in Hawaii
Here you go
You're real pretty
-----------------------------
--------------------------------
Support Item
Lemon Slices
You're real gorgeous
Here you go
Use this
Come over here!
Here you go
-----------------------------
--------------------------------
Support Item
Tonic Shampoo
T/N: Tonic shampoo is used for people suffering from hair loss. It supposedly promotes hair growth.
This is the last before you go back
Kurosawa escapes!!
Kurosawa!!
20 minutes since the start
"I definitely want to be the leader..."
The women continues to clash with their stubbornness
They approach the limits of their physical strength
"I want to be the leader!"
That desire alone
keeps them going
Oshima escapes!!
Oshima probably
Oshima probably wants the
shampoo rinsed off, I think
That's right, she did go in just like that
Do you want to be rinsed off?
Go and sit
Rinse her off
Let's rinse, rinse, rinse
This is tonic shampoo, you know
Let's rinse it all off!
What's wrong?
All rinsed off
Here's a lemon
-----------------------------
--------------------------------
Support Item
Lemon Slices
A lemon
We don't know why, but here's a lemon
You got it, you got a lemon
Need more?
You're so beautiful!
Oshima all refreshed
You can do a few more rows now, right?
You're looking real beautiful
Your skin is very smooth!
So beautiful
Not even one side yet
You're right
Right?
Can't even do that much?!
Oshima, you can't sleep
in a place like this!
Oshima, you can't sleep there!
Oshima, that's bad if you sleep there!
No, Oshima's in a bad spot
Oshima, you can come out if you want
It's okay!
Come on, Oshima!
Oshima, it's a sweltering night, isn't it!
Can't sleep!
Gotta wake up early, but can't sleep!
So hot
Can't sleep on a night like that
Can't sleep at all
She's not listening at all
Oh, is she leaving?
She put up with it for quite a while
Murakami escapes!!
Hurry and sit!
Sit, go over there and sit!
Sit!
Hot wasn't it?
-----------------------------
--------------------------------
Support Item
Sea Salt (Massage)
You're looking beautiful
Watch out, careful
Someone's coming!
Here they come
Kurosawa escapes!!
Come on over!
Hurry over here!
Come over!
What's going on?
It's mine
What are you doing?
They both came out
Both!
Use that
We can see your ass!
I said we can see your ass!!
After this,
the ladies' battle finally reaches a conclusion!!
Knock it off, we can see your ass!!
They finish taking their breaks and
the three of them return to the sauna battlefield
They finish taking their breaks
The three immediately go back to the sauna
They again set their eyes on finishing their Rubik's Cube!
They all still feel strongly about
being the leader
They do
Their eyes aren't dead yet
Weren't their eyes pretty dead looking?
Well... They did look dead
But beyond all that
I don't think it's dead
Well, their eyes did look dead though
30 minutes since the start
It's been 30 minutes since the start
Wait, but...
Kurosawa is looking...
One side
One side...
Oh really?
She's getting there
All white
They completely look like old men
That's a great pose
What do you think of this?
What a great pose
Hah, it's like bam!
She threw it!
Murakami escapes!!
Are you okay?
Murakami
Here she comes
What's wrong?
Murakami, go sit over here!
You look so beautiful right now!
So beautiful!
Oh wow
This is kinda scary
What's going on
What is this
Lift your arms
-----------------------------
--------------------------------
----------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------
Support Item
Armpit Deodorant
8x4 Spray
T/N: 8x4 is the most popular deodorant brand in Japan. Spray type deodorant is also the most common.
There you go
Yep
Other side now
Okay
Just a minute
Go back now
Kurosawa Escapes!!
Two of them are coming! Two!
Why do you guys always come out together?
Looks like you're trying to get into a bar
"Let's go to another bar!"
The fourth bar
Going from one bar to the next
Let's go to another one!
Stop doing that!
Hey hey! No!
We cannot show what is happening here
It'll get all bunched up!
40 minutes since the start
It's been 40 minutes since the start
From here on, only the one with a strong desire to be the leader can remain!
The one who can't give up the desire to be leader...
You've all become beautiful
So beautiful!
They've calmed down quite a bit, right?
So nice
I see
Getting close
Murakami is getting there
The flag
The flag is...
Right now
Kurosawa has it out
That's true
It also takes bravery
to call it quits
That can't be helped
Look at this
There it is!
Really?!
There!
If you leave with that, you'll quit the game!
That's quitting!
Oh, not yet?
Huh?
What're you gonna do?!
If you leave, you'll be quitting the game!
You made it this far!
What're you going to do?!
What will you do?
Murakami quits!!
She left!
Quickly gets into the cool bath
She won't even look this way
So quick to get in
That's enough
Well, can't be helped
Well, yeah
Can't do anything about it, she's already in the water
And there you have it, Murakami is out of the game
44min and 32sec since the start
Murakami's dream to be the leader is wiped out
Murakami
Her dream to become the leader is wiped out
Now, the current leader and Oshima are battling it out
Yes, that's right
There already was some tension between them
True
The atmosphere has gotten worse
Right, before
There was Murakami between them
You gonna fight in there?!
Fighting here is dangerous!
We're also... What?
What is happening?
What's going on?
They're telling the other to take it and leave
I see, I see
"That's your flag"
They just traded places?!
That's it, they traded places?
What the hell
They just traded places, that's it
Huh?
Fighting in there is...
Fighting inside (the sauna)
is dangerous!
Watch out!
Wow, so sluggish
That's all they can manage
They can't stand it
No strength
Get out!
No, you get out!
Get out!!
You hurry and get out!!
Hurry up!!
What is this
So hot!!
Just sweating out crap
Get out there!
Ah!
Bring them out!
Will she kick her out?
Oh, this one!
You can't do that, can't do that
Oshima isn't leaving of her own will
Get out!!
That's right
It's not her free will
Get out!!
That's no good
How many bars have they gone to already?
This is the sixth bar, I think
Is it already six?
"Let's go, I'll pay the next round, damnit!"
Take a look at
Murakami's face, who is just watching this all happen
What do you want?!
Take a look at
Murakami's face, who is just watching this all happen
Get the hell out!!
Completely dead
Just acting as a bystander
What the hell?!
What are they doing?
We cannot show what is happening here
After this, Kurosawa goes back into the sauna alone
Kurosawa continues to work on the Rubik's Cube alone
and completes one side
To continue on the Rubik's Cube
She finished one side so we called the battle over!
So Murakami gave up, right?
-----------------
Murakami
Quit
Kurosawa's flag isn't even out
-----------------
Kurosawa
1 side complete
Oshima, your flag is out here already so
-----------------
Oshima
Quit
Oshima, can't help it, right?
I WANT TO BE THE LEADER!
I understand, but
It's kinda...
Hey Hamada
Feeling pretty ambivalent
I get you, but...
If we think of some other way...
But...
We just have to go with this, don't we?
Oshima, are you fine with losing?
No way!
I WANT TO BE THE LEADER!!
Well, that's it
But if you look at reality, you lost
I didn't lose! I want to be the leader!
No no no
No, look at the reality of it, Kurosawa...
Let's say Kurosawa is the temporary leader!
Temporary, yes. Until next time, Kurosawa will be the leader
Yes
Not the leader! She's not the leader!
Where are you even from?!
For a while now
After this,
We will tell you how not to be looked down by [blank]!!
What the hell did you find while in there?!
Downtown Talk translated by Oolong
Proofreading by typesoshee
Typesetting by DuckToaster
“When you go to the hair salon,
when asked ‘What would you like to do with your hair color?’, how should I answer without being looked down on by the stylist?”
I don’t get the purpose of this question…
What does this mean?
I don’t really know either
Well, there is a way to not get looked down on
Then let’s go with that, that’s fine
First, before you enter the salon, just kick the door like BAM!
Well, it’s not that kind of “looking down on”...
Even those revolving doors, you gotta go BAM!
And those automatic sliding doors, when there’s a slight opening, you gotta go WHAM!
I see
Once you do that, they’ll be like, “Ahh!”
Their scissors will be shaking like, "Snip snip snip"
It’ll be like that
Well… That is pretty scary
They’ll think, “I would’ve never thought this kind of guy would come to Aoyama!”
T/N: Aoyama is a very posh city in Tokyo.
I see, I see
They’ll be like, “Ahh!”
They’ll be like, “S-s-sir...”
Well, if at first…
I see
Those salon chairs, you can’t sit on them like this
Is that so?
You gotta face towards the back of the chair and go like this
What if they turn the chair around?
Well, if they turn it, then just let them do it and then sit properly
And then after that, what happens with the haircut?
You wanna be higher in popularity
You should get a… Star haircut
That’s enough of that. And after that, you get your haircut, right?
You don’t know anything about a star stylist
You may be a star stylist, but I’m a star at getting a haircut
I get it, so shut up already
So you get the haircut
It’s all about getting the cut
I said that’s enough, damnit! So you get the haircut…
And then they say, “What would you like to do with your hair color?”
Oh, I see
What do you mean by hair color?
Like, how would you like your hair colored?
Do you want your hair colored or not?
So they’ll ask if you want it colored or not?
Then they'll definitely look down on you,
if you awkwardly go, "Yes, please"
So it’s at that point
You have to make sure you’re not looked down on
Right. Well, they finish cutting your hair, right?
They finish, yeah
Well they’ll say things like, “Ahhh…”
Or, “Ohhh…” They’ll say a lot of things like that
Oh, while they’re cutting?
While they’re cutting
That thing fastened around you here… You know… I will not put that on
That thing
You’re the one who is going to suffer later
All that hair is going to be on you
Well, well, even if I do, it’ll be a V-neck
V-neck??
A V-neck so deep that even your chest hairs show
To about where you can see the chest hair
Well, if the person themselves say it’s okay, then a V-neck…
Can’t have them look down on you
Right, and then they finish cutting and then, “How would you like it?”
First, you go, “Huh?!!” Like that
“Huh?!?!” Gotta say it like that
Gotta say it like that?
You gotta say it like that
So that you’re not looked down on
Usually, generally, you shouldn't respond to what they say the first time
Before anything, first you have to go, “Huh?!!” to start
Alright, alright
Then, “What would you like to do with your hair color?”
“Huh?!?!”
Right? First, you gotta start it off like this
You have to. Because you can’t have them look down on you
Yes, that’s right.
It’s no good if you make it seem like you’re actually listening the first time
So you say, “Huh?!” the first time, okay
So, “What would you like to do with your hair color?”
“Huh?!?!”
I’ve had enough of that
Typical
What were you saying?
“Would you like your hair colored or not…” If you’re not, then that’s fine and just let it be
Well first, if you ask me,
it’s no good if I’m still there by the time they ask that
Whoa whoa whoa
If you ask me
What do you mean by this?
First, when they come up to me like this, I’ll just go like this
“Stop that”
“Don’t do that to me,” is what I’d say
You’re the one who came to get a haircut, aren’t you?
When the guy comes with the hairdryer, I’d just pull the plug like that
Because I hate that kind of thing
Because I’m not that kind of person
Wait what?
“Don’t treat me like your customers from yesterday”
“Don’t treat me like that customer over there,” you know that saying
Then after that, just be sloppy drunk
Wait, you’re drunk?
Because I’ve been drinking bourbon
Then you don’t need to get your haircut on that day
Even as they’re cutting, slam it, and then bottoms up
You’re an idiot. You’re an idiot
A shot of tequila. Slam it and then take the shot
No way!
I WANT TO BE THE LEADER!!