Tonight Gaki is going to a town they have never been to and asking them the best 5 places: Part 2!
They will draw one of the lots with the names of all the stations in the Kanto region and find out the best 5 places recommended by locals in towns they have never been to.
What is the station that Housei drew?
Where's that?
Iwai.
- Iwai?
- Iwai??
It's JR Iwai Station in Minami-Boso City, Chiba Prefecture.
What are the top 5 recommended by its locals?
First of all, what is the 5th place recommended by Kawana-san, who has lived in Iwai for 30 years, whom we met in front of the station?
It's the beach.
That's Iwai Beach, which is popular among locals and sightseers alike.
- Oh, but there are some people.
- There are some people!
The view is very nice.
That's good.
Then they interviewed people who were at Iwai Beach for the 4th place.
Matsuura-san, who has been visiting this beach for 30 years, told them about it.
For example, there is a observatory on Mt. Tomi.
Observatory on Mt. Tomi?
If we go there on foot, won't we die?
They headed to the observatory of Mt. Tomi, which is said to have beautiful views, and they climbed the mountain in temperatures over 30°C (86°F).
This is intense hiking!!
That's really true.
This is intense hiking in the middle of summer.
And I'm wearing Crocs!!
I'm so tired.
Then 35 minutes had passed since they started their climb.
It takes 45 minutes from here to the observatory.
Okay, we'll split up here.
If we all climb up, we will run out of time.
One of us should climb it.
They decided to play rock-paper-scissors and only the loser would climb the mountain.
- First comes rock, rock-paper-scissors!
That's good!
Who would climb among Matsumoto, Housei and Endo?
- First comes rock, rock-paper-scissors!
- Okay, I'll go.
- Shozo Endo will go climb!
Well, I'll be going.
Endo has to go alone to the observatory of Mt. Tomi.
Top 5 recommended places around Iwai station.
What on earth will happen?
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]
Endo set off alone for the observatory at Mt. Tomi, the 4th recommended place to visit.
Oh, this is insane.
This is really insane.
Ugh, this is too bad.
I'm really afraid of this.
Please be careful.
- It's pretty dangerous here.
- Really so.
Did I lose because I sang Miss Brand-New Day?
Endo climbs up the mountain trail
in temperatures over 30 ℃.
Wow!!
This is insane!
Wait a minute.
- This is insane.
- Yes.
Except for Endo, the four of them came to Iwai Station again to ask the locals for the 3rd recommended place.
First, Housei and Tanaka went to the tourist information center at the station to ask around.
Oh, did you get any good information?
- First, they introduced us to that mountain associated with Satomi Hakkenden.
- Yeah, we went the mountain earlier.
- And the sea.
- Yeah, we went there too.
Oh, Hi!
You're  the owner of the gold.
I forgot to mention this, have you guys been to Furari?
There is a road station named Furari
They were talked by Kawana-san, the man with the shiny gold teeth, who told them about the 5th place, Iwai Beach.
They asked Kawana-san for his 3rd recommended place.
It's a roadside station.
The roadside station?
I see.
What did they introduce you guys to?
- It's the  roadside station too.
- Really?
So this is just fine.
Would you like to go with us?
Why do you want him to join?
Let's not do that.
Don't you think he's a replacement for Endo?
Don't do that.
Well, we'll go to the roadside station.
If there's anything we don't understand, we'll come here.
That's enough!
Please come out when I clap my hands like this.
He's not a pond fish.
They immediately headed for the roadside station he had told them about.
Meanwhile, Endo had been climbing the mountain alone for 20 minutes.
It's too hot!
Too hot...
I had no idea that today's shoot would be this tough.
After that, Endo continued to climb the steep mountain trail.
It's really tough.
What are we going to do?
This would be impossible for Downtown.
And Matsumoto-san was wearing Crocs.
He would never have expected this.
I'll lose weight.
Are you going already?
- Are you ready to head to the observatory?
- Yeah!
If I didn't go to the observatory I would be really pissed off at them.
Meanwhile, the four of them were driving to the roadside station recommended as the 3rd recommendedd place.
I'm starving.
Did Endo eat anything in the waiting room?
- No, he didn't eat anything.
- He must be starving.
He didn't eat anything on the move either.
The roadside station is there.
It's big.
Aren't all locals come here?
Here we are!
They arrived at the recommended roadside station, Furari, and immediately went inside.
It's Biwa-chan, the Chiba-only mascot.
Is she a biwa(loquat) ?
Shouldn't this be 2nd place?
If someone says so, that's fine.
Excuse me.
Is the roadside station only on the first floor?
There is also the second floor.
- What is on the second floor?
- There is a restaurant and a food court on the second floor.
- Can I eat local food on the second floor?
- Of course.
Guys, they have a restaurant here on the second floor where you can eat local food.
Do you have any recommendations?
- How about sangayaki?
- Sangayaki! Oh, good.
- What's that?
- I don't know.
Let's go there and check it out.
They decided to eat the famous sangayaki on the second floor.
Can I eat what I bought here?
That's nice.
It's a food court.
They sell ramen and many other things.
Hi.
This looks delicious.
It says "sangayaki" here.
What's sangayaki?
it's minced horse mackerel with green onion, miso and ginger.
Eating it raw is Namerou, and grilled one is called Sanga.
Is this it?
Whale and sanga are recommended.
You can try them if you like.
Please give me four sangayaki.
Thank you.
I would like to try the meat-wrapped sausage.
That's good.
The four of them each chose what they wanted to eat and bought six items, including sangayaki and whale mince cutlets.
Let's eat!
This is delicious.
This is great, huh.
It's like tsumire(fish meatball).
This one tastes like sardine tsumire.
Yeah.
This is good.
At that time, Endo had been climbing the mountain alone for 30 minutes.
There is a bell.
Mt. Tomi Love Bell.
"We set up the love bell on this Mt. Tomi so that the sound of love would echo through the climbers."
I'll ring this bell for everyone at the bottom of the mountain.
May love come to everyone.
Let's go.
- For everyone.
- Yeah.
Do you think Endo is okay?
That guy hasn't eaten anything, has he?
Shouldn't we buy Endo something?
Nah.
Are we sure we don't need to buy him anything?
He's not here.
But he's going to the observatory instead of all of us.
That's because he lost at rock-paper-scissors.
You right.
Roadside Station, Furari Tomiyama.
The first floor sells flesh local fish and vegetables landed at the local fishing port.
On the second floor, you can enjoy gourmet foods such as sangayaki made with horse mackerel from Minami-Boso.
This place is popular among tourists and locals alike.
So, the 3rd recommended place around Iwai Station was recognized as the Roadside Station, Furari Tomiyama.
Then 45 minutes passed since Endo started climbing the mountain alone.
Isn't this the place!?
Is it here?
It's here!
Wow!!
Look, look, look!!
It's a spectacular view!
It's really a spectacular view.
It's fantastic!
You can see the whole Iwai from here.
It's good enough to be the 1st place.
I think it should be the 1st place.
Mt. Tomi was the setting for the chuanqi novel Nanso Satomi Hakkenden, and is also a popular hiking course with views of Tokyo Bay and the Miura Peninsula.
So Mt. Tomi was recognized as the 4th recommended place around Iwai Station.
This spectacular view that I saw after all this hard work is the 1st place.
But this is the 4th place, right?
Why is this in the 4th place?
They found the 5th to 3rd recommended places.
Then they asked the clerks for the 2nd place.
What is your 2nd recommended place around Iwai station?
- I've only lived here a short time.
- Really?
The mountain.
The mountai?
Mountain...? Hmmm..
Is that wrong?
Are there any shops?
Where is the place that sells your favorite food?
Loquat.
The one who answered "loquat" was Aoki-san, who has lived in Iwai for more than 70 years.
What's her 2nd recommendation for this town?
- A shop selling sweets made from loquat is located along Iwai Beach.
- Sound's good!
What was the name of the shop?
It's Takayama Confectionery.
Takayama Confectionery?
Thank you!
I heard there is a famous loquat sweets.
The old lady at the store there told me about the famous loquat sweets at a shop called Takayama Confectionery.
We should go there.
This town is famous for loquat.
- So, shall we go to the place that sells the famous loquat sweets?
- Yes! Let's go there.
They headed to Takayama Confectionery for the loquat sweets she told them about.
- This is a nice town, isn't it?
- Yes, it's a peaceful town.
Yeah.
Where is Tanaka from?
I'm from Toyonaka City in Osaka.
Who else does come from there?
Takashi Fujii is also from that neighborhood.
- There are many comedians who are from that area.
- Yes!
Right.
- What about Hyogo?
- Surprisingly, there are not that many. Not even in Amagasaki.
But there are a lot of actresses from there.
- Where are they from?
- Hyogo.
Many actresses are from Hyogo.
Keiko Kitagawa.
Yeah.
Saki Aibu.
Yoko Minamino.
- Is the same true of Yoko Minamino?
- Yeah.
Mako Ishino.
Yoko Ishino.
Those two are sisters.
They are taking the world by storm.
And the car arrived near Takayama Confectionery.
Have we arrived?
Here we are!
It was called Sunada, right?
What's Sunada?
The loquat sweets shop.
The shop is over there.
No one said anything about the Sunada!!
It says "Sunada Guest House".
"Here we are!"
You're a mess.
- What was the name of the shop again?
- Takayama Confectionery.
Oh, it's a tasteful.
It says "loquat buns".
Tanaka, you go run to the shop and ask for permission to shoot!
- You are asking me to help, right?
- Are you going to make us wait?
You are asking me to help, right?
You really surprise me.
They asked the shopkeeper for permission to shoot and went inside the shop.
Hi!
Sorry to interrupt.
What kind of sweets do you recommend?
Is this loquat bun a specialty?
There is a mixture of loquat and white bean paste in this one.
- Is that the specialty of this shop?
- Yes, it's.
- Is this what that old lady was talking about?
- Yes.
We will buy this one.
How long has this shop been in business?
- It's been in business since my father and grandfather, since the Taisho era.
- Taisho era!?
They were asking the third generation owner about the store.
Then...
Here he comes!
I'm shocked you could made it.
You didn't have to come.
Hey, Hamada-san.
I'm sure you guys were very lucky to win that rock-paper-scissors.
- My knees are still shaking.
- Seriously?
The slope from...
Sorry, mister.
The slope from there was terrible.
I was just talking to Mister, so I don't need to talk about it anymore.
I don't care about your story!
You're in the wrong place at the wrong time.
I feel sorry for the mister he was just talking to.
They ate the shop's recommendation of loquat buns.
It's delish!
- You were craving sugar, right?
- That's really true.
Yummy!
Really so.
It has a slightly sour taste.
This loquat bun is a famous confectionery representing Minami-Boso, made from loquat produced in Minami-Boso, jammed with just enough loquat grains to remain, and baked with white bean paste and kneaded loquat paste in a sponge cake.
So, the 2nd recommendation around Iwai Station is recognized as Loquat Manju of Takayama Confectionery !
They asked the clerk for the 1st recommended place.
Is there anywhere around here you recommend we should go?
What places do you recommend?
What is the 1st recommended place for Shingo Takayama, the 4th generation owner of Takayama Confectionery, who was born and raised in Iwai?
It can be anywhere.
The sunset is...
- Beautiful sunset?
- Yes.
Where should we watch it from?
Is it okay if the 1st place is the sunset?
Is it okay ?
Matsumoto was worried.
Then ...
Iwai beach is also good, but there is a famous pier on Haraoka beach, about 10 minutes away by car.
That is a popular spot.
It sounds good.
So, the 1st place is the pier?
Yes, it's a wooden pier.
- But let's go back to the front of the station and ask God, too.
- No,no, no, no, no!
Who is God?
I mean the Golden God.
No, no, no, no, that's enough!
- Let's go to the pier.
- Yeah!
Thank you!
They were headed for Haraoka Beach, where there was a wooden pier.
Finally, we can go to the 1st recommended place.
Yes, a lot has happened today.
Endo, do you know why you lost rock-paper-scissors?
The reason I lost?
I tried to think about it, but I couldn't figure it out either.
Endo, you are an idiot.
After we said, "first comes rock," we all definitely thought you would make a move other than rock.
Is this serious?
I played scissors both times and lost.
So I'm confident that I can play rock-paper-scissors with Endo and not lose.
Really?
I might lose to you the first turn.
But from the next turn, I can read your moves.
From the second turn, I'm confident that I can beat you five times in a row.
- Okay, let's play.
- Sure.
Don't count the first turn
Yes.
First comes rock, rock-paper-scissors.
- See, I told you.
- Yes.
First comes rock, rock-paper-scissors.
See?
I won.
I explained it the other way around.
You explained it the other way around?
- I won.
- Because I explained it the other way around.
I was trying to tell you that I was definitely going to lose.
My explanation was the other way around.
I see.
The exact opposite of the explanation you gave happened.
He played the same move twice in a row.
And he lost.
Yeah, what I said was not wrong.
There's nothing wrong with this.
My explanation was the other way around.
I don't think it's necessary to explain it the other way around.
On the one hand, there is that way of thinking.
This is a different atmosphere from that beach.
Is that the pier?
It's here!
- Is that the pier?
- That's good, isn't it?
Is that the pier?
Wouldn't it be nice to walk there?
They parked their car near the first recommended pier and walked to it.
- It was cooler.
- It's just the perfect temperature.
It's like simeppoi.
Simeppoi(Gloomy) ?
This is "simeppoi," which means appropriate for the last.
That "Simeppoi" will definitely come across wrong.
Finally they came to the pier, the 1st recommended place.
Isn't this great?
- And it says you can see Mt. Fuji from here.
- Yes.
Fujimi-no-oka.
(A hill with a view of Mt. Fuji.)
The picture is on the back of the sign.
It seems you can see Mt. Fuji from the front here.
This is great.
But we can't see it at all today.
But aren't we awesome?
You are so excited.
Why are you so excited?
Well, it's great, of course.
- Don't you think it's great?
- I know, but...
It's got a retro vibe.
Look, it's made of wood.
- I'm glad she told me about this.
- Really so.
This is good.
This is great.
This deserves 1st place.
It's nice to walk on the pier.
Okamoto Pier is one of the few wooden piers in Japan.
it's a popular spot to watch the sunset with a spectacular view.
And when the sun goes down, the bare bulbs on the pier light up and you can enjoy the retro vibe.
Okamoto Pier on Haraoka Beach was recognized as the 1st recommended place around Iwai Station!
This is the results.
This was tough.
My knees are still shaking.
Mt. Tomi was recommended by many people.
Everyone recommended this place.
We didn't get to see that view.
Please watch it on the air.
- Let's broadcast that footage in picture-in-picture.
- What the hell!
I worked hard though...
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]