An ecstasy of enjoyment
Captions/Timing/Typesetting:
ShadiHD
Slayeer (Alex)
Hinnerk
Jordan (JordansOcarina)
MaRGa
TEAM Gaki presents:
Translation:
Orbixx
Shizentaisuu
Karl
Mickstar
Yuka
Joker
TG
await those who endure
an abyss of emotional constraint
"No Laughing Enthusiastic Teachers"
Gaki no Tsukai's Best Series!!
Damned Pleasure!!
How was it?
from an extraordinary lineup!
A barrage of laughter
Tanaka,
I'm gonna
#$%& you, moron.
An unbelievable social studies field trip
Time Travel
Back to Edo Period (1603-1868) Japan.
Field trip to the Edo Period
Superhuman hilarity ensues, one attack after the next
She came!!!
You will not be forgiven!!
Events that would shock the Edo Period
Endou is put on trial for his misdeeds!!
and then...
The actress Endou tried to seduce arrives!
Could this really happen!?
The text
in question
was this!!
Confidential
Are you out of your mind!?
The full picture on his misdeeds disclosed!!
Brave men risk bodily harm
Just wait a second
Let go of my foot!!
This year is also a 6 hour special!!
24 Hours
Absolutely No Laughing Whatsoever
Enthusiastic Teachers
Gaki no Tsukai Yaarahende!
New Year's Eve Special
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Endo Shozo
Kokoriko
Tanaka Naoki
So we've come to this time of year again.
Yamazaki Hosei
Um, I say this every year, but
The only time they're this excited is during this brief moment.
Well... it is pretty long
Many are so excited, they can't align their hands to clap.
That excited?
That excited? Yeah, yeah.
So what is it this year, Hamada?
This year's setting is at a School.
My hemorrhoids didn't heal for two weeks after this recording!!
Seriously!
Non-stop leakage?
Non-stop!
Absolutely should not excrete things came out of there...
Uh... but it's absolutely should not laugh
Things you absolutely should not expel
You really suck at backing me up here...
But I haven't done anything...
I hated that
I REALLY hated that
Even though I haven't done anything...
Matsumoto,
Yes! Please!
could you set us up for the clip?
He really let that out
Absolutely No Laughing Enthusiastic Teachers
8:00 am
That morning
The chirp of the birds letting you know its time to wake
A soothing ambiance from the shimmering light of the morning after a heavy downpour
Soothing Ambient Light
We're almost there, let's keep going since we're gonna have to go anyway
We've arrived
Matumoto's done nothing but sigh the entire time
If I could get 9 hours of sleep like you'd
I'd be just as energetic
That is the ideal scenario after all
It's because I've been cut off from drinking for two weeks
What do you mean by that?
I was told by the producer that
"if you let your physical condition get any worse
I'll snap"
It says to wait here
We're really going to do this, we do it every year after all.
So this isn't going to be the year
where we quit while we're ahead?, is it?
or maybe "Play badminton, here"
and we'll go after we're done...
Enjoy ourselves a bit first
There'd be a point limit so we don't do too many sets
No, no point limit
Cut this kinda stuff out...
I don't like it when they come out at random like this
Aren't they dressed like the characters from School Wars?
Jus... wait...
stop!
He's wearing
guy clothes for once!
Ok we're going to start.
They're the Kawahama High School team (from School Wars)
The legendary "haka"  hometown rugby chant
I'm not looking...
but you can see his balls...
Hey, hold up!
Hey you number 1!
We could see your balls the entire time!!
That's no good!
Is he that kind of number 1?
Hey
What is up with that!?
We could see number 1's balls the entire time
Former Downtown Manager
Fujiwara Hiroshi
That was our rugby team's traditional...
our traditional dance
I know the script was so thick and all...
Anyways, ya... yamazaki
how many years since has it been?
How many years since?
It's been a year hasn't it...
Freaking moron!!!
Do you have no sense of
foolishness this year too?
Ah, your response wasn't silly enough
No matter what you say,
it always bombs
If you could at least speak
casually at the right time
That's
"yud atta speak casually"
So how should I go about that?
Fujiwara, on a clear day you can see
your face is just covered in acne...
I think everyone still will come watch
even with me the way I am, but anyways...
this year we're
enthusiastic teachers!!
Ah, that makes sense...
So that's what this chant was about...
Enthusiastic Teachers?
So everyone
is to become new enthusiastic teachers,
and instill in your students
a burning desire to learn
Although,
I'm so old you'd think I'd be the vice principal by now...
24 hours of service as new teachers
The five are put to the test through
If you guys are gonna be teachers,
what's with your clothes!?
Over there are boxes,
there we have prepared a change of Clothes for you.
Let's go
And like that
before working as teachers
they first have to change into suitable uniforms
Once your ready, we'll have you come out in order
Ok, Matsumoto.
How's that?
Macho Muscle Man Kinpachi
I'm not one to leave things in the air so...
It's not like I'm totally digging this look...
Yamazaki!
It's a little small, but makes you look like you got guts
Naive Funny Guy Kinpachi
Thanks!
Good luck!
Endo!
Oh, as usually you're the hunk
Oh really?
Once-divorced hot stuff kinpachi
You'll be popular among the students...
Thanks!
Good Luck!
Then, Tanaka!
Ah,
Ah, the look of a liberal arts teacher!
No good, liberal arts kinpachi
Lastly, Hamada!
You moron
Kinpachi with a bad taste in wig
Only Hamada would pick a wig in poor taste...
Can such a subtle difference
be that funny!?
It's perfect!
It's like a single grain of rice
that makes the whole meal delicious
That's so unfair!!!
Okay, I'm gonna say the rules now...
1st: Henceforth everyone as new...
uh,
novice enthusiastic..
sorry, one more time...
As novice... Novice Enthusiastic Teachers...
you will do a variety of...
COUGH!!
...tasks
1st rule: Work 24 hours as novice enthusiastic teachers
Next,
while performing your duties,
no matter what happens you absolutely can not laugh.
2nd Rule: While performing duties, you can absolutely not laugh.
Next,
in the likely event you do laugh...
you'll receive a severe spanking on your behind.
That is all.
3rd rule: In case of laughter, severe spanking
It's the same pattern as every year...
Okay, everyone...
So let's go to the school...
we're going by bus
Here it comes...
There's even a bus stop over there...
Its time...
Ever growing tension
As the start finally draws near...
the long hated growing air of tension takes hold.
Argh, we're really going through with it
We're going to wait for the bus here...
No! It's already here!
It's here?
Contrarily, y'know, I do want it to come faster, but...
though, I still do kinda want to wait a bit...
The bus is here
The sister bus?
Uh, we'll go to the school by this...
Gaasu Inc. St. Kurobikari School
This is the name of the new school you'll be working at.
The GSG work share bus
On the body of the bus is the school symbol and design of sister Gasu.
Sister Gasu
We'll be headed for the school by this bus.
So we're going on a bus with this shocking of design
This uh...
where do you get these from?
Argh...
don't make me ride this...
Let's laugh at it while we can...
Ok, then...
The moment you get on,
the no laughing rule takes effect!
Once you've prepared yourselves, go ahead and board...
Before we get on,
y'know Hamada's face...
did you
remember to put on sunscreen?
We don't want your face
getting iron hot red and all...
It's already so bad...
wait until tomorrow and he'll be sparkling...
Please just stop...
You're face is just so funny
We're all hopeless
Try a little harder to get used to this wig for me
Argh, so frustrating...
Alright, so once you're ready we'll leave...
If the wind got any stronger, this wig would be out
They always do a good job preparing every time
I'm going!!
You're going?
Damn straight!
We're going and all, but... So soon?
We're gonna have to get on anyway so...
Oh! He went!
Absolutely No Laughing Enthusiastic Teacher 24 Hours
Start
Right now, only Yamazaki will get punished if we laugh...
If I laugh... it'll be totally fine...
See, he laughed!
Hey! Why aren't you guys on board!?
We're not on yet... They're here!
Only Yamazaki is obeyed to the rules...
He saw Hamada laughing
from inside the bus...
Ow! Ow!
4th Rule:
Spankings delivered by the black army unit
Japan's first victim
They came this year too...
Hamada you should get on first!
I don't want to look down at you from above...
Hamada, please go first...
Yeah...
So Yamazaki and Hamada get on then...
Yamazaki, Hamada get on...
Noo!
Look at him while he gets on...
Why do I have to look at him when he gets on?
I don't want to watch as he gets on...
Please watch over him as he boards!!!
Otherwise he won't get on...
Change Hamada's wig!!!
Let's get on, get on... get on...
Ok, we're finally starting...
Is it ok if I sit here?
Once we're like this, he can
get by without looking at Hamada...
Ok, I'm not going to laugh!
At last, the bus departs for kurobikari school, and then the unimaginable...
You don't have anything applied to your face don't you, Hamada?
Did you apply anything while you were in the changing box?
Did you apply something like tsubaki oil?
I didn't apply anything...
You're trying so hard not to laugh...
Laughter will not be forgiven
The tension from laughter becoming prohibited slowly fills the bus
Before long, their comradery will fall to pieces and turn against each other...
If people don't know about Hamada's wig when they get on...
it will be hard for them not to laugh...
Yeah, I agree
If all Japanese wore wigs like these
we probably could win a war...
What prompted you to say that?
There's no point in saying random stuff like that!!
If we everyone tried this out...We'd definitely win
Hamada's hairdo already portrayed as a weapon of mass destruction
We'd win right? I'm already getting the will to fight
We'd win and all, but...
I hate getting called out for this...
Aaah, ow ow...
We're going to start this again...
I'm going to cut it out...
Let's please stop this...
Messing with Hamada is not worth it...
Just ignore it
Yet, I keep getting the urge to tease him since he keeps facing this way...
I was only looking over there for a moment...
Oh no, I said something I shouldn't have...
5 minutes elapsed since starting
Just stop from here
Just another bit I want to say though...
I said something unnecessary. I said something really unnecessary there
Arrival at bus stop
You're kidding, already!?
Wait up!
Band Manager
Touno Nagiko
Band Singer
Himura Yuuki (Banana Man)
I said wait!
Give it up, I'm breaking up with you!
Wait a second, what are you saying!?
I can't do this anymore!
Just wait though, we've got a big gig coming up...
Relationship troubles, talk of breaking up
There it is again!
What is it?
"Gig this, Gig that" Are gigs more important than me!?
Of all the people who'd understand the significance of this gig...
It would be a crisis for our fans!...
you, as the manger, would know best...
Pick one then, gigs or me!
I don't know what's going on in your head!!
Then just ask!
I...love you!
Don't force that viewpoint on them...
Something has started to develop between the two...
You get what I mean, right?
Too long, too long...
That was really long...
This was too much...
They didn't even kiss either!
It's a little tight here...
It was right in the middle of my back...
That was tough Endou...
Nagiko, calm down...
Band Guitar
Itou Ichirou (ELT)
What keeps dragging him to this special so regularly...
Aa, too much!
What's going on? Why so silent...
Hey, nightmare
Why're you here?
What 's up with this?
Two-Timing between band members exposed
I'm sorry, I've been going out with Jade too...
Two timing?
I'm so sorry
You're two timing?
He's not projecting himself...
It's clashing with his look
If you're going to show up on TV, I'd prefer it if you projected a bit more...
Say it clearly!
This one's gonna be tough...
It'll be a challenge...
I can't decide between Jade or Nightmare
I'm going to leave since I'm in the way of both of you...
Hold it, that doesn't matter...
I'm, seriously loving you
Seriously Loving you?
They've lost all interest in their performance...
So what was hamada saying about me just now...
No, it wasn't about you...
Nagiko, what're we gonna do?
I just want you to express your true love for me...
Display her your true love
Nagiko's Demands
A long time ago we went to a traditional massage therapist...
I want to reminisce with your suctioned nipples
Reminiscing with Jade
Suction Tits
Why would you prepare for something like this?
They became sooo big!
This one too!
Why such a disregard for your own band?
You've got a live show after this...
No it's a gig...
The two reminisce about the good times by themselves
What's up with this!?
If you don't take those off...
She doesn't know how to take it off right...
That's really gotta hurt
He's panicking a little bit...
Too rough, too rough
If you don't take it off by the grip on front...
Are you satisfied with this?
Then WHAT?!
Not yet!!
We still need to reminisce about the time on a mountain in Ibaraki...
where you expressed your love for me by letting a stag beetle bite your nose
Nagiko, you've had enough...
Are you going to do this!?
You love me, right?
NIGHTMARE! You got the guts for this!?
Reminiscing with Nightmare
Stag Nose
You mean me?
Haven't we gotten just a little bit off topic?
Man, I want to go to this live show of theirs...
I've really come to like them...
Nightmare's so awesome!
Nightmare's crying!
Not the lips...
Not his lips
He said "Not my lips"
We gotta get going for the gig!
Yeah!
Let's Go!
Ah,
that was...
They got us hit a lot...
The really hit us a lot!
They really did...
With so much aimed at my back...
A mere 20 minutes from starting
The five suffer a rush of non-stop spankage!
Ever more funnier challenges await them ahead
and sure enough...
Arrival at bus stop
I'm sick of this shit
So fed up...
(Sekine Tsutomu)
Movie Critic
Osugi
I loathe being mistaken for piko (his twin clothing critic brother)
Just really, recently it's...
I'm not even wearing pink
and yet I'm asked "Are you Mr. Pako?
Isn't that Tanaka?
What are you doing in a place like this?
It's kokoriko's
Tanaka!
No good, I'm hopeless here...
To stumble upon him in a place like this...
A place like, he he he...
Kokoroki's Tanaka
Ah crap, noo, this'll be trouble
You are Tanaka, right?
Yes...
Darling, I've seen your movie!
By Osugi
"Minna no Ie" (Everyone's House) written and directed by Mitani Kouki
I was really moved! Mitani's world  is full of emotion and laughter as
Kokoriko's Tanaka Naoki stars in this enthusiastic performance
Kannu Film Festival was brought to tears, an absolute must see
Those who don't watch will be trampled
Introduces all five by narration of their stage appearance
Oh! My dear Matumoto is here too!
Darling, I watched your movie too!
By Osugi
"Scabbard Samurai" Directed by Matsumoto Hitoshi
A truly splendid creation
This ultimate parent-child affection story will send you spinning with laughter and emotion
While it is plausible this parent-child affection is purely theatrical,
what's really amazing is director Matumoto Hitoshi's
personal endeavors as a doting parent
and above all else
he remains to be just an old man
just an old man with a bottomless pit of retirement money
Those who don't come see this affectionate style will be trampled
Tanaka, you can do better than that!
You can do better, Tanaka
Wha? Hamada's here too?
My dear, I've seen your movie too!
That's freaking old!
Released in 1991 Nihonkai
(The Sea of Japan)
Why'd you press the "stop request" button?
By Osugi
"Nihonkai" Starring Hamada Masatoshi
This is a very shocking tale, and if you ask why
The star, Hamada Masatoshi, does a splendid job of portraying the dark yakuza world and yet...
I can't get over the fact he looks like a gorilla
Breaking promises or shooting guns, no matter what he does he's a gorilla! A child-faced gorilla!
Whatever he's doing he's still a gorilla! Even though its a yakuza film, it's become an animal film!
Anyone who doesn't watch this gorilla flick will be trampled!!
A gorilla movie... huh...
That's scathing
Harsh!
Yamazaki, you aren't in any movies are you?
Yeah... well, about movies...
I used to do some V-Cinema (direct to video) shoots...
What'd you appear in?
Pappakapa
Pappakapa?
Don't show up in such odd films!
Such a ridiculous title...
It's horse racing, right?
Just the way he said it...
Let alone Osugi's reaction...
Weren't you in some dramas then too?
Yeah...
What dramas?
Pokkapoka
I'd swear they're the same thing...
Enough of this...
Don't show up in things with funny names!
Tough
Endo!? Endo's here too...
Endo, my dear, I've seen your movie too
By Osugi
Endou Appears in "Minna no Ie" (Everybody's House)
Anyways, Endou's bartering skills must be a work of art
To this day he reads from the script without emotion
and brags about what he can hook in
Which is why since said film Mitani has largely ignored Endou
I'm just gonna trample over him
I was only playing a martian in that film...
"Minna no Ie" (Everyone's House)
Endou's Scene
I was only on-screen for like 3 seconds...
Everyone's been in something these days...
Mr. Osugi, you really know a lot about movies.
I'm a movie critique, that's just common sense.
Tada Kenji
Yamada Yoshi
Well, everyone, it's time for our common sense warm-up, Endou Version.
Let's do it with just as much energy as usual!
Common Sense Warm-up
Endo Version
Common Knowledge~ Common Knowldege~ Use your head, Endou
Even though he's from Kansai, he doesn't use Kansai dialect on Lunch Time Wars
Get away weirdo
I'm not consciously aware of that...
It's just so plain obvious, Endo
Uhm...
Get away dunce
You really did that too...
That's true...
Use your head, Endo
I really can't say the alphabet...
His girlfriend is Sekine's (Osugi) Former Manager...
Get away perv
Sorry, but in such case I'm fine if your put off by that
They just don't stop coming...
Last year he danced with 2700
No Laughing Airport
Sekine's Scene
Yeah... yeah he did...
It's so hot...
That was a lot...
That was pretty funny, heh
Kurobikari school draws near!!
The drive to school draws to a close
We'll be arrive at the new school shortly...
Ah~, we've arrived!
We've arrived at Kurobikari School
That was so long
At last the bus carrying the five draws near enough to see the school
however, this isn't their goal, but merely the beginning of a new battle!
That was long
it really was
It was especially long this year
Alright, we're here, we're here!
We're here!
Finally here!
Oh my god...
The setting for our no laughing special...
A school where laughter comes before education.
A very tough battle will start here.
What is with Gaasu Inc...?
I know right... You don't see that anywhere.
Arrived at School
Guys, we're getting off now.
We're finally here.
Check it out. It's a fantastic looking school, isn't it?
Yes
It is.
Amazing huh?
The teachers and student's sweat and tears make this school what it is now.
Kurobikari School Building
Okay this way.
This is the entrance.
School Entrance
Look, it's beautiful isn't it?
Wow, it's amazing.
It's really nice.
That's amazing.
Main School Lobby/Corridor
They've even got a monitor and everything.
You would want to show this kind of thing off wouldn't you?
Okay everyone, the school nurse is over here...
She's the most beautiful teacher at this school so try not to get too excited okay?
Okay, let's go say hi to her.
Excuse us
Nurse's Room
I get the feeling something's going to happen.
Yeah, I agree.
Well it definitely won't be good for us.
Hamada, Matsumoto, Endo, Tanaka, and Yamazaki here.
Lining up to meet Miss Madonna.
Hm, Sensei isn't here.. I wonder where she could be?
She's really beautiful, right?
Teacher!
Miss Madonna
Hisako Manda
This is Hisako speaking.
My manager went and got me a casting role,
on a New Year's special program.
But when I looked at the details of the job,
It was actually a really shitty job.
This is Hisako speaking.
Even though it's such a shitty job,
I only get a little bit of money from it.
What are you saying?!
This is Hisako...
What're the staff making her say?!
It's not even about being out or whatever.
I thought you were the nurse of the school.
I am Miss Manda,
the school nurse.
Fujiwara who are our trainees ?
They are here today to learn
how to be teachers.
Commence analysis of new teachers!
Looks like they could do a good job.
You,
what's your name?
I'm Endo
Endo,
what do you think of the current education system?
Well, umm, I'm not really sure but...
I think they should do orders on achievements in class
so they work harder.
Hmmm,
Hisako speaking.
Endo... Who only got into High School to be a baseball jock,
desperately trying to show himself off
as a knowledgable person.
Even though he tried so ever hard
with his Middle School exams.
He only managed
to be second to last in his class.
As soon as he got his results
he called the testing staff
And asked
"Can you do anything to raise my class rank?"
Matsumoto says "you are the worst..."
Just an idiot...
What an idiot...
Just a bloody idiot.
Wait, hold on a second.
You are really well informed.
Obviously you can't do that.
Everyone, it's so scary.
Can't believe she did that.
And your name is?
I'm Tanaka
Tanaka,
how do you get to work?
I drive.
Hmmm...
Last year,
even after being abused so much about it
Tanaka still drives a
20 year old used Volvo
The car he drove before that was a
used Saab.
On top of that,
the car he bought for his wife
was again, not a new, but a used Volkswagen
Many people before him have used these cars.
What a strange habit to have.
He's just used...
used...
What she mean 'weird habit!?'
a used comedian.
I like riding them
So much knowledge about us
She has so much inside knowledge about us
Scary.. Manda Sensei is really scary...
And... what's your name?
I'm Hamada
Tell me,
how do you usually dress?
Well usually I just wear jeans and a casual shirt.
Amazing she doesn't laugh at him here
Hmmm....
Hisako here.
This man, who was a fashion leader once of a shitty little company called HAMADAA!
Now wears a weird perm,
which have hair resembling pubes
So ugly...
He's just an ugly comedian...
Manda-sensei, let's stop here, please!
So mean.. isn't she!?
Moving on...
what's your name?
I'm Matsumoto
You have a really good body.
Do you work out a lot?
No.. I just go to the gym every now and then.
Really?
Hmmm...
Hisako here.
A long time ago,
I heard a story that, Matsumoto
was told by one of his juniors that
if he had muscles, the public wouldn't find him funny anymore due to his stature
But now, he has a body like
Chuck Wilson (Number 1 Body Builder in Japan)
He even wears tight tops now. Even when wearing a
Hanes top. He's an M size.
He's M size...
He's M size.
I'm sorry for making you wait, Yamazaki.
Now it's your go.
I heard you moved houses lately, am I correct?
Yes you're right, I moved to Osaka.
Hmmm....
Hisako here.
Even though none of his jokes are funny,
Yamazaki, who lives just as glamorously as other celebs,
has mistakenly thought he's funnier now
with his comedic storytelling
He said he wanted to study at University
and then quit straight away.
And even at one point said he only wore suits to look good,
and then comes to work casually in denim
At any rate, I'm sure he will quit comic narration too.
He's all talk,
he's disgusting,
he's just a dirty stain.
She's absolutely ridiculous.
Everyone got destroyed!
From here on, please don't be an embarrassment to the school please, okay?
End of analysing teachers.
Thank you
Thank you so much
Good luck!
First of all, you all need to cut your hair huh?
She's really beautiful huh?
Well yeah, she was beautiful but...
She was meant to be Hiroshi right?
Are there still more people to meet?
Right guys, now we are going to go say hello to the headmaster.
Headmaster?!
He's the man in charge of this school, so don't be rude to him okay?
Excuse us.
Headmaster's Office
Man I'm so scared.
Can we sit down?
Oh, let's stand and wait.
Do we line up in the same order?
Yep, same as before.
Meeting the headmaster
I wonder where he is?
He isn't here.
Headmaster!
Headmaster of School
Takenaka Naoto
I wonder where he is?
He isn't here.
Headmaster!
Headmaster of School
Takenaka Naoto
Here I am! Here I am! Here  I am!
Is this school actually normal?!
WHAT DO YOU THINK?!
Headmaster's Special Interview
What's with that?
What's your problem!?
I mean come on! If he doesn't stop, I'm going to laugh every time!
Yeah, you're right.
No way!
Headmaster!
WHAT'S THE ANSWER?!
This isn't right. This can't be right.
It's not possible to NOT laugh!
He's just so energetic the whole time!
WHAT IS IT?!
I would laugh at this forever.
Headmaster?
What the hell are you trying to say?!
Can you please translate
what he's saying?
Hello, I am
Tarzan.
I eat... Raw meat
HERE, HAVE THIS!
Headmaster's unique welcoming gifts
HERE YOU GO!
AND HERE YOU GO!
THIS IS FROM MY DAYS IN HIGH SCHOOL
MY CLASSMATE, TARO SHIMONEGA'S SHOE.
SNIFF, SNIFF, SNIFF IT PLEASE~!
Damn it, I thought I didn't laugh!
I thought I managed to hold it in.
I guess I will go to my desk
AND SIT DOWN!
That's your desk?
I know it's not my desk, you dumbass!
Don't mess with me, you fool!
He's smiling while being angry...
He's having so much fun.
Okay everyone!
SIT DOWN!
SIT
DOWN!
And...
Oh... Sensei?
Sir?
Headmaster?
OWWW!!
MY KNEE HURTS SO MUCH!
That hurts like a bitch if that happens to you.
That really hurts.
That was really painful!
From here, for a long...
LONG time, we are going to...
Are you okay headmaster?
Well of course that's going to happen to you if you're that energetic...
Faints from being too hyper.
Has he gone to sleep?
Oh no! The headmaster!
Somebody help! Somebody!
Headmaster be rushed to hospital by stretcher.
Is he okay?
No way, he's definitely going to die.
You know the principal's facing downwards?
Usually you face upwards...
Yeah usually..
It's pretty dangerous...
But is everything going to be okay? With the headmaster like that...
It should be fine.
Man, he was so energetic.
Can you be anymore energetic?
Seriously, we haven't seen anyone sane yet.
Guys, this is the staff room for newly appointed teachers.
Finally, we're here.
Finally, the staff room!
Finally. Takes so long just to get to here.
Okay everyone, come in.
We finally made it here.
New Trainees Room
This is the staff room where you guys will be resting.
So if you could just sit at the desks with your names on it.
That's where you're going to be sitting today.
Okay.
I'm really thirsty.
Yeah, me too
An hour and forty-five minutes from the beginning
A time dedicated for the members who fight the temptation of laughter to rest.
But... They cannot afford to be off-guard.
Carelessness  forbidden
Frame in the back to fall out.
Oh man, it's so tough...
*BUMP*
Would that ever happen?
Ow! What the hell man?!
Surely this isn't right?!
There are even these kind of traps!
Come on man, this is just hurting me for fun!
I mean this kind of thing...
All I did was get a piece of cake!
Eraser to fly out.
On top of that, it really hurt a lot.
Tanaka, you get scared way too easily!
You're kidding me...
This is freaky man.
I'm starting to get scared.
Come on,
make this our little safety zone.
I agree. It should be that.
No need to tear us apart more..
The members struggle against the traps of laughter
Two hours in
After this.
The desk drawers await to be opened by the members.
So, we've started now and
Manda was amazing, huh?
Oh yeah, she was
Hisako Manda
Acting as Hiroshi.
She memorized the whole act perfectly too.
And what's really amazing is that those guys...
It was the first time they saw Hamada.
Yeah, you're right.
Well him with his wig.
Hamada's wig.
And they didn't just break down laughing at him.
They're so calm, aren't they?
When you think about it, Takenaka was ridiculous, huh?
Headmaster of School
Oh, the headmaster!
That was a really long part too.
Yeah, he used so much energy there.
Okay, shall we go to the next clip?
Let's go.
Okay Matsumoto. Do your thing.
VTR!
V
T
R
!!
Two hours in,
The mystery contents of the drawers await.
So, what are we going to do?
About the drawers and stuff.
You're right... The one we do every year?
I really...
just want to
rest for a while.
Same. We only just got in.
Oi man, that face you make...
It's like the face when you're reminiscing about something.
I was really shocked.
If I get
called OUT for this,
I am going to be screwed by the end.
You said the same thing last year too 'If I get called OUT for that..'
Oi, he's been smiling
for a while now
but isn't getting called OUT at all!
Oh come on, let's not start the whole 'He's laughing..'
Frame in the back to fall out..
No no, Seriously.
No no no, I agree, Hamada let's not...
*BUMP*
What the hell man! What the hell is wrong with you!
What the hell man!?
It's chaos.
I mean seriously Tanaka,
when everyone is concentrating on over here...
Can you not like be falling over by yourself over there?
What did you do even?
Sorry, I hit my leg on the...
I was thinking "I'm sure Hamada
was laughing there..."
Yeah you're right, he was laughing.
No no no, we all laughed together and then I got hit.
After that, right?
When Matsumoto said "Don't be falling over by yourself
over there"
He was like... KUU KAAW
Come on man! Is that allowed?!
But you really do
have that kind of laugh...
What the heck man?!
If you're going to spell it, do it smoothly and quickly please!
Please stop that laugh like a bird from the south...
The ones that live in the subtropics.
The ones that go 'KU-KAW!'
The ones that live there are really beautiful, aren't they...?
The feathers and stuff...
Hamada, please try harder not to laugh!
Just change the subject!
It wasn't even meant to be funny or anything!
Yeah, seriously guys!
It's because you're saying unnecessary things though!
It would be better if you would just keep your mouth shut.
Yeah, none of that Endo.
Yeah you're right, let's stop that kind of thing..
Yeah we should stop talking about Hamada...
Yeah, I prefer if you stop talking about me.
There's a DVD player again this year...
Oh crap... Inside the desks...
I'm not really worried
about the DVD player...
No, to be honest I'm not worried either.
Endo, you look like Waraimeshi..
Waraimeshi Nishida
Nishida, huh?
Isn't there another style for Hamada?
Can you just try something? With our hair, we can do this..
What would it look like if you do it?
I don't think with mine, I can't really do anything different...
Can you not let down a bit of the left hand side please?! Please?
Don't talk about him anymore... Just ignore him...
Seriously!
That's just who he is, just leave him.
It's so unfair, it is the whole time.
I know...
You look like Koshino Junko.
I hate this guy! Just throw him out already!
How many hits do we have to take because of him!
No seriously...
I won't get used to it...
Throw him out!
I won't ever get used to it, seriously!
No seriously, we are in trouble!
Let's stop, please!
He can't see what he's doing.
It's just endless
It's his hair.. I just can't stop laughing at that hair of his.
And it's not like he's laughing or anything..
Yeah because he can't see himself...
He's just sitting there silently..
What is this feeling...?
Oh my god, please.. wait...
Enough, seriously... Enough.
Hang on a second...
It's the whole time!
Okay fine, let's open the draws then
Do we have to...?
Well yeah, let's focus on something else...
Shall we change the subjects from hairstyles?
Yeah, we talk too much about Hamada...
Yeah, we'll be here forever.
That's why we should do the draws.
Well who's going to start?
Usually I'm first..
That's why someone else should go
Shall I go first then...?
We're going to start with Tanaka then..
First up is Tanaka.
One of the drawers is really wide...
I know right?
I'm opening it....
That's the most worrying one...
Oh!
Nothing?
Nothing.
There's nothing in here.
So just the side draws left...?
See? I told you.. I told you.!
Mystery DVD
There it is...
Just one DVD?
Yeah, there is just one..
No nothing here..
Oh, this year there's only one...
Mine only had one DVD.
Tanaka, there's something underneath your desk... What is it?
Oh yeah, there is.
What is that..?
It's an insole...
Someone's insole.
It's not that funny...
Wait.. Hasn't someone forgotten to take it...?
It stinks!
What the hell was that about?
What are you doing?!
Don't throw it towards Hamada!
Does it actually stink?
The insole smells awful.
I'm really sorry.
I'm really sorry about just now.
Oh my god, you're right, it really stinks
Tanaka, get a tissue and wrap it. We need to bin it
Man, it stinks!
I guess tissue will do
Everything has just been put here to piss us off!
We can't relax at all.
This insole had been worn for 3 months straight by the assistant director and never washed.
What, he didn't use any sprays to clean it or anything?!
That's disgusting!
How rude is it that after realising it stank, he threw it at Hamada?
I know right?
Man, it stinks...
Isn't it better you stick it in a plastic bag or something?
Yeah, you're right.. the smell is just...
Are there any zipped plastic bags?..
I'm so scared to like meddle with the things..
How about this?
Oh, but hold on. There's something in this..
There's something in here.
Oh, this looks like it stinks too.
And it's really freaky, this doesn't shut.
What are you talking about? It shuts just fine!
We over thought the situation. There was nothing about it in the first place.
Let's just hurry up and throw that away!
Just throw it out like that
Oh, thank you for holding the bag.
Go on, smell it once.
No, no, no way, this stinks.
No come on, just once.
Yuck!
That STINKS!
Hamada loves reactions to smells and stuff
Come on let's just stop now
Ow ow ow ow, it hurts
It really really hurts
Go throw it... what?
No seriously, sniff it
Why would I want to?
Look, just throw it away.
Can I throw it away?
Please just sniff it once.
Yeah it really stinks.
No, I think I will throw it...
No, then give it to Matsumoto
Oh no, I'm not good for that.
What?
I'm just not good for that.
I've told the school nurse about it too
Did you throw it out, Endo?
Yeah.
No seriously, we're getting hit loads this year.
Wow, that does smell bad
And also, don't make this frame fall on our
heads everytime we're around here, seriously.
Yamazaki, do you wanna open your drawers...?
Yeah, okay.
Oh yeah, the desks, the desks.
Nothing
Nothing there
There might not be much this year.
Oh?
Scratching Card
Scratch card? Wow...
You might win something if you do it..
Geez your voice went weird there!
Yes, I managed to hold in my laugh!
Just don't bother saying those kind of things!
Yosh Yosh Yosh Yosh!!
Scratching Card
This is a special kind of a scratch card, look
Hold on, let me check the other drawers.
Weird, that's it
Nothing below
So just a scratch card..
You want to do it now?
Why don't you?
Does everyone want me to do it before we open all the draws up?
Scratching Card
So you scratch 1 box from A and one box from B?
And you can win a prize apparently.
This scratch card, which came out of the Yamazaki's drawer.
Let's you choose one box from A and one box from B
If you get two of the same, you get 50,000 Yen. If you get a combination (Downtown/Cocorico) you get 10,000 Yen.
Okay, here I go.
I'm going to go for the one in the middle.
So for A, you're taking the middle one.
Yeah, for A, the middle box.
Put the scratch card straight.
Who is that?
Is that Housei?
I can't see yet.
Oh yeah, it is Yamazaki,
If you get another one of you, you get 50,000 Yen
If I get myself again, I get 50,000 Yen, right?
It says Thai Kick..
What?!
That's the worst thing possible.
THAI KICK
HOLY CRAP!
Wait wait wait!
You can't just casually Thai-kick me as if it's nothing!
Oh my god, wait wait!!
This person, this person!
It's that person.
This person.
You should come over here!
Yeah, otherwise you're endangering yourself.
You need to go somewhere with more space.
Hold on a minute!
Oh my god, this is so scary.
Crap, crap, crap, crap...
You can't do anything about that...
You're the one who scratched that result...
Wait, so this means it was just Housei-san this time who got Thai Kicked.
Yeah, that is... Wait.
Oh crap,
it's not like it was just because it was him who did it!
He just coincidentally scratched his own face out and got Thai Kicked!
So any one of us could have been Thai Kicked...?
Don't scratch out any more out!
Let's hide this somewhere.
I bet there are going to be more of these...
Fearful Scratch Card...
What's up Yamazaki?
Can we just...
Try this one more time?
Just scratching out B and using your face?
Can we just scratch the B box out?
Yeah, just the B box.
No, there's no point doing that.
I want to see something.
Oh, you want to see if all of the A boxes were you?
Yeah.
Oh to see if the staff...
Really hates you that much?
I'm not really that hated though.
This as well as the Thai Kick... Crap
Yeah the Thai Kick is tough.
Yeah true.
Should we have a look
at one more?
How much do we get?
50,000 yen
There's one for each of us,
There's enough for all 5 of us
Yamazaki just had bad luck.
So if by chance it's me...
Yeah
Will you do just one more?
Yep.
Endo, you do it.
Okay, do it from B.
I wonder what they have other than Thai Kick?
Where? From here?
We'll leave it to you, yeah from there.
Thai Kick. . .
THAI KICK
It's not me?
Just a second!
No, NO!
It's not me!
This has gotta be a mistake right?
Cause they said "Yamazaki, Thai Kick!"
So that's Koskei-san! Crap, crap!
Wait!!
Not me!
OWWWWW!
It hurts so much.
So B is just Thai Kick?
And A is only Hosei-san?
Shall we try it once more?
It hurts so much...
Again... crap.
It does hurt!
Yes it does.
Stop complaining so much!
But it hurts...
Okay, okay, so then how about we do it from A?
But B is always going to be Thai Kick.
But A could be someone else?
Yeah, it could be.
No... Let's not...
I can't take it anymore.
Yeah that second kick looked rough.
That second Thai Kick,
even the Taiwanese don't really get kicked like that.
Hey,
he laughed
Yeah he did.
Yeah even I could get kicked perhaps
I've came to realize there is no point in scratching at each other...
God I'm a good leader.
Not even a Taiwanese would get that kind of kick huh?
I'm going to open mine.
You will?
Everyone ready?
You guys were really cold hearted here.
That was really mean!
That was an incredible hit!
Soooo good.
Look at that face!
Quit it with
this cruelness!
Another great hit!
I'm opening it...
Go for it.
Scary!
Matsumoto-san be careful!
Woah!!
Woah! What is it?
Mysterious Panel.
It's a panel.
Yes it is.
Bring it up like this
Let's take it out and have a look.
Should I just flip it over?
Let's flip it first then see what else is in there.
We don't know what else is in there
Let's get it all out first
Here I go
It's kinda scary.
Mysterious Medal
It's for that,
the slot machine!
So there's one for each of us?
Huh, one each?
I'll just put it here.
Yeah.
There was a lot in there huh?
Yeah, that, and this.
Nothing.
So with this there's two items?
Ooooh, wait a minute.
Right then,
the panel?
I am going to flip it over.
"My Family"
By Matsumoto Hitoshi's Beloved Daughter
Title:
I said to stop that!
This is Papa, and that's Mama.
It's really good.
It really looks like Papa.
But this is really suspicious,
a few days ago my wife was laughing...
This picture that my daughter drew...
She put it in my bed room.
She conspired against you!
Scary!
Yeah a conspiracy!!
Even my own house
isn't safe
any more!
"Family" Drawn by
Daughter
Matsumoto Hitoshi's
So this is you?
Dada
And this is Mama?
Mama
And this... who's this?
It's like, if I became a mouse or something.
Turned Into a Mouse
It's pretty good huh?
"If became a mouse."
Another great hit.
You're really
filled with malice today.
Right, I'll open mine.
Should I go?
We're going this way though.
This way?
Hey there's something in there!
What is it?
2 Mysterious Panels
Again...?
Is it the same pattern?
There's nothing in here.
Eh? What is this?
So should I flip it like this?
Yeah, in front of everyone.
I'll turn it over like this and...
1 and 2 isn't written there?
1...
2...
"Gorilla Child"
Hamada + Gorilla Photoshop
What is this...?!
This is amazing.
Wow, I actually saw a normal gorilla for a moment
This is so great!
It doesn't even look odd at all!
Hamada "Gorilla Child"
If a gorilla saw this it would laugh too.
YOU were laughing too!
It looks scary.
He doesn't look very happy...
Is he having a nap?
You can't say that....
Hamada "Alpha Gorilla"
What are you?
Seriously?
That is an awesome picture.
This one's better,
don't you think?
Hamada "Gorilla Child"
That's right.
Amazing!
This part... look...
Hey this is how he looks when he's watching the VTR in the studio.
"Cocorico Bombers"
Damn it!
Yeah.
When he wipes
and it gets his face messy he goes like this.
I wanna show this to a gorilla.
I wonder how a gorilla would react?
Can I turn it over?
Can you just put it here?
That was...
Right then, my turn!
I wonder if I'll get a photo too?
Oh nothing.
"We know everything."
A Mysterious Envelope
It's scary...
Scary huh?
Huh what is this?
I have no idea
What is it?
It's thick!!
Firstly, is there anything else in there Endo?
Endo's secretes are going to get uncovered?
No way, I haven't done anything
Ah you mean that pattern?
There just going to uncover your secretes?
Maybe there's something else in there.
That's true
Ahhh what the fuck is this?
Cause every year something about Endo gets uncovered
ehh, wait, just what is this?
It feels kinda like a magazine
Open it
here I go
WOAH, that's scary
Woah
Look it's a magazine
endo speech
Weekly Tabloid Magazine
Huh? What's this? 'Monday'
"Monday"
Taken late at night in Ripongi Kokoriko Endo's deviance still hasn't finished
What's this?
Isn't this a bit harsh?
Yeah it is.
This is scary
Endos not laughing hey?
That's true
Ladies and Gentlemen, do you remember?
In the spy No Laughing Game two years ago...
NEEDS TRANSLATION
Who's that?
Who's hat?
Who who?
I sort of asked her for her contact details and...
When Endo hitting on the model was exposed!
Endo hitting on the model who appeared on the program
was exposed
..and I sent a really ambitious mail to her.
Huh?
No way!
I wonder if i can tame you
Misa-chan, if you have a boyfriend, you can tell me
From: Kokoriko Endo-san
Received mail
Thanks for your hard work!
With your face your the M (Note: S&M)
That ambitious mail is
The real mail  that Endo sent to her!
this
With your face your the M
I wonder if i can tame you
Endo not having learned his lesson not knowing  the staffs trick  accepted her invitation for a date
Unsurprisingly, endo having not leaned his lesson
Not knowing the staff's trick
accepted her invitation for a date
So then the photo magazine
The photo magazine ran a special on the pairs date
ran a story on the whole of their date
I don't get what it means....
Photos taken late at night in Roppongi?
It says Roppongi?
Can I have a look?
We don't really know what it is huh?
Yeah we don't
Yeah I'm getting a bit worried too, what is this?
Monday
'Weekly Monday'
Endo Shozo  gaki's exploited beauty \n
Suspicions of cheating???
Rippongi date!
'suspicions of cheating!?'
ahhh, my ass hurts
Endo Shozo  gaki's exploited beauty \n
Suspicions of cheating???
Rippongi date!
Super Scoop! Photos taken in late at night
in Rippongi show
that Kokoriko Endo hasn't stopped his Sadism!
"Kokoriko Endo Shozo
Gaki's exploited beauty"
Who?
Gaki's exploited beauty?
The celebrity play boy
Kokoriko Endo shamelessly
meets a beautiful women in secret!
On what must be a date
he spends 3 suspicious hours
with the former manager.
The celebrity play boy Kokoriko Endo shamelessly meet this beautiful women in secrete!
On what must be a date with the former manager
he spends 3 suspicious days with he former manager
3 hours
That's 3 hours.
Matsumoto-san, didn't you read that wrong?
Seriously?
Here please
Really?
(Studio) They should written it bigger
So this is Endo?
Endo Shozo  gaki's exploited beauty \n
Suspicions of cheating???
Rippongi date!
Do you remember this?
What this is?
Gaki's exploited love?
I don't know who this person is.
Who is this person?
Ehh? Who?
I was tricked
I'm being tricked
You were tricked?
This is last years...
There it is! Who they are!
So you kept it going with that girl!
No, not really but
After a long time of not hearing anything, I got this message from her
It said something like "what are you up to?"
Endo was tricked by the staff
Then she was like should we go grab something to eat
And I was like sounds good...
And nothing else happened?
Of course, of course. I just went home after that.
Why did you even meet up with her again?
Well, um....
Taming?
I wanted to tame her.
"I wanted to tame her"
Taming... that's...
When I say taming, what I mean is...
Well even I don't really know but...
Owww
So what do you mean when you keep saying taming?
In side my head.... ummm
It's like....
That word, taming....
Like.. something like
If you manage to catch a ball
It's like that but it's more like
Doing taming, receiving taming
I wanna try it.
Hahahaha
Do you get me?
You still don't understand?
I have no idea what your saying
Yeah you don't understand right?
Me as well, I kinda don't get it
NEEDS TO BE TRANSLATED
That's really odd
Yeah
There was a kerfuffle as Endo got his big surprise
Teaching duties start at 2:30
However, the search for gags still isn't over
Aaaa I'm already worn out
What is this?
Why did I get tricked so soon
I'm so tired
I'm such an moron
Matumoto-san, are you doing to try slot machine?
Oh yeah!
Fuffufu
You just laughed didn't you?
Yeah he did.
He just laughed right?
I didn't, I didn't.
Then what did you just do?
What I really did, was say "fuffufu"
Yeah that's laughing
So you laughed
Hahaha
Those guys laughed too!
They started laughing and then we all laughed
All 3 of us started laughing
Owwwwww
Huh, so that's not it then
I'm gonna do the slot machine
Using the medal for the slot machine challange
What's this?
Huh, isn't this kinda kinda strange?
with 100 medals they'll get the grand prize
Use one medal and...
I'll do it one time
Cause we can get the grand prize
Cause it was in your desk right?
I'll do it once to start with
I don't think it will be that simple
Yeah
Like this right?
Just hit it once
(Everyone) Banana
It's Hamada-san
Almost
Me?
If you look at it, its Hamada-san, right?
Anyone who looks at this would see Hamada-san
Hey you laughed
Ok, I'm doing the next one
Huh, me?
It's me.
Big Prize
Awesome!
They matched!
(On screen) Big Prize!
It feels good when you win, doesn't it?
Congratulations
Ah, 1 medal came out.
Received one medal
Only one?
We won't get there with just one
Yeah yeah
But isn't this the one we put in?
It just went in then came out
We can't get 100 like this
This is hard
Tanaka, Tanaka
Wow
What?
Why why?
Why is this happening?
Ehhh
Why?
Why? Why?
Cause that's the kinda game it is isn't it?
Ehhh What?
That kick really hurts
Woah woah woah wah
Do not want, do not want
Tanaka
Ah, that's scary!
Tanaka, just do it
No, crap
If you struggle it will just hurt more
If you struggle it will hurt more ok
OwwwwAAAA!!!!
No more no more
Oww
Owww
Oww oww
What are you doing rolling around like that?
(M) Why are you so happy about this?
Oww
Seriously...
Oww oww
Ahhh Owwww
Holy crap
Matsumoto-san, isn't your hair hiding your face too much?
Yeah, it's suspicious
Weren't you laughing just now?
I wasn't
Are you ok now?
You ok?
Please, just a bit.
Tell us when it stops hurting
Ok
Did it stop hurting?
No it really hurts
Enough...
Ahhh ahhh
Oww ow ow ow
It hurts, sorry sorry
Sorry
But when I ask it like that, it relived you a bit right?
Yeah
That was a frightful rollet
You can't do it with this eh? (10 yen coin)
No you can't
Lets watch it, the DVD from before
Yeah we should
Tanaka, you ready?
Of course you're not
So then,  your not gonna do it?
Yeah he's not
If we will be subjected to more than 2 thai kicks in a day...
The problem's that... for each person...
Yeah even so I want someone else to get kicked
Of course
So I'm gonna do it for that
Here it goes
It's in
The dead man still lives!
Outrage ?
Oh I went to see this
This meeting of the Sanno Clan doesn't just concern the Yakaza world...
The 69th international film festival of Valencia
Yah this is "Beyond". "Outrage Beyond".
This is going to effect your revenue.
Apprantly Otomo is still alive.
Who says that I'm still a yakuza?
Come to Osaka with me.
Well make a deal with Hanabishi's Chairman
That would mean war between Sanno and Hanabishi!
If this becomes a war who's going to take responsibility? You old fool.
What? You asshole!
Absolutely no laughing
Even the Yakuza have values they protect.
Downtown vs The Laughing assassin
The trap has been set
You shut the fuck up.
No you, fuckwit.
Come on then, just do it.
Come at me,. Come on!
Biito takesi \n nishida toshiyuki \n miura tomokazu
(actors names)
Kado's betrayed us
Exactly! Now go sort this out.
Woooahhh
Who will be the next
to receive punishment?
Once a traitor, always a traitor.
Yaaaa
Should I burn you?
We kill, we get killed, that's Yakuza
Uhhgg
(announcer) Everyone's a horrible person
Oi! Tanaka! Look here!
You get a Thai kick, shithead
(Everyone) ehh
Scary
Amazing
I can't do it
2 kicks is too much
Wait!
Tanaka!
This is pretty rough
Wait!
This guy get's it, kicking the same guy so many times
Owww
Bleahhhh
Bleahhh
Bleah
Cause you laughed
He's not doing so well is he?
Oww
Ow ow ow
Do you feel like your about to puke?
Does it hurt?
This is bad
It hurts.
Does it hurt?
Could it be?
Yeah it hurts
That last one was really rough
Are you ok now?
It hurts.
Has it stoped hurting?
It hurts, it hurts.
Don't say stuff like that all the time
To Tanaka
Does it really hurt
It does
This was a really good bit
Nah I couldn't
You just can't stay still
Does it feel better if you run?
Yeah
It really hurts hey
There's no way something like that can make it better
11 30 am
Now comes the long awaited time
Teacher Duties 3 and a half hours in
I bet everyones hungry
Yeah
Nows the lunch time you've all been waiting for
This school is also recreation so
Of course we're going to have fun while eating
It's here.
Your going to play a fun game where the stake is your lunch
The game will be judged by this guy, so everyone please listen to him
So then, please come in
Thank you.
shinagawa syoji \n shinagawa hiroshi
It's shinagawa
Shinagawa
He just entered so casually
Ah ahhahaha
ow
Your Shinagawa Shoji's Shinagawa?
Yep, that's right
Ok everyone, the challenge for your lunch is..
Composing breath taking poem of 5-7-5
He's really loud
Instantly praising food Senry!!
yayyyyy
Yay!
Shinagawa will pick one of the team
\n
they will pick out a card with the name of a food written on it
Rules of the game
Who ever gets picked
has to instantly compose a Senry about that food
kitsune soba
delicious flavor noodle
accentuated
Those who compose a Senry get one point
if it's not instant or has an incorrect number of syllables, OUT
Let's begin
We'll decide your ranking from 1 to five
and that will determine what meal you get
To determine what meals they get
the contestants will be given rankings from 1 - 5
So it's like that again...?
It has to be instant so...
Fujiwara-san is going to do an example
Ok,, thanks's Fujiwara-san
Example
Instantly praising food Senry!!
Ok! Hamburger!
Hamburger
The hamburger with
it's dripping meaty juices
it's supreme
So good!
Fufufu
They didn't realize still I pointed it out
Then don't point it out!
Hey, he's laughing too!
oww
It wasn't funny though, was it?
No I didn't laugh
I  didn't laugh at the poem
It was when he was like "So good!", his voice
I don't get what your saying, shut up
Look at me
I can't understand you, so stop it
You say all that and then you start laughing, seriously.
The way you just stare at someone
Ahh ow ow ow
I want you to stop staring at people
By the way,
you don't have to put the name of the food into the poem
I see, I see
Even though he just used "Hamburger", you don't have to
Ok, so then, first is, Tanaka-san
Ok, ok, ok, my lunch is on the line.
Here it comes
Instantly praising food Senry!!
Word
Ok, I'm ready!
One, two
Shrimp chili
Ummmm
in the fry-pan
kinda salty and spicy
it's so delicious
He was like ummmm
I didn't expect something like "shrimp Chili"
Waaaa that was scary
"It's so delicious" doesn't add anything
Yeah everyones going to use it now
Is "it's so delicious" not allowed?
Ok, you can't use "It's so delicious" at the end
From now on using "It's so delicious" is forbidden
RULE
It's all going to be tasty so of course "it's so delicious"
Ok, so that was out
Yamazaki-san
Ready
Instantly praising food Senry!!
Word
Steak
It's so thick and
packed full of meaty juices
it's very delicious
Kosukei-san!!
Weren't you listening at all?
You wern't paying attention at all!
Are you deaf or something?
That's just like "It's so delicious"!
Just after it was said too
He said "Meaty juices" again too, makes it a bit easy
But his tempo was really good
Yeah at least he didn't say "ummmm"
My judgment is.. safe!
Yeahhh! Thank you!
Ok next is, Matsumoto-san
Ok
Instantly praising food Senry!!
Word
Tsukimi Soba
(lit. Moon viewing soba)
it's my favorite
because of all the moon viewing
He said "it's my favorite" twice
What was that, "Because of all the moon viewing
You got caught up with "It's my favorite"
I really didn't get it
I really wanted to do it quickly
I think I was faster than anyone else
Ok, Hamada-san
Here we go
Ok
Instantly praising food Senry!!
Word
Croquette
Deep fry it entirely
with so much meaty juices....
"Deep fry it entirely"??
How many syllables was that in your head? "Deep fry entirely"
Deep fry it is only 3 syllables
He said "Meaty juices" too!
No, if you make me do it so suddenly...
It's not like he's the only one who's tired?
None of you have been able to do this
Instantly praising food Senry!!
Word
Endo-san,
Udon plate
it's my favorite food
comes seated on a plate,
da..ts udon
Please don't seat the udon on a plate
"Seated on a plate" that's really strange
Ahh this is hard
I would get it if it were "Served on a plate" though
Just a hold on a sec Shinagawa,
None of us can stop laughing
That's cause this isn't a normal game
Were just laughing more and more
Ow ow ow!
I can't stop looking at it again
Your stupid long hair, it just makes me want to laugh
We're really just having fun
Yeah were having fun
2nd round
Composing Senry
Cooking
Ok then, Tanaka-san!
Instantly praising food Senry!!
Word
Charcoal Eel
the atmosphere of an eel
\n fully mix it around
\n  eat it 3 times
Come on, it's 5 - 7 -5
Come on. I resisted that one.
I didn't really laugh that much
That one was really horrible
He was like "The atmosphere of an eel"
"The atmosphere of an eel, fully mix it around"
It has nothing to do with an eel at all
No way.
It's ok, you don't really have to explain it all
Yeah don't say all that stuff
I get it even with out the explanation
Yeah I'm taking countermeasures
If someone is gonna crap like that, I'm gonna say it
But we still all have a chance
Yamazaki-san, your up!
Instantly praising food Senry!!
Word
Fried Oyster
when it's deep fried-ied
\n let's eat loads and loads of it
\n all together yeah
Did you say it like "when it's deep fried-ied"
You said "when it's deep fried-ed" didn't you?
When it's deep fried-ied!!
When it's deep fried-ied, let's eat loads and loads of it all together yeah
When it's deep fried-ied,let's eat loads and loads of it all together yeah
Stop repeating them!
That's enough...
My tummy hurts!!!
My tummy really hurts!!
Try to give us easier ones. Your hard words really sicken me
That's right
Everyone try to make better ones already!!
Ok then, Matsumoto-san!!!
Ready!
Here we go!
Instantly praising food Senry!!
Word
Gratin!!
even if I'm sick
\n I never really
\n eat it at all however
That was really funny
This time he didn't praise it
Or explain it
Please don't make a story out of that one
Damnit, I've been caught
Hamada-san, your turn!
OK!
Instantly praising food Senry!!
Word
Omurice
stitting on the plate
sti-sticking up on the plate
it's omelet-chan
Downtown really sucks!!
How old are you? "Omlelet-chan"? Your revolting.
stitting on the plate, sti-sticking up on the plate, it's omelet-chan
Look Matsumoto-san and Hamada-san's poem weren't 5-7-5
That was a big laugh!
Yeah he laughed really quickly
Please forgive me, come on...
Cause it was so fast
And the result is that downtown really sucked and ended up on the bottom
Instantly praising food Senry - Results
1st - 3 tiered lunch box
Each competitor is eating the lunch box they won
2nd -  lunch box
4th -  Soba and osukimiyaki
This is really good
5th -  White rice topped with pickled radish
Your not going to eat all of  that?
No I will, I'm really hungry
3th -  Croquette
Sit down while you eat, I don't wanna see that
Sit down to eat, Omelet-chan
If this was primary school then he wold defiantly be called "Omelet-chan" from tomorrow.
Now with their bellies full, after a short moment of relaxation, it's time to start work...
Excuse me
The new teachers begin their work
Joining the staff meeting
...by joining kurobikari's staff meeting
But really, what will they be doing here?
Good morning everyone
This is chairman Susuki speaking.
We will now begin the staff meeting
At the moment we're receiving complaints from some of the parents.
Chairman
Hataka Daikichi (Hakata Hanamaru  Daikichi)
NAME - TODO
Vice-chairman
All the complaints are extremely self centered and unreasonable.
It's rumored that they might be from what is commonly called "monster parents", but...
Hey!
Um, can I help you?
Monster Parent Intrusion
It's you huh?
Recently my kids haven't been studying at home at all!
They've just been playing games
This school should be teaching them the fun of studying.
My daughter got a warning for dying here hair, didn't she?
Panzetta Girolamo
Why the hell can't she?
You said she can't dye it white didn't you!?
Isn't that a personal matter?
I understand that kids of that age want to be fashionable but...
it's banned according to the rules of the school
Miss, miss
My son isn't in the photos taken at last months school trip
Kyoto's Kiyomizu Temple and the movie village and
Nara's... that... some kinda of a temple and...
He's not in the photos at all!
Girolamo forgot his lines
Also
Um... sorry can you please say that again?
Miss, miss
My son isn't in the photos taken at last months school trip at all
Kyoto's Kiyomizu Temple and the movie village and
The most fun place
Nara's east and west... *** and
Um son isn't in the photos
Also in Osaka, um... then that photo of over there
Crap, this is tough
It sort of seems like there were some things left out of what you were saying so...
can you please say it again from the start
Miss, miss
My son isn't really in the photos taken at last months school trip
What?
Ok I've got you, I understand
I understand what everyones saying so...
I'll respond to everyones claims in time so can you please wait till then?
Ok, do it soon
We're counting on you
Ok then Daikichi, please begin
Can each teacher please give a report on the present state their class
Ok, this is class 1-1's home teacher, Ogawa speaking. Yesterday in class...
Report on class state from home teachers
there was an incident where one of the students shoes went missing.
It's possible that this could start
to become a big problem so I want to carefully
help guide all the students to a resolution. Thats all.
Understood. Please deal with the matter quickly
Next please
Ok, class 2-1's home teacher Murata please
In my class there's been a cold epidemic break out
Yesterday 5 students were absent from class
So then, without reveling my intentions I'll
help the students manage their health
Understood
Ok, next please
Yes, ok I'll make my report
Chousuu Riki
Homeroom teacher:
You've got to be kidding
This is bad
Ok then, this is class 3-2's homeroom teacher Chousuu speaking
The results of the questionnaire given to the 3rd years
concerning what (sic) induristry they would like to enter have arrived so...
There's no way we can do this
I know but if we can pull though this...
Yeah yeah, I know
Nakagawa can't quite pronounce his lines smoothly
Nakagawa, can you please say it again from the start.
From the start? Ok
This is bass... class 3-2's Nakagawa speaking
The results of the questionnaire given to the 3rd years
concerning what industry they would like to enter have arrived so I'll give my report
Syssstim engernar, prrogramer ect.
That there are a lot of student's who wish to do
work using their hands with their full strength can be secean.
Come on
Thank you Nakagawa
Thank you
Ok then next teacher please
Ok
Secret
Thank you
Ok then, next teacher please
Ok
No way
Another teacher who can't pronounce their lines smoothly
This is impossible
Defenitely impossible! There's no way we can do it with this guy
Homeroom teacher:
Tenryu Genichiro
Should I begin?
Yes please begin thank you
This is class 3-1's home teacher Tenryu speaking
Impossible Impossible impossible
Is it ok now?
Yes, please speak slowly
Ok, this is class 3-1's home teacher Tenryu speaking. Last week out class
Asuka Shoji's iPod was...
I don't understand it at all
I have no idea what he's saying
No way, they've got to be kidding
They can't understand almost any of the report
Thats just noise, quit it
Tenryu, please speak a bit more slowly
Understood
Please continue your report.
um, things like smart phones and tablet computers
Moreover, ummm...
games that use WIFI, devices with electronic messaging and etc
are now absolutely banned in school
Tenryu, can you give a report on the preparations for the school festival?
Yes, please
Understood
Firstly, concerning items being taken from the school gym...
Enough enough, it's just impossible
Impossible
I can't, it hurts so much
enough, this is impossible
Tenryu, please calm down
Understood
Also the students are making butler cosplay costumes
They'll be running something called a butler caf
Concerning the cafe...
He was just going "brrrrbrrrbrrrr"
Slowly please
Nakagawa-san's been laughing the whole time
He's still doing it, we can see you you know
Thank you
Suzuki, shall we move onto the next one
Yes, lets.
Oiii!!
You!! Come here!
STOP IT!!!
Whatch it!
It's fine, come here!
Stop!
What's going on here?
These 2 were fighting behind the gym, I thought I better give them a warning so I bought them here
Goriraimo:
Oshima Miyuki (Morisanchu)
What's the cause of this fighting then?
Shut up!Shit head!
Shut your face, fuckwit.
Now then, you can't say stuff like that when teachers are around can you?
Shut up! Shit head!
What gives you the right to say that
Stop saying shit head, shit head!
I'm not a shit head! I'm a teacher, am I not?
....What the fuck?
What is this?
What's happening?
It's just one after the other
What the hell, they're really worked up
Oi, you can't talk like that around the teachers
Shut up!! Shit head!!
Why is that you don't stop saying shit head?
What's up with the "shit head"?
Enough! Everyone calm down.
Hey, you!
Take that iron mask off right now
That's right, take that thing off you idiot
Asshole, what the fuck are you doing.
Huh, wha~ wha~
Tanaka's wife enters
I was so supprised!
Huh?
This can't be real?
Tanaka's wife
Kohinata Shie
Huh?
She's finally arrived
She's finally make her appearance huh?
Yep, she's here at last
No way, seriously?
You two, what's the cause of this fighting?
This asshole was talkin' shit about my man
Huh?
That's cause he's gross
I said that he's so gross, what's wrong with that?!
He's not gross at all!
He's fucking really gross
In what way?!
Stop talking back. Even though his arm hair is so thick
his head is going bald, that's why! He's fucking gross
Shut up!
Sure when my man
gets out of the bath his head is so bald it makes me feel ill
But that's fine by me!
Hey, what are you doing? what are you doing?
What a great revelation
Seriously?
This has gotten really great
Hold on a sec...
Also I heard this...
On the sofa in his house
I heard he has this position he uses right?
He just sits there smelling like an ordinary old person
He just stays like that
What is this, enough! What are they talking about?!
Oww!
It's about her boyfriend yeah?
No, I know that but...
He's really over reacting
But that's really cute!
There's no way that can be cute!
It's cute!
Why?
Hey hey, just hold up
Seriously, stop this right now!
You're bad, you're bad too
I'm not bad!
Go and reflect on what you've done!!
Go and reflect!
Stop it!
Yes I will!
Whip of love   The nun's spank
Your going to reflect on this now!
Miss, miss you can't do that!
It hurts! It hurts!
Reflect!
Come on, miss
It hurts...
I think we were really lucky to see that though
It hurts!
Ok, so everyone's ok now?
You've had your fight now get out
Yes mam, I'm so sorry
Yes mam
Lets go
Here you go
Thanks
You ok?
That was amazing
That was so shocking
Miss Suzuki, the final report please
The truth is, in the 3rd year we have the worst problem student
A rumor has started that that student somehow
has been carrying something like a lethal weapon around at school
So then I think I want to 5 new trainee teachers to
go and get that weapon off of them
Understood
We're counting on you
Don't just say "understood"
You've been given a really great task here
Because you say so?
Are we really ok with this?
So that's our job?
Moving to the problem students class room
That was bad wasn't it Tanaka
I was really supprised
Yeah you should be surprised
You didn't know it was going to happen?
No I had no idea at all
Even when she came onto stage?
Of course I still didn't know
The problem student from that rumor is in here so
Please enter
Line up Hamada, Matsumoto, Endo, Tanaka, Yamazaki
Huh what? what? This is scary.
Student who have been pantsed
Come on, this is really scary
Oi, you, what happened?
It's The Pants Hunter.
We encountered the Pants Hunter
Are you talking about the famous Pants Hunter from St. Kurobikari School!?
What?
Woah woah, that surprised me!
Matsuko Deluxe
Problematic student
What is this?
You've got to be kidding me?
Pants Hunter - Matsuko
Get off me, oorraaa
I'm done with you people now, get out of 'ere!
Yes mam
We're so sorry!
You guys, this is the problem student from the rumor, Matsuko the Mammoth.
If your not looking, you look
If your not looking, don't look!!
Yeah ok
I'm looking and not looking
You guys, this isn't a meager thing
You're going to do a body check on Matsuko
Hamada
Huh??
Body check
Checking that Matsuko isn't carrying a weapon
Yeah search her, find it so we don't have to
Yeah we don't want to have to do this too
Your lips are fatter than last year
Fufufu
Scary!
Hamada looked so small
Ah ow ow ow
He looked amazingly small
There wasn't anything?
Was it there?
No
Ok, Matsumoto
Please find it
There's nothing there is there?
Come closer
Your arm's really muscular
What's this?
Woah, amazing
What's it doing?
But she was whispering to me like that...
Yeah she sure was
She kept saying that stuff
Matsumoto, did you find it?
No, I didn't
Endo
Please find it
Um, excuse me...
I'm going to give you a body check
I'm looking for a weapon
It's down lower
Lower? Lower?
I've got an amazing weapon, it's down lower
LOWER!!!
More towards the center
What is this?
Try not to get to hot there Endo
Sorry
Did you find a weapon?
No we didn't
That's right
Anyway, who are these guys?
They're the new crop of teachers starting from today
So then, wouldn't it be polite to introduce your self first?
Self Introductions to the Problem Student Matsuko
Ok, Mr Lips
Ok
I'm the new teacher Hamada, nice to meet you.
Wrong!
Fujiwara-chan, show them how it's done
Ok
I'm like from class 3-b, slightly fat with a pointy face, I'm Fujiwara
My favorite type of girl is
Neat with matching dimples and teeth
Like a princess!
The cosplay I would like her to do is
a dental hygienist
Nice to meet you
AND YOU!!!
They'll use Yanki greetings to introduce them selfs
Got it?
Mr Lips, do it again
Mr Lips is a good name
I'm like the new teacher Hamada
My type of girl is
silent, and perverted, and
Hamada, aren't you saying a little too much?
silent and perverted?
What kinda perve is that?
Ok the next guy is Matsumoto
I'm the new teacher Matsumoto
Ummmm.....
My kinda girl is
someone who, even though she has really big tits
It kinda seems like they don't really and
um, wearing something that looks like a cardian
but a part of me also thinks "is it that good?" and...
This guy talks way to much!
That was way to much!
So long!
That was really detailed
Is it ok if it's a bit rough?
Please
Nice to meet you
I'm the new teacher Endo, nice to meet you
and you
My type of girl is....
Not so much what's on her front side, but what the back side is like,
accentuating what's on the front...
Who?
Nice to meet you
Next
I'm the new teacher Tanaka, nice to meet you
and you
Um, I like girls like office ladies who at lunch time
bring their wallet and go to lunch and stuff
My favorite cosplay is
American Police
Nice to meet you
Wha? I didn't laugh at all
I'm the new teacher Yamazaki, nice to meet you!
and you
The kinda girl I like is a girl with short hair
The shorter the better
My favorite cosplay is, naked all over
NICE TO MEET YOU!!
Naked all over....
I guess they all have that
Huh, they have that?
Thanks
These guys are alright
Till now there's been no one I wanted to consult with about my painful secretes
But I feel like I could talk to these guys about anything
Matsuko, give it a go
This is something I wasn't able to tell ayone till now but...
I can't work an ATM machine
The touchpanel, what should I do?
Well, wouldn't it be best if you lost a bit of weight?
You really think so?
I get that my fat might be getting in the way
There was no one who would tell me that so clearly before
Ah, is that so?
Say something nice
I'm sorry
Try to think about my feelings
Wha?
Prize for resolving her painful secret
I was like "wha?"
It was scary wasn't it??
Rice grown by my grandpappy
Eat some rice balls
The prize is rice balls filled with love
So audacious
It's like squelch, squelch, squelch, squelch
She uses a lot of water huh?
Eat it
Um, now?
Eat it!
Ok
It's not in the center?
How is it? Is it good?
Yeah
It's yummy
Ok
I'm gonna make you all eat one
It's ok, it's ok
No no, she said she's gonna make us all eat one
Even though Hamada was the one who helped her
For real?
It's amazing, my grandpappy grew the rice, look.
It's really amazing
Yeah, it's amazing
Isn't that enough already?
That was a good one
I'm making this one for you (Yamazaki)
Um, that's a bit..
You don't want it?
No that's not it
You don't want it?!
No I don't not want it
Amazing
I couldn't breath
He almost died
He really almost died
Who is going to understand my feelings?
Huh?
Do you understand my feelings?
What the hell is this?
What is this?
Come on... it kinda felt like it that was the end before.
I really thought it was over
GET THE FUCK OUT OF 'ERE!!
What? We're sorry
DON'T FUCK WITH ME!!
GET THE FUCK OUT!!
Ok ok, got it
Her mood changes are messed up
I really thought that was over
It usually finishes with that right?
That really got stranger and stranger
I was so surprised
5 Hours since they've began
The new teachers haven't had a break
We're changing clothes.
Changing?
Um now everyone is going to battle teachers
from another school for this school's honor.
Competition with the rival school's teachers
But if it is just you guys we'll be worried,
so we invited a powerful helper to come.
Come in!
Gushiken Yoko
This is our charismatic gym teacher Gushiken
Thank you
So guys, to prepare for the competition,
please put these tracksuits on.
This is our helper?
This is the helper, the charismatic gym teacher Gushiken.
"This"?
Please do your best
You're going to get changed here too?
Let's all do our best
It's good that Gushiken came to get changed too
Ahh
Ok, if everyone's ready, lets go to the gym.
Yep
Is this helper really going to be ok?
Everything will be fine cause I'm here.
Really?
Leave it to me
Let the battle begin
The schools honor hangs in the balance
Gym
Firstly, St. Kurobikari's entrance!
Ameagari Kesshitai
Committee chairman:
Committee vice-chairman:
Hotohara Touru
Miyasako Hiroyuki
Please, please come on
We didn't know anything about what was happening.
Continuing on, Felistar Gakuen's entrance
This way, this way
(Savanna)
Drunk Dragon
Felistar Private Academy
Fujimoto Toshifumi
KABA.chan
Kinoshita Takayuki
Nishikino Akira
Takahashi Shigeo
Tsukaji Muga
Starting with the arrogant and powerful Nishikino, 6 strong contenders have been gathered.
Now before the game begins, one rule will change...
During the game laughing is ok,
During the game laughing is OK
Rule
however, you can't lose.
So then...
You can't do that
Haa!!
So then...
Eeeehhhhh?????
We said it's ok to laugh but...
He didn't say it's ok to kick!
No we didn't
What is it? Gushiken-san, what is it?
What is it Gushiken-san?
Excuse me
Today, please help...
Please help.. um that's...
His body isn't in good condition!!
Everything is completed so please send your complaints to the complaint department.
His body is in worse condition than I thought!!
Thank you
Both school's honor is on the line!
Felistar Gakuen
Kurobikari Gakuen
They can't lose this battle!
The battle for honor is about to begin!
Naturally the losing team will receive a harsh punishment
The member of the losing team that screws up the most will receive a Thai-kick
Rule
are you going to be ok, Gushiken-san?
My...
ass is weak
I'll say it again
You're saying this when the game it's been decided already.
That's troubling, really troubling
Everyone ready? We're about to begin the competition
So then today for everyone
That's right
students came to cheer for you.
We will do our best!
Do your best Tsuka-chan
What?
I completely didn't notice
I came to cheer for you
Are you that excited?
Suzuki Taku (Drunk Dragon)
Yeah
We will be cheering for you with all our hearts
Huh?
We'll absolutely be cheering for you!
If you only came here for that at least talk louder!!
Sukuki's junior comedian
The kid next to you is laughing a lot
Ok then, let's begin
The first event is "As high as you want, jumping vaulting box"!!
As high as you want
Jumping vaulting box!!
The rules are simple
5 tiers!
Declare the height you think you can jump
As high as you want!! jumping vaulting box!!  Rules:
All of the team member's points will be added together
If you make it you get as many points as tiers
If you make it you get as many points as tiers you jumped
If you don't you get 0
All of the team member's points will be added together
Ok, the first batter up is Felistar Academy, please come down.
Yeahh!!! Lets win this!
Challenge: Felistar Gakuen
Ok, everyone do your best
Who'll go first?
Should we go from there?
From Tsuka-chan? Understood
Top batter: Tsukaji's challenge
Felistar Gakuen
Jumping vaulting box challenge!!
Tsukaji Muga (41 years old)
Ok, Tsuka-chan
How many tiers will you attempt?
Five
Tsukaji 5 tiers challenge!!
5 tiers, you can do it!
you can do it!
I don't remember how to do this...
Can he do this?
Suzuki-kun?
Yeah yeah
Do your best ok?
What is that?
Do you reckon you're gonna go up in flames!?
Just going up in flames isn't enough
Huh what's happened?
Everyone, there's no practice round
So then lets move on, Tsuka-chan's 5 tier challenge!
Ready....!
It must be quite scary to try huh?
It should be OK right?
Ooh? What was that...?
didn't your butt touch it??
Ok guys, if your butt touches the vault,
If your bottom hits the box - 0 points
Rule
your attempt won't count
No no, I didn't touch it!
OK then let's have a look at the replay shall we?
Can you see? His right leg kinda caught the edge there
It's OK isn't it?
Your butt is alright then
Just his leg!!
Yep, just his leg!!
Since his butt wasn't touching it...
his attempt is a success!!!
5 points
Felistar Gakuen
Tsukaji
OK then! here comes Kurobikari Gakuen next
Who's going to go first?
Me!!
What the hell!?
Seriously??
The old ones, you and me, need to do this first
Don't we discuss first!?
What do mean, "old ones"!?
Seriously, you gotta let us old ones do first
Ok then, Hamada...
Yep
So, Hamada-san do you want to go first?
Yeah I'll go first
How many tiers?
Erm, with 5 too...
5 tiers?
Yep!
Go for it!
Hey, what the hell are you laughing at?
Yeah, really.
Hold on, listen! You guys!
You guys may already have got used to see Hamada-san like this today
but this is the first time for us - it's hilarious!!
JUST ABOUT though! We BARELY managed it!
It took us a half day to get to this stage
Has his face always looked THAT hilarious??
Hamada Masatoshi (49 year-old)
Jumping vaulting box challenge!!
Kurobikari Gakuen
Hamada attempts a 5-tiers box...
How will it go?
How confident are you?
Well, I should be fine with that height
Oh, he is quite confident!
OK, now here is Hamada-san's attempt at the 5-tier box
Ready...!
Go for it
Scary, scary, scary!!!!
5 points
Hamada
Kurobikari Gakuen
You can go for much higher one for sure!
You should have tried higher, don't you think?
You could definitely nail 7 tiers
You think so?
Just to let you know, if you don't push hard enough and your team loses as a result,
If your team loses the person who
contributed the least will receive a Thai kick
Rule:
you will receive a Thai kick for crappy attempt.
What!? Why!?
Well, Hamada receives a kick one way or the other right?
Why the hell man!!?
Felistar Gakuen
Jumping vaulting box challenge!!
KABA.chan (43-years-old)
Next up: A professional dancer & excellent at sports, KABA.chan's try
KABA.chan, how many tiers?
Let's try 9 tiers
OK, I'll give it a go
KABA.chan, attempting 9 tiers!!
KABA.-chan, 9 tiers?
Let me try
KABA.chan, if your d*ck pops out
you'll definitely get a Thai kick, got that?
If the d*ck pops out, yeah
Your d*ck will get the kick, alright?
You'll get the kick with the number of occasions you've had your d*ck exposed
That's harsh!!
OK, you ready?
Here is KABA.chan's attempt at the 9-tier vault
Let's see - ready!
9 points
Felistar Gakuen
KABA.chan
That was really good!
No need to check (the replay)??
Surely not for this one
Are you sure?
We may detect the d*ck leakage if we check the replay
Gushiken Yoko (57 years-old)
Jumping vaulting box challenge!!
Kurobikari Gakuen
Gushiken tries 8-tier
Can he prove what it takes to be a super helper for his team?
Gushiken-san, are you absolutely positive about that???
He'll be fine - he's not heavy
Gushiken-san, how old are you this year?
High, huh?
Completely ignoring us!!
Gushiken-san, how old are you now?
Oh, did I ask for 8 tiers?
That's not what we asked!
Not that!
Your age!
Ready...!
Is he gonna be OK?
You can do it, go go GO GO GO!!!
8 points
Gushiken
Kurobikari Gakuen
I did it!!
Felistar Gakuen
Jumping vaulting box challenge!!
Takahashi Shigeo (36 years-old)
Next up is Takahashi; having a go at 8-tier vault despite his incompetence in sports
How will it turn out?
Jeez it's really high you know
HIGH!
Make sure to use the springboard properly to catapult yourself like "boom"
OK
Not that it was something we didn't know...
Yes right
Let's see how he will do,
ready...!
Not good, no
Oooh not good
Whoa it was a bit...
OK, now, guys, let's take a look at the replay!!
Let's watch the replay!!
Even if he managed to do it, it's as good as a failure!
Isn't it though??
He's walking with his hands!!
Bloody hell, he used his hands twice
Yeah, twice! Used hands twice!!
Jeez, awful
Attempt unsuccessful!!!
0 points
Felistar Gakuen
Takahashi
Horrible, we're gonna lose for sure now!
Jumping vaulting box challenge!!
Kurobikari Gakuen
Matsumoto Hitoshi (49 years old)
A 49-years-old old men: Matsumoto's Challenge!
How many tier is this?
That's an 8-tier vault
Oh, is it 8?
I'm so sure that I'm not gonna make 8 tiers
Do you really think it's that funny to watch a bunch of old men hopping around??
Come to think of it, yeah.
It is hilarious
I've already got a bad feeling about this...
Go for it!
8??
Attempting a 8 tier!!
Going for 8-tier, ok?
You sure?
You can lower it if you want
It is tier 8 at the moment
Shall we lower it by 1 tier?
Wanna make it 7 then?
So uncool
Are you gonna be a chicken just like that???
I'm really having a bad feeling about this
I'm gonna screw it up big time, aren't I!!?
You can do it, don't worry!!
It'll be OK, it'll be OK!!
Here comes Mastumoto-san's attempt at the 7-tier vault
Let's get started. Ready...!
You can do it
Can I really jump that?
My god, it's scary
Don't get tense!!
7 points
Kurobikari Gakuen
Matsumoto
It was an easy try wasn't it?
It didn't look if it was pushing him too the limit
It's a bit like, what do I say,
I used something I haven't used for a long, long time
What the hell are you talking about?
6-tier vault successful
Felistar Gakuen
Kinoshita
Heated competition over the vaulting box among the teachers
7-tier vault successful
Kurobikari Gakuen
Tanaka
9-tier vault successful
Felistar Gakuen
Fujimoto
Many of the teachers make successful attempts despite the prior concern,
the battle between two schools over their honor continues...
9-tier vault successful
Kurobikari Gakuen
Yamasaki
Felistar Gakuen
Kurobikari Gakuen
points
With only one competitor remaining from both sides,
Kurobikari has a 7-point lead at this point
Endo plays safe by opting for 8 tiers,
8-tiers vaulting box challenge!!
Endo Shozo (41 years old)
Kurobikari Gakuen
how does his plan turn out?
Here goes the 8-tier attempt,
ready...!
Here I go
He's not heavy is he?
His butt touched the vault!!!
We need the referee for this!
Let's look at the slow-mo replay!!
If his butt touched the vault, that will be nil points
Was it not a successful one??
Your hand should have been positioned little further
I just managed to evade it
Ahhhh!!!
Your but was touching at the very last!
whaaa..!
How will this be considered?
Is it not good?
His butt was touching
Suzuki, what did you say?
Definitely touching
You think so?
Yes
What about his friend?
Most definitely!!
What kind of voice is that?
The friend's opinion will be adopted
Seriously!!!???
Unsuccessful!!
What the hell!
0 points
Endo
Kurobikari Gakuen
Now then...
A 7-tier try is enough to break even
8-tiers or more qualifies
Felistar Gakuen
for victory
Why don't you go for 10 then?
7 tiers will make you even, 8 tiers will make you win
Er, what is it?
10 tiers??
10, yeah
Oh my god that's so brave
Also, just one hand
Huh? ONE HAND??
My hand is not in good shape, that's all
What?
He's got tenosynovitis
So are you doing 10 tiers with one hand?
That's so cool
Celebrity teacher Nishikino goes for a whopping 10-tier vault with one hand,
10-tiers vaulting box challenge!!
Felistar Gakuen
Nishikino Akira (64 years old)
if he is successful, Felistar Gakuen will be the winner without a doubt
Let's get it started
Ready...!
How on earth is he gonna manage it...
I can't watch this, is he sure about this?? It's scary
it'll be alright, do your best!
Wouldn't it be better with both hands anyway?
Resounding success!!
10 points
Felistar Gakuen
Nishikino
Felistar Gakuen is the winner!!
Felistar Gakuen Victory!
Now then!
From the loser, Kurobikari Gakuen
the most useless teacher among them is...!
I really don't want it!!
Obvious decision you know
Yep, I totally get it
Here he comes, here he comes
it'll be bloody painful!
Oh man, aaaaaargh don't wanna do it!!
No compromise, is there?
Ok, let's get this done
I don't like this at all...
Is that position ok?
Aaaargh seriously... oh wait wait!
This is really scary, really is!!
I know it's painful from the sound of it
It's the "asshole crusher"
Must be, yeah
6 hours at work,
Teacher's duty 6 hours done
that man does never seem to cease to unleash his "potential"
We really are getting used to it, aren't we?
To Hamada's appearance, right?
At last, yes, I think so
At last indeed
Well yeah I should hope so
It's been a while...
Bit jealous...
Only with that wig, you know
Why don't you try it then, want me to lend it to you?
You know what, I'm not gonna look funny at all
Ugh, don't wanna wear this
I won't be able to make anyone laugh...
So different.....
Totally different
Completely defeated
Why is it so different though?
Hamada-san, how about this?
Oh, the other way round?
The other way round
Yeah, you see
Ah alright
I see
I don't think it will be...
It's the same as ours
That's right
the 4 of us have been wearing this today so...
What is wrong with you!!?
Yeah, it's too much
Why me!!??
What is this, really?
Seriously!!
Aaaaaargh Hamada-san!!!
It doesn't matter what wig he's wearing
Hamada-san!
Stop it man
Incredible, it really is his ammunition to take us down
Hamada's hair style has become a great threat again
Hilarious
Isn't it?
Oh jeez
Ouch!
Argh!
Half of Hamada-san's face consists of forehead
Yeah I usually hide it with the fringe
I guess so
Of course I can't help it if I get to see myself like that with expectation and all!
He himself can't even stifle a laughter
That was a good smack
Aaaaaaaaargh it hurts, ow ow ow....
Jesus, Hamada-san
Let's not push it any further
Doesn't he need to wear that thing though?
The mask?
seconds
The mask explodes in
If you don't mind
What, this thing?
Yes
Whoa!!!!!
For real!!??
You gotta be kidding
Do we have these kind of nasty traps this year?
I just got taken by surprise, that was all
Jesus....
Can't believe this
Ah, staff made a trap here then
We're in deep shit here
It exploded in his face
This is not good at all
Anything goes at this stage man
Aaaaaaargh!
You can't trust anyone!
Seriously, you're AWFUL
Indeed
I'm considering disbanding DownTown right now you know
He's totally overpowering me as a comic relief
And Hamada is supposed to be the "tsukkomi"...
Yeah, he IS the tsukkomi!!
Yes, he is...
This is a pitfall of double-act, you see
OK guys,
In order to perform a future career consultation for pupils,
Erm, D...DVD...
Er, I want you guys to watch an occupational "how to" DVD as part of your training
"How to"...
I've got a bad feeling about this
Me too
I don't like this...
I'm smelling "him"
Learning session by watching an occupational education video
OK then guys, please pay attention to the video and learn
The best job navigation
We will find your perfect job
Greetings, dear pupils
Assistant
Best job instructor
Miyagawa Shunji
Yuki Maomi
As you will start preparing for a job hunting,
I would like you to learn from this video how people in our society carry out their occupations.
What occupation shall we begin with?
First up is,
A Taxi driver.
Taxi Driver
It is a job with huge responsibility.
Let's have a look
Hi driver,
Would you head to Roppongi please?
Roppongi, yes?
Cab driver:
Uchida Yuya
Yep
REALLY!??
The best job nav "cab driver"
Hi driver,
Would you head to Roppongi please?
Roppongi, yeah?
Cab driver
Uchida Yuya
Yep
Got it.
Really!??
Seriously??
Whoa whoa whoa
I was taken by surprise, didn't actually laugh you know
Holy shit
HOLY SHIT
Why not Jimmy-chan?
Oh shit
I was absolutely positive that it would be Jimmy-san!!
What the hell man
It would have had to be him!!
Me too - I was convinced that t would be Jimmy-san
That was totally unexpected
Yep
What is this new strategy...?
Wow
Driver, is it OK to talk to you right now?
Absolutely
You know,
I was made redundant at work today
I don't know what to do right now...
There are ups and downs in life,
Life sucks sometimes and you can't do much about it
Gotta keep positive, positive
Positive,
positive
And do what you can do, don't you think?
Positive, eh? I guess it's very important isn't it?
Driver,
can you maybe sing something that relaxes me a little,
what do you think?
"Courtesy of a rockin' cool guard,
prison mates partied hard"
"When prison band was jumpin' high
even stone wall started swingin' hard - Let's rock"
"Everybody let's rock!"
"C'mom everybody get together"
"Let's dance the hell out in here"
HERE ROCK!
The next occupation is this:
Pilot
Very popular occupation - let's check it out
Ladies and gentleman,
the Captain for this flight would like to welcome you on board
Captain:
Uchida Yuya
Ahem,
I would like to thank you
for choosing World Airlines flight 69 today.
We will be arriving in London in about 2 hours
Co-pilot:
Shin Onii (New Bro)
Captain,
In...in foreign countries
Veri...vario, various...erm....
Veri...vario, various...erm...
Do you think he was nervous?
I just think these two together will be such a burden for us, eh?
This combination, yes
Ah that hurts...
What's your plan for new year's holiday?
Well, I
I would love to go to Hawaii, I think
Ah that's nice, I like Hawaii too
Yep
Captain's Rock & Roll music is, um
Glob, gbol, glob, globo, global standard, isn't it?
gbol, globo, global standard, isn't it?
Jesus does he still struggle with such a simple sentence??
What the hell happened to Onii?
Is that still not achievable?
Is be having a stage freight?
Stage freight? Really?
Yeah I think so, yes
Paaainful
Uuuuuh it hurts...
I can sense something out of ordinary
He's not himself
Very stiff
Isn't he?
The extent of his nervousness is not normal
Do you think so?
Altitude: OK. Speed: OK.
Direction: OK.
Pilots wouldn't say such things!
I'm not feeling you, you know
Well, I'm not gonna snap, but I'm close to it
Best job nav: Fin
We will find you the best job!
Collaboration with Shin Onii... wow...
Oh
OK guys
As teachers, you too should learn a lot about the world you live
Your moobs are sagging like hell you know
We're going to a little school trip!
We're taking bus, let's go
To broaden the knowledge as teachers
social study excursion
School trip...?
School trip?
Bus...
I'm scared
Where are the five teachers heading to?
They will be steeping into the new world of laughter!!
6h 30mins since the start of teaching duty
They leave the school at once and take a ride to the destination
Needless to speak, it will be plenty of obstacles waiting for them during the excursion
OK guys we're off to the "social" trip
"Social study" trip, you butt
Ooops, yes, "social study" trip, it is
Arriving at a bus stop
Eh?
What is it?
Hmmm?
Why are we stopping here?
Is someone getting on again then?
Seriously? Here?
Actress:
Kimiko Ikegami
Ikegami-san,
I have secured you a role
In a TV dre, dram, eh, 2-hour thr, thriller
OK, now..."Wednesday thriller drama;"
"Hot springs murder case in Wakkanai; the threat from the past"
I see
You have another script right?
Yes
OK, let's do a read-through
Absolutely
Read-through of the script
Ready?
"What made you summon me here?"
"Actually, on that day I saw you in that place by accident"
Hold on a minute
You're not into the role at all!
You have to really, express the feeling, you see?
Again
"What made you summon me here?"
"Actually, I saw you in that place by...."
That is RUBBISH
You're no good for this...OK then
You can go
I'm sorry
What, you going?
Huh?
Excuse me
Yes, you. YOU.
Hey,
can you do a read-through with me?
Matsumoto selected as a read-through buddy
Thank you sir
Ok...
Your part is the one with the red line, ok?
Erm, in...this...position...?
Let's do it...
Yes, let's do it
"What made you summon me here?"
(Kimiko)
"Actually, on that day..."
(Man A)
"I saw you at that place by accident"
"Are you....?
(Kimiko)
Are you suspicious of me??"
"Just because I was there doesn't mean that I am the murderer!"
"I went straight to the airport by myself soon after I said good-bye to him"
YOU
Aren't you improvising too much!?
I don't get the flow!!
I can't react to it if you say the phrase like that...
Oh no no no
What the hell is "YOU"!!!?
Ah
Ouch
You can't beat her with "getting into the role"
You're gonna have to up your game, don't you think?
It's in the script
Is it not??
Is it...?
Right after "what made you...?"
Here, look at it
Matsumoto, skipping the next phrase
There
Oh, apologies for that
Shall we do it again then?
Ok, yes, sorry about that
"What made you summon me here?"
(Kimiko)
"Actually, on that day I saw you in that place by accident"
(Man A)
"are you..., are you suspicious of me!?"
(Kimiko)
"Just because I was there doesn't mean that I am the murderer!"
"I went straight to the airport by myself soon after I said good-bye to him"
"No, you did not go to the airport on that day!"
(Man A)
"Don't you accuse me with such rubbish!"
(Kimiko)
"I went to Paris after that"
"Feel free to take a look at tickets or anything, if you feel so suspicious!"
"Sister!
Please stop...
Let's give it up"
"We can't defy our destiny even if we run away..."
*Enjoy the show even though they laughed already*
"Kanae, What are you talking about?"
Little sister Kanae:
Nakayama Shinobu
"We're finally free as birds after that man is gone forever!"
"There is nothing to worry about,"
(Kimiko)
"we'll live happy ever after, together. OK?"
"Do you really think you can be happy?"
Prosecutor:
Toyota Maho
"You are the one who murdered the man, is that right?"
What the hell is this?
What the heck is going on??
More actors join in the read-through
"I have no idea what you are talking about"
"At around 13.00 on that day,"
"You met up with the man in a hotel room"
I can't follow the plot anymore...
"and you strangled him with the rope while he was having a shower..."
(Prosecutor)
"Stop!"
(Sister: Kanae)
"I don't want to hear it anymore!"
"Then you made everything look like he had commit suicide in the room - and you left"
(Prosecutor)
"Stop it!!!"
(Sister: Kanae)
"Everything started..."
Detective:
Kawahara Sabu
"..with the accident that your father was responsible for, isn't it?"
What a cast
Well, I mean, good casting but...
don't you think the outfit is too spot-on for a read-through??
"He accidentally ran over a person while driving"
(Detective)
Why are they doing this here...
"Since then, the man relatedly pestered you sisters for money"
"Not just that... he started demanding my body"
(Sister: Kanae)
"He's not a man... he's a monster!
(Kimiko)
That's why I killed him!!"
She did it then
"We could be free at last!"
(Kimiko)
"You can never set yourself free by committing a crime!"
(Prosecutor)
What is going on here
What the hell is this complex story?
"Your conscience will be ch, ch, chained down forever"
"I... no, we, sisters...
(Kimiko)
We would find a quiet corner somewhere and build a small house,"
"I wouldn't need anything at all, as long as you can stay happy forever...!"
Anata (You)
Oh, is this...?
*If I build a house one day*
Akiko Kosaka
Singer for the end-roll:
She's having goose bumps
*It would be a small house I guess*
Jeez
Oh man...
*With red roses and white pansies*
*By my side,
right by my side*
*It's you*
The suspect came clean - 2-hour thriller FIN
*You*
They are still in their roles
*I want you to be my side*
Such professionals
Just wow
(Detective)
OK then, let's go
Wait!
What?
She is not gonna run away anymore
Handcuff won't be necessary
(Detective)
...Chief inspector!
Chief inspector!!?
You must have been suffering for a long time
I hope you are feeling relieved by confessing it
Chief inspector
Fujiwara Hiroshi
What is going on man?
Take her
Terrible acting
Huh?
What the hell!!??
That was long
I got totally swept by them
That is not something you would do on a bus ride...
Painful
Wakkanai...
Why Wakkanai...?
The script was totally blank wasn't it?
Yes yes yes
They were improvising right?
Yeah that was a huge surprise
Hey Fujiwara...
Didn't know that you are the chief inspector!
Yeah, all of a sudden
This 2h thriller will get a very high rating for sure!
Of course we ignore him
The casting was top-notch
"Social study excursion" ...
where are they heading to!?
"Social study excursion" led by Fujiwara
Where are they heading to?
Guys,
We are approaching the destination for this excursion
Okey
Yes
Today's destination is,
"Edo" period!!
(Edo period: 1603-1868, the last "Samurai -warrior-" era in history)
Edo period
Social study excursion destination:
We're gonna go back in time to Edo period,
(Edo: old name for Tokyo)
and explore the Edo city
We're going back in time when we press this button
You ready?
Wha..?
Excuse me, I don't get it
We're going back in time...
We're going to Edo period.
We're gonna learn about Edu,
social stu,
Em, Edi...
Let's go back in time
Kabooooom!!
Whoa, we're time-slipping!!
Whooa, we're going back in time!
Whoa, can you feel it happening!!?
Oooooo, getting close!
To Edo period?
To Edo period, yes.
To Edo Period...
what?
Arrived in Edo period
Finally we're here
Looks the same
So it Is Edo period when
we step out of the bus?
That's right
So that was the button for time travelling?
So we time travelled to get to Edo period
Heard it million times already
Hey take a look,
this is, THE real
Edo period!
Oh wow
Looks awesome
Very nicely built
The city looks exactly what you see in the history text book, eh?
Edo period
They arrived in the Edo period when Tokugawa Dynasty was in absolute power...
"Alternative Edo period"
Next stage of batsu game:
The fight against the new bastu assassins will begin
However, this is a place you wouldn't find in a history book...
the alternative Edo period, lost in time...
Shall we go then
What, so, have we had a time travel?
Absolutely; we have arrived in Edo period for real!
A castle town in Edo
"real" Edo period??
Yep, look at the city - looks exactly like what you would see in text book
How many times does he say that?
WHAT
This way
What the hell is this...?
Can you line up in front of the statue here?
Oh here goes again
Would something like this have really existed in the period?
Whoa
Hamada, Matsumoto, Yamasaki here...
Huh?
Look at the statue
This is,
the statue of the 16th Tokugawa Shogun,
Lord Kogemitsu Tokugawa
Did it not end after 15th guy?
Another one after Yoshinobu (15th Shogun)?
16th Shogun
Tokugawa Kogemitsu
By the way,
you can't wonder around with clothes like that
otherwise people will be suspicious of you
You guys need change into something, ok?
Each of you has clothes in cubicles over there
So please change into Edo period-appropriate outfit!
OK let's change in something more appropriate
Oh man...
Second costume....?
Changing into more appropriate clothes
in order to blend in
Everyone changes into something more suitable for this period
First up is...
Fujiwara changed into a typical town girl
Are you all ready??
Yeah
OK then can you all come out at once?
Go ahead
The five change into classic traveller's clothes
You all look good; totally nailing the Edo style
...Okay...
Hmm
Yamasaki.
Can you produce some words of praise?
What, about you?
Um, well, eh...pretty...
Pretty kimono you're wearing
Thank you
OK let's explore then
What the hell...?
Yeah OK
What does he want from this shitty talk??
Why a town girl costume...?
He looks like Anmitsu Hime
(Anmitsu Hime: Heroin in a comedy cartoon popular in 80s)
Why would you want "words of praise" anyway??
Anmitsu Hime, right?
It looks so real - very detailed
You sure that people won't notice that we don't belong here?
No worries, you guys blend in perfectly
Who are we dressed up as?
Once we cross this bridge we'll get to the town centre
Town centre
Can you form a line here?
Wow
Wow it looks awesome!
Gosh it's cold
Wow
Impressive
Where do you want us to line up?
Facing that way?
Amazing
Uh huh
The town centre is just minutes away from here
Hmm?
Oh?
Who are they?
Look
"Secret"
HERE SHE IS!!
Who are they?
Look
Endo Toshihide (Endo's father)
Shimizu no Jirocho
(Shimizu no Jirocho: Famous mafia member in late Edo period - active around Shimizu area)
(Endo's name)
Shozo!
I didn't know you would be here in Edo town!
Wasn't expecting him here!!
Him again?
You know, I thought he seems someone familiar
Really?
Additional rule: The five will be pun
ished by Ninja squad in Edo period
This was totally unexpected - ouch
Ah!
Ouch!!
Seriously, we didn't think it would be him right?
I didn't think he would be here
Ah hurts...
Greetings!
Born in Saihaku, Tottori
Endo as my surname,
given name is Toshihide
People call me as...
Shimizu no Jirocho!
Completely different name
Name is different
Toshihide, isn't it
This one over here is called Ohmasa
Hey, your turn to greet them
Would it be...?
Well, it could well be...
Definitely is
It will be...
Really?
I'm convinced
Endo Kiyomi (mother)
Jirocho Clan, Ohmasa
What the hell is going on with my family??
Greetings
She is incredible...
She can't get into it
This is dangerous
A woman saying that...
She is moving her hand so much
Greetings
My family name is Endo,
my given name is Kiyomi
People call me Ohmasa
My father is..
I am sorry
It's ok, don't worry
That kind of act is impossible for my mother
It's impossible, so...
It's fine, don't force yourself
My first kiss was when I was 18
It was with the boss
The one who snatched my first kiss,
was the boss
But,
in this society, the boss is a very good person
what does that mean?
It's enough seriously
There is still one more person to speak
That is the end of my introduction
Nice to meet you
We can guess who is the last one
It can't be anybody but him
Endo Junji (little brother)
Jirocho Clan - Komasa
Greetings
I...
people call me
Komasa
Recently,
something shocking happened in our house
Our dog is
pregnant!!
That's irrelevant, I don't want to know
I don't care about that episode
Miruku-chan is our dog, and she came back home pregnant
Her breasts also became bigger
That's the end,
nice to meet you
Shozo,
these are our family members
I almost forgot
There is another member
Oi!! Come here!!
What?
Are you kidding me?
Chiaki (Ex-wife)
Mori no Migimatsu
HERE SHE IS!!!
Here she is!!
Onii,
long time no see
Enough of Chiaki
His ex-wife and his family - A miraculous performance together
This is awkward
Onii, it's been some time
My given name is Chiaki
People call me Mori no Migimatsu
Ten years ago...
I married 3rd grade comedian Endo Shozo
We had really sweet and loving times
They are listening
Chiaki, my parents are listening
His parents are going to hear you
Moreover,
there were photos taken while we were drinking once.
After divorce,
keep writing your own gags.
Like right now, here,
in this special show, for the sake of making people laugh,
you get called to this pstion
Speak properly
There are so many traps just in this spot...
We want to do this faster!
The end, nice to meet you
Shozo,
do your best!
Farewell
These 4 together is certainly awkward
Do they meet in private?
They do not
After the divorce
this is the first time like this
It's been 5 years
Let's move on
This is an amazing beginning of the edo period for me
After we enter the district there will be more people
This is amazing
Kogemitsu Clan
What?
What's wrong?
The Kogemitsu Clan thing...
You laughed?
No, I did not laugh at all
Fujiwara please, scold him about this
I always hear this by my side:
Hyuuuuu hyuuuu
or something like that.
That's wrong you know
Did I do that?
"Did I do that?" you ask it again...
like you want to make me laugh.
That's not right, that "hyuuu"
There does not seem to be anyone
They will appear
Suddenly, a collision noise
What's this sound?
There is smoke over there!!
Let's go look!
Fire?
What the hell is that?
Incredible
Here,
everyone come here
A place filled with smoke appears
So much smoke
What's this?
What?
It's a time slip
Terminator appears in Edo period
Censured
Itao Itsuji
Terminator:
There's no need of that kind of entrance
What does this mean?
During his time slip
did he get the time wrong?
You are kidding right?
Why is he not wearing any clothes?
Hey you
did you forget to put clothes on this morning?
Terminator VS Group of samurais
If you do a dogeza (prostrate) we might let you live
Amazing performance
Terminator's incredible apparition
We are sorry
His p*nis... is shrinking by the minute
I was surprised!
It was actually longer than this...
And it was cold
The shrinking part got me...
At first I thought he was wearing one of those that look like you're not wearing anything...
that's why I thought I didn't see anything...
but it's just that it's shrinking
There was something there...
Let's move on
We are also
on a time slip that is
different from his
The generation is...
Let's board the boat cabin
Where are we going?
Is this order ok?
Trip in a boat cabin to the east of Edo city
For the 5 to understand the Edo city even more,
we let them enjoy the boat cabin.
Look! Koi!
Amazing
A peaceful and quiet moment...
This is supposed to be a relaxed trip for the 5, however...
They can't let their guard down
It was a little long, wasn't it?
It was.
What is this?
Nothing happened...
Nothing happened and...
I thought, this is not good...
Really, we will get sick of this
Nothing happened at all
In the end, the trip ends with nothing happening at all
The trip ends with nothing happening at all
Once we got out we got punished
Nothing happened at all
That was long, seriously!
What the hell?! Ah!!
I was certain something
was going to appear from the lake
That was really funny
It was something new
This is your station
Edo's rookie training room
Please sit at your own respective seats
Isn't this amazing?
This is just amazing
Take a rest
Just amazing
Here is our room
Yes, once again, they'll see what's in the drawers
7:30 minutes since the start
Brief stop of activities
I only took a glance on this but, what is it?
This is a claw crane machine for the figure Tokugawa Kogemitsu
Tokugawa Kogemitsu giveaways
I don't want to play it
What is written?
100 yen?
It's 100 yen
So it's using cash
Ah!! maybe it's in the drawers?
In one of them
On the lookout for the contents of the drawers
It's here
It's here too?
Maybe it's in the drawer of one of us
We just arrived and we have to do this again?
Let's do this then, from here
First batter: Endo
Well we don't know yet
Nothing
It might be something old too...
There's something
Lots of 100 yen coins
There are a lot of coins
Open everything
Waa... again
It appeared
Look at this
Weekly tabloid magazine
Why are they bringing this here again
Then it's my turn
Wa!!
This is probably the same too
There is enough 100 yen coin
Ramen?
Black
Suga Cup
Tonkatsu with black oil
Cup ramen
I should be safe, come on!
Suga-san's face is...
What the heck
Suga Cup
That is all
I think there's one for each of us
Gasu?
These are edible right?
Tonkatsu with black oil
Black
Suga Cup
Cup ramen
I wonder how does it taste
Black
Suga Cup
1.8 times
Tonkatsu with black oil
1.8 times, it says
Let's look at this (the panel)
Hamada (Baby Gorilla)
This picture is seriously...
It shouldn't be allowed
Tanaka, want to go next?
Yes
A scroll
Suspicious scroll
What could it be?
Put it away for now
Isn't it a hanging scroll?
Nothing here
Last one
Nothing
Then I will go
next
Nothing
There's something there
Ahh what the hell is that?
Maybe it's full of coins for that
Suspicious box
It is for that, right?
Eh?
Ticking sound
Wait a moment
This seems like a time bomb
It sounds electronic...
Scary, I am so alerted
OH MY GOD
It's dynamite!
Money box = time bomb
We just cut the wire
Which one should I cut?
How come we have time bomb in Edo period!!?
Come here, come - stay with me!!
Stay with you?
Seriously come here
Just do it
Just one person!!
Just one person!!!!
Who?
Tanaka!!
No~!!
Just cut it
Come here
Which one are you going for?
Red red RED!!!!!
Stop pulling me!!
Ready?
Yes
I will cut now
10 seconds left
Cut!
It is not stopping at all!!
Bloody hell man
This blows!
What a prank - I'm annoyed now
It's irritating
What's wrong with you Tanaka
How delayed was that explosion? Awful
If the explosion doesn't happen in 0 second
why would it display the time in the first place, don't you think?
They are making fun of us
They are really making fun of us, yeah
What a waste of energy - totally I'm drained
My body
went into defense mode - tightened up
My turn
It's very scary
It's fine
I'm really not keen on something
jumping out from the drawer you know
Maybe it will in Matsumoto drawer
One more
It's the last one
What is this?
It's him, isn't it?
It's him in puppet form
Ventriloquism puppet Hama-chan
It's DownTown
It's really well made
It moves
I got a bit excited with that
What the heck
We all got excited you know
I am tired
So tired!
We'll be chilling a bit so
go get those Kogemitsu figures with those (100 yen coins) from your drawer
That's right
I have never play in a claw crane machine before
Just try it
Maybe you will get it
That's good
Ooh
Nice one
Here comes
There we go
Are you kidding me?
Pushing it?
That is not possible
No way we can get it now man
So you hit the side
That's right, so it will be pushed
Both figure toys successfully obtained at the same time!!
We were just celebrating weren't we...?
It's just joy
That's amazing
Because it's 2 figure so it stuck inside
The dispensing hole is clogged up with the boxes
Hey everyone
Currently at the courthouse...
an unforgivable criminal is being judged
Let's go take a look
We can look?
Yes we can
Observing villains in Edo town
being tried
in the courtroom
They will observe a trial in Edo period court,
What will the five be witnessing??
Wow Daimyo Gyoretsu?
Yep, that's Daimyo Gyoretsu
Daimyo Gyoretsu
(The long line of regional governor (Daimyo) and his entourage, typical in Edo period. Town residents must be bowing down while the entire group goes past. Governors were authorised for "instant execution (Mondo Muyo)" of those walking across in front of the line, or not bowing to them)
That
Let's go to the side guys
Yeah you can't cross the street right?
Where shall we stay?
Line up here and site down
Bow down, bow down
You must not cut across in front of the line
So cold
You imbecile
Small girl cuts thought the line
Girl,
how dare you
- you are not respecting the Lord!
Even if you are a kid,
it is still unforgivable
Ohana!!!!!
Oh no Ohana....
Girl's father
Maomasa Musaka (actor)
Sir, please forgive her
Since
my wife passed away 5 years ago,
I've been taking care of my daughter Ohana on my own
We've been living strong no matter what we go through - together!
She is the joy of my life...!
Silence!!
You need to be taught a lesson!!
You are unforgivable!!
Father gets executed on behalf of his daughter
Ohana,
from now, by yourself
keep living your life
Heartbreaking moment - father bades farewell to his daughter
Father!!
Let's
Carnival!!
It's showtime!!!
Happy Boy Daimyo
Okada Keisuke (comedian)
Here I come! Yeah!!
It's enough seriously
Everyone say yeah!!!
The comedy
is all about the timing
Please bear with the drag
- the machine moving too slowly!
Everybody!!!
Happy boys, in business as usual!!!!
Thank you very much
Carvinal is passing by! YEAH
Stop!!
Very well
Hey, bit
bit
OPEN
WHAOOO!!!!
I see,
thank you very much
Look at these robots everyone
I just don't get what the hell he is doing
It's here,
punishment time
Ok c'mon!!
One
&
two
Very good, that's very good
You're swinging (the bat) from the waist - very good technique
That aside,
I am currently on a laughing spree
Ooh?
They are not laughing at all??
Maybe he is dead
Happy boy attempts resuscitation on the father
There is no other choice,
mouth to mouth
Although the same surname Okada,
(*Ijillie Okada - comedian, famous for pervert comments. Used to be in a popular porn TV programme in 90s)
I am now Ijillie Okada
(Gilgamesh Night - a porn TV programme in which Ijillie Okada used to be a presenter)
Gilgamesh!
WOOOOOW!!!!!
What the hell is wrong with you man!
No time to wow you know!
Seriously what a cheap act man!!
Everyone got it
A cheap act is my specialty!
Yeah use your waist (to swing)
Five,
five!
Delayed five!
Thank you very much
If it's like this, there's no other choice
I will use my body heat
To resurrect your father
My nipples and his nipples, like magnetic poles
Combined!
This guy is an idiot, a real idiot
What the heck is that
What is the matter with you
For me to be in this position
is a very fruity happy boy's love (fruity gay moment)
...what am I talking about!!
Did I work enough to deserve my commission then!?
See you!!!
Doesn't he say "wow" for the exit huh?
He should have said "wow" for one last laugh don't you think?
Why am I the only one
At least end it with a "WAW"
Doesn't these happyboy's robot seems expensive?
They are seriously using lots of money
Let's go
In the end, no one saved him
Just laying dead
That girl is a true actor - shedding so much tears for real
I was this close to start weeping in sympathy
True that
Me too
That was really good acting
Don't you think these robots could have been better-looking?
Agree
Look, there is a crowd in the street over there
What is it now?
Let's have a closer look, shall we?
What is it?
People in town gathering up; what is happening...
Are we not supposed to be observing a trial?
That's right
Can you guys line up here?
Hey look!
(*Known for his extravagant style to throw a box full of gold to people in the street)
Edo's Robin Hood - Nezumi Kozou the chivalrous thief appears
Whoa
That's Nezumi Kozou
Wow
Oh my goodness
Henmi Mari (actress)
Town resident:
Nezumi Senpai (comedian)
That's Nezumi Senpai
Oh wow
Oh yes, that's him
Ah, I see
Oh I get it - "Nezumi" combination...
Enjoy the show although the five have laughed already
Why is he not getting the Nezumi Kozou role?
Here come the police officers!!
Nezumi Kozou makes an exit
Officers in pursuit of Nezumi Kozou
Oh my goodness
Egashira 2:50 (comedian)
Town official:
There he goes
YOU IDIOTS!!!!
Hip Attack!
Punishment to those who picked up the stoled money
Are you OK??
Nezumi Senpai is completely knocked down
Get out of my way!!!
Ooooooah here we go!!
A town resident taken in custody
and transported by wheelbarrow
Wheelburr...
Yeah man
Uuuuuuh
What the hell...
Don't do that
It's cold out here, you know
OUTTA WAY!!!!
What the hell man
Dear me
He's insane, really
Goodness me...
OUCH
Argh!
Argh!!
Ah hurts
Aw
Shouldn't Nezumi Senpai play the role of Nezumi Kozou?
Absolutely
Why was he butt-attacked instead?
Shall we make our way to the court?
Everything is just so unpredictable
So what was Ega-chan (Egashira 2:50) angry about after all??
I am not sure
That was definitely Mari (Henmi) by the way
What? Who's Mari?
Noone except Hamada noticed
Town resident: Mari Henmi
Henmi Mari
WHAT, seriously??
I didn't notice that at all!!
I didn't either
I failed to notice too
We're going to a courtroom now
Cold
Let's go inside
Let's take a seat in the front row
Looks so cool...
Chihara Junior
Magistrate Official: Constable
I had no idea...
Kitamachi Magistrate:
Sir Tohyama Saemonjo
Approaches!
Takeuchi Riki (actor)
Tohyama Saemonjo
Everyone, raise your head
We are here today,
as one man under the title of a doctor,
has repeatedly groped our daughters
and we'll examine what this perverted doctor has done.
Habitual Sexual Harassment Doctor
Villains of Edo: The 1st
Without further ado, sir Tohyama
Shall we bring the criminals out to the court?
Bring them out
Come!
Sit!
Azuma Mikihisa (Actor)
Town Doctor
Sit!
You are accused of repeated lewd body contact with the oiran
(Oiran = Predecessors of Geisha restricted to High-Class individuals)
Perverted Doctor,
are you not Azuma Mikinohei?
Yes
Sir Tohyama,
the daughters who were groped by this perverted doctor are here...
shall we call them out here?
Of course
Come in!
Kanou Sisters
Oiran
Was this doctor the person who groped you?
Yes,
We would not forget, ...re certain it is him.
We would not forget, we are certain it is him.
Is it supposed to be so out of synch?
These pebbles are something else...
Azuma Mikinohei,
Yes
Do you have any rebuttal?
I lost sight of myself,
and committed such conduct
However, this time!...
I'd like to express my remorse
with an apology letter I've written.
If at all possible, I'd like to convey this remorse,
is this ok?
Sir Tohyama, shall we let him?
You can read it
Thank you
Apology Letter
While I,
Azuma Mikinohei,
am currently titled as a doctor...
To my patients the Kanou sisters,
I have comitted lewd ac... acts
with my past conduct,
and conduct I've gone on to do,
I offer my sincerest apology.
He stuttered because it was cold...
I'd like this to go more smoothly
I offer my sincerest apology.
However,
if you allow me to offer an excuse for my actions...
that would be because the sister's bodies
are so lustful exactly like American women
I couldn't care less whether they were Oiran or Inran (slut in Japanese).
As the sisters were in horny & flirtatious attire,
I could not help myself but fondle those unnecessarily huge boobs.
The enormous boobs unable to tell whether fake or not,
and huge nipples...
The sisters' huge nipples, and the fact that they are such horny sluts,
I never dreamed of myself so aroused by the combination.
What are you talking about?
What the hell are you on about?
You aren't apologising are you?
Apologise to the sisters!
Ouch...
Please, I beg your pardon
Oiran sisters,
How was his appeal?
I am so upset how dehumanising he is!
Sir Touyama,
please make a judgment on the case.
Enough of your bloody excuse - I'm sick of listening to you!!
The sun may shine on you despite your crime,
but me and my "Tohyama Sakura" won't forgive you for what you did!!!
(cherry blossom tattoo on his shoulder)
Sir...!!
Quack medic,
Azuma Mikinoppe
I sentence you to Sanzoku (bandit) Mue Thai kick!!!
Quack's sentence:
Sanzoku Mue Thai kick
What?
Thai kick???
Get up!
Bloody hell, there's no mercy
Do not move!
Freeze!
Be strong, Mikinohei!!
Mikinohei!
Mikinohei, it's really, really bad - I tell you
Don't put your bum up so high man!!
Lower your bum a bit
Don't hide your butt!
Mikinohei...!
OH MY GOD
That must hurt...
That looks SO painful
That must hurt so bad
That's painful
You bet your ass it is
The pain will last for a while, alright?
It won't go away...
Aw
It will linger for a while
The pain will go away ...in due course.
Case closed!!
Take him away!!
Get up!!
Well well... that kick must have been sooo painful
Move!!
Oh man....
He's feeling it
Sir, please proceed to the next case
Well then
Recently people in Edo have been talking about a man,
(Ikkyu: a monk known for his knowledge and quick wit)
He is known as "fake Ikkyu" - I would like to put him on trial.
Bring him in!
Edo's villain #2
Fake Ikkyu the trickster
Fake Ikkyu
Shin Onii
He is known as "fake Ikkyu" - I would like to put him on trial.
Bring him in!
Edo's villain #2
Fake Ikkyu the trickster
Fake Ikkyu
Shin Onii
Recently there is a man who claims himself as Ikkyu,
and tricks people in town
Are you the one?
I am the real
I am the real Ikkyu!!!
Ikkyu is supposedly among the best in town when it comes to quick wit.
If you insist that you are the real Ikkyu,
let's see how good you are - it that understood?
I will have a go!
Is he the real Ikkyu!?
Verify his identity with quick wit questions
Here is the first one
Bring "it" in!
Yes sir!
Tell you what,
the tiger on this screen,
keeps Judge Tohyama here awake with its howling every night - he is not able to rest soundly.
Ikkyu, show us how you capture this tiger on the screen using your wit, in front of us now!
Ready?
Catch the tiger drawn on the screen
As long as this tiger is inside the sc- screen
I cannot make this beast quiet
Please make the tiger come out of the screen first.
After that, I will make this tiger stop howling as you wish
That's the famous punch line by real Ikkyu that everyone knows
Use your own wit and come up with something new!
If you cannot make the beast come out of the screen,
I...if you get a cage over here
I will put this screen in the cage
and let me demonstrate how to get the screen out
Eh?
Hmmm....
Well, we have no cage that we can use!
Come up with something else without using the cage!!
W- without the cage,
it's impossible, right?
He gave up on it so quickly
Why is he angry anyway?
That's enough!
Ikkyu,
I hear that real Ikkyu has a passion for acting
and apparently he excels at reenacting a number of very well known scene from famous soap operas.
Is he the real Ikkyu!?
Verify his identity with his acting skills
Let's see how good you are with acting
First off is the very famous one;
Scene in which Inspector Jipan is killed on duty
Let us see how you handle it
*From 70s drama "Taiyo ni Hoero" (Howl at the sun) - Inspector Jipan's last words "What the hell is this!!?" while looking at his own blood after getting shot by suspect during pursuit)
Scene in which Inspector Jipan is killed on duty
Taiyo ni hoero!
I cannot do that!!
> What? Why can't you do it?
I don- don't know that sc- sc- scene
What a firm rejection
The reason of rejection is unbelievable
What the hell...?
Aaw!
Uuuuuh
Oh that hurts!
Then he is not a real Ikkyu is he?
He has tried so many things and accomplished a lot before
That's right huh?
You are supposed to be the real Ikkyu
Is that right?
Y, ye, yes...
Then you must be good at acting!
Right then,
the scene from "Kita no kinu kara" where the family is at a ramen restaurant
Mmm
Yep - in which Kuniei Tanaka (actor)
snaps at the waitress.
Let us see that famous phrase
"Kita no kuni kara (From the Northern Country)"
*Actor Kuniei Tanaka yells "can't you see my kids are still eating!?" at waitress who tries to take the unfinished plate away from his kids as the restaurant is closing for the day
Famous phrase at the ramen restaurant
With the cold weather like this,
ramen tastes so good!
The cold weather and the warmth from the ramen...
Ramen tastes so GOD DAMN DELICIOUS WHEN IT IS SO BLOODY COLD OUT THERE!!!
He's just angry - not acting!
Just angry
"Ramen tastes so good when it's cold out there!" he said...
So painful
OK next
from "The 101st Proposal",
you know the scene where Tetsuya Takeda (actor) shouts the famous phrase when he bolts out in front of an incoming lorry, don't you?
Let us see how you reenact the scene
"The 101st Proposal"
*Tetsuya Takeda shouts "I will not die! Because I love you!!"
Famous phrase after jumping in front of the lorry while the heroine watches him in terror
Oh careful, careful!!!
It's the 101st proposal!!
He just shouted the drama series's title
What the hell
Just shouting the title
Shin Onii doesn't know any of these famous drama series at all, does he?
Indeed
I just don't understand why though
"101st proposal!!!!"
He doesn't even try to impersonate the actors at all
Enough!
You are not a real Ikkyu!!
Your Honour,
please pass the judgement
Oi, you!
Enough of your bloody excuse - I'm sick of listening to you!!
The sun may shine on you despite your crime,
but me and my "Tohyama Sakura" won't forgive you for what you did!!!
Fake Ikkyu!!
You are sentenced to
public humiliation, then death penalty by decapitation!!
Public humiliation & death penalty by decapitation
Sentence to the fake Ikkyu
Harsh punishment...
Stand up!!
Quick!
Do you want to leave us the last word before the execution?
Toam- toa-, it's--...
It is such an honour to be given the sentence by Sir Judge Tohyama
I can, erm, I can die with real fun now
What a joke!!
I can't handle him - too funny
What the hell is "I can die with real fun"?
Oh bloody hell...
Too much, too much to handle
Your Honour.
Shall we move on to the next case?
Sure
Next up is...
a man who seduces innocent girls by flirtatious texts
An outrageous pervert will be put on trial.
Your Honour,
Edo's villain #3
Flirtatious pervert
Would you allow me to bring the accused into the court?
Yes - bring him in!
Yes sir!
Whoa
Stand up!!
What?
Endo is put on trial
Move!!
Shake your legs!!
Come on!!
Sit down!!
Wha...what???
Huh???
Sit down!!
Eh???
Well then,
bring his family in too!
WHAT
Huh?
Kidding, right?
The Endos are also brought into the courtroom
What the hell...?
Chiaki too?
Bloody hell man...
So she is still considered as his family huh?
What the hell is the "Endos"...
Your name is Endo Shozo - is that correct?
Yes
The reason why you are put on trial...
do you know what it is?
Well - to be honest,
nothing at all
"Nothing at all"?
Yes
Let me ask you something then
Your inappropriate photos were up in a tabloid paper in the past- is that right?
Is he cheating!?
Photo taken by TV crew
Scoop! Cocorico's Endo & a pretty girl from
Gaki TV crew goes on a date in Roppongi
Ahem - yes, that is correct, however,
Erm....
To be honest with you,
I believe I was framed by the crew
You are right about that
As you said, this article was based on TV crews' conspiracy to frame you
Yes that's right
However - what lies beneath is that, with this girl, Misa,
you are still in touch with her via texts according to our intelligence.
Your Honour,
I would like to show you some of the texts Endo sent to the girl - is that OK with you?
Very well - let's have a look!!
Disclosing the content of Endo's texts
Is Endo a flirtatious pervert!?
Seriously?
Hey Endo, are you alright??
Hang in there buddy
Oh?
What's the matter Endo?
Please sir...
Endo!!
Please, I beg you for your mercy...
Step back!!!
Well...
My own parents and brother are here...
And my ex-wife is here too...
Seriously please...
Ah man
Hold on man, it's just some texts right?
Is that THAT bad??
Texts... hmmm....
Are your texts so bad then??
Aw that hurts
I'm not sure which part of the texts you will be showing so...
It all started 2 years ago,
Endo flirted with Misa who used to work as an extra in this program
Misa-san
when Endo eyed up on Misa, who worked as an extra in Gaki episodes,
and started flirting with her after work, while no one took notice of his behaviour.
This incident came under scrutiny during the Gaki's "absolutely no laughing" episode a few years ago,
Disclosed text message
From: Cocorico Endo "Good work today!
Misa chan, be honest with me if you have
BF already. From the look, I see you are
definitely M (sexually submissive)!
Shall I teach you a lot of "lessons"??? :-D"
Since then, his attempt to play around with her has ceased.
However!
HOWEVER!
Last year, in December 2011,
after a year without any apparent activity,
Misa got a text from Endo!
Sorry...
You brewed it for a year, didn't you?
Please, I beg you...
Here is the text he sent her!!
Endo
Misa-san
Secret
sent
Definitely this time,
@$&)*^%$!@$
Last year, in December 2011,
after a year without any apparent activity,
Misa got a text from Endo!
You brewed it for a year, didn't you?
Please, I beg you...
Here is the text he sent her!!
Endo
From: Cocorico Endo
How have you been?
I want to see yooou Misa ^_^
It's been a year ;-)
Misa-san
Next time we meet up,
sent
shall I give you a "lesson" then? LOL!
"it's been a year"
"how have you been?"
"I want to see you Misa"
"Next time we meet up, shall I give you a "lesson" then? LOL!"
What the hell were you doing man!!?
What a bombshell that was
Couldn't we have not aired this?
Ouch!!
We didn't know what the TV crew was up to either you know
Sit down Endo!
My parents are here...
Look behind you Endo
How can I look at them!!??
Well well well
You know what,
not just your parents - look at the one on the right!!
Jeez, scary
Oh my god...
Well?
What do I do now...?
And then,
Have you got more??
Of course
Since the message was sent to Misa, he started flirting with her
And in this occasion,
what did you ask her to do - eh?
Endo!
Yes
What did you ask her?
He hasn't heard anything - nothing
I don't know anything either
Erm, well, I'm not really...
To be honest
I don't remember very clearly so... you know...
You must remember - are you sure you don't?
I really don't - honestly
Sure?
Endo started asking her to send him a mobile photo of her
Here is the text message by him:
"Awwww! Your photo pweeeese!"
"Hey, I want your photo just for me, pweeese!
Can you send me a recent photo of you??"
"I'll be waiting for it! I want something
a little naughty pweeese! Hurry uuuup"
Endo
From: Cocorico Endo
Misa-san
sent
"Hey, I want your photo just for me, pweeese (please)"
"Can you send me the recent photo of you??"
Next one is "Awwww! Your photo pweeeese!"
Dear me - Shozo!!!
"I'll be waiting for it! I want something a little naughty pweeese! Hurry uuuup"
Shozo!!!
Seriously...
You...!
Endo!!
Endo!
How come we don't know this man!!?
Shozo!!
Please sentence me to death right now
Yuck!
Shozo!!!
Seriously
Well done you!
What a lady killer!! Come on!!
Come on Endo
Shozo!
You! Seriously!
Man up!!
"Awwww! Your photo pweeeese!"
"Hey, I want your photo just for me, pweeese!
Can you send me a recent photo of you??"
"I'll be waiting for it! I want something
a little naughty pweeese! Hurry uuuup"
Endo
Misa-san
sent
"Pweeese", "Pweeese", and "Pweeese" again,
what the hell is wrong with you?
Hey (Endo's) mother! Why are you laughing!?
And the last texts he sent out to her,
let's have a look
"When we meet up next time,
1) Pweeese
2) No pweeese
Endo
From: Cocorico Endo
Misa-san
do you want a "lesson" from me?
sent
which is it??"
"When we meet up next time, do you want a "lesson" from me? 1) Pweeese 2) No pweeese - which is it??"
Shozo!!!
Ahh....
You're such an idiot!!!!
Fool...
You're the biggest fool aren't you!!??
What the hell is wrong with you?
"Pweeese"... the word doesn't even exist in this world you know
What the hell are you trying to achieve by asking her like a quiz?
Huh?
Yes...
So bad
Your Honour,
This Endo guy
What would like to do with him?
Well, I kind of understand where he is coming from, as a man, hmm
This is a difficult case...
Mmm?
Huh?
Your Honour,
I am actually able to present you
another case against this man
WHAT?
There are still other crimes Endo has commited!!
You're kidding right? What the hell? What the hell?
During the exact same time
Endo tried to get in with another woman at the same time.
He was trying it on another woman at the same time!
Is Endo a complete pervert?!
Wait, what is it? You're kidding me right?
Ehh, wait a minute!
Even more surprising is that she is
also a comedian
You've been REALLY pushing it on her
haven't you!?
EHHHHH, what what what what?!
Is it ok if we call her in?
Wait, wait, what, seriously what?!
Bring her in
Enter!
No seriously, who is it? Who?
After the break
Her identity is revealed!!
Mystery Talent
ENTER!
Seriously what? Who is it?
I'm sure everyone here knows who she is
Food researcher
Morizaki Yuki
She is from the Food research show, Morizaki Yuki.
So Morizuki san, if I may ask
Has Endo tried to
seduce you?
Yes, no question about it.
How much shit do people have on you!?
Ye and we're getting hit because of you!
Why then do we have to sit here and listen to this because of you?
Wait, look, he can't move or say anything at all!
You're right, he's hardly moving at all.
Anyway, the whole thing started..
All started on Cocorico's program
It all started on the famous Cocorico's show
where Morizaki-san was starring as a guest.
At one point, Morizaki san
went to check everything was okay in one of the scenes she had just done on film
and so went to the studio.
And the person who was there
was Endo Shouzou.
He liked Morizaki so much
after one look
that he did something unbelievable after the recordings had finished
He went to one of his juniors, who was good friends with Morizaki
and asked Tano Shingo
Tano Shingo
and forcifully got Morizaki's
email adress and phone number.
Why are you standing?
OOOOIIIII!
Don't run away.
Pwease sit down properly.
Forced contact details off a junior.
Is Endo a complete pervert?!
So he got the email adress and the phone number.
And then he straight away went and
called her, didn't you
And according to Morizakisan's records, the phone conversation was as follows:
Endo's phone call
Oh hello, do you know who this is? It's Cocorico Endo.
I just wanted to thank you for working so hard on my show last time
The TV ratings were so great and I'm so grateful
that I want to thank you, so let's go out with Tano Shingo sometime, what do you say?
However
this
dinner
Due to unfortunate scheduling differences,
Due to scheduling, didn't happen
they never got a chance to go to dinner.
Aaah, that's good!
So then Endo..
I guess he just couldn't wait any longer
He abused his powers as a comedian
He contacted one of the production companies and asked
Can I not do a show with Morizaki san?
and tried to sort something out with them
Tries to force getting closer to Morizaki-san
Is Endo a total pervert?
And just really coincidentally, really coincidentally,
there was a food show which was being planned out
and the only person who had been casted
was in fact
Morizaki-san
and so reluctantly, they mentioned Endo's name
and he was booked to come onto the show.
And he was made one of the co-stars
That did happen!
A cooking Gran Prix show
Morizaki
It did, didn't it Endo-kun!
I remember..
Of course, you're the one who made it happen.
So, whilst filming
The show itself was good but
Endo wasn't experienced in
cooking programs and
whatever nice food he ate, he shouted
'That's SHOOO NIIIICEEE!!'
and he would just shout that
time after time again.
what the hell does that mean?
You don't really do that on a cooking program..
What the hell is that man..
Seriously man..
That's like a different kind of punishment
On this night
Endo sent this kind of email to her.
Endo
Thanks so much for making me food today.
It was so nice that when I return to Tokyo,
I would love looooove it if you could
make me some for myself, pwease?
Morizaki
sent to
Thanks so much for making me the food today.
It was so delicious
that when I return to Tokyo,
can you make some just for me, pwease?
Always say 'Hochii (Pwease)'
Is Endo a complete pervert?!
This isn't the truth, right?!
This is all fake right?
It is all.. True.
I feel so weak right now
Please
punish this
complete pervert
You're right, I can't let him off.
To the guys that have been listening the whole time,
Endo family,
as his family members, do you have anything to say to defend him?
Toyama-sama
Can I make a statement to defend him?
Who are you?
defends her ex husband
The ex wife
I am his ex wife
What does the ex wife have to say for him?
Go on then
Toyamasama, you may not know something.
Ex wife - Chiaki's statement
Endo is really stupid
but he is a very kind and cute person.
Even coming into 2012,
even though he has a girlfriend
he was cheating on her with another woman
that was exposed
and nearly made the news as a huge scandal
At that time
Endo called me, his ex wife
and asked me to do something about that newspaper article.
and he begged me
Why would you ask her!?
What the hell?
I just don't get this world..
And one more thing..
It's a completely different story to the one just now
Ex wife - Chiaki's statement
but a few months ago,
he told me he was really after this woman
and he was close to getting her where he wanted her
and he called me, his ex wife to tell me this!
What's wrong with you, seriously?
So Toyama-sama, please forgive him.
It's just been affairs
after affairs with you.
Even if the god of the sun forgave you
I,
and the blowing cherry blossoms
will not forgive you!!
You will
Face the ass cannon as punishment!!
Ass Cannon Punisment
Total Pervert's punishment
Hurry up and do it
Egashira 2:50
The cannon itself
Today there is going to be a revolution!
I'm going to make it happen in the Edo times!!
Here it comes!!
This is way too much. I wouldn't be able to take it
This is just ridiculous
Now the punishments have been handed out
Just amazing.. No one is laughing even..
Shall we head back?
Yes please
Let's go right now.
Endo, let's go
We're leaving.
Seriously man...
That was just amazing.
I know, I never expected it to become something this big..
Wow man...
Can they really show this on TV?
It'll be ok
They can, it's fine
Wow, if it was me, I don't think I would let them.
ENDO? ENDO? ENDO?
Let's recover. Come on.
Get a hold of yourself man.
The Edo Times are a laughing hell
To the bum and the heart
a huge scar is left!!
Even in the Edo times, there is a ton of traps for them.
will continue to haunt the 5!!
And after this, there will be even worse yet to come.
Even worse things and laughter traps
Right then,
the last part was just so ridiculous that..
I know right..
It makes the whole of the first half look kind of like....
If there's one thing that I can say right now
don't air that part on TV...
pwease
Good on you man..
Brave..
I think everyone feels for you and you have more fans now.
Seriously, yes, you were able to take that much..
Yes, you should just use it from now on every time you get yourself into shit.
I'm going to try make this a famous catch phrase. I will.
Ah... I'm so tired.. So so tired..
They really got me good...
Please initiate the next segment
I want the next video,
Please~!
9:00 P.M., and the injuries from the verdict still have not healed.
Seriously...
That was powder from Ega-chan.
Yes it was.
I wasn't expecting that stuff when we were told "Let's go see an Edo trial"...
I have too many eccentricities...
Yeah...
Tanaka, can't you stop him?
His eccentricities...?
Why don't we live together?
I'm sorry... that's impossible.
As your eldest son? Is that impossible?
But the best option would be...
to be under Hamada's jurisdiction, don't you think?
I was thinking that too.
What do you mean? Why?
I think it's best if he became Hamada-san's adopted child...
Yeah, the younger one...
Father...
Hama-father...
What the hell are you saying?
What about injecting female hormones?
What do you mean?
Apparently you'll calm down if you take female hormones...
In the end it's just that your male hormones are too strong...
It's not good to say this myself, but it worries me...
This is a church built by a foreign missionary,
Where You Can Tell Your Secrets
Church
where people can reveal their darkest secrets
Seeking Salvation
People Who Bear Problems Visit
Many people bearing problems come here to seek salvation.
Father
Jimmy Onishi
Enter, troubled one.
Even this video is set in the Edo period.
He sure has an incredible face.
We livdgin....live in Edo and we've decided to get married.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I've heard that you provide marriages of your country's style, Ohnishi Xavier-san.
(The character is based on Francisco Xavier, a famous christian missionary who came to Japan.)
If it's done Xavier-style, then you must read the vow of...vows so
if you can vow....vow everything
that ceremony will fini...finish.
When the
husband
dies, then the wife
cannot
choose
the next husband, correct?
No...
Let's try not to laugh.
Sorry.
You can hit harder!
Wasn't there supposed to be a song of blessing?
Holin la~
silen nai
With you~
success you~
Little hagen
there
three
one
two
Jimmy-san's no good, even in Edo.
*He accidentally says 'onameru mono' (one who licks) instead of 'onayameru mono' (troubled one). Not sure how you might want to do this one. Maybe you can think of a better one than I did?
Enter, trebbled one.
What kind of person is that?
Don't let them in!
At least say that properly!
How shall I use the contents of this box?
Very Stinky Harmonica
Could you show me how to use it?
Yes
Urgh
cough
Oh please stop it...just stop.
It's gonna be a long road from here. He just came out.
Yes
Urgh
cough
URRRGHHH!
Oh please...seriously stop it!
Kukukuku! (Chuckling)
You can hit harder.
-- Seriously, please stop it.
It's only the beginning.
Are you okay?
Ugh
Gufgh
URGGHH
I'd like you to play more because it makes a lovely sound.
Please...just take this away now.
-- No but please!
It's on my hands...my hands...it's disgusting.
I don't want to hold it anymore!
No, no, no! I don't want...I don't want to hold it!
Please go home! I don't want to do this!
Please...
Please stop....URGH
UVVEEERGGH
My nose is really very sensitive.
VGHEEARRGH!
OGGHEREEEGH!
It's on my hands.
URBOEEGGH
GAHA
His sense of smell is good so...
You need to put more elbow into it.
You should be able to put more elbow in it.
Right, please go home. It's not good anymore.
Ohnishi Xavier Continues To Save Many People
Ohnishi Xavier now continues to lend a helping hand to many people.
Finally!
That's a relief.
He's even here in the Edo period.
-- Yeah he is.
Everybody, there's trouble!
The two fire fighting squads of Edo city are disputing over territory!
Come before it gets too serious!
-- Oh forgot about those guys...
Can you go and mediate, since you're teachers.
A fire fighting territory feud erupts
The 5 go to mediate as teachers
A feud erupts between two fire fighting groups.
Being teachers, the five hurry to mediate.
They seem to have somewhat realised,
but just what is awaiting them there?
What is awaiting them there!?
Edo city is beautiful at night too, isn't it?
Huh?
I thought that Edo city is beautiful at night too.
Sorry.
Assembly Hall
I'm coming in.
We came to stop the fire cuz you guys took so long!
Woah!
Explosive Mood
It's an explosive atmosphere.
The place where you guys came to extinguish a fire
was the territory of the Degawa Group!
Don't just leave a fire burning, ya idiots!!
I'll leave the rest to you!!
You wanna fight aye!?
Bring it on then!
Fine then asshole!
We'll put our bodies on the line and battle then!
Let's go you dogs!
Negotiations Breakdown Settle it with a body risking battle!!
Maaan, they're really angry.
We're gonna mess you up!
We, the Ueshima group are gonna...
Ueshima Group Wakagashira
Kendo Kobayashi
show you how gutsy we are!
Bring "that" thing!
Hurry up damn it!
Our boss Ueshima...
Ueshima Group Boss
Ueshima Ryuhei
...isn't scared of jumping into fire!
Right boss?
Yeah, that's for sure.
Don't push yourself!
From now, the boss will extinguish this fire...
with his ass.
Alrighty!
I won't even leave a trace!
Extinguish the candle fire with his ass within 1 minute
Ueshima Group's Will
1 minute is enough, right?
Yeah, 1 minute is fine.
Ok, in 1 minute....put that fire out!
Come on boss!
You can do it boss!
Wow.
Did ya see that, bastards!?
That took you more than 20 seconds, ya wuss!
That was nothin'!
Degawa Group
Hosshan.
We got a guy that can do it in under 20 seconds!
Stop lying, jackass!
-- S
Go on!
Degawa Group
Haranishi Kouki
Let's do this!
Check out the thickness of this candle!
Degawa Group's Will
Will extinguish fire with the ass on a thicker candle than before
It's more than twice the thickness!
Not my problem if you get hurt!
How many seconds will ya take?
10 seconds!
You ok?
I'M FINE!
Ready...start!
YEAAHH!
See what we can do?
You did better than we expected.
Well done Haranishi!
This is standard! This is standard!
What do we fire fighters put out fires with? Water of course!
We also need this. Hey bring it out!
Woah!
Have you heard of goldfish scooping?
Of course I have.
I'll put this tube on my head,
they'll then pour goldfish inside it
and I'll catch all of them with my mouth!
Ueshima-Group's Will
Wear a special water tank, put lots of goldfish inside and catch with mouth
Are you serious...?
Wonder if you can do it?
Can you handle such a tight thing?
Is he okay?
This is dangerous.
You're gonna die!
-Yeah maybe if I was one of you!
ARE YOU STUPID!?
What was he trying to show us?
What the hell is this?
What the hell is this thing you suggested?
What the hell was that supposed to be!?
I applaud your commitment but I don't understand.
I'll show you how to actually catch them!
Shall I show you how?
Degawa Group Boss
Degawa Testuro
You can get them all, right boss?
Of course!
Look at the quality of these goldfish!
They are huge!
Degawa Group's Will
Wear a special water tank, put bigger goldfish inside and catch with mouth
Pour the water in up to here.
Okay, so I'll fill it to half way.
Yeah.
All at once won't be a good idea.
Oh, sorry!! My bad, my bad.
Huh, what's wrong?
I'm seriously sorry.
I forgot to take off my contact lenses!
You wrecked the tense atmosphere!
We don't care about stuff like that!
-- Don't look this way!
I had been asked to take it off!
Contact lenses in the Edo period...?
Please put it up to here to start with.
Why is he speaking with honorifics?
You ok?
What the hell are they showing us?
He's in trouble.
Hurry up and do it!!
No! I'm preparing myself!
You're not prepared!?
What the heck is this!
I'm sorry.
I'll prepare myself.
Shouldn't you have come after preparing yourself?
Prepared yet!?
Ok.
Here I go.
Go!
Get them!
How do you succeed at this?
This is friggin' crazy!
All goldfish are collected into the pool.
I at least got one in my mouth, didn't I!
Then bring "that" out!
We'll finish this fight right now.
This cushion we just place in the middle is
an odd one that suddenly explodes.
Huh?
On top of this explosive cushion...
our man Wakky will...
Ueshima Group
Wakky
finish eating a bowl of udon.
What does he mean?
Are you ready Wakky!?
Finish eating hot udon while on a cushion that suddenly explodes
Ueshima Group's Will
YEAAAHH!
Wakky has changed his look a lot recently.
And he won't even feel the heat!
This looks pretty dangerous.
This is really scary.
What the heck is this?
Alright, do your best!
Ready...GO!
Come on, you can do it!
He's having no problems.
He's just eating normally.
What the hell is this?
Seconds
Until the explosion
What the hell is this?
Crap that scared me!
HOW'S THAT!?
Is it ok to laugh at this?
That scared the crap out of me
That wasn't hot at all!
Man, you guys are SOFT!
If it was us, we'd eat nabeyaki udon on there!
Nabeyaki Udon: Udon served in a steaming pot.
Degawa Group's Will
Finish eating hot udon while on a cushion that suddenly explodes
Can you handle that!?
Our Hosshan can eat something waaay hotter!
Hell yeaah!
Who's that?
Was there ever a guy like that?
Who is he? Seriously.
He's our boss!
Since when did your boss look like that?
Show 'em, Hosshan!
Here I go!
That would be hot for sure.
Yeah.
Hurry up and eat!
Nice work! Nice work!
That looks really hot.
Isn't he having trouble eating?
Seconds
Until the explosion
Go! Go!
Keep laughin'! Keep laughin' Hosshan!
No problem at all!
You didn't even eat it!
He ate it AND he's laughing too!
To be honest, the Degawa Group is winning.
Yeah.
Bring "that" over here!!
You shouldn't try so hard!
What they brought were electric eels over 1 metre in length.
Surely this ain't okay.
Electricity emitted from it's body can make cows unconscious!?
The electric current they emit to catch prey
may be strong enough to bring down a cow.
They will move this dangerous creature
Move the electric eel to a different tank with bare hand in 1 minute
Ueshima Group's Will
to another tank with their bare hands, within a minute.
They get agitated if you make loud noises.
So let's do this quietly.
Sure, whatever.
Go Iwao.
Looks like he doesn't wanna.
Ueshima-Group
Iwao Noboru
Can you do it? Can you do it?
He's stronger than a cow. GO!
Seriously?
I don't get this.
Don't push yourself.
Be careful!
Are you scared?
NOOOOOO!!!
He said that from the pit of his stomach.
Are you gonna challenge this? You decide.
Please let me quit.
We are actually using eels with a low electric charge.
Well, these eels can make knock out cows!
Next, a leg strength training machine called the "Room Runner" is brought in.
Leg Strength Trainer
Room Runner
Degawa Group's Will
While running backwards
dips noodles in the hot soup and eat it.
They must dip noodles into the hot soup on the ground
and then eat it, all while running backwards.
Degawa Group
Kojima Kazuya (Unjash)
Degawa Group's Kojima decides to do this challenge.
This is a tough one right here.
Keep your eyes on me!
START
You can do it! Okay, now dip it.
Nicely done, nicely done.
You're still fine! Okay, okay!
You can do it!
What kind of situation is this?
It's exactly what you see!!
It was clearly less entertaining than the others
Seriously, what is this?
He totally ate that.
Bring "that" in!
Let us
show you just how
strong our guys are here!
Show 'em Tanaka!
Degawa Group
Tanaka Takushi (Ungirls)
I'll show you!
Now...
This macho guy's gonna give him a Romero Special!
And during that, he won't react at all
to being slapped in the crotch with this rope!
Degawa Group's Will
Withstand being hit in the crotch with a rope, while held in a Romero Special.
A Romero Special will be tough. Owww.
This won't be nice.
It looks like his arms will snap.
Haranishi will hit the crotch with a rope
Hit him really hard!
Ready....start!
What the hell!? Who benefits from this!?
Awesome as expected!
That was crazy right there.
Well done man.
I hit him pretty hard!
The Degawa Group is a bit in front now.
How'd ya like that!?
Our Yoshinobu can be hit twice as much!
Nakamura Yoshinobu (Producer)
Ueshima Group
Yoshinobu-san can't handle this, right?
Wakky will hit the crotch with the rope
With twice the strength as well.
Here we go.
Hit him twice as much!
But he's an amateur!
Twice as much!
This is hell!
People buy tickets for this stuff.
Brought in next was a boiling pot full of clothes.
Degawa Group's Will
Take out and wear a shirt, slacks and necktie from a pot with boiling water.
Inside are a collared shirt, slacks and a necktie.
Wear all the clothes within 1 minute!!
Haranishi says that he'll wear all of these within a minute.
Don't do it, jeeez.
Just don't do it...
Seriously, don't do it.
Ready...START!
Necktie first.
Come on! Come on!
He's friggin' saying that it's "hot".
See! He wore the necktie!
Next, a tank full of honey was brought in.
Degawa Group's boss sees how long he can
Degawa Group's Will
Put his head inside the tank and see how long he can hold his breath
hold his breath after dunking his head inside.
He takes time to prepare doesn't he?
When you're ready...
Hurry up!
He's preparing himself.
I'm preparing myself right now
He put his arms inside too.
Why did he put his arms in first?
His head's not even in now!
So sweet!
Why did you put your arms in?
Sweet!
He thought there'd be more space.
It was like he dived in.
Stop being chicken!
There's no choice. Let's put an end to this!
Bring "that" in!
It's what the Edo fire fighters do when they wanna settle a battle.
We'll challenge you to an arm wrestle!
But not ordinary arm wrestling!
See this can of oxygen?
We'll shove this up our asses...
and the first to fart loses.
That's just damn crazy.
What is this?
Well then boss...
That old man there is in a mess.
We smashed you at this last year!
Are you sure about this?
Your leader's looking a bit weird.
Sorry, can I just have one more towel?
It gets in my eye and I can't do anything!
It's like a guy that stayed in the sauna too long.
Thanks.
OK, I'm fine.
Let's do this!
Arm wrestling competition
Tanaka Takushi
Team Degawa
Team Ueshima
Ueshima Ryuhei
I'll put lotion on you.
Ueshima's ass had growths on it last year and it wouldn't go in.
SHUT THE FUCK UP!
STOP TALKING ABOUT GROWTHS ON MY ASS, STUPID IDIOT!
He's totally pissed.
It's a delicate subject for him.
Never speak again about growths on my ass, you dickhead!
Ready, set...
Both insert oxygen at the same time
Relax your muscles!
OK!
Oxygen Injection Complete
OK, get on standby!
READY!
GO!
Bfft!
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
Do it again!
Reorganize and start again
Well, it was my first time ever so...
"Ready, go" isn't the signal to fart.
Man, this is scary.
It's scary, I'm telling ya.
Put in more for me.
Alright.
Ready
GO!
Pfft
Brp
That's enough!
Of course this'll happen!
Of course this'll happen.
I gotta praise you despite being an enemy.
We're sorry too.
Ends in peace
Well, let's go then.
It was amazing again this year.
It's good we've become friend, huh?
Huh?
Isn't that the Terminator?
Terminator appears
Isn't that Mr. Terminator?
Oh, he stole some clothes.
Searching for someone?
Terminator checks the five
Mr. Terminator, are you looking for someone?
Mr. Terminator, where did you get those clothes?
Mr. Terminator.
What's your reason for coming to Edo?
Jeez, come on....
He doesn't understand the meaning of the words.
Hey! Wasn't she a person picking up coins?
Henmi Mari
Villager
A person that picked up coins!
Pursues Henmi and fires gun randomly
His shooting majorly sucks.
He's shooting somewhere completely different.
Time it properly!
It's not hitting at all!
Damn, he sucks at shooting.
He really sucks.
What the hell, man?!
I'm guessing Terminator
came back from the future just to find her, huh?
I guess that's how it was..
I hope she was able to run away successfully.
Let's go
I have no idea
What's going to happen next..
You're right there..
10:30 in the evening.
They start to play with the thing they were curious about.
It's just so cute.
That's so cute.
You really like it don't you Housei-san?
Particularly the lips.
Ventriloquist puppet 'Hama-chan'
Play with it.
For real?
How old are you?
I'm 45 years old.
Hey. You're not even trying
You're not even try to use ventriloquism
Why me as well?
Who?
Who, me?
I really wasn't laughing though..
You're so dirty man...
What the hell...
Right there..
There it is, there it is.
I wonder if
they might try and sell this
they might sell it again?
What the hell is the point in selling something like that?
Again.
Shit man.
That is scary.
Isn't the back of the head just normal?
No, well it's...
What, what? I'm scared.
There's like a part you shouldn't see
like on a backstage.
Like the thing you should never see in the backstages..
Shit man.
That's amazing
It's not cute even in the slightest.
Do you hate it now?
I don't like it, it's creepy and weird.
Play with it Endo.
Let's find out who's the best at it.
Ok.
Hama-chan is a fine name.
Ok then.
Actually, Koma-chan
Koma-chan?
It's better if you fiddle and get used to it a bit.
Ok.
Ok, go.
Oh, you're going to hide your face?
No, you're meant to hold it next to your face.
Endo, you really know nothing, huh?
Please.
I'm guessing the staff really wanted us to do this though
Ah, I get it.
Man, so tired today, huh?
@($$(@)@$?!
Yes, I'm fine. How many hours do you think I work?
@($$(@)@$...
That is just fascinating.
I have no idea in hell what Koma-chan is trying to say.
We can't understand a thing, not even a word.
Just like 'mogo mogo, mogo mogo'
You're not meant to move your own mouth, so you try and hide your lip movements.
It's like a retired person.
If you're trying to do it properly, that's what it's going to be like.
Wow, this is nostalgic.
It's really properly made so it's heavy.
Koma-chan
What were you doing?
@($$...
I have no idea what you're saying.
It's so hard... Impossible!
No, no, it's so hard to do this..
The whole balance of the situation just gets weird.
Oh, so you begin to wonder how the pros do it.
Yes, and then you begin to lose yourself.
Housei-san looks like he would be good at this.
Hey, Koma-chan? What's wrong?
What's wrong Koma-chan?
I'm a little tired~~~
You're talking normally!
The subject of the conversation is just so boring.
You guys are so pathetic because
It's just not dynamic at all
Oh I see
You can ask me anything
How old are you?
Shut up, you bastard!!
Where did you come from?
Shit!!
You're so cute, huh?
I'll kill you!!!
What's your favourite fo-...
YOU!!!
Scary!!
Koma-chan...
So scary man.. All the kids would cry
All the kids would cry.
He's not loving in the slightest.
OUCH!!!
11:00pm. 15 hours since the start.
Next, they will go and see what Edo men love to see, a Courtesan's dance.
"Courtesans dance"
is what they'll see next!!
It attracts a lot of the Edo times men
Between the 5, there is a strange feeling about this next event.
Red Light District
Everyone, it's here.
Wow, there are so many people here.
Everyone, go to the front.
Edo men all gathered in the hall.
Wow, there's loads of men here.
Hell and welcome everyone.
I would just like to thank everyone here for coming today.
Anyway,
today we are going to show you
the courtesan style of Yoshihara.
It's a little bit more special than our usual shows.
So please, enjoy it until the end~~~~!!
Start
Courtesan Dance
Here comes
the Courtesan...
Goddamn!!
Chouno Masahiro's
Magistrate's Office's
Government Official
appearance
Oi!
Goddamn!
Goddamn!!
Chouno Masahiro's
Magistrate's Office's
Government Official
appearance
Oi!
Goddamn!
Oi!!
Don't let anyone get away now!!
Shut the doors!
Oi, you Edo Bastards
I've got good news for you today.
In this room, there is a huge burglar
Nezumi Kozou
Burglar - Nezumi Kozou
within the crowd!!
Today, I am going to capture him.
Anyone have any idea?
Any information is good.
I have solid proof today you know?
Oi!!
Here it is.
Secret Agent
Nezumi Sempai
This is my secret agent, Nezumi.
This is a really good portrait of him
. The 'solid proof' is
a drawing of Nezumi Kozou!!
So he's in this room somewhere, right?
Yes, correct.
You're not going to own up then?
You sure you're ok with that?
Fine then, I have no choice..
Seriously?
No way, no way...
It can ONLY be Yama-chan
Seriously?
Anyone have any idea of this man?
I'm correct in thinking no one does, right?
Ok fine... then one by one...
you'll put this little hood on your head.
Find the thief by making them
put the hood on their head!!
I guess we have no choice.
Hold this for a second
Right, let's start with you
Right, wear this.
Ok
Put the wear on like this
Are you a man?
I'm a woman.
No, it's not you.
Ok, next.
Ok
I am a woman...
It's not you either.
No, it's not you.
Oi, just hurry up and own up already!!
You're being a nuisance to everyone!!
You're ugly but it's not you
Phew
No, it's not you.
Ok, you do it!
Yamazaki, just stop.
Just stop it already.
Just put it on normally!
It's just ridiculous
This is just all so ridiculous.
Just put it on normally
for crying out loud.
Look closely, can you see?
Nezumi Kozou. Isn't that you?
It's not me.
Ok fine, then stand up once.
Stand up once and show your face to everyone.
What is with your face.
Is that your face when you took the photo?
What kind of face do you have?
It's the same!!
You knew from the start, huh?
We will meet in any era... you get it?
Any era?
Get up on the stage!!
Wait, please..
Seriously, but these are my friends
They know that I am not Nezumi Kozou...
Are you saying that
that they knew and protected you?
Yes
If they did, they are just as guilty as you, you know?!
Yes.
Please clarify with them that it's not me.
Oi, did you know about this?
No, we had no idea at all.
See, they don't.
But they didn't know, so...
Surely that proves that I'm not Nezumi Kozou.
Just get on the stage once.
Wait a second, wait a second!
A really hard slap!!
Punishment for Nezumi Kozou
What should I do?
Just the same as usual.
I'll give you one chance to redeem yourself.
Yes, yes.
You have 1 minute.
1 minute?
Yes, 1 minute.
Make everyone... laugh.
Make everyone laugh and
there will be no slap!!
Including me, everyone has to laugh.
Get it?
Get set... Go!!
Please look at this stick...
Tries with the stick that was coincidentally on the floor
Please look at it closely!!!!
This stick!!!
Oh man, this is the most humiliating thing ever...
You did try though..
What the hell is this!!
It's just messed up.
You were never going to do it with such a stupid joke!!
Oi, is that insult aimed at me?
No, not at all.
Chouno-san.
What?
Chouno-san, please.
Just get it over with
I will, I will.
Ok, I get it. I'm going to get it anyway.
I will take it. There's no point...
Good good good...
Yep...
Right, here we go...
Say 'I am Nezumi Kozou and I am sorry'!!!
Hurry, say it!
Don't move around.
Just wait a second, please.
What now
Please get your foot off!!
Wait, ow!!
What happened?
My thigh hurts!!
My thigh!!
Hurry up and stand up!
The joint in my hip seriously just ripped!!
The joint! Ow!!
You can't stand up?
No I can't!
Don't lie man!
Please, let go!!
The joint in my hip ripped!
Come on, just stand up
Come on, come on.
See, he stood up fine.
Just come here.
Oh my god, he was lying so bad...
Everyone's waiting you know?
Ok, ok, ok, I get it.
Everyone is waiting for you, you're being a nuisance.
Ok I get it..
Ok I will do it, I will do it.
Wait, just this, this this...
Please just stop this, ow!
Your thumb is hurting me
OW OW OW OW OW OW
That would hurt..
Seriously, that's enough.
I'm still shocked he lied so much about his hip joint.
I'm liking the scared face on you right now.
No, seriously, please, just this.
You'll run away otherwise.
I won't run away, so please, just this.
OW OW OW OW OW, THIS REALLY HURTS.
I can't take this, please please please wait a second.
What was that about...
Ok I'm going now, seriously, I will do it.
Here I go, ok, you ready?
OK!
Ready?!
Yes.
Sure?!
Yes
Here I come.
Yes!
Punishment Slap
Success!!
Goddamn!!
Oi!! Take this home with you!!
It's a souvenir!
Let'sh go.
Let's go and regain our focus.
16 hours from the start.
The long school trip is finally...
Wow
Everyone.
Our trip is now finished. We're saying goodbye to the people of the Edo times.
Time to head back huh?
Ok everyone, let's change to our normal clothes.
We can come back from present time to the Edo times that easily, huh?
He just ignored me
This is yours I think...
Changing back to their normal clothes
The trip is finished
Now the school tour is over.
They get dressed back into their teachers outfits, and say their byes to the Edo town.
Get on the bus
and time slip back to the future
It's only been a little while since we got off the bus...
They get on the bus, and time slip to the present.
Again the bus.
Again the bus, it doesn't stop.
There's no end to the enthusiastic teacher life.
Even if they get back to the school
their ordeal continues
There's no end to the enthusiastic teacher life
The ordeal for the 5 of them will continue even once when they get back to the school.
1:00 in the morning.
The staff members are having a meeting.
We're going in guys.
Conference room
Just sit where your names are located.
Right, we are starting the PTA meeting now.
Ok, let's go guys.
Well, this school accepts drama students, so...
If there are comedians who are a bad influence on our students...
Comedians who are a bad influence
to the students, are put on a black list
PTA information meeting
I would like you to report them in this meeting.
Yes, can I go?
Yes.
Yamazaki Housei
He doesn't get how TV works...
Yamazaki Housei's secret information
There was a special Sanma-san progam.
Yes.
And in that program,
there were two groups of famous people.
One would tell the truth, one would lie.
You have to tell which one is lying. You guys took part in it too, right?
Yep, we did.
So as the program continued, there was a 'reaction battle' game
Yes
They said 'Ryuhei's team and Yamazaki's team'...
'Please come out to the front'
Yamazaki then said with a really loud voice
I'm so going to trick you lot!!
You're right.
That was just.
Yep, I remember that well.
Me too.
So there were 2 teams, and on the outside 2 rooms.
He doesn't get how TV works...
Yamazaki Housei's secret information
In one room, there would be a really bad smell
In the other one, there would be a scent of flowers
So they get in, right?
Yes.
So they get in, and Yamazaki Housei alone started shouting
It stinks, it stinks!!
Yes.
Then Joshihara said.
Now the balloon in the room will inflate
and when it breaks, a smelly gas will come out.
That is shocking...
Even though I've been in showbiz for 25 years...
It really screwed up the game in the latter half.
This is quite a small thing...
Iwahashi of Plus-Minus told me this.
Secret info received from
(Plus Minus)
Iwahashi Yoshimasa
'Airhead' story... (1)
Hamada Masatoshi's secret information
While in the karaoke, Hamada said...
'Iwahashi, change this straw, it's clogged!!'
while he was sucking a muddler.
(A muddler is a pestle for cocktails.)
He was sucking a muddler?
That's just a plastic stick basically...
Ok I have one
I heard this from Higashino Kouji
'Airhead' story... (2)
Hamada Masatoshi's secret information
I heard this from Higashino Kouji
'Airhead' story... (2)
Hamada Masatoshi's secret information
Higashino Kouji
Secret info from
Right now, Hamada and Higashino are doing a program in Osaka called Gobu Gobu.
A regular show, right? Yes, yes.
They were recording in town, but...
Hamada was being immature saying
"I don't want to walk around too much"
So the staff thought of an idea
Until the opening, they would carry him by a wagon
Then open the door, he would jump out and they would start recording
So when the recording finished, Hamada would just get onto the wagon
So they can go to the next point, then Hamada can just get off
So the staff made this system for him
Every single time he got on and off the wagon
he hit his head.
I see.
I guess he just doesn't have any sense of distance anymore.
Anymore information on anyone?
Ok, then I have one...
Ok sure
It's about Mimata Matazou.
Rip-off Bar... (1)
Mimata Matazou's secret information
You know he has the worst personality, right?
Yes I have heard..
Until last year, he owned a rip-off bar in Roppongi...
Only to get in you had to pay 1,700 Yen, it was unbelievable
But that shop was closed down anyway.
Lately, he opened another bar up.
And he said to me 'I've opened a new bar and'
I won't rip you off again so please come over sometime.
So he basically recognized that he ripped me off before.
Man my jaw hurts
I guess it's just the kind of guy he is, he just wants to rip people off
Anyway, I went there
Rip-off Bar... (1)
Mimata Matazou's secret information
And it's a really lovely shop and...
The atmosphere is really nice and the alcohol tastes really good
And I went once and there is basically this system
To get in the bar and have a sit, there's a fee you have to pay...
You have to pay 2000 Yen just for that alone.
But from the prestige of the bar, that's acceptable
Well I guess, it's a high class bar, right?
But there are private rooms
and these private rooms have karaoke
The charge for one hour is 5000 Yen per person.
It's a seriously hefty price and so me and loads of other comedians keep getting calls from him...
and he says 'If you know anyone who is like a manager,
can you bring them to my place?'
And he called my junior called Harro Ueda and...
said it so many times to him,
that he eventually took his boss to the bar.
Then Mimata said 'Director, shall we go to the private rooms?'
He was really pushing him to go to the private rooms
Even when the manager was saying 'It's fine, I like it here, I don't even like Karaoke.'
He kept giving him drinks and he got so drunk he started to fall asleep.
Then Mimata said 'Manager, let's sleep in the private rooms'
So he took the sleeping manager into the private room
and then charged him for the hours he slept in there.
You're the worst!!
Why do I get hit for something that's got nothing to do with me!
That is horrible. I went to that shop lately as well
Rip-off Bar... (2)
Mimata Matazou's secret information
Yes
I can actually drink quite a lot but
after drinking 3 bottles of beer, Mimata said to me
Miyasako, aren't you sleepy?
Unbelievable
He's so dirty!
You can't do that man...
I didn't know there were other stories like that...
No seriously, I'm getting hit way too much.
He's such a liar...
Seriously, sort it out..
It's about Mimata again...
In a club one night...
Mimata Matazou's secret information
I got this from Author Sada-san.
Sada-san and Mimata-san went to a sushi bar together,
and Sada-san said 'Oh man, I haven't had a girlfriend in years'
And he was looking for a shoulder to lean on
And Mimata, who was drinking loads and loads at the time
kind of started to act arrogant and said:
'Oi Sada, I'll take you somewhere real good then'
So he took him to this 'gentlemen's club'
Well Sada-san didn't want his or Mimata's face to be recognised
so he got a mask and a hat for Mimata to camouflage him.
But when they were in the club choosing which girl they wanted,
when the owner of the shop saw Mimata disguised,
said 'Mimata-san, you are still
banned here so please leave'...
Banned?!
What could he have possibly done which was that bad?!
What did he do!?
Yes, why?
What could it have been?
For a comedian to be banned...
I guess he tried to force something on them..
Any others then?
Ok you.
It's about Matsumoto-san
When he wears an Adidas watch,
The watch talk...
Matsumoto Hitoshi's secret information
He says 'This is really good' even though he hardly ever wears it
And he started getting more interested in watches or something...
and eventually he bought a really expensive and prestigious watch.
And even though he always wears this watch when he's with his juniors...
When he's with the 'watch obsessed' Miyasako
I guess he feels inferior, cause he definitely won't wear that watch.
He definitely won't wear it.
I've never seen it!
You haven't seen it!
I do want to see it...
I wonder why..
So strange..
Hopefully he will soon..
This is also about Matsumoto-san.
He was in Okinawa and
Dinner party with the family...
Matsumoto Hitoshi's secret information
Matsumoto-san, his wife and child
and my family were eating Yakiniku.
Matsumoto's wife's iPhone case is...
that one with the rabbit ears,
and he said 'Check this out!'
'It basically means that everyone can hear your conversation.'
Everyone was laughing at his little joke
And then his wife said...
'Ah... You make that joke all the time...'
'I don't say it often.'
I see.
He said 'I don't say it often.'
Dinner party with the family...
Matsumoto Hitoshi's secret information
The wife said 'The last time we went out, and the time before...'
Matsumoto 'No no, I've said it maximum, twice...'
(Wife) 'I think there's been more than twice...'
(Matsumoto) 'No way, no way, no way.'
7 minutes. They were debating about it for a total of 7 minutes.
Wow, that's a seriously long debate.
I see...
Anybody else...
Go ahead.
Then I have something...
There's somebody who usually has no stories,
somebody who is called the king of peculiar personalities...
called Tanaka Naoki-san.
We rarely hear any stories about him!
Talk about his high spirits...
Tanaka Naoki's secret information
That's right, ehm...
The thing is that we couldn't get any information from his long time friends, so...
so we asked his wife about it.
(Tanaka Naoki's wife)
Kohinata Shie
Secret info from
Even when he's in his house his spirits aren't particularly high...
that's how Mr. Tanaka Naoki is, right?
One specific day, his spirits were so high...
when he came back home...
that when all the family was eating together...
he said "Look at this photo!!!" and the photo he showed...
was an expanded photo of a tick.
Eh?
A photo of a tick?
Amazing...
It was very rare...
And he showed that to his wife.
In a TV show, his wife...
Tanaka Naoki's secret information
Some time ago, in a special television show, the duo Ameagari Keshitai...
gathered a lot of wives from famous people,
to talk about funny stories about their husbands.
That time we asked Tanaka Naoki's wife too.
She's not a person who usually appears on TV, so...
she tried really hard and told like 7~8 episodes about his husband.
She talked a lot.
None of them were funny.
Nobody laughed.
The quantity was right though...
There was quantity...
She tried hard.
Yes.
It's not his wife's fault.
It's not his wife's fault. It's just that his stories aren't funny.
Can I have a go?
Well, this is about Tanaka-san's partner, Endo Shouzou...
A phone call late at night...
Endo Shouzou's secret information
This is a very recent story.
I received a call from Endo-san very late at night.
I really want a ****** from Shinjuku.
can you come with me to buy it?
A man in his 40...
Disgusting!
There's even more...
A phone call late at night...
Endo Shouzou's secret information
Oh, there's more!
It was a second-hand one.
Eh??
I eventually stopped doing that. I stopped.
Ow!
So you don't do that anymore?
I stopped it in the end.
Is there anything else?
Well then, shall I?
Er..
The Katsura Group... as it were has many rules.
Although he's an apprentice... (1)
Katsura Sando's secret information
The Katsura Group... as it were has many rules.
Though smoking is not permitted
Katsura Sando is a chain smoker.
You can't do that!
That's a total act of betrayal.
I've got one too.
Ah, please, if you would.
I heard this from Sando...
Although he's an apprentice... (2)
Katsura Sando's secret information
As a promise to his master
Katsura would not drink alcohol for 3 years.
I've heard he's been drinking every day.
This is getting serious now.
Wha~?
No question, some people just love a drink!
You're kidding me!
If there's anything else...
May I speak for a moment? Is it alright?
Yes.
This is about Matsumoto Hitoshi.
This story is
In the middle of town...
Matsumoto Hitoshi's secret information
about a walk
Matsumoto Hitoshi went on one day
About 4 or 5 office ladies. Young ones.
"Ah! It's Ma-chan!"
they said, approaching him.
Well, I think this is a good a time as any...
One of the women says,
"Mastumoto-san,
you've got an amazing body!"
Wearing a summer t-shirt, well, he had everyone's attention.
A terrific, finely tuned body.
The same woman
reaches out to touch him.
Two other women join in and start touching him.
I'm thinking "This is bad..."
"Ah-! Wait.. If I were to do such a thing with women like these... "
From Matsumoto's point of view,  he was coerced.
With a hesitant attitude,
He lets them
grope him all over.
Finally, his pecs
begin to twitch.
He starts feeling pretty good...
and that's it...
Geez.. amazing.. I..
That's uhm..
Yes.
You're
not very good at telling stories, are you?
Gaaah.
Mimata-san!
Ow!
Ouch!
For this to be the last story is a bit of a disappointment, isn't it?
The story we had originally planned...
This guy decided to go off on his own, leading us to this result.
There's nothing we can do to get out of it now.
Teaching Duty: 18 hours elapsed
They come here to face that man.
Asamade Current Events Discussion!
~Has the sun not yet risen in Japan?~
Good evening. I'm Tahara Soichiro, the journalist.
Journalist
Tahara Soichiro
This is Asamade Current Event Discussion 2012.
This year, too, we've been witness to many events.
The American presidential election.
The succession and replacement of high-ranking Chinese officials.
To look back on such issues,
I'd like to speak with an international journalist.
Please, come in.
Good evening.
Good evening. Welcome.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Have a seat over here.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming to the show.
International Journalist
Mr. Oonishi Hideaki
Thank you for having me.
Firstly,
It's being said Noda-san has put his political career on the line.
He says there will be an increase in taxes.
Yes.
On that topic, what percentage is the tax currently?
He doesn't hold back at all, does he?
Without hesitation, he says 20%.
Yes. 20%", he says.
You don't have
even a bit of restraint, do you?
We're getting it non-stop.
Ow!
Ouch!
They really put their all into it.
The truth is many countries in Europe have a tax rate of about 20%.
Hm...
In Japan, it's less expensive. I wonder how much less.
There's no way he meant that low when he said "less expensive".
That's over the top, right?
Alright.
Uh! Ow, ow, ow.
0.5?
Higher than that.
Okay.
Hamada-san is stone-faced.
You're amazing, Hamada-san.
That's it for me..
"0.10"!
It's no use. 0.10 is amazing.
You see the tax rate is actually 5%.
Whooaaaaa.
Let's move on, shall we?
This person here. Do you know his name?
Yes.
Who is he?
Er..
Se.. Seko the athlete.
Former Marathon Runner
Seko Toshihiko-san
Se.. Seko the athlete.
You're kidding me!
They do kinda look the same.
They do look alike though.
Seko the athlete.
Urg!
Augh!
Ouch!
Ah! Ow!
That's it for me.
Seko the athlete.
This person here. Do you know his name?
Yes, er...
Se.. Seko the athlete.
Former Marathon Runner
Seko Toshihiko-san
...his um, son?
I'm done for. This is too much.
We've got to persevere.
Seko's son?
Ow!
Well done!!
Did he hit your thigh?
Yes.
Your bum hurts?
Medical/Physiology Nobel Prize Winner
Professor at Kyoto University
Yamanaka Shinya
This man here is Yamanaka Shinya.
Nobel Prize winner.
iPS cells.
These, well..
With artificial cells from all over
If this was implemented we may be able to go as far as making a human.
Wow!
Someone who looked like you, Oonishi-san, 2,  3, even 5 of them could be created.
Someone who looked like you, Oonichi-san, 2,  3, even 5 of them could be created.
What should be done?
That's a bit of a problem.
My wife's body would be worn out.
My wife will probably end up getting destroyed.
You're talking about sex, is that right?
He just out and says it that way.
Geez!
How blunt!
It's no use.
Ahh....
It's the two of them in combination that's sorta..
It might be that, too.
My wife will probably end up getting destroyed.
You're talking about sex?
Yes, of course that's the case.
I see. I understand well.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Asamade Current Events Discussion!
End
~Has the sun not yet risen in Japan?~
They really got us that time.
It's me, Fujiwara!
School P.A. Broadcast
The thing is, while I was walking in the hallway a rather large,
long-haired woman kidnapped me.
I've been locked away in a cage.
Wha..?
It seems that the key to the cabin
Is in the security room on the 2nd floor
Here it is.
Will you get the key and bring it to me?
Here we go.
Also, from here onward you're allowed to laugh, but
If you're surprised it seems you'll be OUT.
Geez!
What was up with that? The way he recited that story. It sounded like Kawashima Eigo.
Late Night - Special Rules
Must Not Get Surprised
Enthusiastic Teachers
And so, the three of them head off to the second floor to retrieve the key needed to release Fujiwara.
Yamazaki and Cocorico
head to the second floor
to get the key!!
Here I go.
Are you coming?
Yes!
Ok, off we go.
Be right back!
Let's go.
As usual Downtown is left behind.
This is scary!
Eek!
Wow, it's unsettling in there, isn't it?
The lighting has changed inside the school
No running around or freaking out, ok?
Us 3, Let's stick close together and go, ok?
Yes, let's be sure to do that, please.
CO2 Gas Spray in...
Seconds
And, with really loud noises, we should...
Whoa!!
Look like this!
This
This!!
It'd be better if Tanaka went ahead a bit
Let's stay together, please
Of course, we're partners in this
Eh? What's this?
The surprise "Magical Banana" commences.
From here onward, the surprise "Magical Banana" commences.
Sh-
Should we read these?
If I Said Banana
Monkey
If I Said Monkey
If I said Banana
If I said Monkey
Monkey
Red Butt
If I Said Red
Red.. Oh! Red is over here.
If I Said Banana
Monkey
If I Said Monkey
If I Said Red
Red Butt
Ferrari
If I Said Ferrari
If I said Monkey
Red Butt
Ferrari
If I Said Red
If I said Ferrari
Italy
If I said Italy
Seconds until...
Secret Gag
Pasta
Pasta.
Ah.
How's it been going lately??
How's it been going lately?!
Is the pasta winding!?
Winding?
You scared the crap out of me!
Comedy Duo, Hi-Hi - Prime Joke Material
What the heck is "winding?"
Meanwhile, as for Downtown...
The two lone members of Downtown
Where are you going for New Year's?
Hm?
It's a common question to ask. I don't care if it airs or not.
No, geez. I don't want to do this.
Even when they tell us it's OK to laugh,
To have a regular conversation with you, with no rules in place. It's pointless and nerve-wracking.
You're laughing way too much about this!!
That's because it's not a big deal.
No, I.. ugh.
This is absolutely the worst moment of the year.
This situation is just so depressing!!
Ah, there's the security room!
In front of Security Personnel
Room 2F
Key
Oh my god..
Hey, there are some pen lights here. Three of them.
Pen Light
Electric Shock in:
Seconds
I wonder if we have to bother signing this sheet.
Ahh!
Zap!
Wha??
Ahh!
It shocked me!
Scary!
Are these shock pens?
Don't do it.
Does the zap come out from here?
But mine might be the only one that works.
Why did only my pen went off?
Huh, that's weird.
Wait a minute, my zapper
Er, I mean my pen light is..
Wait a moment.
Wait up.
Security Personnel Room
I don't understand why
my penlight went off..
We're here, we're here.
The key's inside this room.
But there are a lot of them!!
Eh?
Something's written here!
Seconds
Secret Prank in..
Just this one here.
Oh man, oh geez...
Aaaaaah!
Waaaaah!
Ah!
The Room Suddenly Blacked Out
Aaaaah!
Yamazaki, Tanaka and Endo have only their penlights for illumination (The bright light you see is an infrared light.)
No!
Wah!
No, I'm scared!
No!
Bad..
What's that over there?
This is bad
Oh no, oh no...
Ijirii Okada (comedian) wearing a speedo
Who's that? Who's there?
Ah, it's Ijirii-san.
Greetings.
Is he giving us some sort of a clue?
Housei-san, why are you pointing your light at his crotch?
Eh?
Only pointing it at his crotch..
Wha..?
The lights have been turned back on
Aah!
Look at this.
The key has been obtained
The three of them safely retrieve the key.
Why am I the topic of conversation, here?
I'm just asking.
I'll be going to a resort this summer
Whereas this winter it's already a little..
Ah, I see.
Where will you be going? This summer.
Guam, or somewhere like that?
I've always wanted to tell you this.
Yes, yes.
Stop calling it Gamu.
It's Guam.
What the hell is that?
I can't stand that. Calling it "Gamu".
What the hell...
The only people who call it Gamu is you and, you know...
Shinsuke-niiyan...
Meanwhile, after getting the key, Cocorico and Yamazaki are..
Seconds
Secret Prank in..
Let's go back, seriously.
There are markers pointing the way.
A Group of Jason Mask-Wearing Men
Eeek! I just pressed the button on my penlight again!
Uuuwaaaa!
A Group of Mysterious Masked Men
Aaaaah!! Aaaaaah!!
Waaaaaah!!
No more, no more! Wait!
I hate this. Hate this!!
Handcuffed and Restrained
Ah, ow ow ow.
What're we gonna do?
It's no use.
ANNOUNCEMENT
EMERGENCY!
What the..?
Seconds
Secret Prank in..
Waah... I'm freaked out.
What? Wait..
Whoa!
A waste of 5 seconds!
It Went Off in the Training Room Too!
I'm so pissed off
I'm so pissed off".. Hahaha.
What was the point of doing that?
Now, I'd like to challenge you..
SPECIAL QUIZ
Savanna's Yagi's
.. to my SPECIAL QUIZ!
Out of 702 of my gags
As chosen by my wife.
please guess my BEST 5 jokes.
We'll start with this.
The scissors from Rock-Paper-Scissors.
My Wife's Favourite Gags
The scissors from Rock-Paper-Scissors
Top 5
What do you think it'll be? Tanaka-san?
I don't know.
The correct answer is..
Enjoy the Rock-Paper-Scissors scissors panoramically!!
...please.
I've seen that
the other day on "King's Brunch" (the TV show).
Please don't say that.
And while Yagi continues with his Special Quiz...
But to properly do it...
You have to
use the correct words.
But it's just with Guam so...
Other words, not particularly...
Um...
What do you call a machine that washes things like pants and shirts?
A wash machine.
Geez, that's not right.
The way you say it is totally wrong.
What? What are you on about?
It's washing machine.
That's so...
It's normal..
You sound like an old man from Osaka. I can't stand it.
What is a thing filled with fish swimming around? People come to stand in front of the glass to watch. What is that?
Fish bowl!
He's an old man!!! Hahaha!
It's aquarium!!
What the hell?
What the hell is up with saying fish bowl??
Disgusting.
I think you've been speaking the same way lately.
That's..
I think I say it in a good way.
You've gotta be kidding me!!
It's out now.
A typical response, "You've gotta be kidding me!!".
That's enough, seriously. This is so irritating right now!!
What the hell, man.
Well then, in first place, of course, is..
The announcement of Yagi's wife's #1 favourite gag!!
This!
People of Brazil, can you hear me~?
Seconds
Secret Prank in..
Brazilian Samba Dancers Appear
This place is hell.
As for these three, who savor this hell...
With their mouths gagged, they're completely confined.
they're completely confined.
Downtown go to the second floor
in order to search for
the other 3 !!
This time..
The security room on the second floor..
Geez, these guys, man.
CO2 Gas Spray in...
Seconds
Oooh!
Where? Where is it?
Geez..
I don't like this.
Seconds
Secret Prank in..
This... geez, this is...
Mikitty!!
Whaaaa!!
Wow, he scared me.
Cut that out, man.
Shouji (comedian) is looking for Mikitty
Mikitty!!
This guy's starting to piss me off.
His attitude is totally diferent from when he's with his partner!
Geez, his voice just came out of nowhere..
Mikitty!!
There's no way Mikitty would be in a place like this.
This guy's a moron.
He's really full-on.
No, not therenot there.
No, not there, not there.
No, geez, seriously.
You're freaking us out
I said you're freaking me out.
Seriously, stop it.
Ok, enough already.
Cocorico and Yamazaki are Imprisoned
Downtown Passing By
Mikitty...
Shouji No Longer Notices Their Presence
Man, what the hell?
No, he's the worst.
Huh? Where?
The Pay Phone is Ringing
I'm really scared.
It could shock us or something, huh?
Hello?
The time for a surprise telephone quiz
has come. Without further delay, here is your first question:
When you say vitamin you think of [C]
Okay.
When you say "Let's go to the end of the world" you think of [Q]
That being the case,
The mega popular idol group,
Momoiro Clover is what?
Seconds
Secret Prank in..
Momoiro Cloveris what?
Um, Momoiro Clover is "Z".
Z!!
Mizuki Ichirou announces the answer
I wasn't expecting that!
Holy..
This is bad for my heart.
Huh? What's this?
That guy is still
wandering around aimlessly.
It's really getting on my nerves.
Security Personnel Room
Eh? What the...
Is there anything in here?
Aha! There's a key!!
Right here.
Oh, up here. They're up here.
Seconds
The Room Goes Dark in..
Huh? No, no.
Which one are we supposed to take?
Whoa!!
This is not good at all!!
The shining light you see is an infrared light. Downtown can't see anything at all.
This is not good at all!
Wai-wait. What is that?
I'm scared. I'm scared!
Wait, we can't see a thing!
Hip-Shaking Old Ladies
Eek!
Someone!!
Someone's touching me!!
Aaaaaaagh!!
Someone's touching me Someone's touching, I'm telling you!
Someone! Someone is here! Someone's here, man!!
What are you talking about?
what are you talking about?
What are you talking about? What is it?
You scared the hell out of me!
The Lights Come Back On
Gross!
Wh-what the..?
Man, I'm really freaked out right now.
Huh? It won't open.
What?
Whoa!
What is it?
Mikitty...
He Can't Find Mikitty
Man, enough already! Seriously!
Give it up, man.
I'm afraid.
Jason Voorhees Attack in...
Seconds
Ah, man, I'm so freaked out.
Uwaa!
No! No!
Downtown Passes The Confinement Room
Eh?  Over here?
Eh? Over here?
What's wrong with you guys?
Downtown safely rescue the three of them
And then...
School Public Address
We have received information which states that Fujiwara Sensei is being held
in a storehouse near the school grounds.
Rookie teachers. All of you,
Make your way to the school grounds immediately, please.
Head to the
and save Fujiwara!!
storehouse
The 5 of leave for the storehouse to save Fujiwara without delay.
What's happened? Geez.
The five are just about to leave for their destination.
A barrage of terrifying  attacks while en route to the storehouse:
Sudden Wall Explosion
Jason Voorhees Raid
Flying Missiles
From here onward,
three terrifying pranks, one after another!
What the? We used to always have to save Heipo.
1F  Hallway
We did, didn't we?
I've gotta take a piss.
What's this?
The Wall Explodes
Definitely distressing.
Group of Jasons + A Missile
No, no! It's hopeless!
Huh? What?
Everyone
Go To The Storehouse!!
Ride The Motorcycles and
Are we all supposed to get on?
(The motorcycles)
Hey, they're connected together.
Ah! They're all attached to each other.
Ready?
Yes.
Ready.
Seconds
Secret Prank in..
The pedals are moving too fast!
Tadaa~! Long time, no see.
Yuutarou Appears From Beneath The Ground
Yuutarou.
It's been 2 years, you know.
You weren't here last year, were you?
That's right, isn't it Yuutarou-san?
He's soaking wet!
I'm quite saturated, aren't I?
As usual, he's got some wine poured!!
Yes, he does but this is going a bit far!
Let's go already!!
I'll be back.
Ok, I guess.
The directions are pointing left.
School Grounds
There's the storehouse.
Oh, it's here?
The Storehouse Is Surrounded By A Cemetery
Alright. Is this going to be OK?
I'm afraid.
We've made it here safely.
I've been holding onto the key, here.
Oh, did it just open?
Phew! That scared me.
The ground's all muddy, isn't it?
He's here.
Oh! Fujiwara.
Are you alright?
I knew you'd save me!!
What the hell is all that?
They Escape With Fujiwara Riding In A Baby Carriage
They safely release Fujiwara.
Without delay, they leave the storehouse and make their escape.
We're leaving now, Fujiwara.
Please be careful.
Ahh.. everyone. I'm not safe yet.
The rather gargantuan woman with long hair
may be here, so be careful, OK?
Who is this?
Seconds
Secret Prank in..
What are you going on about?
You're making no sense at all.
Gigantic Sadako + A Gang Of Sadakos
Waah! Scary!
Holy crap!
Scary!
Successfully Rescued Fujiwara
It's turned into Hakata Dontaku (a festival).
Active Teaching Duty: 19 Hours Elapsed
3 am.
These Enthusiastic Teachers,
who have travelled through time in the span of a day.
From the time of Edo to present day at this school.
They welcome that time at long last.
You've done well. You've completely fulfilled your duties.
Thank you so much.
It's over!
Hamada, how was it?
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work!!
Thank you as well.
Matsumoto, how was it?
Downtown will be turning 50 years old this year
Heh Heh Heh Heh
What are you laughing at?
Eh? The rule's still in effect?
Of course! How many times have you done this?
In all seriousness,
After us the younger members will take over.
Years Old
That's right.
Younger members...
I thought I'd have you guys do it.
Years Old
Thank goodness we have another happy ending.
Well, shall we go?
We're allowed to leave now.
I suppose so, huh.
Alright, we're done.
They new year has begun, hasn't it?
It sure has.
Oh? It's already the new year?
Happy New Year!
Here we go, now.
Ninomiya Kenjiro
Suga Kenji
Thank you all for your hard work.
Downtown-hyan, Cocorico-san
Tsukitei Housei-san, thank you for your hard work.
Right now, all the Ninomiya Kinjiro's bronze statues are gone,
the poses were of me reading a book, falling and hurting myself
so the new pose is going to be... wait...
The statue will be like this
That's what I suggested.
They told me "That's just somebody relaxing!"
So, for that reason...
That's pointless spank...
Pointless!
Well then...
Your hard work is appreciated.
Please excuse me.
He pisses me off.
Every year we do this, though.
Endo Shouzo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Number Of Hits On The Bum:
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Hosei
Good work.
Seriously... Happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
Fujii Fumiya
TRUE LOVE: The Gaki no Tsukai Version
When I look back, you were always laughing.
With only that wig on all the time.
You're so fine, even when I close my eyes, you shine through.
You're so fine,even when I close my eyes,you shine through.
You're so fine, even when I close my eyes,  you shine through.
It changesinto tears.
It changes into tears.
My only beliefis in Sekine.
My only belief is in Sekine.
Until COWCOW emerges.
Hisako spits venom
Far, far distant, lengthy Takenaka.
Nishida's outburstwas a must.
Nishida's outburst was a must.
When the meeting began, for some reason Sawa the one was in charge.
When the meeting began,for some reason Sawa the one was in charge.
When the meeting began, for some reason  Sawa was the one in charge.
A husband shocked by his wife.
Even if this combo were to say something, I wouldn't understand it.
Even if this combowere to say something, I wouldn't understand it.
Even if this combo were to say something,  I wouldn't understand it.
Goriraimo's bum is exposed.
Being kissed byMatsuko.
Being kissed by Matsuko.
Awkward and embarrassing satirical haikus.
We traveled by bus far, far into the past.
We time traveled by bus far, far into the past.
We slipped through time.
Why was my familyand ex-wife here when we arrived?
Why was my family  and ex-wife here when we arrived?
Why was my family and ex-wife  here when we arrived?
Itao, naked and experiencing shrinkage.
Okada's shtick hasn't changed.
Degawa and Ueshima...
Chouno slaps his face.
Mikihisa getsa kick in the bum.
Mikihisa gets a kick in the bum.
Endo was put on the spot.
Our secrets are always laid bare.
Our secrets are alwayslaid bare.
Our secrets are always  laid bare.
And an explosion, too.
The shame of wussing out.
Gazeonly at the laughter.
Gaze only at the laughter.
And so, another year has passed.
We must always dream of a future
We must always dreamof a future
We must always dream  of a future
filled with laughter.
A future filled with laughter.
We hope this year will be a wonderful one...
This year, too will overflow with laughter.
Ah, it's all over!
Thank goodness for that!
While the tape was playing, we welcomed the New Year.
Everyone, Happy New Year!
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year, everyone.
Happy New Year.
Yes, Happy New Year!!
Friday, January 8th "24 No Laughing Enthusiastic Teachers!!"
We will be airing a 2 hour special of never seen before footage!
Ahh, most definitely.
At least half of our audience is crying.
They're crying?
It was a moving performance.
I don't see anything at all.
Uh, look.. When everyone is watching like this
would you stop farting in my direction?
My reaction won't get filmed... and I can only
remain calm and smell it while you're farting away...
I know, right?
But if you think about it, it's hitting you two and us two.
It's being spread around evenly.
If you think about it, the last round (of farts)...
was exactly when we hit 12:00, new year...
Amazing, isn't it?
Everyone, Gaki no Tsukai thanks you for this year, as always!