I was watching the back of Yamasaki's head the whole time before we started.
C'mon, stop that!
There's nothing wrong with looking at it
He was really staring at the crown of your head
What did you think when you looked at it?
I thought "it must feel nice and breezy"
It's not really that breezy. This part is breezy though.
He was like, half smirking while staring
Zaki-san uses a lot of, what do you call it,
Anti-aging stuff I think? Right? Even before filming
He got Fujiwara from License to apply something like this.
I asked what it was and...
He was getting his gray hairs covered
That is anti-aging
Like black ink type stuff, painting his white hairs
That mascara type thing right?
Yamasaki was amazing, but Fujiwara was too.
He was like a programmer
He's getting better at it, you're asking him to do it every time after all
Hamada-san's senility is evolving in new ways I just experienced
Even just now, right there
In the dressing room, after we were done talking,
They said "It's almost time"
and handed us these to change into
He very confidently jammed his leg into the arm part of the Tanuki costume
"It fits so well" he said
It's things like this that make him like [!@!@# !@#!@]
REALLY?!
He's going to catch up to [@#%!@ !@((%] soon
TEXT 2
It's been a while.
Yes it has.
It's been three weeks.
Since our last meeting.
What were you up to during then?
We all had different things going on right?
I was-
How many times did you [*@!$%]
We're talking about [*@!$%]?
C'mon tell us
[*@!$%]? Almost never, almost never!
Almost never?
My mom and my dad,
Had their 50th anniversary
Their 50th wedding anniversary. So my mom's family, my sister's families, there were about 10 of us,
My dad is from Kumamoto. So we went to visit our family there. All of us.
That's quite a large group
And the other side had 30 people
So all 40 of us had dinner together
And basically,
Everyone had a bit of an underbite
My dad's face looks exactly the same
Only half had an underbite
Hey, not all of my relatives have a big chin
40 people with an underbite would be incredible
It's just his half, so 20 people. Exactly half.
All 8 of my dad's siblings were there
So including grandchildren, around 40 people
A dinner party
There was a toast at the beginning,
There was a person from the Kumamoto side, who said since we came from Osaka,
My dad is called Goji. He said "Goji-san, please do the honours"
My dad really doesn't like doing things like that
Yeah, he's a reserved man
He was asked a while ago,
In our neighborhood there was a summer karaoke competition
And my dad was the MC, and he isn't that type of guy at all,
And you couldn't hear him when he talked. And this drunk guy said,
"We can't hear you man!"
And as a child that really hurt me
Seeing my dad getting humiliated
That's something you don't want to see
That's the last thing you want to see
He was doing the toast in front of 40 people,
I was worried if he'd be alright
But maybe he's gotten better with time
He got the glass, and everyone was standing,
And he greeted them
"This time, this night,
I'm glad we were able to get together after so long
"So tonight let's enjoy ourselves!"
and he was speaking loudly
"Let's enjoy ourselves! Kanpai!" - everyone replied "Kanpai!"
And when they started to sit down, my dad started talking,
"I was born in Kumamoto"
And THAT'S when he started talking, and for so long
He got the order backwards, the cheers and the speech
He spoke forever
Everyone almost sat down and then got back up
He's not used to it
And the speech too, like nobody was really paying attention...
That pisses me off
He's not used to it
It pisses me off, for real
But the relatives,
They said they love the "No Laughing" series
An 86 year old grandfather asked me,
Does the Thai Kick really hurt?
He's concerned for you
86 years old!
It'll definitely hurt for him
It's the first time I've heard an 86 year old say the words "Thai Kick"
For me I...
Endo what do you do? Seriously
For me I have a family, so that takes up most of my time
Basically I just go home,
and there's a cafe in front of my place,
I'm usually over there
In a cafe by yourself?
In the cafe yes
You don't go home?
I go home, leave my bag at the entrance and head straight to the cafe
Just chilling out
There's a slightly bald guy named Jun-chan
I just talk to him
I go in the night a lot
Do you eat there too?
The food is good too, they have stuff like green curry
The other day on a shoot for Hirunandesu
We had to buy a lot of vegetables for a segment,
At a superstore
And I brought them home with me, but I didn't use them for anything
And I went to that cafe
Jun-chan?
Yes Jun-chan
And he was, I think, slightly balding
Yes I mentioned it 1 minute ago
He's not balding, he's bald
Jun-chan is balding
And I gave it to him, "Jun-chan here you go"
"Even though you're balding"
Could you make something with this?
"Thank you. I'm happy even though I'm slightly balding"
He wasn't that bald...
It's not enough to mention it, although he is balding
But that's about it
What was the furthest place you went?
In these 2 weeks? The furthest place I went to was...
Probably Wangan Studio
I didn't travel at all. Just the same places.
I'm worried for Endo
For real Hamada is always saying he's worried for Endo
Yeah
"What's gonna happen to him" he said, for real
See even Atsushi
He got married right?
I was concerned. How will Endo's future turn out
I do want to marry again
Oh you want to?
But when you do get married, will Jun-chan be able to keep quiet?
Jun-chan and I don't have that kind of relationship
Shut up!
The only thing I said about Jun-chan is that he's balding. And the green curry is delicious. That's all.
What were you imagining?
I thought green curry was a euphemism
Like a code word
What the hell are you imagining
I do want to marry again
I really want to see what Jun-chan looks like now
How old is Jun-chan?
36 years old he said
What do you like about him?
He's a good cook, I just entered the store by chance,
Jun-chan is a nice guy
The cafe is open until 00:00
The first time I went, with Wakky,
There was nothing available and it was past midnight. We peeked inside,
We asked if we can come in and he said of course.
And that's how it started
That's how we got to know each other
The start of your coming out
And did Wakky start frequenting it too?
Wakky's house is far, but it happens to be really near my house
So at first it was a threesome
That's a strange way to put it
You're just going to a restaurant in your neighbourhood right?
Exactly! I just checked out a nearby place
But do you really go everyday?
You have no feelings towards Jun-chan?
I obviously have no feelings for someone who runs a cafe near my house,
Plus, he's a balding old man
A divorced old man like me,
is not going to have anything with a balding old man
I really really like women
Matsumoto-san does a lot right?
Hamada-san also went overseas,
Someone I know told me,
Hamada-san went to Yankee stadium
Yeah, for a TV show
For Jump
New York?
What did you do?
I spoke to the players
Oh it was talk thing?
Any famous players you spoke to?
I wouldn't recognise them though
Kuroda, Uehara, Tazawa, and Ichiro
Ichiro?!
Ichiro and Hamada-san...
It's not that impressive!
They say Ichiro is hard to talk to, he doesn't speak much
Ichiro has a reserved image, and it's hard to interview him
He only eats Curry right?
There's no way that's true
He does have a routine,
I've heard he eats curry every morning
He eats curry every morning? He eats curry in the morning?
He eats some homemade curry every morning
Isn't it amazing? It makes no sense
He doesn't break his routine. That's his morning thing
But still why did he decide to eat curry for his morning routine?
He's been doing it for a long time
I bet even Indians don't eat curry in the morning
If I had curry from last night then I would eat it in the morning
Try to turn it into Udon
He eats curry rice
Does he eat the same curry everyday?
Or like "cutlet for today", or vegetable,
I don't know that
Are you even curious about that?
Aren't you curious?
Not at all!
The exact same curry?
He eats a large amount
There's nothing special about eating it with cutlets if you have them
The base is the same, probably
A simple one
Yeah so basically I just worked
Did you do anything during your off time?
I was free one morning so I played golf
Golf with Ichiro?
By yourself?
Of course not!
I was with the staff who came with me
If he started playing golf alone,
I'd think Hamada has finally lost it...
He starts talking about losing .... It's dangerous
You had a thing for your movie
I went somewhere for my film
I was fooled, by my manager Kimura
We had to go to Canada, I asked what plane, he said ANA
And ANA is fine with me
It's great, using a Japanese airline
And on the day, seriously, it wasn't ANA!
It was *** ******
It's the goddamn worst, it had nothing!
What do you mean?
Like there was nothing!
It was 12 hours! No movies or anything!
There was a fold out screen, there was one,
But it was in a foreign language
There was nothing Japanese
It was hell, 12 hours
And if they told me from the start I would have prepared
Yeah exactly, something to pass the time
Japanese first class is amazing isn't it?
They have pajamas and everything
I've never been in first!
I've never been in first either
How did you go to New York?
That was in Business
That's a lie for sure
It was definitley first
It wasn't economy right?
No way, he's beyond that level
He probably sleeps on the pilot's shoulder
That's more tiring, sleeping like that
I wanna lay down!
He rides in a never before seen class
I think Japanese airlines are amazing
If you go in first, they ask you,
"Would you like to change into Pajamas?"
I didn't know about that
Do you really not know about that?
That's a thing. And then the Attendant changes the washroom,
How do I put it, they turn it into a changing room
Oh, to change into pajamas?
Yes, so you change in there. And...
They put out a boy- actually that's not it
A boy? Oh a bed?
Yeah they prepare some bedding, when it's time to sleep
And it's amazing, it's totally flat with clean sheets
First is amazing!
First is amazing
I've never been in there
I seriously thought "I might just  **** ***"
TN: I think he's saying jerk off
That's not allowed is it
That's a grey area
It depends on how you do it
I haven't gone that far yet
But usually Hamada-san, you use first right?
No no no. I use Business
Yeah but for your own trips you use first for sure
No that's not true. I use business
What kind of vibe are you trying to put off?
There's a big gap between first and business
Yeah the price is a lot lower
It's this big a gap
How much do you think it costs to go to New York from Japan in First?
I was shocked when I heard,
It's over 3,000,000 yen ($22K USD)
That's a car
Wow
It's like driving there, coming back, and leaving your car at the airport
And that's all
Hold on, only 3 of us are shocked
One of us knew already
I was surprised too
Hold on, now that I think about it,
You own a private jet don't you?
Idiot!
On the H mark
I don't travel that often!
One that can land on the H mark
We just talked about Matsumoto-san's movie,
There's more about it
The other day Matsumoto-san surprised us by promoting his new film R-100 on a Hokkaido TV station
Why did he choose to go on a local broadcast? How was the promotion?
There's a video
There's a video of it
Enough already!
Matsumoto appeared on Hokkaido new program Ichioshi
Hello. We have something special for you all
And that is a special guest
A movie director
Today Matsumoto Hitoshi-san will be joining us
Welcome director!
Everyone in the studio seems to be smirking at me
This is amazing!
This is what I hate, watching this here with you guys
And it's almost released right?
I'm not sure what kind of facial expression I should have
Ah there's a red lamp on that camera there
And I forgot that
He's laughing so much
ENOUGH ALREADY
He's going HAHAHAA
C'mon it's a commerical now
And then, Matsumoto was asked to convey his feelings towards the movie in one word
Go ahead.
Ichioshi! (Highly reccomend it!)
I get it! You're promoting it
There's a lot of applause
Please watch the movie when it comes out. Thank you very much!
Amazing!
It was a local broadcast only
I did a lot of promotion for the film so far,
There aren't many national programs left to do it on
Yeah you've been on all of them
So I thought I want to do something different
On a local broadcast that doesn't play here at all,
I thought it would be new,
I thought it would be interesting
It was interesting, but it was a pain. I got so nervous.
After all this time in the industry,
There's always at least one face I recognise in the staff
There's at least 1 to 2 people I would know
It was ALL people I didn't know
I've never experienced that before
Even when I was a total rookie, I knew at least Hamada
That's right, you were with him
But even Hamada isn't there. It was literally just strangers.
There were some, what do you call them, local celebrities,
And you go like
You go like "AAAAHH"
They get a chance to meet you too
"I don't know your character!"
But they were laughing though
You don't see it often this kind of thing
But that's also interesting
Is that right?
But even though I went through the trouble of doing a local broadcast,
Watching it here with everyone ruins the point!
This is the most embarassing thing
Even people who don't know about baseball know Tanaka Masahiro,
And he's a very good player
He has 21 wins from the opening of the season
25 consecutive wins this year, it's the best record in the world
Yeah #1 in the world right now
#1 in the world?
"Could you use a comedy industry analogy to explain how amazing this is?"
by pen name "Gyudon Taro-san"
Gyudon Taro-san?
(Mr. Taro BeefBowl)
Yes.
There's no mistake, it says Gyudon Taro-san
I wonder how old he is now
I don't know the original name
It says it's a pen name
He hasn't lost since September 18th
So 21 times this year,
You played baseball so you understand,
Basically if you pitch good you win
I don't know baseball so I can't grasp how impressive this is
(TN: Sorry (; _ ;) idk what he's saying here)
And he hasn't lost once in the last 25 matches
Which means he's responsible for 25 wins by himself
I don't really get that
I don't get it
No way, really?
If you use baseball terms I won't get it
Use an analogy to explain
I know baseball so I can only explain it in baseball terms
These two just sighed so loud
If I had to explain this in comedian terms...
We're comedians but we don't really know baseball
Endo-san is a comedian and he played baseball so,
If Endo-san doesn't explain it  we won't understand it
If I had to convey how impressive this is...
He didn't lose means...
If I use TV ratings as an example,
It's like getting 25% viewership ratings every week for a year
That's how impressive it is
That was hard to understand
Gyoza, can you use Gyoza to explain it
TN: Gyoza are dumplings
It's not hard to get at all
That was pretty easy to understand
I like Gyoza
I really love Gyoza. Can you explain it using Gyoza?
"I don't give a shit about Gyoza so do it yourself" - is what I would say
It's like a comedian never bombing. Basically.
It's like in Oogiri and getting laughs with everything you say
It's just that face.
That face
Amazing.
Masahiro is from Hyogo prefecture right?
From Itami
Right, from Itami
There's so many impressive people from Hyogo prefecture
People from Hyogo prefecture?
Yeah people from Hyogo prefecture
They're doing well for themselves?
Yes! It's impressive
Aibu Saki-CHAN
Ueno Juri-CHAN
Hyogey's Kitagawa Keiko-CHAN
Todo Erika-CHAN
They're all women
And this grown ass man going "CHAN CHAN CHAN CHAN"
Counting on his fingers going CHAN CHAN CHAN CHAN
And Nena-Chan!
They're all women!