Cocorico
Endo Shozo  Tanaka Naoki
Gaki no Tsukai's Backstage
Good Morning
'Morning
Manager
Yuichi Tajima
Excuse me
Err...
It's about Hamada-san, but...
He kinda...
Found something he's crazy about to become
And said he also said "If you run after two hares, you will catch neither"
He was wondering if you would come and watch him
No way
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
But, guys...
Hamada-san said "If you run after two hares, you will catch neither"
What he's up to and why should we come?
Yamazaki Housei
I thinks is something related to comedy, but
It's something about the thing he's crazy about to become
About that thing that punk wants to become...
I'm positive it's going to be something he can't do
But you know, where we are right now is the actual spot of our job!
I know that
Well, anyway
Hamada-san said that "If you run after two har-
We got that already!
Really, right now
You look like a poster of Youku Hata
(March 2005)
Japan Entertainment!
You've been looking so long at this Youku Hata's poster!
Subtitles, encoding and translation: Mauro (マウロ) (aka Shion from TeamGaki) Visit: teamgaki.com follow me on twitter: @0daruma
So, what's this going to be?
Right...
Enough already!
Really!
It's in here!
Guided by manager Tajima, towards the place where Hamada is waiting
Where again?
What's that?
Enough already!!!
It's cold in here!
What's that?!
So... is this going to be part of today's broadcasting?
Is that true?
Huh?
I can kinda hear a voice
And it's loud, too
He must have realized (we're here)
In front, in front, in front!
What is that...?
Go in front, in front!
How did this happen?
More forward, you dumbass!
Forward, I'm saying!
Don't be afraid you bastards!
Are you afraid of the ball?!
Don't be afraid!!
You should come nearer the net!
Don't be afraid of the ball, you bunch of idiots!
Hamada's rage in the gymnasium!?
What's the true meaning behind
It's close, it is really close!
The tournament is drawing closer, you idiots!
What the hell is he doing?
I want to go too! (to the tournament)
What is he doing?
Takahara, come here a second, you brat
What the hell are ya doin'?
I'm sorry!
Do the stance, brat
Yes!
What the hell was that?
Don't let everything be vain, you idiot!
I'm so sorry!
Bend your leg more!
Your stance should be that way, you idiot
Yes!
Do some squat, brat
Yes! I'm really sorry!
BACK ON TRACK!!
Is Hamada-san
Doing a volleyball coach
Or something like that?
I WANNA GO THERE TOO!! (to the tournament)
I have no idea
Oh, wait a second, just a moment
Guys..!
Good Morning
A total different Hamada from before
Which is even showing his smile
Good morning
What's that all about?
What?
Well, that's
Our daily practice session
Because the tournament is really close!
And I want to go to it too!
That's...
What do you think, Endo?
Excuse me?
What do you think?
Well, what should I think about this...
In order to get them into the tournament which will begin shortly
We need to finish up some preliminary contest during in a month or so
I want to be part of those, really
The tournament, uh?
What do you think, Endo?
For some reasons, Hamada asks only for Endo's impressions.
Well but...
This is going to take some time, right?
U-uh, you got that right
That's why I'm scolding those girls for good
Say, Endo
I got a nice bunch of young £@!#=&s, right?
Wanna take some of them? Are you thinking about this?
No way...
Okay! Next up is blocking, blocking! Blocking practice!
Wait a little, won't you?
They were doing squats...
The break is over!
His voice turned all raspy with all those screams!
You're right
He shouted so much
Jump, jump, jump!
Wanting to live by his true nature, uh...
Probably his new life purpose
What the hell is that?
What the hell dude
Risk your life and jump, you idiots!
Shut up and go jumping!
He seems to be merciless
Their hope is going to vanish rapidly
Etou, come here a second
What the hell was that, you idiot?
You should jump more and you know that, you moron!
DON'T YA DARE MAKE FUN OF ME!
Are you despising volleyball?
No
YA REALLY ARE DESPISING IT, YA ASSHOLE!!
I'm sorry!
Why did ya ran away, you moron?
UH?!?
Yes!
DON'T YA DARE UNDERESTIMATE VOLLEYBALL, YA IDIOT!
YES!
UNDERSTOOD?!
Now drag the tire!
Woah... so strict...
For real?!
No one does this nowadays!
Let people from outside do this!
It won't make sense anyway
Really...
I wonder if it's slippery in here...
That's so pointless
Jump a lit-
Don't try to slow the pace!
Yes!
ETOOOOOOOU!
Sorry there
Woah, really
As you see, being strict is necessary
So they won't make the same mistakes again
What do you think, Endo?
What do you think?
Well, you're acting very harshly...
Well, Etou won't take this seriously if she's not scolded
Etou?
Etou, Etou
Ah, Etou-san
Well, she has a nice #"%£
Uh...
Well, that's how it is
That's...
I think that's the only way possible to raise them
I'm protecting them
Just like Mama's Volley?
Yeah but...
The preliminary contest already began
And I want to be part of it too!
I WANT TO GO TO IT TOO!!
Hamada ends up raising the tone of his voice due his overwhelming amount of passion
Trainer!!
Trainer!!!
What happened?!
She hurt her foot?
In here?
Call an ambulance, an ambulance!!
Hang in there
Wasn't he saying "I want to go there too"?
There's too much fuss in there
He's back
Use this
I don't get the meaning of this
He brought a tree branch
Stay still or I can't place this branch, you moron!
Hamada is performing a first aid by using a tree branch
Isn't the ambulance already there?!
An ambulance?!
Get her in the ambulance!
What the hell...
Oh, they came
That was fast.
Oh, they're there
Nurses are there, but where's the doctor?
She hurt her feet badly, so take good care of her
Aahh, wait a sec
You know, during this time the street is crowded
Be sure to take kototoi street
Yes
What's with that thoughtfulness?
I agree
You should encourage her!
Take care!
Encourage her!
Get well soon!
Remember: from kototoi street!
It's "KOTOTORI STREET"!
Why giving instructions about the street?
Alright, let's take a break
Yes!
After this get serious about your training!
Etou, no one told you to stop running with the tire
Got it
He's so strict on Etou, isn't him?
He's a jerk against her
So strict on her...
We broke a sweat, didn't we?
A break...
The preliminary contest is very near, that's why I'm being so strict, you know...
Hamada suddenly turns into mama-san during the practice, concealing his rude side
Who the hell told him anything about that?
You're right...
Really!?
It would feel bad even to have a chat with him
I agree
That's a sandwich I made!
Eh? Really?
Looks delicious!
Thanks a lot
Hamada is being a real mama-san, having his pupils making him try the hand-made food they brought
That's disgraceful
Cucumbers? That's good!
Stephanie, how about that matter of your?
That's possible...
Huh?
He totally answered randomly
He answered so bluntly
Just like a "is that so.."
I didn't understand anything
Well, if you think it is like that, isn't that enough?
Once more a random answer
Shouldn't he answer in english?
That's right, he should
But he's answering in japanese
That's delicious, it's ok to me
But that sandwich, it just
It has too many cucumbers in it!
It looks as if he's very popular
The tension completely vanished
Looks like it
He's coming
Endo?
Yes?
Eat up
Ah.. okay, right
It's safe
Everyone eat one, starting from Endo
This time not only Endo?
If it's like that, I'm going to eat
It's hand-made
Hand-made cookies
Cookies?
They're delicious
Well, they're not bad
I told ya
Yeah
That's it?
If you want another, take it
Thanks
Who made those?
Ah, Stephanie's grandmother
She's a baker
You can have this, hold them
Take them home
Huh? All of those?
Uh-uh
Let your daughter Hoheto have some of those
Her name is Iroha
Thanks a lot
Hamada, you too should uhm...
You know is getting sunny
The weather is going to be good...
yeah...
Well but it's still cold outside, I prefer train in here
If we can do it, it's good
Etou is still running
Isn't okay for her to stop now?
Well, she has a nice #%!&, so this won't hurt
You've been saying #!%& a lot, recently
That's because I'm working on them
If they accomplish this training, I'm coming back for sure
Okay?
You know, the preliminary contest is drawing near
I want to go to it too!
ALRIGHT!
Back to practice!
Etou, get to training!
I wonder why he snapped at us
Because "I want to go to it too!"
Mama Hamada is beginning the attack practice
Woah! she's good!
Really good!
Huh?
He didn't get angry on that person just now
He snapped at Etou but not at the old lady
More, more!
Strike the ball harder!
Awesome!
She's on a high level!
We're doing great!
Number 7 is strange
Yeah, she's strange
Number 7's figure looks like a red wiener
Tatemori, wait a second
You've been acting strange
What the hell? Your hand must be like this to strike
*Guu: rock in rock-paper-scissor
Why are you doing the guu--- what the-?
What's that? What happened?
Well, actually...
What
Why are you keeping the guu, what the hell
What's that?
It's chocolate!
It's Valentine day, you know, today!
So...
You've been holding this from the beginning?
Coach! Me too!
Me too!
For real?
Me too! Me too!
What the hell
Really?
What the hell are you doin'?!
From me too!
Girls! let's lift up our coach!
What the hell are you sayin'!
There's no need to do that!
I didn't get the meaning of this lift-up.
Good, isn't it?
What do you think, Endo?
Isn't a relation like this a good thing?
Yeah, it is... yeah
Well...
There are also times in which I'm harsh
But relationships among us humans should have this feel... kindness and the rest...
*bell rings*
Perfect timing, this bell
It rang at the most perfect moment
Are we done with this, now?
That wasn't part of the performance, am I right?
Subtitles, encoding and translation: Mauro (マウロ) (aka Shion from TeamGaki) Visit: teamgaki.com follow me on twitter: @0daruma And don't forget to read the description! More has to come...
Okay! Back with the practice!
Shall we go?
I'm done with this, I don't get its meaning
Really, dude