Gaki No Tsukai's Famous Series - Shichi Henge
A situation where a comedian must not bomb, showing their true talents
The comedian taking part tonight...
Gaki No Tsukai ya Arrahende  CHIKI CHIKI - FUJIWARA Fujimoto Shichi Henge!
Downtown
Hitoshi Matsumoto
Masatoshi Hamada
It's been a while
Right?
So it's Fujiwara today,
Not Haranishi (his partner)
That does seem to be the question
Yes
Really?
And it's Fujimon...he's not really that funny,
What the hell?
He gets by using his health
Let's introduce him
It's strange
Come in FUJIWARA
Looking forward to this
Thank you
FUJIWARA
Takayuki Haranishi
Toshifumi Fujimoto
It's not Haranishi right?
Yes, it said Fujimoto on the schedule
You look weird!
Weird
What kind of face was that?
It's too early for us, for a guy like me
Ah really?
"Ah really?"
Encourage me
Right right
Was the room always this small?
My face is too big!
Sorry?
My face is too big
It makes the room feel small
Oh is that so?
He's the 25th one,
What's your goal?
The top
Indeed
Where do you think you'll come?
Right, I want to be above 13, Miyasako
Ah I see
Ameagari Kesshitai - Miyasako
I think of this as a turning point for us
You think you can still succeed?
I can still keep going!
You should be telling me that
You'll just dawdle around after
I don't want to dawdle like that!
Fujimoto you might get job offers after this
That's true
Just keep getting laughs here,
You might get top billings after this
People might talk about your performance
But I've been doing this for 25 years. I can usually tell the face of a comedian that's going to fail.
So, how will Fujimoto fare?
Downtown Gaki no Tsukai Arrehende!!
Typeset by portnoyd
Translated by senor_wristband
Planning Meeting
What should we do?
Maybe that one
"Hamada presents Comedian Impersionation competition" - Why does Hamada present it?
Cocorico
Hosei Yamasaki
Naoki Tanaka
Shozo Endo
So this guy can't do impressions?
They must pay 1000 yen for laughing
Probably not this one then
Hamada's not doing anything?
Well I don't know
Hamada has to do it right?
Shichi Henge ~ Start
What?
Hamada has to do it right?
TN: Endo should've called him Hamada-san
You're calling me Hamada?
I said Hamada?
He said Hamada right?
You heard that right?
I was taken back
What about this one?
"How much coffee is Matsumoto worth?"
How much coffee can we buy using Matsumoto's savings?
I wanna see that
I bet it's a lot!
I bet it is a lot
He's changing the subject
I changed the subject
He changed the subject
The Yama no Ishimatsu, we did that because I did Kendo before
Came from Osaka
Fujimoto's mom
Haranishi's mom
It was rather funny
You didn't bomb today, don't worry
Don't get so upset
People laughed at your jokes
You and Kito-san
I'm gonna go greet Tamori-san, alright?
That was awful, we got no reaction
Nobody was laughing
I told you right?
Shut up bitch
You're the one who froze up!
What's your problem?!
Asshole!
What the fuck do you want?!
You keep messing around like that
Tell me what you mean
What do you mean?
You messed it up
Well it's your fault too!
It's your fault
I didn't do anything
You only blame others!
I got some laughs didn't it?!
I want to get good ratings, what's wrong with that?!
It's cause you messed up! It's cause-
Am I wrong?
All you care about is the ratings!
This is - *pant* - your fault! - *pant*!
Let me go!
Let me go, then I'll show you
I'm not ever letting you go
What? You bald asshole
You're fucking bald aren't you?
Bald!
Baldy!
Shut up bitch, you're gonna go bald too!
What the hell are you doing?! Stop it! Stop it!
How did this happen?
Calm down, alright calm down
Calm down, alright?
What are you doing?!
What are you doing? Cut it out idiot
Shut up!
What?!
What are you doing?!
Stop it stop it
Stop!
STOP! STOP IT!
It's her fault!
Bald!
Stop
Stop saying that
Bald!
Stop
Don't say that!
Bald!
Stop!
Don't say bald!
Bald!
Stop, stop saying that!
He didn't do anything
He didn't do anything right?
It was so long too
It was so long, they were really fighting!
Right?
This isn't Shichi Henge
This isn't Shichi Henge at all!
Penalties are given to charity.
Was that your mom?
It's my mom, and his mom
That was amazing, they were so angry
They sure were
That aside, he didn't even perform his first act by himself
He left it to his parent!
Have you ever seen that? A comedian who leaves it to his parents
Commercial Break
Well, we should get started on that soon
If we don't get the first steps done,
Yeah
We can't keep going like this-
That's true
That guy plays dirty doesn't he?
Put it in
It was too long,
He needs to stop doing multiple transformation during one transformation
That's true!
He had his skits written on his hand
The next skit he's gonna do?
All the timings and everything
He's quite a crude man isn't he?
Hidenori Nakai
- Yoshimoto executive who helped out DownTown when they were young
Good morning
Hey Fujimoto
Good Morning
Yeah recently-I've asked for an appoitment
An appoitment
To get-
You're not taking this seriously
How many regular gigs?
Yeah, yea-
Zero
Zero?
Yes
Who gave you the name FUJIWARA?
Oh um, you sir
You know, when FUJIWARA does bad,
It's like I'm doing bad too, right?
Show me your payslip, your latest one
Oh, yes
So short!
"Job Change Festival"?
"Job Change Festival" huh?
yes
You made 60,000 from this? (< $600)
It was um, it was half the payment
Just 60,000 yen ?
So with the apperance fee that's just 150,000 yen
No that-
This is the only work you had for one month?
Yes
You're fooling around
I'm doing my best!
You're getting mad?
I'm working really hard too
No if you were-Are you trying to look cool?
You're putting up appearances
Let me get my payslip
No you don't need it
Sorry just-
Who needs that shitty payslip
I can't let my juniors see that
That guy is the lowest of the low
Nakai-san huh?!
I looked and saw Nakai-san heading over, I thought we're in trouble now
That was his real payslip right?
It must be
I saw everything on it
That guy is way too careless
Nakai-san can speak better than comedians
I was thinking the whole time, "Man he doesn't stutter"
How come after his skits end, we're the ones who get all excited?
TN: He's parodying one of Hamada's songs
"Should I put down the car seat and take--Masatoshi Stinky Mouth
"The cigarette fills up the room-Masatoshi Stinky Mouth
Hamada you're not funny, You're not  funny Hamada
"Make the sunrise my background music"
"Hamada is f*cking an ugly girl on the side"
"Everything"
"Hamada by himself"
"A fading dream - ****** Hamada"
"A place I want to reach"
"In your arms, Hamada's Black Sunday"
If you're gonna use me, get a few more laughs!
Yeah. This was simply your junior insulting you!
I'll never forget that bitter smile he had when he came in
She is Fujimoto's stylist
Morning!
Good morning
This will be your hat today
Ok
Alright. Will it fit?
It's a bit tight
Oh? I apologise
This is a larger one
Ok
My head really hurts
It kinda hurts
This, this one
I can't do that one
Are there more?
This is impossible!
I can't get it on
It even says LOVE, let's do this one
That one? Alright
Let's go
2 more left?
He got some money at the start right?
But we didn't laugh because of him
Yeah it wasn't cause of him
Nakamura-san and everyone, they're pretty vintage
That's true
Where is the Gundam?
I found you Gundam!
Put your hands down!
Your ha-
Guntank!
What are you doing?!
Amuro's gonna hit!
Well done Amuro!
Well done Amuro (x5)
Amuro's gonna hit!
The Gundam guy was funnier
That was an avant-garde performance
Indeed
A song is good too
I couldn't hear anything at all
Yeah, we need to bring them in again
Marks from the bat on his bare ass
That's dirty!
That's why he did the Gundam skit!
That's why!
What's he doing?
This guy...I bet he got his ass smacked while preparing
It's swollen isn't it?
Amazing!
I've never seen someone with such a swollen ass!
In these few minutes
That's amazing if he planned it
That hurts, that's gotta hurt
I couldn't hold back against that
Couldn't hold back
If he planned that ass swelling, that's amazing
He probably calculated that
Indeed
Well it's over
Thank you!
Well done!
He passed 30,000
Hmm?!
35,000 yen
9th place
Where did I come in?
9th, amazing!
Exactly as I predicted
Exactly as you predicted?
Did you really plan that ass thing?
Yes
It would be hard to see otherwise
I told them to smack it hard, real hard!
He got so excited from showing off his ass
You really cultivated that joke
Maan...
(Can't hear over audience)
I heard from LICENSE,
Yes
They got laughs for the first time in a while!
They always get laughs!
LISCENCE is getting laughs!
It's fine!
Those M1 Comp-
Enough already!
That's fine, they're doing their best
Just before this, I took a shit,
Yes
The toilet at my house, has an automatic lid,
An automatic bidet,
And it also flushes automatically,
If I get used to this,
He's so rich!
No no
It's amazing you knew those toilets existed!
It means you have one like that too right?
What's with that reaction?
You're like (hilarious reference)
So cause of that, the other day I went to a store
And I took a shit without flushing!
Right?
You thought it would flush by itself
I thought it would flush by itself!
So I let it all out, got up
"Well you know" - "OH SHIT I DIDN'T FLUSH!"
You know, there's something that pisses me off,
Yes
The washing machine,
It's too new
It has a child lock on it!
Oh?
So I can't open the dryer!
Cause it's locked
During the cycle, like enough already I can see it's totally dry!
It's definitely dried out, I can see that the clothes are fluffy
And I'm the one who told the dryer to make sure it's thoroughly dried
And I did do that, I did that, but,
You know I-
Cause you're too young
You overdid it?
I overdid it, I apologise
I want to open it, but "Channel Lock Channel Lock"
Sorry that was a TBS thing
The child lock
I can't open it, it's impossible
It opens after a certain time right?
And like if you press the suspend button,
If you press it?
After that, no it doesn't open, after that,
It enters "Cool Down"
Yes
Cause it's too hot, so that's another 5-10 minutes, sometimes 2 hours!
I see
It's horrible right? All Japanese manufacturers have this
Oh? I didn't know that
And I want to open it, and I'm just waiting the entire 20 minutes
And when it finally finished-
So just go do something else!
I want to watch it the whole time
I can't do anything else
If I do something else I'll forget about it
Just come when it's finished
And sometimes when it's finally finished, it's not dried properly!
"What the hell!" I thought
And then it takes a really long time for it to heat up after cooling down
So you're judgement was wrong then, it wasn't fully dry
No no, first off what's the deal with that child lock?
Why is there a child lock?
It's so you don't open it right?
What's gonna happen if I open it?
You'll get burned
I'm not gonna get BURNT!
If I was gonna get burned then my pants would be on fire!
They won't!
What the hell! What the hell!
It should be enough for a mom to say "Don't do that!"
It's to prevent a need for that
Even in a new car,
Sometimes you drive it home with the child lock on right?
I've never done that
You know in the side of the door, like in the back door there's a child lock right?
So the guy at the dealership probably left it on by accident
And so you can't open the back door from the inside!
You have to open it from outside right?
Exactly! And well this is an indecent story,
I told a girl to sit in the backseat and hide herself
Did you really need to say that
Well maybe not,
So I want to keep her hidden right?
But when I said "Alright, get out now!"
She said "It won't open!"
Like that
What was that?
Like "Ladies first"
It would be awful if someone took a photo of that!
That would suck. The fact you had to get out really sucks too
They should make different products for people who have kids and people who don't
You...
And if a kid sticks their hand in and gets hurt it'll be another pain in the ass
yeah
You have a shredder?
Yes, I have.
Why?
Because there's something I don't want anyone to see.
What's that?
It's an obscene document . . .
"Obscene!?"
It's not obscene.
"Obscene?"
It's like a pay stub or something.
Ah, do you cut up your pay stubs?
Of course, so what?
It's not just a vertical slice now, It's a full slice.
It can be cut very small, like this.
Even if it's a vertical slice, that's still a "full slice."
It can be cut very small.
Is that so?
Mine can be cut very small.
But the amount of money in my pay stub isn't small, though!
I see.
Last minute subbed by RAIDEN
(u/raiden1017)
Let's help each other :-)