0 0 m -220 -48.125 b -227.875 -49.125 -249.25 -48.125 -247 -30.25 b -248.125 -20.375 -226.75 -0.75 -221.125 0 b -212.125 5.625 -208.75 -0.75 -203.125 -1.875 b -196.375 -8.5 -189.625 -10.75 -182.875 -27.25 b -180.625 -42.5 -195.25 -43.75 -196.375 -45 b -205.375 -49.125 -213.25 -48.125 -220 -48.125 m -214.375 -42.5 b -204.25 -45 -190.75 -38.375 -193 -31.625 b -200.875 -40.25 -207.625 -40.25 -214.375 -42.5 m -271.75 -139.25 b -267.25 -139.25 -229 -131.625 -234.625 -81.125 b -242.5 -49.125 -263.875 -33.75 -270.625 -30.25 b -274 -29.25 -292 -15.125 -316.75 -38.375 b -322.375 -49.125 -333.625 -61.5 -325.75 -88.75 b -322.375 -99.75 -316.75 -120.875 -296.5 -132.75 b -290.875 -135.875 -281.875 -141.5 -271.75 -139.25 m -170.5 -141.5 b -168.25 -141.5 -141.25 -149.25 -117.625 -108.5 b -114.25 -98.625 -105.25 -86.375 -110.875 -55.75 b -117.625 -30.25 -128.875 -29.25 -135.625 -27.25 b -141.25 -27.25 -149.125 -20.375 -176.125 -39.25 b -185.125 -46.75 -198.625 -51.375 -204.25 -82.125 b -203.125 -82.125 -216.625 -102.125 -188.5 -132.75 b -182.875 -137.375 -177.25 -141.5 -170.5 -141.5 m -274 -105.25 b -305.5 -99.75 -287.5 -65.625 -272.875 -69.125 b -268.375 -69.125 -258.25 -71.375 -256 -86.375 b -259.375 -104.375 -266.125 -102.875 -274 -105.25 m -274 -95.25 b -267.25 -97.625 -263.875 -88.75 -265 -86.375 b -265 -78 -271.75 -78 -275.125 -78 b -279.625 -78.75 -281.875 -83.25 -280.75 -88.75 b -280.75 -91 -278.5 -95.25 -274 -95.25 m -271.75 -91 b -275.125 -89.75 -274 -85.625 -271.75 -85.625 b -269.5 -85.625 -267.25 -89.75 -271.75 -91 m -162.625 -105.25 b -187.375 -100.875 -176.125 -66.75 -162.625 -69.875 b -158.125 -69.125 -146.875 -71.375 -146.875 -91 b -150.25 -104.375 -159.25 -105.25 -162.625 -105.25 m -162.625 -95.25 b -148 -95.25 -152.5 -78 -160.375 -78 b -162.625 -76.75 -171.625 -78.75 -169.375 -88.75 b -169.375 -91 -168.25 -95.25 -162.625 -95.25 m -160.375 -91 b -163.75 -88.75 -161.5 -84.375 -159.25 -85.625 b -155.875 -86.375 -158.125 -91 -160.375 -91 m -276.25 -85.625 b -278.5 -85.625 -277.375 -82.125 -276.25 -82.125 b -275.125 -82.125 -274 -85.625 -276.25 -85.625 m -163.75 -84.375 b -166 -84.375 -164.875 -81.125 -163.75 -81.125 b -162.625 -81.125 -161.5 -84.375 -163.75 -84.375 m -333.625 -159.25 l -104.125 -159.25 l -104.125 63.75 l -333.625 63.75 m -106.375 -157 l -331.375 -157 l -331.375 61.75 l -106.375 61.75
TPF
Shock Confessions! Memory Ryokan!!
Yamazaki Hosei
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
It's cold recently.
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Yeah all day.
In cooperation with Godzilla radio:
Down Town's Gaki no tsukai ya arahende!!
Godzilla radio
Otviss
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
**We also have facebook and twitter.**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
Godzilla radio
If you're unhappy about anything regarding the episode, please send us feedback at: Tofupandahost@gmail.com
Proofreader:
Thank you so much Godzilla radio for translation and timing.
Please visit his webpage:
http://www.jburogu-godzillaradio.blogspot.com
Translators:
Typesetters:
______________________________________________________
Excuse my intrusion.
Please have one.
Excuse me.
Thanks
Rocky
Rocky Balboa
"Rocky"
Rocky, a low ranking boxer is given a shot at fighting the world champion.
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Ahhh...
What happened again?
Hmm...
Mmkay then.....ready, set...
YES...!!
It must have been quite tough, huh?
What?
You had it quite tough, didn't you Hamada-san?
Hmmm...
What? Why?
Yeahhhh, well, I was quite a bad dude back in the day
During your student days?
I used to do boxing.
Ohh? I never knew that.
Ahh, and?
I ended up fighting in a match.
What? I never heard of that!
Really? But, Matsumoto-san, you've known him for ages!
Yeah, now that I think of it, I did fight someone.
But...I hadn't really done any proper training, you know?
You know?
I hadn't, you know?
Ohh yeahh okay.
And I did shit like....
punching meat and stuff.
You were punching meat?
Your story is all over the place, man.
Nooo, I was punching meat and stuff for training.
Why were you training like that?
Some old geaser was telling me to punch meat.
I don't understand your story.
He was my trainer!
My opponent was super strong. I beat him up real good too though.
I beat him up good, but I got smashed to a pulp too.
Who did you fight?
The champion.
THE CHAMPION!?
You were at that level?
Was it a world championship?
What? Wasn't he the champion?
We don't know! That's what you told us!
Oh...yeah it was the champion then.
He was strong as fuck. Maan, I got fucked up.
What was the result?
I.....lost. I think?
Maybe I lost?
Oh, wow, you got beat up so badly you can't remember.
Anyway, one thing I do remember
"Adriaaaan!"
I was screaming after the match
Who is that?
The name of my girlfriend at the time.
Oh at the time?
Adrian? Were you dating a non-Japanese person?
She was butt ugly though.
I've known you a long time, but didn't know that story.
I don't want to do that again.
So you stopped right after?
That was your one and only boxing fight?
No, I mean I don't want to talk about this anymore.
I seeeee.
It was rough. I didn't think I'd talk about it now.
Ohhh, well I'm glad you let us know about it.
There's a lot we don't know, hey?
I've never heard stories of how you grew up.
Yeah, that's true.
Human Role:
Colonel Taylor
Planet of the Apes
"Planet of the Apes"
Colonel Taylor
Colonel Taylor and crew crash landed on a planet ruled by apes who speak words like humans.
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Please, not me...please.
Everyone good? Ready, set...
YES...!
That's a relief!
What's wrong Endo? Did something bad happen to you?
There's a story I wish I would never remember.
Seriously?
I told my story, so you should too.
I don't think you'll believe my story, but just hear me out.
Hey man, don't say shit like that.
I'll believe whatever you say, Endo!
Yeah of course!
Well uhh....
I was bullied by monkeys in the past....
Wait, what did you say?
You were bullied by monkeys?
What do you mean? Like dude, I believe you but...
Basically, I had to fly away from Earth.
What?
Fly away from Earth?
Might seem sudden, but basically, my spaceship broke down and...
The one you're in?
The spacehip I'm in, yes.
Why's that?
Ummm well..
engine troubles or something....
That's an incredible story!
It's amazing you survived!
Yeah so, I crash landed and...
That's amazing.
....and, that was when I started....
....to be bullied by monkeys.
What are you talking about?
I don't get it. Your story just jumps from one place to the next.
Why are you suddenly being bullied by monkeys?
You won't believe me, but you know how Earth is ruled by humans?
Instead, monkeys rule over this other planet.
And...
The Statue of Liberty
......I saw it there
In America?
And I was like "Woaahh!"
"So this was Earth once upon a time"
....and that's kind of how it ended.
The world is a strange place.
Well yeah, I guess.
It's good you got back safely.
Yes it was.
I was worried what might have happened to you.
I didn't understand a lot of the story though.
But hey, it's hard remembering old stories, isn't it?
It sure is.
You just remember bits and pieces.
Ashita no Jow
(Joe of Tomorrow)
Yabuki Joe
"Ashita no Joe"
Yabuki Joe starts boxing under the guidance of Dange Danpei, and fights against the likes of Rikiishi Tohru and the World Champion.
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
There are heaps of others who haven't spoken yet.
Might be weird for me to bring this up now...
But my name is actually "Joe".
What?
You're already gonna say that?
That far?
You said you used to do boxing, right, Hamada-san?
Yeah.
I used to box as well.
Really?
Why didn't you say before?
Well I didn't want everyone to turn their focus onto me.
Why did you do boxing?
There was this old dude...
...with a, what's it called?
An eye patch.
He said "You got a good punch. You should fight in a match".
I was quite happy like "Oh what? Are you serious?"
And so I fought, but I think a girl came out at some stage...
...or something. Maybe?
What are you saying?
Were you fighting girls?
No, that's not it.
Aren't you just talking about Moriman?
No they weren't girls.
My opponent was....
...that guy, a foreigner.
Jose Mendoza!
I was getting beaten down like this and....
the eyepatch dude kept saying "Stand up! Stand up!"
Because I was sitting down a fair bit.
Oh you were down?
"Stand! Stand up Joe!"
and I was like "Yes! Yes!"
So I tried really hard fighting and.....
...in the end....I died.
Wha?
You died? But you're alive.
In a sense you died, right?
Oh as a boxer, you died?
That's messed up!
In the end I was like this, and all white.
Were you ok?
You skipped a lot in your story.
I didn't want to remember that.
What's up with everyone today? Got a lot of things to get off your chest?
Ikkyu-san
"Ikkyu-san"
Ikkyu
Ikkyu would continuously solve many problems with his quick wit.
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
I'd like to hear more about Hamada-san.
Yeah, I'm sure you experienced a lot.
You just told us about you as an adult. How about as a child?
Oh, yeah, right.
Yeah please tell us something.
When I was little I....
I was made to go to a temple often...
The big-wig of the town at the time was an evil guy.
What the fuck are you talking about?
It doesn't make much sense.
Well, ahh you know...
...he'd make ridiculous demands
that piss people off.
Even to little kids, despite him being a grown adult, he'd say all this unreasonable shit.
You know how there's a 'hashi'?
"Hashi", as in bridge?
Yeah, he put a sign on a bridge saying,
"Crossing the bridge is prohibited".
Well that's pretty annoying of him
I crossed it anyway.
But you're not supposed to!
It says you can't cross it.
Hah!
Well it could also mean that you can't
cross the "hashi", meaning "edge"!
What?
I strutted straight down the middle.
You must have been a pain in the ass as a kid.
Yeah a bit annoying.
Bit of a smart ass.
I liked to use my wit.
So I did stuff like that a fair bit.
I did that a lot.
Fuck, it's hot.
Well, we're glad to hear a story from long a go anyway.
So that's the kind of kid you were?
Yeah, that's right. People might not have liked me, I dunno.
Jason
"Friday the 13th"
Jason, a serial killer, murders the men and women who come to visit a camping ground, one-by-one.
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
What the fuck...
Ready, set...
Give me a break! Not my memories again!
What's wrong with that? C'mon dude.
Just do a quick version.
Well, I....
...wore an ice hockey mask and...
Who did?
I did.
When you were a kid?
No, it was...
really recently.
Recently? What for?
I just got really frustrated....
...so I wore an ice hockey mask, got a machete
...and just massacred people.
You can't do that!
I couldn't help it! I was just so pissed off!
Who did you kill!?
Just whoever was there.
Some guy that came to stay over.
Someone you know!?
It happened last month, or like...
on Friday....the 13th.
Woah, you're scary, dude.
I'd never wanna stay at your place.
Shiiiit, that's terrifying.
You're fucking scary.
Hoshi Hyuma
Kyojin no Hoshi
I heard that Tanaka is actually kind of into baseball?
"Kyojin no Hoshi"
Hoshi Hyuma
Hoshi Tyuma joins the Giants ,thanks to the spartan training methods employed by his father Ittetsu, and competes with rivals using makyuu (magic pitches).
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
That's right!
You'd think Endo has more to do with baseball.
But it's actually Tanaka?
Since everyone likes to link Endo with baseball a lot...
I kind of hid it. It was hard to say.
Ahh yeah, I get you.
My old man,
really loved baseball.
Yeah some dads are like that.
He was extremely strict too.
Yeah.
When I said I don't want to train anymore
he flipped over the dining table
Wow, he's scary.
He then forces this thing on me.
What?
Springs.
Springs?
He put springs all over my body.
Why?
He made me wear this thing that made it harder to move
so that I could train to throw balls faster than usual...
or something like that.
You should've told someone about that. Didn't anyone speak up for you?
My elder sister was worried for me.
But...all she'd do was peek out.
..and wouldn't speak out for me.
So I couldn't stop. Anyway....
I eventually joined the Giants.
You were in the team?
That's amazing!
It might not be very well known but...
I had no idea!
The training was effective and I could throw...
"Magical Pitches..."
You what?
Like a magic throw where the ball disappears...type of thing.
Type of thing?
As if it would disappear!
It does disappear! Everyone's shocked, like even...
Ban-kun...
Who the hell is Ban-kun?
He was the catcher.
The catcher?
There was also a guy called Hanagata.
Who's that?
He might have been a first draft pick of the Tigers.
There wasn't anyone called that.
I'm pretty sure that he did exist.
He had front teeth like this....
Front teeth?
I mean his fringe...
Anyway, how do you make the ball disappear?
I stretch out my arms, and jump up...
That's Banba Ban. (different manga)
Anyway, that's the story.
Wow, hadn't heard that before.
Well anyways, maybe we can talk again another time.
Yeah we'd like to hear some more stories.
I'd like to hear a story from Matsumoto-san.
Momotaro
"Momotaro"
Momotaro, born from a peach, is raised by an old man and woman, before leaving for the Demon Island....
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
So.....what was it like?
During your early childhood?
Well....
...I don't really think this story is suitable for television
Just tell it to us then.
That's right.
Well, I actually....wasn't even born at a hospital.
There was no midwife either.
So you were born at home?
Yeah, well kinda. Nowadays you'd
call it a....cesarean birth.
But it was a really crude version of a cesarean.
What do you mean by that?
Don't worry, you won't believe me.
C'mon! We all told you our stories.
Yeah, well....
....I was sort of protected by
a fruit like object...kind of.
Sorry, what?
What is he on?
Okay, if I say this you'll all find it a bit awkward, but basically
...I was something like an abandoned child.
I was shoved in a fruit like object and...
thrown in to a river.
Yeah, so I must have had some horrible parents.
Anyway, a random old lady just happened to pick that up and..
....also, thinking about it now...
...and I might sound mean but...
...she was living with an old man and
when she found me, the old lady was washing clothes in the river
so if you think about it, they were probably homeless or something.
Yeah, well.
That's a possibility.
Aren't...
fables a bit hard to do?
Gaki no Tsukai is so much fun!
Gaki-Gaki-kun!
Gari-Gari-kun!
Sorry to bring this up now but...
it has become clear that you will suffer a punishment game.
The staff are busy preparing at the moment.
It should begin very soon though.
What will I be doing?
Errr, you'll be going on an adventure for a while.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Should be alright if I apologise twice.
What do you mean, adventure?
You'll be returning around....February.
Don't worry, just go all out.
Aww hell no. This ain't Denpa Shonen.
It'll be okay. Don't worry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Just apologise three times.
I'd always wanted to say this during our talk sessions.
But I just always forgot to mention it.
I see.
It just so happens that I remembered clearly this time.
Oh, then let's hear it.
It's just about something that pisses me off.
Go ahead.
Well, if you don't know the number of a shop, you'd call
1042.
Yes. Can you find out that way?
Yeah it's a service where you can check numbers.
Oh okay cool.
Do you know how much you get charged, doing that?
Nope.
Surprisingly, almost everyone doesn't know this.
(Roughly 1,5$ in 2003)
You get charged 150 yen!!
Everyone needs to be more outraged by this, don't you think!?
Taken by some old hag!
And the last half is just a machine!
A hundred and fifty fuckin' yen, motherfucker!
Did you know that!?
Most people don't know! Y'all didn't know did you?
Call twice, thats 300 yen! Call three times, that's 450 yen!
Your cost doubles each time! Well, actually it doesn't, but...
This is what I think. So it has been 20 odd years since you created Downtown, yes?
Yes? Yes?
Yeah.
Over that time, you would've hit me around 40,000 times on the head.
Well, I don't know about that.
From around next year, I'm going to start charging you 150 yen each time.
I'm sorry.
Don't mean to disrespect.
How can we work then?
Mkay that's 100 yen.
I think I should be allowed to charge that!
Why?
I'm clearly developing injuries from it.
From being hit?
My sense of taste is fucking up a bit...
Bullshit, asshole!
I can taste sweetness, and sourness.
but not sweet-and-sour these days.
You don't even need to know that taste.
Fuck off mate. Sweet-and-sour is essential!
Who cares! You won't eat something that strange anyway!
Sweet-and-sour is important, surely!
Oh that's sweet....Oh that's sour.....
What the fuck is this?
It doesn't matter!
Of course it matters!
There aren't many foods with that flavour anyway!
Yeah there fucking is!
You won't eat much of it, I'm telling you!
You're so intent on convincing me that I won't eat something like that.
Shouldn't you be questioning why I'm charging you 150 yen or something?
150 yen is a large amount!
No one here even agrees with you.
Why does it cost so much to get an old hag to tell you a phone number?
Can't they just use machines the whole time if it switches over anyway?
I have no clue what you're saying.
So, you'd speak to a lady first, who says "Please hold a mament"
"Mament?"
....and it changes to a tape after that, right?
Yes it does. It's probably not a tape though.
It's not tape.
Oh, isn't it?
It's not tape! Surely it's something more computer-ish!?
She won't be like "Please hold" and go....
(Tape rewinding noise)
You were just doing the actions for recording a tape.
Well it would be strange to be tape, anyway!
Yeah, you know what I mean. There's a tape or it's connected to something, somewhere!
It's connected to a place where the voice comes from, right?
Like, you press a button and a voice starts speaking.
What are you imagining?
So there's a list of restaurants and bars in a certain area....
Oh okay, err maybe there is?
and, she'll choose a button from from there.
What!? There'd be shitloads then!
"Please hold for a moment".
What are you doing?
Using a pole or something to press the button.
I didn't mean they're on a wall or something!
You'd have to step back heaps to be able to see!
Don't worry we still have heaps of time to talk.
I'm not worried about that, I just thought we could have just let it be a tape, and moved on.
Keeping it plain and simple.
But there is no fucking tape in the first place.
What's with you? Repeating "Tape" like you're possessed.
What the fuck is tape, anyway?
Shut up!
Okay, that's 150 yen.