Are we rolling?
Well, not like I care...
There's no need for you to film any of this
You know, today...
I'm going to take divine retribution on those four
I'm talking about the "4 idiots" of Gaki no Tsukai
They're all helpless
I've been angry at them for so long
They've been making me angry for so many years!
That's why they'll all face
My divine retribution
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
TRANSLATION: SHION
TYPESET & QC: KEDOMAS
The one I can't forgive the most
between the four of them is Hamada, that idiot
The things he did to me to this very day...
Do you remember them all?
Let's go back to 20 years ago
It's Tanaka! Let's all gather!
This is from a show we did over 20 years ago
An episode called "It's Tanaka! Let's all gather!"
Just take a look at how guilty that idiot is
For this bit,
They had to snap at my poor host skills
So that the whole episode's atmosphere would be ruined
That's what the prank was all about
The small fry won!
I'm the champion?
Small fry won!
Eh? What about us?
Can we actually broadcast this on TV?
You think we should not?
Is this really the best you can do?
I'm being foul-mouthed, so...
Is that how you call that shit?!
Did you see that?
You see how he actually hit me?
Let's watch that one more time
Is that how you call that shit?!
We're sorry, we're sorry...
See?
That one actually hit me too
He grabbed my head
He grabbed my head so tightly
We were joking!
That was no joke
None of that was a joke
He clearly hit me with that racket
You know,
This was supposed to be a prank
So you gotta arrange it accordingly
But regardless,
Hamada, that idiot,
Hit me so hard with that goddamn racket!
And pulled my hair like this!
Hitting someone's head for a laugh is typical of Osaka's comedy
But to keep that style and bring it to Tokyo...
That's why he relies so much on violence
He's so quick at being violent, 'cause he thinks it's fun
And he can't just stop
In other words...
He's just a remnant of Osaka, isn't he?
But that's not all there is
In "Hot Blooded! Hamada's Cram"...
Hot-Blooded!
Hamada's Cram School!
It's a series with more episodes
And there's this section, the "non-stop club"...
In which we have to keep on moving until he tells us to stop
We basically have to keep on moving
Alright Tanaka, activate the turbo!
He ordered me to activate the "turbo" mode
And so I've started moving like crazy, but then...
This isn't very "turbo", is it?
This is how you break a person!
Engage in a 1vs1 turn-based war cry battle
If you shout the same war cry more than once, you lose
If you shout the same war cry twice, you lose       - I see
Komoto!
Tanaka!
At this point, I had an headache
My head was hurting like hell
Tanaka won!
Tanaka won!!
Go away, Komoto
Tanaka won, so he stays
- What's wrong?
What does that mean?
Tanaka's personal hell is just beginning
You won, you stay      - You heard him, Tanaka?
War cry battle, let's start from Tanaka
Come on!
In the end, Hamada...
Made me do the same shit
Countless times, over and over again
Tanaka!
Tanaka! Tanaka!
Tanaka won!
He's strong!
Tanaka won!!
Looking back at his Osaka's years...
He said "I only eat flour-based dishes"
I bet the flour is the only flavor he knows
So I don't think he knows the flavor of comedy
He's a flour-dish remnant, isn't he?
That Hamada, here in Tokyo
But this isn't the end of it
As you know,
There's also the "Hamada's aging trial"...
Second
Hamada Masatoshi's
Old! Old! Aging Trial
Second
Hamada Masatoshi's
Old! Old! Aging Trial
I'd like to start the second "Hamada's Aging Trial"
This was the second time
As more and more years go by,
Hamada gets more and more senile
This episode wanted to prove this theory
But it's not just this,
As you know, he cares a lot about Inomoto and the Dorians
But we have some evidence from his manager
This one really shocked me
He asks "what's my schedule for tomorrow?"
He exchanged messages with his manager
"For now, you have tomorrow off"
"toriaezu"
- That's his manager
But then, Hamada replied...
And he called his manager
With a very threatening tone in his voice
It should have been fine
"Hey! What do ya mean?!"
"Dorians have a day off? No one ever told me!"
"toriaezu"
He misread "for now" as "Dorians"
This really shocked me
"toriaezu"
How can you misread "for now" as "Dorians"?!
This really shows how he's aging
And the way he snapped, too...
He's starting to look like Eiji Bando
Ah, Mr. Bando?
He's just an angry old dude
That's how he's becoming
- Bando gets angry in the same way
But it's not something worth a laugh
It just doesn't feel right
Hamada himself believes
That if we make an episode out of this, we can laugh it away?
Like, "isn't it ok if we can just laugh at it?" -- He's getting it wrong
The same goes for our audience,
They think it's good as long as they can laugh at him
They're all delusional!
This show itself is misleading us all!
This isn't ok!
This is just promoting Hamada's senility!
He's a remnant of senility!
That's what Hamada is
The same can be said to Hamada's partner...
He's nice to himself, but severe with others
Check this out
In this episode
We entered this stage to perform a play
And we had to fall over
When the timing required us to do so
You have to fall over, but only once
Because that's the best comedic fall we can do
You're gonna learn a lot from this!
You can see his legs, right?
As you can see
He's wearing knee pads
The four of us had to fall over countless times
And we didn't wear any knee pads
On the other hand,
Matsumoto only fell down one time
But he asked the staff to wear knee pads
He's a remnant of knee pads, isn't he?
I mean...
This...
I can't...
Matsumoto always says that
"Comedy has to be objective to work", but...
We recently had this episode, the "Breathless Club"
Lactic Acid Frenzy!
Battle - Read "The Turtle and the Hare"!!
"Lactic Acid Franzy! Battle -
Read 'The Turtle and the Hare'!"
Matsumoto will face the challenge!
What?!
Basically,
It's a challenge about how much
one can read after producing lots of lactic acid
You can hold it! I'm starting to feel nervous
It's fine, it's fine
Here, stop, stop
I can't!
I can't run for that long!
Stop the tape for a sec
See?
He could run for only 26 seconds, right?
But you see, before doing this bit,
He said "I usually run a lot, I won't produce any lactic acid!"
"It won't tire me at all!"
"If I'm doing it, it's not going to be fun at all"
That's what he said to the staff
But what's this?!
He can't run at all!
He could only run for 26 seconds!
What's "objective" about you, huh?
But this isn't the only shocking footage
There's more right after it
From this point on
There were less than 10 seconds left
Look at the machine
You gotta be kidding me
Can this actually happen?
It stopped
Are you kidding me?!
The staff was so worried they plugged the whole thing off!
But it was too fast!
- See this? Stop!
Tell me, what is this?
He can't run at all
But because he was still trying
The staff got worried about him
And they decided...
To plug the machine off
You haven't even done it
I think it was, like, two years ago...
Matsumoto made a post on Twitter
"I'm worried about my juniors.
Matsumoto will move on."
But now I'm really worried about him
Why don't you move?
Why don't you move, move, run?
Hosei
That guy...
He started from Osaka
And being a "remnant of Osaka", he moved to Tokyo
Then he became a remnant of Tokyo and went back to Osaka
He's always dragging along old stuff with him
So what can I say about him?
That's beautiful
He became some sort of flawless embodiment of remnants
Every year, on the opening for our New Year Ceremony,
Yes! Yes! New Year!
If they ask me, "what's a remnant of Osaka?"
I'd reply "It's this"
"This is what a remnant of Osaka looks like"
He's repeating the same thing for years
Then we have Endo
This guy...
I mean, he---
I don't have much to say about him
Because he's got nothing
He's not even a "remnant"
He's just like a bell
A bell without a ball inside
In other words, a bell which makes no sound!
But this Endo here...
Has once found something which "made a sound"
Ogo! Ogo! Ogo!
This really made a sound
Louder!
If you missed this episode,
you can find it subbed on shionnotsukai.wordpress.com:
Life Of The “Ogoo” Endo Pteranodon
Ogooooo!
This is one of the things which made more sound for him
But regardless of it, this guy completely forgot about "Ogoo"
And didn't do it at all after that!
He just threw it away
And never tried to use it again, not even once
Even with his "Ogoo"...
He could have conquered the world...
I've talked a lot about them
But in the end
The one pulling the strings of those idiots
Is Hamada
Check this out
You have no idea what's going on, right?
That's because it's not ethical to broadcast this!
That's why all you see is a censored clip
And I've [censored]
Until it was destroyed!
But I bet all I just said got censored too, right?!
You have no way of knowing what's going on here!
What the hell is this for?!
But anyway,
Today I'm going to punish them all
To my heart's content
Without holding back
First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai!
Get a 100-hit Badminton combo
And win 1 million yen!
Tsukitei Hosei          Matsumoto Hitoshi         Hamada Masatoshi         Endo Shozo
Nice one!
1 million each?
No way
- Oh, it's shared
As you can see, Tanaka is absent today
- Ah, you're right...
Alright, it's finally revenge time
They think I didn't show up because I'm sick,
But now I'll reach them and I'll get my revenge
Alright guys, let's aim at that sweet million!
Yeah, let's do this
We gotta make it
Nice one, like this
Four!
Six!
Come on...
- I think it went too far
You shouldn't hit it with the edge, that's not how it works
Here!
I can't believe it!
- Sorry about that
Yamazaki could have gone for it, though...
But he didn't go at all
- It was Endo's
Let's start again
- We're doing great!
17...
- We can do this!
19!
Get it!
28!
That damned spot...
- I thought it was Endo's...
You both hesitated
Maybe we should call it
- I agree
Like, "I'm going!" or such
- Alright, let's go
One...
Two...
- Nice one!
Three...
Four!
Aw, crap!
Let's try again
Ready...
Hey...
Let's call it when it's ours
That's...
That's why I didn't go for it
I see...
But I think we can do this
- We should try it
Maybe we should aim lower?
I think Endo's quite good at it
Ow!
Let's just go
- Yep
Can you please...
Lower it a bit, would you?
Three!
Here...
Let's go
- Not much progress, huh?
It's because the distance is off--
I'm going
I'm going!
- Feel free to
You all ready?
One
Three...
Like this, kinda
Oh boy...
- Get ready
We can definitely do this
Let's not take any break
- Ok
Three...
- Shoot!
It went right through it, man
Two...
Yama-chan!
Yama-chan, what the?
Get a grip, man!
Can't be helped
It can happen, I know
Let's go...
- One!
Two...
Okay!
Hey, Shozo!
Come on, we can do this!
No way
- We're losing focus   - You're right
Maybe a 100 combo is too much for us?
Maybe...
How about, like, 51?
I agree, we should aim at that
One!
- If we can pull this off...
Here
Oh, no!
That's too high
Let's do this
One!
Two!
Three!
Go get it, Hamada!
Shoot, I'm sorry!
You're not getting a single ball...
- I'm sorry
What's wrong?
- I can't figure out the right distance
You're hitting it too softly
- But I just got that one, didn't I?
Let's go! One...
Oh, crap!
- I'm sorry about that...
Here it goes
Let's get it back, come on
Let's go
- One!
Oh, crap! I'm sorry!
Let's start again
Get ready...
One...
It's not even reaching me!
It's not?
Get it flying over here!
Come on
Counting on you!
- Alright, one...
Hamada, whenever you want!
- Oh, I'm sorry
Is everything alright?
I'm going
Hamada, please
What's going on? We can barely even hit it
Come on, man
Are you ok?
Let's go, Yama-chan
Alright, let's go
Come on, come on
Are you ready?
Come on, we don't have much time
We barely even made any progress
- That's right...
Yama-chan what's wrong? Did it slip?
Sorry, it just fell
Come on
One!
- Nice
Two-- hey, can you even see it?!
I can, sorry
- Come on, guys!
Let's do our best here
I can see it, but...
- Matsumoto!
We're counting on you
- It's there
It's right there
- Please!
He can't even pick it up!
Three!
Four!
It's yours, Hamada!
Five!
- Go get it!
Hamada!
Five!
- Go get it!
Your turn, Hamada
Let's go again
Come on
- Go, Hamada!
Come on, come on!
Let's go for that million!
- We're almost there
Whenever you want!
Here!
Sorry, sorry
Let's go already
Are you feeling tired?
- We are, actually
I see
Are you ok?
We can't even reach five
Not even five?!
Let's at least go for five
- That's strange...
What?
I think that's enough for them to realize
they should never do any of that again
My revenge was successful
We had fun!
Isn't it a bit hard to see?
- Yeah, I agree
I agree, I can't see that well myself
That's what makes it fun, huh?
One... two...
Three!
staff) Ok, we're done!
Thanks for today!
Tanaka, that fucking hurt!
When you slammed it on my face, it hurt so much!
I'm sorry
I've felt Tanaka's kindness
In the sweetness of this cream
BEFORE THE RECORDING
Excuse me?
Good morning
- Morning
This script...
Badmouths Osaka and Kansai so much, don't you think?
It hurts my heart, I swear
Can I actually pull this off?
Was that good?
I think so
It's just an old dude empty laugh
Today's director is Ishikawa
- Ishikawa, huh
It's his debut
If I don't perform well on this one...
He's going to hate me so much after this
Can't we even reach five?
- Not even five
The first throw was so strong!
I'm sorry for all of this
Well...
I think it went just fine, right?
What's this feeling?
For a moment I thought
This was going to be a reverse-prank
and Hamada would hurt me again
My heart was racing
I couldn't breathe easily
Was that the original plan?
No, the plan was...
For you to act and choose when to end it
Ah, so I could have done more?
I see... that's not what I heard before
I'm glad it worked out, now I see
Sorry for that
And thanks
Alright, thank you so much!
Translation & edit: Shion
Typesetting & QC: Kedomas
more episodes: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
twitter: @shionnotsukai
facebook: fb.com/shionnotsukai
If you feel like it, you can support this project
by donation @ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Or by becoming a patreon and gaining access
to schedules / softsubs before anyone else, on
patreon.com/shionnotsukai
m -47 -6 l 160 -6 l 160 93 l -47 93