Lastly is Matsumoto
What type of cooking is he particular with?
Has anyone fried gyoza?
I have
I think most have failed once or twice...
I have done it
Until now, I have never failed at frying gyoza!!
I would like all of you to watch me today
Let's observe him
I'm not saying to copy/follow me
My talent would come out truer,
if I used my own frying pan...
Isn't it bad that it's steaming?
From the frying pan?
You remove the pan from the burner?
Remove it from the burner?
The reason for taking it off the burner
There would be a time laps from the first and the 10th gyoza
I see
By doing so, you don't really need the high heat
That's really true
But from here, it's really the "Feel"
I like Tanaka earlier, you have to "Feel" it
To ensure the heat has gone through?
That's right
I have a little more cooking oil...
Is it medium cooking temperature?
Yes, it's medium temperature
Got it, medium heat
It should be crisp like this
Looks delicious
You look at it?
You could look at it!!
Followed by adding water, cover the pan and let it simmer-steam
Let's raise the heat
I see
You bring up the heat
I really didn't want to do this
The cover is transparent, but it's best to cover it completely
I see
Just by the sound
Gyoza is cooked by just the sound
I'm listening to the sound, it's saying "shuwa, shuwa"
When it's saying "shuwa, shuwa" the water content is high
I see
When it says, "chiri, chiri" it's ready
It's ready?
That's right
You know, the staff were suggesting to add cornstarch
To give it a more crisp texture
It's a waste of time
Waste?
There's no need for it!!
I want them to enjoy the gyoza even further!!
Enjoy it further?
Almost throw it in!!
Throw it in?
I want them to enjoy it in the "raw/pure" state
It can't be raw!
Not literally
After 2 minutes
Listen, "chiri, chiri"
Is it coming?
Yes, it's ready
See!
Okay it's ready
It's done!
Are you serious?
Is it done?
It does definitely looks good
Doesn't it look delicious?
Definitely look delicious
Looks really good!
Definitely looks tasty
Doesn't it look very tasty? It always turns out this way!
Beautifully done
It always turns out this way!!
You getting carried away
But, normally
Isn't it 100% perfect?
Yes, the appearance, I will enjoy it
Tasting time
How is it?
It's delicious
Yeah, it's tasty, but others who fry gyoza
Isn't it all the same?
All right then!!
You try frying them!!
Calm down now
I'm not saying
Hamada will now challenge frying the gyoza
You don't even say a thing
It's not hot enough
I didn't say anything earlier
Matsumoto-san you said
You should say something
Gyoza are always getting stuck together
You know
Your effort is "Half-heartedly" done
Now for the water
Hamada who has never fried gyoza is doing
it from memory of Matsumoto's visual earlier
Is the amount of water enough?
Yes
It should be enough
It was about 1/2 cup
I see
Waiting 2 minutes
The sound
The sound really
It really
Does it mean it's ready?
It's not making much noise, so it means it's ready
What do you think?
He covered it
It's not a funeral
Please make sure to look at it
Interrupted Announcement
Favorite personnel, the World Acclaimed Heipo
His history in All five parts
Will be on sale
All will be on sale, on March 5th
The gyoza Hamada had cooked for the first time
All right, it's done
Here you go
You've seen these before?
Please look at this
There are this type
I'm talking about these
There are these type
Then eat it!
You see, they are just normal
It's really not the same!
What's so different?
Hamada's Gyoza
Matsumoto's Gyoza
Then please just eat them
I'll eat them, I think they're tasty
Delicious!!
Don't lie!
The burnt part is good?
Isn't it bitter?
It must be definitely bitter
If it's burnt
It's delicious!
There is no problem
What's wrong?
The outer layer is powdery
The outer layer is a bit hard
Right
It's normal, just regular, it's alright, it all tastes the same
There is a difference
It's a "Bad" gaki = kid's prank...
It was a "Bad" kids's comment...
You too ate my gyoza, but picking on the water content, etc...
You really showed the bad brat's side...
Hamada thinks he's really better