First time ever on Gaki no Tsuaki ya Arahende:
Gaburi Chicken Food Marathon - 100,000 yen prize - Tokyo 20 store challenge!
I just wanna say; Every time, I actually try to reach the goal,
Yes that's true
But these two "Lady Boys"
Nah, last time it was Yama-chan
Yes, you couldn't eat anymore
Since you 5 can't do it, Fujiwara is joining you
This time you should make it to 20 stores
This time, the Food Marathon is hosted at;
Gaburi Chicken! With their specialty bone-in chicken, popular with young people and salarymen
The rule; They must eat one Hinadori (chick) and Oyadori (hen) bone-in piece
As well, 2 people must cooperate to finish 1 of the 6 fried chicken items
The key to victory will be how the 100g of fried chicken are shared between the 2 people
2 people?
- Yes, 2 people
So for sure we'll get this and that, or that and this
Can we modify the rules a bit?
These Lady Boys are already done for
It's not my fault I'm a Lady Boy!
First, they decide the fried chicken dishes for each member
So if Hosei-san gets Neck, he has to eat Neck whenever it's his turn
I just wanna say, if I keep getting eating Gizzard I think I might die
So this draw really matters then?
Yes, it decides what you eat
Toritoro?
Hamada gets the part between the wing and the neck,
The juicy Toritoro!
Those guys just went "Ohh!"
I do know this,
The Toritoro is a pain in the ass
Alright that's it, that's it we're done
Next, Matsumoto
Matsumoto draws...
The neck!
How is the neck?
The neck meat is taken from the neck! The texture is it's special point
And I've heard about the neck as well,
It's a pain in the ass compared to the Toritoro
Really? Neck is like that?
Next is Hosei
If it's not Breast I can't do it
I think not, eating breast all the time, it's gonna mess you up
But still Breast is the easiest to eat. Here I go
Yes! I won!
Hosei gets the healthy breasts he was asking for
And Endo gets the Gizzard, distinctive for it's mouth feel
This is dangerous!
Tanaka draws chicken wing flats.
Chicken wing flats.
Fujiwara gets boneless thigh
And with their selections set, they choose who eats fried chicken at the first store
The first person,
Alright, flip,
Matsumoto-san!
He was the one who flipped it
The first person is Matsumoto-san,
Next, the 2nd person
Typset & Timed by GakiDave
Translated by senor_wristband
The 6 head towards Shimbashi
When was the last time you ate nothing?
I had one bread today
When?
In the morning
How the hell am I supposed to know when you woke up?!
The Old Man who Snapped
I'm right aren't I? I don't know what time that is
But, it was around 9:00 I think
You've eaten nothing but 1 bread at 9?
Because of this project
What kind of bread?
It was a "Lettuce Dog"
What kind of bullshit bread is that?!
What is a "Lettuce Dog"?
This way, please.
They arrive at the first store in Shimbashi
So it's about that size
This is the first time for everyone here
This is the hinadori, and this is oyadori
Looks delicious
First they enjoy Gaburi's special bone-in fried chicken
The oyadori (hen)\ has a firmer bite, and the flavour spreads in your mouth as you chew
And the Hinadori (chick) is very soft and juicy!
This is a popular menu item that lets you enjoy both flavours!
Woah, looks delicious
Bon appetit!
It's so tender
Please, dig in
It has a strong flavour
The oyadori right?
It's great
The bone-in chicken is gone in a flash!
Next is Matsumoto and Hamada's fried chicken
Toritori and Neck right?
That's quite a lot, that's why I told you,
If we keep getting this we're gonna die!
Eh, I'm finishing this by myself?
Yes, it became your responsibility
If you have to keep that up for 3 stores,
Hold on, we can't redecide the dishes half-way through?
Exactly, you keep the same dish until the end
Cause it's your responsibility
It is delicious, but,
The greasiness is a bit, well ..., alright I guess
It's only the first store
They didn't suffer at all
Hamada-san, that's the face you make at the 10th store
He looks stressed
That's the face of anguish
100 grams of fried chicken...
It may be too much for the 55 year old DownTown\
You know Salarymen and the like, after a hard day's work,
They eat this while watching TV. That's the kind of dish this is.
This is not something a single comedian eats by himself!!
This is gonna take some time
There's 20 stores after all
Let's move on already!
You ass...
You're all still hungry right?
We're still hungry!
This enemy is stronger than I thought
Hamada-san is finished eating
Store 1 cleared!
With that, they choose the fried chicken eaters for next time
So we choose the 4 SAFE people first?
Safe people first
Endo-san safe!
Amazing, Matsumoto-san!
Matsumoto safe!
Please!
Tanaka safe!
"Hosei"! "Hosei"!
Oh, Fujiwara safe!
Which means ...
It's Hamada-san, and Hosei-san
The 2 Lady Boys
Wow, we might end on the 2nd store for the first time
For the second store, Hamada and Hosei are responsible for the fried chicken
There's 19 stores left,
However...
No, I think,
This is dangerous
This is a bit risky, we need to change the rules
They're tender, but each piece is so huge
There were a lot of pieces
This is hardy blood
A continuous stream of complaints!
And one more worry
It's totally possible to get chosen 3 times in a row
That's true, that could happen
I'm trying my best, but I have a limit
I'm really sorry, but
Yoshinobu-san got it 3 times in a row (in the simulation)
But he made it to 11 stores
That's just cause his hostess was watching. Of course he'll push himself.
He took his hostess to a location scout?
Of course! They're soulmates, him and his hostess
Gabburi Chicken marathon - The 2nd store is in Akasaka
This is the Oyadori
I can totally finish this
Go ahead
So breast, and toritoro
Thank you
The breast is for Hosei-san
That looks really good
I kinda want some
Mmm, it's very soft
Nobody is even looking at Hamada-san
That looks really good
Hamada just went "unnnh" - that's not good.
Can we ask, what's the condition of your stomach?
I'm 80% full
It's still only the second store
Zaki-san is finished his breasts
It was easy to eat. It was tasty.
Who would eat 8 of these massive pieces?
I wouldn't eat that normally
Exactly right?
So I'm gonna take my time. I've never eaten 8 pieces before
Then Hamada as well
2nd store cleared
Fried chicken selection for the 3rd store
The first card, the first person is;
Hosei gets the breast!
Well, at least-
No not "at least"! This is bullshit!
What happened all of a sudden?
This the second time in a row!
TN: I think Hosei's chances are actually (1/6)*(1/5) = 1/30
Well that's bound to happen, you have a 1/3 chance!
And the other person,
Tanaka-san, and his wing flats
The first wings of the day
The battle has only just started
Are there any vegetables?
Ah, there's a lot on the side menu
Like onion slices
But I have to pay for this myself right?
You can get the person who gives up to pay for it
I see, that makes sense
I see. I can order anything then
Since I'm definitely not gonna give up
It's fine isn't it?
In a quiet voice he said "It's  fine isn't it?"
I don't care if he orders anything
Yes, just order whatever you want
I'll get Hamada to pay for this
The toppings and vegetables are another specialty of Gaburi
The 3rd store is in Shinjiku 2-chome
Merry Gaburi-masu!
(Note: Matsumoto is reading the store's advertisement which reads \n"Merry Gaburi-masu" - a play on "Merry Christmas.")
It said "Merry Gaburi-masu"
The oyadori?
Merry Gaburi-mas!
And the Hinadori
That worker really hated that
"Merry Gaburi-masu"
This much Oya?
There's quite a lot of this
It's perfect for take-out
Ah there it is, thank you!
The wing flats?
They're huge!
And Hosei-san's consecutive breasts
It's mostly bone!
I think that's rude to the store
Maybe he's pregnant
These wing flats are 100g including the bone
And then,
I think this guy might cheat a bit, we should pay attention
No there's no way
Look look at that
This?
There's a bit there
Of course, of course
And there too
The checks are strict
TN: Also known as "Ulnar collateral ligament reconstruction"
This Tommy John Surgery location
That's finished there isn't it?
No way, that part needs to be surgically removed
That too?
Meanwhile, Hosei finishes his consecutive breasts
Are you lying?
I'm done too
Hold on, everyone is checking it first. How is it?
C'mon cut it out, stop checking my wings
But that part,
C'mon!
Isn't that meat there?
That's not meat
Really?
It's the bone
Hold on, stop bringing the camera closer
Cut it out
This is how much everyone has eaten after the 3rd store
Hamada and Hosei have already eaten 440g!
And the next fried chicken eaters?
The first person,
Ah, Fujiwara
Here I go
Again!
You got it consecutively!
We did say that before, it's bound to be consecutive!
The 4th store, in Kabukicho
What was that? Are you alright? You tripped, are you alright?
There's no step here right? But he tripped on that
It's just the colour that's different, he thought it was a step!
Are you alright?
That's no good
Hinadori
She said it was "Hina", but this is "Oya"
There's no need for that face
This is so much
Mmmhmm!!
TN: Tanaka is not using honorifics for his senior Hamada
What the hell do you mean "Mmmhmm"?
That was out of line
No that's not right, that "Mmmhmm" was not right!
The fried chicken is Tanaka's 2 wings and Fujiwara's boneless thigh
Itadakimasu.
Is it better than the Oyadori?
It's as tender as the Hinadori
Fujiwara enjoys the 7 time winner of the Fried Chicken Grand Prix
And Tanaka's wings?
Can we check your wings?
How is the wing check?
Stop, move out of the way. That's meat isn't?
It's hard to judge the wings
Yes, it's hard
You need eat enough so that we don't say anything
They might be bones, but you need to eat them like they're meat
He gets over the strict check
Look at that, that's meat
Tanaka manages to finish
Ok ok ok, I'm sorry!
The 5th fried chicken eater;
So the first person to eat fried chicken,
This is dangerous
Your third time
Seriously?
He sounded like a trapped chicken
And the next person,
The Lady Boys once again
This is amazing!
This is the 3rd time for both of you right?
Gaburi Chicken Marathon - This is the current total
Hamada and Hosei have passed 520g. What will happen?
I think the card draws are a fantastic idea
You've changed your opinion from the start
That's true, I got it first. But I haven't eaten in a while
I'm starting to miss the neck
I want some neck. I want neck more than I want a necklace.
That wasn't funny at all
Well of course, if we start laughing at stuff like that...
Yes, I understand too
Once I start making neck puns,
I will quit comedy
What should we get for the topping? Something Japanese?
Of course. Ponzu
You should've gotten it with your breasts!
I want to try it
It will be a real pain in the NECK if we can't get a topping for neck
He said it
God that was painful
No, that's not good
The 5th store, Takadanobaba
Here too they start with the bone-in chicken
It wasn't this firm before
I'm getting used to the Oya
Yes, you start to feel it by the 5th store
But you've gotten pretty used to it
This is the 7th store I think
It's the fifth one!
Man this is some weird editing you did here
Editing?
The problem starts with this
Hamada and Hosei's 3rd serving!
Oh man my back hurts
Do you want some topping?
Doing that will slow us down, let's just get through them
I just can't eat anymore
Certainly, I understand
He means just for now
These 2 aren't moving their chopsticks
He's such an old man
We're just waiting on the breasts now. The Lady Boys™
And with that,
Hamada-san is on his 10th piece of chicken
It's the 11th isn't it
He's on his 11th, wow
This ADULT. This 50+ man is on his 11th piece
Including the initial bone-in chicken, Hamada-san and Hosei-san are at 700g
They struggle, but manage to get the chicken in their mouths
Such small bites!
Just eat the whole thing already
I think we're in danger
Will the next card draw be alright?
And then Hamada as well
He passed on!
"Passed on"?
It's cause we thought you died
The fierce battle at Gaburi chicken continues ... What will the result be?
Next time;
Gaburi Chicken Maratathon - Finale!
An uncertainty lingers
What awaits the 6?
And then, a sudden change for a man
Oh shit oh shit
Please, not that
I can't eat anymore...
Is that a Give Up?