First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!
Appreciation meeting for "The Bus Hijacker Returns" starring Endo!
Thank you
Isn't it... a bit cold here?
I thought the coldness was from the AC
But it's coming from the screen...
It's the AC
The AC
Should come from here
No way it's from the screen
Fujiwara Kazuhiro, Imoto Takafumi, Endo Shozo, Tsukitei Hosei, Tanaka Naoki
note: from left to right, up to down: Matsumoto Hitoshi, Hamada Masatoshi
The movie is not on yet
It hasn't even started yet!
There's nothing here
No way
After all it's not a lame movie, right?
note: "cold" and "lame" are both "samui" in japanese
Yeah, not lame at all
Oh, is that so
The movie "The Bus Hijacker Returns" starring Endo
Has been released this year (2017) in July!
But there's a certain reason for why this movie was made...
I actually felt like taking part on it
For real?
For real
You know
Before this movie I worked on
Right
A previous project (Busjack)
But it didn't really sell good at all
But we got to joke about it on No-Laughing Prison
Right
lower screen: The first solo-movie Endo starred in, "Busjack" was revealed to be the 40805th movie on Amazon DVD popularity ranking
And its popularity suddenly rose up
It was funny so it got popular, I see
And then the two of you told me
That it would be nice to have a sequel
So it felt like I had to make a "return"
We talked about this on a costume talk
Yes
Yeah, on September, last year
lower screen: The day after Downtown stated they would take part on a possible sequel, "The Bus Hijacker Return" 's production was decided
I really thought about taking part in it
On the other hand
Hamada-san was more like
"Enough of that crap"
He's so rude
I haven't said such things
He said something about it being pointless
After all if we are together we're Downtown
Even if we're attending a funeral, we want to act as Downtown
Anyway, it became a big topic on the internet
Just look at this
This is an article from Yahoo news
"Even though it's Endo's movie premiere, the theater seats are empty"
"A resentful complaint from Downtown"
What does it mean?
Now that you've seen this article, take a look
At what Matsumoto recently tweeted
"I'm sorry Endo, my stomach hurts"
What do you mean with that?
Well, first of all I'm feeling sorry for it
The fact is... it was too funny
I thought "why is it funny?" and felt sorry for him
There was also... that guy, Onigiri
Yes
That huge Yoshimoto comedian
He actually paid to go see your movie
And he was like "man, that was really hilarious!"
Really?
Yeah he said it
And he was like "Matsumoto-san please go see it!"
In the end I didn't go, though...
He invited you
That's weird
Lots of people liked it
Of course
By the way, here's the cast chart
It's just like that
Endo-san plays Noboru Komiya
That's the main role
His colleague is Kurosawa from Morisanchu
Yes
And his younger colleague is Iwao-san
There's also Honkon-san playing
A Yakuza boss
Actually the role
Ozawa-san is playing
Was planned for Matsumoto-san
Oh? Was it not Hamada?
No, it was you Matsumoto-san
The mysterious man is played by Jimmy-san
And this role was supposed to be Hamada's
Why is that?
You are similar comedians
I just agreed to him!
They are similar, yes
If you look it up on the GPS their field of activity
Is pretty much the same
Is it?
By the way, we also have the producer Ohta-san, today
Really!?
Thanks for having me
text: "The Bus Hijacker Returns" 's director: Ohta Masayuki
Nice to meet you
Thanks for coming
How dare you came here!?
Please don't mind him
It looks like the reviews aren't really praising it
Is that so?
Yeah, it was a flop
Really?
Even after all that motion?
What could the reason be?
I had this conversation with members of the staff too
And they agreed that Endo's acting is kind of...
Are you for real?
Yeah...
Was it my acting?
Was it that bad?
You should have know that from the first movie...
So for example what is it? The acting?
Yes they said it was kinda...
Unskilled
note: "kusai" means "smelly", but it also means "unskilled", "poor" figuratively
Unskilled?
Smelly?
His acting smelled?
I've talked about this
To Ohta-san too
Yes
As you watch the movie and you think Endo's acting is unskilled
You can press the "that smells!" button under your hand
You can press it every time
If they feel like Endo's performance is "smelly", they'll push the button
Screening Rules
When the movie ends, the number of "it smells" will be counted
You think his acting is poor
We're going to watch it that way?
I mean, the whole "it smells" thing
That's what the producer said!
You sure it's okay? It's not a good thing
Nah it's okay
Is it ok?
It's ok...?
It's fine, it's fine
Translation & Notes by Shion
Typesetting & Quality Check by Tiny_Paw
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
This is something
Aren't we too close?     - Yeah
note: on their button / button sound "kusa-" ("it stinks" / "it sucks")
What's going on!?
Quick
He made someone angry
Nothing happened yet
How can there be a bus tour
guide who suffers car sickness?!
I'm terribly sorry
Which was your plan this time, huh?
It's Asakusa Mystery Tours
"Approaching Shitamachi's Mysteries"
What is that? Asakusa Mystery Tours?
You're part of the route
That's the problem!
That happened just before!
I'm sorry
You're too quick...
You're ruining everything, everything!
Is it that bad?
It sucks
It's really high-paced
Your acting as you're being scolded sucks
Aren't you exaggerating?
That...
You better get rid of that frown you're making!
No sorry it's that my tooth hurts
Go to a dentist then!!
[movie] I did but I---
This is actually linked to the first movie
His tooth hurts only here
[movie] I couldn't fix it!
Komiya, I'm done with you
Komiya...
You're fired
No way!
No, president!
Can't you just give him one last chance?
He'd only make more mistakes
It's fine, I say!
You can show him, right Komiya-san?
...Mh-mh
Please, president Yamai!
Was it my "mh-mh" just now?
Alright
President!
But this really is your last chance
Fail this one and you're fired
Why that?
Kurosawa is pretty good!
Yeah she's good
Come on, Hanako-chan
It's fine, really
But you're always...
Doing so much for me
If you weren't there I'd be fired everyday!
Damn guys... your pace for pressing the "it sucks" button sure is fast!
I think the next tour plan is perfect for you, Komiya-san
Which plan is it?
It's about having the passengers
Escape from an hijacked bus!
Huh? Is that...?
Yes... It's Busjack!!
"THE BUS HIJACKER RETURNS"
Right from the beginning...
Excuse me, this time--
By the way, that guy is Suga-san's son
Suga Kenji
They look alike!
You're right
It won't be a windy day
It's the transmitter
Man, it's him
Few days ago it started acting up
They look a lot alike
Yeah they really look the same
Oh, that seems like it
His nose is the exact same as Suga's
Isn't the bus just acting weird?
You can't be sure about it
Huh?
He doesn't suck at all
He's going to aim at the next bus with passengers
I'm talking about Sanada-san
...Sanada-san?
Yes, this person
It's just a picture
He's an international terrorist
Isn't that helping too much?
So, it's a heat-induced bomb
Mainly made of RDX
Did that one really suck?
So... what I should do
Is to hijack... that bus!
It stinks (kusai) even with the air freshener
It's really there
The air freshener...
I'll hijack that bus
His smelly acting doesn't want to lose to the air freshener
But he's not really a bus hijacker, right?
Yes, it's just his role
Oh, I see--- oh, here he is
This guy was supposed to be Matsumoto-san
Would have been good
Ya have somethin' to say?
N-no, I don't, I-I'm sorry!
We all pressed it
This one should have been Hamada-san
We had a similar scene
Yes, I see
I'm sorry
My contacts--!
What's wrong?
My contacts!
Jimmy is 100% ad-lib on this
Is that so?
Yes     - Wow
You're too close
I'll take care of it
Sorry
Wait here!
Bro! Over there!
Huh?
Excuse me
Yes?
Are you Sanada-san?
Ohh... you're the guys from the job?
...Yes?
You've been employed
To help me, right?
Yeah, that's it
Alright, there's no time:
Let's hurry!
Got it!
Guys from the job...?
I'm just walking...
[movie] Sorry I'm late
I'm glad you made it in time
Huh?
I've never seen that tour guide before...
Komiya-san sure is late...
This bus is the one
This one?
I should have actually got in
Yes
This is a Hagihara bus
I see, misunderstandings
Yes
This is a Ogiwara bus ticket, right?
note: Hagihara (萩原) and Ogiwara (荻原) are written with 2 similar kanjis (萩 & 荻)
The other tour is the "Love Mystery Tour"
Lots of people usually get it wrong
Komiya, our protagonist,
Ends up boarding the wrong bus
I don't have the ticket, can I pay in cash?
The passengers board holding various expectations
And then the bus departs
Alright then, it's going to be a short time
But I'd like to have you share it by introducing yourselves
You over there, if you please
Uh... err... name's Kaneko--
W-woah! Look, bro!
What the-?
Sanada-san! It's Sanada-san!
What's wrong?
How is he looking?
His face-...
Shall we begin?
Huh?
I think he said we should begin
The hell is that, really
This really sucks
Don't move!
Oh, here we are! It's starting
We're here
Stay still
Starting from now
I'm hijacking this bus!
What is-
Don't move!
This is bad
I'm gonna kill you if you move!
Busjack?!
He's acting accordingly to a memorized script, that's the setting
Yes
I see...
So it's like a play within the play
Exactly
If you move even an inch away from me...
I'll make the whole bus blow away!
Joichi...
Don't try to get
Maruo Sanada mad
You have no idea what he could be thinking
When the moment arrives...
He'll use the bomb you've made...
And boom
It's not supposed to be a funny scene
Seriously, it's not supposed to be funny
And just as we-
His expression is so unnatural!
It feels like he's putting that on for the occasion
Got it? Don't you dare provocate him
He became Joji Shimaki
note: actor & comedian
Don't ever try to
Excuse me
What?
Is it true you've placed a bomb on the bus?
It's true
Which type of bomb is it?
Type of bomb..?
Nishiyama-kun...
It has been bugging me since before...
But doesn't the face of that man seem familiar?
Huh?
I mean... doesn't he look like that terrorist named Sanada
Gono-san showed us before?
H-he's real! That man is a real terrorist!
Wha-!?
The one behind that incident in Kansai...
Are you for real?
A terrorist?
I never thought I'd meet the real deal
Come on, even there?
Komiya gets mistaken for a real bus hijacker from everyone
And the story moves on
Got it? You just have to do what you're told to
Your purpose? What is it?
You'll get to know it soon
He's balding up
Here comes!
Be sure to act like a policeman!
Hello?
Is this the police?
Is that you Sanada?
Itsyouisntit?
What?!
And you're...?
"Itsyouisntit"
I'm the police superintendent Yanagita
It should have been "It's you, isn't it?"
Itsyouisntit~
This time it's up to me
To deal with the negotiations
Is that so? Glad to hear that
Bro! It's the police!
What the hell is he thinking?!
Come on! I wasn't even facing the camera!
I've taken control of this bus as I planned
There's a bomb set on it
And I have all their lives
Come on
In my own hands
Stop with this foolish act! Release them at once!
I'm really hating this "it sucks" SFX!
Enough!
The passengers...
They're safe, aren't they?
They surely are
At least for now
Was that combo really necessary?
After the break, a rapid development! Repeating "it sucks"!
It really started to suck bad when ??? kicked in
Hey!!
What the-!
Piece of shit!
Don't move!
And keep on driving this thing!
What the...?
Bro!!
Are you ok?
It really started to suck bad when the tension kicked in
Yeah, that's the tension scene
I see that
That's a new level of smelliness
You got that wrong
I'm not a policeman
I'm the same as you
The same?
What's going on?
The same? You mean...
A bus hijacker?!
Sanada-san
Yes?
I never thought I'd be able to meet you
Huh?
You didn't check my body and I got away with it
You got away?
I'm talking about this
I-is that!?
There's another bus hijacker aboard!
The real bus hijacker appears
And the real trouble starts for Komiya
Just stop this, Gono-san
Whaddya want?
Why are you doing this?
You're not someone who'd do such things!
Come on, I'm just there
That sucks too?
What are you talking about?
What do you know about me?
I just do!
Matsumoto-san I'm just--
'Cause I've taken part in a bus tour
You've been doing before!
I'm just standing there! Does that suck too?
I...
I'm just popping out from the left background, how can that suck?
When I first took part on a tour like this
That's 'cause you're on screen
I wasn't the only one who was left alone
He has already given up
And I really felt so down
He's hiding behind her ribbon
But then you, the tour guide...
Thinking about it, I've heard it before...
Someone here got fired because he caused a problem...
A problem?
That's not like it
I was blamed for something I didn't do
And was forced to leave my job against my will!
In the end it was all for nothing
There's no way you can possibly know how I feel!
I do
That felt weird even for me
I feel you
I know how it feels
When nothing goes well
No matter what you do
It's the same for me!
For you? Sanada-san?
But see...
What you're doing is wrong
Huh?
Things that don't go well...
Or things which don't make any sense...
I know they exist, but that's wrong!
I want to stop you
Before you commit a crime!
With Komiya's desperate persuasion
The bus hijacker gives up on his plan
What about you?
Huh?
Aren't there people grieving for you out there?
Huh? Wha-
She's the heroine
Is he in love?
She's the real heroine
Yeah she kinda likes him
I've always
#@"%!£$€*\=!
%§°#;&%!\)=
I can't hear anything at all!!
With all this button sounds
This is the good part!
Is that so? Ok ok
At least hear the lines
Look at his shoulders
Yes... more than anyone
Even my shoulders now?
How can my shoulders be a problem?
Komiya-kun...
I see, they're hearing him
Yes, that's right
These people
Gave me a chance
That's why
I had to do this hijack thing
Because I respect them
Is he judging them?
I have to do this!
No no, listen
We're almost there
Sit down
Alright
Drive us back from where we set off
Ok, count on me!
Isn't that...?
Huh?
Oh, he's here, he's here!
What is...?
Get away
Kashira!
Boss?
I got your call
What a great surprise
...Or is it?
Joichi...
This man is not Sanada
What?
I made a mistake
The current Sanada
Got a plastic surgery and changed his face
Here's a picture of him
I'm astonished
Who the hell are you?
I am... Sanada!
Don't fuck with me!
I am Sanada
I know you're not him!
I am...
Whatcha tryna say!?
Why are ya trying to act like one of us?
Stop! Please stop it
That's enough
Calm down
You-- are you trying to boss me around?
Shige!
Quit it
He's just a public safety employee
As long as there's a criminal
I can't just let it go by
That's just it
Shige...
#@&£%!=§
I can't hear a single line!
Coming after, it's finally time for the climax!
Man, that was my last chance...
And I've failed
We're almost there
Don't say that
Isn't that right guys?
It was the best thrilling tour
We've ever experienced!
But...
Well, I had fun!
We could experience something unusual!
And that's all thanks to Komiya-san
You guys...
It's not over yet
All of you... thank you!
Hey, no need to
That's not really yakuza!
Listen to me: I am Sanada
Come on
I'm about to change my plan
Which is now to release
All of my hostages!
You're free, everybody!
They're pressing it accordingly to the clapping
Your friends are here!
Eh?
Please go, Komiya-san
What the hell is this?
Man, this is amazing
So in the end Kurosawa..?
Yeah, he can reach her
This is incredible
Hanako-chan!
How was it?
I did the bus hijacking tour
You did?
And I was able to save everyone
All thanks to you
You did it with your own strength
That's because you were there
Until the very end
@#%&)(\-
I can't hear a goddamn line
It's way too noisy in here
This is the last part, I promise, it's almost over
Aaaaaaaah!!
What's wrong Yanagita-kun?
Is something wrong?
Look at that
...What does it mean?
It's over now, we're done
As long as you're on screen
You press it even if only my name is showing?
Come on!
Next: total of pressed buttons & a word from Endo!
Matsumoto-san, opinions?
I think that everyone around him
Seem to have given their best at it
I think that
Doesn't really apply to Endo or Honkon-san, though
To be honest I couldn't hear a single line from Honkon-san
He was on screen too much
Too much?
He sucked pretty hard
Now it's finally time to find out
How many times you've pressed the "it sucks" button
Let's show the results
Here
Your summed up total counts 2278 times
Housei-san pressed it the most
I really enjoyed this, to be honest
I'd love to have an "it sucks" button like that in theaters
It would be something new, I think so too
I agree, it's great
Have this, Endo
Sorry, and thanks
Is that..?
A promotion from our protagonist Endo
It will be nice if you promote it
Like, talking about why it's worth watching
Yeah, really... everybody, we gave our best to film this
And worked for three days straight
Translation & Notes by Shion
And we got it screened on theaters too
Typesetting & Quality Check by Tiny_Paw
So if you wish to see more in the future
Please, consider buying this
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
It's out on September the 1st! Thank you!
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Want to support my translations? Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Which was this movie's signature phrase?
When I recognize my role as Sanada
Even though I'm Komiya and I've been mistaken
After everyone realizes that, I say "I'll lead this bus"
Was that part there?
Of course it was
You were just pressing too much
You didn't even notice
There was, I promise
We were too shocked