The First Annual Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende, Chiki Chiki
I am the one who understands him the best!
At any rate, this item suits you right? Championship!
Choshu Riki version~!!
Matsumoto-san, it's this theme again
It has been a while though
The regular theme with Gaki members buying items that they think will suit the guest
This is the theme where Tanaka shines
Or more like making himself shine
Tanaka ranked last for 9 items over the past 12 rounds
No, that's not true
Well, I bet he's doing it on purpose though
No I'm not, not at all
It's fine, you can do it on purpose
But don't go too far, so that the audience notices it
They must have noticed it
No they didn't notice it...
I mean I'm not doing it on purpose
Subbed by Appieopie, more episodes at
www.laughseejapan.com/user/18797
For today's guest...
-He's a big guy
-Yes, he is
It was difficult to find things for his size
And he has long hair right?
There's not much people with long hair and large in size
It was difficult
Let's welcome today's guest
Welcome Choshu Riki-san
Nice to meet you
The legend of Japan's professional wrestling, Choshu Riki
Gaki members will buy tops and items that suit him,
The former strongest wrestler that the mere mention of his name was enough to silence a naughty child
Do you usually wear like this?
No, I don't
-You don't?
-Not at all
They forced me to wear this
-It's a T-shirt of Choshu Riki right?
-Yeah it is
This is embarrassing
Is there any meaning for this T-shirt?
I have no idea too
Seriously?
That illustration was obvious
The members went to buy items that suit Choshu Riki beforehand
What is your impression of Choshu-san, Hamada-san?
Well, he must be a wild person right?
He is tall and stout even at his age
So I'll choose something that suits a strong old man
-This seems to be strong right?
-Which one?
No, no way
This is not about being strong dude
This is a weapon
It's really heavy
I have no idea whether this is for aunt or uncle
These leather jackets seem to suit him too
Just let him wear something like this around his neck
At the same time, for Endo
Chono-san right...
It's Choshu-san
Not Chono-san, I mean Choshu-san
This one is perfect for hat lovers
This is so cute
This looks like President Trump's cap though
I think Pokemon could work too
Pokemon should work
-So we're at the shop for plus-size clothings?
-Yes, we are
Because I thought normal-size clothings won't fit Choshu-san
So I decided to go straight to this shop with various fashionable plus-size clothes
What is your impression of Choshu-san, Tanaka-san?
Maybe this sound a bit impolite
But I think that he is a very charming person
So I want to choose something that can show the charming part of him
Maybe something like this?
With pigs?
Nope, he may feel like being looked down upon
-Is this a T-shirt?
-Yes it is a T-shirt
Are you joking?
This is a T-shirt?
Well, although I have no idea at all
I'll go for something with Japanese style
This one is common, but it must look cool on him
He can wear this at dressing rooms
This looks good too
Housei got hyped up with his favorite Japanese style clothes, and continues to try them on
This is cool
He can just tighten the Kimono belt, and shout "Let's go guys"
What kind of illustrations do you think suits Choshu-san?
Well, Choshu-san never crossed my mind, so...
To find something that suits Choshu-san,
Matsumoto is heading towards...
Could there be anything that suits Choshu-san here?
Well, I don't know too
But this seems to be good right?
This suits him right?
-I think this may suit him surprisingly well
-Well, yeah
Because his head is big
I just want to confirm this with you
According to the shop owner
This shop is targeting high school girls
Are you fine with that? Not mistaken?
Well...
Choshu-san is also their target isn't it?
The guest will take the item that ranks first
The item on last place will be paid by the member who chose it
Each of us will be presenting our item
-Please don't say anything like "this one is good"
-Yes, I understand
Tell us after everyone presents
Choshu-san should be angry with what he said just now
-He's looking down upon you
-No, no, no I didn't
Choshu-san teach him a lesson
Endo will be the first to present a top that suits Choshu-san
The item that I've bought is over there
Choshu-san please open it
Can I open it?
Yes, please open it
The act of opening a bag doesn't suits him though
-Looks like he is rummaging around the bag
-Yes, exactly
Can I take it out?
-It's a leopard print parka
-So it's a parka
Choshu-san would you mind trying it on?
You can open it with the front zipper
There's a zipper right?
Yes, there's a front zipper
It just hit him in the face right?
The hood just hit him in the face like "bang"
It fits him like a glove
This looks really cool
And suits him very well
Please look at yourself in the monitor, and rank it in your mind
You'll need to choose one at the end
Is it comfortable to wear?
It's made of nylon fabrics...
Choshu-san is not speaking at all
I can't speak about it right?
You can tell us things like "is it comfortable to wear"
Leopard print’s popularity has never gone away
It's the classic style type
So it's good to keep one in your closet
-So you can always wear it
-Yes
Do you like leopards?
Leopards?
Well, I don't dislike it
It's now Hamada's turn to present a top that suits Choshu-san
-This is a riding jacket
-I see
Is that an "oh" of happiness?
I wonder what it means
Well, I don't know whether Chono-san have this type of jacket as well
He is really not speaking at all
I was talking all the time, and yet Choshu-san never speaks
But I can't speak about it right?
It's because Hamada you've warned him too much
I have to warn him because he is an idiot
He can't wear it on his own
The size is too small isn't it?
It should be out if he can't even wear it himself right?
-It's fine
-It should be out already
But he looks like a cool old man now
*Tospo is the post box used to receive letters from the audience in Downtown DX
-He looks more like Tospo now
-Yes, he looks like Tospo*
The personification of Tospo
The next presenter is Housei
What is the Japanese style top that he chose?
I think Japanese style suits Choshu-san better
Instead of Western style
Please open it
What is this?
It's not even coming out from the bag
That's just because the bag is small
What is that?
You screwed it up
No, no, no way
Where are you supposed to wear this?
You seriously screwed up
-No way dude
-It fits perfectly
-Where are you supposed to wear this?
-Exactly
When are you supposed to wear this?
You can wear this anytime, anywhere, right?
-Where?
-Eh?
-Where can I go with this?
-Where can you wear this dude?
-You can even go to convenient stores with this
-No, no, no way
If he happens to wear that, others might think that he's here to warn people for holding a cigarette in the mouth*
*Choshu-san is wearing the cloth of "Megumi", a famous firefighter brigade during Edo period
That's so true
The next presenter is Matsumoto
Did he find any top that suits Choshu-san?
You guys are focusing too much on the wild part of Choshu-san
But he is indeed wild
Wild people tend to like things that are completely opposite
I'm confident about this
-Can I take this out?
-This sounds horrible
This is perfect for him
Oh my god, oh my god
What the heck is this?
I'm sure that this suits him
It's Tanaka-ish
Look at this
Oh my god, this is awful
This suits him perfectly right?
This must be...cute
Just having it is already cute
No way
His grandchild will treat him like an idiot
He'll get kicked by his grandchild
His grandchild will say "no way!" and kick him
-Saying like "I hate grandpa!"
-You're right
Choshu-san don't know how to unzip the zipper
How do I unzip this?
Just unzip it normally
This has two versions Choshu-san
Let's try this side first
-So cute
-No way
-That's super cute right?
-No, no way
The size doesn't fits
This is awful
-Super cute!!
-This is terrible
-This is super cute right?
-I told you this is terrible
This doesn't suits Choshu-san at all
That's super cute
The cloth is the only thing that is cute
Tanaka is the last presenter, what will happen?
-Is it fine for you to be the last presenter?
-Yes, no problem
I was thinking "that's wrong, that's wrong"
while watching everyone's item
Choshu-san gives me a charming and cute impression as well
This is absolutely terrible right?
What is this?
-It's a long knit
-Huh?
-The one that moms wear
-No it's not
It's not the one that moms wear
The one that moms wear after cooking curry in a hurry and head towards the theatre
Not the one that moms wear when in a hurry
-Is this men's clothes?
-Yes, men can wear this too
You can pull it to the bottom, because it's a long knit
What the heck is going on?
-You must be kidding right? That's awful!
-No, no, I'm not
There's this new trend of being "aggressively cute" right?
Help him fix it dude
-Is this the front
-Yes it is
I really want to show the cute part of Choshu-san
He looks like an aunt now dude!!
No, no, no he doesn't
Let's try to roll up the sleeves a bit
Tanaka that's not gonna help
What's wrong with you dude?
This kind of long knit is really popular among men
The trend is now to be "aggressively cute"
No way dude, I never saw any man wear this
What a look!
That's the mom at class observation day
Other students would say "your mom looks so powerful"
How long should the bottom part be?
You can wear it as an one-piece dress without pants
-One-piece dress?
-This is so wrong
I want him to look charming
He's a mom now dude
All that's left is to wear lipstick
Before Choshu-san tell us the ranking
He wants to confirm this desperately
Choshu-san please tell us the 2nd best top that you like
Is this really men's clothes?
-He finally speaks out
-That's so true
That being said, which one is the 2nd best top?
Thank god!
I knew it! It's cute right?
-The size is a bit small though
-Yes it is a bit small
But it feels good to wear it right?
Yes it feels good
I told you guys
It's shocking to know that's the 2nd place
The 3rd place is...
I see
Choshu is weird
It's really hard to tell
I thought mine is better that
Hamada's riding jacket is the 4th place
So Matsumoto-san, only Cocorico is left
Yeah, and again
Yes only we are left, but I don't think he will stand a chance to win
-I'm just being honest
-Come on, it looks really good
Tell us what is good about it
You never saw him like that right?
You never saw Choshu-san like that right?
-That's exactly the reason why it's awful
-He keeps on talking about this
Which one is the top that Choshu Riki likes the most?
It looks absolutely cute on you
-Let's see which one is the best
-It was super cute...
You're annoying dude
I feel sorry for him
Choshu-san even pretends to choose the another one for us!!
Although that couldn't be true
But Choshu-san tried hard and moved 2 steps forward for us!!
I feel really sorry for letting him do this for us
-He's acting out for us
-Yes, he did it for us
Choshu-san, can you tell us why is this the worst one please?
Well, I don't dislike the color of this
But is this men's clothes?
We all want to ask this question
He asked this for several times
Tanaka is paying 15,246 yen for the item bought
The turbulent bonus item section!!
At any rate, this item suits you right? Championship!
A bonus item that suits Choshu-san
The first presenter is Hamada
Choshu-san just started using SNS recently
Yes, he just started using Twitter recently
But I heard that there's a lot of typos in his post
So you can use this...
Eh, what's this?
-Put this here...
-Oh, I see
The text will look bigger so there should be less typos
Can you see it clearly?
I can see it very clearly
*Shinjuku no Haha, or Kurihara Sumiko, is a famed fortune teller in Shinjuku, for over half a century
He sounds like Shinjuku no Haha*
Saying like "I can see it clearly now"
I can really see it clearly
The next presenter is Endo, who won first place in the tops section
That's huge
-It's not about being big though
-Yes, agreed
It's from CA4LA the hat shop
Eh, again?
I need to open it again
Well, these things happen, Choshu-san
Here it comes
What did you buy?
Well it's from CA4LA, so it's a hat
-But for this hat...
-What is that?
It's a bucket shaped hat, which is trendy right now,
plus a cap on top of it
What does that even mean?
This is very trendy right now
He looks confused again
Just look at Choshu-san's face
Choshu-san is pitiful
He looks like he's about to cry
Please try the hat on
What is that?
This is awful
Endo, this is awful
Try to wear it backwards
-Backwards?
-Yes, backwards
He looks like a dumb kid now
-It's a bucket-shaped hat
-Don't say bucket again
It's the same color as his face
The next presenter is Matsumoto, who presented a cute top in the previous section
-Please, Matsumoto-san
-Okay
I've tried to bring out the cute part of Choshu-san previously
But we should not forget his wildness as well
In addition, they are perfect in these days
He's laughing
And I've prepared two items
It's good right?
*Strong style is an approach of wrestling as a combat sport
-A mask?
-So he can always be in a "strong style"*
Can you please try it on?
It's for Bōsōzoku
Bōsōzoku?
*Yoroshiku written in Kanji is a greeting used by Bōsōzoku
So it says Yoroshiku
This is not necessary at all right, Choshu-san?
No, no, please try the another "Come fight me" too
This is absolutely unnecessary
But think about it...
Wearing a Micky jacket, and a "Come fight me" mask, that's a masterpiece
Like "what is that guy thinking about?"
It's no good to be a masterpiece
Can Tanaka save his face?
-He was confused all this time
-I bet he will laugh hard this time
-You have to save your face here
-Yes, otherwise I'll be losing 2 times in a row
-Eh?
-He's saying "Eh?" already
What is it dude? He's saying "Eh?" already
What is that?
Mine is also a hat
What?
Look at it
-No, no way
-That's awful
-Are you serious dude!!
-Why? That looks good
Is he a surgeon?
What the heck is that?
This is terrible right? Look at it
-No it's not
-What are you thinking about?
You can hang out without setting your long hair every time
Well no, you can't go out with this thing
He told us the answer already
No way, that's not true
He is speaking smoothly for the first time in a while
The last presenter is Hosei, who chose Japanese style items
Please, Yama-chan
-Are you confident about this?
-Yes, of course
But Choshu-san made a weird face though
And he don't even want to take it out
What happened Choshu-san?
Hey dude, it's not a shit right?
Where can you even buy a shit
What is that?
Please take it out Choshu-san
-That looks scary
-What is it?
Choshu-san?
That's terrifying
How come? What happened to you?
What happened to you, seriously?
This is terrible
This is just terrible!!
Please try it on
Yes, just like that
This is absolutely terrible
No way
Wow, it suits you perfectly
Your grandchild will be so happy to see this!!
How can you use this?
Well, I hope Choshu-san can wear this and play with kids
I'm sure that kids will be happy with that
You have a grandchild right?
Yes, I do
The ranking for bonus items will be announced!!
At any rate, this item suits you right? Championship!
Which bonus item do Choshu-san like the most?
He can use mine immediately
Thank you very much
Of course, of course
This comes in handy
This is really useful to me
This is definitely useful
So now Choshu-san, which item gets 2nd place?
Please tell us which item gets 2nd place
Well, so the key point is to be practical right?
He should choose mine
I knew it!
I told you! Right?
No way, wait a second, we should leave now dude
Choshu-san, why is this 2nd place?
This is because...
I'll take it, and give it to my grandchild
So that's indeed the reason
To make them happy
Matsumoto's masks got 3rd place
Why 3rd place?
This is the gauze mask that I used since childhood
-It makes you feel at ease right?
-Yes
Choshu-san are you fine with those words on it?
Well, so probably just for a walk around the neighborhood
So not for going on an outing
Well, yeah that's true
Which one is the worst bonus item for Choshu?
-Like "are you treating me as fool?"
-Yeah
I wonder which one he'll choose
Both are hats
That was fast
He told us the answer already
Seriously? You don't like it?
If you have to make a choice between these two,
then of course it's this one
This is totally unnecessary
No way, it really suits you well, and it was super cute
It's pointless
Can I borrow this Choshu-san
Tanaka when are you supposed to use this?
What is it called?
It's a Turban, and this looks perfect
No way, that's so weird
This is really good, and it's warm
Who will look good with this?
In addition to the top, Tanaka is paying for the turban as well
How do you feel Choshu-san, with all these tops and bonus items?
We thought over this and bought it ourselves
I'm really grateful for this
I really feel sorry today
But if the size is a bit larger, maybe the ranking could have changed
Okay, I see, but even so...
He was wearing it backwards just now, this is the front
Eh?
This is the front
Well, but even so...
It was backwards
You look horrible
*Tanaka is hosting the tv show "ZIP!" every Thursday
Wear that on ZIP!
Wear that and go to ZIP!
That's a Batsu game