[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
The First Gaki No Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
The First Gaki No Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
Azabujuban Edition!
Thank you for having us!
That was quite the voice you made.
People gather around if I talk out loud, and it's annoying.
Annoying?
I mean, all the normal people.
Oh, right.
But it sure has been a while since last time, hasn't it?
That's right, it's been a while.
Is this the 7th time?
Yes it is.
The last celebrity we encountered was Yoshi from COWCOW.
In Shimokitazawa, right?
Right, in Shimokitazawa!
It was Shimokitazawa.
I still have no idea where he was going.
He might have been returning from another place.
He might have been returning from somewhere.
We'll never know.
This is the seventh iteration of this program, where the guys aren't allowed to go home until they find a celebrity!
They have wandered and struggled to find all their celebrities!
And this time around, the guys are looking in this area.
Azabujuban in Minato Ward!
A town with a good atmosphere with countless famous shops lining the streets.
Overflowing with tourists, it is one of the capital's most popular spots!
Many celebrities wander these streets unnoticed, but will the guys be able to find them?
We're in Azabujuban today
There's not a lot of people here at this hour...
I don't know, I think we'll finish fairly quickly today.
There's tons of famous people in Juban, right?
There really is.
We just have to go over there.
There's tons of famous people in Juban, right?
There really is.
We just have to go over there.
Really?
There really is.
We just have to go over there.
Really?
But this timing is a bit...
I also dressed a bit lighter today...
So we have to make it a quick one.
Tanaka has it worse though.
Are you one of the Kano sisters?!
What's up with that outfit?!
What happened?
This guy's got no sense of the seasons.
I'm wearing something underneath!
It's so thin though...
You've gotta be freezing!
And what's that pattern?
It's a bird print.
-Birds?
-Yes.
That's so intricate!
It's over the top!
(鳥がらスープ 'Tori Gara Su-pu' = Chicken soup, sounds the same as 鳥柄 'Tori Gara' = bird pattern/bird print)
It's like chicken soup!
Totally.
(鳥がらスープ 'Tori Gara Su-pu' = Chicken soup, sounds the same as 鳥柄 'Tori Gara' = bird pattern/bird print)
Intricate indeed.
Let's stroll around until we find a celebrity!
Azabujuban Edition!
These are the rules:
The shoot won't end until we meet a celebrity.
However, all members must know the celebrity's name.
And naturally, we also need filming consent from their respective agencies.
Now, will the guys find any celebrities in Azabujuban?!
If we find someone now, we're done?
That's right.
But they might not be allowed to appear on the show.
Yes!
But you know, we've found too many comedians at this point.
So I'd like to find someone that's not in comedy this time.
Right.
It would be nice.
And also, the viewers might think we've somehow set this all up if comedians keep appearing.
Totally.
We want the element of surprise.
Right, someone you'd never expect to see in Gaki.
That would be nice.
Yeah.
Well, yeah...
But we still have to find them.
You're right.
I actually spend a ton of time here.
So getting spotted through this kind of show in my private time would be my worst nightmare.
-Right?
-I would be livid!
In your private time, right?
I'd be like: "How dare you film me in my private time?!".
"What station are you with?!"
And that's what we're about to do right now.
The clock reads 2:31!
And the search has started on this cold, 5 degree weather.
-I've never been to Juban at this hour.
-Right, me either.
You're right, I don't think there's many celebrities at this around.
I wanna make this a quick one...
I think I can say this since it's well known information...
But Mr. Shimura hangs around here all the time.
(Yasunori Shimura, aka Ken Shimura)
But it's always at night, right?
That's right.
We'd find him in no time if we stood in front of a Girls Bar. (Hostess bar)
That's right, he mentioned he was a regular in this area while we were filming another show.
Does he come here for the Girls Bars?
And he even goes to places in plain sight!
With big glass windows!
Yeah, you can see him right from the outside.
And he even goes to places in plain sight!
With big glass windows!
Yeah, you can see him right from the outside.
That's crazy.
And I even asked him if he should say that...
He replied: "It's fine".
That's crazy.
And I even asked him if he should say that...
He replied: "It's fine".
His bald spot was clear as day from the street!
What?
-Look! Look!
-Who?
Let's stroll around Tokyo until we find a celebrity!
Azabujuban Edition!
Will the guys find them?!
First off, the guys are walking down Patio street towards the train station.
Matsumoto, where do people go at this hour?
At this hour? I don't really know...
But I heard Junichi Ishida is spotted around here regularly.
Mr. Ishida?
That's be nice!
And there's a ton of tourists too.
But we need someone we can name.
Alright then...
I'm gonna start reaching out to people who look the part.
Of course, go ahead.
Look the part?
Lookalikes?
We've gotta find them.
They're drinking wine at this hour?
There's a ton of bottles too.
They're having fun.
-We'd better find someone wearing a mask.
-We should find someone in one of these cute stores.
Right...
Right, anyone with a mask...
-Yeah.
-They are always wearing masks.
They are.
So Tanaka, you should get right in their faces and take the mask off.
You just go up to them and take it right off.
You'll freeze to death if it gets dark and we haven't found anyone!
I have to work hard today.
Of course, I would be against it from the get-go...
But you know what to do.
Tanaka, you have to sacrifice yourself.
You have to go like: "It's fine" "Don't worry about it".
"This much should be fine".
"This is normal".
Perhaps it is the time, but there are no signs of any celebrity around.
It's deserted.
There are no people here.
We have to walk around first.
Right, let's look around first and see what's on the down low.
But it sure would be amazing if we found someone on our first walkthrough.
It sure would.
I'm telling you, it's too early.
Yeah, it's a problem.
Yeah, nobody's around at this time.
The guys are now heading down the main street where most of the people are!
There's a lot of fancy people around here.
Well, of course.
-They all look like celebs.
-Totally.
Well, of course.
-They all look like celebs.
-Totally.
Tons of celebrities also live around here.
-A lot of them live around here.
-This is one of their neighborhoods.
We haven't spotted any potential celebs.
Surprisingly...
We might be in trouble.
Yeah, this could get bad...
Should we have a look in Starbucks?
Starbucks sounds good.
-What was that?
-What a reaction!
That was an amazing reaction to Hamada.
That was hilarious.
Right?
It's a Yakitori place.
Yakitori.
I'm gonna ask that girl with the glasses in front of Starbucks.
Let's go.
Hello...
Are you a celebrity?
Have you had any famous customers today?
Was she not a celebrity?
You get a lot of famous customers, don't you?
Right?
Oh really?
Have you seen any around?
I've also eaten here.
Oh, really?
Hiroyuki Yabe.
Oh, Yabe!
Miho Yabe.
Miho Yabe?!
Yabe?
There's no point going over there...
Over here?
Did you let someone get away?
Did Miho Yabe escape?
It wasn't Miho Yabe.
There's too many people talking.
She said Hiroyuki Yabe hangs around this part of town.
Other than comedians?
Like actresses?
I've seen Haruka Igawa around.
Haruka Igawa!
Excuse us.
Thank you!
Let's go, bastards!
-Come on, don't get mad!
-You're wasting time!
We were just gathering some intel!
We were asking about celebrity sightings.
Matsumoto comes here regularly.
He's eaten here before.
Yeah, but it was just the one time.
And they said they haven't had any famous customers today.
We let one slip away...
She really looked famous.
She must have been.
That girl with the sunglasses?
Yeah...
She just sneaked right past us.
-Oh, really?
-Yes.
She just sneaked right past us.
-Oh, really?
-Yes.
But we wouldn't know her name anyway...
Yeah, there's no way I'd know.
She really could have been famous.
But her name though...
Alright, I'm starting to come down with a cold...
Time to go home...
It's only been 12 minutes.
Only 12 minutes have passed.
We haven't even done one lap!
But I did mention I was coming down with a cold.
Fight through it.
What are we gonna do?
Someone should go into this Ishii.
-Should I look inside?
-Yeah.
Shall I?
Oh, I think it could be worth looking at.
Go and have a look.
Cocorico goes into Seijo Ishii to look for potential celebrities!
Why do we always send Tanaka?
Is he gonna be alright?
He's got the worst eyes.
It's Kokoriko.
He's always missing the celebs.
He's got a bad nose too.
After a 5 minute wait...
No luck.
It's just time... You never know.
We'll find someone after a few laps around.
Let's keep this place in mind.
But I can't smell that air of potential yet...
Right...
I keep thinking about the girl that got away...
I wonder who she was...
She was wearing sunglasses, right?
She could have been someone...
She really could have.
This girl's got sunglasses too.
This girl too...
Let's ask.
Go ahead.
Excuse me.
You're in the entertainment business, aren't you?
I'm not.
Haven't you appeared in a commercial?
I haven't.
Oh, really?
Thank you.
Thanks.
What's wrong with you?
What's with the questions?
The guys keep walking down Azabujuban's main street.
When Endo finds something!
There's some signatures over there.
Autographs of famous people.
You know who that is, right?
Sho Aikawa?
-Sho Aikawa?
-Hello.
Isn't that Masaki Kyomot's signature?
-Which one?
-On the top left.
-Hello.
Hello.
Really?
-Who's this?
-It's not?
This is Junji Takada's.
You're totally off!
What's with everyone today?
And that's Satom Ishihara, right?
(Kuniko Ishigami, aka Satomi Ishihara)
I can't tell.
It's really difficult to read.
They should write more neatly.
Do you get a lot of famous customers?
Well yes, from time to time.
Right...
Thank you.
That looks super delicious.
That's the Taiyaki shop from "Oyoge! Taiyaki!"
(Song by Masato Shimon)
The original one?
Of course.
Really?
The song is based on this store.
That was here?!
It's been 20 minutes and the guys haven't found any celebrities!
Whoa!
This place is empty.
I think there'd be way more people if it were a little later in the day...
By the way, Heipo lives in that building, right?
(Toshihide Saito, aka 'Heipo)
I think there'd be way more people if it were a little later in the day...
By the way, Heipo lives in that building, right?
(Toshihide Saito, aka 'Heipo)
Oh, really?
Here, here.
I've seen him coming out of this building.
Heipo!
This one?
He can't hear you.
It'd be so funny if he was home.
He would've come out if he was home.
I've also spotted Heipo twice in this Soba place.
Is Heipo the only celeb you've seen around here?!
I always run into him.
You sure do.
-He's a pretty small guy, but he stands out.
-Right?
I don't really see him though...
-He's a pretty small guy, but he stands out.
-Right?
I don't really see him though...
Heipo!
I'm telling you, he ain't here.
Closing in on Roppongi Hills, the guys are just about to reach the end of Azabujuban.
If this were anything like our previous searches, we would have found at least one celebrity by now.
Totally.
A potential candidate, right?
Someone not very well known.
Yes, that's right.
What about this car?
-That's a good car.
-This could be it.
She totally looks like a celeb.
-This might be it.
-You're right.
Let's give it a try.
Alright.
MamaTare. MamaTare.
(Mama + Tarento = MamaTare)
MamaTare?
She's got a very nice car.
It's gotta be a MamaTare.
"Good afternoon, I am a MamaTare."
They wouldn't say that.
Are you a MamaTare?
-"Yes, I'm a MamaTare"
-No way.
He wouldn't ask it like that.
-That's way too insane.
-Sorry, and thank you.
-No luck?
-Yeah.
She doesn't speak Japanese.
Oh, she doesn't?
She's from China.
She came from China.
-She's really pretty.
-She really is.
She came from China.
-She's really pretty.
-She really is.
So pretty.
She's from China and has that car?
Why do you care?
Who cares...
I'm guessing she lives here.
Oh, right, right.
Yeah.
You thought she was on holiday.
How many Chinese celebrities can you name?
That would depend, are we counting people from Hong Kong?
How many?
There's Jackie Chan, right?
Right.
You've got no one left, right?
Chu Yun-fat, right?
Chu Yun-fat? Are you serious?
Yeah, it's Chu Yun-fat.
From 'A Better Tomorrow'.
Chu Yun-fat?
Isn't it Chow Yun-fat?
Oh right, Chow Yun-fat.
It's deserted...
Totally empty.
No one's shopping!
How far are we going?
Just a bit longer.
Right, we can't go much farther than this.
We'll turn back now.
Wait, which way?
Over there.
Let's go back that way instead of this way.
Yeah.
Right?
This way is definitely better.
Also, let's stop by the Taiyaki shop.
I wanna eat Taiyaki.
Let's.
-Right?
-Yeah.
I'm craving it.
Let's warm up.
-Or we'll die.
-Let's search while warming up.
The guys are heading towards the train station once again as they enter a busy street full of cars.
There's no people on this street.
Yeah, this street is only busy at night.
Worst case we can go to that apartment building and knock.
Knock?
You never know, someone might come to greet us.
Some celebs are bound to be living there.
That's like the ultimate invasion of privacy.
-Totally.
-No way, no way.
That's like the ultimate invasion of privacy.
-Totally.
-No way, no way.
How would you react if they come to your house?
I'd be so pissed.
If they suddenly rang your doorbell?
I'd be so livid, I'd ask for the producer's name and call him every single day.
I can't believe you came dressed like that, Tanaka.
I'm not that cold.
But you are!
You dressed like it's spring.
Really?
It's so empty...
For real.
This car has to belong to a celebrity, don't you think?
-We could wait around and see who comes to pick it up.
-Right?
He might be having some coffee inside.
But I'd be super pissed if they did that to me.
But we're doing it right now.
Are they MamaTare?
Mama Tarento.
-Hello.
-She could be Nozomi Tsuji.
(Nozomi Sugiura, aka Nozomi Tsuji)
Everyone is so well dressed around here.
It's been 35 minutes since the beginning of the search.
The guys have arrived at Shinichinohashi intersection.
This is Croket's place.
Oh, this one?
Should we wait for Croket here?
(Croket operates his own impersonation comedy show in this building.)
I'd love to have Croket on this show.
-This is his place.
-Right here.
Amazing.
-We came here once, right?
-Yeah.
You're right.
When they had just opened.
They are in such a prime location.
His gags are filling my mind again.
-That's amazing.
-It really is.
Hey! Don't just go look all at once!
What are we gonna do if someone passes by?!
Tanaka!
Just take turns, dammit!
Hamada is totally in the right this time, so I can't talk back.
You're right.
All of us went to see.
We were so focused.
We were all like: "Amazing!"
All of you piled up at once.
Totally.
"Amazing!"
Is there such a scary program?
Should we walk towards the shopping district?
And the guys go on the day's second lap around Azabujuban.
Once again, they search around Azabujuban's main street.
It's already our second lap.
We've entered the second lap.
We've already been through here.
Yeah...
Right...
I'm telling you, let's go to the Taiyaki spot.
Why Taiyaki?!
Should we take a break?
Here?
Can we even afford to go to a side street coffee shop?
We'll keep searching while we rest.
There's a coffee shop with an outside terrace just further down the road.
A terrace?
Do you mean outside?!
Yes, they have those heaters.
No way...
I think that's fine.
I mean, we're filming...
Once you go mad, you just stay mad.
Hold on, I'm not mad.
I'm not.
Once you go mad, you just stay mad.
Hold on, I'm not mad.
I'm not.
He's so scary, isn't he?
Hold on, I'm not mad.
I'm not.
Geez...
So, we're not getting the Taiyaki?
How badly do you want those Taiyaki?!
He's been going off about Taiyaki this, and Taiyaki that.
Really?
I wanted some at the beginning, but not anymore.
You can eat Taiyaki anytime you want.
But why Taiyaki?
-I mean, we're already here...
-You're really keen on the Taiyaki.
But why Taiyaki?
-I mean, we're already here...
-You're really keen on the Taiyaki.
But that place doesn't have a great view of the street.
We'll just get take out.
There's the Taiyaki shop.
This is the famous place, right?
That's right. Look at the queue!
There's always a line.
That's amazing.
Can't someone on staff stand in line for me?
How much do you wanna eat them?!
We're already here...
There's another shop over there, look!
But those are the famous ones!
Oh, those aren't Taiyaki.
Those are Imagawayaki.
No, no, no, I want Taiyaki.
-It's just a different shape!
-Oonuma!
No, no, no, I want Taiyaki.
-It's just a different shape!
-Oonuma!
Get in line!
Imagawa and Taiyaki are just shaped differently!
Poor Oonuma...
He's got a very important job now.
Let's go to the coffee shop.
Where's this coffee shop?
A bit further.
It's Heipo's building again.
Heipo!
He's not coming out...
Right?
He's gotta come out eventually.
We've been yelling for him this whole time.
He's never coming out.
It's been 50 minutes since the start of the search.
They guys are having a break in an open coffee shop while they wait for the Taiyaki to arrive.
This spot is warm.
The guys sharpen their gazes so as to not miss any celebrities.
This isn't that great...
I know what you mean.
But actually...
What about that guy?
That guy’s wearing a mask.
-With the coat?
-Yes.
Who? Who?
That rapper guy.
-Who could he even be?!
-I wouldn't know his name.
I would never know his name if he's really a rapper.
Right...
He does look like he's in the entertainment business.
I only know KREVA.
(Takashi Hatakeyama, aka Kreva)
No luck. They are just normal employees.
It wasn't Zeebra?
(Hideyuki Yokoi, aka Zeebra)
It wasn't Zeebra.
I only know of Zeebra.
Rappers?
And then... Endo notices something!
What?!
Have they finally found a celebrity?!
The members were all enjoying a coffee in their break time.
When Endo notices something!
What?
Look!
Have they finally found a celebrity?!
Hello! Hello! Hello!
What are you doing here?!
What are you doing?
These your kids?
Yes, yes.
Oh, your kids!
What are you up to?
Yeah, well I'm just doing some pickup.
Picking up my kids from school.
And you've got that with you?!
-This is so perfect!
-I've been playing this while we walk.
While you walk?
That's amazing!
You've got a guitar with you on your pickup?!
You see, we're filming a show right now.
Is that so?
We can't go home until we find a celebrity.
Oh, really?
Everyone knows his name, right?
One, two...
Thane Camus!
(Thane Alexander Camus)
Thank you.
By the way, we can air this, right?
Of course, I don't mind at all.
Okay!
All clear! All clear!
We should blur your children's faces, right?
Well, he's actually on NHK right now.
You also play?
Yours is way bigger than your father's.
This one's huge.
Or this one's just really tiny.
We were just walking around and playing.
That's nice.
While you walked?
It's very cold.
Yes, it's so cold my fingers hurt.
What a cheerful encounter.
I was so shocked.
You're such a good dad.
-Right?
We've completed our mission.
Thank you.
Success!
We've hit it out of the park.
Mission complete.
Anyway, thank you.
No, thank you.
Who spotted you?
Endo.
I was spacing out and I just saw him.
Wonderful!
That's wonderful!
We would have totally missed him otherwise!
Thank you.
Anyway, let's grab our tea.
Take care.
Let's go back inside.
We're so lucky.
We smashed this one.
It was juuust right.
Thane Camus is juuust right!
Right?
-He's a perfectly normal guy.
-Totally.
Right?
And he was picking up his two kids.
It's juuust perfect!
That's Azabujuban for you.
It was just right.
It's suuuper real!
And it was also the perfect timing.
You asked him if his kids could be on the show right?
And we're only blurring his daugher.
Yeah.
That was also just perfect.
It adds to that feeling of reality.
Totally.
But the older brother can be on TV, right?
We actually found two celebrities.
He's on NHK, right?
Yes.
Now I'm starting to get really pissed off about those Taiyaki.
Why the hell is that guy waiting for your damn Taiyaki?!
I was just about to mention this...
I'm over Taiyaki.
Right?
We met a celebrity and that guy's stuck in line!
Your priorities are completely backwards!
Heipo is here!
Heipo.
Heipo don't you live over there?
Yes, I am living there.
What?!
-Really?
-Yes.
Alright, then can you go back and wave at us from your window when we yell your name?
We wanna get that shot.
You're really doing this for us?
Does your apartment face the street?
Yes, it does.
Amazing.
This is such a pain in the ass.
It's right over there.
It's just a little extra for the viewers.
Lastly, the guys have decided to go by Heipo's building in Azabujuban.
Yes, I am living there.
-Really?
-Yes.
We're here, right?
It's here.
What floor is he on?
I wonder...
Ready?
-Alright.
-Let's go.
-Can he even hear us?
-Ready?
Heipo!
Oh, it's right there!
Heipo?
Oh, there he is.
This is so funny.
You're right!
So funny!
There he goes!
This is hilarious.
I didn't think he'd be this close.
He looks like a patient at a hospital.
I thought he'd be so far away we could barely see him.
But he's right there!
His window is getting really misty.
The humidity in that room is no joke!