Murakami Shoji's Ninja Class
Ninja Class
Murakami Shoji's Class Series started without anyone wanting it to
Murakami Shoji's Green Beret Class
Green Beret Class
It started with Ninjas, then it was Green Berets and then Pirates
Murakami Shoji's Pirate Class
Pirate Class
Murakami Shoji's Pilot Class
Pilot Class
It even went on with Pilot Class
And without a single improvement, we got our 5th episode last time
Murakami Shoji's Clown Class
Clown Class
Which class are we going to attend today?
"Hold it" - that's what I just told you
Why can't you do it?!
Cocorico
Downtown
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Hosei
Now...
Don't make that face
How come that every time we do this the weather always sucks?
It's always like this with him
I know, right?
It's chilling, really
Yeah, it's cold
Let me just get this one clear for you
I didn't mean that but yeah, it's cold
I had to make this clear
What a day
I guess we're doing this today?
Man...
"Ghostbusters"
Isn't this too much?
You know, our staff has like
A list with different options for this series
I know for sure that he clearly spotted this one
You think so?
He really did?
But he never actually does it
Well, yeah
He never does as planned in our meetings
Right
And then he blows his fuse
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI ~ TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI ~ PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TYPESETTING & QUALITY CHECK BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Headed to the meeting spot
Where's senpai?
Right, where is he?
Yeah...
I'm worried
Shouldn't we ghostbusters be indoors?
I guess so
We shouldn't even pop out during daytime...
There's something there
Huh?
"Ghostbusters class - assembly here"
I see
Is he gonna show up then?
Man it's cold
Yeah...
Oh, I don't mean it that way
I thought so
Uhh
Wow
Ghostbuster!!
He's finally here
From so far away...
So grand
Ghostbuster!!
What--
How should we react to this?
Ghostbuster!!
Sometimes it's like this
Let's go with it
Ghostbuster!!
Impressive
Is that it?
His voice is so loud today
Ghostbuster!!
Something's off
This sucks
Ok
Good job today
Come again tomorrow, will you?
Money?
Counting on you for tomorrow too
5'000 yen?
He paid him
Masahiro
Yes?
How about tomorrow? Can you make it?
Yep
Alright?
Yes
Good job
Alright then, call me if a ghost pops out, ok?
Sure
What about tomorrow...?
Take care
He told them to meet again tomorrow...
I'll get back to you, Masahiro
What about tomorrow?
Good morning
'Morning
They did a good job, huh?
Here we are
Murakami Shoji
Here comes our Murakami Shoji, back from his brief impromptu act
You know, japanese people don't want to do ghostbusters anymore
So I had to hide foreigners, it's awkward
What the-?
Come again?
What is he saying--?
"Hide" them...?
I don't get it
I had to hire foreigners, that's what I said!
Alright, alright
Can I ask you one thing?
What?
Bro, for how long do you think this class is going to last?
Let's see...
Your bro is planning to go for---
Who the fuck are ya callin' "bro", you scum!!
Is that no good?
You can't call me bro here!
It's "captain"
Ah, captain
Captain
For how long, is that what you asked?
It's gonna last till you become qualified!
You can never clear a sinnnnngle thing
Since we did Ninjas
None of you became a ninja!
I got a load of calls from my boss, you know
He told me to get my shit together!
Captain, you have such a powerful voice today
It's incredible
Ghostbusters Class will begin!!
coming up
You can tell he's feeling really good today
His voice is amazing
Really powerful
He's in shape
First off
Ghostbusters can't win with bare hands
Yes
Got it?
I've got some real stuff (weapon) for you here
Really?
No way
Of course
I want one
Now we're talking
Ghostbusters Collector's Edition
Ghostbusters classroom, lesson 1
Weapon supply
They'll be given the Ghostbusters' weapon, essential to get rid of ghosts
Woah, look at that
It's pretty big
It is
Be careful with these
Sure
I'm gonna hand them out
This is... it's yours, Matsumoto
Yes
Take it
Here
Thanks
Make sure to backpack it for good
"Backpack it"...?
Endo
Yes
Thanks
"Backpack it---
Why are you repeating that?!
Oh, I'm sorry
It's---
Thank you
It's heavy
Hama-chan
Yes
Thank you
So...
Excuse me, captain...
I don't have any equipment
You want it?
I do
Come here!
Yes
You others just wait here
Sure
Why does this always happen?
I wonder why
Complaining is the only thing you're all good at
Wow...
Oh my
Impressive
What a bother
Woah...
That's a big handicap
Huh?
And now
Everything alright?
This is a washing machine
Are you dumb?
Where does it look like a washing machine to you?
I mean---
Where does it---
From which angle does it look like one?!
I'm asking you: from which angle?!
I mean, it's pretty obvious---
What's obvious?! How is this a washing machine?!
I told you so
I'm talking to you
He's so pissed off
How is this one? Huh?
Apologize
It's only lighter
You brat
"Pour", "rinse", "evaporate"
It's a washing machine
It's 100% a washing machine
I told you so
That's what they want you to think
But it's actually the latest prototype made by NASU
. . . .
NASU?!
- NASU...?
You mean Nasu Highlands?
It's the Highlands
I see, the Highlands
You're referring to them?
I meant NASA!
Ah, NASA
With an "A"
We can't let ghosts hear what we say, so I shortened it
Ah, I see
I said NASU instead of NASA
Oh, is that so
Quick, come here Yama-chan
Here
Washing machine, huh?
Kinda, yeah
If that's a washing machine, then wash up your body and mind!
Always complainin' around...
Where do you think ghosts normally are?
Matsumoto?
Let's see... I'd say sheds or attics
These kinds of places, right?
My sister had a problem with a tooth in the attic, they're dangerous and you shouldn't glet cose
The end of that sentence...
It was a mess
So shabby
You know where they are?
It's that place...
What are you laughing at?
I'm sorry
What the heck!
What's wrong?
I just thought...
Maybe he's about to blow his fuse
We said that before
Who said that?
Him?
Sometimes you do that
Hamada?
Yes?
I didn't say that!
You said it, didn't you?
What are you talkin' about?
I'm not blowing any fuse here
Yes, I understand
I've been thinking about the best way to phrase that...
Yes
But there are too many drawers inside my head
Sure
And
It feels like they're empty when I open them
There goes his fuse
Who said that?!
Sorry
You said that? Matsumoto?
I apologize
It's about time
Yes?
Roger
To start our training
Let's go folks, follow me
Yes
Let's go
Ghost!
Buster!
Ghost
Buster...
Ghos---
Yama-chan?
Sorry
What are you doin'?
I think his model is too heavy
That's a bit...
I'm giving my best here, but it's so heavy
Take it off!
Can I just---
Take it off
He's gonna kick him out
It's so heavy, I didn't know I was going to run up a slope
We didn't know
Just take this instead
Excuse me?
Take this with you
Is this really ok?
Mh
I spoke to your dad before and he uh-- whatever, let's go
Guess we'll never know
It's fine to me
Yeah...
Ghost ascertainment​ training
Ghostbusters Collector's Edition
Ghostbusters classroom, lesson 2
Ghostbusters must recognize a ghost when it appears and get rid of it
For this training I'll have you eat some soba
Listen closely
I'm going to secretly insert this ghost doll inside em
Got it?
Yes
Once you get it
You have to shout "I've found a ghost"!
I see
Ok
But you don't know when it's coming
Got it
How about you try, Endo?
Sure
Good luck
Thanks
Endo's challenge
Go for it
Ready?
Yes
Here we go
If you find it, shout that
Ok, if I do
Here
Start!!
He's so friggin' slow
Here
That's a lot
He's eating a lot
Yeah...
True
Hang on
Here
Fwunda ghosd!
Exactly!
Ok!
Ghost captured!
Well done
Tell me
Yes?
When did you notice it?
As soon as you poured it in
Good job
Thanks
Endo, that's impressive
Yes?
Thank you
Come here one sec
Oh, sure
You like baseball, don't you?
Oh, is it ok?
Right?
You're a fan of the Hanshin Tigers, right?
Yes
I'll give you this
Enatsu Yutaka
It's from the past
It is
Can I have it?
It's yours
It's Enatsu...
Must be old
Thank you so much
You did well
I'm taking this
Thank you
Do your best next time too
I will
I have lots of more
Sure, thank you
Alright, you go next, Hamada?
This is gonna take forever
Let's go Hamada
Hamada's challenge
Will Hamada overcome this harsh training?
The captain is making soba
Stay focused
Do your best
Sure
Hurry the hell up
Come again?
He got it, I'll say it for him
Alright
Don't rush things
Got it, sorry
- Really
We're here to face monsters today, you know
. .
Monsters? Are you sure?
What do you know?!
I saw them pointing their fangs at me recently
Yeah but I mean, "monsters"...
Let's do this
I'm ready
Start!!
Do your best
Go for it
Gho--
Founna ghosd!
There's two of them
Ghost captured!
Playing dirty, huh
I saw you stopped moving your chopsticks
Yes! Thank you
But you weren't quick enough to say it
I was surprised to see two of them
Impressive
Nicely done
Thank you
You really did great
Normally a person would end up eating one by mistake
I see  By mistake?
Yes, by mistake.
Yamazaki's challenge
Now it's time for Yamazaki who has yet to satisfy him
Start!!
Do your best
There's a lot
Eat it up
Don't give up
Be careful
Here comes another
The ghost is about to come
Watch out for it
He's pouring more soba while he's eating
Careful
It's about time
We know for sure it's going to come
It's time
I'm sure of it
Scary
3 minutes later
It's coming
Make sure to shout when you see it
It's time
There's like two times a regular soba portion
He's--- it's not--
Isn't it about time?
I can't see it
I bet it's going to appear
It should
Here it is
There!
Yes?
You know why I made you undergo this test?
Why?
Because of your father
Wha-?
When your father used to work at Naniwa Soba...
He used to play so many pranks on me
He would bring me curry if I'd order soba
I cried so much I couldn't even see in front of me
But you know what your father said to me that time?
"Stay by my side dish"
. .
Alright, you're fired
Eh?!
Am I really fired?
Say you're sorry
Please forgive him
Let this one slide, please
We're sorry, we'll keep on looking for ghosts
I understand
I'm gonna give you another chance
Thank you so much
Ghost deceiving lesson
Ghostbusters Collector's Edition
Ghostbusters classroom, lesson 3
Sometimes when a ghost appears you must hide and wait for a chance
If it spots you, there's no guarantee you'll survive
First off, lie down here
So I can run you over with my bicycle
If you make a sound or shout when I run you over
The ghost will get off his bicycle and slap you
The ghost is riding a bicycle?!
With that being said, Matsumoto
Yes?
Your turn
Do I have to lie down?
Take this off
Matsumoto's challenge
Move closer
This is scary
Get your hands inside it
This looks pretty scary
Is this gonna be ok, cap?
I'm scared, captain
Ready?
I'll be the ghost, I'm going to run you over
What? Really?
Get ready
Yes
Captain?
Captain!
So far...
He's running around so much
Yeah
Here I come
This is...
It's dangerous
Place your hands inside
It's not safe
Oh shit!
He shouted so much!
You can't shout, you're gonna get slapped
But it's so scary
I told you not to shout
I'm sorry
A middle aged man got down his bycicle and slapped you
Weren't we talking about ghosts?
A man?
Matsumoto's 2nd challenge
This is the scariest one yet
Watch out, it's dangerous
Really, what is he planning to do?
I wonder
Is he really going to run him over?
Yeah, I don't know
Looks like it
Wait--
Ouch
So goddamn noisy!
But I'm really freaking out, captain
What's with the apologies?
I'm sorry
I told you not to speak, didn't I?
I know, I'm sorry
Matsumoto's 3rd challenge
How can one do this?
It's the unsafest thing
Really, be careful there
Captain?
Oh shut up, so noisy
I'm sorry
You suck
Such a noisy prick
I was afraid, cap
Sorry
They're gonna eat you
I'm really sorry
Are you gonna be that frightened against ghosts?
Yes
Tanaka
Your turn
Do it
This time I'll run
Tanaka's challenge
Eh? Wait a sec--
What do you mean?
I'll be the ghost
I see
Think of me as one
It's not like they only ride bicycles
I see
Move here a bit
Sure
In which spot are you going to run?
I'm just running
Yeah but, where?
Where?
How should I know this?!
You think a ghost is gonna tell you where? Idiot
Yeah but--
Yes?
Wait...
Are you dumb?
It's not like---
Alright alright, I got it
But I'm not mentally ready for this...
I'm not... I'm sorry
You think you can say that in your situation?
I don't
Remember that time we were together in the backstage?
Yes?
You told me "please teach me anything about comedy"
Yes
It was back then
And that time you told me...
"Don't ask me anything comedy-related", don't you remember?
I haven't forgotten that
You said I sucked so bad at R-1's second round, am I right?
Am I?
Did you say that?
That's not true
Don't you remember that?
I should have cut ties with you that time, you idiot
There he goes
It's beginning
I'm coming
Why are we doing this?
Yes, yes!
You just said something, didn't you?
Ouch
Get those glasses off, you shithead
Sorry
You're all no good, let's quit this
I'm really sorry
Ghostbusters Collector's Edition
Ghostbusters classroom, lesson 4
Presence of mind training
Ghosts hate it when they're being laughed at
Therefore it's important to train your mind presence
Mind presence training now
You won't ever be able to pass it
If you shout for every minor thing
Got it
On the other hand, if you shout too much
The ghosts are gonna stab you harder
Are they going to?
More than stabbing
Let's just say they'll get mad
Actually...
When I used to work at the office,
they told us to bring a pic from our childhood
When they told me that
I've brought this with me, it's the only one I have
Mom - Kasumi
This is my mom, Murakami Kasumi
And this one is Murakami Keiji
Keiji
It's not Shoji, he's my big brother
But I always chose this picture
'Cause I didn't want them to know I was poor
I told them "I have this one pic here" pretending it was me
I've always chosen this pic
Dad - Naoyoshi
My dad
Murakami Naoyoshi
This one
Does he ring any bell?
It's Keiji (big brother)
He grew up a bit here
He never shows up in photos...
What the-
Got you waiting enough
This time there's also a relative of mine
So...
Remember this guy?
He already appeared
It's him
Keiji
It's Keiji
Murakami Keiji
This one
Ah, your relative?
It's this girl
That's right
And finally, this is me
Murakami Shoji
We have a pic
You can tell by the background, right? We weren't rich---
Yaa～wn!
Are you really going to yawn over my explanation?!
What the hell!
It was perfectly timed just now
Right when he's talking about himself
It's time for an unexpected training!!
coming next
That's not polite
Yawning around
Follow me
Listen
Here
Matsumoto, start from here and do a long jump
Yes
...A long jump?  Behind the line, ok?
Got it?
What should I do?
Like this?
Ohh, right here
Yes
Here
Tanaka
What's this about?
Yes
Oh! That's impressive
Incredible
He's tall after all
Ever took part in the athletics?
No, not actually
What's the point of this training?
Even more impressive, then
Alright, Endo
It's your turn, Endo
Yes
I think he lost to Tanaka
Uh! That's nice
Right here
Oh, ok
Ok, Yamazaki
Not bad at all
He made it
A tiny bit behind Endo's
Yeah
Your turn now
Sorry captain, can I ask you what's the point of this?
Eh?
What was that?
"What's the point"? Is that what you asked?
I mean... we should fight ghosts...
'Cause the episode would be too short otherwise
What?!
So, this has nothing to do with ghosts?
Of course it doesn't!
You should have known this
Yes, we're sorry
We're really sorry
We'll do our best
You know there's so much stuff from golden hour to midnight
Yes, sorry
Bear that in mind!
Be like "ohh right, maybe it's not enough yeah? Mhh" ya know?
With that being said
Let's do our last thing
Ghostbusters Collector's Edition
Ghostbusters classroom, lesson 5
Marshmallow man's counterattack
Now we'll get to see what they've learned today
By fighting the strongest ghost, Marshmallow man
If you get rid of Marshmol---mallow man
You'll save the world
Yes
Got it?
Now we'll get to decide which one of us is gonna be him
By majority vote
Ok
That's how we'll decide it
Rock-paper-scissors is no good, you can cheat
Alright, raise your hand if you want
Yamazaki to be Marshmallow man
Who votes for Yamazaki?
Anyone?
Who wants Tanaka to be him?
No one?
Then...
How about Endo?
No one...
Hamada
Here!
Me!
Hamada got one vote out of five
He's in the lead
One vote
Hamada-kun!
You have one vote now
Yes
One point for you
Matsumoto
No one, huh?
Alright then, last one... Murakami
Here!
Achoo
The fuck was that sneeze?!
I'm sorry
That was unacceptable, captain
I know
I'm sorry
It didn't look like you were about to
That's no good
Forgive me
And as soon as I said my name...
You think I'm gonna lose to your sneeze, you idiot?!
Please do it
Counting on you
Can't help it, after all I made myself a nominee
Yes
Mh
Alright, I'm getting changed
You'll be Marshmallow man, captain
Are you gonna become it?
We'll wait
Thanks
Marshmallow man's counter-attack!!
coming next
It should be him
It's Marshmallow man
Looks strong
I'm Marshmallow man!
He even said it himself
It's speaking
Listen to me
You gotta shoot me now
Ok
If you don't shoot me until I melt, I'm going to attack you
Got it?
Captain?
Now, get ready
Roger
Are you ok with this?
Yeah, go all out on me
Got it
It's full
Make sure to finish me off before I attack you
Ok
Can we begin?
Can we?
Ready and... go!
We're coming
Here we come!
Here
Cold! It's cold!
Oh shit
He says it's cold
It's really cold
Take this, Marshmallow man!
Wait a sec--
It melted
We did it
Yeah, we did it
We won
We made it
Today you wiped the evil clean!
Your training for today is over
Thank you
Thanks for today
Now go and tell everyone about it
TYPESET & QUALITY CHECK BY KEDOMAS || TRANSLATION BY
SHION || MORE EPISODES: SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
LIKE MY FB PAGE: FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | FOLLOW ME ON
TWITTER @FGRNDNOISES | WANT TO SUPPORT MY CONTENT?
YOU CAN DONATE FEW BUCKS ON KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
OR ON PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI || THIS IS A NO-PROFIT
TRANSLATION, MADE BY FANS FOR OTHER FANS TO ENJOY. NO
COPYRIGHT INFRINGMENT INTENDED, BUT IN CASE NTV FINDS
OUT ABOUT THIS DON'T FUCKING PUT ME IN JAIL BRO, JUST
HIRE ME, HIRE ME PLEASE HIIIIIIIIIIREEEEEEEEEE MEEEEEEEE PLEE
EEEEEEEEEEEEAAAAAAAAAAASE COME ON MAN I'M RIGHT HERE ;)