subbed by /u/senor_wristband
Hai!
New Years Party!
Excuse me please,
Excuse me, sorry,
Yes?
Surely this is too unfunny?
Hosuei-san really wanted to start it off with this
Seriously?
In the midst of this explosive laughter,
this party has started!
His hearing is off
Let's ring in this year!
The 22nd annual!
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arrahende!
CHIKI CHIKI
This year, let's work hard-donut
New! Years!
PARTY!!!!!!!!!!!!
With that said,
Are you gays rady?
They literally won't laugh at all
Yeah
You're just saying normal things
You just stuttered a bit
Just stuttered is all
If I can't even get a laugh by stuttering, I've had it
They should laugh at that at least, right?
Please go ahead!
This is kinda scary
The 22nd annual Gaki No Tsukai New Years Party!
Plenty of great food and sake!
I haven't watched TV in a while,
so I thought let's watch TV once in a while,
TN: Housei often appears on this show
and DRIVE A GO GO was on
Thank you very much
You were mentioned in the episode right?
Oh I don't know
I just turned it on, and honestly,
I said "Wa!" and changed the channel
Why?
I mentioned you in that episode
Oh really?
I said "Matsumoto-san is watching this!"
"He loves this show!" I said
The staff gift them brand new Gaki no Tsukai merch!
Jenga!
This is pretty good
52 things Hamada Masatoshi Quiz
Let's see one of the cards
"Which of the four do you think is the filthiest?"
The answer,
"Tanaka"
Yeah, this is where that all started
The start of the joke
Oh yeah, Takasu-san is...
Takasu's getting married
You didn't know?
I had no idea!
Ahh maybe cause you went to Australia?
I had no idea
Him and hip-shaking Obachan
Congrats!
Ms. Hip-Shaking Grandma
Congratulations!
I'm not sure what to say
Marrying who?
Her name, what's her name?
That's enough man
Look into the camera,
and say "I love you"
This is Gaki's tradition
Staff: Into that camera
Ah, so this is how Endo felt
I wanted to just simply say it, but I just can't!
Uwah do I really have to say this?
It would be better to hurry up
Right?
If you wait too long it's weird
This is the worst!
Do I really have to say this?
Hurry up and say it
Then here I go
Midori! I love you!
Now I don't care anymore
You already stopped caring?!
Honestly I,
I wish you didn't say that
Wait, wait
So evil
What's up with these two?!
Would normal people do that?
Would people normally say that?
He'll do anything you tell him to!
5th ever, Yama-1 Grand Prix!
Yamasaki's project to find new talent!
Every year, hosting new comedians looking for their big break
Who will win this year?!
Zaki-san, how do you think this Yama-1 will go?
M-1 Grand-Prix is a television manzai contest
There is no more M-1 Grand Pee
To find the best comedians in Japan,
only this YOWA-1 Grand Prix will do!
"YOWAMAN"?
Ladies and Gentlemen!
Let's have some fun-piahhhh
Tamura Kenji's gag is "Chiaaaah"; See Documental Season 5 episode 1
You're ripping off Tamura Kenji's joke
Totally ripping him off
With that said, let's begin the YAMA-1 Grand Prix!
What a shit intro!
Let's introduce our first presenter!
Please come out!
Ignoring every tsukommi, super masochist comedians in their 5th year,
Presenting, "Open Space"!
Hello everyone!
What is it man?!
What is it with you already?
Hello Everyone!
On this new years,
This fatass is here
You're the fatass!
The fatass is clearly you!
You goddamn pig! (buta)
I'm not a buta!
I'm not!
You're a buta!
Then what are you?!
I'm a "pig"!
That means buta!
"Pig" is English for buta!
BUTAAA!
You bloody BUTA!
Anyways, I'm really into these dramas right?
There's a common scene I like in them
The father asks the teacher how his son's exam results went
Oh yeah I know that kinda scene
"Teach, how did my son do?!"
"I'm so sorry sir, he tried his hardest, but unfortunately ..."
"Why did my son ... why?!"
"WHY?!!!!"
"This is a prank!"
Why the hell?!
Why the hell is it a prank?!
What kind of teacher would do that?!
BUTAAAAAAAAAAAA!!!!!!!!!!
Alright just cut it out
Thank you very much!
Let's ask them their impressions of your act
Matsumoto-san, what did you think of Open Space's manzai?
I think it was very good, however
During the performance,
Hamada-san was, uh,
checking his text messages
Hamada-san!
We're counting on you, please!
His text messages
I didn't, I didn't!
They probably caught it on camera
That definitive moment was caught on camera!
Hamada checking his texts during the performance!
An unexpected shocking moment!
Hamada-san please we are counting on you
Yamasaki-san, your impressions?
I'm gonna give the score first
Ah I see
OK let's get the score first
Please, present their score!
10 is the highest right?
Yes, 10 is a perfect score
TEN POINTS!
Wow full points, right out of the gate!
Why did you give them full points?
I thought I should give 10 points as soon as they got on stage
Before the performance?
Before the performance
But after the performance,
I'm glad I thought that they deserved 10 points straight away
Thank you very much!
It's this kind of thing, every year
OK thank you very much!
Let's continue
If you listen to them once, you'll get hooked
In their 9th year, presenting "2700"
2700?
I have prepared a marvelous song, please listen to it if you'd like
Right elbow, left elbow, look at them alternatively (x3)
When I meet, a new friend,
I don't rub the right one
Only rub the left one
I'd like you, to confirm, that I've cleaned it up, nicely
Right elbow, left elbow, look at them alternatively (x3)
Look at my shoe
Look at my shin
Look at my knee
Look at my thigh
Look at my hips
Look at my abs
Look at my chest
Look at my shoulder
OK, here we go
Right elbow, left elbow, look at them alternatively (x2)
Thank you very much
Matsumoto-san, what did you think of this performance?
After watching that whole thing, what you said at the start,
"I've got a great song please listen to it" is funny now
That set the tone right?
OK, let's continue
Judge Yamasaki, their score please!
TEN POINTS!!!
Another 10 points!
Could you please explain why they got 10 points?
It felt set up like a German Suplex Hold
To use an analogy
Bring out the next guys, hurry
I don't see anyone, hurry up
Let's continue,
Up next, in his 11th year, Toshi
TN: This guy's act is Dajare (wordplay). Sort of like puns. I suck at translating them to English, so I will do my best to explain
11th year huh?
Hello!
Berry nice to meet you!
TN: I hate puns
I'm a fruity comedian,
[Yorushiku onegaishimasu + Muskmelon]
Yorushiku onegaishi-Muskmelon!
You see, I made a pun using Muskmelon!
Fruit Man wants to show you Fruit Man's special skill
Fruit Man is very good at fruit wordplay
If you give Fruit Man the names of three fruits, Fruit Man will make a short story for you
Counting on your cooperation,
Yamasaki-san, a fruit please
Muscat! (Grape)
Muscats. Those are tasty!
Matsumoto-san?
Uhhh, lemon
Lemons? Those are sour!
Hamada-san, last one please
Peach (Momo)
Peach?
Those are pink!
OK so, Muscat, Lemon, and Peach
It's ripe! (the story)
Already ripe?
That's fantastic
Fruit Man,
the other day, I fell in love with a peachy young girl
I wanted her to like me, so I bought her lots of stuff
Stuff like this, and that, and this and that
[This and that: a-re mon, ko re-mon (lemon)]
But still, she rejected me!
But anyways,
[Impossible: Masaka -> Muscat]
you thought this was gonna be impossible, right?
It's Fruits!
Wait, did he use the momo (peach)?
"Peachy"
"Peachy young girl"
I sort of, this is my personal opinion,
It was similar to W-Colon (comedy duo)
Oh I only watch the Fruits Channel, so I wouldn't know
Let's see his score, please
TEN POOOOINTS!!!!
Hold on, 3 in a row?
Toshi got 10 points
Please explain why he got 10 points
We're still filming this episode
Sorry give me a second
I have a headache...
Just get lost
With his refined impersonations that capture the spirit,
in his 9th year, Koga Shu
With that said, first off we have,
Suzuki Muneo gets too excited at a public conference, and becomes inarticulate
TN: Suzuki Muneo is a politician
TN: He is speaking incoherently
Next up,
Hamada Koichi laughing wickedly after getting angry
What are you saying you bald son of a bitch?!
Please #!@$$!
*@!@# please!
You there, laugh please!
Thank you very much!
Hamada-san, your impressions?
It was great, he nailed the impressions
Yeah it was amazing
I want to watch some more
Right?
Yamasaki-san is kinda ... right?
He's giving off a bad vibe
He looks to be in a bad mood, but regardless,
the score please!
TEN POINTS!!!
10 points again!
All 10 points so far
Why 10 points I'd like to ask
He had a headache before ...
What did you just say, Endo?
You had a headache before
Before that, before that!
What did you say before that?
Uhhh
This is the fourth 10 points in a row
I asked you about this before but your headache ...
Before that, before the headache
Before that?
What the hell?
Nobody remembers that
"Why 10 points" is what you said
Yes, yes
Right?!
Yes, exactly
Why do you think?
Well 10 points is a perfect score, so
You thought the performance was funny
Or like Hamada-san said, the imitation was good
So something like that could be why
That is exactly why
OK thank you very much!
You got a perfect score
Let's present the next competitor
A fresh new take on comedy,
in his 13th year, Kobayashi Kenta
Sound Effect: Picture Story Show
"Real" Theme Park
The Elephant's fart ended things nicely, right?
Next up is this,
That's one fast mouth!
Fighter Plane Baby
This really is the ending
Thank you very much!
I heard you have a bonus performance?
I will clean a perverted window
Huge-Face Obachan didn't laugh at all
OK, Yamasaki-san?
The points, please
TEN POINTS!!!!!!!!
10 points!
This was like art
It was amazing
2-chome is Tokyo's LGBT hotspot
Aiming to be 2-chome's top queer character,
in their 13th year, Kathu-Naoya
2-chome Tongue Twisters!
Raw Barley
Raw Rice
Naked Festival
Held at Ni-chome!
(can't understand this part lmao)
To the transvestite next door, watch out!
1-chome
2-chome
3-chome
Finished
You're not a real transvestite right?
To your rude question I say,
Ogenko!!!
"Ogenko" is supposed to be like 2-chome slang, like "Dondake"
That is my gag (catchphrase)
Kathu-san,
I heard one of the Gaki members is your type
Oooh should I say who it is?
Please go ahead
Hitoshi's Matsumoto Hitoshi-chan!
If you'd like to, you could join him for some drinks
Oh may I?
Endo that's enough man
You might awaken something
If you keep it up Endo, to you I say;
Ogenko!
OK I got it I'll cut it out
Housei-san, the score please!
Oh that's not good
That's not good
TEN POOOOIIINTS !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
Another 10 points
Why 10 points?
This fully bloomed flower of a newhalf,
did very well
Thank you very much!
That's my thing!
Ah!
I'm so sorry!
Don't worry!
You did nothing wrong
It's not your fault
They apologised on stage!
Then let's continue
Finally, something to succeed the air guitar
in his 20th year, up next is Chubby Cowboy
Hello everyone!
The belly guitar is here!
Oh, fatty fatty
If you ask a fatass, for advice in the desert,
He'll just tell you to eat watermelons
TN: I'm not sure about this translation
I'm the Chubby Cowboy
I've been earning my keep with this belly guitar
Why is he tuning it?
There's places where fatties like to gather
For example, Akihabara
Ryogoku
Famous for its sumo wrestlers
Or perhaps,
Chikage!
Yup
Oh, fatty fatty
Fatties are,
He's humming
Thank you very much!
Time for the score
Yamasaki-san!
TEN POINTS!
10 points again!
That's amazing
You're in your 20th year?
Yes this is my 20th year
So that means,
You're a senpai to Cocorico?
He's the senpai, yes
What do you say to that Cocorico?
What do we say?
He's pretending to be angry
Honestly uhhh,
He is our senpai so, we watched him with that in mind
So we can learn something from him
Save me, please
Save me, please!
Those guys are looking this way
Can you please get me out of this?
We're waiting on you, Yamasaki-san
He just,
As if he was proclaiming his love in the centre of the world
he said "Please help me"