First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
Jungle Pocket Saito's Shichi-Henge!
Downtown - Matsumoto Hitoshi & Hamada Masatoshi
Today is our 48th episode
That's right, also
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
This ceiling is so low
Its echo is amazing, I can still hear you
They told us to keep it down
But why?
I don't want to
You would be too noisy
I won't, I'm just praising them
It would bother
Come on, I don't like this
One more time, please
First tim--
Enough!
Alright, let's call them
Jungle Pocket please, come here!
It's a pleasure
Good morning
Thank you, good morning
48th challenger
Jungle Pocket: Oota Hirohisa, Saito Shinji, Otake
You're not doing this as a trio?
No, just Saito
I'll do it on my own
Will it be ok?
It will
I guess when you think of "Saito"
Trendy Angel
Saito
You think of Saito from Trendy Angel
Ohh, I guess so
You should stop being "Saito"
How about "Kinoshita" or such instead?
Come on, I'm Saito
And it's Mr. Saito for you!
That was uncalled for
What a great day, today
I'm pumped!
I'm full of energy, you heard me!
Which position are you aiming for?
Well, Bob Sapp isn't a comedian, right?
Bob Sapp: 4th on the list
That's right
Then I'm aiming higher than that, for sure
I'm not going to lower your expectations
I won't make any excuse about being nervous
I see
I'll go full power on this!
Who's the same age as you?
Naomi Watanabe
Naom-- oh, she did this before?
Naomi Watanabe...
She didn't
Yamazaki, are you a senior to them?
Are you asking me if I'm older then them?
Tsukitei Housei
I'm hella older then them!
We're like 20 years old apart
Oh is that so? I thought you were closer
No way, not at all
Planning meeting
Man, you have tons of grey hair
Zaki-san
I thought getting a haircut would cover it a bit
It's pretty amazing
The white ones are increasing
Is that so?
Hm
Shichi-henge: start!
They were great on that episode
Ohh, thank you
Just for once
They felt smooth
Smooth you say?
If you watch him like that on a 4k tv
You can see how nasty his skin is
How about this?
I mean, you can easily enter there, let's do this
"Our Tanaka ZIP! Live-broadcast, questions & limits challenge!"
_____________________________________________________
Let's take it to ZIP
Our Tanaka
I think if I show there as "Our Tanaka"
note: A gag from another episode | find it @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
They won't ever call me again!!
That's not the point
What time is your show?
At 16:00
At 16:00, yes
Let's ask your lover first
What are you talking about-
Excuse me
I'm entering
Oh, sorry, excuse me
Well
I'll be your manager from now on
My name's Saito
Before you I used to be
2016 - New Member: Saito Shinji
The manager from Chidori, the duo
Lots of stuff happened with them
I know it sounds cheeky, but Chidori received
Chidori
A lot of advice from me when they came to Tokyo
At first, when they had shows in Kansai
Whenever there was a filming,
everyone thought they were there
But when they came to Tokyo,
at first they couldn't fit in
Nobu at first was a more playful character
And that made him kind of famous
But...
I told him that he could easily
become a great tsukkomi
I thought he wasn't being persuasive,
maybe because he was made fun of
But I knew he could do more
And when I told him to do like that,
he did, and started changing
And now they're having great success
So...
So I'd like to have a talk
With your current members,
to make Yoshimoto better
And maybe give you some good advice
First off
Let's talk about Cocorico
Yes?
Maybe it's not really
something good to say, but...
I don't think there's
Something special in your duo
I mean, as a duo
Of course you have the right spirit,
but your explosive power...
There's nothing special in it, isn't it?
No explosive power
罰金 = fine (1000￥)
That's not something good
I think that's your weakness
I don't even know what to say to you
It's so difficult when it comes to Cocorico!
Like, a lot!
I think you can solve this together
If you start thinking about it
I guess you can move
on to the upper stage
Am I right, Matsumoto-san?
Yes?
Let's change this Cocorico
Alright, we got it
- You got it? Good
Housei-san
I think you are
A really good person
But when you try to make
someone laugh, it backfires
Well, that's because you're
surrounded by such monsters
You're not the type who
can make someone laugh
Face it, Housei-san
Still
The problem here is Downtown
It's actually them
You know
Can I say it loud and clear?
I think you're not funny
when you're in tv shows like this
As much as you act like a duo
I wanted to say that
You're definitely better as a duo
Also, you're not feeling
that greedy, lately
You're not feeling it, right?
You're feeling pretty
satisfied, ain't you?
He's really satisfied!
He's ok with it
But you see
You should aim higher than that
Get one level higher
No, you could aim for two
If something can change now
That's you
Hamada-san
You can change as
a Downtown member
Do your best to become the
comedians I want to you to be
Please
Oh sorry, excuse me...
Yes, hello?
Yes
Your Shinkansen ticket?
Sorry
I'll take it for you, sorry for that
Please, put my advice into practice
Hamada-san
Now it's time to change
Excuse me
That was long!!
He got us good
Yeah, sorry for that
You know
He made us reflect
...or make a small donation @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Want to support? Like my FB page: facebook.com/shionnotsukai
more J-comedy @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
translation & subs by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Shichi-henge - Saito from Jungle Pocket
The phantasmagoric man's challenge!
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
That Hamada's Cram School...?
What's that "Hamada's Cram School Trip"?
What is Yoshimoto doing?
I want to do that
Yeah but that's kind of...
Is there someone on his thirties here...?
Jusme?
Jusme
It's jusme
Someone with short sleeves?
Oh, jusme?!
It's jusme, oh, jusme
Jusme?!
Starting from who?
Oh, fromme?
Fromme
Who's goin' next?
Amigoin'?
Imgoin'
Amigoin'...?
Come on, who's next?
Isitme?!
Imgoin' again
Itzzmee
Who wants to go next?
Shoudigo?
Amigoin'?
Next one?
Come on, next one?
Isitme?!
Itzzme
Itzme
Shoudigo?
Amigoin'?
Shoudi?
Itzme
Shoudido the last one?
How did this happen?
Wasitme?
Itwazme!
note: Atasu = weirdly pronounced "Watashi" ("I", "me")
One by one took so long!!
That was amazing, though
Was it a coincidence?
- It was
Was it?
staff) it was a coincidence
So it wasn't on purpose, huh
The best part was he turned it at the end
Don't you think?
I didn't know what was going on
It was a lucky first-shot
I wonder how it went yesterday
Yesterday was hard
Just thinking about it...
I think I really lost my temper there
I even read the horse name wrong
But still...
So today I started talking about the main race
But you see...
There are lots of match races
I have to take back the
money I've lost yesterday
I'm sure I can do it!
There are tons of em
I'll get some right for sure
Alright
Let's start the bets
You see at this point I think that
You can all go home by now
'Cause I think I can do yours too
But you see, the real problem
here is how will it unfold
I think it's going to change, so
you can't tell anything from the start
Geez... but
If that happens it's bad
'Cause it will be all about chances
But, you see...
Something like that can happen
The main problem is
once the 1,9 km is passed
Just after the 1,9 km distance
There aren't much choices after that
Ugh.. this is...
Here
This is... here
You saw it, right?
The forecast
And you came here 'cause you saw it
But why did you look at it?
Doesn't it ruin it?
Don't underestimate us risk takers
It's not good, really
Got it?
What's the point on coming
here if so? Think about that
So goddamn persistent
Everyone: safe
All the way to the end
He likes horse races right?
I saw him on a show
He likes them, and plays too
I hope not like that
No but it's true
There are dopesters
Who use seals that quick in Oi Racecourse
I think he was mocking them
If so...
I think we have to apologize to them too
I guess it wasn't that clear
Where'd ya go?
Get outta here
Ya gettin' another one, ya punk
What the hell?
Couldn't they leave together before?
It stinks!!
It stinks
- It does stink
It reeks
Can we
Open the windows?
One spit would have been enough
Is there an air freshener?
- That should do it
It stinks!
Spray it over there
Sorry for this
We're sorry
This has to be done
Sorry for the trouble, we didn't know
I must say, this scene
Is making me wanna pay 1000 yen
This view is hilarious
Geez
What a weird way to bother someone
We're sorry!
\
The freshener didn't do much
First off, no need to be that nervous, ok?
I'm here today to give
you guys some advice
And I think it you
will benefit from it
First of all, why
You, why are you in this world?
Well, it's...
Since when I was little
I dreamed about getting on tv
I see
Look,
After all
I think that it's quite difficult to succeed
If you don't have the right attitude
To give to this industry
everything you got
Take me for example
I got my debut work
You know?
From an actress, and...
So, my debut work...
Its offer rained down on me
You know what made me have it?
Sleeping with her
The fact I slept with her
This feeling is important
And I know you guys
Haven't *** since ages
But if you do like me
You'll be rich
You'll get em all in your dressing room
And they'll jump towards you
Do you really think
it's not a bad life?
I even had this
bathrobe prepared ahead
That basically means I'm a king, right?
Right?
Isn't it so?
Anyway, I've been thinking
Your body is great, huh?
One can tell you worked out
But see, the problem is
Only 20% of nowadays
women likes macho men
The remaining 80% is different
You should know that feel, don't you?
That's why girls don't approach you
Really
What girls really like
Are plump guys, like me
This kind of body
It makes em feel protected
Or something like that
Don't you all think so?
Believe me
A woman feels secure with this
So, if you have time to
work out to become a macho
Find some time to
do researches on girls
You won't be able
to move on until you ****
Don't you want to get
in the real marketing worl--
See?
That's a sign
Come on...
Not fair
Seriously, think about that
All these happenings
That...
That was amazing
It felt like a forced termination
＊all the collected money will be devolved by NTV to the Kobato cultural company
I mean, the chime and everything
Even the falling thing over there, all coincidences
Could it be that he knew we had the windows opened?
That's possible, you're right
It could be
Sorry for that
Also, Endo, he asked you that
And you replied with
your honest comedian feelings
That felt weird
How about something more
Abstract?
Well, he asked me "why am I in this world"
coming next: a man who will perform "chicken rice"!
I tought "man, Endo's such an idiot"!
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
That felt too normal--
Today is Christmas ♪
♪  "Chicken Rice" (2004)
singer: Masatoshi Hamada | lyrics: Hitoshi Matsumoto
The whole city is lively and festive ♪
I won't feel at ease eating turkey ♪
I'm still going with chicken rice ♪
Today is Christmas ♪
The whole city is lively and festive ♪
I won't feel at ease eating turkey ♪
I'm still going with chicken rice ♪
Today is Christmas ♪
The whole city is lively and festive ♪
I won't feel at ease eating turkey ♪
I'm still going with chicken rice ♪
Today is Christmas ♪
The whole city is lively and festive ♪
I won't feel at ease eating turkey ♪
I'm still going with chicken rice ♪
Today is Christmas ♪
The whole city is lively and festive ♪
I won't feel at ease eating turkey ♪
I'm still going with chicken rice ♪
So irritating
Today is Christmas ♪
The whole city is lively and festive ♪
I won't feel at ease eating turkey ♪
What the hell was that?
Man he's so pushy
coming next: a man who came from the future to protect Gaki!
Yeah he's like that
He was
He made me laugh    - It was fun
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Well, but...
That's all we have
Everyone, get out
Get out, quick
Get away from here
Listen to me
I came from the future
A meteorite is about
to crash right here
You know what it means?
If a meteorite crashes down, Gaki will end
I came from the future
so I know that for sure
The meteorite is about to---
get out, quick!!
Run away, now!
It's not saf--- here comes!
Get away from here, now!
Do you want Gaki to end?!
Get outta here!
Go away!
Get away
Matumoto, get away
Why are you not going away?
Just get away!
Cocorico!
Get away from here!
What are y---
Go, now!
Quickly!
Please, get away now
Hamada...
Matsumoto...
Do you both want Gaki to end?!
Get outta here, it's going to explode
Quick
Just leave this to me
Macchan
Run away
Is it ok to you to let Gaki die?
Are you fine with it?!
Hamada...
What's wrong with you two?
Are you ok with it?
For real?!
Is it ok to you if this show ends?
What are you gonna do, Housei?
Am I right?
Are you ok with it?
Matsumoto...
Get over here
I'm stopping this meteorite for you
See? That's how much I care
But if that explodes
It's the end
Cocorico!!
That's your time to shine
Don't you want to get on stage again?!
Cocorico!
You know what to do, right?
What's with your lack of activity, recently?
Really, guys
This is your chance to show your strength!
Aim higher!
Hamada, you should be more greedy
One like you can go way higher
You guys...
I have to go, whatever happens
Get away from here
You can't let
Gakitsuka die!
It exploded
Hamadaaaaaa!
He wanted to say something at
the end, he shouted your name
I have no idea
Oh? Wait a second
That's a lot
It's 51'000 yen
What?!
51'000 yen
He placed sixth
51'000 yen?
Amazing!
Really, it is
Thank you!
You're sixth with 51'000 yen!
Sixth?!
- Yeah
I'm so happy
Let's ask the freshener about it
Did that smell? Sorry for that
More Gaki & japanese comedy @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Updates, news & more @ facebook.com/shionnotsukai (like it!)
Want to support? Donate few $ @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
this is a no-profit fansub, made by a fan for other fans