0 0 m -300 -65.625 b -310.75 -67 -339.875 -65.625 -336.875 -41.25 b -338.375 -27.75 -309.25 -1 -301.5 0 b -289.25 7.625 -284.625 -1 -277 -2.5 b -267.75 -11.625 -258.625 -14.625 -249.375 -37.125 b -246.25 -58 -266.25 -59.625 -267.75 -61.375 b -280 -67 -290.75 -65.625 -300 -65.625 m -292.375 -58 b -278.5 -61.375 -260.125 -52.375 -263.125 -43.125 b -273.875 -54.875 -283.125 -54.875 -292.375 -58 m -370.625 -189.875 b -364.375 -189.875 -312.25 -179.5 -320 -110.625 b -330.625 -67 -359.875 -46 -369 -41.25 b -373.625 -39.875 -398.125 -20.625 -431.875 -52.375 b -439.625 -67 -455 -83.875 -444.25 -121 b -439.625 -136 -431.875 -164.875 -404.375 -181 b -396.625 -185.25 -384.375 -193 -370.625 -189.875 m -232.5 -193 b -229.375 -193 -192.625 -203.5 -160.375 -148 b -155.75 -134.5 -143.5 -117.75 -151.25 -76 b -160.375 -41.25 -175.75 -39.875 -185 -37.125 b -192.625 -37.125 -203.375 -27.75 -240.125 -53.5 b -252.5 -63.75 -270.875 -70 -278.5 -112 b -277 -112 -295.375 -139.25 -257 -181 b -249.375 -187.375 -241.75 -193 -232.5 -193 m -373.625 -143.5 b -416.625 -136 -392 -89.5 -372.125 -94.25 b -366 -94.25 -352.125 -97.375 -349.125 -117.75 b -353.75 -142.375 -362.875 -140.25 -373.625 -143.5 m -373.625 -129.875 b -364.375 -133.125 -359.875 -121 -361.375 -117.75 b -361.375 -106.375 -370.625 -106.375 -375.125 -106.375 b -381.25 -107.375 -384.375 -113.5 -382.875 -121 b -382.875 -124.125 -379.75 -129.875 -373.625 -129.875 m -370.625 -124.125 b -375.125 -122.375 -373.625 -116.75 -370.625 -116.75 b -367.5 -116.75 -364.375 -122.375 -370.625 -124.125 m -221.75 -143.5 b -255.5 -137.5 -240.125 -91 -221.75 -95.25 b -215.625 -94.25 -200.25 -97.375 -200.25 -124.125 b -204.875 -142.375 -217.125 -143.5 -221.75 -143.5 m -221.75 -129.875 b -201.875 -129.875 -208 -106.375 -218.75 -106.375 b -221.75 -104.625 -234 -107.375 -231 -121 b -231 -124.125 -229.375 -129.875 -221.75 -129.875 m -218.75 -124.125 b -223.25 -121 -220.25 -115 -217.125 -116.75 b -212.5 -117.75 -215.625 -124.125 -218.75 -124.125 m -376.75 -116.75 b -379.75 -116.75 -378.25 -112 -376.75 -112 b -375.125 -112 -373.625 -116.75 -376.75 -116.75 m -223.25 -115 b -226.375 -115 -224.875 -110.625 -223.25 -110.625 b -221.75 -110.625 -220.25 -115 -223.25 -115
0 0 m -455 -217.125 l -142 -217.125 l -142 86.875 l -455 86.875 m -145 -214.125 l -451.875 -214.125 l -451.875 84.25 l -145 84.25
TPF
Memory inn!!
Shocking Confessions!
It was a good bath
Tanaka you want to drink beer, right?
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Oh really?
Cocorico
Tanaka Naoki
He drinks a lot recently
Tanaka was like "I wanna drink, I wanna drink"
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Wow really? You...
So everyone shall we have a toast?
For real?
Yamazaki Housei
Then I don't want any
Just have one drink, c'mon
Hamada-san, you should have some
Really?
You're gonna wish you had some later
Definitely
It's a good excuse
"I was drunk so it's okay"
If you can say that that's good
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Otviss
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
Ayumi
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on Youtube
individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own. Please go back and
support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit. You can
download episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching!
Translator:
Typesetter:
____________________________________________________________________
But it was a good bath, right?
I could go again though
I could actually go...
Excuse me
... three more times
Maybe it's normal to think that way
Well that's...
At least three times
I'm going again tomorrow
A morning bath's pretty good
Let's take one before going home
John McClane
(Bruce Willis)
New York police officer John McClane attends
a party on a high-rise, but terrorists arrive...
Rec
「Die Hard」
I don't really...
I'm not very good with this one...
To tell the truth, I'm not really...
Rec
Whoever gets the "talker card must
talk about the given movie as their past
Then I'll be taking the middle one...
I wanted the middle one...
1, 2
Yes! That was close...
really close
You take baths many times over?
Isn't it like that? It's an onsen after all...
I would want to go maybe 3, 4 times?
To go again is kind of...
I might go now, actually...
For real??
Right now?
Um, before you go to the onsen again...
can I have a moment of your time?
What is it all of a sudden?
I want to go right now though
It will be really quick
What is it?
I don't
think that you'll believe me
This is from a while ago
but in the past
when I'd go a journey... or rather trip
a lot of things would happen
Isn't that something that happens to all of us?
Once, actually,
I was on a very tall building
and it was getting bombed, or no, there was a fire
and I got caught up in the terrorist attack
But I saved everyone
In the end I was just in a tanktop all messed up
I don't get this at all
Who the hell are you
I know you really won't believe me
But a few years later, I went abroad
and there were these bad guys
who took control of all the control towers
and all of the lights on the runway
went out so the planes didn't know where to land
so all of the planes
kind of fell
No, wait, so what were you doing then?
I was actually just traveling...
well not traveling but just kind of around
I don't get it at all
I'm sorry
Your story is kind of..
Then can I just say how I defeated the bad guys?
You defeated them?
Yeah in the end
That's amazing
There was a lot of engine oil leaking
so I used a zippo lighter or whatever it was
to set in on fire
So when the bad guys tried to leave
the fire flared up
their plane just went "BOOM"
everything ended well... but a few people died...
What are you even saying
Nothing ended well!
But with the least amount of casualties...
But some people died right
"with the least amount"...
"the least amount"...
I don't get it at all
I don't remember that incident
I just remembered it just now
So you stopped us when we were gonna take a bath
that's amazing... You're pretty tough
there was also the subway
when it exploded when I was walking
but I don't really remember that part
No, I get it
Yeah when it's the third time you don't really remember
If it was me...
"Oh, this again?"
I see...
I guess people go through a lot huh
Yeah
Fisherman Urashima Taro saves a turtle from being bullied,
then is taken to a mythical undersea palace as thanks
Rec
Urashima Taro
「Urashima Taro」
I'll take the last one
This one!
1, 2
So are we going to that bath?
Yes, let's
I want to go but there was a karaoke too right?
I want to go
For real? Then let's go
Actually can you wait a second
What is it?
Um, there's something I want to tell you I guess
This story is going to go way back, but
I was fishing by the sea and that was how I made a living
What?
You didn't have any period like that
Actually...
it was one day I went fishing like any other
and by the shore I saw a turtle being bullied
Oh really?
"Hey you there"
"Cut it out," and I stopped them
But then the turtle didn't leave
It kind of felt like he wanted me to get on his back
The bullied turtle?
Yes the one I saved
so I get on his back
and he goes straight into the sea
Why didn't you let go?
He was just so fast
So just let go
Just let go
and you can swim back up
Yes, that's true, but it was like he wouldn't let me
Isn't that just you then?
Yeah it's just you
Yes that true but
it was like I had lost the composure to
Y'know like when you go up somewhere too high and you lose the timing to let go
Is this gonna be a long story?
It shouldn't be too long now
What are you even talking about?
I don't understand what you're saying
So we just went and this sea bream and flounder
were really dancing
Dancing?
And this princess person showed up
and was like "if you're leaving"
Wow you really skipped... not that I know
Not that I know but yeah
"If you're leaving take this with you"
You got something?
Is was like some
wooden box and
so I get this wooden box
and I reach the shore and I'm like "What is it?"
It would bother you
She said it was a souvenir
and I opened it
and was very surprised
What happened?
This smoke...
Just came out
and I got the full force of it
and I turned like 80 years old
my aura did
Your aura...?
your aura?
My appearance's aura
Just your appearance?
Just for that moment?
I think he means it like that
But it's not like that now?
Not right now
But I used to be much younger
If it was the real me
I would be much younger
I don't really get it
I'm sorry, really
I guess we just aren't smart enough to understand
What were you even talking about?
But it's really true
Actually if I think about it now
it was like a dream
It was a dream
I don't really know if it's true
Why do we have to listen to a story about your stupid dream
Really
I just really wanted to say it now
So should we go take a bath?
I wanna go to the rocky one again
A mysterious bottle was actually home to a genie family,
discovered by Kan-chan, and they all cause mischief
Kan-chan
Rec
「The Genie Family」
This one
Sorry
1, 2
Yup, it's decided
You wanna go?
Let's go
Yes, let's
I'm sorry, but this is really
it will be over really soon
I promise it's really quick
What is it with you guys?
I'm sorry, I really am
What is it now?
It's really quick, but
Once I sneezed and a weird old dude came out of a vase
What the hell are you even saying
I'm really sorry
I would just sneeze a little
and out of the vase at home
a weird dude would just come out
What's with the weird old dude?
He looked like he came from Arabia or something
this weird old dude
Arabia?
I'm sorry it's just that an old dude from Arabia would come
and he looked maybe 47, or 48?
and he would come out
47, 48?
About right before 50
That's pretty old
Yeah that's pretty old
I would thought that it was really creepy and was wondering
Yeah that is creepy
if you all could help me solve this problem
That's... you must've been followed around
It might be a goa...ghostly kind of thing
He's not a bad guy though
If he's not hurting anyone...
Well, then let's go
shall we?
Let's go
Gorou takes Jun and Hotaru home to Furanou,
the stage where their growth takes place
Jun
Yoshioka Hidetaka
Rec
「From the Northern Country」
1, 2
So I guess we should go
Yup let's go
Wait wait wait wait a second please
it will be very short
A long time ago
I went to Hokkaido
and lived there a while
I've never heard this before
I had no idea
I thought you were from Nishinomiya
Well, Nishinomiya was
a place I lived once, then I went to Hokkaido
and in Hokkaido
I lived with
my dad, and my sister
all three of us
And we were all living together
But my dad
wouldn't really work
He didn't work?
But I guess it happens
So then
he was like "I want to build a bath by myself"
You really skipped huh
Self sufficiency...?
We didn't have water, gas, electricity... we had nothing
But he wanted to build a bath
Anyways my sister's name is Hotaru
And I was Jun
This is messed up
I was called that for some reason
this is so messed up
Aren't you Housei?
I guess your old man was selfish
He named you and then
And then he selfishly nicknamed you
Yeah he would nickname me
You were in Hokkaido the whole time?
Me?
Until you grew up I mean
But once
I came out to Tokyo
Oh really?
Did you work in Tokyo?
I did... in like a little factory
Oh really...
Why'd you go back?
Well, this is really
close to my heart but
I mean I don't really want to say but
I got to know this young girl
well...
we had
a child
she got pregnant?
Yes
Really
But I was young so we couldn't get married yet
so then my dad came from Hokkaido
and he brought
some radish and then...
he gives it to the young girl's father
right?
And then he got really angry
Well if he only brought radish, wouldn't you?
radish...
It's not much of an apology
some radish and some potatoes too
I don't really get it...
So vegetables, right?
Ones your dad made
Yes, because we had no money
I see, self-sufficiency....
I can't say any more now because I just remembered
We all cried together though, sorry.
No more
It's tough when you start to remember
What even is this
If he remembers...
It's so fragmented
what is this
Yeah it's too fragmented
I'm sorry, so many in a row
Well you can't help it
Can you just deal these out then
Yes, please
Please
then this one
this one
A slice of life about Kuruma Torajirou,
a vagabond's travels
Hiroshi
Gin Maeda
Rec
「It's Tough Being a Man」
1, 2
So let's go
Yup, let's go
Wait wait wait wait a second, will you?
Wait a second
No we're going
Wait wait wait
You know,
my little sister's...older brother...
Your little sister's older brother....
My...
That's a little
What is he saying
He said, "my little sister's older brother"
My wife's
Yes?
older brother
Oh, your wife's older brother
He was a little troubling
Troubling...?
Well what I mean is that he wouldn't really be at home
Well, that's...
So he was wandering around?
He had a lot of wanderlust
and he was trouble
and a lot of times he would complain about me
why would he do that?
Well, I don't know... there was a factory I worked at
A factory?
You worked in a factory?
Sorry, yeah... I used to work at a factory
And the boss would be so annoying
"your brother...."
The director, huh
And so I would be like
"Octopus Director!"
What director?
The director was completely bald
Oh, I see
the factory director
And I would see that and go, "Octopus Director!"
that's kind of rude
That's a little bad
Yeah yeah
But I guess
he was that kind of person
But he'd still sometimes be a little touching I guess
He'd be a little touching?
I don't get it at all
I thought it was just going to be bad things
He wasn't a bad man. he had little henchmen
Henchmen?
His hair was kind of scraggly
But he'd clean the shrine grounds
Was he a volunteer?
I don't really understand
the direction of the story
I'm sorry but anyways
I just wanted to say
that my wife's brother was a handful
I actually hadn't really interacted much with her brother
I only talked to him a little when he came home sometimes
So I never really had too much to do with him
So you were looking at him objectively?
Objectively?
So you weren't really in it
He is really into it
Well he is your brother right?
Step-brother
He was my step-brother but I never really knew him
He'd just come home sometimes and be like "Oh, Hiroshi"
Hiroshi?
Not Masatoshi?
He was probably mistaken
That's pretty...
That's pretty bad
That would suck
He was a handful, but he was a good person
You had such a point in your life?
Yup, yes
Really... In a factory?
that's kind of weird
I'm sorry, I really am
Everyone's weird
1, 2
Ugh~
Well I'm
going to go take a bath now
I wanna go to sleep
Yeah
Kenshirou
Kenshirou faces countless battles as he searches
for his fiancee Yuria in a world post-nuclear war
Rec
「Fist of the North Star」
Oh, shit
Shall we go now?
Should we go?
Wait
Before you go to sleep, will you listen to my story?
What is it now?
I wonder how many years ago it was....
wasn't Earth kind of in danger?
No, no it never was
Yeah there was no such thing
So like Nostradamus
but he was just saying that stuff
But listen
when I was little I was trained
by a lot of old men
What does he mean?
Do any of you know?
Know about the Hokutoken?
Isn't it a school of martial arts?
It is
You don't really hear about it though
So I was just walking down the street
and there are bad guys out there, y'know?
And those guys bring axes, you know?
For real?
An axe out of the blue?
An axe
So it's pretty dangerous
Yeah that is dangerous
So I was like "Atatatatata!"
What?
What is that?
That's the Hokutoken
Oh, so like a battle cry?
Yes, a battle cry
"Atatatatata!"
So like "Atatatatata!"
and I'd hit them
They taught me that
So...
I'm sorry, but none of this is coming through
So how do you do it? You have to do it more seriously
or we won't get it
Well it's actually pretty straightforward
So you take the stance
Why is it like this
It's weird, like a cat pose
Well they'd bring axes and stuff, so I dodge, then
"Atatatatata! Atatatatata!"
A lot of "Atatatatata!" is what I'd do
Basically
What happens to the other guy?
The other guy... His face gets messed up
And in the end, he explodes like "boom"
that's amazing
No way
You can do that?
Well, it's not exactly that I can do it
But it looks like I did
And I don't know what happened to that person
Huh?
Did they die?
I don't get it at all
What happened?
It's gone already
Well it's gone now but
did you know there were 7 little scars like this?
I've never seen them
I've never seen them either
Did they use to be there?
Yeah, seven right here
I don't recall ever having seen those
I had no idea
Well I guess from now on, with those stories...
You all are really weird
I guess if you come to a place like this that kind of thing happens
You're right
I don't like it
Go ahead
No more
1, 2
Finally
Should we go to sleep?
Yes let's go to sleep
Alright alright alright
Um, everyone
3-B's teacher Kinpachi Sakamoto solves
the many problems in his class
Katou Suguru
Rec
「3-B Kinpachi Sensei」
Wait a second wait a second wait a second
Shall we sleep?
Wait a second wait a second
What is it? Let's just go to sleep
I have something to tell you
Can you please let us sleep?
Yeah, you're right
Please wait a second! So um...
There's something I've been keeping from you this whole time
And if I think that we're gonna be in this together from now on
I felt like I had to tell you today
So it's a story from back when
I was still in school, but...
Oh really
so when I was in school
I've once been hit by my teacher
Well I guess that's something that happens
Yeah in our age they would do that
So I guess it was...
no joke
Anyways I was with my friend
and he hit me in the police station
You were arrested?
Yeah I guess I was also a little bit...
What'd you do?
Well it's a long story but
basically...
my school's teacher, well, my homeroom teacher
My homeroom teacher...
would say "If you put oranges near oranges"
"If you put them near rotten oranges they'll rot"
I would think, "What is he even saying?"
And before I knew it I was getting hit
What the hell?
How are you supposed to know?
"Before I knew it I was getting hit"
No... at my old middle school
I was pretty bad
And you transferred?
Yes I did
Yes
And the teacher I met at the school I transferred to was really good
But he had long hair
Long hair...
Well even if you say "long hair", its...
pretty normal
normal length
yeah, and he was really well-liked
And oftentimes he'd be on an embankment
and yell his class's name
His class name...?
So then I'd actually run to him
And be like this.... But I didn't even like him that much
Anyways he'd yell his class's name
The class he was homeroom teacher for?
Yes the class's name
What happens after that?
So there was like a rule that everyone had to go to him then
Wow that's a drag
What a drag
So what year and class was it?
That was 3-B.
Was it on a particular day?
I feel like it was on Fridays
So every time it was Friday...
What a drag!
he'd say his class's name
Well I liked him but in the end he really hit me hard
I didn't think I'd be hit that hard
Why were you hit if he was such a good teacher?
Yeah why?
Well that's because
I did something bad at school
I occupied the school? Well actually the details are a little...
Yeah you were still in school then
And the police got involved?
Yeah the police got involved
and it was a train crossing but
even though it was a train crossing
he went under it to get to me
in my mind
That long haired teacher?
So basically the police came and took you away right?
Yes they did, but
since it really was the first time it happened
it was kind of...
"If a teacher doesn't believe in his students"
"Then tell me!"
Wow you have a good memory
"Tell me what I should do!"
So it was like that and us students really liked him
He's a very passionate teacher
But then at a very different time
He'd be saying stuff like "I won't die"
The same person?
The same person, and he'd say stuff like "I won't die"
Why would he say such a thing?
I don't know... he was kind of weird
And sometimes he'd rage holding a hanger
What?
He was unprecedented
Yes he does seem that way
Yeah really
But somewhere along the way he started cold perming his hair
And that became this
That became like this, and after that like this
I'm very sorry, thank you
Congratulations
Thank you very much
This isn't just me, I also have family
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
And there's this too
And because this is this
And sometimes this
I'm very sorry, but thank you
Happy Birthday to You
Why "happy birthday"
Nobody thinks it's funny
Nobody at all!
No it was funny!
Not at all!
Everyone knew it so it was funny!