First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai!
My first one-man-show debut!
TKO Kinoshita's Shichi-henge!
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Too loud, don't you think?
That was incredible
What's your problem?
I mean, it's perfect for other occasions...
What are you talking about?
Like, in case of SOS or such
You know? It can come in handy
Alright, tonight we're having our 41st contestant
"First one-man-show", huh?
You know...
Me and the rest of the staff
Yeah?
Were all like "are we sure this guy hasn't done it before?"
So we made sure to check
And yes, he hasn't done it yet
No, right?
It felt so bizarre he didn't yet
We were all like "why hasn't he done it yet?"
Until now
We have huge expectations for him
Oh my
I'm gonna get so pissed at him if he scores lower than I imagine
Alright, here's our challenger, come in!
TKO's Kinoshita Takayuki
'Morning!
Here they are, Matsumoto
Kimoto Takehiro
Kinoshita Takayuki
Today's protagonist
I'm so nervous
What's up?  His partner is here too
You're setting me up
What are you talking about?
Why?
It was you who said "I really wanna do it"!!
That's not true
You told me that yourself
No way
I swear it's true
What are you talking about?
That's not what I mean
Last time we met after shooting High Tension
I had a meeting with the staff and they told me "sign here and you can take part in Shichi-Henge"
And I was like "I see... yes, I'd love to do it"
So, you said it
Of course I said it!!
Does it mean you don't really want to do it now?
No, I want to do it! It's literally the best job for me
That's not it
What the?
No way I'm not going to
That's not it
Matsumoto just before said it felt strange he still didn't take part in it, right?
He told me the same once
Really?!
"It wouldn't be strange if they'd call me, but they're not"
Are you an idiot?!  That's true
Are you a complete moron?
Are you double-crossing me?!
Seriously, is that it?
No, I just didn't say that!
- But you did
He told his manager
"Shichi-henge is what I need right now to step up my game"
Is that so?
I have no idea why he's trying to hide it
Which one is it then?
You said it, exact same words
You wanna do it?
Of course, to me it's like a person you like so much you don't wanna meet
What?
Yes?
Who--?
I mean...
Who are you talking about?!
I mean, this episode
What the hell
I like it so much I'm afraid to take part in it
Take a look at our previous contestants
Here they are
That's how it is
I see
Have you seen any?
- All of them, actually
And how high are you aiming?
At least above the smaller characters part
So, above the 20th?
- Shocking!
- That's right
I mean, yeah...
I still have only 6 transformations at the moment, after all
Huh? What do you mean?
What was that?
At this point
I have no idea if he's joking around or simply anxious
Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
MORE EPISODES: SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FOR UPDATES: FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
FOR DONATIONS: KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
EARLY ACCESS TO SUBBED CONTENT & SOFTSUBS, UPLOAD SCHEDULE
AND MORE TO COME BY BECOMING A PATRON ON PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TKO Kinoshita's Shighi-henge
An unexpected turn of events right off the bat!!
What's in there?
Plan meeting
Let's do this one, with Momiji
Oh, a Kyoto trip?
"Matsumoto Hitoshi & Yamamura Momiji's trip around Kyoto"
Gaki no Tsukai plan meeting
"A trip around Kyoto", huh
You like her, don't you?
Well, in one of many ways, yes
Oh, please
I don't know why but I always picture her with red eyes
(momiji = red leaves)
Must be her name
- Yeah
Shichi-henge: start
Ah, makes sense
Kinoshita is nervous, feeling the pressure of his first one-man skit
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
Shichi-henge - Rules
The contestant enters the room with a set of disguises
Whoever laughs at his skits must pay 1000 yen per round
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 15 l 25 15 l 25 0 l 0 0
Which transformation will he show us?
Right?
I see...
Not bad
Wow
What should we do?
Don't know
Same problem every time
Can you please
Give me any sort of job?
I wanna join your show
I'll do anything
If I can choose...
I'd like to be an AP
assistant producer
You know why?
Because the producer has to be on site, no way
The director has to review the footage, and his assistant is always busy
But the AP...
I feel like I can do it
I want to meet TV stars
Waiting for them in front of the elevator
And ESH--- escort them to the backstage
The same when they're done
From the backstage to the elevator
Well...
I can't deny I like TV stars
That's why I want to be part of a TV show
Alright
I'll be an AP
I'm gonna get busy soon
Alright alright, time to get busy
I'll give it my best!
I'm coming here tomorrow around 3 P.M.
Or is it ok if it's 4 P.M.?
Alright then
You're gonna make good use of me
And the same goes for you, guys
Alright, I'm an AP
I almost laughed, but for a different reason!
But we're all safe, right?
Everyone: safe
Are you ok, guys?
He got really nervous
Like, crazy nervous
He was, right?
Man, he was so nervous!
Yeah, I can tell
That stutter almost got me there...
That's the type of stuff you gotta watch out for
You were almost literally laughing, Hamada
Not true, not true
But I was about to, I didn't know what to expect
You saw him, right?
And after he was done, there was sweat everywhere
Right on the table, I was like "oh boy, he's dying"
Right
I think it didn't go as he planned it to
Yes, definitely
I think that's how it went
Makes sense
He probably thought "that's the part where they'll laugh"
Yes, definitely
That's it
He put everything at stake
On the line, yeah
Does he usually sweat that much?
He does
Everytime I glanced at him, it kept on flowing down
That's true
You know, he did a surgery to stop his forehead sweating
Are you kidding?
I'm not
They do this surgery here to stop you from sweating
But it doesn't seem to work
It really didn't
Yeah, his... his sweat is stronger
So it was useless after all
I swear, he really did
And he still sweats?
Saying he wanted to be an AP...
Mmhh...
Yeah
What's going on?
What...
What is this?
I'm freaking out
I can feel a button... is it going to set me free?
I'm pressing it
I'll press it!
No way!
It hurts like hell
W-wait--
My right eye hurts like hell
Is there something I can do about it?
This--
I've reached my limit here
I can't stand this
Please-- what can I do?
Penalty
I think I'm safe
It hurts
What was that?
Why on the same button?
Again?
It started again
What does this mean? What's going on?
Is this a bug or something?
What's the meaning of this?
What the-
What's going on?
What the hell!
Put them in
Did you see that?
That's crazy
It almost came off at the beginning
I saw that
That's no good at all, to have it coming off
I mean
He fiddled with it too much
He was just doing this and it almost came off
I couldn't believe it
Geez...
The collected money will be given to the Kobato foundation
That wasn't really safe
Yeah, it's dangerous  His right eye...
You can tell he was in trouble
Right
At one point he was so hurt that he
took the mask off while talking
Yeah, I saw that
Over his eye, yes
And from that point on, a waterfall of sweat
It never stopped since then
Right, absolutely right
Goddamn it...
Penalty
His face...
Take a look at his face...
His face
Penalty
Please, look at him
Look at him
Penalty
This is so dumb
What the hell was that
He scored a lot with this one
Yeah, this one was good
But again, I saw more sweat drops than teardrops
They just won't stop
Not many tears there, but oh boy the sweat
Nice, huh?
Feels nice?
It feels so nice to me
Don't you think so?
It's good to play around once in a while, right?
Right?
Wanna sit down a bit?
Like this, there
Don't you think it's great to play around once in a while?
You're great, don't you know that?
If you were only a bit cuter I'd be nervous
But you're just fine
She's just about right, ain't she?
Am I right, huh? I found a really good one, right?
Look at her! Isn't she just fine?
Penalty
So fine, right? Very very fine
If you think she's fine, raise your hand
Penalty
You think so too, right?
We got it, we got it
Yes? That's nice! Don't you think you're fine too?
Don't you?
You got here just fine when I asked you
I mean, you came as soon as I called you
Right?
What the hell is he talking about?
Really, it's just fine
Go away, idiot
He's an idiot
Shall we go? It's the best time to go
Go away
This is fine
Really good
He's such an idiot
That was fun
It was really fun, yeah
Yeah, can't deny it
I'm not sure that girl knew what was going on
I think so too
What do you think was on her mind during it?
I don't think she got it
Right, I don't think so
Oh boy
Penalty
What the-?
Was that a monster or something?
Sounded like one
He was fighting something incredible
That's crazy
It's funny how only during the
tug of war skit he didn't sweat that much
You're right
It's the opposite
You're right, I expected him to sweat more
A rush of penalties on the chaotic second half?!
Coming up
That should have been normal
Sorry, excuse me
Hello?
I'm at work-- why are you calling me?
I told you not to call me
I'm done with you Taro
Because you
You kept me that secret
And I couldn't do anything
And yet you're calling me now
I can't now, everyone's here I just--
I'm telling you I can't
I told you so last time, didn't I?
Alright...
One last time, ok?
Excuse me
He's waving the pincers up to the sky
You got your eyes on somethin' good
Fresh and delicious crab dishes
Ah, Kyoubashi is such a nice place
Come here to Grand Chateau
He's waving the pincers up to the sky
You got your eyes on somethin' good
Fresh and delicious crab dishes
Sorry for disturbing your work
Tetteteetetette ♪
Teetettetette ♪
Penalty
This is where he sweated the most
He was drenched!
Oh, stop
I almost laughed thinking about the sweat
That was something
Oh boy
Feels like he's a human being
Why does it feels like it?
You, kid!
Wait
Isn't this my bicycle?
Where do you think you're going?
I just got in that store for a moment
Grrrrrr
And you stole my bicycle
Penalty
Where are you going?!
Some people would say
Maybe you stole it out of a sudden impulse
But still...
That doesn't give you the right to steal it!!
Did you steal it?
Is that how you're being educated?!
Is that how your dad has raised you?!
Penalty
Which one did you want?
In the end?
Huh?
Oi, shitty brat
You shitty brat!
Tell me the truth
Penalty
Did you steal it and realized there was a
dog in it, or did you focus on the dog?
You fucking brat!!
Which one is it?
Penalty
Answer me, you piece of shit
Shitty brat!!
Penalty
Shitty fuckin' bratfuck!!
Are you crying, huh?
Are you?
Is he?
Penalty
That dog is incredible
He's drenched in sweat!
That's too much
Can someone sweat that much?!
Do you like it?
Such big sweat drops
Do you like dogs?
Hey
Do you like dogs--
You fucking brat!!
Come here, shitty brat!
Come on...
Holy cow
It's finally time for the results!!
coming up
That was so funny on so many levels
Alright
It's 40'000 yen
Oh my, 40'000 yen
40'000 yen
Tenth place
You're currently tenth
Nice
That's where you wanted to be!
Wow, tenth!
That last one was really something
Oh, I'm glad
That was really good
We laughed so much at that
We all thought the same today: can a human sweat that much?
That's right
Man, human potential is unbelievable
It came out when I didn't expect it to
Yeah, with big drops too
And that shitty brat didn't have a drop on him
So smooth, not even a particle
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
MORE EPISODES: SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FOR UPDATES: FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
FOR DONATIONS: KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
EARLY ACCESS TO SUBBED CONTENT & SOFTSUBS, UPLOAD SCHEDULE
AND MORE TO COME BY BECOMING A PATRON ON PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI