The first "Gaki no Tsukai Ya Arahende" Chiki Chiki
Personally Special Song Drive!
COCORICO
DOWNTOWN
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Hosei
Yes yes!
We're going for a drive today.
That's right! But since it's this weather,
let's watch how long it takes Irie to get angry from being in the rain.
He's getting really wet!
Holding the Chiki Chiki banner for 22 years
Irie Yutaka
Super Veteran Prop
Let's do this for 30 minutes.
He's been there for ages!
He just stays there.
He's still smiling though.
Yes, well he's still smiling now.
Anyway, everyone brought their favourite albums today.
And songs you want us to hear.
As they drive, the five will play "personally special" songs and explain an episode behind it.
Today's Theme
Good songs that you think "I've got this memory about!"
We've prepared some!
I'd like you all to reveal some.
What's this?
Oh, thank you very much.
Yes so...
Hamada-san! I knew you'd be curious about this!
Why do you always have an item like that recently?
He had a thing for the "Hit and Wear Scissors Paper Rock" too!
Yeah.
Socks!
Oh yeah socks!
But the audience were apparently saying my socks were cute.
And that's....
Yeah but what is it?
What? They're my CD's.
Oh you put it in there?
I've got quite a lot so, I put it in this.
A lot?
Yes, I can't tell you much though.
Even during this pointless talk, Irie is still enduring it.
That's right!
I think that annoyed him a bit.
But seriously....
Songs that we have attachments to.
Well I'm sure there are some related to the rain too but...
There are heaps.
But you haven't chosen any have you?
Well, I wonder...
So how is it then everyone?
Somebody may have chosen one.
But I really thought "Yamazaki's so stupid" before.
Wait a second! Why?
Well we've got this corner today right?
Yes.
And we were in the dressing rooms together right?
He was friggin' singing it.
I was like "He's such an idiot!
What? A song that he's gonna play?
That's right. He's probably thinking in his head like....
Whaaat?
"I really like this song~"
He was casually humming it during a normal conversation.
And I was thinking "Man, he's totally gonna use that..."
I've heard several songs already!
You have right?
I couldn't help it!
Seriously...he's so stupid~
Are you excited or something?
I am~!
Because you want us to hear?
Well no, it got stuck in my head when I was choosing.
That's what I thought.
And it just comes out.
Can I play some now?
Yeah I think so.
Can I play one of mine then?
Yes please.
I'd like to hear yours.
I wonder what you think about this one.
It's the first track on here so...
This is it.
I still don't know...
I know this! This one already?
Don't you know Tanaka!?
No I don't.
Ma~n! I'll tell you later!
What the hell?
Honey cherry, even a tired heart ♪
is sexily "Shakin' in the night" ♪
This is... Sano-san's
A nighttime merry-go-round, I'm always a lost acrobat ♪
"Downtown Boy" but...
1981 October release
Downtown Boy/ Sano Motoharu
Matsumoto was 18 years old
This used to be the entrance music for Downtown.
Match the rhythm of Marvin Gaye's sad soul ♪
Oh really!? That's nice.
Because it's called "Downtown Boy".
Except I didn't know this song when we made our name "Downtown".
I'm about to lose someone's love in this city again.
I didn't really even know Sano-san that much.
Downtown Boy ♪
But one time someone asked "Are you guys fans of Sano Motoharu?"
Was it Inomoto?
So I found out this song existed and
I decided to make this our entrance music.
Because it matched us nicely.
But the mixer was this stubborn old geaser
and he won't play it unless if you ask him
and go give him a carton of cigarettes or something.
Are you serious?
Won't he play it otherwise!?
That's how it was in the old days.
What? So you have to bribe him?
It's not a bribe!
It's so that he'll do his job happily.
They'd also set the mic too low otherwise.
Whaaat!?
We went to the centre mic and it was way down here.
But that's just being spiteful!
That was common back then.
It's like saying "You're not good enough yet"
We also didn't have a master.
Yeah, that's why we had to take a carton or a bottle.
You had it tough!
But our voices got trained a bit because of that.
Our voices got louder.
Can I go next then?
I've also got Sano-san!
You're gonna continue with Sano-san?
Might as well listen to a different one...
Plus why would you already say, "Sano-san"?
Yeah, "I've also got Sano-san!"
Everything is crumbling apart.
You're a mess!
If you stayed silent we'd been like "Sano-san again!?"
Right, being surprised after listening.
It's something you'd know in your 2nd year.
You'll know in your 2nd year of other jobs too, not just comedy.
This is also the first track.
Oh the first track?
Here it is!
Don't you know it? Wait.
No no, baby!
It's Rock and Roll!
A lamplight beckoned me like a goddess~ ♪
A lamplight beckoned me like a goddess♪
Yeah, I like this one.
Right?
Yeah.
1981 February release
Kimi Wo Sagashiteiru (Asaga Kurumade)/ Sano Motoharu
Yamazaki was 13 years old
The small birds of the night rest their wings on the guard rail♪
The small birds of the night rest their wings on the guard rail ♪
I can't understand what he's singing!
And you have to talk of an episode. Not sing the song.
Are you gonna start singing Zaki-san?
Why're you singing happily?
I don't really have a story.
It has to have some importance to you!
We could have 20 songs if that's the case!
Exactly!
We could play all of Momoe-chan songs right from her debut!
Yamaguchi Momoe: Very popular idol of their generation.
Yeah that's right!
Really?
Say your age when you heard this and stuff.
I was in high school.
So it was still when Downtown were opening acts and I was a student.
And I was most interested in music while in high school
and in this song you can't tell if he's talking or like...
♪ Even if it's somebodies trap ♪ Like that.
You're making fun of him aren't you?
No I'm not!
It was quite fresh for its time.
It's right between singing and talking.
Listen to this bit!
In one hand is a jewel, and in the other hand
there is a violent passion beginning to howl ♪
Shut up! I can't hear!
I want to listen but can't hear!
Go Tanaka!
Yes, I...
Tanaka we're entering the highway.
Highway?
Have you got a good one?
I didn't... prepare a song to suit the highway....
Never mind!
9th track.
9th track?
Yes, excuse me, please play it.
Unicorn!
It's Daimeiwaku
Ah right.
1989 April release
Daimeiwaku/  Unicorn
Tanaka was 18 years old
This is the song that prompted me to enter this business.
Why?
Well, I went to a design school after finishing high school but
I had to do a massive graduation project
where I had to make heaps of panels and
I was so late at finishing it that they told me I couldn't graduate.
But just around the time I was worried about not graduating,
Endo came back to Osaka from working in Kagawa and
became a part-timer so he'd come to my house everyday
and help me with my project, morning, day and night
for  7 or 10 days.
And thanks to that I somehow made the deadline and graduated.
And the whole time I worked at home I...
Played this song?
Played this song.
Endo worked on that project so much that
I think of it as his work.
He doesn't seem good at that stuff.
I could do it though.
And I graduated, but there was no way
I could get a job if I graduated at that timing.
So then Endo said, "Do you wanna try out comedy together?"
and since Endo worked that hard for me
I decided to answer his call and spent 19 years in this business.
Yeah, this will be our 19th year.
I played this song everyday.
So this makes you remember that?
That's right.
You had always planned to team up with Tanaka right?
Yes I did.
Yamazaki, since you didn't have an episode,
can you stop butting into other peoples'?
Why not?
He comes in from time to time.
This is what it's about!
I really do have a special attachment to this.
Can I go next then?
Oh yes sure.
It's the 12th track.
12th track...?
The 12th track?
So Tanaka said before that I invited him to Osaka
and work together but
this came out the year we started.
It's Nagabuchi-san's album "Japan"
Oh, yes it is.
Yes.
It's called "Tokyo Seishun Asayake Monogatari".
Oh, this is a popular one.
Yes.
1991 December release
Endo was 20 years old
Tokyo Seishun Asayake Monogatari/ Nagabuchi Tsuyoshi
Well it's just as the lyrics say,
"From today, I will become a person of Tokyo♪"
It totally matched us when we came to Tokyo.
Also, at the time I worked part-time at a cafe and
Tanaka worked at a hall in Shibuya but,
I think you all know, he has hairy arms.
Yeah, his arms are bushy as.
Yes, and the third day after he got the job,
a customer complained about his hairy arms
and he got moved to the kitchen.
For real?
Yes, it was like a cafe where girls gather.
It was stylish.
Did they say it was gross?
That's right!
It's not very clean.
I thought, "Tokyo is tough".
And that's when we were listening to this song.
It was the same for us right?
Please play yours Hamada-san.
It's your birthday today right Hamada-san?
It's the 14th track.
Urgh, make it the 1st track you guys!
I wonder what Hamada-san's is?
He's probably planning something unexpected.
No, no, no. They're all cliche songs.
This song is really popular.
Yeah!
It's Morita Kensaku.
Yes, Morita Kensaku's...
"Let's Say Goodbye To Tears"
1971 March release
Hamada was 8 years old
Namida Ni Saraba To Iou/ Morita Kensaku
This was the theme for a drama.
Yep!
We never dreamed that he'd become a governor.
How old were you then Hamada-san?
I was in primary school.....
grade 3 or 4, I think?
Hamada matured faster than us.
Why!?
Because this drama was watched more by
people slightly older than our grade.
So it's normal if you had an older brother or sister but
he was the eldest son and still watched it so
he must have.....
had bushy d#*k hairs.
The day after an episode finished airing, I went to school
and I'd always sing this song with Takasu.
Takasu-san watch it too?
Yeah he did.
Oh, Takasu did too?
Yeah.
We sang it together e~veryday!
My older sister liked it so...
I watched it a fair bit too.
Someone go then.
Oh should we? Can I go then?
Go Yama-chan.
May I?
Yes.
The volume is different depending on the CD.
Don't know it.
What's this?
This was....
my alarm while in high school.
Who is it?
It's a band called X-Ray.
Heavy metal?
You had heavy metal as your alarm?
It was my alarm. Seriously!
What did they say before? Xton?
It's X-Ray
It's a song called "Question" by X-Ray.
1984 Januray release
Yamazaki was 16 years old
question/ X-RAY.
Questio~n!
So they suddenly say "Question"?
Is it just that we don't know who they are or....?
Do only core fans know them?
Well, yes I'd say so.
Heavy metal was very popular then, with
Foreign groups like Michael Schenker Group, Van Halen and Rainbow.
For Japanese metal there was Loudness and Earthshaker and stuff
and there was the young "Kodomo Band" too.
And they're basically a bit.....
Ummm....
It got turned off.
It got turned off quite quickly.
It's too loud.
Questio~n!
Questio~n♪
Why did you make this your alarm?
I was bad at waking up.
I think it was 6:40am, it goes,
QUESTIO~N!
Oh really.
Well I suppose you'd have an attachment to it then...
Right, he listened to it every morning!
Your mother must have been worried. QUESTIO~N!
"What's that boy doing?"
That's the real question.
Okay, Tanaka.
Yes. This was a bit of a....
shock to me and it's a song choice related with my dad.
It's not something I listened for my own liking.
Don't you know it yet?
We know it right?
Yeah.
Listen a bit longer.
It's Atsumi Jirou right?
Yes! It's "Yumeoi zake".
1978 February release
Tanaka was 6 years old.
Yumeoi-zake/ Atsumi Jirou
My dad really loved this record and
would always play it at home and make me listen as a kid.
Anyway, once every year at the summer festival
we'd have a karaoke contest in the neighborhood
and usually we'd have it at a spacious park but
it was raining, and so, because we lived near a highway
we had the contest under an overhead road.
We did it every year right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And my dad was intent on singing this so
he practiced all the time at home.
So the contest started but he still wasn't any good.
And I was watching this as a kid but...
when he was nearly finished singing,
another drunk person there yelled
"You suck!" or something.
It was the first time seeing my dad get harassed
so it was a huge shock!
Because he used to be like an absolute power.
Well yeah, that's right.
But that dad was getting yelled "You suck~!"
After practicing that much.
He practiced so hard, so it was a shock.
But I often remember the rain and other distinct details
from that time when I hear this song or when it's raining.
Thank you.
This is my trauma song.
Well okay.
I think this is from the same year as you, Downtown.
When I was in high school, all I did was baseball and...
This is your trauma song right?
Yes.
Ohhh! No this is 1 or 2 years before us.
Before?
Yep.
I know it.
Right?
Yes I do.
It became really popular.
It's "Take A Chance" right?
"Namida no Take A Chance" and we were in 1st grade of junior high
1984 December release
Namida no Take A Chance/ Kazami Shingo
Endo was 13 years old
and break dancing became very popular because of this song.
Anyway, all I did was baseball ever since primary school
and the only other thing I decided to try a little bit was
break dancing to this song.
There's a bit in the song where Kazami Shingo break dances but
I fully copied that and danced my hardest in front of everyone
but they just erupted in laughter.
They said "What'cha doing En-chan?"
Even the girl I liked was pointing and laughing at me.
It was really traumatic for me and
after that I delved even deeper into baseball.
This song made me not want to like anything other than baseball.
That would be traumatic!
It was very traumatic!
Nobody would've done it back then.
No. It was a period when I wanted to seem cool.
I might have been laughed at the most in my life then.
Even compared to when you tried to make them laugh.
Even after becoming a comedian.
Yes. Nothing tops that sadness and humiliation.
Can I play this one then?
This might be the song I've listened to most in my life.
This is sort of has the roots of a comedian.
Can I play this one then?
This might be the song I've listened to most in my life.
This sort of has the roots of a comedian.
This is a good one.
Oh man, this'll make me cry.
This is good right?
Yes.
I listen to this a lot.
This really is a comedian's.....
This really is a comedian's.....roots.
That's exactly what I said!
You completely said the same thing!
Laugh for yourself ♪
1980 February release
Doukeshi no Sonnet/ Sada Masashi
Matsumoto was 17 years old
Laugh for me ♪
This is nice.
Doesn't matter how old you are.
We are on a small boat
This first song particularly gets to me.
carrying luggage called "sadness".
Yeah...
We're like boatmen drifting down the flow of time ♪
This was actually made into a movie as well.
Yes it did.
Wasn't it "The Tower of Red Lillies?"
That's totally different!
That's completely different! Well there is a movie called that though.
In those small hands of yours,
Was I wrong?
Umm, it's completely different.
It was a movie called "Clown's Sonnet" and.....
you possess more sadness than you can hold.
I'm not sure if that or the song came first,
I think the song came first and they decided to make a film about it.
If it means that I can save your smile,
Oh really?
The movie wasn't bad either.
then I can become a clown for you.
It was a movie about a clown right?
Yes, yes, yes.
And the clown sort of dies at the end.
Yes yes.
Laugh for yourself
And you know the jacket for the record?
It has a picture of Sada-san dressed as a clown.
Laugh for me
There's another person who has confessed to me
that this is his most favourite song.
Who?
Jimmy-san.
Jimmy Ohnishi-san.
So Jimmy-san likes it too.
I tend to have similarities with Jimmy!
I wonder why?
Well we've already reached the place.
Oh, it's Shiodome already.
Sorry Hamada-san.
Oh should we listen to Hamada-san's last?
This will really be our last one.
Yes, we'll reach Shiodome soon.
Find a store where you can be alone.
That's right, it's okay to grimace sometimes.
What is this....?
It's a song from Downtown's first CD released.
1982 December release
Hamada was 19 years old (1 year since debut)
Hitori ni Narerukai / Downtown
Is this you or Matsumoto-san?
We sang it together.
Together?
Yeah we sang it together.
Is this your first song?
There's lots of songs we sing alone in the album but
this is the only one we sing together that I like.
This is nice.
This is very valuable!
They once had a concert and
they got so happy that
that they even hugged, but afterwards backstage....
No, we went straight to my room to change because
I was renting a room near that hall back then.
We left from the back because the audience would rush to us.
So we basically went into my room
and straight after that he did a massive shit.
And he didn't flush it away.
I flushed it!
We were hugging emotionally just a few minutes ago.
I might forgive him doing a poo
since it's a natural occurrence.
But not flushing it? He fails as a human being.