We're making gourmet mixed fruit juice.
This set is 8,640 yen.
Are these by weight?
Yes, they are
-Should I grab this one then?
-Go for it, so that's the price for three?
-This can is 1,700 yen
-That's expensive.
NOT USING AN EGG IN THE JUICE?
What do I know?
I've never made it myself.
So, I don't know if you're supposed to put egg in it.
LET'S MAKE THE BEST MIXED FRUIT JUICE - GOBU GOBU
Seriously, I'll try to help you but...
Let's ask those guys from Nara area about it.
If they put egg in their fruit juice.
Well, mixed fruit juice from Osaka...
or ones you used to make at home had...
egg in it?
-No, there weren't.
No, there isn't.
Is it because you're from Nara area?
-Why are you picking on us from Nara?
-Aren't you from Yamaguchi area?
-I don't believe there is one in it
-I don't think so either.
Nara has their own culture, right?
Nara was once the capital, it's a refined city.
Well, it was once a capital for a very short period of time.
No, it was for a while...
Well, Nara's still trying to hang onto the glory...
No, we understand it once was a capital, that's all.
There's nothing in Nara...
I may need a spoon here.
Wow, a whole thing is in here.
Look.
Are you supposed to use the fruit itself or just the juice?
It depend on how sweet we want the juice to be...
The whole fruit or the juice...
I need to try it first and see...
We have different preference in mixed fruit juice, right?
You think so?
Well, you don't want to put an egg in the mix, right?
An egg, no.
You like the sweeter taste.
I don't want it too sweet either...
I'd like a happy medium...
You'd like the sweetness from the fruit though.
Well then...
I'm not gonna use the juice in this can...
Okay.
I've been listening to this true Osaka citizen...
This old hag from Osaka...
is suggesting that I use both egg and juice from the can...
So I'm guessing they'll create the truer form of mixed fruit juice...
I see...
Should we follow their suggestion then?
-I'll try not to use all of the ingredients at once.
-Right.
Alright, let's make some juice.
You got it.
You're gonna leave some, right?
If we're trying different combination later...
I see we have plenty of banana left, so I'll use lots of them.
Yea, dump that whole bowl in there.
Since there's plenty left over there.
How about these apples?
-Half, maybe
-Or it'll turn sour.
-Three?
-One more.
-Four then
-Yes.
-Put those oranges too
-Got it.
The problem is this one...
-I'd say use about a half
-That sounds good.
How will this not be any good?!
-Here goes 3,000 yen worth of fruit.
-Serious?
This is gonna be delicious.
Throw those peaches too?
Let's toss them in there.
Don't worry, we still have some left.
This has to be good.
That's it? No milk or anything?
Why not try it first
without the milk, then we'll decide if we want it?
I'm afraid it'll turn very thick without the milk.
You're right...
Use milk then?
We'll do without at first.
Huh?
"Thicker juice setting"...
Shut the hell up!
Something's wrong.
It's not turning because there's not enough liquid.
What are you doing?
-What are you doing?
-Sorry about that.
But I heard them...
say that this blender works with very little liquid.
They said that?
-Yes, she was sure
-Yes, now I remember.
But it's not blending.
Oh, now it's working.
Man, that looks pretty thick...
But I bet you it's good.
Can you blend it faster? Oh there it goes.
I remember an old school cafe used to make that same noise.
-Looking good
-Doesn't it?
It's a good looking color.
Nicely done.
I think it's done.
How about you try it as is?
We'll add milk if this isn't any good.
Or add some ice to get it chilled.
This isn't chilled for sure.
Of course,  it's not.
Why didn't we put any ice in?
This is gonna be luck warm.
How is it?
Well...
It's not bad but...
it's just way too thick...
Maybe I had higher expectation
than this?
I bet it needs some ice.
It'd be better chilled.
-Would ice lessen the flavor?
-I think it'll be okay.
I wouldn't blend it too long.
You should crush the ice but not too much.
-Three ice cubes?
-How about some more?
And no milk?
Sounds like you know how to make it?
No, no I don't!
I was merely suggesting...
-He wants milk
-You're suggesting?
But I believe the milk would make it milder taste.
Put some milk in then.
It's up to you how much you want to put in.
Maybe like this much...
Let's blend it.
I like the sound of that!
I think the ice make it!
That grinding sound is very familiar!
Answer me, damn it!
You couldn't hear them over the blender.
They acknowledged.
Pissing me off...
It looks somewhat...
Looks smoother, but the ones sold in store aren't this thick...
They're less thick for sure.
-Delicious!
-Way better than before!
Delicious!
Way better!
-Really good
-Really good!
Good.
That must mean...
We can add more milk...
You want the egg?
There it is...
It's a risk.
Can we try it again with more milk first?
Yes, try it with more milk first...
License, why don't you try it?
It's good stuff...
-Tasty!
-Right?
-Awesome!
-Good!
It's really good!
Now what do we do?
Don't you think the color is pretty good?
The ones you get at the cafe looks like this. We needed more milk.
You have a point.
Cafe must add lots of milk to make as much juice as possible.
I see.
I get it. I get you!
You have a good point.
I believe we're getting close...
-You sure?
-Yes.
Look how much the color has changed!
Right, it's more or less white.
It taste milder than before.
-It's good
-Very good.
So no egg then?
I'd say egg will add another layer.
Why you...speaking like a champ?!
Seriously?
It'll help bring all the flavor back.
The egg yolk it is.
I could never sound that confident.
Nice, using one hand!
You show-off!
I'm only going to use the yolk, okay?
Go for two?
Still not sure if eggs are part of the juice...
That's what you get for showing off!
Seriously, do we need eggs in the mixed fruit juice?
Anybody, say anything, damn it!
-I'm sorry!
-What the hell?!
I can't take this anymore!
I was preoccupied with cracking eggs.
It's not just you, all of you!
I mean, we got all these staff here!
We all need to apologize.
Hamada-san, we're sorry.
Of course, that was our bad...
What about the camera-man?
-So the egg
-I'm only gonna use egg yolk.
Wow, the color changed so much so quick.
I think using only the egg yolk was a good idea.
Maybe we shouldn't have put more ice...
I think the ice made it nice and chilled...
-So this is it
-Yes, that's it.
I'm going to pour all of it.
Amazing...
This looks like the ones you get at the cafe...
Well...
-We did it, Hamada-san
-Yes, we did it.
Here's our gourmet mixed fruit juice.
The color is good.
Fruit cost us 11,000 yen.
The blender was 6,000 yen.
Oh, 6,800 yen.
We spent 20,000 yen on these.
So this is the last attempt.
The last attempt...
Let's have it.
It is...It's great like nobody's business.
Good...
-I must say I can't taste any of the yolk
-No, zero.
It's way better than the juice I had at the Osaka station.
Yes, this is very good.
It caught me off guard because it wasn't chilled but...
it's delicious.
To be frank,
I liked the one we tried two attempts ago the best.
That was the best, wasn't it?
The one where we're so into it.
Well, it's hard to relive that moment...
I'd say this is about as close to the real thing as we can get.
Let's ask the viewers if they'd use an egg or not.
By mail?
Let's ask people in Osaka.
"Do you put an egg in your mixed fruit juice?"
Send in your postcard answering just that.
We'll take a poll then.
Sound good.
This day and age, why not use Twitter? Is postcard okay?
Postcard, it is then...
We won't accept any other form of voting.
Simply state if you put egg in it or not and send it in, please.
We do have a website for this show, right?
-There is one?
-Yes, there is.
But no email address? Okay then.
No email address...
Please send in your postcard then.
-It turned out good
-Yes, we did it.
Here's a letter from Sakai-city in Osaka.
Mr. Hiroaki writes...
Greetings to Hamada-san and Atsushi, I enjoy the show every week.
The curry episode really was really shocking...
How could a cookbook writer like Atsuhi could get so sweaty after eating curry?
Truthfully, I was a bit disappointed.
Please, everyone has their weak point.
It's refreshing to see the different side of Atushi like that,
so I enjoy the angle of the show.
I almost want to see what would happen if he keeps eating the curry and have the sweat going.
One thing though...
As Hamada-san pointed out, perhaps the show Gobu Gobu, is trying to make
-Atsuhi look like a good person.
-He's so right about that.
Am I wrong about that?
You're right, sir.
As Atsushi is known as the instigator,
it's baffling to see him in the new light.
Could Atsushi actually be...
the Ryo in disguise?
LOL...
Shut up, not funny!
Did you have to say that?
See?
But I'm not trying to make myself a good person...
-But viewers see it otherwise
-That's right...
I'd say the viewers are seeing the different side of you for sure...
One thing about curry though...
I do sweat uncontrollably...
-Okay
-But...
I always stop eating after few bites so my sweating stops.
I see!
If I keep eating the curry, I would keep sweating...
I'd like to see that.
Next stop...
Hama-chan will show you what his favorite Osaka stuff is.
What the hell?
That's the episode?
What is it?
-Let's get going
-Serious?
We're all ready to go.
We're doing more than this mixed fruit juice?
Amazing how much we're aimlessly running around...
What are you gonna do?
LET'S SHOW ATSUSHI WHAT SOME OF HAMADA'S FAVORITE THINGS ARE IN OSAKA.
Let's start from here...
Why are we here?
Hama-chan will show you what his favorite things are in Osaka.
But why here?
Why are you asking me?
This is what YOU like...
Not, not really...
I don't mean that in any disrespectful way...
But it's not like I frequent here often...
I personally like this place, especially the gate...
-Well, as tourist like you.
-Right...
But seriously....
Look at the gate.
Yea, I get it. But why here?
Why here?
You guys need to talk it over.
You're not on the same page...
Right.
He's not showing me anything...
Hama-chan knows but Atsuhi doesn't.
I get it but...
where the hell are we going?
How about Bunshi-san and Tsurube-san's favorite egg salad sandwich?
Oh, from the cafe?!
Oh yeah, it's that way!
You should've told me...
I didn't know we were heading there from here?!
I get it now...
What's the name of the cafe?
Cafe Kerun.
It's by Hanjo-Tei
-So you really like this place...
-Where?
This cafe...
Well, I just happened to stumble into the cafe...
on the way to catch Rakugo show at the Hanjo-Tei.
Rakugo performers like Tsurube-san and master Bunshi and I walked in,
And had their favorite egg salad sandwich there.
And I really like it....
I remember I was really into it!
But that's about it...
That's where we're going?
The sandwich was delicious for sure.
-You loved it?
-Yes, I did.
Look at this gorgeous building.
How can you tell if this is s cool building....
This is called "Toryumon".
I know Toryumon
-Well, that's it.
W-Why didn't you say that earlier?
It says it right there!
Why didn't you...
Seriously, this is awesome...
Nice looking gate.
What the hell?
This is the original Toryumon?
So anyone who's about to take an entrance exam...
should walk through the gate...
And you'd be prosperous?
Well, Tanmangu is known as the god of learning...
We're not allowed there today?
N-Not today...
Get out of here.
I'm tired of you...
You certainly don't need to go through there.
But I need to aim higher...
Seriously...
But that was a good learning...
Are you saying if I didn't ask, we would've just ignored that?
Yeah, just walked right by.
What a close call.
I'm glad I asked.
Oh, there is Hanjo-Tei.
Are we almost there?
It's a pristine building.
It's a hall mainly used for Rakugo show.
Anyone performing today?
I'm sure there's someone performing.
There, look at today's program.
I see.
Anybody you know, Hamada-san?
Well...
-I don't think so
-None?
Looks like lots of veteran performers are...
Yea, I'm sure some of them are here to perform.
But I don't recognize them...
Don't you know Koeda?
Ah yea, I do know him.
I see Hachimitsu, too.
Oh right...
I see master Kinshi, too.
Do you know Sanzo-san?
Sanzo Katsura?
What does he look like?
There he is, Sanzo Katsura.
Ah yes, I know of him, yes.
He's been around...
-The show must be going on now
-It must be.
Let's barge in and be the buzz-kill.
Why don't you go right in?
Scream as you enter the hall.
I would never do that!
Not even once.
I would not disrespect the show.
Oh my bad!
-Huh?
-What??
You kidding?
Are you serious?
What the...?
How's this possible?!
"Temporarily Closed"?!
They knew we were coming...
Serious?
Right, they had pretty good egg salad sandwich.
We can't just end it like that...
Wouldn't any producer make sure the business is open?
We're different.
You're different?
What kind of weird policy is that?
What are we gonna do now?
It's obviously closed.
But I was so ready to eat the sandwich.
He said, "My bad!"
What now?
I don't know why you're sighing...
There's one more place...
Why not think about the alternative while we talk?
I have a place in mind...
Croquette from Nakamuraya?
Is that Hamada-san's favorite?
Their stuff is no joke. It's awesome.
-Is it close by?
-Yes, very close.
Shouldn't someone make sure first...?
Go check it out.
Go see if people are lined up.
I don't know what to say...
While shooting in Tokyo, AD bothers to travel to Osaka to shop there?
Yes, that's true...
like while I'm shooting a drama or something.
You make people go?
I'm not really making 'em per se.
If there's someone in Osaka, I would ask them...
-You must really love it then
-It's that good.
But I've heard they get here in bullet-train...
So someone has to come all the say from Tokyo then?
You say, "Go get the croquette now!!"
You're making me look bad.
Sure they're scared.
Is it open?
Yes, it's open.
-Crowded?
-Not at all.
-Good then
-No line.
Why didn't you call them instead of actually going there?
We're different that way.
"different that way"?
Again, I don't get that policy...
Wait, haven't we been here before?
Atsushi, I'm pretty this is your first time here...
Remember, All the shopping districts look the same.
You're just thinking of a different one.
This is just another shopping district.
I see this is a pretty long alley.
This is the longest shopping alley in Japan.
See how far it goes?
Amazing!
See it goes all the way over there.
Longest shopping alley in Japan.
It's so huge!!
Keep it down...!
I've never seen this!
They are all part of the same district?
Please, I can't even see the end of it.
Want the tiger shirt?
Want some clothes?
N-No thank you...
But they're unique...
-Amazing animal prints...
-Crazy...
-Very much goes with Osaka ladies
-Right?
So Osaka....
-So this is where...
-Only 780 yen...
That's cheap!!
Oh man, this is so Osaka!!
Like how this bike is parked right here!!
Now you're making fun of us.
-Thank you
-I watch you on TV...
Is this your bike, ma'am?
-No, but I don't miss you on TV.
-Thank you
Thank you, see you around.
-Let's go.
Why are you in such a hurry?
It'd been nice for you to stop and wait for me...
See how people are lined up already?
Here?
It's very...
I wasn't expecting it...
What?
-Smaller than you expected it?
-Right.
Yes, it's a small place.
But you've been here many times.
Yes so many times...
Once people found out how much I dig this place,
people started to recommend other places.
Saying it's better but...
Okay
Oh, I see the sticker!
Hello.
They're the older stickers.
Can we put these newer ones?
I'm putting one over the old one...
No, don't!
Just put them below the old ones.
Nice.
Order for six croquettes is up!
Anyone?
Please, go right ahead.
Please excuse us.
Thank you for waiting.
Now that I can see the inside,
it is a pretty hefty operation.
Oh, that wasn't it.
I see if people are still waiting for their order.
They're all waiting.
Do people place their order and go off shopping?
Order for four croquettes is up!
Please, step right up.
-Someone else almost got this.
-Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Can we place an order for two, please?
Two croquettes please...
Three croquettes are ready!
Please, ma'am.
-That'd be 750 yen
-750 yen.
Let me put these on...
Can you hand him the money?
Thank you.
Could you put these stickers later?
Yes, I'm the second side-kick.
-This is it!
-Yes, from Nakamuraya.
It's smaller than I thought...
It's still good today!
I'm sure they put some drugs in this...
What?!
There's some sketchy stuff in it to make you hooked on this.
Am I safe eating this?
-It's sweet!
-Right.
It's sweet!
This is so good...
You're right, it's delicious!
This is awesome.
I'm positive this is laced with something...
I'd say they're using quality potatoes.
Very tasty potatoes...
So this is...
Hamada-san's favorite.
Among all the croquettes we've tried,
nobody can beat Nakamurasan.
They're the best.
I can see why...
This is delicious.
It's only 70 yen?
Now I know why you'd go as far as to ask someone
to go get these and share them with everyone.
This is very unique. It's their own flavor.
So good!
-Shinano noodles next?
-No, we've been there...
How many times do we have to go there?
Well, I haven't been there yet...
I've never been to Shinano noddle house...
We meant to hit the sandwich place...
But they were closed.
So we're here, now we're off to Shinano?
Again?
What's going on now?
What am I supposed to do?
So...What am I supposed to do now?
Camera's on, right?
Damn, it's getting heated over there...
I don't like it.
The tension is killing me.
Man, he can argue with croquette in his mouth?
Scary...
He's about to throw a punch or two...
Serious?
Should I intervene?
Sounds like it's a no-go.
Let's save Shinano trip for the future.
Okay...
-Not today?
-No, not today.
Don't you want to go though?
We need to talk...
Delicious.
They still go it.
If you like, I can try to convince him.
I can at least try...
After all, we're Gobu Gobu. (50/50)
I appreciate that.
But...
We're wasting time!
Like I said...
He may not show up at the next shooting...
If we push our luck too much.
Understood...
I don't want that to happen either so...
LET'S GO TO HAMADA'S FAVORITE PLACE!
Okay, I'm lost again.
Where are we going now?
-Where to?
-Have no idea...
So you don't know where we're heading either?
You didn't settle with producer about where we're going next?
I just didn't see the point of going to the Shinano noodle house again.
So I brought that up with the producer.
It was a peaceful argument.
-Didn't look like that though
-But it was.
He agreed and decided to hit the next business...
But he didn't say exactly where to...
-I'm clueless too
-But didn't you
talk to the producer, too?
-Yes.
-He didn't say anything?
Well, he said that you didn't want to go there.
But I thought,
since we're supposed to be 50/50,
don't I have some say in this, too?
But the producer was afraid if we forced you, you wouldn't show up at the next shooting.
Shut the hell up!
No way!
So I gave up...
No, I wouldn't do that!
I won't want you to be a no-show, so...
We're holding off the noodle house for the future...
Don't worry, we can go there anytime.
Is that right?
Seriously, I pretty much own that place.
-You guys are like family.
-Right.
I will say though...
that beef noodle they serve is like the croquette we had.
They lace their food.
I don't think so!
It must be their seasoning.
Seriously, you'd get hooked on their beef noodles.
It's that good...?
I get it!
Scared me...
I see!
Huh?
Let's see...
"Let's check out Hamada's favorite love hotel"?
Greetings!!
God, it's them!
Good to see you again!
That's CURRY'S!
We're LICENSE!
I thought you've changed the name...
We've made that mistake once before...
We've learned our lesson then...
God, I can smell it here!
The curry smell!
It's very strong...
But this isn't about that.
Then what?
Fujiwara has some...
He'd like your help.
-What?
-I'd like to talk to you.
-May I?
-You're serious?
Can we go somewhere more private?
I know it's gonna be curry!
I know we can smell it but...
This is more about Fujiwara's issue.
-Serious?
-Yes.
Hello. We're from Gobu Gobu TV show.
Excuse us.
This must be something big...
It's a big deal.
Please have a seat.
Okay, let's hear it.
It's rather a severe issue...
And I hope you can help me.
First of all, I have my own blog page.
It's written by me, Fujiwara from LICENSE.
Most of us comedians use Yahoo blog.
And I'm usually ranked between 3rd and 5th every week.
Every blog gets their ranking.
And I've never been ranked the highest.
I'm guessing the top blogger gets so many viewers and comments.
But I want to beat them, if not only for once!
I've been at it for a long time...
Who's No. 1 by the way?
It's your wife, Natsumi.
Huh?
You serious?
Yes, uncontested.
I've used many tactics, but just can't beat her.
Not just me, but many other comedians have tried, too.
Not matter how much effort you put into the blog,
Nobody can knock her out of No. 1 status.
It's impossible.
Did you know about this?
Well, I knew she had a blog but...
didn't realize she's been No. 1 all this time.
So, what I'd like to ask you is...
Could you make a cameo in my blog?
That's it?!
I've seen Hamada-san in Natsumi's blog.
And when he's in, her readership skyrockets.
Yes, she'd blog about our dinner outing and stuff...
She'd post some photos, too.
Only the man of the house can beat her at this point.
I see.
The introduction is important.
I don't want to just introduce you like any other blogger.
Here. I have a tentative caption,
which I'll use on your photo.
I see.
I'd like to know what you think of it...
I hope you're okay with this...
So, his photo will have to match with the caption.
Yes, but I think it'll be fairly easy.
"Greetings to all Fujiwara's blog readers. It's me, Masatoshi."
"Today, I'm here to help make Fujiwara the No. 1 blogger."
"I, Masatoshi, is behind his blog 100%."
"Don't miss Gobu Gobu on May 6th for more details."
"Masatoshi over and out."
What the hell is that?!
Now we just need a photo to match...
That'll get some attention.
I'm moving up for sure.
Public will love how you'd call yourself Masatoshi.
-In the blog world
-Yes, only in the blog.
This is so embarrassing...
Once the show airs, you'll be okay.
But if this doesn't air for some reason,
people will never get this.
But you'll score some interested readers regardless.
Also, because media is always hungry for some news,
until this show airs on May 6th,
the news headline will be
"Masatoshi refers himself in third-person."!
Yahoo news headline?!
So embarrassing...
You better cut it out.
This could also serve as the advertisement.
It's good for Atsushi, too.
Me too?
Because it's essentially for Gobu Gobu.
And I want to win against your wife.
It all depends on how Masatoshi-san feels.
What do you say, Masatoshi-san.
Well, all you want is photo, right?
The photo needs to reflect on your close friendship.
Showing a different side of Hamada-san per se.
It needs to be "Masatoshi."
All "Masatoshi."
"Masatoshi" face.
No place for "Hamada".
Right...
Can't have the usual overpowering Hamada-san.
I want to see a huge smile.
If you would flash a smile...
It'll just be me in it?
As your Masatoshi reference.
Why not both of you?
How about you two in the photo?
Is that okay?
Let me take the photo then.
Atsushi-san, could you help me with the angle?
Is this better?
Mmm, you two look too stiff...
Vertical shot is okay?
Fujiwara needs to put his arm around Hamada-san too.
Please smile, Hamada-san.
That's good.
Smile now.
How's this?
That's pretty good.
Cut it out!!
Ready?
Looking really good.
Here we go.
Thank you very much.
This has to work...!
If I can win over Natsumi-san with this,
what else can I do?
Why are you asking me?!
Don't worry, you got this!
If all else fails, ask Atsushi-san.
Well, me...?
You'll have to ask Atsushi-san too.
Atsushi-san and his two suns.
Yes, I used that phrase at my wedding.
"I'm now blessed with two suns."
Right, each sun represents Ryo and my wife...
My speech, yes.
That's my wedding speech...
Embarrssing? How dare you?
-But you made the speech.
-Yes, I did but...
Why is everyone ganging up on me...?
That was his speech.
I get it. I know.
Oh, thank you.
Wow, that looks so good.
It is delicious.
And the flavor from simmered onion is something else.
Let's dig in.
Please enjoy.
I see the place is called "Gentle Time"?
Cafe Gentle Time.
Thank you for pointing that out.
I'd like to believe the flavor is also "gentle"...
-Let me see if there's any peppers in here...
-There's none.
Wow, it smells amazing...
Yes, I know!
It doesn't have the typical spicy curry smell.
Is that so?
It looks great for sure.
-Looks great
-I'm going for it.
I think we finally found one for you.
-Is this a potato?
-Yes, it is.
What the hell...?
We may have accomplished the task...
Here I go.
It's hot, isn't it?
-How is it?
-Mmm?!
Um?
-Um?
-You okay?
Delicious, wait, it's HOT!!
Shut the hell up.
The spice crept up on you...
Calm down...
-It's really good though
-Isn't it?
Really delicious!
I could've told you that. I mean it looks delicious.
Very spicy...
But I can get into this flavor...
- Tasty
-Yes it is!
-Good
-It's beyond curry, isn't it?
This is no joke. It's good.
-Good, isn't it?
-Yea...
It's easy to get hooked on the flavor.
You're sweating already?
-If this weren't as spicy...
-Then, it wouldn't be a curry.
It'd be the best.
Then, it would be hashed beef rice.
Seriously, this is one good curry.
Good, isn't it?
-It's really good.
-Yes, it is.
You're getting really sweaty...
Once the spice gets me like this,
it makes me not want to try any other curry...
Don't get me wrong.
I love the taste.
So you guy's goal is to find the perfect curry
that he can finish eating, right?
I mean I want to see him clean the plate.
You found this delicious but too spicy, right?
Yes, are you guys really doing your homework before you recommend these?
Of course, we're taking mental notes!
But why am I the only one eating?
Because we tasted them already.
We think we're getting closer to your liking.
I will say that this curry stands above the rest.
You mean, the flavor is the best.
I wish they'd ease up on the spice a little more.
Then, it wouldn't be a curry.
The spice is what makes their curry.
But I believe they could do away with less spice.
-Don't use any spice then?
-Right.
Why do they have to cater to your preference?
And why are you sweating so much?
Cut it out...
Again, it's a good curry.
They need to add more jam in this.
Shut the hell up.
You're making us feel bad.
How can't you not finish this?
-There's no denying it's good.
-You're sweating so much.
You two need to find him another curry.
Yes, we'll research some more.
You're getting close.
Thank you, it'll be even better next time.
So, we're just gonna keep going with this mission?
Huh? Do I want to shower at the love hotel?
You suggest I clean up at the love hotel?
And Hamada-san will be waiting for you outside.
What a terrifying image.
I don't ever want him to tell me to hit the shower.
Only then, your roles will be split 50/50 (gobu gobu).
You just might beat Hamada-san...
-I don't wanna be a cat
You could split it 70/30.
OFF TO HAMADA'S FAVORITE LOVE HOTEL
Huh? I don't remember it being here...
Well, isn't it around here?
So, this area is pretty much taken over by love hotels..
There are tons of love hotels around,
but this one I'm about to show you is my favorite.
Do people usually have their favorites?
I'm curious to know what you think of it.
I'd like to hear your honest opinion on it.
Like you liked my favorite croquette, right?
That was delicious, yes.
But I don't know how to if I can review love hotels...
I'm not that confident.
Well, you'll gonna find out.
I will look the room objectively.
And see if I personally like it.
Or, if you'd consider booking a room there.
I'm not suggesting you go behind your wife or anything.
You're speaking hypothetically...
But it's not like I frequent the love hotel with my wife.
Imagine facing a love hotel from your apartment like that.
Here?
-Can we just walk in?
-Hope you guys got the permission to enter.
"4 hours"?
-Lots of cars here...
-Means people can stay for just four hours?
Not quite clear myself...
Ah! It's been so long since I felt this weird vibe from a love hotel.
Room 505
Press 505
This one?
Wow, look at these gear.
C'mon, let's get to the 5th floor.
This should get us there.
It's been a while...
I remember the room had ping-pong table and whatnot...
So, why do you come to like this room?
Like I said,
I would know once I see it?
I'm saying I'd have enjoyed it if I were younger.
Excuse us.
Ah yes, these flickering lights.
Remember this?
It's set up in the way that nobody would ever know that you've been here.
Here it is.
Huh?
The sign says, "Sakura No Miya Station"?
A station?
Welcome.
Our hotel accepts all major credit cards.
If you're a membership holder.
What's it say? "Don't..."
Don't rush "IN," it says...
It's a safety warning.
They're looking after our penis' safety.
What do you say, Atsushi...
This isn't anything unusual, right?
Well, this room offers that option like nobody's business.
What? They have things like that in the open like this?
-What?
-Time has changed, you know?
That's for massaging...
Come over here, Atsushi.
Sakuranomiya Station...
It's all about the Sakuranomiya around here.
I see...
Amazing!!
Isn't it?
There's more.
Check out the flooring.
What are they suggesting here?
I was cool with croquette but...
What am I doing in this theme-driven love hotel?
Isn't this amazing?
Looks like a fun place though...
I could only imagine...
They've made a train replica.
Huh?
Multi-functioning toilet?
I see they're on top of each other...
I don't get it.
You haven't seen one of these?
-No.
-Don't know what this is good for?
Well, that's alright..
But you get the idea...
Well, how does this...
I see, you get to tie your hands up there.
Really, no need for you to be an example.
I don't need the picture, really.
Are you into that kind of stuff?
Get out of here.
I was just trying to show you.
-So you're saying you wouldn't be tied up.
-Of course.
What a relief.
But you looked so happy being tied up.
Alright, let's go this way.
It's supposed to be "Tenma".
But they changed it to "Denma"
Whomever created it must be a super pervert.
Um? What's this?
"Call front desk and ask for the ending theme song"
Oh, we're already done here?
This is the end?
"Osaka Kancho Line"
I see, it's supposed to be "Kanjo" and not "Kancho".
I'd say this was a distasteful segue from curry episode.
You have a point.
Is that it?
Atsushi, will you make a call?
And ask for their favorite song.
Front desk is nine...
Excuse me....um...
I would like to ask for your favorite song...
Does that make sense?
I'm sorry if I'm not making any sense...
"Osaka Rhapsody" by Senri and Mari
Ah, I see!
I got it!
Hamada-san is familiar with that song.
But it doesn't really ring a bell for me.
Thank you for the request.
I get it.
Take care, bye.
It makes perfect sense.