Subtitles: Zurui
(Aho = Idiot or Idiotic)
Are you ok, Yuko?
- Yes, I'm ok
This is...
This is the hideout
Aren't you scared?
It hurts!
Are you ok?
- I am ok
I'm scared but...
The baby inside my stomach gives us protection
That's right
We will win against them
and protect the earth!
Let's go!
Hey! What's that?
It's a Rika-chan doll!
(popular like Barbie in Japan)
Yuko-chan!!
- Help me!!!
It's a trap!
- Yes, it is!
"Aho Aho Aho Aho..."
(help me!)
It was you guys!
We knew you were coming here
It's a Rika doll!
- What are you saying
What's with this person?
Sorry, I have bad help...
Yuko, are you ok??
This hole is 30 meters deep
Aho Aho Man help us!!
You're an idiot, right?
What are you doing?
Yuko fell into the hole
Help her, I can't live without her!
Aho Aho doll!!
(Make believe this is Yuko, and live your life)
I can't do that!
Help us!
She's in the hole
Aho Aho Rope!!
(Aho AHo Rope is made from "super alloy"
and can support 100,000 tons of weight)
That's too short!
(help me)
- Get a longer rope!
Aho Aho Long Rope!!
(Aho Aho Long Rope can support 100,000
tons and is twice as long as the Aho Aho Rope)
That's still too short!
Why is your tongue sticking out?
Get something longer!
Aho Aho Chain!!
(Aho Aho Chain is as strong as diamonds)
(...with weak plastic links)
(help me!)
They are laughing at you
Yuko are you ok?
I can't breath!
The oxygen will run out soon in this hole
Just 1 minute left!
Hurry up and do something!
Aho Aho Vacuum!!
That's right!
You will use this to suck her out?
We won't let you do it!
What do you think you are doing?
Let's do it now!
It's working!
More... more... more!
Give it more power!
What happened?
The fuse blew
You really are an idiot!
To be continued