Translations: Zurui
Laying Eggs
So this is a love hotel
Nervous, huh
There is an angel
Oh, yes
Such big boobs
Shall we touch it?
Eh...
Together
OK, right?
I can't wait
Yuuko-chan, are you OK?
Hey!
What is it?
Why...
Are you OK?
Are you OK, Yuuko-chan?
It that you again?
Hey
Let me give birth
What..what the hell are you doing?!
My Yuuko-chan is a mess!
Fish man
Let me give birth today
Don't bother us
Yeah right
Let me ride a condor
What are you talking about?
That's dirty
Clean Yuuko-chan's face
Hey, don't be hard on me
What..please go home really..
Admit this is your child
Why should I?
Listen to his thoughts
Close your eyes
Close my eyes?
Daddy... daddy...
Please... please do something about me!!
What's wrong with you, boy?
What are you talking about?
What was the last half?
Go home
Move over
Stop it. I told you to go home
Dump that woman!
Why are you saying that!
I love Yuuko-chan!
Please... accept Ken-chan
Who are you talking about? Who's Ken-chan?
Accept him
I said I won't
Close your eyes and listen to Ken-chan
Again?
Daddy... daddy... do something about me!!
This time Ken-chan was not upset
What the hell!
Don't be a bother us... just leave!
Leave!
Go home!
I'm going... I'm going if you say so
Yeah, go home then
I'm leaving soon
Hey, don't use the phone
Go away!
What are you doing!
Are you OK, Yuuko-chan?
Yes, I am
Never come again!
This is so bad
Are you OK, Yuuko-chan?
But you are beautiful, Yuuko-chan
Me like this?
OK, right?
Let me give birth
That's enough
Let's go, Yuuko-chan!
Yes!