DISASTER
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Yoko-chan! Yoko-chan!!
What's wrong, Yoko-chan?
You can't sleep
You'll die
Yoko-chan!
Yoko-chan!!
If you sleep, you die! Yoko-chan!!
Yoko-chan!
Yoko-chan!!
Don't sleep!!
But...
It's been three days since we're lost...
It'll be ok, Yoko-chan
Someone will come and rescue us
So don't sleep!
Sleep equals death!
Yoko-chan!!
Wake up!
Something's coming
An helicopter
The sound of an helicopter!
Hey!!
We're here!
Rescue us!
I'm here to rescue you, get in!
Wha-?
Just get inside
Alright
Yoko-chan! Yoko-chan!!
You alright?
Yoko-chan!! Yok---
Man that's small
Quick, get inside!
A-alright
This is...
The clothes are in the way
Yoko-chan!
Just get inside!
- Yes!
There's no time to waste
- Y-yes
Alright, let's go!
You're not inside, get inside
I'm sorry
This... wait, how...?
How should I...?
How am I supposed to...?
Ok, you can go
You're not inside yet
What should I do?!
Let's take this