Mitsuru-san
Translation: Zurui
"Please stir it just a little longer"
It's not working, my body feels heavy
I can't even move!
Didn't you gain weight?
What?
We're idols, so we should diet
Sorry about that
Yes
Try it again
Hey, Tatsuya!
Why don't you have some fun dancing with us?
Hey
Leavi him alone
-Why?
He failed the audition but didn't tell his production company
He failed miserably
The judge told him he has zero talent
"Zero talent" that's pretty bad
So he's depressed huh
Tatsuya
Cheer up, we're on your side
We are... 1, 2, 3, 4
"Hamigakitai"
Shut up!
What are you doing Tatsuya?!
How the hell would you guys know how I'm feeling?!
What are you doing?
Yes, that hurt
You didn't need to hit him
They said that was my last change... do you understand?!
Yes but...
I'm sorry, I was hard on you guys ultil now
Why are you saying that?
I'm sure the 2 of you will hit it big
Bye
Stop Tatsuya!
Wait, what are you doing?!
What??
If you jump from here, you'll die!
That's fine with me
Can't someone help?
Don't do it!
Isn't anyone here?
Oh! Mitsuru-san
Please stop Tatsuya!
What are you guys doing?
Tatsuya gonna jump!
Hey you!
Not me
Not him, he's there
Not me! Tatsuya's going to jump and die
Stop thinking like that!
Come here!
See ya!
Tatsuya!!
No way!
Tatsuya!
Knock it off!
Wait just a minute!