Toll Booth
http://zurui.blogspot.com
We finally arrived
- This is the toll booth
Is this it?
- This is it
It's written here, 16km
Here right?
- Yes, this is where we pay
They're eating...
But it says "Toll booth"
- Are you sure?
Oh yeah, the price is 600 yen
Excuse me!
They just talking...
Hello?
ex.. cuse me!
Not too many cars here
- Yeah, cause this is the country side
Hey, hey, hey wait a minute!
Excuse me!
Hello?
She looked at us right?
- Yeah
Excuse me
Try and ask her
This has to be toll booth
Yeah?
Excuse me, this is the toll booth right?
Yeah
600 yen?
- Yeah, 600 yen
Ok, here you go, thank you
She closed the curtain
Excuse me!
Excuse me! Hello!
I can see her shadow!
We see your shadow
- You're there right?
We can see your shadow
What is it?
Um.. it's 600 yen right?
600 yen
Can I have my change?
Hey!
Seconds!
Can I get my change?
- We gave you 1000 yen
Our change
She's giving him a second helping
Excuse me, my change!
Hello!
Please give us our change!
What?
- Please give me 400 yen change!
Change? What change are you talking about?
We just gave your 1000 yen right?
It should be 600 yen
- I don't have your 1000 yen
I just gave 1000 yen to you
I didn't get it
We gave it to you
- Oh, there it is, the 1000 yen
That 1000 yen is ours
What are you saying?
No, that's our 1000 yen on the table, right there
I didn't get 1000 yen from you
We gave it to you...
YOU DIDN'T GIVE IT TO ME!
Pay her again
What are you saying?
Don't try to fool me
Never mind about them
This is the toll booth right?
- What time do you think it is?
This should be open 24hrs
Don't be so harsh
Thank you
Ok
- Yes
I only have large bills...
You have to pay 600 yen, that's why
I'm telling you to give me 600 yen!
Ok, here you go, but I only have a large bill!
Please
Can't see what she's doing when
she closes the curtain
Are they eating?
excuse me, hello?
Hello!
Excuse me!
Excuse me
They took our picture
Excuse me!
Our change!
WHAT NOW?!
Give us our change
Hey, you talk to them, I don't
know what they're saying!
I don't know!
I don't understand about this new generation
What is it?
We gave her 10,000 yen but we didn't get our change
Before that we gave her 1000 yen
Did you get it?
- No I don't
You just took it from us, right?
- It's the first time I'm seeing you
First time she's seeing us?
Ok whatever, but give us back 9600 yen
Our change, 9400 yen
What are you saying?
Never mind about the 1000 yen, just give
me back the change for the 10,000 yen
I'm really sorry
Hey, wait!
Hey, please open the window!
What?
We are in rush, so please give us back our change!
There's cars behind us too
My husband.. isn't feeling too well
Don't cause too much trouble
When we get our change, we'll leave
He's been bedridden, but was feeling
better so he come out to eat
Please leave him alone
Just give us our money back
Give us back our 9400 yen
You have family right?
Yes
Then please leave us alone
I understand, but we just want our change
The 10,000 yen over there
Here, give it to them, it's ok
Ok, here it is, now leave
No, we aren't talking about this 1000
yen, we want the 10,000 yen
You're Yakuza right?
No, we aren't
We're college students
College students
We want change for the 10,000
yen, forget about the 1000 yen
You guys don't understand huh?
No we don't
What you're doing is the same as stealing from us
Scary, so scary
Give me a break
Dear
- Yeah
Can you go and call the police?
What for?
Let them take care of this
Good, let them call the police.
- We can talk to them too
I don't know what you're talking about
We paid you right?
You're Japanese right?
- Yes we are
I don't understand
We're just asking for change
What's the problem?
They're giving us trouble, are you the police?
Yes
You're the old man that was eating in there!
That's just wrong!
They're giving us trouble
Police?
That's for the American police
That's completely wrong
You're not the police
Did you pay?
Yes we did!
- No you didn't
If you want to call the police, call the police
We paid 10,000 yen!
Call the police
We are just regular folk, and they
came suddenly asking for money
Driver's license
Why should I show it to you?
What kind of attitude is that?
Show me your license!
What are you doing?!
She took a picture of us
Now I have evidence
What evidence?
Evidence of violence
That's not good
Let's go, let's go
My husband is sick
Ok, I'll give you money!
Your husband is young!
You're young! What happened?!
That's gross!
Let's get out of here!
Idiots!
Stupid!
Stupid idiots!
The next car's here, get ready!