Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
I am reporting from the headquarters of
Mercedes Venz in Stuttgart, Germany
where a test drive is in process
We are here
to observe how they conduct a test drive
On their latest '97 Venz model
Rumor has it that the model
has undergone a 100% change from previous years
So without further adieu
Here's the world's first footage
of the Venz' latest model
C'mon now
This way, this way
Yes, yes
What's the hold up?
Pick it up
You can do this
Faster, faster
Come around this way
Around the corner
Alright, alright
Stop right here
Alright, are we good?
Let's do a test run
Let's beat your time from yesterday, OK?
Ready
Go!
No good, no good
Come on back
Get back here
Come back
That's a good boy
Don't forget to look both ways
before you start into drive
It's called defensive driving
"What if a child runs into the street?"
"What if a cyclist shows up"
That's being defensive
So don't ever forget to look both ways before you go
Don't ever assume anything
"Oh, I should be fine to go"
or, "Oh, nobody's gonna jump out in front of me"
That's a dumb move
You ready?
Look both ways
Both ways
Yes, both ways
Look to the right again
just to be sure
OK, let's go
Let's do better than yesterday
better than yesterday
Oh no, the rain
Here comes the rain
Raining
Alright, good job
Let's wait it out
Wait it out
OK, no more rain
Rain's over
Shake it off
Shake the water off
You're making better time than yesterday
Keep it up
Looking good
Alright, alright
Good boy
Good job
Let's break for lunch
Go for it
Wait!
Hold on!
It looks as though Japanese automakers
will face stiff competition
Good boy
We'll be heading to Japan very soon
That's my boy
This model also comes in red