(Translator's note: "rangai"
is pronounced as,
"ran-jai", a mispronunciation
of the word "ranger" .
Enjoy!)
The Future Century
Squadron: The Five Rangai!
It's past 8:00 already!
"A" Kanji has started already.
Ah good. It just started.
Stop it!
Help!
My name is Skeleton Mask!
You are mine from today on.
No!!
Somebody help me!
Touchy touchy!
Stop!
Red Rangai!
Yellow Rangai!
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
Alright!
Go out from there!
Thank you!
Hurry up and run away!
No.
Huh?
It's all wrong.
Who are you guys?
Your group name?
The Five Rangai.
You aren't five rangai.
What color are you?
Yellow Rangai!
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
Hold on a second!
Hold on, hold on.
You. Who are you?
Yellow Rangai!
And you?
Ridiculous!
Why are there two yellow ones?
Red Rangai!
Yeah, yeah. You're red.
What about you?
Red Rangai!
And you?
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai.
Stop! Stop!
Nooooo!
Don't you see something wrong?!
Why are there 3 red ones
and 2 yellow ones?
Well, you see.
We're not all about colors
or anything like that.
But the colors...
You see we want people to focus
on our individual characters.
But, no one can tell that
kind of thing offhand.
Kids focus on how you look.
But I think that somehow
we can get by that...
Because...
Because if you look, it may
seem like the same red color...
...but he really, really has deep affection
for his mother. Things like that...
He has a really good story about her.
I don't need to hear it.
That stuff makes no difference.
I'm talking about you guys look.
Ridiculous.
Just look.
Don't you think it's strange? Why
are you red and they are red, too?
My dad said the same exact thing.
Well, your dad is right.
It just isn't right!
You can't form without consulting each other about your colors first.
But we're different on the inside.
I already told you no one
can tell that offhand!
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
Stop, stop, stop.
Stop, stop. No, no, no.
You're not there yet.
You're not formed yet.
I'm the arrogant one!
Fine, fine.
you...
You MAY be the arrogant one.
But no one can tell!
Fine then.
Huh?
I give up.
Give up? What are you talking about?
But, well.
I'm not saying you should give up.
If it's this important, I'll
switch to green so...
Really?
I'll switch to green, too.
Why the hell?!
We attend the same high school.
It's gotta be different!
I mean 2 green ones-
Why are you taking off your clothes?!
If you become green
then you can stay yellow.
Why are you eating right now?
Just ridiculous.
No matter how you look at it it's all wrong.
So, what are you saying is... Umm...
So you... uh...
...um... won't battle us today?
Of course I'm not fighting you today.
It wouldn't feel right.
I'd feel strange attacking you.
You should have a discussion with
each other when you get back home.
You guys hang out all the time, right?
Actually...
...I have no idea who he is.
You guys aren't friends?
No, no, no.
We just met for the first time today.
We were introduced to each other...
Is that right?
Yes.
Through the personal ads or something?
That's no good.
I mean...
... you have to practice a little
bit with each other first.
It's to soon. It's to soon.
You're to soon.
I'm in my 14th year now!
I'd destroy you in a minute!
Using this!
Ok?
We understand.
So leave.
But I'll be back next week.
So you'll be back next week.
Yeah.
So try again next week.
Ok.
And show me what you learned from today.
Ok?
The Future Century Squadron: The Five Rangai!   To be con't.