TYPESETS & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
Aw man, I'm stuffed
Alright, let's go! Get in
Oh yeah!
- Wait a second, you
What?
Can't you see this?
It means you can't park here
Oh, my mistake...
- This isn't ok
I'm sorry
- What were you...?
We were having breakfast
and now we're off to kindergarten
And that's fine, but this is no place to park in
- It was only for 30 minutes
It was 30 minutes, right?
- Forgive us
Rules are rules, show me your license
I see...
Can't we do something about it?
I don't think we can
- Aw, don't say that
Don't let me say it again, your license
Let's see...
- Bang!!
Don't kill her!
It's just a joke! A joke
- Quiet, kids
Check that out
Can I have it back?
- Here's your fine
Make sure to pay it within the next 2 weeks
- Shut up, ugly
Quit it, and make sure to pay up
Alright, got it
- Just do as we say
By the way, do you wear seatbelts?
- Of course, everytime
Is that so? Good
- Yes
Ok, shall we go?
- Oh, wait
The US president will land soon nearby
Can you show me what's inside your trunk?
Can you...?
- Huh?
Can't we just... go?
After you show me what's in your trunk
Alright, I'll open it
No, no, I didn't ask to see your engine
That won't help us
- Oh, I see...
What we want to look at is your trunk
Mister, you're sweating a lot
- It's nothing
Can we see your trunk?
What now?
May I...?
- Ah! Don't take my key
We're only checking your trunk
Ah-- wait--
- Are you hiding something?
No, I've got nothing in there...
Looks like you got something big here, huh?
Huh?
Something big, huh?
Not that much...
- What's this?
It's Hamashou
- You have Hamashou, huh?
Look at this and tell me what it is
It's... Hamada Shogo
Hamada Shogo, am I right?
And why are you carrying this around?
Huh?
Sorry for making you cry, lady
- It's my first time seeing it...
How can you say that about
a person in your trunk?
He's not that kind of guy...
- Lady...
This is stuff violent gangs do!
- I'm sorry
Do you know that?
- I know
Enough with your excuses
Can't believe you got this...
Hey, excuse me...
We just found a Hamada Shogo
inside someone's car trunk
Alright, got it
Please, sing your famous line
Dom Perignon
- We confirmed it
We have no doubts, it's him
We did what we had to
Everyone is... ♪
- Shut up!
Not only that... you got yourself
a cheap Hamashou, didn't you?
Was it worth it, really?
- I'm sorry
Sorry but, I'll have to arrest you
- No way
Daddy!
It's fine
It's not fine at all, lady
It's a crime to put that thing in your trunk
You take care of the car, ok?
- Got it
You're all coming in the patrol car with me
No way...
I didn't know, really
- Liar
I swear
- Shut up
Another sleepless night... ♪
You were crying, weren't you... ♪
Dom Perignon on my bed... ♪
Money... makes him crazy... ♪
TYPESETS & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
patreon.com/shionnotsukai