Translation, Timing & Typesetting: GakiNoSuitGuy
Quality Check: Rylix
For those who cannot wait
we have a very special episode today.
Let's reveal it:
My First Errand
Never give up Baby Special
George Tokoro
Is it "Never give up Baby Special"?
It is.
We brought the staff to talk about the special.
My First Errand staff room
What is it really like?
Really, when watching from home
I cry
When I cry in the studio
I hate being filmed by you.
I really have to endure it.
You know, it's not a cool emotion.
You know, the camera is constantly pinned on me.
No matter how much wells up
I have to suck it back in.
I try to find ways to dry it.
I can never express myself fully.
I open my eyes fully so
the tears
will dry easier.
Is that so?
How is it for this person?
Never give up Baby Special.
Moriguchi Hiroko
Singer
Doesn't that strike a chord?
Never give up baby.
I am sure that this song will play in your heads
as you realize that it's the new theme song.
"My first errand".
I've recorded them all.
And I rewatch them when I need to be moved.
It's so powerful that I completely cry.
Complete
emotional crying
how refreshing
Thank you children.
Let's cry and feel emotionally refreshed.
First up
The 6 year old bigger brother has a little brother who looks up to him.
Fukuoka â— Kyushu
Kyotaro, dinner is ready.
The big brother Kyotaro is in
third grade elementary school.
The one going on errand
is the little brother, Minato.
He is only 2 years and 8 months old.
2 years
8 months old
Minato
Will he be okay?
I am worried.
Big brother, stop playing around.
Kyotaro,
dinner is ready.
Kyotaro, the big brother, went on his first errand when he was 2 years and 3 months old.
Kyotaro (big brother)
Elementary school 3rd grade.
That's great.
Well it was for his own ice cream.
When his younger brother heard
he couldn't take it.
Isn't it dangerous to go to the apartment complex?
He wants to assist his brother.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
Kyotaro leaves for his penmanship classes.
The penmanship school is past the park
inside the apartment complex.
Cars can't go there.
Right! Time for Kyotaro's plan
his first errand.
Look at this.
Minato,
Your big brother
has forgotten this.
Did he forget it once again?
It can't be helped.
The goal is to go to the penmanship class
and give the pen to his big brother Kyotaro.
If you go
then say
Kyotaro, okay?
OK.
It is one way up the hill.
There are many students in the class
so he has to call out "Kyotaro brother".
In order to not scare the 2-year-and-8-month-old boy
the crew is hiding while filming him.
It's raining lightly outside.
Don't slip, okay?
Even when she has to throw out the trash
he hates being apart from his mother.
What an emotional second son.
But today there is something that he must do.
Since his forgetful brother is in trouble.
His shoes are cute.
When being told to wear a raincoat he answers
"I want to use the umbrella like my big brother"
He has started to use umbrellas recently.
It must be heavy, right?
Whoa, all those huge people.
They are middle school students.
Without mommy
everything feels so far away.
The umbrella feels heavy.
1 week from now and
he will be finished with nursery school.
Growing a little every day
his mother can't keep up.
These are the steps leading to the class.
Kyotaro brother,
is doing pretty well.
The entrance to the school.
Phew, I arrived.
Let's show you a brief moment of a growing 2-year-and-8-month-old kid in one cut.
He is putting it in like that.
No, the umbrella can't go in like that.
"Oh, so it can't go in like that."
No no no, this isn't it.
Oh? Indeed.
Yes, yes, yes. That's how you close it.
Exactly. That's how.
He did it.
Doing like others. Look!
Oh no, it can't stay still.
He thought of something.
Finally managed to put the umbrella in.
Pheew
From here he will call his brother.
Do it in a loud voice.
Kyotaro
Kyotaro, your dinner is ready.
Dinner?
Though a bit embarrassing for his big brother
he couldn't help himself from being so worried.
Minato,
You sure have a great big brother.
Thank you Minato.
Brother, if you forget it again
I will bring it to you.
After these stairs
will you go
by yourself?
Can you go back alone?
Mom is waiting.
Bye.
Splish splosh.
Big brobro, make sure to do it well.
He parts with that emotion.
Hold on. My head feels wet.
Umbrella, umbrella.
The umbrella!
He has forgotten what it is that he has forgotten.
Mommy, open up, please.
Did you come running?
You are
awesome,
Minato.
Where is
the umbrella?
Did you forget the umbrella there?
Yes, even though you went all the way.
You forgot
the umbrella.
Just like your
big brother.
Yes, just like his brother.
He forgot it.
My First Errand staff room
So this is how
the cameramen
disguise themselves?
In the staff room we keep the disguises.
This looks good on me.
Wait a minute. This isn't the reason why I am here.
You have collected the request letters here.
The mothers send us letters.
Everybody, they really have gathered all the letters.
For the mothers, the memories of the first errand
turn into mail correspondences back and forth several times a year.
Happy new year
Children really grow up in the blink of an eye.
New year greetings
I would truly be happy if I received this kind of letter.
Right?
Yes.
It really is impressive.
Putting things
in order is important.
If you just leave the letters around in a big messy pile
when you want to look back
you would think "where did I put it again".
This is a folder.
Folder
Holds something important.
Inside of the folders we have also collected images from the errands.
We have shown the images to Moriguchi.
These are the brothers Hen!
She remembers the entire story.
This is when they went out.
Ah, it's that, right?
It's the errand where they had to bring a hairpin from the beauty salon for a wedding.
That's right.
These children sure can talk.
The
chit
chat
kind of women.
Now we will present you the chit chatting for free.
Talking sisters in practice!
Aichi â— Toyokawa
Toga shrine in Aichi prefecture.
It's been said that
a bride marrying here will be happy.
Since the one making sure you look pretty is the esteemed Beru.
She runs the beauty salon
associated with the shrine.
She has two grandchildren. Maya and Momoka.
Maya
4 years and 3 months
Momoka
2 years and 7 months
"Grandma is great" the big sister says admiringly
followed by her little sister.
The grandmother's beauty salon.
Grandmother is busy so they have come to help their mother.
Salon
Belle Jouvence
Grandmother is busy so they have come to help their mother.
Please line up the slippers.
Momo sure is in high spirits.
Not those slippers.
She is so mature.
These are for the customers. Not us kids.
A model big sister.
Not like that.
These can be found over there.
I see.
She was arranging them?
That's a big sis for you.
She has lined up
many slippers.
What a
prosperous help.
Here is the phone.
The errand is about to start.
Hello, this is Belle salon.
It's me.
Yes?
It's the grandmother.
I want to use a yellow ornate hairpin for the bride
Can you have Maya and Momo bring it?
Yellow hairpin.
They have a lot of hairpins at the headquarters. About 40.
Look here.
Cute.
Dreamy â¤
A desirable bride.
You understand that it's no good if they break.
Can you bring those?
Yes.
Even Momo?
Momo, can you do it?
If sister is going then I will too.
Since mom here can't go,
Maya will be mother.
Mother Maya.
Call her that.
Mother Maya
Listen to what mother Maya tells you.
Can you pay attention to cars?
Always doing the routine.
Raise your right hand.
You can't cross yet.
Right, left, right ...
You are not looking.
Cute.
And now Momo can cross with a raised hand.
Yes, perfect.
I want to see how pretty the bride is
Can you take
a picture?
Also taking a picture?
Say to the bride
"Congratulations
on the day"
"So beautiful"
Just like how adults do.
Do you want me to apply makeup
so you don't lose to the bride?
Yep.
Mother, letting the two girls do it takes great preparation.
Of course, it's the first time they try makeup.
Momo's extraordinary smile.
Lipstick?
Fabulous.
What to do. You've become
prettier than the bride.
Momo loves being treated as an adult.
What about big sister?
You don't have to make that face.
How great. It's done.
Are you ready? Can you go?
Yep.
Grandmama is waiting, let's run.
You shouldn't run. You will fall over.
Totally mother Maya.
We crab walk here.
Overcoming it superbly.
Next obstacle is to cross this bridge.
Toga shrine
For 2-year-and-7-month-old Momo
these stairs are a bit too tough.
Why haven't we arrived at Toga shrine yet?
After you cross here it's not far.
Good day.
Someone they know?
Mother Maya greets strangers in the neighborhood.
We finally reached the hallway.
I see, the shrine gate is a hallway.
Mother Maya keeps others safe.
Cars are crossing.
Momo, don't raise your hand.
You must hold my hands.
Momo
She's mad.
What did mom say?
Listen to what mother Maya says.
That's what she said!
Jeez
You don't listen to what I say.
Mother Maya
What?
Momo, you sure know the words to please your sister.
Let's go.
Ah, there are leaves.
Yes, because it is autumn.
Ah, it's because
it is autumn.
She understands
the seasons.
Right.
When it becomes autumn, Momo becomes
so super happy inside.
What about you Maya?
Maya likes winter
Winter is so darn cold
But you can make snowmen
which makes me happy.
Yes! Momo loves snowmen.
Sorry to stop you here but you've already arrived.
Ah! This is grandmas house.
No, not her house, her workplace.
Amazing.    So white.
Mr. horse is here.
See the horsie.
What about the compliments to the bride?
Congratulations for today
beautiful
Sorry, they just arrived.
The grandmother is inside.
This is the first time they enter
grandmothers workplace.
The carpet is so soft and
the kimonos are so pretty.
Momo
Cheer up Momo.
Excitingly entering the dressing room.
Scared of disturbing their grandmother during work.
Thanks for
helping me out.
She is especially kind today.
Thank you both for bringing it to me.
Even congratulated the bride properly.
Isn't it great?
Did you go to the bride?
So this is where grandmother works.
The bridal dress matches the color of the hairpin.
Isn't the bride
beautiful?
Yellow makes her even more beautiful.
Does it
suit her?
Isn't the ornate hairpin you brought elegant.
Thanks.
Let's take a picture of the bride.
Yes, we must also take a picture.
A testament to grandmother's important job.
Will it be fine?
I took it.
Image â— Maya
Got it all.
Even our staff in the background.
What kind of charm do you want? Momo.
"Go and buy a charm" said grandmother.
charm for being able to do homework fast
a charm for curing sickness.
There are many kind of charms, so?
What kind of charm do you want?
For babies
thing
So that a baby will be born healthy?
Momo wants a little sister.
If she has a little sister
she can help her mother.
A charm for babies being born healthy.
A safe birth charm.
Mom doesn't have such plans, though.
quick           quick
I want to hang it quickly.
Hand, hand, hand.
Don't complain.
That's what matters.
Again with that.
I want a little sister fast.
Let's do our best.
Mom will definitely be happy.
Momo, give me your hand.
Momo! Give me your hand. â˜ #ï¸ðŸ’£!
Do not cry.
I want a little sister.
We are back.
Welcome back.
Did you go and come back?
Amazing.
What a big sister.
I knew that I was able to do it.
Hurra
Here, a charm.
Wow, what charm did you purchase?
Momo wants that a baby
comes out healthy.
You bought a charm for that? Really?
Mom, I will ask for one more thing
A little sister that listens to what I say.
We keep our special filming equipment in the staff room.
Wait...
Isn't this great?
A remote controlled camera for filming inside.
Specially made.
I
this
want
It's too expensive.
I want this for my office.
It can be operated from 30 meters away.
In an apartment it can be used 1 to 5 floors away.
I wonder what it can be used for in a house.
I want everything.
This is nice.
At the bottom of Japan's tallest, Mount Fuji,
Yamanashi â— Fujikawaguchiko town
is a boy going on his first errand.
Mount Fuji can be seen from their house.
While known for strictness in his work
the father has a soft spot for children.
3 years
8 months
Shougo
He loves to pamper his only son.
He is raising a boy who is quick to cry.
His tough mother has decided
to send Shougo on an errand.
She believes that he can do it if he is by himself.
Can he do it without crying.
This is Shou(go).
The product that his mother has ordered has arrived.
It's here. What is it.
What has arrived is malt starch syrup.
Malt starch syrup
After hearing on TV that it is good for the throat after mixing it with daikon
she had it sent all the way from Sendai.
It's here.
I want to send some
to Runa's house.
Shougo, can you
bring it to them?
Eh!?
Look, it has started.
He will cry at these times.
Come come.
Not you Ri.
Shou.
Shou has been crying for 30 minutes.
Since mom has decided to make him go on an errand
she is hard set on not spoiling him no matter how long he cries for.
Sit!
Are you going?
I want to go.
You want to go?
Yes.
So he wants to go.
Can you do it?
Yes.
Will you do your best?
Do you really mean it?
Yes.
Do you want to try?
Okay.
Yes.
Will you go and see?
Mom, will you teach me?
I will,
I will teach you how.
Will you teach me the way?
I will. I will.
Can you quiet down
and go?
Yep.
Then go and pee first.
Home
Runa's house
Shared farm
Sister Chi's house
Taking daikon from everyone's farm
Giving sister Chi the daikon and 3 syrups
and finally giving Runa 2.
Sister Chi's baby, Mana, has a cold.
I have to bring this to her.
Arriving in the shared field.
All the children in the nursery school are free to take from it.
Everyone's field.
First, a quick lick of candy.
Yes, this is the good stuff.
The farm worker is a cameraman.
Shougo is too focused to notice.
This one.
He chooses the biggest one.
I will take this one.
Found it!
It's huge!
It stood out.
The biggest one.
So big that even mount Fuji would be surprised.
Isn't this the biggest daikon
in the entire shared field?
It will be tough to carry.
That's right.
Straight like a bee on an autumn road.
he has marched in small steps for 10 minutes
He is dragging
the daikon
It will bruise.
Ah, the syrup.
Oh no, he will cry.
Once he starts crying he can go on for 30 minutes.
Don't cry, don't cry, don't cry.
But he won't cry.
Mommy
He promised his mom
not to cry.
Do not cry, do not cry.
Today I will not cry.
I have decided not to cry.
Using the spare bag that the mother packed.
The mother
is remarkable.
As the mother said: "if you feel like crying
then look at mount Fuji."
All good. I won't cry.
Is the daikon alright?
It's no good if it becomes small.
But the daikon
is disappearing
Don't cry
Having overcome the urge to cry
the heavy carrying Shougo has come this far.
What? Is the daikon alright?
Hasn't it become small?
It's chafing, it's chafing.
It's chafing on the ground.
It sure was a big daikon.
It's being grated.
The beige house over there is sister Chi's house.
She is mother's cousin so they often come here.
Oh noes, there is a dog.
Woof
Got to escape.
I dropped it.
The bag ripped.
Have to overcome the disaster.
Won't cry this time.
Admirable.
Malt daikon.
He can't carry
all this.
He even became able to carry the entire daikon.
He sure has dragged it a lot.
So short.
Facing his fears.
Yes. I made it safely.
Phew, arrival.
Why is he still holding two?
I see, for Runa's house.
Pass the scary dog again.
Don't look, don't look
Yes, yes. If I don't look it won't be scary.
Runa's house is here.
No one is here so I will just leave it.
This is where
he leaves it?
Shou?
Where is
your mom?
This is Runa's mamma.
Mom is home.
You came
by yourself?
Yep.
That's so amazing. I got a phone call about it.
When it runs out I will personally bring you some more.
Thank you.
You came by yourself?
That's remarkable.
This is Runa who is the same age.
A policeman!
It's a cameraman.
A policeman.
Be careful.
He will arrest you.
Walk properly.
Suspicious.
Scary.
Please don't arrest me.
Bye bye
Bye bye.
Mother has called Chi and explained that something nice will arrive.
TN: Not actually his sister. He uses a honorific used
for someone who is like an older sister figure.
Sister
Chi.
Yes.
Malt daikon here.
It's you Shougo?
What? It's the daikon from before.
Ah, despite all his hardships it has become this small.
Where did you bring it from?
From the nursery school.
Nursery school?
Yep.
It used to be the biggest one.
Shou, you brought it?
It has become
grated daikon.
Mana has a cold.
Show us how you cut it at your home. Let's do it together.
Careful of your fingers.
So skilled.
Indeed, this is how you put it in.
Just like how your mother taught you.
5 minutes later.
Wow, we put more daikon in it than mother.
It's true.
the juice
Brother Shougo brought this for you.
This will help cure your cold.
She licked it.
Even if it doesn't taste good.
Try it out like you always do with your mother.
Did the mother's errand succeed or not?
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Not scared of a simple dog anymore.
I am not afraid
See? I am composed.
Maybe a bit scared still.
Bye bye.
Shougo has grown a lot.
Chi called mother right away and said:
"He was such a cry baby yesterday
what he accomplished today really surprised me."
Bye bye.
He returns home bigger and stronger.
Mother.
I'm coming home.
What's up?
Did you go?
Yes.
You are amazing.
Mom, I can do it.
Awesome. It's so amazing that you could.
Did you cry, though?
I totally did.
Shou, you might be greater than mount Fuji.
Fight!
Aaaaaaaaaaah!
Dad will be surprised.
Nine years
later
Was it really
that long ago?
Are you always preparing the daikon like this?
13 years old
Shougo
Yes.
Shougo is in 2nd grade of middle school.
He can even grate daikon now.
So you like
to cook?
I like it relatively.
On what
occasion?
When my mother is (coming home) late.
I think about what I want to make for her.
I will peek into the fridge and notice potatoes
so I start to wonder what can be made with potatoes
I will look into it and find out.
He finds it on the Internet.
What makes you want to make this for her?
Because she is always working so hard on her job.
Mix potatoes, starch and milk.
What is today's meal?
It's imo (potato) mochi.
Imomochi?
Mash the potatoes until soft.
If you don't
straighten it thin
it will become
like powder
I see.
I make
it round
and stretch
it thinner.
He puts cheese in it.
Instead of
salad oil
I usually
use butter
The flavor
is strong
which makes
it delicious.
It's done after being heated on both sides.
It's finished.
It's imomochi.
No way!
It's
Shou-made ã€ŒImomochiã€
- I'm home.
- Welcome home.
Today, mother comes home all happy.
We will add
grated daikon
for today.
They also add grated daikon?
Thanks for
the food.
Please enjoy.
Just right.
It's fluffy.
Just like always.
Thank you.
Mana has come over to play.
She's the baby from before.
She is in 5th grade in primary school.
Mana
No way.
She is destined to eat what Shougo makes for her.
Be honest if it's bad.
Delicious?
Delicious
She has become somewhat better at complimenting.
I also want to meet Runa.
So I decided to call her.
Runa?
They've come so...
What will do you? Can you come?
Right away!?
That embarrassing thing years ago.
What is she saying?
Wait 10 to 15 minutes.
10 to 15 minutes? Okay, okay.
We decided to go over there instead.
Runa is also in 2nd grade of middle school.
They are in the same class.
Runa
'day.
TN: It's worth noting that they use san next to her name - unlike what they did to Shougo - to treat her as an adult since she is a bit embarrassed by the past.
It's Runa.
I hate this.
Is that a policeman?
Yes, it's the same cameraman from that time.
What will he introduce us to this time in the staff room?
Seems like he has given up.
What's up with this coffee.
Smash in one of those that go grr grrr
buy it!
Is that possible?
Remember to put the recording equipment back.
What a plain-looking boombox.
We value our things. We have made the program for 20 years now.
Isn't it too plain-looking?
The chair is new.
Can't you use a nicer chair?
Is it not good?
It's no good. The dreams. The children's dreams.
Little by little we have surpassed the 20 year anniversary for the first episode.
It's like
my own neighborhood
that you are filming.
That's because we film from the perspective of a neighborhood.
"My First Errand" is wonderful.
No no.
Really.
Gotcha
What is that?
There was a gotcha.
What was gotcha again?
I remember! Choo choo.
What was it again? Oh, it was that. Gotcha.
Presenting Gotcha
Roar with laughter!
Tatsuya
4 years
This talkative brother just loves TV commercials
and his little brother follows suit.
Both the nursery school teachers and people from the neighborhood agree
Sacchan talks funny. That's what they say.
Their house is a store that's why he is so talkative.
Helping out today?
Here?
Yes, put
it there.
Here? Next to it?
This is Sea bream â— Japanese butterfish â— Tuna
The dad thought up an errand to make him buy an important item used in the store.
Look here Tatsuya, what has happened here?
The bulb has burned out.
LED Reflector Lamp
Has it happened again? Without the reflector lamp the sashimi won't look as appetizing.
Mom has thought of an errand.
There is no pacifier.
It has been lost. He will have to buy a new one for his little brother.
Not here?
Tacchan, can you go?
I will go.
Do your best.
Drugstore
Home
Home center
He will buy the lamp at the store with the red sign.
And a pacifier for his little brother at the drug store.
Even if Tatsuya is by himself he talks all the time.
Walking, walking, walking.
If I keep walking
won't I arrive?
The name of the lamp is difficult.
Reflector lamp
Indeed, reflector lamp.
We have told the store in advance that a camera man will come inside.
But we haven't told them who will come and purchase what.
"Please do as you always do" is what we told them.
Sounds hard.
This person is the customer
even though he is small.
What?
Perhaps the shop personnel hasn't noticed?
One of our reflector lamps burned out.
Say it in a loud voice.
Talking about the reflector lamp. It burned out.
Did it burn out?
We are fishmongers.
You have a fish store?
After it burned out we went into deep consideration about what to do
Then my mom said "go by yourself and get it".
What did you
come to
purchase?
Reflector lamp
I told you from the start that I want to buy a reflector lamp.
It's over here. There.
You finally get it. Reflector lamp.
Is this it? Reflector lamp.
Can you take it with you?
It's such a difficult thing to buy.
This is the correct item but this product is slightly different from our usual.
Is there another kind?
Amazing.
There is a different one but...
Here we go again.
Yeah, it was different but one burned out. So...
I see.
Thank you for going with it, sister.
Tatsuya's talking engine has been kickstarted.
Next is his brother's pacifier.
Not talkifier, pacifier.
A pacifier please. Remember to say that.
Welcome.
Hey you, gotcha.
What?
Gotcha is totally lost.
Gotcha?
Gotcha is lost.
Do you understand "to lose"?
*Mumbling* Rikuto.
Rikuto...  gotcha... lost. What?
Gotcha!
Cameraman please make it clear. What is gotcha?
We don't know.
Sorry, some assistance please.
Hey, it's a pacifier.
Tatsuya doesn't get it.
Why don't you know gotcha?
Get me a real adult.
Please, can you take care of this customer?
Someone must know. Since there are so many people here.
Veteran
shop employee.
Where is the gotcha? Gotcha.
Rikuto's gotcha. Where is it?
Just as expected from a veteran.
She knows what a gotcha is.
That's what we thought but then she just got another person from the back office.
Gotcha.
Gotcha?
It's a gotcha.
It belongs to Riku.
Then he lost it. We can't find it anywhere.
What is it used for?
Let me see. It's used for sleeping.
Used for sleeping?
That's what a gotcha is.
Used when sleeping?
Can't know.
And...
In the shop... until noon.
Sleeping until afternoon.
Since he eats lunch.
At that time.
During that time he uses the gotcha.
The staff hurries to the mother and asks her.
We need to ask you.
What happened?
What is a gotcha?
A pacifier. A pacifier.
A pacifier?
How did it become a gotcha?
When Rikuto finds the pacifier he gladly proclaims "gotcha!"
so Rikuto calls pacifiers for gotchas.
Doesn't Tatsuya know it's called a pacifier?
How could he know?
It's a gotcha, you know.
That's right, a gotcha.
It's a gotcha. That's what they are.
Was it really a gotcha...?
Gotcha is just fine.
Gotcha
Is it called a gotcha?
It must be hard for him.
It's not
something
you eat?
You shouldn't never eat it.
Do you
put it on
your head?
What will you do if you put it on your head?
Wrong
You chew on it.
Exactly, it's a pacifier. What a great kid. Now the store manager has to know.
Is this it?
It's a bit too small.
Actually, it is breast goods.
What a tough situation. Maybe they've sold out of gotchas.
Found it here.
It is there.
-This thing here?
-No.
It is yellow here.
And there is no Winnie-the-Pooh on it.
That's how a proper gotcha looks.
Please have a look and tell me which one.
-Among these?
-Which?
-Like Ronald McDonald's...
-Ronald's?
Ronald's...
-The normal kind.
-Normal?
Found it
This this.
This indeed.
Found it. This is it. Finally found it.
Found it.
Gotcha           found it.
This here is a gotcha.
ã€ŒGotchaã€
The yellow and blue kind.
Precisely the same as the one Rikuto has.
Congratulations, big brother.
There are so many adults who are unfamiliar with gotchas.
Even that man following me didn't know.
I went by myself.
Welcome back. Did you come back from shopping?
All by yourself? Oh, father is waiting. Hurry up.
Yes, the lamp.
This is great.
Amazing.
Did it.
It's bright now.
What is this?
Gotcha
Is it a gotcha?
No mistake about it.
Wakayama castle
In Wakayama castle Yoshimune was born as the Tokugawa shogunate.
Speaking about lords, doesn't that make you think of umeboshi?
Here is a shop that sells luxury umeboshi.
Please regard these optimal
a vast amount of the most luxurious plumps.
At this shop the one who will go on their first errand is
Ririi
4 years
3 months
Ririi who is refined like an adult.
Please give a hand over where.
She is very self-composed.
She never troubles her mother.
And often helps out.
Even friends of the mother say: "She is like an adult".
Though she is
at such a
young age.
She is like a mother.
Yeah, she's great.
She's still a child, though.
Cute.
Grandmother often visits and
they often go shopping in the neighborhood together.
Great. Just like me.
Mama...
Tomorrow,
we will get
some visitors
Can you go
and purchase
umeboshi?
Yes.
Two of mothers friends will come from Tokyo.
The umeboshi's
name is
ã€ŒKuuã€
Kuu!
I understand.
Kuu (sky) refers to the size of the box.
The size for a personal gift.
Kuu sized
Honey and
shiso
(a mint plant)
please.
Honey and shiso please.
Okay. Great.
They are ordering two kinds, made with honey and shiso.
Today is
my birthday.
I would like
to eat some cake.
You can!
Can you buy it for me?
What I want
from the
cake shop
is ã€Œcabbageã€.
Roger that.
Cabbage from the cake shop?
Sprinkling macha powder on huge cream puffs
wow, it looks like cabbage.
Looks tasty.
Money for visiting
Ksitigarbha*.
TN: Ksitigarbha is a bodhisattva who looks over children, travelers and the underworld
I will
take it
in my hand.
You will hold it in your hand?
Same as when she goes with grandmother.
I will depart!
Yes.
Will you
be fine?
I will be fine!
-See you.
Take care.
I will.
When people say she is adult-like this could this be it?
Pink boots and strawberry fur coat.
Cute.
Making a fine face.
We can now see the shop for the luxury umeboshi.
Looking right, looking left and then right again.
Even if there are no cars she is a kid who does what she sets out to do.
This is not the kind of shop where a kid goes inside by themself.
Can she carry herself as an adult?
Welcome.
Shiso and
Hello.
honey,
please.
She remembered.
Honey and what?
Shiso please.
Honey and shiso.
What honey
did mother
say?
Kuu
ã€ŒKuuã€,
you are
awesome.
I was so nervous.
Will you eat
umeboshi?
Yeah
Since we are being refined
we will sample the umeboshi with some warm tea.
Just like a proper adult.
Here you go valued customer.
She seems
a bit perplexed.
Yeah.
What a gracefully light-colored tea cup.
Get a good grip on it.
Will she
find it
palatable?
What a refined way to hold it.
It's hot.
She totally drinks
like an adult.
They are using a pretty nice tea here.
My mother loves umeboshi
Does she?
Here you go.
Please flatter a bit more.
This is her first time trying umeboshi.
First experience.
Wonder how
she'll react.
A bit
too sour?
Sorry.
What an adult taste.
"I will put your change in" thinks the shop assistant.
I will give it to Ksitigarbha
so I will hold it in my hands.
You will
hold it?
Okay.
For Ksitigarbha? I apologize.
Since I couldn't enjoy the umeboshi
I hope I behaved well today.
Maybe I didn't.
Thank you
very much.
It's fine. Looks like I didn't do badly.
I am able to do this errand just like an adult.
Next is the cake.
This is Ririi who has finished purchasing luxury umeboshi.
If it is a cake shop then I can go in without constraints.
Despite there being no customer on the other side the door moves.
She noticed.
Welcome.
Hello.
Her face is relaxed.
What do
YOU want?
What looks
good?
The cream puff that looks like a cabbage, right?
This one?
Strawberry short cake?
It has been purchased.
Oh yeah, even the coat is strawberry.
She must really like strawberry.
It's fine.
It's supposed
to cabbage.
It's fine.
On the way is Ksitigarbha.
Holding on to the 25 yen all this time they've gotten warm.
It is said that this will double your chance*.
TN: 20 and 5 yen sounds like doubling your chances.
She is putting it in
correctly.
She's great.
She is.
She must do this
often with grandmother.
I love my mother so much.
What a great child.
She sure is.
Mama!
Yes?
I bought cake and umeboshi.
That was quick.
I am surprised.
She was faster than her mother.
Perfect.
You got the
right thing.
This and this.
Mother, we have one unfortunate announcement.
Isn't it too small?
What is this?
Isn't this Ririi's favorite cake?
Definitely!!
Got you good.
It's fine. I can eat strawberry.
"My first errand - Never give up - Baby Special"
It really is amazing to see when children do their best.
I shouldn't lose to their spirit.
Oh yeah, the band that sings the theme song "B.B.Queens"
They are currently in the studio recording a new album.
We will be the first to bring you
"Never give up, baby" 2011 version.
Never give up, Baby
Let's give it a listen.
Never give up, baby  go to sleep and feel better
Don't you worry about mother's needs
Never give up, baby   let's go for a walk
Let's look for a flower bouquet and go home
More than dad I know the kindness of mother's eyes
The beauty boasts of me and is my best friend
I only have one request don't throw thunder around me
because both dad and I will be good kids
Never give up, baby let's drink the two of us
half of the milk is left     just don't cry
Don't give up, baby when you grow up
I will definitely present my bride to you, mother
July the 18th on marine day we will bring you another special
It's starting. Don't lose to the children!