Hamada's Holiday in Thailand.
These six comedians
have researched about Pattaya...
...to pitch fun activities to Hamada.
Inomoto's choice, ranked sixth by Hamada was...
Pattaya's popular attraction,
the floating market.
The canals are the roads.
It feels very Thai.
This is great.
Greetings.
This is relaxing.
-We have a local on board.
-Really?
Shall we get a drink?
Good idea.
I wish they sold drinks here.
That place looks good.
-Where?
-To the right.
Tapioca drinks.
You like tapioca, Hamada?
No I don't!
-Tapioca suits the tropics.
-It doesn't.
Let's drink some.
-Let's go for tapioca.
-Okay.
He's taking us there.
Let's go there.
Since we are here...
We'll get tapioca?
Let's do it.
I guess we'll drink some.
What technique.
We can buy it from the boat.
Let's go for it.
Can we order like this?
-Is someone serving?
-Hello.
Let's buy some!
Yeah, let's buy.
-Do you have cash?
-I'll pay.
I'll pay. It was my idea.
-I've got this.
-Taiki, you pay.
Thank you.
Excuse me...
Seshita and Masayoshi, you're going to
fan me from behind, right?
You brought a fan, right?
-Here.
-Thank you.
A fan...?
Here you go.
You didn't bring a fan?
Well...
-The fan?
-That works.
No, don't blow on me.
That's gross.
-Please don't blow on me.
-Least I can do.
It's lukewarm.
Don't blow on me.
-I can use this.
-That's good.
Thank you.
They cost...
240, free one.
One, two...
One's free?
-300.
-Thank you.
She thinks we're Korean.
We're Japanese. Arigato gozaimashita.
-Thank you.
-That's it!
Tastes like real tapioca balls.
Delicious.
Tasty rice balls.
It's tapioca.
I paid for it, so let me tell you, it's tapioca.
-Masayoshi, you wanted to come here?
-Yes.
I know we've got drinks,
but there's lots of food too.
-Thailand is known for seafood.
-Seafood?
-We can buy it from the boat?
-That's right.
They're selling T-shirts.
Durian T-shirts.
It says "durian" on it.
You should buy that.
Stop the boat, please.
Might be better to get off first.
That'll be easier.
-That'll be fun to have.
-They even have those.
You won't get it anywhere else.
Remember where the shop is.
Look at the corn.
-The Dorians...
-Look.
Look, grilled corn.
Looks delicious.
What's this?
It's crocodile meat.
Crocodile? Wow!
30 bahts. That's about 100 yen.
Do you want to try it?
Hirai, try it.
Go back.
Masayoshi didn't do a good job explaining.
-Hamada, Hirai will eat this?
-Yes.
Let's eat some crocs!
I'm not too excited.
Seshita will eat crocs too!
Seshita too?
No spicy.
Who wants spicy?
Spicy for me.
Crocodile looks tasty.
-Do you want one?
-You try it first.
Here we go.
Let's try it.
You'll get hives!
-If it gets you sick.
-How was it?
-It's delicious.
-Really?
-What's it like?
-A cross between chicken and pork.
Only 100 yen a stick.
It doesn't taste funky.
It's good.
Good, right? Tastes like chicken.
Delicious.
Good.
It's very tasty.
It is.
A genuine Thai vibe.
The Pattaya vibe.
The Pattaya ambience.
Everything looks tasty.
This is nice. Thanks.
-Thanks, Inomoto.
-We found this by chance.
Thank you, Inomoto.
-It was my idea...
-Can we stop by a store?
I've seen that on TV before.
It was an experience.
This looks like fun. This kind of shopping.
This market is great.
What's that?
Is it takoyaki?
-Takoyaki?
-A whole octopus on top.
Interesting.
Taiki. Buy some.
-Me?
-He told you.
I paid earlier.
Just buy some.
I want to taste the takoyaki here.
Three packs for 100 bahts.
Unusual takoyaki... very interesting.
Thank you.
Eating this is a bit...
Eat it.
I'm on a diet.
What?
Just eat it. We bought all this.
Don't tell me you're on a diet.
Dig in. It's the Hamada diet.
Yeah, the Hamada diet.
Go for it.
-It's delicious.
-Is it good?
It's heavy on the batter, but...
...the octopus has good texture,
and the sauce is nice.
It tastes like the Japanese sauce. It's good.
Maybe they use Japanese sauce.
I think the seaweed they use is better.
Go on, eat more.
-No, I had enough.
-Stop talking, eat.
The Hamada diet is about eating carbs.
It's very stodgy. Loads more batter
than the takoyaki you get in Osaka.
It's octopus on top of a ball of batter.
It's good but very heavy.
So many unfamiliar things.
-There is.
-Is that duck?
-That's duck.
-It's the beak.
I thought it was a spoon.
Wow. Impressive.
Wonderful!
Who's eating?
Who's eating scorpion?
-There's scorpion?!
-Scorpion.!
Or grubs. Who's eating grubs?
What insect's larvae are they?
What insect do they turn into?
Hirai. You're up.
Which one? I'll let you choose.
Lucky, you get a choice.
Hirai, go for the scorpion.
Is it good?
Never been so close to a scorpion.
Not the eyes. I don't eat with my eyes.
-You start from the claws?
-Is it edible?
-This is scary.
-Go for it.
When you bite down, the legs move.
This is a new texture for me.
What does it taste like?
Can you eat it like that?
That's disgusting.
No way...
Oh, it's delicious!
-No way...
-Scorpion's too much.
I can't believe you ate it.
-It's not that bad.
-I can't take the smell.
-It tastes like liver.
-Seriously?
So it's soft?
You're sweating like a pig.
It boosted my metabolism.
You ate scorpion, and now you're all sweaty.
-Taiki, 200.
-I've paid.
Thank you.
We should have bought those T-shirts.
They're over there.
Oh yeah?
There it is!
I found it!
It's perfect for you.
This is really nice.
-Do they have my size?
-You're really into it.
-I want one.
-You should both get one.
Now?
You'll have to buy it.
Hey, it fits.
That's great!
I'm surprised they have his size.
-How is it, Hirai?
-It's the best!
Durian!
"Dorians!"
They'll both buy it.
He doesn't look happy about it.
-Taiki, what's up?
-What's with that expression?
Isn't it lame?
-Well...
-It's fine for Thailand.
We were looking for an outfit for our duo. Right?
No we were not!
Hirai, pay for it.
Oh, thanks.
Hamada, I'm like everyone's sponsor.
I've paid for everything.
You said you'd pay.
Yes, for the tapioca drinks.
But the shirts are for your duo.
It'd be odd for us to pay.
-What's that about?
-A laugh machine.
He pisses me off.
-That was good.
-Thank you.
That's a good buy.
You're not going to wear it, Taiki?
-What's that?
-Sandals.
Who'd wear that?
-Fish sandals.
-It's funny.
-They look fun.
-The first time I've seen one.
-Hirai's buying sandals.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-This, okay.
Looks like a plate at a Japanese restaurant.
Taiki, your partner is unbelievable.
It's too small.
It's the biggest size.
Don't force it.
Take your socks off.
You look really fat now.
So tacky!
Your feet look fat.
Weird sandals.
You could never get them in Japan.
Can't get them in Japan.
That's about it.
There were lots of nice shops,
food, and drinks too.
-That's good.
-I enjoyed it. I'm glad we came.
Right? When you come,
you realize it's worth a visit.
Next up, Inomoto has arranged for
Hamada's favorite activity: golf.
Inomoto, thanks for taking us
to the floating market.
It was the best. It really feels like a trip.
Excuse me. Sorry for interrupting, everyone.
It was my idea.
-You did a good job explaining.
-Thanks.
I've got more information.
We're lucky that we got this taxi.
It was because Inomoto was facing this way.
The thing is, there's another beach back there.
Actually, I wanted to go there.
I see.
I thought it'd take us up to lunch.
There's a good restaurant there.
-"Cafe des Amis."
-I found that online.
It's really famous.
Right.
It's ranked number one
in the Pattaya restaurant rankings.
Yes, number one on TripAdvisor.
And it's ranked seventh in Asia.
Seriously?!
The idea was to suggest going for lunch there.
But we happened upon the market,
so we went there instead.
But it turned out well.
It happens.
Oh yeah...
-Remember how I bought these?
-Yep.
I was thinking...
And I bought a pair for Hamada's wife Natsumi.
She might like it.
That's nice.
It's better to buy gifts as we go.
A different color.
-Cute color!
-Pink!
She'll love it.
-She'd like this, right?
-Yeah.
She'd say, "I'm not wearing that, idiot!"
-You think she'd say that?
-Would she?
I got a different color for Hamada too.
-There's a blue one?
-Wow, a blue one.
Hamada likes blue.
No way. When would I wear that?
You and your wife.
"I'm not wearing that, idiot!"
Natsumi, what do you think of these?
"No way, idiot!"
You're imitating your own wife?
-Does it fit?
-Perfect fit.
I had trouble finding his size.
-I'm so glad.
-Thank you.
Hamada and the group arrive
at Thailand's leading golf course.
Siam Country Club Plantation.
Stop that.
Cut that out. Sheesh.
That's too edgy, cut it out.
-You practiced?
-Don't act like him.
We're here.
-How is it?
-Great.
We've come all the way to Thailand,
so we should play.
Let's play.
Owing to its stunning beauty,
this world-renowned golf course
hosted the LPGA tour in 2009.
The course exploits the natural landscape,
allowing one to revel in
the beautiful and strategic course.
There are restaurant
and shop facilities on the grounds.
They are sure to delight all visitors.
This is a beautiful course.
They first head to the "Sugar Cane Course."
The sixth hole is a short par three.
What will they be doing here?
Closest to the pin
with Hamada against the other six.
-How was it last time?
-Last time...
-We got three on the green.
-Yes.
-But then Hamada won by two meters.
-What a superstar.
It was in Guam.
That's right. That was good.
Say it again. How many meters?
-Two meters.
-That's right.
You were closer.
We'll hit one each.
-And you get three.
-Okay, I understand.
If we win, dinner's on you.
Yeah!
OK? And if you win, you can slap us.
Understood.
I'll slap you as much as I like.
Isn't it one slap?
First up is Tsutsumi of Dorians.
Ah! I topped it!
Don't worry, we've got more shots.
Too much to the right!
The team of six isn't doing too well today.
That's no good.
-It's too short.
-Yeah.
-Looks good.
-It's too short.
Is that so?
No good.
After five shots,
no one has landed on the green.
Last up is Hirai of Dorians.
Nice!
It's going straight.
Is it on the green?
-Might be the collar?
-Yeah.
Wait! It's rolling back.
-I did it!
-Amazing!
Nice!
-Seriously?
-It rolled back.
Incredibly, Hirai's super shot got him
less than two meters from the pin.
It's going to be hard to beat that.
Hirai's shot was awesome.
Uh oh!
-It's straight.
-No way.
Seriously?
No way.
-No!
-It's gone right.
No! It's gone over there.
It rolled so much.
Hirai is much closer.
Two more shots.
Hamada really is good. He got it on his first shot.
It went straight.
He's going to adjust his shot now.
Perfect distance.
He's got three chances.
This isn't good!
-And it's a straight shot.
-Oh no!
Don't go there.
Go right, right!
It's rolling.
There it goes!
-That could have gone either way.
-It went slightly to the right.
-It was right or left.
-It was close.
Hirai's still got this.
-Your last ball.
-Hamada is good.
You keep saying that.
He'll adjust his shot even more.
He said it was off.
He adjusted slightly to the left.
Oh no!
It's no good.
It's no good. Too far left.
-I'm sorry.
-We win!
We did it!
We won!
He seems disappointed.
Thank you.
I'll tell you the truth now...
-I have a fractured bone.
-Really?
For real? Where?
My pinky. I can't grip the club.
Your right hand?
What's he saying?
-Just slap Iwahashi, and we'll call it even.
-Okay.
His pinky is broken.
What's that for?
What the heck?
My neck turned against my will.
What was that about?
That was too strong for comedy.
They continue on Sugar Cane Course.
First hole, par four.
A very tricky hole with an acute left curve.
We'll split into groups and set the rules.
We can keep adding one baht to the pool.
We'll use that for dinner or something.
The teams are:
Hamada and Iwahashi, Inomoto and Hirai,
and the last three are...
The numbers don't work.
Taiki and Seshita team up.
Hold on...
You're on your own.
What? That's not fair.
-Let me join a team.
-It's alright.
About the rules, we're in Thailand.
It's a country with many transgender women.
Normally we ban English,
but as soon as Hamada says to start,
we'll all talk like women.
-Like women?
-Since it's Thailand.
Instead of banning English.
We'll talk like women.
If someone doesn't, the team is liable
and will have to pay one baht.
Don't talk girly, pay one baht.
Masayoshi is like a transgender woman.
I guess so.
-That's an advantage.
-It is.
If he teams up, it'd be unfair. So he's alone.
I see. Thank you, honey.
He's good at it.
Hamada will start it.
Here we go...
Get ready... go!
Yay! This is like so much fun!
Totally fun!
It's so pretty here!
-It's too much.
-Enough already.
Who's going first? Let's decide.
Let's pick the order.
-You decide.
-Really?
Rock, paper, scissors.
Seshita, you go.
Ready? Rock, paper, scissors.
Oh no, I lost! Can't believe it.
Why did I use scissors first?
Rock, paper, scissors.
Oh no, I lost!
Scissors are totally weak.
I wish I hadn't used scissors.
Let's pause a moment.
I think we've gone too far.
Is it too much?
You guys are going full throttle.
What was all that?
-Do that bit when you lost.
-Oh no, I lost.
-That's too much.
-Why did I use scissors?
That's unnecessary.
Start over. Go.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Ouch! Why did you kick me? You're mean!
Stop, think about her feelings.
Violence is wrong.
I'm leaving.
-Wait, wait.
-I can't do this.
It's taking too long.
Let's decide the order.
It took some time, but the order is as follows.
First up is Dorians Tsutsumi.
It got stuck.
Pretty good...
That wasn't girly.
Taiki is out.
Taiki! I can't believe it!
It got caught.
I'm up. It's my turn.
It flew too far.
-That wasn't girly.
-It was feminine.
It sounded masculine.
Yeah. Just hit the ball.
You're just talking normally.
Penalty for Hamada.
He's so brazen.
I have to watch my tics.
Will the caddies laugh at my tics?
What about the locals?
They're laughing.
-What are you doing?
-Take your shot.
Hurry, take your shot.
Might be too far.
That's too far.
Is it out?
-It's safe.
-Thank you!
It's safe!
The teams' positions are as shown.
After this, girly talking causes turmoil.
Was mine out? "Chaplin, bolin-bolin..."
What does that mean?
I'll pay one baht, so let me say this. You suck!
It's really bad. You suck at it.
-Masayoshi.
-Yes? Me?
You're over here.
I'm exposed. Forgive me.
I'm so embarrassed. Don't film me.
-All exposed. So embarrassed.
-You're great at this talk.
This ball is blushing.
Go get your club!
Amazing shot. It looks good.
Wow!
By the pin!
A bit far.
Good one! Yay!
Such high spirits.
How bendy is her spine?
-Hurry it up, girl.
-Hamada is mad.
Wait up! When we go, we go together.
Why does he sound like that?
That girl's so not funny.
Don't say that she isn't funny.
Don't say I'm not funny.
She's got good ears.
That's what I said.
-What are you saying?
-Hurry up.
-That's out, right?
-Not girly.
That's just scary.
Really scary!
-You're scaring me.
-My tics are gone.
That was so weak.
That was weak.
Excuse, for that weak shot.
What's "excuse"? I might hit you.
-Oh girl, you're scary.
-That's the scariest.
She's seriously scary.
Looks good.
Almost!
You're good.
Just put it in.
Nice!
We did it.
Here's how much each team was penalized.
The money will be spent on dinner.
Though it was my idea, it wasn't a good one.
Agreed.