Hamada and his juniors have arrived
in Pattaya, Thailand.
Let's go.
They check out Hamada's suite.
Let's have a look.
What a view.
-This is amazing.
-It's beautiful.
I'm not from here, but welcome to Pattaya.
Thank you, Pattaya!
Look at this bath.
There's no privacy.
This is awesome.
It's...wait, what's he doing?
Who's in the bath?
Nobody's used it yet.
Seriously?
Who...? Oh, it's him.
Hey! What are you doing?
It's great. I was sweaty.
Don't get my towels wet. They're unused.
The bath towels?
Don't get them wet, I said.
Turn off the shower.
Don't take a dump!
You're butt naked!
He'll be mad.
This is comfortable.
What are you doing?
You're dead.
It's comfortable.
Drain that filthy water...
What on earth are you doing?
Is he for real?
You've gone too far.
The bathroom's soaked.
It's like a sinking ship.
They were still gaining their footing.
Six young comedians
gave presentations on Pattaya to Hamada.
They really tried this time.
In past seasons, they were really sloppy.
They relied too much on the staff.
This time, they took more responsibility.
I'm relieved.
I'm seeing their individual strengths.
They're now at the starting line.
The past seasons were dry runs.
Let's see who came in fourth place
for their presentation.
Fourth place, for 200 bahts, goes to...
Seshita!
He did a great job.
Thank you.
He actually fought for it.
That was incredible.
I'm really happy.
I didn't think you'd actually fight.
Neither did I.
I thought we'd just observe.
Was three minutes long?
It was. I couldn't believe it.
Let's see Seshita's presentation.
It's Seshita's turn.
Isn't it hot?
It is.
So let's go somewhere indoors.
Sounds good.
It's a mall called
"Central Festival Pattaya Beach."
It's the biggest mall in Pattaya.
A shopping mall?
-We don't really have time to buy souvenirs.
-True.
And I know that you have family,
so you can get them gifts there.
-It's the biggest mall?
-Absolutely.
But shopping malls are common.
Plu's, it's close to our hotel.
Then whoever wants to can go after we wrap up.
But we'll hang out in your room then.
Why?
We need to keep that time.
There's a fruit market nearby.
Sounds great.
We can try tropical fruits and fruit juices...
...that we can only get in Thailand.
When we tried tapioca juice,
we were all so happy, right?
Here's the video.
Stick to your presentation.
Everyone was so happy then.
You're presenters, not editors.
It's just that it was so fun last time.
He's a real pro.
Anyway, there's juice.
And fruits?
And there's another thing near there.
When you think of Thailand, you think of Muay Thai.
It's a must-see.
This is Thailand, after all.
-The K-1 fighter, Takeru...
-Yes.
He went to that gym to train during high school...
...and became the K-1 fighter he is today.
I see. What can we see there?
-We can watch professional boxers train.
-I see.
They're there, and we can also train with them.
You can try Muay Thai.
-No way.
-It's too dangerous.
You've never done a Muay Thai kick, right?
I don't want to, but I do want to observe.
You can experience Muay Thai
at this gym, so how about it?
I'd be interested in observing.
-Not fighting?
-Exactly, I won't fight.
Then do you want to see me,
a former street punk, fight?
Seshita, don't be reckless.
Don't talk crazy.
I really want you to come.
-Look at his eyes.
-He's dead serious.
I might even win.
-You?
-Yes.
You're so confident.
That's unlikely.
Street fighters always win.
You work out, but...
I've been training extensively at a fitness gym.
I guess it would be interesting to see Muay Thai.
Yes, to see it live.
It's all nearby, so let's go.
The gym and the fruit market?
Let's go.
Fine then.
-You'll go?
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
-OK.
Let's go.
Seriously, Muay Thai?
We can see it live.
Sure, but why must Seshita fight?
-You'll win?
-Damn right.
And so the group heads out
for Muay Thai and the fruit market.
They go first to the gym.
This way.
-It's this way.
-Camera's over there!
Sorry. That's a great punch.
-You're warming up.
-I'm not.
This way.
What is this?
It doesn't seem like a gym, does it?
It's like a hotel.
It is a hotel.
It's a hotel?
-The gym is over this way.
-Next to a hotel?
This is one of the reasons why
it's popular among foreign kick boxers.
They stay here and train here.
There's a gym. It's really a hotel.
Yes, there's a normal gym, too.
This is really the place for sports.
Just past it is our destination.
Wow.
It's so clean.
Look at the sandbags.
-Look.
-It's huge.
There are so many boxing rings in here.
Look at those fighters.
They're training. See?
Wow.
That's Muay Thai?
Look at them go.
-Wow, he got it right in the jaw.
-Is he alright?
Hello. Excuse me.
Sorry.
-Hello.
Tell us your names.
I'm Semapet.
I'm Chawalit.
What titles do you have?
I'm a Channel 7 Champion.
Champion?
Champion? Wow.
I'm the champion of Pathum Thani Province.
The provincial champion.
Can you train with the sandbags?
They'll kick and punch?
This is incredible.
They're preparing.
We get to see all of this.
His shorts are really high.
It doesn't matter.
Stop, sir. Let's go back to your room.
-Sir...
-I'm not senile.
Sorry. He's kidding.
There are so many types.
How do you use them?
You kick down here, I guess.
That's the head, or not?
Really?
They kick there, too.
It's really heavy.
It's heavy.
This is incredible.
There's a ring for cage fighting.
-That one?
-Yes.
-This gym is huge.
-It is.
I wonder if it's ever full.
There must be many boxers.
Apparently, it becomes packed at times.
On TV, you see gyms in dirty garages.
This is really clean.
Look at him.
Wow.
It's amazing.
What do you think?
Can they use their elbows?
Yes you can and even grab the opponent.
-You can?
-Yes.
Wow.
Thank you!
They're amazing.
Isn't it intense?
Yes, watching them up close like this.
This sandbag is heavy,
but they kick it like it's nothing.
-That was amazing.
-He's a champ, yeah.
Let's see them spar a little.
Really?
Please start.
That looks painful.
He keeps going for the head.
The red one.
Did you see that grab?
-That's allowed?
-Yes, in Muay Thai.
He goes for the head.
Watch out!
Don't kick in the head!
He's supposed to.
Are you his coach?
He's telling him not to kick.
A body blow.
Ouch.
He grabs him!
That's karate.
Thank you.
Incredible.
That was incredible.
That was really intense.
Amazing.
Shall we go?
-Incredible.
-What?
Aren't you forgetting something?
-He is.
-That's not what you presented.
You want me to fight?
You said that you would.
That's why we came.
It's a let-down.
Ask him to fight with Seshita.
Would you spar with him?
-Sure.
-He agreed.
That's settled, then.
That was quick.
Please tell him Seshita is saying,
"I'll kill you."
Wait...
OK.
Come on.
What was your nickname again?
My old nickname? The Red Devil of the South.
How lame!
Go on, Red Devil. Tell them who you are.
Hey! You may be Muay Thai boxers, but...
What are you doing?
Quit doing that or...
What did you say?
Look.
Go do that.
Go, Seshita! Put that down and go.
Let's go.
-Come on!
-Let's go, Seshita.
You can win, Seshita.
That's a punch? Give me...
Time out! Time out!
He's hilarious.
How is it, Seshita?
A piece of cake.
-Liar!
-You were on the floor.
He can also try receiving kicks.
Yes, to see how strong it is.
It's worth trying.
Kick, kick.
Let's go!
He can aim for the chin, too.
Be serious.
Where? Like this?
Impressive!
How's his kick?
It's impressive!
I'll keep my guard up.
Ouch! That hurt!
Ouch!
He's strong!
-How is it?
-A piece of cake.
-I'll win for sure.
-Really?
I used to be a delinquent.
Go, Red Devil!
Now for Seshita versus
the Muay Thai Champion.
Fight hard for one round, three minutes.
Stare him down!
A Japanese glare!
Here he goes!
He's intimidated!
You can do it!
Go, Seshita!
One round. Ready, go!
Get in a kick!
Kick him!
Good one!
Keep your eyes open.
Come on.
Punch him.
Go! Go!
He's losing stamina.
He grabbed him!
What's that?
What move is that?
One minute.
Two minutes left!
You can do it!
Seshita!
Seshita, Seshita, Seshita!
That was a clean hit.
Come on!
You can do it, Seshita!
Come on, you can do it!
He got a knee kick.
Seshita, come on!
Are you giving up?
No!
Then fight!
Go!
Seshita!
Oh no!
Technical Knockout!
That was amazing.
Champion! Champion!
It's over.
Good job.
Shake hands.
Let's end with a handshake.
He's down!
He got a low kick.
He's done.
End of Match!
Great job!
Thank you!
-It looks like a toy.
-You fought hard. You should be proud.
It's a training belt, not a winner's belt.
He's so strong.
You did well.
-I lost.
-Please thank them.
Thank you.
That was great.
Good game.
What's wrong with your leg?
You're limping.
I'm impervious to pain.
-Really?
-Absolutely.
Good job!
Muay Thai's interesting!
I hope our viewers visit too.
That's it for my presentation.
It was good.
Yes, it was excellent.
Great job, Seshita.
Thank you.
Wait, what about the fruit market?
After the Muay Thai gym,
you skipped the fruit market.
Oh yeah, he did.
"That's it for my presentation."
-That's right.
-We didn't go.
I didn't think I could add any more value.
-That's your decision.
-Yes.
Someone is about to get
a scolding from Hamada.
-Shame on you!
-Huh?
-Here we go.
-What? Me?
You fought with a martial arts fighter for years.
You should have volunteered to fight
after Seshita.
Honestly, when I saw that cage,
I thought I'd have to fight.
Then, when Seshita started sparring,
I was relieved it wasn't me.
I had two choices: asking to fight...
...or avoiding getting hurt this time.
I was torn.
And you chose...?
Staying safe.
Shame on you.
I stayed silent, and tried to be invisible.
That's true, he was quiet.
All of a sudden, yeah.
-It was your chance.
-We were already there.
The staff prepared gears for you.
I have a lot to learn.
You should remember that.
Of course. You're right.
They had lunch at Krua Nha Bann,
a restaurant famous among foodies.
He has one.
Let's start eating.
This dish is on the house.
Really?
Thank you.
Try it. We have one here.
Their specialty, full of green chili,
is a Thai dish called Gapao.
The spiciness can be adjusted,
but since they're there,
the group is given the spiciest version.
Hey, that's too much.
Let's dig in.
It's spicy!
What's wrong?
Oh crap.
I'm sweating.
What's that?
Milk.
Seshita... give me some!
What's with you?
Give me some! It's spicy!
Be nice.
We need more.
One more milk!
Taiki, try some.
-It sneaks up on you.
-Yeah.
Taiki.
No thanks, I know it's spicy.
You have to eat it.
You don't want any rice?
It's spicy! It's spicy!
It's spicy... give me some!
I said it's spicy! Give me some milk!
It's that spicy?
Wow.
-Seriously?
-Inomoto, try some.
No.
-No?
-No.
Make him!
Really?
He has to try this.
-Why me?
-Hold him.
What do you think you're doing?
Are you serious?
Oops.
Maybe you should try some too, Hamada.
Give me that. You eat.
I'm not a poison taster.
Poison taster?
That was spicy.
That was spicy... so spicy...