Let's go.
Hamada and the others arrived
at the airport in Bangkok.
Hamada, e-cigarettes are banned in Thailand.
Anywhere in the country.
Now, you usually smoke it.
So I brought this, just in case you need it.
What is it?
Please use this, if you have to.
-No e-cigarettes?
-Not in Thailand.
Those are the stuff, right?
-A must for a boss.
-Wait, wait.
It looks like poop.
Nice. You look really cool.
-Pattaya will be different.
-Apparently.
Why are you wearing shorts?
Don't kick me.
I was wearing them all along.
I'm hot in my pants.
Don't stretch yours.
You got scared about it.
-Shorts are bad.
-Yeah.
Not on TV.
Your shoes are terrible.
Worse than my shorts.
Are you going to school?
They're loafers. I'm trying to be stylish.
-So unnecessary.
-No, it's not.
Don't look for faults.
I'm glad my outfit is fine.
-Okay, let's go to Pattaya.
-Let's go.
Yeah, let's go.
Pattaya is about a two-hour drive
away from Bangkok.
Fellow comedians researched Pattaya
and gave presentations to Hamada.
He ranked them and revealed up to third place.
Who is going to win first place
for the best presentation?
-Who is left?
-Me.
-You're either first or second.
-Yes.
Which are you announcing first?
So nervous.
-In the right order.
-Second place.
-Okay.
-Second is fine.
Second place is...
The prize is 2,000 bahts.
Wow, that's awesome.
Hirai.
Nice one.
Wait a second.
What? No way.
I'm in second.
It's good. Thank you.
I had to give you second place.
You even went to the barber,
not knowing what will happen to you.
That's right.
-It was a gamble.
-Well done.
I'm humbled.
Not just the haircut.
-You did well overall.
-Thank you.
You ate a lot of creatures like scorpion.
I did.
You did well throughout.
Really? Thank you.
Hamada was full of praise for Hirai.
What was his presentation like?
Okay, next presentation.
I think we've seen enough.
The floating market was fun.
Yeah, Hamada.
Your sticker suggests that
you want to go to the market.
You left it on you.
You want to go back?
You must've loved it.
-It's a pass.
-Yeah, that's right.
He can go back there today.
No, why didn't you tell me I had it on?
We didn't see.
I only just realized.
I just thought...
I thought you were just enjoying yourself.
I mean...
Hey, come on.
My neck...
This is deja vu.
You say that, but...
You haven't realized?
No, don't tell me...
You had it on all along.
He had it on all along.
I thought someone put it on him.
You put it on.
Why would I? I didn't even notice mine.
Was it you?
You put it on your own back.
I put it on myself? Come on, that makes no sense.
So what's the deal?
We still have plans to make. Go, Hirai.
Here I am.
Ah, it's your turn, is it?
Hirai, go for it!
Welcome to Thailand.
-That's not it.
-Gangnam Style.
Cut it out.
Do Gangnam Style.
-Gangnam style.
-Hirai party style.
I'm taking these off.
There's so much more to Thailand.
I used magazines, the Internet,
and reviews for research.
That wasn't enough.
I wanted valuable information from CEOs...
...who had been to Thailand.
So I went to Shimbashi and looked for
CEOs like Yama-chan.
Who? I don't know him.
Yama-chan knows Thailand well.
Let me tell you something he said. OK?
"He who rules the Thai night rules the journey."
What the hell?
What does that even mean?
So I'm going to focus on nighttime.
I mean, you must be quite tired.
You've been busy in Japan too.
That's true.
So first, let's go for a massage.
Thailand is famous for great massages.
There's foot or face massage and all sorts.
But there's one that I recommend.
They use wooden mallets called "tok sen."
And this type of massage that
uses tok sen is really something.
Massage using fingers can
only work on our muscles.
But actually, it's the inner bones that are tired.
Their technique works on
the inner parts effectively.
According to Yama-chan.
-Yama-chan.
-Who is he?
The famous Yama-chan?
Doesn't it hurt?
Oh it hurts bad.
-It's really painful.
-Who'd want to go then?
I don't want to go there if it's painful.
Everyone there was shouting in pain.
But the next day, you really feel the benefit.
Ah, the next day.
A transformation.
But it hurts?
It really hurts on the day.
That's right.
That's scary.
Here, listen up.
Don't tell me to listen.
This way, this way.
Why are you facing that way?
Tell me how it's done.
Initially, they're gentle.
Sounds fine.
Right. And they tap rhythmically.
But on the beat, they tap you hard which hurts.
I see.
So it doesn't always hurt.
-And the next day you feel good.
-I see.
You won't get this massage in Japan.
Yeah, I get what you mean.
Just guarantee me that it'll be fine.
And there's one more place.
It's the night market.
Pattaya's famous for the night market.
There are 300 stalls, including food stalls.
They sell gifts too, but all sorts of
Thai food are sold there.
A whole row of them, right and left.
-You don't visit stalls in Japan, do you?
-Nope.
So I really would like to go there
with all of you here.
Stalls all the way?
Like what?
Chicken skewers.
Yama-chan says chicken and beer are "Hmph."
Yama-chan said that?
Chicken skewers and beer are a great combo.
Why "Hmph"?
The famous Yama-chan.
That's one option, but...
There's a lot more.
I want to go there together.
Let me think.
Hmm, well...
-Can we do shopping?
-Yes.
Hamada became more and more excited after this.
This is Pattaya's famous night market.
It's the weekend as well.
-It's packed full.
-Wow.
Workers, tourists... everyone comes here.
Look. T-shirts for 60 bahts.
60 bahts?
About 180 yen.
Wow, 200 yen?
And this is the start.
It smells really nice.
If you fancy anything, you can also try it a bit.
-Really?
-Yes, you can.
Are there things that I should eat?
He said chicken skewers.
According to Yama-chan.
That lady's got a chicken skewer.
Let's eat some chicken.
-Let's eat it.
-This is fun.
There's a chicken skewer called "nok"
that you can only eat here.
Nok?
I can't read the signs.
There it is.
So this is nok?
-Yeah.
-Three skewers?
Thank you.
That's the best choice.
Look at this.
-Scared?
-I'm fine.
Let me taste it first.
-This is delicious.
-Yeah?
Please try it. It's delicious. A bit spicy too.
It's good.
Right?
It's quite unique.
Yeah, it is.
It is unique. Nice though.
Very nice.
It's fatty too.
-You don't get this in Japan.
-Yeah.
They look nice.
They look great.
Tell me what you want.
Look, they look beautiful.
Shellfish look good.
They say these chicken balls are nice.
Really?
Shall I get one each? One, two... seven.
Let's eat.
A saucy one should be good.
What's the sauce?
It's sweet and spicy.
Each stall has their own recipe.
Nice.
-It's nice, huh?
-Yeah.
-A bit spicy.
-Delicious.
Hamada.
We saw this earlier.
Oh dear.
In this night market, they sell...
Crickets, caterpillars, etc.
But I heard that the caterpillars taste great.
Can I have one?
One, okay?
He ate it.
It's delicious.
Come on, don't be silly.
Try it.
-No thanks.
-Really?
You're gonna get told off.
It smells.
It's a whole cricket.
-A grasshopper?
-Yes.
-Not a cricket?
-It's famous.
Well?
Wow, it's tasty.
Seriously?
I'll try one of them.
They heat it up.
I see.
I hope they were cooked.
He ate it uncooked?
It had to be deep-fried.
They were shocked.
It tasted good.
How much is it?
It's 40 baht.
Well, it actually smells really nice.
Please try eating one.
Come on then.
Masayoshi, try one.
Scoop it.
Yum. It tastes good.
How so?
It's kind of like soft chicken cartilage.
Does it burst and go slimy?
Not at all. It's really easy to chew.
Nice and plump.
Inomoto, you try.
Me?
-Really?
-Yes, you.
Well... I guess it's edible.
It's good.
Hamada, try it.
It's quite edible.
Stop it.
Come on, come on.
Have a cricket.
Cricket?
Sorry. It was my mistake.
Nice aroma.
It's edible, right? I told you.
It wasn't bad.
Crickets aren't bad.
I mean, in Japan too,
some people eat grasshoppers.
-I'm enjoying this market.
-It's fun.
They sell everything.
You come here to find out about Thailand.
You can learn about their food.
I was told that this rice was
popular with Thai people too.
There's pork meat and egg on top of rice,
like our rice bowls.
It looks tasty.
It's pork and egg.
Is it 60 bahts?
The meat is tender.
Shall we try it, yeah?
And you get a boiled egg.
You can't go wrong with this.
I bet it's tasty.
We got something.
Gapao and green curry.
It was 45 bahts.
Was it?
How is it?
Nice.
It's spicy again.
It's good. Really good.
Let's try this one.
Hamada, try it.
Looks so nice.
Do I just eat it like this?
There's rice underneath.
I see.
Try the meat first.
Now this is good.
Everyone likes it.
You can't go wrong.
It comes with rice and sauce to combine with.
Sauce?
Isn't it seasoned already?
I like it a lot.
It is seasoned, yes.
It'd be even nicer with some more sauce.
So tasty.
Have more sauce.
This is really tasty.
So tasty.
Hamada and the others
all enjoyed the night market.
So what did you think of it, Hamada?
I enjoyed the food. The atmosphere was fun too.
Definitely feels like Thailand.
He can't go to a market in Japan.
I only see them on videos.
I was skeptical.
It's more fun in real life. I got you the sausage.
Thanks.
Did he like it?
It's good.
They were all tasty.
I know, right? Everyone comes here.
A lot of the tourists.
Ready for the next spot?
Hirai of "Dorians"
had also presented another plan.
-They all sound good.
-I agree.
I guess the shops and things might be interesting.
Really? OK, I understand.
I'm sorry. Excuse me a moment.
I'm sorry.
Let me...
You're like Steve Jobs.
Is it Jobs' style today?
-We can go to the night market...
-Hamada.
Let's go.
What was it?
What did you see?
Tell us what it was.
What happened just now?
Let's go.
-Tell us what it was.
-Come on.
Hamada, there's more.
We're going!
-Thank you!
-Let's go now!
You got excited.
Just tell us what it was.
Nice. That's awesome.
I'm glad I had it. And if...
He loved it so much.
He really loved it.
Let's go!
He's so different now.
Okay, let's go then.
Let's go. He's hyper now.
They head out to have some nighttime fun.
This is the biggest
entertainment district in Pattaya.
Awesome.
It's a strange atmosphere.
-Very Southeast Asia.
-Right?
Exotic.
It reminds me of Kabukicho in Tokyo
from around 30 years ago.
That shop has a sign saying "Taboo."
It looks suspicious. What is it?
What a place.
What is this place?
Bright red.
So many lights.
That woman must be the negotiator.
Look there.
It's a famous go-go bar.
A go-go bar.
This is it.
You can't see it from the outside. You have to go in.
It's so long.
It goes on.
This is amazing.
That guy is advertising happy hour.
Wow, amazing.
She's got a tummy like mine.
It's an ice cream stall.
-Yeah?
-They tease you.
They find a Turkish ice cream shop.
Wow.
It touched me.
Oh wow.
Oh come on.
Hey, hey.
You're too funny.
Wonderful.
I'm really impressed.
-Awesome, huh?
-The Internet can't tell you half the story.
They went deeper into the night scene.
Don't go there. They're all men.
No, Hamada, don't go.
They're all men?
I'm going alone?
Wait...
Masayoshi goes alone into
a shop full of middle-aged men.
You're mean.
This is so mean.
There are eight guys in swim shorts.
This place is dangerous. I can't go in.
They're all men.
Girls are at the back.
No, they're all men.
Go to the back.
They're there.
They're not.
There they are.
I knew it.
No, that's a man in a blond wig.
They're men.
Only men.
They sent Masayoshi alone to the shop
and enjoyed the night life.
So, Hamada gave first place
for the best presentation to this guy.
Are you ready guys?
-You'll announce the winner?
-Yes.
-Please announce the winner.
-Alright.
Close your eyes.
The winner gets 3,000 bahts.
The winner of the 3,000 bahts is...
-Sam.
-Sam?
Sam?
Huh? Who the hell?
Sam? What?
-Sam?
-Yes.
For Sam?
Give this to Sam for me.
Sheesh.
I'm giving 3,000 bahts to Sam?
Give it to him.
Sam worked the hardest by far.
It's true.
I think he worked hard too.
Who is this Sam who won first place?
This was four hours after
Masayoshi was abandoned in the shop.
Hey wait. There's something odd.
He seems different.
He has more presence.
What's going on?
To put it politely, he looked like...
Guts Ishimatsu.
Initially, we couldn't communicate at all.
-No English?
-Nope.
-No English at all.
-That's scary.
He didn't speak English?
That's tough.
That's really tough.
He understood "What's your name?"
He told me he was "Sam."
Sam
Sam!
He wanted to show me something.
What was it?
There's this traditional dance in Thailand.
He started dancing it.
It makes no sense.
That's a bit sudden.
He started dancing.
Right in front of me.
-Sam did?
-In front of me.
I asked him to take a shower.
What did he say?
He said no.
He won't shower?
No way.
Masayoshi talked about Sam passionately.
Seriously? Unbelievable!
Wonderful.
-What a great experience.
-Yeah.
Sorry I went on my own.
More like I came on my own.
That's enough.
Enough.
Hirai and Seshita, kiss.
On this journey,
it became a rule to kiss
and make up after an argument.
Through physical contact,
they became even closer to each other.
He's so sweaty.
Overall, you all did very well.
Thank you very much!
It's been great.
This is how I want you to perform.
I consider this to be a start.
-Thank you.
-Lastly...
Make it big as comedians!
Ouch.
We're trying. We really are.
How old are you?
I'm 38.
I'm 39.
I'm 39 too.
39.
I'm 38.
You're old geezers.
We're still rookies.
You're not rookies.
Yes we are.
At the age of 40?
Yeah, we're all rookies.
Use this as an opportunity to do better.
Now you know how TV works.
Yes, we do.
I think you guys learned a lot on this trip.
If you want people to listen to you more,
use two microphones.
You sure? I'll take your word for it.
There was an incident related to microphones.
Shall we go with that?
Hamada, you're wearing my mic.
Is it yours?
You're wearing my mic.
He was desperate to be heard.
I want to talk too.
You're so desperate?
He thought it was his.
I dropped it and before I picked it up, he put it on.
Why did he think it was his?
He didn't drop it.
I've been moving but Hamada was just sitting.
When would you have dropped it?
He stole the mic off me.
Use your own mic.
I've worked on many shows,
but I've never seen someone put on two mics.
I saw the sound girl adjusting levels.
It was a double feed.
She looked confused.
The frequency...
Look at this one.
It all on me.
Even showbiz people have never seen
anyone putting two microphones on themselves.
It was my first time in 13 years
working as a sound engineer.
I wasn't sure what had happened. It was a shock.
I did it on purpose.
-On purpose?
-Of course.
You did it on purpose?
-So you're heard?
Of course. Don't be silly.
You're gonna rip my face off.
That's bad.
I heard him saying earlier, "Why did I put that on?"
I said, "You were sleepy?"
Apologize.
I refuse.
You've got to apologize, come on.
You should both apologize.
Come on.
Don't fight.
That's how eager you should be
to make it big in showbiz.
Mr Two-mic.
This guy...
-Don't call him "this guy."
-Yeah, don't.
-You should kiss and make up.
-Let's put this behind us.
Come on, kiss. You had an argument.
I didn't argue with him.
I didn't.
Make up with him.
What the hell?
This is the ending?
A nice country, Thailand.
Thank you, Thailand.
Bye!
In the past, we went to Guam a lot.
But in this trip, the scenery was spectacular.
So I'd like to search for more places like that.
We run out of places to go
if we visit the same place.
I want to see the footage from this trip,
because I'm sure it's spectacular.
So I'll look for more nice places.
I can't say where right now.
I'm interested to see...
...what they'll achieve when
that bunch gets together again.