Hamada's Holiday in Guam.
When you first get to know people,
they keep a distance. About this far.
Now, Dorians are close to me like this.
It almost hurts.
They're very close,
and I think they sometimes forget...
...that I'm their senior.
Talking in the middle of the night, part one.
"Hamada learns for the first time
about when everyone met him."
We met Downtown for the first time
opening for their program, right?
When did you meet them?
For us, the opportunity to come
to Tokyo from Fukuoka...
...was a talk show called Matsu-Shin.
We were M-1 Grand Prix semifinalists
and invited to be on Matsu-Shin.
We got invited with Pu & Mu and met
Hitoshi Matsumoto of Downtown.
He asked, "Are you coming to Tokyo?"
We met Shinsuke Shimada there too.
So we answered, "We would like to come but..."
Matsumoto said we should,
and Shinsuke said to him,
"You should let them open for your shows."
Matsumoto answered,
"I can't, since Hamada decides everything."
Yeah, that's what he said.
We decided to go to Tokyo that year.
It must have been luck.
Our first job was opening for Downtown.
Which was HEY! HEY! HEY!
You opened for that show?
From then on, we did it all.
Now we're able to work on
various sets with Downtown.
They often say their dressing rooms are separate,
and when I heard that, I didn't believe it.
But it's true.
They're separated until filming begins.
Our manager, Nagae.
He's been with us for long.
When he was a rookie dressed in a suit,
we did our first opening act.
He was still new to TV work then.
You were new too.
He asked what we're supposed to do,
but it was our first day.
None of us knew.
The guy in the suit didn't know,
so we were at a loss.
We decided to greet Downtown,
who were in different dressing rooms.
We didn't know who to go see first,
Matsumoto or Hamada.
Someone told us where Matsumoto was,
so we decided to see him first.
Matsumoto was reading a newspaper.
We said, "Our name is Dorians.
We'll be the opening act."
And he answered, "Dorians? Oh, that's not good."
We asked, "Not good?"
He said, "Well, I don't think that's good."
I started sweating.
I didn't get it. He said, "Your name is not good."
"Hamada is extremely mad about you guys."
Really?
We went to see Matsumoto first,
so we were late greeting Hamada.
Oh, I see. You didn't know how things worked.
We were late greeting him.
-Matsumoto just said that.
-Yes.
We were told Hamada was angry.
That's nerve-racking.
Our first TV work! We thought,
"We had to greet Hamada first."
Then Matsumoto advised,
"You should go apologize."
We thanked him and said we'd do that.
We knocked on Hamada's door and apologized.
"We're truly sorry."
We could only say sorry.
We apologized about our name,
but Hamada started laughing.
We were confused and didn't understand.
We had just met.
Hamada was laughing just like this.
He said, "Hang on." He yelled, "Matsumoto!"
He said to him, "What did you tell them?!"
This was at a dressing room.
He left his dressing room
and went over to where Matsumoto was.
"You must have said something!"
Wow, that's unbelievable.
I knew right away by Dorians' behavior
that he had said something.
After he went there and came back,
we were confused, saying, "What's happening?"
We were the only ones laughing.
We thought, "Downtown gets along well."
I didn't get it, because I thought
they didn't get along.
He smacked Matsumoto,
and everyone laughed, so I was confused.
We asked Nagae if it was normal
to be pranked, but he didn't know.
We asked the other crew,
and they said that never happens.
They said Hamada never goes to see
Matsumoto before a show.
That was our first meeting with Downtown.
The very first time.
That's nice.
They weren't scary.
They were kind and really got along.
That was our impression.
My image of them changed.
Even to this day,
Downtown doesn't share a dressing room,
so recalling it now, that was shocking.
That was the first and last time.
The first and last time that happened.
-But you had met Hirai.
-Right.
I brought him along when we went out.
He was so nervous he ordered
a rice omelet and plain rice.
Of course I was nervous.
-Rice omelet and plain rice? Rice with rice?
-Yes.
That's what he got.
I told him to order something.
We went to Mishuku, the three of us.
I had just gotten used to Inomoto,
then Hamada showed up.
-And I invited you suddenly too.
-Yeah, that's right.
Hamada invited me to dinner,
so I asked if I could bring him.
He was shocked when I said
he'd be seeing Hamada.
That's normal.
He's relaxed now, sitting near Hamada
banging his head on the chair laughing.
But at that dinner, he sat like a samurai.
Of course, you'd be nervous.
We all experienced that.
All his replies sounded like hisses.
Sounds like you're leaking air.
"Hiss..."
-"You're full?" "Hiss..."
-Yeah, I really did that.
Hamada told him
to order something, and Hamada said,
"Hurry up and decide!"
So Hirai got a rice omelet,
and Hamada asked if it's enough.
So he ordered plain rice too.
Hamada said, "You're weird."
"Rice omelet and rice?" "Hiss."
When did you meet Downtown?
I...
-You haven't met them yet?
-Not yet.
Who is that?
He's been sitting there.
He's been sitting there for a while.
I met Masayoshi long before Hirai.
He's the first one.
He met Hamada before all of you.
You were?
It wasn't work related,
but I was invited to Mishuku
with Inomoto out of the blue.
I was surprised when he called.
When was this?
A long time ago.
You've known Hamada for long.
He's the longest.
Over ten years.
You've been around for my moving.
I ordered him to come to Shinjuku
and made him pack with me.
-I packed for him.
-You did that?
Inomoto, you were at work,
and I had to get it done.
So you asked him.
Inomoto used to look after me back then,
and even though I lived far,
he'd invite me out for drinks.
Inomoto told me to move closer,
so I moved close to his house.
We became closer after that.
I'm not a graduate of Tokyo NSC.
Right.
I entered Yoshimoto
as Ikuyo Kuruyo's apprentice.
So surprisingly, Hamada
has known Masayoshi for long.
I didn't know.
I think it's over 15 years.
Masayoshi is the oldest one.
Yes, I am.
We spend more time outside work.
I've never worked with Masayoshi.
Really?
-Yes.
-After all this time?
He's done opening acts for some of my shows.
No studio filming or on location?
No.
-I haven't.
-So you haven't met Downtown yet.
I thought so. Who is that man?
-Not Hamada.
-Right, Matsumoto.
We've opened for HEY! HEY! HEY! too.
We opened for most of Shinsuke's programs then.
Because he's my master's fellow pupil.
So we opened for all of
the programs Shinsuke was involved in.
That led to opening for Downtown.
Once, Downtown hosted Shinsuke's program.
To help him, yes.
We did the opening act then,
which led us to open for Downtown's
programs like HEY! HEY! HEY!
Back then, my impressions
of Hamada at work and outside of work...
...were completely different.
We were still scared of him.
Well, you two of Dorians have
a different relationship with him,
but I still feel a distance between Hamada and I.
In your relationship with him, right?
-I get nervous.
-He was scary back then.
-He was very scary.
-Oh yeah?
I still remember my master Ikuyo saying,
"Hamada appears on TV like that,"
"but he's actually very reliable."
She told me,
"Don't mimic how rowdy he is on TV!"
-How's he in real life?
-Rowdy.
He was nothing like what Ikuyo said.
-Just rowdy?
-Yes.
We ate ramen yesterday, so I offered
to pour beer, but he said not to worry.
He told me to just pour him beer
when he got too old to do so.
When the pot stickers came,
he yelled at me to hurry with the soy sauce.
I don't understand.
He's crazy.
He's rowdy like Rambo.
-Rambo.
-He's Rambo.