So let's begin the middle round.
Translator/Timer/Typesetter:
Kai_guy01
From the White Group... DanceMan!
Song Translations:
projecthello.com
And from the Red Group... Kago Ai-chan!
Editor/Encoder:
SacredCultivator
Please visit us at:
http://www.hello-fansubs.com
Mind if I use my original indoor shoes?
Go ahead.
Original indoor shoes.
Ah, you mean you won't take
off your boots then.
I see.
He's engrossed about his health I see.
Let's not ask why so... whatevers.
You hair's not gonna come off?
Not at all.
It'll be okay.
Let's not focus on this.
Let's pay attention to our objective.
This is it! Here we go!
Ready... and...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Kago!
"Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
DanceMan!
"Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Kago!
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Kago!
"Jankenpon!"
Aha... sorry!
Kago!
"Jan...ken...pon..."
DanceMan!
"Jankenpon!"
Kago!
A strike just now!
A beautiful one!
Kago is the winner for this round!
We had some flying going on didn't we?
That's right!
She came off very strong.
So let's continue on with a
second in command battle!
So the next person from the White
Group will be Go Hiromi!
And from the Red Group... Tsuji Nozomi!
If you please.
Go Hiromi isn't smiling at all is he?
Go-san, this kind of game... you haven't...
It's my first time.
It's your first time?
Go-sama doesn't seem affected at all.
That's true.
Ah! Handshake!
That's wonderful.
He understands pretty well
even if it's his first time...
Let's get started!
Ready... and...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Go!
Tsuji!
"Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Tsuji's win!
What are you doing?
She ended up covering!
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Tsuji!
Wrong!
You won that one!
She's quick to protect herself!
Tsuji Nozomi-chan!
Okay? Please remember and do it properly.
Here we go!
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Go-san!
"Jankenpon!"
That's wrong!!!
If you don't strike, you'll lose okay!?
Ready?
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Tsuji!
Wrong! Wrong! Wrong!
Looks like no decision...
Are you able to see?
She wants to protect herself.
She has that kind of feeling.
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Go-san!
Safe!
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Go-san!
"Looks like a tie!"
Go!
Once again okay?
Are you two like some hopeless kids?
Okay? Okay?
Here we go!
Ready... and...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Tsuji!
"Jankenpon!"
Tsuji! One more time!
"Looks like a tie!"
Ohh! Go-san!
"Jankenpon!"
Go-san!
Tsuji-san!
"Jankenpon!"
One more time Tsuji!
You're the one hitting!
"Jankenpon!"
Go!
Tsuji~!
"Jankenpon!"
Go!
Tsuji~!
"Jankenpon!"
Go!
Tsuji!
Oh almost! But no good...
Wrong!
WRONG!!
This is getting painful!
This is... long...
"Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Himori!
"Jan...ken...pon!"
Tsuji's win!
"Jankenpon!"
Himori-san!
Himori!
"Jankenpon!"
Go!
Go Hiromi!
The White Group!
Go Hiromi is the winner!
That match goes to the White Group!
Truly magnificent!
That was quite a drawn-out battle.
Well... that was pretty long wasn't it!?
Our judge is pretty tired aren't you?
We waited a while for sure.
Tsuji-chan, what did you think about it?
So the... it quickly... are you
tired? Was it difficult?
It was hard.
More than you thought?
You see...
I thought I was the one who lost.
But you did lose!
Yes, you did at "Jankenpon" right?
Tsuji-chan thought she would lose.
Kinda like, "I thought I'd win after all."
Tsuji thought she won... at the end.
Actually, I raised the flag for me.
And so,
this... kendo challenge...
the outcome of this kendo
match is entrusted...
to these two.
It's the match of destiny.
A great battle! From the White
Group, Hamada Masatoshi!
And from the Red Group, Yasuda Kei!
Kei-chan!
Between us it should be
decided pretty quickly.
If we remember one year ago,
in a hard-fought battle, MoMusu's Yasuda
caused Hama-chan's tragic defeat!
Will the outcome be different this time?
Hamada-san, you seem
to be more than ready.
Here we go!
Ready.. and...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Yasuda!
"Jankenpon!"
Hamada!
Just like the Hamada-san from last year.
Kei-chan, battle hard!
Do your best!
They're battling hard!
Ready... and...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Yasuda!
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
"Jankenpon!"
Yasuda!
Hamada!
Go! Go! Go!
Hmm... just now...
Hamada was just barely safe.
"Safe" is the call on that one.
Let's continue on with this match!
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Hamada!
"Jankenpon!"
"Tie!"
Yasuda!
She did "scissors" just now!
She won the janken?
She won! She won!
Serious??
Why did you... I was the one...
Well... doesn't count.
With that kind of energy I thought I won...
Just now, she won right? With "scissors".
"Scissors" right? And Hamada did "paper".
Well, let's keep going then.
Ready... and...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Hamada!
"Jankenpon!"
"Tie!"
Yasuda!
"Jankenpon!"
"Tie!"
Go Yasuda!
"Jankenpon!"
Yasuda!
So what I'm thinking is, Hamada-san has
to defeat three people in order to win.
So another two people.
Ah, so three people total then...
Aside from the people on the board?
After watching Yasuda, think they'll try?
I'll go!
Really?
For real?
Yossi! Let's go!
So let's hurry then.
Do your best!
Yossi...
And here we go!
Ready... and...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Yoshizawa!
"Janken..."
She's getting active...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Yoshizawa!
"Looks like a tie!"
"Jankenpon!"
Hamada!
"No" right?
No, no, no, no...
That one didn't count now.
Right there.
"Jankenpon!"
Was she mistaken just now?
No good!
I won that!
Hamada won!
I won the "janken!"
I won it right?
Just now you were like,
"Whatever happens I'll hit him anyway!"
That surprised me.
And actually, Hamada won that round.
Really surprising.
I didn't think she was that mean.
It had nothing to do with the match I think.
That was a really beautiful hit just now.
If it was that beautiful, then she's
already won at janken...
She's got plenty of confidence...
I failed at that one.
Let's keep going.
Ready... and...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Yoshizawa!
"Jankenpon!"
Hamada!
Yoshizawa!
"Jankenpon!"
Hamada!
What the hell!?
Do it right!
She's uncertain which hand...
It's all right. Let's keep going.
"Jankenpon!"
Hamada!
Hey! What the...
"Jankenpon!"
Hamada!
Okay... so, Hamada-san's second win.
Right, so one more round right?
Ahd here we go.
So, one more person...
he must defeat in order to win.
Is there anyone who wants to go?
Lots of pressure on this person.
Leader!
Iida!
Let's go with Iida.
Do you have anything to say now?
You smacked my cute members
too much so...
That's okay.
She hit me for no reason!
Been a while since I've seen
something that pretty.
You guys ready?
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Onegaishimasu!
Scary~!
Ready...
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Hamada!
"Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Iida!
She let it fly!
Flew right out of her hand!
Nice! Nice!
I'm sure your feeling pretty hurt right now.
Shall we continue?
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Hamada!
You can get a little closer.
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
Iida!
Looks like a fail...
"Jankenpon!"
Iida!
Hamada!
That was... I don't really know.
What did you throw?
The sound wasn't good and
it wasn't very TV-like so...
He's decided he doesn't like it so,
she's safe for now.
So, keep doing your best!
"Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Hamada!
Ouch!
"Jankenpon!"
"Looks like a tie!"
Iida!
Looks like Hama-chan's the
one truly getting hit.
Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!
Hamada!
"Jankenpon!"
Iida!
"Looks like a tie!"
"Jankenpon!"
Iida!
Well? Well? Well!?
Red!
Morning Musume!
And for the White Group, with two wins at
50 points each, they receive 100 points!
They'll receive them respectively.
Final Match:
Relay!
Right now, the White Group
has a 50 point lead!
So, the winner of this last
battle will get 500 points!
And so... this could be... anyone's victory!
Can't it be just a 100 points?
It could be, but they said to
make it a good 500 so...
This will be a relay of 7 laps
arounda  120 meter course!
Starting from the studio, they'll race each other
until they reach middle point in the back straight!
Finally, turn the corner into the hall
and back in the studio
to complete the course!
The Red Group Morning Musume's
first runner will be Abe Natsumi.
They'll race half the course in this order.
The anchor, Iida Kaori, will
runa a full lap by herself.
And here are the White Group members...
Hamada Masatoshi!
w-ind's KEITA!
Da Pump's ISSA!
DanceMan!
Kawamura Ryuuichi!
Go Hiromi!
And then Matsumoto Hitoshi will anchor
in this relay of certain victory!
So did you guys practice at
all for this relay this time?
Not at all...
Not so much huh...
That's... yeah...
So uh, for the new members
how do you feel?
Is running your specialty?
Not really.
It's not?
That's not good.
Are you shaking a little?
Please try your hardest okay?
Okay.
It's only halfway okay?
And then...
We have a lot of members
that did club sports so...
But I'm not too sure about DanceMan...
DanceMan-san's shoes are those... uhh...
fried soles... I mean...
thick-soled boots!
Sorry! With the thick-soled boots!
I'm distracted by his boots there.
You'll be okay?
I'll be fine!
I'm faster than I appear.
I think maybe Go might be our best one.
Ah that's true.
Go-san is considerably...
he seems to be pretty fast at the end...
Everyday you've done some training right?
It's like you were born for this moment...
And so, let's have the first runners
Hamada-san and Abe Natsumi-san
stand over here at the starting line.
Well then, in this gathering
for the sport contest,
I'd like to start this final relay battle!
To these two runners... are you ready?
So then, here we go!
On your marks... Get set...
And they're off!
The first runners are Hamada
Masatoshi and Abe Natsumi!
An overtake!
Abe-san will hand off there.
And the second runner is Konno Asami!
Hamada-san's at the hallway.
Ohh! Hamada's been passed! But!
New member Konno overshot!
Up next is Yoshizawa Hitomi! Yoshizawa!
And Hamada to Kei... Keita!
w-ind's Keita!
w-ind's Keita has a slight lead!
w-ind's Keita and Yoshizawa Hitomi!
How does it look?
Still has the lead!
And Yoshizawa Hitomi will pass
off to Ogawa Makoto!
Ogawa Makoto has the baton!
It's Ogawa Makoto versus Keita!
Keita's out of the hallway
and entered the studio!
Next is Da Pump's ISSA!
Da Pump's ISSA!
Baton's been passed! To Yasuda Kei!
The Red Group's Yasuda Kei has the baton!
Yasuda Kei!
Yasuda Kei to Niigaki Risa!
Niigaki Risa will take the hand-off
in that changing area.
It's been passed!
And Da Pump's ISSA is entering
the studio very nonchalantly!
It's DanceMan!
DanceMan running with
those beautiful strides!
This time it's Yaguchi Mari!
Yaguchi Mari's receiving the baton!
She's chasing after DanceMan!
She's catching up with DanceMan...
Almost there! Off to Takahashi-san!
And Yaguchi-san passes off... wow!
Takahashi Ai... right there... overtook first!
Takahashi Ai and DanceMan
coming into the studio!
Next runner Tsuji Nozomi
receives the hand-off!
Tsuji Nozomi!
And to Kawamura Ryuuichi!
Kawamura Ryuuichi is going
after Tsuji Nozomi!
Kawamura might catch up with her!
Will Tsuji be okay? Tsuji
will pass off to Kago Ai!
Now Kawamura Ryuuichi's chasing Kago Ai!
The lead could change!
This will be a close one!
Go Hiromi!
Go Hiromi and Goto Maki!
Goto Maki's in front but
Go-san's right behind!
Goto Maki will pass to Ishikawa Rika!
Goto Maki... Ishikawa Rika!
Ishikawa Rika! They're in the hallway!
Go Hiromi's still up front!
Go Hiromi's arrived! Then
comes Ishikawa Rika!
And now...
the batons are passed!
And the anchors Matsumoto
Hitoshi and Iida Kaori!
These two are giving it their all!
She's chasing!
Can Iida Kaori catch up!?
He's 3 meters ahead! 3 meters!
Still about 3 meters!
Look like she tripped a little!
Will she be okay? Mmm... doesn't look good!
And Matsumoto is now...!
Matsumoto's crossed the goal!
Iida Kaori crossed the goal too!
It was about a 1 second
difference this time!
Woo~too close!
We won but, wasn't that a
spectacular battle though!?
Especially at the end!
That was a really great match.
A very good match!
The White Group...
DanceMan for the most part shortened it.
Aah, it was like that towards the end.
DanceMan was like this...
Hiromi Go was like running for real.
Like full-on serious...
Let's take a look at Go-san again.
That's not the face of a star right?
So how was it? This course...
Well... uh... it was pretty
difficult to run right?
But things like getting the
baton I completely forgot.
And so, the result of this
round was 500 points so
it goes to the White Group.
So it's now 800 to 250 which makes
the White Group the winners!
Congratulations!
A hard-fought win!
So they have the overall victory!
And the championship flag will be
awarded to the White Group!
Who will accept it?
Ah, Hama-chan should!
Congratulations!
Even from the start there
were a lot of difficulties.
And from now, we do "Strike! Cover! Jankenpon!" again right?
Wonder how I'm gonna do.
Well the last part of the
contest was the relay...
I think... maybe... during the relay...
they were confused about the baton.
That right?
How was it?
For the Red team, the batons
were giving them trouble.
Ya, we couldn't do it properly.
So handing off the baton was
what took them so long.
With DanceMan being there,
it helped us a little...
That handicap over there...
How was it? This time was a
sudden upset victory maybe.
We lost it.
Right.
It's very regrettable.
It was but...
We'll come back and do it again!
So how was Morning Musume's teamwork
among the musumes for this contest?
Right but you know...
The 5th generation members joined and
it's their first time in a contest like this,
so I kinda think our teamwork
wasn't that great.
Ah! I see...
Aren't you the only one thinking that?
Well, I thought your teamwork
was pretty good.
These guys here will have to go to camp!
ISSA-san, how was it?
It was a lot of fun surprisingly.
I thought it was a lot of fun, this meeting...
How was the last part?
It was a lot shorter than
I thought it would be.
That right?
And DanceMan-san,
Well, I can't really come down
with these soles so...
That's beside the point!
The fact that you're wearing
them is ridiculous!!
He really packed it on.
That was already said wasn't it?
And so, everyone we hope you
had fun while you were here.
So in the HEY!HEY!HEY! Huge
Autumn Sports Contest,
the White Group was the winner!
Thank you!