You have one new message.
This is your realtor.
Your electronic payment for
last month's rent has not come through.
Please make your payment to our account
by the end of the week at the very latest.
Hakamada Yukio
Attorney at Law
Tokiwa Publishers
Kanae-san!
Hakamada's assistant
Nonomura Kanae
It's your serial's one-year anniversary.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Plus, look at this reader
survey from last month.
You're in third place.
3rd place: "Divorce Chaser" Nonomura Kanae
Monthly Manday March Issue:
Author Popularity Rankings Based on Reader Survey
Wow!
This is the third consecutive month
you've been ranked third, too!
You're a full-fledged,
popular manga illustrator
and contributor to
Monthly Manday, now.
Nonomura-sensei.
Oh, don't call me that, please.
Chief editor of Tokiwa Publishers
Ueki
Nonomura-sensei,
Would you be interested in doing a serial
for the weekly publication of Manday?
Weekly Manday?
As you already know,
it's Tokiwa Publishers'
powerhouse manga magazine.
We publish five times the number of
issues of the monthly publication.
Your monthly serial is highly
regarded by our readers.
You can now move up as a
professional manga illustrator.
Editor at Tokiwa Publishing
Tabata Misato
Of course you'd have to end the
current serial, which is too bad.
In the final episode,
we want you to reveal
the protagonist's past,
You will be divorcing
your husband, then?
and bring the series to a
supreme and conclusive end!
You got a serial in Weekly Manday?
Amazing!
You've joined the ranks of top
manga illustrators, Nonomura-sensei.
The pay! How much do you make?!
Is that an appropriate question?
You're so lucky.
You'll be super rich now.
Freelance Investigator
Umemoto Kurumi
Plus, you get monthly compensation
from your ex-husband.
About that, he hasn't been depositing
the compensation fee lately.
What?
Really?
That's quite common.
Temp
Shinozuka Rina
When compensation gets divided
into monthly payments,
those men eventually fade out.
But even if you grow in
popularity, even if you get rich,
you have to make him keep paying.
That's right.
You can never get enough income.
Office landlord
Toyama Yoshie
I'll teach you how to rent out apartments!
Well, to tell you the truth,
I'm still hesitant.
If I have to do a weekly serial,
I'd be too busy to continue
working here.
What?
Why are you hesitating about that?
That's right.
You should dump this place.
The faster, the better!
We don't get paid consistently, either.
I know, but...
Attorney
Hakamada Yukio
Anyway, let's celebrate
Kanae-chan's promotion today.
Sensei, pour some sake!
Wait...
Yoshie-san, not so fast, please!
I haven't received
Hakamada-sensei's permission, yet.
You have my complete approval.
What?
You were once my client,
but you carved out a path for yourself,
and are about to begin a new life.
What better news can there be?
Come on, Kanae-chan. Drink up.
Sensei, my glass is empty.
Sorry.
Hurry up. Sensei, why aren't
you drinking, too?
I can't drink.
You're seriously a bore of
a man, you know that?
Sensei, how come you never got married?
If you're not drinking, at least
entertain me with stories or something.
Kanae-chan, maybe you shouldn't...
Well, I've never felt the
need to get married...
Be honest. Tell the truth, would you?
Keep it coming.
Wait, I know!
You're gay? Gay?
No, I'm not!
I knew it! He's gay!
If they're busy, I can come back later.
Oh... one moment please.
Kanae's ex-husband
Kurasawa Yoshihito
Cheers!
You know, it's because he's seen
so many failures come through his office.
"Failures"?
What?
Were you talking about me?
No, I didn't say anything about you.
Sure, my marriage was a failure.
But I chalked it up to experience,
you understand?
How could I have known that
husband was an adulterer?
Sensei, please come with me.
Oh, yes!
You can't escape me, Hakamada!
We have a client.
A client?
Y-Yoshihito-san?
It's been a while.
What are you doing here?
Oh, well,
I work here now.
Sorry I've been late on
compensation payments.
What?
You came here to tell me that?
Actually, I came to consult
Hakamada-sensei today.
Me?
Divorce Chaser
~Let's Turn Your Tears into Money~
Divorce Chaser Episode 11
An unsurmountable crisis!!
A formidable attorney enters the scene
Hakamada-sensei.
I apologize for having caused
you trouble in the past.
No...
So, what can I do for you?
Well...
it's about another
compensation lawsuit.
Compensation?
That guy never learns.
He must've cheated again.
He's sick, that's all. Sick.
He's truly divorce material.
Right, Kanae-san?
Um...
It wasn't me who was cheating.
You heard us?
Sorry.
The one caught cheating was...
my wife, Shiori.
Shiori-san...
Yoshihito's wife
Kurasawa Shiori
How do you do.
Soon after my divorce with Kanae was official,
we legalized our union.
But I had a monthly
compensation fee to pay,
and couldn't afford to give her
the kind of life she expected.
Do you like this? Isn't it cute?
How much was it?
It was on sale. It wasn't much.
About 50,000 yen.
Didn't I tell you we don't have
that kind of money right now?
Oh. Sorry.
Eventually cracks started
showing in our marriage.
I'm home.
I'm going to a dinner party with friends tonight!!
And then, I received an envelope
with a letter from a lawyer.
Compensation lawsuit for damages
incurred from illicit activities
Shiori was accused of
illicit activities.
illicit activities
3 million yen in damages
Three million yen in compensation?!
Yes.
My wife's illicit partner had a wife.
It was the wife who filed
the lawsuit against Shiori.
Is that what you call
a double-adultery?
Your wife never learns.
She's the kind who wants
what she can't have.
Has Shiori-san admitted
to illicit activity?
Yes.
Yeah.
I did it.
What were you thinking?
It's all your fault.
Our married life wasn't what
you promised it would be.
Shiori!
My wife moved in with
her parents after that.
We're living separately now.
I see.
We have no savings,
or any means of paying
for compensation, either.
I was wondering if you
could help me somehow.
Are you sure you
want me to help you?
After all, I'm the one
who slapped you with an
exorbitant lawsuit in the first place.
Actually, it was because of that,
that I am now seeking your help.
We're scheduled for a talk with the
other party's legal representative soon.
I was hoping you could
sit in on the session.
Hakamada Law Office
Today's the day.
Of what?
You know, the meeting with your ex-husband.
The other lawyer's
coming here today, too.
I see.
Kanae-san, are you okay with this?
With what?
Hakamada-sensei is going to represent
your ex-husband's obnoxious wife.
That's Hakamada-sensei's
decision to make, not mine.
Excuse us.
You don't have to hide.
Good to have you here.
Please come this way.
Huh?
This is your lawyer?
It has been a while.
I'm Hakamada, attorney at law.
Wait a second, here.
Why's it have to be this guy?
Huh?
And what's your ex-wife doing here?
Well... she's been working here.
You've been seeing your ex, huh?
And you have the nerve
to berate me for cheating.
That's not how it is, Shiori.
Before we have our discussion
with the other party's attorney,
I have a few questions for Shiori-san.
I have nothing to say to you.
Huh?
Our married life was ruined
because of this guy.
Can't we find another lawyer?
Hakamada-sensei is
an outstanding lawyer.
He's on our side now.
Your ex-wife is working
at this office, too, right?
She might sabotage us out of revenge.
No, that kind of thing will not happen.
Anyway, I refuse.
I'd rather pay the lawsuit
and get divorced.
I want a fresh start,
as soon as possible.
Pardon me.
Oh, yes?
I am Honjo Yayoi-san's
legal representative,
Karasuma Keiko.
Hakamada-san?
It's you, isn't it, Hakamada-san?
It has been a while.
Even when I heard "Hakamada Law Office,"
I never expected...
But, you're still practicing law.
You know each other?
Yes.
Sort of.
Sieg Law Office attorney
Karasuma Keiko
We worked at the same law firm
before I went solo.
You were very kind to me, then.
You were a corporate lawyer, too?
Yes.
In fact, I still specialize
in corporate law.
I'm the in-house attorney
for Honjo Industries
presided over by my client,
Honjo Takashi-san,
who has requested that
I represent his wife in this case.
Hakamada-sensei,
I look forward to working with you.
Hakamada
Law Office
Will your client be joining us today?
Yayoi-san
suffered a physical breakdown after she
discovered her husband's affair.
She will not be joining us today.
I see.
Kanae-san.
You're curious, aren't you?
No, not really.
I'm going to go hunt for material.
Well then, to begin...
please have a look.
These are only a part of
the evidence of the illicit affair.
You have been seeing him with
some frequency, documented here.
Adultery investigation report
So many times...
Can everything listed here be proven?
Yes.
Care to have a look?
I will study it later.
Based on our evidence,
we are suing Shiori-san
for five million yen in compensation.
Five million?!
Isn't that higher than the figure
you gave me the other day?
Yayoi-san and Takashi-san are getting
a divorce due to his illicit affair.
As a result,
Yayoi-san has suffered
psychological illness.
Hence, this trauma was added
in the compensation fee.
Just a moment.
Is there a causal connection between
the illicit affair and mental illness?
Shiori-san.
When did you start seeing Takashi-san?
I don't remember.
According to Takashi-san,
it started six months ago.
Yayoi-san discovered
it four months ago.
This is the doctor's diagnosis report.
The time coincides with her
being diagnosed with depression.
Diagnosis
Mrs. Honjo Yayoi
Ailment: Depression
The above named upon examination has been diagnosed with severe and self-harming depression. We suggest protective hospitalization for one month to monitor her condition.
There is no question that
the situation impacted Yayoi-san.
Why am I being blamed for that?
Takashi-san came onto me first.
Actually, not according to this.
Shiori
Takashi-san r u free next week??
Yes.
This side is Shiori-san's texts,
the other is Takashi-san's.
I want us to go to Yokohama next time <3
There's a super yummy pancake place there.
It is clear from this that Shiori-san
was the active initiator.
Take me out for lunch today
Understood.
Those aren't real.
You can fabricate texts.
Fabrications, you say.
Shiori-san, may I see your cell phone?
Perhaps the same conversation
is in the history.
Takashi-san r u free next week??
I want us to go to Yokohama next time <3
There's a super yummy pancake place there.
Take me out for lunch today
Yes.
Understood.
Oh yeah.
I forgot because we always
talked on the phone instead.
Then prove to us that you have
had those phone conversations.
Prove? How?
Do you have any recorded conversations?
Who records phone conversations?!
Sensei.
I understand the case you are making.
We will examine the material,
and respond to you accordingly.
However, five million yen
is beyond Shiori-san's means.
I believe you would
have to reconsider it.
You're not just trying to
buy time, I hope?
Yes.
Um...
I have a question.
That compensation fee...
Am I the only one liable for it?
Fundamentally, that would be the case.
However,
where you get the money
is not our concern.
I understand.
Hey, can I be sure this
Sensei is trustworthy?
He didn't even argue in my favor.
Well, that was a waste of time.
I apologize for her rudeness.
Do you think we stand
any kind of chance?
To be frank,
we are at a disadvantage.
You might have to brace yourselves
to pay the compensation.
I understand.
Goodbye.
Honjo
I had a conference with the other
party's legal representative.
Takashi's wife
Honjo Yayoi
Thank you.
And how did that go?
You can leave now,
I'll hear what she's got to say.
But I'm her client—
Never mind. You don't need to butt in.
Shiori's illicit partner
Honjo Takashi
I understand.
So?
What did they say about the
increased compensation fee?
There is no problem.
The other party made only one statement.
That it would be difficult
to make the payment.
I see...
But it was merely
an appeal to sympathy.
There are many ways to extract
compensation from her.
I made the right decision
hiring you for the job.
And it's not even your specialty.
You're splendid.
Speaking as an attorney,
divorce cases are the easiest.
If we are well prepared,
our victory is assured.
Your instill me with confidence.
By the way, I hear you're
acquainted with the other lawyer.
Yes.
Lucky me, too.
He is an easily-defeated opponent.
Glad to hear it.
Now,
until the compensation
agreement is finalized,
you must continue living
together with your wife.
Yeah.
Yayoi, did you hear that?
It's only because you'll need
the money after our divorce.
Yes.
I know.
What's that?
We've got trouble.
Sensei is baking good bread.
What?
Try it for yourself.
It's better than the highest quality
bread at the Imperial Hotel.
You're right. It's delicious.
Which can only mean...
Yeah.
His anxiety this time is
also of the highest quality.
Excuse us.
Wait. Hold on, Shiori.
They sent me this.
Provisional seizure notice
A provisional seizure notice...
What's that?
It's possible to seize the other
party's assets even before a trial,
Notice proclaiming seizure of properties and income before trial.
Provisional seizure notice
by simply reporting the
illicit activities to a court.
This implies Shiori-san's future
income will be garnished.
Huh? They can take her income, too?
They can garnish up
to 25% of her income.
I can't make a living
if they take that much.
And that's not all.
There's a provisional seizure notice
of the bank account in Shiori's name.
You had said you had no savings.
This was a fund we kept
for our wedding ceremony.
Authorization for seizure, index
Amount total: 2 million yen
Because we haven't had one yet.
I moved my savings to her account,
and we've been adding to it since.
Do I have to give it to them?
Yes,
if the compensation lawsuit
becomes officially recognized.
But, that's where you come in, right?
I don't know what to tell you...
I told you we should
go to another lawyer.
Huh?
What's so good about this guy?
They're beating the crap out of him.
Come on. Stop it.
No, Shiori-san is correct.
So for this particular case,
I think you should consult
a different lawyer.
Sensei.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Where is Hakamada-sensei?
He got a call, and dashed out.
I see.
How's the weekly manga serial going?
Well, so-so.
What was that reaction?
It seems you're not making
any progress with it.
Are you bothered by your
ex-husband's situation?
It's not anything you need
to be concerned about.
That husband's only
reaping what he's sown.
It's not him I'm concerned for,
it's Hakamada-sensei.
Hakamada-sensei?
Yes.
Something's not quite right
with Hakamada-sensei.
Especially after he met
the other's party's lawyer.
Who was it?
Someone called Karasuma-san,
from the Sieg Law Office.
What?!
Could that be Karasuma Keiko?
Yes.
Do you know her?
Karasuma Keiko is...
Hakamada-sensei's ex-lover.
What?
Ten years ago,
Hakamada-sensei was working at a
firm specializing in corporate law.
Attorney at law
Hakamada Yukio
10 years ago
He was an outstanding new
lawyer, with a lot of promise.
He was in charge of forty
clients at the time.
Hakamada-san,
the damages lawsuit of
Asabishi Brokerage...
Karasuma Keiko was working
on the same team at the time.
They worked perfectly
with each other.
The two of them won every case
they fought together as a team.
Ready for the shot?
Strike a pose...
They soon got closer and closer...
That's enough pictures of me.
Let's ask someone to take
a picture of us together.
Don't mind me.
Okay, one more.
I think Hakamada-sensei was
planning to get married to Keiko.
Please marry me.
But...
What's the meaning of this?
That's a client who is negotiating with our firm.
And that's not all.
How many relationships have you had?
Please tell me.
Division Manager's Office
Excuse me.
Division Manager, you wanted to see me?
Karasuma-kun told me everything.
I'm disappointed in you, Hakamada-kun.
Huh?
You're a professional attorney,
and you're stalking your coworker?
Stalking?
No, that's not it.
We've been seeing each other
for six months now and—
That is false.
It was all in Hakamada-san's own head.
What are you saying?
It's all this man's delusions.
There's no proof whatsoever
that I've been seeing him.
I do have proof of that...
And there was no photo, no email
that would have proven
their relationship...
They were all gone.
It was as if she had
anticipated what was coming.
Hakamada-sensei was falsely
accused of stalking ten years ago,
and was fired from the law firm.
Karasuma Keiko took over
all of Hakamada-sensei cases.
She used Hakamada-sensei
as a stepping stone
to get promoted at the law firm.
What did Hakamada-sensei do after that?
Bad rumors about him spread,
and he couldn't work in
corporate law any more.
A little while later,
Hakamada-sensei opened this law office.
He wanted to save people
from the same kind of pain he endured.
So that's why he decided
to become a divorce lawyer.
Karasuma-san.
I'm glad you accepted my
invitation, Hakamada-san.
What would you like to drink?
I don't want anything.
A glass of water, please.
Yes, sir.
I remember. You don't drink.
I came here because you said
you had information
concerning the current case.
I'm not really interested
in husband-wife squabbles.
We all know who will win, anyway.
Thank you for waiting.
On another note,
would you be interested
in joining our firm?
You have some nerve, asking me that.
Come on, Hakamada-san.
You didn't become a lawyer
to handle divorce cases, right?
It's a lot of tedious
work with little payoff.
Oh, and I did a background
check of your office.
About two or three clients per month...
After deducting all expenses,
you must be flat broke.
If you join our firm,
you'll make ten times
what you're making now.
That is, judging by your ability.
I don't practice law for the money.
What do you do it for, then?
Oh, yes. I remember what you
said a long time ago...
"The work of the attorney is
to walk in your clients' shoes,
and discover the best
ways to help them."
But can you say the same for
clients with malicious intent?
Lawyers can't choose their clients.
We are obligated to protect even
those we'd rather not protect.
Justice is a relative thing.
Therefore our sole concern
is whether we win or lose.
There's no justice beyond that concern.
Are you...
still holding a grudge from that time?
I was desperate, then.
I wanted to further my career a lawyer.
But...
When it came to you,
it wasn't like I got close to you
just to use you.
My feelings for you were genuine—
Let's not talk about that.
Anyway,
drop by our office if you want a job.
Um...
Excuse me.
That lady who was with you?
She left without paying.
Hakamada Law Office
Where were you?
I should ask you. What are
you doing here so late?
Waiting for you, Hakamada-sensei.
Waiting for me?
Please don't turn Yoshihito-san down.
As I have already explained,
he doesn't stand a chance.
Is that because your opponent
is Karasuma Keiko-san?
Yoshie-san told me about
your past history with her.
She did it again...
Are you going to compromise your
fortitude for something like that?
This isn't like you.
You have always put yourself
in your clients' shoes, always!
Then you'd always find the
best ways to help them.
But not this time around.
The opposing lawyer was your ex,
so you're cowering and running away!
You're just trying to
protect yourself!
That is not true.
Why did you refuse him, then?!
Because he doesn't stand a chance?
Those aren't Hakamada-sensei's words.
I read this month's issue.
The protagonist's crisis
in the story is trite.
What?
It makes me wonder if you can
handle a weekly serial.
Now, how did that feel,
to hear an opinion from
an absolute amateur?
You're doing the same thing to me.
If you have time to be
concerned about my work,
you should be getting ready
for your weekly serials instead.
I don't want to hear the opinions
of someone getting ready to quit.
Understood.
But before I quit,
I'm going to take over
this case, and settle it.
There's nothing
that you could do.
I have been watching you
work for a whole year now.
I know the methods you've
used to help your clients.
I know them very well.
So, I'm going to help that client,
the way that you would do it.
Sorry to say,
but I agree with Kanae-chan's opinion.
The way you've been lately,
Hakamada-sensei...
is not like Hakamada-sensei at all.
Not only have you not put
yourself in your client's shoes...
You don't even understand
Kanae-san's feelings, do you?
What do you mean?
Kanae-san turned down
the weekly syndication.
Why?
She said she didn't want to discontinue
the monthly Divorce Chaser manga.
To succeed as a manga illustrator,
weekly serials are the fastest track.
Instead,
she said she wants share what
she learns at this law office,
with all her readers.
She wants to help people, too,
using whatever means
she has at her disposal.
In the same way that you
hepled her, Hakamada-sensei.
Kanae-chan must be pulling out
her hair, seeing you like this.
You will pay the
compensation!
Of all the men
I have ever met ...
you are a "dumb man"
of the highest order.
And yet, notwithstanding, you haven't
asked Kanae-san's forgiveness,
not even once.
I have no intention of lessening the
compensation for a person like you.
Ichikawa-san. You truly
are in pain, correct?
Yes.
In that case,
it is only proper we
demand compensation.
You're nothing but a third-rate
ambulance chaser!
I have representation by a first-rate law firm, you're in for a treat!
Can you stand living
with him as you have,
for the next 25 years?
I can't do it.
In that case,
all we can do is forge ahead.
The total membership fees
and compensation...
you will pay, won't you?
After all, you shallowly judge
people based on appearances...
you're not qualified to
oversee human encounters.
I never turn anyone down
if they are truly in need.
You have always put yourself
in your clients' shoes, always.
Then you'd always find the
best ways to help them.
Because he doesn't stand a chance?
Those aren't Hakamada-sensei's words.
I'm glad you came, Hakamada-san.
Thank you for yesterday.
Since you're here,
I assume you're accepting my offer?
No.
With regard to the offer,
I respectfully decline.
What?
I came here today because there
is something I want to tell you.
And what could that be?
First of all, please give me 1,200 yen.
Huh?
That's the charge for the
glass of wine you drank.
It's fine to put on airs
and walk out of the bar...
but you should pay for
your own beverages.
Still as petty as ever...
And I believe we will be suing
your client, Honjo Yayoi-san's husband,
Honjo Takashi-san.
Are you joking?
You don't stand a chance.
A lawyer who turns down clients
because he believes he
doesn't stand a chance...
is not a lawyer in my books.
I know I'm overstepping
my bounds, but...
you should be prepared to lose.
Your change.
The shocking final episode
Next episode
I am prepared
for disbarment.
Now that it's gone to court,
The final battle, laying his life as an attorney on the line
there's no way you can win.
Damn, she got us good.
What will be Hakamada Yukio's fate?!
I won't take
this lying down.
This drama is a work of fiction
Now, let me make a counterargument.