Saionji
Dear father and mother,
Thank you for everything.
I am going to be happy
with Takayuki-san.
Ayaka
One year ago
2012 Health Diagnosis
2012 Health Diagnosis Report
Name: Saionji Tadashi
Age: 64
Good
Ayaka's due date for the baby
is the 20th of next month.
Ayaka's childbirth
due date
What kind of present should we give her?
Present
Money would be better
than material objects, I think—
Anything's fine.
Don't ask me silly questions.
Let's give them money, then.
Cash, huh?
Does that displease you?
There are times I don't want to eat fish.
Shouldn't you know me by now?
I'll fix you something else, then.
Would you like meat of some kind—
Forget it. How's the bath?
It is ready.
Your robe is ready, too.
Please take it when you please.
I come home from work, and
there's nothing decent to eat.
I am sorry.
You're not bowing low enough.
It's meaningless!
Investigation Report
Urai Asako, 22 years old.
She's a student in your husband's
Japanese literature class.
Saionji Tadashi (65)
His student?
I will thoroughly investigate
their behavior.
Freelance investigator:
Umemoto Kurumi
Congratulations.
You finally have a basis for divorce.
Hey, hey...
An illicit affair between a university
professor and his student?
Isn't this a little too scandalous?
We scored.
We couldn't ask for a better way
to corner the husband for infidelity.
Office landlord:
Toyama Yoshie
We'll make a bundle in
compensation, a bundle in fees,
and you can pay your rent!
Please excuse them. I know you've
just learned of your husband's affair.
Hakamada's assistant:
Nonomura Kanae
I don't mind.
After all, Fumiko-san's
been hoping for this.
Hoping for it?
Sensei, is the tea ready?
Temp:
Shinozuka Rina
Please hurry. Our client is waiting.
I'm sorry.
Attorney:
Hakamada Yukio
I made you some tea.
The turtle bread will be done soon, too.
I could barf from the name alone.
What's the idea behind it? Aggravation?
Healthy turtle bread is the first in my
winter nutrition fortification series.
It will invigorate
Fumiko-san for tasks that lie ahead,
and it's also delicious.
Sensei, forget about the
bread for now. This way.
Come on.
Hakamada-sensei, thank you
for all you've done for me.
Current episode's client:
Saionji Fumiko
I can finally divorce my husband.
No, no.
We can't let our guard down just yet.
All we've done is identify
the illicit partner.
These photos aren't proof
they're having physical relations.
Please bear with us for a while,
until we have gathered solid evidence.
We've been married for 34 years.
I've endured and endured...
But, ever since my daughter got
married and left home a year ago...
Thanks to your help, I've been
able to prepare myself for this.
A year?
You've been making
preparations for a whole year?
I have been following Sensei's
and everyone else's instructions.
Oh, right!
This was the first time I've ever
watched a foreign drama.
It was a greatly helpful
resource for my research.
"Iron Spy Woman Marilyn"
season 3, "Invasive Investigation."
Invasive Investigation
Iron Spy Woman Marilyn
It's a unique and
bodacious action series.
Amidst psychological
warfare, we see Marilyn's
feminine sorrows oozing
out for the first time.
It's the most mature season so far.
I'm a spy first and a woman second.
I'll feign love if necessary,
to gather information.
I want some, too!
Let me see it.
Those are my eyedrops.
Don't use them for stupid games.
By the way, how are flower
arrangement classes going?
I'm making a living with it.
I have a room at the Culture
School near the station,
I have more students now,
and have saved up a lot.
Beautiful.
1,240,000...
Did you save all that in a year?
My daughter is having
her baby next month...
and I don't have anything
to worry about any more.
I am finally confident
enough to live on my own.
I saw my husband's health
diagnosis report after
One year ago
my daughter's wedding,
the night I came home.
2012 Health Diagnosis Report. Name: Saionji Tadashi. Age: 64
The projected life-span was 89 years.
Projected life span: 89 years.
My husband will be 64 this year.
That means that after my daughter
has gotten married and left home...
I would have to live alone with that
boorish man for another 25 years.
The very thought of it...
Hey, where's my food?
Ah, I'll prepare it—
Fumiko's husband:
Saionji Tadashi
I'd better not catch your cold!
I have reached my limit.
I cannot bear it any longer.
Please relax.
What's essential when
divorcing at an older age,
is to have the funds necessary to
plan your life after the divorce.
Because you are a housewife, I advise being patient
with the divorce until you enough for living expenses
until you have sufficient
savings for living expenses.
Savings for living expenses...
In general, there are three ways for an elderly
wife to obtain money in a divorce.
Money obtainable in senior citizen divorce
Property distribution
Property distribution, split
pension, and compensation.
Split pension
Compensation
In my rush to leave him,
I had not thought that far...
Firstly, concerning
property distribution...
Property distribution
Even if your financial properties
are in your husband's name,
The wife is entitled to half the estate.
as the wife, you are entitled to half.
Research his savings,
insurance, and so on,
Kanto Central Golf Club
Life Insurance
Certificate
and make a list of them.
Even if he's been hiding them,
U&F Bank
financial institutions
send statements regularly.
Regarding split pension,
Split pension
if your husband agrees, or if the
court decides in your favor,
It is possible to receive at most 1/2 of welfare pension
it's possible for you to receive,
at most, half of the annuity,
Pension Ledger
as of April 2007.
You can inquire about his pension
at the social security bureau.
Yes.
Regarding compensation...
Compensation
it is contingent on whether
your husband has been
engaging in illicit activities,
which would be reason for divorce.
It can be collected if there have been illicit activities
"Illicit activities"?
Has there been any domestic
violence? Or adultery?
Domestic violence, adultery (affairs)
I have been dismayed by my husband's
constant infidelity for many years.
Let's take that route, then!
While researching your husband's finances
and pension to prepare for the divorce,
we'll wait for your husband to show signs of cheating.
I understand.
Lastly,
please secure three months worth
of living expenses for after the divorce.
Let's say you were to
find a room to rent.
Living expenses would be at
least 170,000 yen per month.
Plus, you'd need to make a deposit, and
pay a finder's fee to the Realtor.
Right, so...
To be on the safe side, save
up about one million yen.
One million?!
But, my husband is in
charge of all our finances...
Is it possible for you to
work and earn the money?
I have gotten on in age...
I have no work experience either...
Do you have a hobby of some kind?
A hobby?
It could be anything.
Well, I am a certified
flower arrangement instructor.
That's it. That's a good one.
You've been steadily
preparing ever since...
You can take your first step
toward self-sufficiency, at last.
Hakamada-sensei, and everyone else,
I cannot thank you all enough.
I must reiterate, however,
that these photos are not enough
to demand compensation.
They are not sufficient
evidence of illicit activity.
As to the invasive investigation,
our performance is about to begin.
And if you would, please continue
with the investigation
of your husband's activities.
We're now at a critical stage.
I hope you're ready.
I have been ready for a long time now.
This is the final stage
before compensation.
Proceed with caution.
Divorce Chaser
~Let's Turn Your Tears into Money~
Divorce Chaser Episode 3
Old Age Divorce, Top Secret Win-Win Method!!
Let's see...
Enandai Culture School
2:00PM
Flower Arrangement Class
Saionji-sensei
What if you inserted the yellow orchid here?
And one more.
How lovely!
Thank you very much!
I'm so honored to be taught by
the wife of professor Saionji.
It is an honor, isn't it?
Saionji
What were you doing out so late?
I am sorry.
I wish you had told me
you would be home early.
It's all because of that
flower arrangement class.
That's why you weren't home
to greet your husband.
Throw this crap away!
What are you doing?!
The flower arrangement class means so much to me...
Who cares about your flower arrangement class?
It's just a hobby, isn't it?
As of today, you're quitting!
I said, you're quitting!
Please, stop!
My students count on me!
What?
Yeah, sure.
Cut the cheap trick.
You can't even keep house properly.
Flower arrangement class, my ass!
I am truly sorry.
I will return early from now on.
So please, please let me
continue the flower arrangement class...
Please let me continue
the flower arrangement class!
Who feeds you, huh?
I said you're quitting, and you'll obey!
What's with that look?
Now, draw me a bath.
Then, make dinner.
Understood?
Get on with it!
Where do you think you're going?
I told you to proceed with caution.
I understand how you
must feel, Fumiko-san.
You have bear with
it one last time.
You have to go back.
Hey, Sensei.
Your "invigoration bread"
isn't cutting it this time.
Fumiko-san.
We must establish a solid
premise for divorce.
We will have solid evidence of your
husband's illicit activities soon,
so you have to persevere
just a little longer.
I know it's painful,
but please, return home.
I'll go with you. Okay?
Fumiko-san!
Are you all right?
I can't do it...
I don't even want to breathe
the same air as my husband.
Fumiko-san...
I...
I... If I stay with him...
I may kill him...
You mustn't.
If you kill him, you
won't get compensated.
Sensei...
Now that Fumiko-san has left her home...
I have to use the moral harassment card.
Moral harassment
Moral harassment -> psychological violence
With it I'll bill for the divorce,
bill for matrimonial expenses
in case of separation,
and set the stage for
the longer-term battle.
What are "matrimonial expenses"?
Matrimonial expenses
The husband can be billed
for living expenses during a separation
for living expenses during a separation.
However, so that he
doesn't get suspicious,
I'll keep that under wraps
until we have evidence of his adultery.
You're buying time while
Kurumi-chan gathers evidence.
But, what if we don't get solid evidence?
Based on the current situation,
it would be difficult to get compensation.
I hope Fumiko-san can go on with this.
The year-long preparation period is also
a barometer of the client's commitment.
I believe she will pave
her own path from here on.
No matter what happens.
Fumiko-san can do it.
No way. Really?
I'm so happy.
Excuse me. I'd like
another one of these.
Right away.
Hold on.
How do you do?
I'm an attorney from the
Hakamada Law Office.
My name is Hakamada.
I represent your wife,
who is requesting a divorce.
Requesting a divorce?
Divorce.
She must be momentarily confused.
Your wife can no longer endure
your moral harassment,
and desires a divorce.
There's a misunderstanding.
She was doing that flower arrangement class
and neglecting her household duties.
So I cautioned her a little, that's all.
Poor thing.
That woman can't do a thing on her own.
Just leave her be.
She'll come crawling back to me.
I wonder about that.
According to Fumiko-san's research,
the net worth of the Saionji household
is 60,252,063 yen,
Saionji Tadashi Financial Property List
Net worth: 60,252,063 yen
What is this?
She can't do anything on her own?
I'd say her research was quite splendid.
Don't be absurd!
I worked for this money.
This is my money!
It might be in your name,
but financial properties acquired
during matrimony belong to the couple.
In the case of divorce,
your wife is entitled to half.
That is, approximately 30 million yen.
30 million?
When did she do this?
Where is she?
We are keeping her safe at our office.
I won't agree to it!
She's the one who walked out on me!
I won't give her a single yen!
And I won't consent to a divorce!
Don't.
This is a load of crap!
Go right ahead.
We've saved the data.
Rip it up to your heart's content.
Get out!
Get out now!
I see.
It's just as Fumiko-san said.
You have trouble
controlling your emotions.
You and I will have a discussion later,
concerning compensation for
moral harassment of your wife,
and matrimonial expenses while
she lives separately from you.
Please look forward to it.
Hakamada Law Office
Now, everyone.
Nutrition fortification series, part two!
I have just finished baking
red adder Korean ginseng bread.
Let's have lunch.
Go ahead.
After you.
No, you go ahead!
No need to hesitate.
How very kind of you.
I will try one.
Well... I don't think you should...
Please. It's fresh from the oven.
Thank you.
Dear.
Is that the moral-harassment husband?
Hey, what do you want?
Out of my way.
Hey. You're going home.
No. I will not go back.
Never mind. You're coming back.
Hey you!
Please stop!
Boy, you're stupid.
Don't you know they're conning you?
Let's go.
Please stop it.
I may be overstepping out bounds,
but I don't tolerate
harassment in my office.
Sensei.
What's all this about harassment?
Bastard.
My name is Hakamada!
No, you're a bastard.
You're the culprit who tricked Fumiko.
If you don't let go,
domestic violence will be added
to your compensation fee.
Are you okay with that?
Hakamada Law Office, my ass!
You're nothing but a third-rate lawyer.
I have representation by
a first-rate law firm,
which has served my
family for generations.
You're in for a treat!
Yes.
I'm in for a treat, all right.
Saionji-san states he has no recollection
of instances of moral harassment.
Wilson-Nakatani Corporate Law Offices
Attorney at Law: Nakatani Takuya
Regardless of the fact that
her husband is faultless,
the wife has requested
divorce of her own accord.
Saionji's legal adviser:
Nakatani Takuya
This being the case, the wife will be
liable for compensating her husband.
It will be deducted when their assets
are divided on occasion of a divorce.
Is he intending to take it to court?
The wife started a new business,
then neglected her family life,
thereby leaving her husband
in the lurch, all to himself.
He is emphatic on this point.
Concretely explain what
you mean by "neglected."
Preparing meals,
cleaning...
General household duties.
It's typical in cases such as this.
These journals contain
One year's worth of entries since
Fumiko-san started her flower arrangement class.
For one whole year she has logged
with dates, morning and evening,
the two meals per day she prepared,
the upkeep of their home, doing laundry,
and so on, accompanied
with photographs.
If I may say so,
Fumiko-san is a very meticulous person.
And coincidentally, the journals
provide fodder for her case.
2013 February 3 (Sunday).
A month has passed since I began teaching flower arrangement class...
My husband said, "Mussel soup again? Did you forget you served it yesterday? Are you dumber than an elementary schooler?"
Daikon salad, he left two bites untouched.
The exit is that way.
Saionji
Your wife's journals are sufficient
evidence for the court
that she was not neglectful
of her household duties.
So what?
That lawyer Hakamada...
He looks like a goof,
but he's quite wily.
Though they appear
to be your wife's journals,
he probably advised her a year
ago to keep a detailed record.
Gauging the fact that she has even
listed all your financial assets,
we must assume our opponent has
even more thorough preparations.
My home, my property.
She's going to take half of everything?
As for that, please don't worry.
Estate inherited from previous generations → exempt from property distribution
Separate property
We will claim it as separate property,
in which case it will be exempt
from property distribution.
Everything you have inherited from your family
is exempt from property distribution.
Anyway, do something.
You're a legal advisor, aren't you?
And don't let her take
a single yen of my money.
Saionji-san.
If as you say you don't
want her to take a yen,
we would need your wife to withdraw
her request for divorce.
What am I supposed to do about it?
Firstly, sincerely apologize to her.
Then you apologize, apologize,
and keep apologizing.
I've been feeding that
worthless woman for 34 years.
Why do I have to apologize?
Do you want her to make off
with your fortune?
It's cheaper to apologize.
However, if you decide to apologize,
be as sincere as you can,
keep your emotions under control,
and keep apologizing.
I don't want to see Saionji ever again.
His lawyer says your husband
is deeply repentant,
and wants to beg your forgiveness
from the bottom of his heart.
Beg my forgiveness?
I know what that Saionji is up to.
I don't want to see
his face ever again!
I know you can't bear to breathe
the same air as him.
I know how that feels.
I was like that, too.
Let's meet with your husband.
Huh?
Hakamada
Law Office
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were so unhappy.
This is the first time you
have ever apologized to me.
I make no excuses. Truly.
"I am sorry."
"I make no excuses."
I want you to show me
your genuine feelings.
Genuine feelings?
How dare you talk to me that way!
Saionji-san.
I am sorry. I mean it!
You're not bowing low enough.
It's meaningless!
What's the matter?
Is that not what you always say to me?
You're not bowing low enough.
It's meaningless!
You...
Do you have any idea
of why I was unhappy?
Isn't that what you came
to apologize about?
Tell me. Why was I unhappy?
Well, you know...
You don't even know why
you're apologizing.
You're a riot.
What's so funny?
How dare you take advantage of my—
So, you wanted to apologize.
I knew it was just a ploy!
You trapped me, didn't you?
I fed you for 34 years, and
this is the thanks I get?
That's right.
For 34 years as a housewife,
until Ayaka grew up, I had no
choice but to live with you.
With a person like you!
"A person like you"? How dare you!
Saionji-san.
Fumiko-san has lived with you,
and knows what kind of person
you are, through and through.
On the other hand, for 34 years,
you have known nothing about Fumiko-san.
And now you have to face reality.
What you can do now,
is to learn of Fumiko-san's pain,
and express your genuine feelings.
Ha!
Wake up, you dumb woman!
Don't you realize this
lawyer is tricking you?
Saionji-san, please calm down!
You don't know how the world works!
You'll never make it alone!
You're going to regret this!
Your wife is firmly
resolved to divorce you.
To protect your assets,
we will take it to court.
But before we do, it would be most
judicious to refer to arbitration.
You're saying I should get the divorce?
By referring to arbitration
before taking it to court,
we can minimize the compensation.
I will outline the arbitration proposal.
Before the opposing attorney
garners any evidence,
I advise you to make
your decision immediately.
Goodbye.
Divorcing at old age...
Divorce?! You think you can
make it on your own?!
You're coming home!!
A woman's grudge is a scary thing.
The crux of the story is that the husband
is clueless that his wife loathes him.
Makes you wonder what
marriage is all about.
It's your job to find out, Kanae-sensei.
"Sensei"?
Oh stop it. "Sensei."
Jeez, come on.
Your popularity is off
the charts lately.
Please keep up the good work.
Editor at Tokiwa Publishing:
Tabata Misato
I can't wait to find out what
happens to the senior couple.
Me, too.
I wonder what's going to happen.
Cafe waitress:
Mizutani Sara
First there will be thunder...
Then, there will be a rain of blood.
Excuse me. I didn't order tomato juice.
Hello.
You weren't in class today
so I was wondering...
Hello?
Oh, Ayumi-san.
Do you know where everyone is today?
I...
think I'm going to quit.
What?
I'm sorry.
W-Wait, please!
Please! Please tell me why!
I'm in a hurry.
No one came to class.
What's wrong?
If there is something about me
that is amiss, please tell me.
It's not you, Mrs. Saionji.
Then, why?
The students stopped coming
to class, all at once?
Could your husband be
behind this, somehow?
No, that's not it.
It's suspicious that everyone
stopped coming all at once, though!
No, one of my students told me,
so I know what happened.
Everyone came to class because
I was the wife of professor Saionji.
That's ridiculous.
Just because you're Saionji-san's wife?
What's that got to do with anything?
The Saionji family lineage has
generations of prestigious men.
The students had connections
with them in various ways.
But, when they learned
about the divorce...
In short, the students stopped coming
so as to not offend Saionji-san.
"You don't know how the world works!
You'll never make it alone!"
Maybe my husband was right.
Fumiko-san.
Be that as it may, would you
want to return to your husband?
Can you stand living with him as
you have, for the next 25 years?
I...
can't do it!
In that case, all we
can do is forge ahead.
Your husband's lawyer drafted
an arbitration proposal.
I'm certain he intends to
take it to court after that.
I shouldn't have been so
hasty to leave the house.
If he takes us to court,
my husband will win.
That remains to be seen.
But, before the hearing,
can you fight one more battle?
What have you got up your
sleeve, Hakamada-san?
Why would you suddenly want to have a
meeting with Saionji-san before arbitration?
We have no intention of
canceling arbitration,
unless his wife agrees
to return back home.
I told you she'd come
crawling back to me.
Just look at her.
How's she going to make it on her own?
Saionji-san.
Fumiko-san insists there's something
she must tell you before the hearing.
Fumiko-san.
This is your chance to express
yourself fully to your husband.
Everything you couldn't tell
your husband for 34 years.
Do you remember this place?
This is stupid.
You proposed to me here, 34 years ago.
Don't beat around the bush.
If you want to come back,
be straightforward and say it.
I'll forgive you this time around.
All right. Let's go home.
What are you doing?
I heard Ayaka is having a baby girl.
Huh?
Takayuki-san is beside himself with joy.
He said he's stocking up on all
the baby girl goods he can find.
So what?
I don't have time for this.
Do you remember what you said
to me at the maternity ward,
soon after Ayaka was born?
Maternity ward?
"Damn it. It's a girl."
The fulfillment I had felt after
enduring the pain of delivery,
the joy I felt of becoming a mother...
You crushed them all
with those cold words.
Why are you bringing that up now?
That was years ago.
My parents were desperate
for me to have an heir.
I was scared!
"You married into the Saionji family,
but you can't even produce a boy?!"
You tortured me constantly for
my subsequent infertility,
and escaped from me by
repeatedly having affairs.
If another woman were
to bear you a baby boy,
Fumiko-san had determined
to leave the Saionji family.
That was how desperate she was.
Affairs?
You have no proof.
Why didn't you tell me these things?
How could she?
She knew you had withdrawn from her,
because she couldn't bear you an heir.
Your ill temper,
your ignoring me, verbal abuse,
crude remarks...
Even when I would get sick,
you were only concerned
about your meals.
You did not view me as a woman...
no, you did not view
me as a human being.
You're not young any more.
I thought maybe we'd give our
marriage another chance, but...
It seems there's no choice now
but fight it out in court.
Are you sure you want
to take it to court?
Yes.
I'll tear her apart.
Too bad for you.
Because when it goes to court,
you're the one who will be torn apart.
So what?
This woman was nothing but a diversion!
She seduced me!
Even as a diversion,
illicit affairs are bad news
for a marriage.
Isn't that so, Nakatani-sensei?
Even in the case of illicit affairs,
we won't be charged more than
three million or so in compensation.
Let's go.
I personally don't care, but
this is going to be a scandal.
Having an illicit affair with a student.
Your student?
Sure, maybe you'll get away
with three million in compensation.
However, losing your position
as a university professor.
would be an immeasurable loss,
would it not?
Fumiko-san does not want
to tarnish your reputation.
She just wants you to consent to the divorce.
That's why she asked you here,
to this place full of memories...
Because I know, that if you lost
your university professorship
it would be the end of you.
Saionji-san.
We're done for.
You...
You would go to such
lengths to leave me?
That day...
2012 Health Diagnosis Report
when I saw all the "good" listed
on your health diagnosis report...
I thought to myself,
"How much longer must this man live?
It's true that I am not young any more.
But, I still have many
more years to live.
I don't want to die as Saionji Fumiko."
Fumiko.
Yazawa-sensei.
Enandai Culture School
2:00PM
Flower Arrangement Class
Yazawa Sensei
Yes, how nice!
How do I arrange this part?
You balance it out delicately, like this.
Oh, I see! Thank you very much.
Nice work.
Saionji-san has some shred
of decency, at least.
He notified the flower arrangement students
and had them return to class.
He was raked over the coals.
Even Mr. Moral Harassment
himself did some introspection.
A good divorce is something
that helps people grow.
That's my opinion anyway,
as my client's attorney.
I hope that Fumiko-san and Saionji-san,
now that they've gone separate ways,
will live out their next 25
years in a much better way.
Neither does he marry nor divorce.
Such is the bread baker man
we got here, who doesn't grow.
It's ready at last.
The final in my nutrition fortification series:
the whole turtle red viper
Korean ginseng special!
Looks delicious.
Hey everyone, please try the...
Huh?
Next episode
You're completely useless!
You're suffering because
of a monster wife.
You cheer them on before the
divorce, that's how it's done.
The Horror of the Monster Wife!
Intense Revenge of the Cowardly Husband!
Who do you think you're talking
to, you piece of trash?
Get on your knees and beg!
This drama is a work of fiction.
Let's turn your fear into money.