Thank you very much.
Tavern
Yoshi
Add an order of yakisoba and yakitori.
Did you bring the beer to table two?
The day will end
before you get it there!
Yes, I'll do it right away.
Table one's yakitori, thanks.
Yes.
Were you listening?
I said the beer first.
Yoshioka family, bride
Yoshioka Miki
Yoshioka family, mother-in-law
Yoshioka Tomoe
Go do that first, like I told you.
What a useless bride!
I'm sorry.
Thank you for waiting.
So, this is your favorite
tavern, Yoshie-san?
Hakamada's Assistant
Nonomura Kanae
Office landlord
Toyama Yoshie
What do you recommend?
Other than the yakitori.
Yoshie-san.
Huh?
Is something the matter?
Nothing.
Nice place, right?
Their stews are the best.
You're drinking Oolong tea at a tavern?
I don't drink.
Jeez, you sound just like Sensei.
That man doesn't drink,
doesn't pay the rent...
Landlord, we paid the
rent just yesterday.
Oh, I wasn't talking about
your place, Yoshi-san.
This restaurant is one of my rentals.
Really? Here, too?
Here's your yakitori.
Thank you for waiting.
I'm so sorry for the wait, as well.
Why are you such a slug?
The food'll get cold.
You told me to serve
the beer to table two first.
You're blaming me? How rude...
I'm so sorry about that.
How about I bring
a stew dish on the house,
as a token of our apology.
Come on, get the stew.
I'm sorry.
It's not cold at all.
And I was going to order stew anyway,
so just put it on my tab.
But—
Don't worry about it.
I just heard. I am so sorry.
Don't just stand there looking stupid.
Clean up this table. Do I have
to tell you to do everything?
I'm sorry.
I have to tell you to do everything.
Nao-kun just bought me this shirt!
Are you alright, Rie-chan?
I'm sorry.
Sorry, for our bride.
I'm so sorry.
What if it stains?
Be careful!
I'm sorry.
We will pay to have it laundered.
Please come this way.
I'm so sorry.
That's enough of you.
Get cleaning! Hurry up!
I'm so sorry!
Are you all right?
I can do this.
If I let a customer do my job,
Mother would get angry.
It's fine, really.
Your hand is bruised.
You can't go on like this much longer.
It'll be your death.
Yoshioka
Do you know how much
dry cleaners cost nowadays?
Shunsuke can't grill enough yakitori
to make up for your losses.
I am sorry.
Look at this filthy room!
Do I have to come home
exhausted every day to this?
What is this?
I had to hurry off this
morning for preparations.
Don't talk back. Just clean.
Shunsuke, you must be tired.
Yoshioka family, groom
Yoshioka Shunsuke
Why don't you take a bath first?
Yeah.
Good job today.
This place is pig sty.
Make it fit for human habitation
before you go to bed.
Yes.
There, at the corner.
There's debris everywhere.
It's midnight.
Vacuuming would bother the neighbors.
You're full of excuses, aren't you?
Here. Try this.
I'm taking a bath.
Yes.
Mother drained the bath by mistake.
Mistake?
But I'm always the last to bathe.
Of course she wouldn't
do it on purpose.
Don't be so paranoid.
Mother's tired. That's all.
I'm tired, too, you know.
I work just as hard
as you and your mother,
but she makes me do more
chores when we get home.
You once said, "I'll endure anything
if I can always be with you, Shun-chan."
You knew you were going
to help at the tavern,
and that we were going to
live with my mother...
from before we got married.
But...
Give me a break. I'm tired, too.
Good night.
Hakamada Law Office
Don't worry.
I don't really want to
go to a law office...
Hakamada
Law Office
This place is actually
my friend's bakery.
Don't worry.
Sensei, I'm borrowing
your place for a second.
You'll go crazy if you
let that mother-in-law
keep bullying you like that.
But, I have no intention
of leaving my husband.
You're from the tavern.
Did something happen?
Temp
Shinozuka Rina
Tavern?
Oh, the one Yoshie-san
goes to all the time.
Let's try and think of a solution
to your problem together.
Hey, Sensei.
You're making too much
noise with that dough.
Attorney
Hakamada Yukio
Well, I'm infusing the dough
with feelings of gratitude to you all...
and in looking forward to spring,
I have named this bread "The Special Spring—"
We don't need to know the name.
Never mind the gratitude
or the bread!
Pay the rent!
I'm so sorry you have to
see all this ugliness.
I told everyone I was just
going shopping.
I have to get back.
Are you okay?
You got really pale!
Miki-san, take a little break here.
Sensei, tea.
Oh. Yes!
Hurry.
It's ginger tea.
This is Yoshioka Miki-san.
She's the bride at my favorite
haunt, the Tavern Yoshi.
I've been noticing it lately,
but her mother-in-law bullies
her something terrible.
I saw it for myself last night.
It was terrible.
You look very tired.
By the way, how long did
you sleep last night?
About four hours, I think.
Four hours?
It's like you're in cram school.
I go in for prep at six in the morning.
Then, I get the tables set up.
At night I do all the cleaning,
and by the time I get home
it's close to one o'clock.
Then, I have to do chores.
So I can't sleep more
than that each night.
Sleep deprivation is bad for your skin.
What about your meals?
Are you eating properly?
Between chores and
working at the tavern,
I'm too busy to eat sometimes.
Often I don't have time to sit
and eat lunch or dinner.
That's not good!
You have to eat properly!
You don't look well at all.
Why don't you ask your
mother-in-law for a day off today?
I once had a fever of 104 degrees,
and she still made me work.
Come on. Get on with it!
Hurry up!
That's like an underground sweatshop.
Sensei, do something.
Miki-san will die if she
continues like this.
Pardon me if I may ask, Miki-san,
but what do you want to do?
I don't want to separate
from Shun-chan...
that is, my husband,
no matter what.
So...
I'm fine.
I understand.
Miki-san...
Shun-chan was my upperclassman in
high school, and I admired him.
He had a girlfriend for a long time,
so I gave up on him for a while...
But, after graduation,
he told me they'd broken up...
So I aggressively pursued him.
And we finally got married
seven years ago, and...
it was like a dream come true.
She's taking advantage
of your love for him.
Can't something be done about this?
Like asking your husband to have your
mother-in-law live elsewhere?
I agreed before we were married
that she would live with us.
Seriously, I have to get going.
Thank you for the tea.
Goodbye.
Oh. Miki-san.
Wait—
Jeez...
What a spineless husband,
not standing up for his wife.
She should dump him
and sue for compensation.
Yoshie-san,
you have to consider
Miki-san's feelings, too.
You can't casually make
drastic decisions for her.
Then, let me ask you, Kanae-chan.
Are you going to do nothing
while you watch Miki-san slowly die?
That's not what I meant!
Please, both of you calm down.
Then you'd better do something, Sensei!
I have to respect her decision
to stay with her husband.
What about suing the
mother-in-law for bullying, then?
Oh!
Good idea.
Let's do it!
Unless circumstances
are quite extreme...
it's difficult for a daughter-in-law
to sue her mother-in-law.
Who cares if it's difficult?
Hurry up and get the ball rolling!
That's right!
Do something.
Sensei.
Don't move in... so close...
Divorce Chaser
~Let's Turn Your Tears into Money~
Divorce Chaser Episode 10
Put an End to the War of In-Laws!
Closed Today
Why are you cleaning
so vigorously today?
Because Mother will gripe
at me if it's not clean.
Maybe that's not all
there is to it, though...
Mother doesn't approve of
anything I do, regardless.
It's futile for me
to try to please her.
That's enough.
All you ever do is complain lately.
I'm sorry.
Try to get along with her.
It's hardest on me when you don't.
Mother, how is the seasoning?
It's hot, so be careful.
Mm, what refined seasoning!
It's delicious.
Yuri-chan.
Yuri-chan?
This young lady is Kubo Yuriko-chan.
She and Shunsuke are childhood friends.
Shunsuke's childhood friend
Kubo Yuriko
And here's the bride, Miki.
How do you do? I'm Yuriko.
I'm Miki.
Well, I'd better get going.
Thank you for lending me this.
You're leaving already?
I haven't seen you in so long.
Oh, Shunsuke.
Yuriko-chan brought
us fresh red snapper.
We cooked it together, didn't we?
Mother invited me the other day,
so I thought I'd drop in.
It's so fun spending time
with you, Yuri-chan.
Hey, why don't you stay for dinner?
Can you? You can show
me your cooking skills.
What a feast.
It's like a celebration or something.
Never mind the comments.
You're always in my way.
Mm, delicious!
All I ever have to eat is
half-baked swill around here.
This has brought me back to life!
Shunsuke, eat up while you can.
It's all your favorites.
It's good.
Your cooking's gotten
even better, Yuri-chan.
You.
You should try it, too,
for future reference.
I will.
Well?
Does it meet with your approval?
It's good.
Well, so she does know the
difference between good and bad.
She's so bad at cooking,
I thought she didn't
know the difference!
That's terrible, Mother.
Of course she knows the difference!
Try to get along with her.
It's hardest on me when you don't.
Oh, Mother, please.
Always kidding around.
Truth be told,
I wanted Shunsuke to marry
someone like you, Yuri-chan.
We have the same
taste in food, too.
There's nothing I could do, anyway.
Yuri-chan was already
in an arranged marriage.
I was too young, anyway.
But it's okay.
You got to marry this lovely girl instead.
Um...
Yuriko-san, how long ago
did you get married?
Let me see...
seven years ago, I guess.
Seven years ago...
Yuri-chan, you haven't changed a bit.
You look ten years younger.
She's always been so pretty.
And compared to this...
You shouldn't sit next to her.
Mother, please.
Delicious!
I can't help it.
I'd like to make myself pretty, too,
but I'm always exhausted.
I don't even have time to sleep.
Hey, Mother was just kidding.
I do everything Mother tells me to do,
at home and at the tavern,
to the best of my ability.
Oh, please, listen to this.
You make it sound like I'm forcing you.
You see how rude she is?
Right? I'm sick of it.
I'm not your slave, Mother!
Miki!
You can't talk like that to Mother.
Shun-chan.
Apologize to her!
Miki-san, don't be so angry.
Let's all enjoy a friendly meal.
You...
What do you know?
Hey.
Miki!
Let her be!
Hakamada Law Office
I made chamomile tea.
It's very soothing.
Thank you very much.
So, this so-called
childhood friend, Yuriko...
Was she  your husband's girlfriend in high school?
Shun-chan said that seven years ago,
before we got married...
that his longstanding girlfriend's
parents arranged her marriage...
and she dumped him.
But, why did your mother-in-law
invite his ex-girlfriend to the house?
I assume she's been married
the past seven years, too.
Mother is spiteful.
She praised Yuriko-san's
cooking in front of me.
She compared my looks
to hers and laughed.
She even said she'd wanted
Yuriko-san to marry her son.
Are you kidding?
Isn't the one working
her fingers to the bone
you, Miki-san?!
How can you be expected
to cook anything spectacular
when you have no time?
This is an outrage!
And your husband...
Did he just quietly watch
all that happening?
"You can't talk like that to mother."
That's what Shun-chan said
when I talked back to her.
That's awful.
I've reached my limit.
At this rate,
I'll gradually turn into
a horrible person.
I've endured this much because
I love Shun-chan, but...
I...
am going to divorce him.
Sensei.
Understood.
You are officially my client.
She overdid it by inviting
his ex-girlfriend.
Let's get ready for the divorce.
Let's sue the mother-in-law
for compensation.
Compensation?
You're young, so you probably think
you don't need compensation...
but you can't let people
walk all over you.
From everything I've heard so far,
the situation sounds like more
than just a case of bullying.
How so?
What do you mean?
In other words...
there's something more behind it.
Firstly, you must gather
evidence of bullying.
So, provisionally, please
apologize to your mother-in-law,
and go back home.
Mother.
I am sorry.
You think an apology is enough?
I think we did the
right thing. Don't you?
There are times people have
to stand up for themselves,
even if it's hard.
You've been worried about
Miki-san for quite a while now.
I...
have a daughter.
You have a daughter?
About seven or eight years ago,
my daughter was in the
same situation as Miki-san.
She was bullied constantly by her
Oedipus-complex husband and his mother.
And she ran away from them,
leaving all her belongings behind.
It was Sensei who helped her, then.
She received compensation...
She got her divorce...
That's why I still rent the office
out to that penniless lawyer.
I see...
That's why I had to do something.
Something for Miki-san.
Cheers!
Ladies of the Shopping District
Women's Association,
thank you for your continued patronage.
We're celebrating our
newest member today.
Wow, you really guzzled that beer!
How impressive!
Oh, please! I'm shy!
May I take your order?
Miki-san, don't bully your
mother-in-law too much.
Huh?
Freelance Investigator
Umemoto Kurumi
You haven't attended
our meetings lately.
Because my mother-in-law
says I don't need to—
Miki-chan, good job.
You must be tired.
You can take a break now.
Yes.
Good job.
Thanks.
She's what you call a monster bride.
When she gets in one of her moods,
she complains that she's tired,
she yells at everyone...
That's so scary.
You must be careful
to never become like her.
I'll be careful.
I'll bring you some edamame.
On the house.
You're always so good to us!
Um...
when did Miki-san stop coming
to the meetings?
Let's see...
It's been three years, I think.
Speaking of which...
I think that's when it all began.
That's when her relationship
with her mother-in-law started to sour.
Three years ago...
That's right.
That was about the time she started
talking trash about her daughter-in-law.
I think it's quite complicated.
Hey, you, hey!
I told them I'm giving
them free edamame.
Why didn't you have it ready?
I'm sorry. I'll get on it right away.
Just forget it.
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry.
"I'm sorry.I'm sorry."
You think can get away with
anything by apologizing!
I'm sorry.
Too bad I can't get rid of you.
Hakamada Law Office
She's been bullied like that
for three whole years!
For three years...
Three years ago,
did something happen
between you and the mother?
There was, wasn't there?
It wasn't about Mother, though.
It doesn't matter.
Three years ago,
Shu-chan cheated on me.
It was cold then,
so I think it was around
the same time of year.
Cheating?
With who?!
I don't know who it was.
When I questioned him,
he turned it around and said,
"Let's get a divorce, then."
But, I didn't want a divorce.
I said, "I love you, Shun-chan.
I'll never divorce you."
The guilty spouse,
or more accurately,
the husband who had an illicit affair
which could destroy the household,
The party guilty of an illicit affair
has no legal standing
to ask for a divorce.
has no standing to demand a divorce.
If he still insists on a divorce,
he'd be liable for a
hefty compensation fee.
And what did your husband say?
He said, "I'm not seeing her any more."
Shu-chan was very upfront about it.
Sensei, is there a connection between
the affair three years ago and the bullying?
The mother-in-law told her she didn't
have to attend the meetings any more...
Kurumi-san.
Closed today
The rest, I'll leave in your hands.
That's our meeting for today.
Good job, everyone.
Good work!
Good work, everyone. Please,
have some beer on the house.
I'm going out for a bit.
Sure.
Chairman, good job today.
Thank you, Madam.
I always look forward to
having our meetings at Yoshi,
especially this part.
Thank you for your
continued support.
This is about all I can
do for you, but...
By the way, I got you an estimate
for renovating the tavern.
Oh, thank you very much.
I can always rely on
Kobayashi Building Contractors.
We're working on the blueprint.
Shopping district chairman / President of Kobayashi Building Contractors
Kobayashi Hiroyasu
Yes.
Let me bring you some snacks.
Thanks.
The tavern's getting renovated?
Well... yes.
Chairman, you're the president
of a contracting firm, aren't you?
My place needs renovation, too.
Can you tell me how
it works in some detail?
Y-Y-Yes.
Iron Spy Woman Marilyn season
11, episode "Honey Trap."
I'm a tigress.
There's no man who won't fall for me.
It appears your mother-in-law
is having a renovation done
by the shopping district chairman and
president of Kobayashi Building Contractors.
Renovation?
Interior Renovation Work
Miki-san, you didn't know about this?
It's always been this way.
Shu-chan and his mother
make all the decisions.
There's one scenario
that is conceivable.
The two of them are keeping
the matter secret to you for a reason.
But why would they need to hide
their plan to renovate from Miki-san?
He cheated three years ago.
The bullying started at the same time.
And they've been keeping the renovation
plan secret from Miki-san.
When you connect those
three dots together...
Do you mean...
her husband is in on it, too?
That can't be...
But, for what?
I cannot say anything for certain.
However, if they are
conspiring together...
there is a high probability
your husband wants a divorce.
Perhaps it would be best
to confront him directly,
and ask him yourself.
Directly?
Are you sure that's a good idea?
I don't mind.
I'm leaving them anyway.
Miki-san.
Sensei.
I am relying on you.
Understood.
First off,
let's see how they respond
to the compensation lawsuit
on grounds of bullying.
On that occasion,
please be careful to not
use the word "divorce."
Because I am going to draw
that word out of them.
Yes?
I am Hakamada Yukio of the
Hakamada Law Office.
As Miki-san's legal representative,
I am here to discuss a compensation lawsuit
based on your psychological abuse
toward your daughter-in-law.
Psychological abuse?
Attorney at Law
Hakamada Yukio
Suing her own mother-in-law...
How bad can this
bride's character get?
I am told Miki-san has been placed
in charge of all household chores
after working full-time at the tavern.
As a result,
Miki-san has been averaging four hours of
sleep a night for the last three years.
She has had no time for her
regular meals on a daily basis.
This is Miki-san's health
diagnosis report.
As you can see from the report,
Miki-san has incurred considerable
Health diagnosis report
Name: Yoshioka Miki
Diagnosis: weight loss and
anemia due to malnutrition.
Additional notes: Probable cause
of malnutrition is due to excessive
labor and sleep deprivation
on a daily basis.
physical damage, including weight
loss and anemia due to malnutrition.
Health diagnosis report
Name: Yoshioka Miki
Diagnosis: weight loss and anemia
due to excessive labor and sleep depravation
I'm helpless.
I'm getting older, and taking this kind
of abuse from my daughter-in-law,
I'm helpless.
Mother.
When I was married,
I didn't get along with
my mother-in-law, either.
But I never would've sued her.
If she doesn't like it here,
she can leave any time.
Sir,
what are your thoughts on the matter?
She shouldn't have resorted
to asking a lawyer.
We're family, after all.
We should talk it out like one.
Miki-san has sought
your help several times.
But every time, you evaded her by
asking her to just "get along."
All I wanted was for Miki
to get along with my mother.
But...
If she can't, then it can't be helped.
Meaning?
I will divorce Miki.
I'm tired of all this, too.
Miki-san does not want
to divorce you, however.
She is willing to withdraw the
compensation lawsuit,
on the condition that you
and your mother treat her fairly.
Withdraw or not,
my mother has never done anything to
deserve a lawsuit in the first place.
So you choose your
mother over Miki-san?
I have only one mother, after all.
Shun-chan.
Understood.
I will relay your message to Miki-san.
The husband initiated
the talk of divorce.
There is no question he and his mother
are conspiring together.
Miki-san.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm firm in my decision.
It seems you were right
about the conspiracy.
How did it go?
I investigated as per
your instructions, Sensei.
About this girl.
Yuriko-san.
So this woman is your
husband's ex-girlfriend.
She and Miki-san's husband have been
friends since elementary school.
They were in a relationship for nine years
starting their second year in high school,
and seven years ago,
a little before Miki-san
would marry her husband,
Yuriko entered a marriage
arranged by her parents.
So, it's just as Miki-san said.
Kubo Yuriko...
While she was married, her
name was Nishida Yuriko.
While she "was" married?
In other words, that Yuriko
woman is divorced?
She got divorced three years ago,
citing adultery.
Three years ago...
Wait a second.
It was three years ago when
Miki-san's husband cheated on her.
Which means that his cheating
partner must've been...
Could it be?
It is probable...
that it was Kubo Yuriko-san.
It can't be true...
However, based on the situation alone,
we cannot ascertain that your husband's
cheating partner three years
ago was Kubo Yuriko-san.
What are you saying?
Both of them were involved
in adultery three years ago.
Since she's divorced,
it must mean that Yuriko-san
must've admitted to the adultery.
Sensei.
Can we sue the husband for compensation,
for having an illicit affair?
Unfortunately, we cannot.
You can't?
Why is that?
Legally, adultery has a three-year
statute of limitations.
Illicit activities have a three-year statute of limitations -> no compensation lawsuit
In other words, since
three years has passed,
he can no longer be sued
on grounds of adultery.
Only three years?!
I wouldn't forgive him
for the rest of my life!
The problem is how
we prove the husband's continued
relationship with Yuriko-san.
The statute of limitations has passed,
so we can't sue him for compensation...
She's a demon...
Even the bullying...
There's still stuff there.
It's a pig sty in here!
You're really useless!
I'm not your slave, Mother!
I would never forgive her... demon hag!
Editor at Tokiwa Publishing
Tabata Misato
Please calm down!
But, this mother-in-law is a demon!
She's not human!
May I help you?
Demons reside in the human heart.
The world is full of demons.
What?
It's true. Demons everywhere.
Cafe waitress
Mizutani Sara
Your heart also has a demon.
Here.
You are a demon, too.
Huh?
Looks like she'll finally
want a divorce.
It took three whole years.
That's one stubborn bride.
The statute of limitations
for adultery has passed...
There's no way that lawyer
can sue for compensation,
not to mention for bullying.
She's the one who decided to leave.
Why should we have to pay?
I was against this marriage
from the beginning.
Things will go as planned, Shunsuke.
This is the household's list of assets,
in its entirety.
Yoshioka Family Assets List
Real estate
License for tavern proprietorship
Savings, cash
Life insurance
Miscellaneous properties
Wait a second.
All of them are in the
mother-in-law's name.
There's no joint asset
of husband-wife anywhere.
That's because my mother-in-law
managed all the finances.
We can't expect property
distribution, then.
This can't be happening...
And the statute of
limitations has passed...
Sensei.
I used my womanly charms
and enticed the blueprint out of him.
Thank you very much.
This is your husband and his mother's
blueprint for renovating the tavern.
The name of the tavern is...
Now we have all the
pieces to the puzzle.
Renovation Blueprint
Mother, in this open area here,
can we install another oven?
I want grilled items on the menu, too.
Of course.
You can do anything
you want, Yuri-chan.
That was quite a detour,
but I can finally be
with you, Yuri-chan.
I can't wait to run the place together.
It's going to get busy.
No time for coughing up lawsuits.
Since she's married to me,
we won't have to pay
her severance, either.
What is the meaning of this?
So you've finally agreed to the divorce?
For seven years,
I endeavored for this tavern.
Hardly getting sleep at night,
skipping meals, working,
and working some more.
And now you do this?
This establishment is in my name.
You can divorce
Shunsuke or whatever,
but I don't have to distribute
a penny of my property to you.
So, you at least accept me as his wife.
Then why are you naming
the renovated tavern
after your son's illicit partner?
His illicit partner's name?
Dining Bar "Lily" Renovation Blueprint
Dining Bar "Lilly."
"Lily"
"Lily" is English for "Yuri."
As in Yuriko-san's name, right?
What are you talking about?
I remembered the other day
when Yuriko-san came to the apartment,
that it was three years ago to that day
that I discovered Shun-chan was cheating.
What are you trying to say?
It was as if you were
celebrating that day.
Ridiculous.
Don't make creepy accusations.
No, that day was indeed
a day of celebration.
That was the day the statute
of limitations passed,
for the adultery between
Shunsuke-san and Yuriko-san.
I know who you had the affair with,
three years ago.
It was Yuriko-san, wasn't it?
Hey, you.
Where did you learn to
get bossy like that?
Because I learned that I can't
just let people walk all over me.
They're not walking all over you now.
You stood up for yourself.
Yuriko-san.
The reason for your divorce...
It was because of your affair
with him, wasn't it?
Who cares?
The statute of limitations
is three years for adultery.
That's right.
It's too late now!
So the three of them were
celebrating that day.
And right in front of Miki-san, no less.
What disgusting people!
And I believed in you.
Even though I knew
your ex-girlfriend was always
in your heart, Shun-chan.
I believed that some day,
you would only have eyes for me.
So I endured Mother's bullying.
I wanted to be a good wife.
And did my best.
I'll send you the divorce papers.
If there's nothing else, leave.
I may be overstepping my bounds,
but there's one more
thing before we leave.
Let me explain to you
supplemental information
regarding the statute of
limitations for adultery.
Supplemental information?
You admit that you and Yuriko-san had
an illicit affair three years ago, correct?
Yeah, I admit it.
But it's past the limit.
Indeed.
There is a statute of limitations of three years
to sue for compensation for adultery.
Compensation lawsuit for illicit activities
But that is when the
perpetrator is identified.
When the perpetrator is identified → Statute of limitations of three years
And if the person is unidentified...
When unidentified
the statute of limitations is three years
after the person becomes identified.
-> 3 years after identification
The perpetrators in this case
are the husband and Yuriko-san.
It is a fact that Miki-san knew
her husband was guilty of an
illicit affair three years ago.
Hence, we cannot sue the husband
for compensation any more.
However, there is one more perpetrator.
The illicit partner in the adultery.
That would be Yuriko-san.
Miki-san found out that it was her,
today, for the first time.
Hence, within the next three years...
Yuriko-san can be sued
for compensation.
Hey, Shunsuke, this isn't
how you said it'd go!
Why do I have to get
sued for compensation?!
Calm down. Calm down.
And you too, Mother!
I did this because you promised
you'd chase that wife out!
I waited three years
to be with Shunsuke,
and this is what I get?!
Zip it, be quiet!
I've had it!
Yuri! Yuri-chan!
Yuriko-san was waiting for
Miki-san to leave, she said.
Which means the husband and Yuriko-san's
adulterous affair continued until now.
That means the statute of limitations
to sue for compensation
has not yet expired.
Don't be ridiculous.
I can finally renovate
this establishment.
I have no money to pay
for compensation.
Tomoe-san.
You were going to renovate the place
into a European-style restaurant.
You were going to name it "Lily,"
in reference to Yuriko-san's name.
Thus, in order to drive Miki-san
to file for divorce of her own accord,
you continually bullied
her for three whole years.
Shunsuke and Yuri-chan are
destined to be married.
But, he had to marry
that bride there instead!
Again, I may be overstepping my bounds,
but the mother-in-law
conspired with her son,
planned on driving out his wife and
getting her son hitched
to his illicit partner.
Which means you are guilty
of a joint unlawful act.
Hence it is possible for Miki-san
to sue you, the mother-in-law,
for compensation as well.
This can't be happening...
I'm sorry...
Yoshie-san, you're in high spirits.
The place has a new owner.
Guess who it is?
Could it be?
Miki-san?
Thanks to the triple compensation
from husband, his lover, and mother-in-law,
Miki-san is now the official owner.
And today's opening day!
Why don't we all go for a drink there?
She gave me vouchers, too.
Restaurant Miki
10% off voucher
See?
Wow, look at that!
How wonderful for Miki-san!
Okay!
I'm going to drink until I puke tonight!
Please, count me out.
I told you, I don't drink.
Both of you,
how cold can you get?
Don't you want to go and
support her establishment?
Regarding that,
as a main point of
attraction on her menu,
I invented a bread that
will go well with liquor.
What's that got to do with
supporting her establishment?
Because it's a main point
of attraction on the menu.
I'm getting the chills.
I'm getting bad vibes.
What's this numb deja-vu?
Here they come.
The perfect complement to shochu,
pickled-plum bread!
Fail.
For Japanese rice wine,
salt-pickled squid bread!
Fail.
And one more added bonus,
green-pea-soup bread!
Fail.
Let's go there on our own.
Let's.
And this goes well with beer...
black-beer bread!
Fail!
Oh wait, there's one more.
How about this one?
A friendly companion
to sodas... soda bread!
The sales pitch is over.
Fail!
All of them failed...
The Divorce Chaser's Final Battle
The client is Kanae's ex-husband!
We're being sued
for compensation.
My wife, Shiori,
was caught cheating.
I am Honjo Yayoi-san's legal
representative, Karasuma Keiko.
The opponent is a formidable lawyer. Hakamada's ex-lover!
She's Hakamada-sensei's ex-lover.
Hakamada-sensei was falsely accused
of stalking ten years ago,
and was fired from the law firm.
She used Hakamada-sensei
as a stepping stone
to get promoted at the law firm.
A dramatic past is revealed
There's no lawyer who can surpass
her ability to garner information.
This drama is a work of fiction
So for this particular case,
I think you should consult
a different lawyer.