I feel it...
An evil spirit is approaching,
filled with anger.
An evil spirit?
Hakamada's assistant:
Nonomura Kanae
What is that?
What? Are you talking about Misato-san?
Editor at Tokiwa Publishing:
Tabata Misato
Kanae-san, sorry I'm late.
She's not angry at all.
Cafe waitress:
Mizutani Sara
No, I am never wrong.
As far as I know, you've always
gotten our orders wrong.
I brought someone who wants
to meet you, Kanae-san.
Oh? Who's that?
She's chief editor of our company's
restauranteur magazine, Gourmet-Goo...
My name is Yukawa Natsuko.
This episode's client:
Yukawa Natsuko
She's the one filled with anger...
What?
Are you Nonomura-sensei,
the manga illustrator?
Yes...
What can I do for you?
I want to meet the actual protagonist
of the manga, the lawyer.
What?
Hakamada Law Office
I'm chief editor of Tokiwa publishing's
Gourmet-Goo, Yukawa Natsuko.
I'm Hakamada, attorney at law.
Attorney:
Hakamada Yukio
Please come in.
I'm an avid reader of
Nonomura-sensei's manga.
I'm always impressed by
the gallant way the lawyer
sues for compensation, so this
time, I want a consultation.
Sensei is only a model
for that protagonist.
So, what can I do for you?
I want to report them.
Number one in matchmaking
"Get-Marriage"?
It's a marriage consultation firm.
I'm a registered in the 40,000 yen
per month premium member course.
40,000? Expensive.
Temp:
Shinozuka Rina
It's been ten months since I enrolled.
At the end of every week, Get-Marriage
hosts a marriage interview party.
I've attended every one,
and have had over fifty
interviews with potential partners.
Fifty times?
But, I haven't found a single
marriage prospect yet!
I see...
I have never neglected
my womanly endeavors.
I'm conscientious about
beauty and fashion,
my income is higher than men of my age,
and yet I can't find a man to marry.
That's because this marriage
consultation firm is incompetent!
Therefore...
I want to sue them for all
membership dues I've paid,
and for compensation.
That's just a minor complaint—
Do you have the
membership contract form?
Yes.
Right here.
Membership Contract Form
Based on what I see here,
we might have difficulty.
Why is that?
It says here in the clause that
there will be no refund in the event
a marriage partner is not found.
We don't have a claim to make.
Claim?
Are you saying I'm just making a claim?
Well, no...
Sensei, you're no different from them.
Huh?
I spoke to the representative of
Get-Marriage concerning my situation.
This is not the fault of our services.
Get-Marriage representative:
Ozaki Masashi
But, if you want to lay blame...
Sensei, you're also saying it's my fault
that I can't find a partner, right?
Um... Not at all.
I want to meet a man, fall
in love, and get married.
But I'm no beauty, so my
chances are slim.
I have no choice but to rely on
a marriage consultation firm.
But, those people take
advantage of our weaknesses,
and rake in membership fees.
Well, yes, um...
Sensei.
Let's take on this case.
Kurumi-san. When did you get here?
A marriage consultation firm
like this ought to be punished.
Who are you?
I am a freelance investigator,
Umemoto Kurumi.
Freelance investigator:
Umemoto Kurumi
I will accept your request to
investigate, for a discounted fee.
Thank you!
However, seeing as they
do have this clause...
This case will be difficult.
We would have to prove that the
marriage consultation firm
is purposefully preventing
you from finding a partner.
Which means what?
That their scheme is to keep
billing for membership
while setting up its members
with mismatched partners.
Or, perhaps the matched
partners are hired fakes.
I can easily find evidence.
Sensei, will you take this client on?
No, my specialty is divorce.
I have no experience in compensation
lawsuits against corporations.
Don't say that.
Sensei, your specialty in the past
was corporate law, wasn't it?
What, is that so?
Well, concerning that...
He was quite outstanding,
he fought tooth and nail
against corporations.
Wow.
Then what's the problem, Sensei?
Please.
I will pay you handsomely.
Office landlord:
Toyama Yoshie
You don't have anything else to
do anyway, do you, Sensei?
I will go all out on this one!
You don't have to display
your enthusiasm.
You really don't.
No, I want to.
Divorce Chaser
~Let's Turn Your Tears into Money~
Divorce Chaser Episode 7
Infiltrate the Suspicious Marriage Consultation Firm!
Let me know what day you're going
to the marriage consultation firm.
I'll be going with you.
Kurumi-chan is all fired up.
You're right.
I've never seen her so insistent
about a client before.
I understand how she feels, sort of.
Meaning?
Look at this.
Who's this?
That's Kurumi-chan. From four years ago.
What?
Before she became an investigator,
4 years ago
she was a regular salaried
employee of a commerce company.
Kurumi!
Umemoto Kurumi (4 years ago)
Oh, Yohei! Are you done, too?
Yeah, let's go home together.
She had a lover who worked
at the same company.
They were virtually living together,
and were even discussing marriage.
But...
You're being transferred
to the Osaka branch?
For how long?
The company says for six months.
Six months...
This is a good opportunity for me.
But, I'm making a promise.
What?
When I come back to Tokyo,
let's get married.
Yohei...
That's how their six-month
long-distance relationship started.
Hello, Yohei?
Today's your birthday, isn't it?
Sorry, I'm still at work.
Kurumi-chan doesn't act like it,
but she doesn't like being alone.
I think the stress of the long-distance
relationship took a toll on her.
We cannot answer your call right now.
Please leave a message at the beep.
Kurumi, I'm home.
Six months later
Yohei! Welcome home!
Who are you?
What do you mean? It's me, Kurumi.
The marriage is off.
Huh?
You said we'd get married
when you came back to Tokyo.
Look at your body.
How can you speak of marriage?
Have you looked in the mirror lately?
Give the ring back.
Hey, what are you doing?
Give it.
Stop it! Ow, that hurts!
It was quite the shock to her.
Someone who was once so kind to her
changed completely just because
her appearance changed.
I see.
Right.
She can't forgive people who disparage
other people's appearances.
I'm the representative of
Get-Marriage, Ozaki.
I'm Yukawa-sama's assistant, Tachibana.
Natsuko's assistant:
Tachibana Tetsu
I'm Hakamada, attorney at law.
Please, have a seat.
Well, this is quite a surprise.
You even hired an attorney.
Of course.
I intend to clearly expose
your wrongdoings.
That's unfair.
Our Get-Marriage has the number one
success rate in the matchmaking industry.
We have extremely high rates
of customer satisfaction.
We have introduced many
partners to Yukawa-sama.
Every one of them had
outstanding personal backgrounds.
But, I haven't found a partner.
Are you hiring planted fakes to keep
collecting membership dues?
Our company would never
do anything like that.
The law is very strict
about such things.
Also, Yukawa-sama has
not been satisfied,
so we have repeatedly recommended
that she cancel her membership.
Is that so?
Well, yes...
If her dues were all that we wanted,
we wouldn't have done that.
We have done our utmost to satisfy
Yukawa-sama's demands.
But, as to why she cannot
find a partner...
well, the cause must lie elsewhere.
Just a second.
You want to lay the
blame on Natsuko-san?
Kurumi-san, wait.
I never said that.
I think Yukawa-sama is
a magnificent woman.
Let me ask you, Mr. Assistant.
Are you married?
No, not yet.
How does a person who's never been
married assist in matchmaking?
Right!
These men don't
understand women at all!
Yukawa-san, please—
Your necktie and shirt
combos are always
hideously mismatched!
Yellow necktie and blue shirt?
No sensibility!
And look at you, with
those smarmy rings.
Are you flaunting the money
you gouged from your members?
Both of you, please calm down.
Kanae-san, take them outside.
Yes, let's go.
What? We didn't say anything wrong.
This way.
I find their comments offensive.
Perhaps I could counter
sue them for slander?
I apologize.
Well, I don't want matters
to get out of hand.
We will ask for Yukawa-sama
to cancel her membership,
and refund half of her membership fees.
Do we have a deal?
Please let me discuss it with her.
Sir.
Do you think we're in the clear?
Get rid of our list.
The "planted" list?
I wouldn't worry about it.
That lanky, frumpy lawyer doesn't
have the means to investigate us.
Hakamada Law Office
Half of all the dues I've paid?
I won't settle for that!
What's the point of
being your client,
if she was going to settle for that?
Considering the circumstances,
I don't think that's a bad deal.
It's not like you to say
such things, Sensei.
You're a compensation lawsuit
specialist, aren't you?
As I said, I'm a divorce specialist.
Anyway, based on the current situation,
it would be difficult to
sue them for compensation.
Is that so?
No.
Don't worry.
We'll do something about this.
Kurumi-san, please don't take
matters into your own hands.
I have an idea.
What idea?
Infiltration.
Marriage interview
party
Okay! The three minutes are up.
Now, gentlemen,
please take your profile cards
and move to the adjacent seat.
As quickly as possible, please.
How did I get roped into this?
Speed dating, round two.
Let's go!
I'm Umemoto Kurumi.
I work as a researcher.
I see.
Lately, I've been addicted
to a foreign drama.
Do you know it?
"Iron Spy Woman: Marilyn."
There is no target I can't blow away.
Your heart is no exception.
I don't watch dramas.
Is that so?
I've spotted one.
This guy is a planted fake.
Name: Kawajiri Daisuke
Age: 33
Height: 171
Highest education: Keimei Central University
Profession: Private Medical Practice
Keimei graduate, private
medical practitioner.
Annual income of 200,000.
His profile would be
attractive to women,
but he doesn't seem
interested in marriage.
Okay! Our three minutes are up.
Gentlemen, please move to adjacent seats.
Name: Nonomura Kanae
Age: 32
Height: 162
Highest education: College graduate
Profession: Manga illustrator
Wow, you're a manga illustrator?
I admire creative people.
Oh, thank you very much.
I've been addicted to this drama lately.
Its original manga is very interesting.
He said he didn't watch dramas!
I think manga authors are sublime.
By the way, she's got
one strike already.
What? Wait...
Huh?
Oh, I admire people
who have life experience.
I've been speed dating
like this for years...
but of all the women
I've interviewed with,
you're the most wonderful.
Are you for real?!
Did you hear that?
That must be a plant.
I-I'm sorry.
Hakamada-sensei is participating, too?
I had to twist his arm, but...
You mumble, you don't
make eye contact,
and all you talk about is bread!
Do you really want to marry someone?
Yes, yes.
Okay. Gentleman number 6!
Iizuka-san!
Yes.
Lady number 2.
Nojima-san.
Yes.
Congratulations.
What a happy occasion.
How do you feel?
They've paired five couples already.
They say they're number one
in the matchmaking industry.
Perhaps it's not a scam.
It's suspicious.
For example, I, an alluring woman,
have been left out.
They give the newcomers
the cold shoulder,
then they try to prolong
our membership.
Now, on to the next.
Gentleman number 9, Kawajiri-san.
Yes.
Lady number 8, Nonomura-san.
Oh... yes.
Congratulations.
We have yet another couple.
Nonomura-san, how do you feel?
I never thought I'd be picked.
I'm shocked.
What annoying modesty.
We have one more couple left.
Let me announce them!
First, lady number 1.
Kuramochi-san.
Yes.
Gentleman number 10.
Hakamada-san.
Congratulations!
Isn't that nice?
Sensei, too? But why?
Hakamada-san. How do you feel?
I want our relationship to be warm,
like freshly baked bread.
What an annoying analogy.
Don't get carried away
because you got paired.
This is just an investigation.
Of course, I am aware of that.
Kurumi-san, you're the one getting
carried away. You're seriously upset.
I'm not upset at all.
Were you satisfied with the
marriage interview party?
Ozaki-san.
Are you trying to infiltrate us?
I can't say I approve.
I will pretend this never happened,
as long as you never do this again.
You're making a nuisance
of yourselves to our members.
I understand.
I apologize.
Hakamada
Law Office
How did it go?
Did you get paired?
Well...
That's not important.
Sensei, don't get carried away
because you got paired up, too.
I'm not getting carried away.
Sensei was paired?
That's too weird.
I think we shouldn't investigate
Get-Marriage directly for now.
President Ozaki warned us, as well.
They're definitely suspicious, though.
Indeed.
They are on the lookout for us,
so there's a high probability
they've got something to hide.
That's where my investigation comes in.
This case pertains to my client.
Please follow my instructions.
Oh.
Who is it?
The lady I was coupled with.
You even exchanged phone numbers?
Hello.
It was nice meeting you today.
Tonight?
No.
I'm not busy.
They're going on a date
right off the bat.
You see? He got carried away.
Ah.
Well, Kanae-san.
Could that be your partner?
Oh, yes.
But, I'm going to properly explain
my situation, and turn him down.
Wait a second!
What?
Your partner...
Didn't he say he was
a long-time member?
I was only participating in the
speed-dating party for research.
I'm very sorry.
I see.
But you are single,
aren't you, Kanae-san?
Well, yes...
Even if it was just research,
we've still managed
to meet each other.
Please date me,
with an eye toward marriage!
I'm sorry.
I don't care if you've got one strike.
I will embrace your past,
and love you and the whole package—
I'm sorry.
Please give up on her.
Huh?
I'm here today because I want you
to tell me about Get-Marriage.
What do you want to know?
Have you ever been
dissatisfied by them?
They're very considerate.
I'm registered with other
matchmaking establishments,
but in comparison to the others,
they're warm and accommodating.
Have you ever suspected
they might have planted fakes?
I don't believe there's
anything like that.
I've always gotten legitimate
responses from matches.
Oh, but come to think of it,
there was this one time
I got turned down.
By whom?
She's the chief editor
of a gourmet magazine.
This was Yukawa Natsuko-san?
That might've been her name—
And who was the assistant at that time?
His name was Tachibana-san.
Hakamada Law Office
You were being followed?
Did you get a look at him?
I could only see his back,
so I can't be sure who he was...
But I think that it was
Tachibana-san of Get-Marriage.
Tachibana-san?
Actually, this isn't the first
time something like this happened.
Can you explain?
I've been followed several
times before, on my way home.
There was a man asking
about me at a local bar I frequent.
You think Tachibana-san
has been doing these things?
It's very possible.
This was the first time I actually
saw him in person, though.
I wonder what's they're scheming.
We have testimony from a member
that Tachibana-san has been obstructing
Natsuko-san from finding a partner.
Tachibana-san...
Excuse me for a moment.
Hello.
I enjoyed the visit.
That must be his partner.
He's totally immersed
in "get married" mode.
Ah, that's it! Tachibana
has been following
and gathering personal
information about me,
so he can find a completely
mismatched man for me!
That is entirely conceivable.
But, Get-Marriage has
over a thousand members.
Would they go to such lengths
to scam a single member?
Maybe Tachibana-san has a personal
grudge against Natsuko-san.
Against me?
Can you think of some
reason why he would?
No...
Not particularly.
A reason why someone would have a
grudge against chief editor Yukawa?
Yes.
Misato-san, you're in the same office.
I thought you might know something.
Well... I can think of many reasons.
You know her personality.
She makes lots of enemies.
I see.
Hello?
It's Kurumi. Have you found anything out?
I've been speaking with
my editor about her.
I see.
I investigated Tachibana's history.
That guy was proprietor of a ramen shop
before he landed the present job.
His shop went bust in less than a year,
and he's been knee-deep in debt.
He's got debts from a ramen shop?
A ramen shop?
Does that ring a bell?
Maybe his shop was featured in an
article in Yukawa's magazine.
There was a time they had an article
with scathing reviews of ramen shops.
Maybe his shop got reviewed,
and that's where his grudge came from.
That's it!
I knew he had a personal grudge.
I'm going to go see Tachibana,
and nail him to the wall.
Wait, before you do that, we should
get Hakamada-sensei's instructions...
We were warned by Get-Marriage, too...
This iron woman isn't
intimidated by warnings.
I feel it.
What?
I feel a tremendous grudge the
man called Tachibana has against
the female chief editor.
Yes, but we know that already.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Do you remember this?
It's got an article about
your ex-ramen shop.
Ramen,
Yeah Right!
"Ramen Tachibana"
Evaluation:
Materials
Noodles
Soup
It's quite a harsh review.
Several months after the publication,
your establishment went under,
and you were left with an enormous debt.
You've had a grudge ever
since, haven't you?
Against Natsuki-san,
the author of the article.
That's not true!
My restaurant's business was
declining way before the article.
The article had nothing to do with it.
My restaurant was destined to close.
You could say I'm actually thankful
to Yukawa-sama about that,
because that article woke
me up to the hard facts.
Then why are you obstructing
Natsuko-san's marriage interviews?
I heard you spread bad rumors
about her to prospective partners.
I'm not allowed to discuss
proprietary information.
Wait, you!
Please, leave me alone!
Representative Ozaki is
stringent about rules.
If he found out I relayed
proprietary information,
or that I got involved with a member,
I'd be quickly fired, and
forced to pay 15 million yen.
We know you've been following
Natsuko-san around!
What would you do if
that fact got publicized?
I think that's enough of that.
I warned you to stop
sniffing around us.
Who are you calling?
The police.
Your actions are no
different from blackmail.
I told you not to do reckless
investigations, did I not?!
I got a serious warning
from the police.
One more wrong move,
and you could have been arrested.
But, we need to find a way to win—
Win or lose, that's my responsibility.
Because of what happened,
Get-Marriage will
tighten their security.
Now it will be harder than
ever to gather evidence.
You have worsened circumstances
considerably for our client.
Please cease your
involvement with this case.
Understood.
Um... here.
I recorded my conversation
with Tachibana.
I was hoping it might be of some use.
Excuse me.
Let's go out for drinks.
It's happy time.
Marilyn.
Huh?
Was there a fight?
Yes. Somewhat.
I see.
Kurumi-chan overdid it.
I've never seen
Hakamada-sensei get so angry.
She must've grown impatient with
Hakamada-sensei's procedures.
What do you mean?
There's more to the story
of Kurumi-chan's dissolved engagement.
4 years ago
Umemoto-san, time to
pay this month's rent.
Ms. Landlord...
Are you still sniveling about that?
I'll introduce you to
someone really nice.
Huh?
I understand the situation.
Please leave the rest to me.
Oh. The rice is ready.
Would you like to eat before you go?
It's freshly mixed rice.
Mixed rice?
At that time, Hakamada-sensei
was into mixed rice, and not bread.
Is that so?
And what Hakamada-sensei
did for her after that...
was splendid.
In other words, you're saying
Umemoto-san is entirely at fault
for the engagement dissolving, correct?
Of course.
How could I marry an
unsightly thing like that?
I wonder if that's true.
Here's evidence you were cheating
on her during your stint in Osaka.
I know I'm overstepping
my bounds, but...
before you disparage
people's appearances,
you ought to reflect
on your own actions.
We're suing for one million yen,
for breach of engagement.
You will pay, won't you?
Umemoto-san, you were
lucky this time around.
Huh?
Because you didn't wind
up marrying a cheater,
who shallowly judges people
by their appearances.
Sensei.
What can I do for you?
Will you please let Kurumi-san
continue her investigation?
I can't have her getting us
into any more trouble.
I heard from Yoshie-san.
Kurumi-san was once your
client, wasn't she?
She sure likes to gossip.
Kurumi-san put her
hopes in you, Sensei.
She wanted you to save a client,
who suffered like she once did.
Maybe it's just me,
but you're not yourself this
time around, Hakamada-sensei.
Maybe you got carried away
because you've been paired now,
but you should consider
your client's feelings,
consider her happiness.
Isn't that how you always work, Sensei?
Kurumi-san forced you to
take on this client...
because she believed in you.
In that case, I wish
she had kept believing in me,
just a little longer.
Huh?
I haven't gotten carried away
in the least.
The reason why I was
seeing my partner...
I see, so you wanted to investigate.
I'm truly sorry.
No, I'm glad you were honest with me.
I've gotten into relationships with
partners who stopped calling me,
or reject me outright without
giving any reason whatsoever...
Is that so?
A friend of mine recommended
the company to me.
I've been a member for two years now.
But, it ends the same
way every time.
Would you mind sharing details with me?
She gave me references to other members,
and I spoke with several of them.
Strangely enough,
people's opinions of
Get-Marriage got split in two.
Between those who are completely satisfied,
and those who aren't.
What's that mean?
I think Get-Marriage sorts its members.
They're sorted into people
who will aggressively
get paired, in order to
raise their success rate...
and into people who are scammed,
who only get set up with fakes.
If you know that, you can
sue them for compensation.
The only thing I'm missing
is solid evidence.
However,
thanks to this, I now
have a course of action.
Huh?
Please call Kurumi-san for me.
I need her to do further investigation.
Understood.
Eternal Partners
Have you agreed to our
terms from the other day?
No.
We will be suing for a complete refund
of all membership fees paid,
as well as compensation.
What?
Why have you decided that?
Because you have purposefully obstructed
Natsuko-san from finding a marriage partner.
And what advantage would we have
for doing something like that?
Well.
You've been selecting targets.
You pick out people who
seem prone to rejection...
and to keep raking membership
fees from those people,
you obstruct them
from finding a mate.
That's nonsense.
You have no evidence.
True, I don't have evidence.
However, there is one thing we know.
Tachibana-san.
Yes.
You were obstructing Natsuko-san
for a personal reason, weren't you?
This again?
I don't have a grudge
against Yukawa-sama because
of that ramen shop article.
No.
The personal reason isn't a grudge.
What?
He is fond of Natsuko-san.
Fond?
The first time I noticed,
was when she commented
on your tie and shirt.
Your necktie and shirt
combos are always
hideously mismatched!
Yellow necktie and blue shirt?
No sensibility!
A few days after Natsuko-san
criticized your color combinations,
you took her words faithfully to heart.
You changed the color of your tie.
Because you are fond of Natsuko-san,
you wanted Natsuko-san for yourself...
so you were obstructing her prospects.
You can't infer all that
from the color of my tie.
That's no evidence of anything.
There's more evidence.
Hey, you, enough is enough.
You had fair warning.
I wasn't investigating you two.
I found this site.
The author is anonymous,
Even if I only can talk with her
(Wednesday)
She came to our matchmaking firm again today.
She makes me happy, even speaking with her face to face. Even at my age, she makes my heart pound.
One-sided Confessions of a Matchmaking Firm
but it's blog by an employee
of a matchmaking firm,
The joy of meeting with her
confessing his secret love for a member.
A lovely bar
It talks about how he follows her home,
and how he would get information
about her from people in her social circles.
He's quite passionate about
her, as you can see.
A lovely bar
She's like an angel
Oh yes, and have a look at this.
There's even a picture
of his secret love.
It would be easy to find the blogger.
This is ample evidence, wouldn't
you say, Hakamada-sensei?
Yes.
I expect no less from you,
Investigator Umemoto.
Tachibana-san.
Isn't it time to tell the truth?
I've had enough of you, Tachibana!
Who was it that got
you out of your debt?
Have you forgotten the rules?
Employees that leak proprietary
information will be penalized.
Are you trying to get
yourself in debt again?
Is that the rule that would
force him to pay 15 million yen?
He has exposed the illegal
activities of his company,
and you would penalize him for that?
Public Well-Being Informant Protection Law
The law that protects workers who report unethical insider conduct
Based on the Public Well-Being
Informant Protection Law...
you can't do that.
Shortly after I joined the company,
representative Ozaki gave me a list.
The "planted" list...
What this?
It's a list of members who I believe
are unlikely to find a partner.
What?
Set them up with fake "plants,"
and let them believe
they're getting somewhere.
People like that
desperately cling to us...
and they'll keep paying
membership fees for all eternity.
How awful.
Yukawa-sama's name was
on that list, as well.
Yukawa Natsuko
I thought I'd happened
upon an opportunity.
Because as long as I was setting
her up with nothing but fakes,
I wouldn't have to worry about
Yukawa-sama ever getting married.
It's true that I have
been obstructing her.
I thought maybe some day
she would go out with me.
You shouldn't have been so devious.
Why didn't you just come out and
profess your love to Natsuko-san?
Company rules prohibit relationships with members.
I was afraid of being penalized.
That's why...
that why after Yukawa-sama resigned,
I was going to properly ask her out.
So that's how it is.
It's clear you've been scamming
your members using fakes.
The total membership
fees and compensation...
You will pay, won't you?
And one more thing.
Tachibana-san.
Please inform all members on that list.
Like Natsuko-san,
they have fallen victim to a scam.
If you do that, our company will be ruined!
And what's wrong with that?
After all, you shallowly judge
people based on appearances...
You're not qualified to
oversee human encounters.
Umemoto-san, you were
lucky this time around.
Because you didn't wind
up marrying a cheater,
who shallowly judges people
by their appearances.
You look like an
insignificant lawyer...
but I guess you can't judge
people on appearances.
Hakamada Law Office
Major corporation Get-Marriage crushed
Illicit activities toward its members uncovered
Wow, the matchmaking firm
went out of business.
That's our Hakamada-sensei.
He rescued not one, but many people.
I am truly sorry about how
I behaved this time around.
If you are,
then please do not do reckless
investigations any more.
I understand.
Sensei, we have a guest.
Yes.
Natsuko-san.
Thank you for everything
you have done for me.
You too, dear.
Everyone. I have caused
you much trouble.
Tachibana-san.
Why are you here, too?
Well, we are getting married.
What?
That day, when Tachibana-san
confessed his feelings,
I couldn't get that out of my mind.
So I got brave, and called him.
I brought hardship to many people.
For that, I must make amends
for the rest of my life.
But, Natsuko-san forgave me.
I will make her happy, I promise!
I'm glad for you.
The compensation we received
will help us make a new start.
We cannot thank Sensei enough.
If you're going to show gratitude...
it should be toward her.
Huh?
We couldn't have sued for compensation
without her investigation.
Speaking of which, here is the bill
for the case's investigation.
Can you please wait a little for that?
You said you couldn't have sued for
compensation if it weren't
for my investigation, right?
That and this are unrelated...
Wait! Grab him!
Please, don't do this!
I will pay it.
I promise I'll pay it!
You're taking the children
away from me, too?
Next episode
He's a pathetic husband
who can't find another job.
Childcare worker husband VS career-woman wife
So I threatened
him with a knife.
The wife admits
to illicit activity.
A mess of a custody battle:
What will happen to the children's future?!
In which case we can
sue for compensation.
You're not a
superhero of justice!
You're a villain that's
splitting Mama and Papa apart!
This drama is a work of fiction