Let's get started with our first request.
Subtitles by: /u/CatZombies
Airdate: 2018-01-26
Our first request is from Houtani Mizuki-san, a 25 years old office worker in Suginami Ward, Tokyo.
Good evening to everyone at the Detective Bureau.
Good evening!
I love pork belly stew.
I love, love that soft pork fat flavor that builds up. It's irresistible.
Ok, ok.
That's what my request is about this time detectives.
Okay.
I want to eat some stew I froze in my fridge 5 years ago.
The appearance has turned pure white, so I don't know if it's edible.
But no matter what, I want to eat it.
Actually, in that stew that my deceased mother made, there is her flavor.
Please help me make delicious, 5-year-frozen stew. Thank you very much. That's it.
I was laughing at it a bit in the beginning,
Yeah, yeah.
but I feel like I need my handkerchief or something.
Well, you may need it.
Well still, this frozen stew is 5 years old.
5 years ago, huh?
Yes.
Usually you'd throw it away I think but,
No matter what, she wants to eat it.
She seems to be obsessed with the idea.
What was the result? Were we able to eat that 5 year old stew? Please take a look.
You have stew frozen from 5 years ago?
That's right.
It's impossible, isn't it?
No! That's...
From 5 years ago?
Yeah.
I wonder if it'll give me stomach troubles. I want to eat it,
but as you know, it's been 5 years.
5 years.
It's 5 years old.
Without Knight Scoop, you're not sure you'd be able to eat it on your own.
I don't know.
You don't know, right?
Well it's scary, so I thought I'd make someone do it with me...
No, no, no.
First of all, we can see it?
Yeah.
That 5 year old stew.
Yes.
There, huh?
Ah, tupperware?
Tupperware.
It's in tupperware.
No way, it's ice. Inside the tupperware...
It's really pretty.
It looks like crystals.
What is this ice? This is really pretty isn't it? Isn't it intricate?
In here simply put, is what you believed in.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ah, I see.
It's not silky, right? It's all dried out.
Yeah.
In your request letter, your mother made...
Your mother's altar is here.
It's how she was 5 years ago.
When I was 20, she suddenly had a brain hemorrhage.
Then you didn't throw it away.
Yeah.
That day she passed, she made stew for dinner.
Eh?
Yeah.
The mother's final cooking.
So it's like that?
So, that's why you haven't eaten it.
It's sad.
Her last meal?
Yeah.
That morning before I went to school,
That day, my mom had work, um, sorry.
In the morning, she asked "What do you want to eat for dinner today?"
I really liked stew and Mom liked stew so,
I said stew was good.
Then, I said "I'm off". But when I came home,
she had a kind of unsteady appearance so I immediately called an ambulance.
I stayed at the hospital until the next morning. I didn't feel like eating or anything.
I have an older sister but she's married and lives in Kumamoto Prefecture.
And my father was on a business trip in America. So I was suddenly all on my own.
You were alone?
Yeah.
In the morning, I came back home, but
Just seeing the pot...
It's a little sad.
The next day, my father came back.
He came back from America.
Yeah. So I put it in the tupperware.
Then I put it in the freezer. For some time, stew too...
I wasn't able to eat stew for some time. It was sad.
I see.
The reason you felt like trying to eat it now is to little by little bring peace of mind to yourself.
That's right.
I can probably eat a little bit, I think I can do that.
It'd be nice if you could eat it.
Yeah. I want to eat it.
Right?
You want to be able to eat it, but
on the other hand, there's the possibility that eating it is dangerous for you, Mizuki-chan.
It could be.
Right?
Mizuki-chan, if you got sick. Your mom wouldn't...
Right? We can't make it. She'd be angry.
Honestly, we need to know if it's edible, if it's okay to eat,
if it's unsafe to eat.
So, we have no choice but to investigate.
Yes.
To start.
I'm really sorry but I don't have any days off work.
Could you go in my place?
That's no good.
That's no good. It's your mom's stew. That's no good.
When are you done?
7 p.m.
Until then, shall I investigate? Since I'm free today.
I only have this, so I'm free.
Really?
Now, since we're researching various things about food, we've come to Tokyo University of Agriculture.
Excuse me, Professor Uchino?
Yes.
Excuse me, we're from Knight Scoop. Nice to meet you.
Could you take a look at this for a moment?
Ah, okay.
What's this?
This is it, sensei.
Okay.
This pork stew.
For 5 years, this was frozen in the family fridge.
Okay.
Is that so? That's awfully long.
Yes.
About that, can you eat it?
I would think that after 5 years it'd be pretty difficult.
Another thing I'd be curious about,
how was it kept since it was prepared?
Then, the problem is food poisoning.
Whether or not any bacteria got into it before freezing is one concern.
First is the microscope. To see if there are any microbes inside.
If there is bacteria, it's possible that food poisoning bacteria has gotten in as well.
There's only a little bit, but it is there.
Eh?
There is some bacteria and it's possible it's the food poisoning type.
Well, there's a bit more.
If we run an experiment, we can determine whether it's food poisoning bacteria or not.
Sorry for the sudden imposition.
Not at all.
8 PM
Oh, Mizuki-chan.
Takeyama-san!
Sorry. Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm done with work.
You're done?
I'm done.
You go to work like this?
I go to work like this.
Ah, nice to meet you Dad. I'm Tantei Knight Scoop's Takeyama.
Ah, welcome.
Good evening.
Mizuki, does he know the request?
He knows.
I've heard.
That's why he's here.
How many times have I said "Is it okay if I throw this away?"
To your daughter?
Yes, she was strongly against it.
I went to Tokyo University of Agriculture.
I've done some research into whether we can eat it.
Okay.
Now I'll make a phone call and we'll hear the sensei's answer.
Can we do it?
Ah, I'm nervous.
Hello.
First of all, sensei, in short, I want to ask, what's the result?
If you ask, I think
Yes?
on whether or not you can eat it, you can more or less eat it.
We can pretty much eat it?
We can eat it?
Yes.
However, the microbe risk isn't zero.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, properly...
Ok.
Heat it up over 100 °C, ok?
Furthermore, if you eat a small amount,
Ok.
the risk can be considerably reduced I think.
But it may upset your stomach a bit.
Ok, ok, ok.
Alright.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Yes, yes.
Let's eat it.
It's good?
Even if it may hurt you a little.
It's alright.
What about you?
Let's eat it.
Is it okay?
It's decided.
But we don't know how it will turn out.
The most important thing is that it tastes good right?
Yes.
We've called just the person for it.
Eh?
Please come in.
Hayashi-sensei.
Yes.
Good evening.
Good evening, sensei.
Stop with the "good evenings".
Always calling me.
Yes.
Without warning.
Su-suddenly.
Yes.
Making me to come to Tokyo without telling me anything.
Yes, well...
Sensei's abilities are absolutely necessary.
It's not bugs is it?
It's not bugs. Not bugs.
Sensei, this is frozen stew.
Oh wow.
This was frozen 5 years ago.
We want to eat this.
Are you an idiot?
If it's a small amount, it's okay to eat.
That's... eh?
They want to be able to eat this. In here...
I can make it from scratch of course. That 5 year old stew is...
No, that's no good. Making it from scratch is no good.
Why?
This stew in particular, about 5 years ago...
Explaining the situation.
This is the last meal their mom made.
Eh?
How about it?
If I hear that, I've got to. I've got no choice.
Right?
In addition, if at all possible, I want to it as it is.
Is that so?
That's right. Your mom's flavor.
It's in quite a state.
The meat is awfully dried out.
To restore it from being this dried out,
the broth needs to be added back.
But I understand, that's how it is.
This smell is a little...
Freezer smell?
Yeah, yeah.
Are you not confident?
No, that's not it.
It's impossible for even Hayashi-sensei, huh?
No, it's not.
If you say impossible...
I can do it.
I'll do it. I will.
Starting cooking.
You're warming in the water to release it from the tupperware, right?
That's right.
Ah, it's come out. It's come out.
Amazing.
Wow, it came out.
This is all in once piece because of how it came loose.
Ah, I see. I see.
We'll not cook it too much or it'll become really dried out.
Somehow we're microwaving it to eat it.
I didn't get the feeling we'd be microwaving it.
You didn't think we'd be microwaving it to eat it.
The microwave will heat it up this way but
Yes.
there's still the previous problem. It will become extra dry from microwaving it.
It'll still be good even if you microwave it?
Yeah.
The broth. The broth's come out.
Seriously? There's broth.
There's broth, right?
The broth's come out.
You're separating the meat and the broth?
I'll the use broth after I heat it up a bit.
But there's broth that's come out.
That's right.
I would add some flavor but I can't do that.
We're going to heat it up to over 100 degrees.
I'll cook it in this pressure cooker.
If you move them too much, they'll fall apart.
Ok.
Since they're being cooked again.
You're placing them one by one so the meat doesn't lose its shape as it's heated.
Yes.
If you do it like this, it's hard for them to fall apart.
What do you think it'd be like if sensei weren't here?
It'd be really bad.
Sensei is amazing, huh?
We're not done yet.
Look here. There's a bit of a bad smell from the meat.
Uh huh, it's the meat.
Smells like meat.
I think I can get rid of that bad smell a bit.
Ok, ok.
The taste will be the same, we won't change that.
Spring onions and...
And ginger peels. We use the peels so there's no spiciness. Only the flavor.
To get rid of the smell.
You're not changing the mother's flavor, right?
That's right.
This won't change the flavor.
We can't leave it in this state.
If we add the broth in, we can cook them together.
That's the broth you're adding back.
Yes, yes.
I'm putting it in.
Okay.
I'm looking forward to it. I want to eat it soon.
Has the 5 year old stew been resurrected?
Ouch, ouch.
Sensei, did you do it?
Hmm, I wonder.
Amazing!
I'm shaking.
Amazing, huh?
There's no bad smell.
It has the perfect smell.
The perfect smell?
It smells perfect.
That's how your mom used to make it?
It smells just like it.
Really.
That feeling?
It was this smell?
Yeah, this smell.
While it was dried out, I tried to bring it back as much as possible.
Right?
Amazing.
Your mom is watching now, right? I feel like she's been brought back.
Shall we eat? As we're reminded of your mother.
Somehow my hands are trembling.
Itadakimasu.
Please.
Delicious.
Delicious?
It tastes like your mother's cooking?
Yeah.
Just like it.
Yeah?
It doesn't feel like it's been left for 5 years at all. Really.
Sensei, are you glad?
I'm glad. I'm glad.
It's the same, right?
Truly.
Yeah.
Again, it's really delicious after so long. Thank you.
It's delicious?
Yeah, delicious.
I feel like, from tomorrow on, I'll do my best.
You feel you can?
I feel I can.
Even though Dad said to throw it away.
That too.
Sorry about that.
Well done. Hayashi-sensei did an incredible job for us.
That's right.
Yeah, the father and Mizuki-chan had it as the mother's cooking.
Yes.
The thing is, they were able to eat the stew after being frozen for so long.
It's done there, right?
Yes, yes.
But Mizuki-chan in the beginning,
when she saw the ice crystals, right?
She said "This is really beautiful. I want to keep this."
She put it back in the freezer.
So it didn't disappear.