Airdate: 25 November 2016.
Edit and re-release by: /u/CatZombies
Original subtitles by: /u/nirvashprototype
Let's hear our first request.
Okay, the first person is Saneyoshi Sakuya, a 9 year old third grade elementary school student from Tokyo.
Ok.
"Dear Detectives, good evening. I've had a pet dog for 2 years at my house. Her name is Kinako.
Good evening.
Ok.
How cute.
She has a light brown color that reminds me of sweet kinako (roasted soybean flour), so I gave her that cute name.
Nice, isn't it?
There's a neighborhood Obaa-chan that when she goes out,
she walks in front of our house and gives Kinako a treat. She cares so much about her.
But there is one problem, that Obaa-chan keeps calling her Tarou-chan.
Even though she's Kinako?
What, what, what?
My mother told her, "Her name isn't Tarou-chan, she's Kinako"
but next day, she continued saying "Tarou-chan, Tarou-chan" again.
Since I gave her that unique name, I wish that Obaa-chan would learn and use the name Kinako.
I get a little sad every time she gets it wrong,
so I want help to make her remember it in a gentle manner." That's the request.
That's kind of a cute request.
Yes, it's very cute. This a request from 9 year old Sakuya. She's a very gentle girl, huh?
Yes.
Let's see if we succeeded in making Obaa-chan remember the dog's name with that same gentleness.
Please.
Here we go.
Please
Ah. She's barking.
Here she is. Kina-chan.
She's very watchful.
It's alright.
Kinako-chan?
That's probably because she's hearing a new type of human voice. (Joking about his own lisp.)
Hello.
Ah, hello there!
Hello!
Sakuya?
Y-yes...
Nice to meet you.
I'm pretty sure you are a good person.
Why am I feeling like you are so gentle?
Thanks for the request.
Ok.
Can we talk a little?
Sure.
The Obaa-chan in our neighborhood keeps calling Kinako, Tarou-chan.
Since she's not a boy, I want her to call her Kinako.
That Obaa-chan comes here everyday?
She comes here almost everyday.
So she gets it wrong almost daily?
That's right.
I took a video.
You recorded a video?
Yes.
That's great.
That camera looks gentle too.
Can I see the video of the "Tarou Obaa-chan"?
Good morning!
Tarou-chan! Tarou-chan!
She appears suddenly and is greeting "Tarou-chan".
Good, good, good.
Here she comes.
Tarou-chan!
Kinako is so excited.
Oh. She's calling her Tarou-chan.
That's how it is.
She's calling her Tarou-chan.
You're so lively. Liveliness is very important!
Kinako is so excited for that food.
Here you go!
What if grandma is actually a grandpa?
What if we're the ones who are actually wrong?
That's not it, right?
Oh you already eat it? You're so fast. Here you go!
She's treating her like a son.
There's no more. No more.
"Ah, I want it!". You can't say that. I don't have any more.
Maybe she had a dog in the past.
Oh, and the dog's name...
Maybe it was Tarou.
I see. That could be it.
That's a possibility.
Maybe she sees her old, beloved "Tarou" in Kinako...
See you later!
She's so cute.
She's leaving like she doesn't want to.
Makes me want to call her Kinako-chan instead.
So, she really believes the dog's name is Tarou.
I'm always wondering if I should correct her or not.
I see.
I understand your situation now. Correcting her feels difficult.
She's got a good spirit, right?
Her aura, yeah?
That's why I've been wondering how I could correct her without being rude.
Oh Director, that's what I call "tender village problems".
Let's try the "Kinako challenge".
Kinako challenge?
The nonchalant "Kinako challenge"
We've written Kinako.
Strategy: Casually put it in her line of sight.
Usually there's nothing in that place right?
Since it's raining, I wonder if she'll come.
Yeah, will she come?
She hasn't come today?
It's 10:30.
She hasn't come yet.
So she didn't "early morning Tarou" yet?
10:40 a.m.
Hey! Tarou-chan!
She's come.
Why are you not barking? Because it rained?
Rain!
Obaa-chan is teaching Kinako about rain.
It rained!
It's rained.
What's wrong? Why are you not barking?
She didn't notice the paper.
Oh wow, she's at the perfect angle right now!
She's in the "Kinako angle"!
Is it tasty?
Please see it.
Obaa-chan is watching Kinako instead of "Kinako".
I don't have any more.
Obaa-chan, where are you going?
Obaa-chan? That's a fail.
Just a little more.
Wait, huh?
Obaa-chan?
Tarou-chan! Bye bye!
She didn't see it.
Bye bye. I'm leaving.
Cute.
I'm off!
So cute.
Kinako Challenge: Failed
Damn...
I have a suggestion, how about name her Tarou?
No way.
But she's a female.
How many times a day she comes here?
Usually twice.
2 times?
That's right.
First in the morning and in the afternoon on the way back home a second time.
A second time?
The "Kinako Challenge" has 1 more chance.
So this is our last chance.
Sakuya, do you have any ideas?
How about put a mic in her collar and someone talk through that? To make it as if Kinako is speaking.
Make Kinako talk?
Huh? Put a mic in her collar and...
Make her say "I'm not Tarou, I'm Kinako".
Since Obaa-chan likes Kinako, I think she will remember her name that way.
Ohhh...
I get it.
Because Obaa-chan always talks to Kinako, right?
She does.
If Tarou speaks in my voice, Obaa-chan will think "This dog is cursed."
Kinako looks like she's feeling our nervousness. Like "something is going to change today".
3:50 p.m.
Here she comes!
Oh, what's happened? Why you are in that location?
"What's happened?"
What's happened?
Obaa-chan.
Huh?
Hello.
What's happened?
Just basking in the sun.
Obaa-chan, come here.
Huh?
Obaa-chan can you hear me?
Obaa-chan, listen to me.
Obaa-chan.
Tarou-chan.
Me?
I'm not Tarou, actually.
What's happened? Huh? What is it?
What is it?
Can you listen to me please?
I'm a girl called Kinako.
Really? What's that?
I'm not Tarou.
Can you call me Kinako from now on?
Huh, what?
Chisako?
Is that it?
Kinako!
Kinako-chan!
Yes, Kinako!
Ok, you're Kinako. You weren't Tarou. Now I know.
Kinako-chan!
Thanks! Call me by that name ok?
Yes, I will call you Kinako from now on.
Obaa-chan forgets things very fast you know.
So please do your best to not forget, ok?
I got it, I got it.
I'll write it in my notebook.
Kinako-chan, right? Got it, got it. Kinako-chan.
Yep, it's Kinako. Kinako.
You're called Kinako. I see. I see, I've got it. Got it.
See you later ok? Bye bye.
Bye bye.
See you tomorrow.
See you!
See you later.
Alright, alright.
I hear talking from somewhere but where is it coming from?
Obaa-chan.
Hello.
What, what, what? What is it?
What is it?
Nice to meet you.
Yes, yes.
The dog is always happy to receive treats from you.
Yes.
Really? I'm doing this without permission so maybe I shouldn't be.
They're happy that you always say "Tarou, Tarou" and dote on him, but
since her name is actually Kinako. So that...
Who did I hear it was Tarou from?
Yeah, who told you it was that?
Have you had a dog before?
Yes, I had an Akita dog.
What was his name?
What was it?
Was it Tarou?
It wasn't Tarou.
It wasn't even Tarou!
It wasn't Tarou I think.
"You think". That's not clear either.
Obaa-chan, you've got to learn the dog's name. Have you memorized it?
Yes, I've got it.
What's her name?
It wasn't something like Sakura-chan...
You forget so quickly, Obaa-chan.
The next day.
Good morning! Kinako-chan! Kinako-chan!
Kinako-chan! Good morning! Good morning!
Good morning!
Kinako challenge: Successful!
Kinako-chan, here you go.
So cute.
Adorable.
I know.
That Obaa-chan is so cute.
Obaa-chan is really a good person, as you could see, that's why Sakuya was so resistant to correct her.
In the end, Obaa-chan's daughter came to see her and they came back together.
When she was asked to write the dog's name, she still wrote Chisako.
We were able to correct her though.
Cute.
Thanks for the assignment.
Wonderful.