Let's get to today's first request.
Yes, our first request comes from the 44 y/o Shintani Kazutaka, a manager of a sports shop, who lives in Osaka.
"Good evening, Detectives."
"For 10 years, there's been an old man that's constantly on my mind."
"From my eldest son to my youngest child, it's the old man that has kept passing me by every morning as I drop my child off at the nursery."
"He sprints down the street every morning, wearing a suit & leather shoes, and carrying a bag."
"I've never seen him stop or walk at a normal pace."
"If it only happened once in a while, one might think 'Perhaps he's running because he's late?', but every morning for the past 10 years, he's been running fast enough to gasp for air!"
"Why does he run at full speed every morning?"
"I've meant to ask him before, but he's running so frantically, I can't bring myself to stop him."
"Now my child will finish kindergarten soon, so I have little time left where I get to see him."
"Could you please resolve this mystery I've been carrying for 10 years?"
This request has really got me excited.
It's been happening every morning ... for 10 years!
And it's a situation where he can't just approach him.
He doesn't know how it would turn out if he did.
So what is this old man's goal, running continuously for 10 years?
Well, we had a chat with him, take a look!
Good morning! - Good morning!
I'm with Tantei Knight Scoop ...
I'm sorry. - Good morning, it's so early!
I'm Ishida. - Good morning!
Is everyone up already? - The children are still sleeping.
Good morning! Excuse me.
Good morning. - Have you been up all night?
It's always this early, honestly. - No way!
Preparing bento! - Ah, please, stop it!
And what's over here, apples, ah! You're preparing fruits.
How old do you think he is? - Somewhere ... in his late 50s?
And he gets there at 8 ... - Yes, around 8:22.
Everyday? - Yes, everyday.
Seriously? - Yes, I'm serious.
I recorded him. Should we take a look?
From inside your car? - Yes.
Ah, on such a clear and straight street?
Here you'd easily spot someone running towards you.
He will appear ... is that him? - In just a bit.
Ah, it's really him.
You just recorded him once? - No, well ... day after day.
2nd day
There he is! So full of spirit!
It's really true.
He seems a little tired today.
3rd day
There he is!
It's a different angle, but the same guy.
It was a bit rainy on the 4th day
There he is!
5th day
Isn't he like a police detective?
This is like "Bark at the Sun*"!
[*Detective drama running during the 70s and 80s]
Tried to combine it with "Bark at the Sun!"
[Theme song of "Bark at the Sun!"]
Your wife should also see this, this is really good.
I see him, too. And our daughter also saw him when she was running late.
That's why in this family ... he often gets brought up.
That's amazing! - It's a mystery.
Everyone in this family has noticed him
So at the dinner table, everyone talks about him? - That's right.
Ah, the kids. Good morning!
You've still got such a sleepy face!
You also saw the running old man, what did you think of him?
I was also running late, so it's like we were colleagues.
Ah, were you running side-by-side? - No, we passed each other.
I see! Do you know why he's running?
I dunno ... - You dunno?
You're still gradually waking up?
Usually, we'd just go there, stop him and go "Excuse me, this is Tantei Knight Scoop ..." ...
Do you reckon we can stop him? - I think if you do that, he'll be late to work.
100%. - Then that's off the table.
It might upset him if we just started recording him, so we're going to tail him first and figure out the best timing
So we'll only interview the running man ... once he's calmed down .
Then it's time to go to school
Have a nice day! - We're going, see you later!
Get to the scene
On this street? - That's right. - He'll come this way.
The street where he always encounters the runner
Is it here? - Yes, he uses this way.
And in the direction he's running in ... - There's the station.
Ah and over here we saw him in the video.
So over here, we'll make it look like I was interviewing you ...
That's how we'll do it, as we wait for him.
First act like they're doing a street interview, then start tailing him.
What do you think? Will we get him on tape?
Uwaaah... - He'll get here any moment now.
He's there! - No way! Where?
He's there! He's there! There he's running! He's made his appearance!
I'm getting nervous ...
Please come this way ...
"Ah, so that's how it is!" - "Yes."
"So, you really like Knight Scoop, then?"
"That's right." - "Thank you very much, that makes us very happy."
"Do you live in this area?" - "Yes." - "Ah, they have nice houses around here."
He's run past us.
And he's off in an instant.
I'll get going.
Detective in pursuit
Awaiting contact from the Detective
I got a Line message. - What does it say?
He got on a train to Umeda.
Got to the platform all via stairs-
So then his company is in the Umeda direction, right?
Ah, got another one.
Train took off. He's standing at the
door, panting. Window fogging up.
He got off
Got off at the first station?!
Got another one.
Got to the platform all via stairs-
He got off
He got on a train to Umeda.
Train took off. He's standing at the
door, panting. Window fogging up.
Where did he get off? ---
Got off at Okamachi,
reboarded the same train,--
but 2 cars towards the front.
Now, panting, he's reading out
the Nikkei newspaper. ---------------
So he didn't change trains at all? - He didn't.
Mysterious behavior
Ah, got another one.
He's calmed down now
Soon we'll get to Juso
In what area are you now?
Now, panting, he's reading out
the Nikkei newspaper. ---------------
What does it say?
He got off at Nakatsu!
Seems he's going to Nakatsu.
He's calmed down now
Soon we'll get to Juso
In what area are you now?
Now, panting, he's reading out
the Nikkei newspaper. ---------------
I'm sorry.
He got off at Nakatsu, ran, and re-
boarded the train 1 car to the front.
Gets back on the same train, further towards the front?
Were we exposed? It's as if he was running from someone.
Without switching trains
Did he notice us?
Ah, I got it! Is it because the ticket inspector is drawing closer?
Is he moving up the train to avoid ticket inspection?
Because he didn't have time earlier.
Ah, another one.
He got off at Nakatsu, ran, and re-
boarded the train 1 car to the front.
So we were exposed? --
We weren't exposed
He hasn't noticed us at all --
He's reading the newspaper
We've arrived at Umeda
It seems he's going to run
He's in a real rush for his commute. - Ah, another one!
He got off at Nakatsu, ran, and re-
boarded the train 1 car to the front.
So we were exposed? --
We weren't exposed
He hasn't noticed us at all --
He's reading the newspaper
We've arrived at Umeda
It seems he's going to run
He's running!
Breaking into a flat-out run in Umeda during rush hour?!
Ah, wow! I'll read it out.
He got off at Nakatsu, ran, and re-
boarded the train 1 car to the front.
He's running!
So we were exposed? --
We weren't exposed
He hasn't noticed us at all --
He's reading the newspaper
We've arrived at Umeda
It seems he's going to run
Got off at Umeda, boarded the Mido-
suji Line, got off at Yodobashi and
ran into his company building
Wow.
How was it? - He's a fast runner!
Before he got inside, I managed to give him my card and asked if he was ok with doing an interview.
I asked if he could contact me ...
And now we'll wait for his response. - Ah, I see!
Waiting uneasily ...
6 hours pass by
It's the running person for you
Detective Ishida speaking.
We'll meet up?
Thank you so much!
Interview arranged
So, we've gathered everyone from the Shintani family.
So in a few moments, he'll be coming this way. - I really want to meet him.
I wanna see him! - I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it. - I'm looking forward to resolve this.
How can he run everyday? - Ah, he's coming this way, running!
He's running!
Stop, stop, stop!
Thank you for your hard work! - Thank you very much.
These are my clients, the Shintani family. - We see you all the time!
We noticed you because you always put so much effort into your running.
How old are you now? - 57. - Ah, I'm glad to hear that.
What do you mean? - It's just you don't see it very often close to retirement.
So why do you run every morning?
I'm terribly sorry to say this, but it's because I'm running late.
Even though we were deeply impressed!
Are you serious? - Absolutely.
Couldn't you get up 15min earlier? - Ah, I do get up early.
I just hate wasting time traveling.
At Okamachi, you got off, moved to the front, and got on the train again.
Every morning?
It's because I'm running late.
Showing him what his running looks like
You can spot yourself already
Are you coming in sight? - There I am.
Ah, there you are! You're panting.
Oh man ...
You've been running constantly for 10 years.
Why do you keep this up?
Well, it's just because I'm running late.