Well, let's hear today's first request.
Subtitles by: /u/CatZombies
Airdate: 2019-11-15
Okay.
Our first request is from Kashiwagi Mone-san,
a 21 year old part-time worker from Osaka prefecture.
"To Director Nishida and all the detectives, I always enjoy watching."
Alright.
"Actually, I have a problem that I don't really talk to people about."
"That is my mom's love is too intense."
"In any case, her physical affection is incredible."
"When I come home, she immediately
embraces me and insists on clinging to me."
"Every day, she kisses my cheek over and over."
"When I ask her for a favor, she makes me kiss her on the lips."
"At night, we sleep together in a single size bed. It's cramped."
Cramped, huh.
"No matter how many times I ask her to stop, she won't listen."
"I'm already 21 years old. How freaking long are these days going to continue?"
"In order to put an end to this intense physical affection,
can you persuade my mom to stop?" That's the request.
Oh~
The mom can't help but be that doting, huh.
Well, that's how it seems.
The client's mother is a single mother and
when the client was in nursery school, she helped out there for example.
Is that so?
She seriously and carefully raised her and
it seems her love for her is exceedingly intense.
This physical affection she does every day has crossed some boundaries.
What kind of physical affection is this?
What was this mother's love like?
Please take a look.
You're 21? And still?
She still does.
She showers you with physical affection every day?
Every day.
Your mom goes a little too far with your body and
it's become sort of irritating and you dislike?
I love my mom but...
You like her, right?
I'm loved but,
it's a little bit too much.
When you're at home, what percentage of the time is she doing it?
Always.
Seriously?
Where's your mom today?
She's at my grandma's place right now.
Well, the mother who is out will be home soon, so
we'll watch from the other room.
I'm home~
She's come home.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You here, Mone? You didn't go out?
Yeah.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
A welcome home kiss. Mwah~
No way... eh?
Were you lonely?
No.
Were you a little lonely?
I'm not lonely.
Not a little bit?
No.
You really were lonely, Mone-chan.
I'm not lonely.
Wait, one more hug....
Enough already. You just did.
You didn't hug me!
Here we go, okay, hug. Even harder!
Hug! Okay.
Eh?
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
She's really looking.
Leave me alone for once.
Okay then, if you give me a kiss.
Quit it already.
If you give me a kiss, I'll leave you alone.
No!
That's really irritating.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
Mwah~
Seriously?
What are you doing?
Hahahaha... you surprised me.
Are you kidding?
It's this, Mone-chan?
This is it.
This, seriously?
What is it?
It's always like this while you're at home?
It's always like this.
That's hell!
Why?
When you come home,
You immediately start searching for your daughter.
Yeah, because she's here.
When my daughter comes home, I always do it.
That time is different, somewhat?
A little.
Woah~ I kind of want to see that a little.
Can you do that? Can we see that?
I'm home~
Welcome home~!
Mone-chan, welcome home~! Welcome home~!
No way...
It's like this every day?
Every day.
If Mone goes to sleep before me,
So, Mone is asleep here.
Mone-chan, are you asleep? Mwah~ Good night. Mwah~
...I'd do. I'd put my arm around her like this.
There's one more thing I'm curious about, when you ask for something,
The having to kiss her on the lips, that you don't like.
Yeah.
I want you to show me everything.
Try asking for something.
Make dinner?
Eh~ that's a bother.
Please.
Eh~? What should I do~?
What is that mouth?
Alright, I'll make it for you.
You did that one to yourself.
If I don't do this, she keeps pursing her lips and
won't listen to me.
Want to try eating a little from Mama?
Okay~
Is it tasty?
She doesn't let up even while they're eating.
Still, she's 21 right?
So, it's alright until about 30 I guess.
So long! Until her thirties?
Well, I understand Mone-chan's hardships.
You understand?
I understand.
Wait mom, let's talk as adults.
How did this intense physical affection
get started in the first place?
She's my darling, my beloved
It's irresistible?
Yeah, irresistible.
Inside me, I will always
feel like she's my baby.
So the case is, since she was a baby,
you've always done it?
That's right.
When my daughter was 19,
she said she wanted to live on her own.
She went out and did that.
And after 1 year, she came back.
After that, it became sort of more extreme.
It poured out?
Yeah.
What did you do during that time?
At first, I just cried.
And then, I bought this child.
I got this child.
Since you couldn't be affectionate with her, to distract yourself
you bought this child?
Yeah.
When Mone wasn't here, I slept with this child.
This is really serious, huh. You really like her, huh?
Yeah.
Isn't that right, mom?
I just spoke with your mother.
She's cute and my darling. She's cute, so it can't be helped.
You understand parents, right?
However, there are limits, right?
Yes.
It's draining.
Well, after all Mone-chan, this... hmm.
Let's say your heart is decided.
Earnestly telling her.
Now, about what you really think,
let's seriously and thoroughly discuss it.
Well then, if you would.
Alright.
Let's see, I'm already 21 and I'm not a child anymore.
Yeah...
After a few words from the daughter!?
Aren't you a little quick to cry?
The daughter too...
She only said a few words.
She only said "I'm 21 and not a child anymore."
She said "I'm not a child anymore."
She's not a child.
I thought she was a child...
She's 21. She's had her coming-of-age ceremony. Let's continue.
Someday, I'm going to get married and
when I move out on my own,
I have my worries.
Will you be lonely?
You're worried about your mother, right?
When you're suddenly not here anymore.
If she gets married, she won't be here anymore.
What do you intend to do then?
Well...
If she marries a rich person,
we can establish a two-generation household and we can live (together) but...
if it's a poor person, it can't be helped and we can't stay together.
There's a strange pressure hang above, huh.
There's a strange pressure
By the way, do you have a boyfriend now?
Yes.
Do you know that boyfriend?
The last guy was better...
What kind of comment is that?
Reply to her. This is no time to be laughing.
The current guy is better.
Say why he's good.
He's got money...
Money she says...
No, that's not right.
What's not right?
Mom, why did you want to do this until now?
Can you convey that?
I had the terrible thought, that Mone suddenly wouldn't be here, so
I clung all over Mone.
Now,
I'm no longer a child so,
I want to be alone...
It's no good if you use those words.
She's bursting into tears because you said "I'm no longer a child."
She heard that and started crying again.
You want to be treated like an adult, right?
Yes.
Why's that?
Because I'm not a child.
Why are you crying like that?
That's why with things like the clinging and the kissing,
I want you to stop.
I understand.
Well, um, Mom,
if you suddenly have to stop now, you maybe become lonely and
your reaction to that may make it even more intense...
This physical affection isn't allowed!
Because of that, today is the last day of intense physical affection.
Mone-chan won't refuse anything.
You can do that, right?
If you won't do anything from tomorrow on, I can endure it today.
How long do you have to do it to be satisfied?
1 hour.
So long...
The last physical affection of their lives.
Ready, start!
She's giving her a tight embrace.
Once this 1 hour is up,
she can't do this kind of intense physical affection ever again.
Cute, cute.
Cute. Mwah~
Endure it, endure it. Hang in there, Mone-chan.
If you can endure 1 hour, you won't have to ever again.
I want it to hurry up and be over.
Like that time...
What are you wanting to do?
When she was a baby, I'd do this.
Ah, when you would rock her.
30 minutes have elapsed. There are 30 minutes left.
There's things I haven't done yet.
Do this and I'll feed you.
The last "Aah~"
What are you happy about?
The last co-sleeping.
There's 15 minutes left.
It's become intense.
Last is, where she always overdoes it, on this sofa.
3 minutes remaining.
This isn't physical affection anymore,
she's got her in a Nelson hold now.
Her last time to experience this with her daughter, Mone.
1 minute remaining.
She's kissing her. On the mouth.
A kiss storm. A kissing storm.
She's now kissing her right on the mouth.
You can't fight back, Mone-chan. Endure this last part.
10 seconds left, 9, 8, 7, 6,
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
That's it!
Well, mom, you're crying but those tears are?
It's like,
she's climbed the stairs of adulthood I think.
Well, no more physical affection.
Can you do that?
Yes, I can do that.
I'm not a child anymore, okay?
Why? Those words were so gentle.
Oh~ intense, huh.
A mother's love.
So, the mother has now,
since then, she's not done any intense physical affection.
Oh, good.
Not being able to do any physical affection is a little pitiful, so
when Mone-chan gets home,
there's nothing intense, but a normal hug.
For only 5 seconds. That's what they decided.
Just 5 seconds.
But the mother, for those 5 seconds,
she counts really, really slowly.
"5~~" she'd say.
The mom has got the best child.