Let's move on to our last request today.
Yes, our last request comes from the 35 y/o Nagata Nami, a housewife, who lives in the Wakayama prefecture.
"Good evening, Detectives."
"My request concerns my 4 y/o daughter, Nana."
"She has abnormal strength in her fingers."
"In fact, when we start a thumb war, in a position where she holds me down ..."
"... I can't manage to free myself, no matter what."
She's that strong?
"No matter how often me or my husband have tried, she always pins us down."
"Could one of the Detectives come and try to challenge her?"
It's something everyone does, right? Thumb wars.
Everyone does it! Holding the other one down like this.
Yes, everyone.
And you can easily free yourself, right?
But when this 4 y/o girl pins you down, you can't get out!
Could you say the same of yourself? Probably not, right?
As a matter of fact, I thought our client just wanted their daughter to appear on television.
That's what I thought. Wouldn't you?
Yes, probably.
And would you have no idea what to tell her?
In any case, I went there for the time being.
Take a look!
Our client claims, that if we start in a pinned down position, it'll be impossible to break free.
Is is easy to keep the opponent from breaking free?
Trying it with the show staff first
That's right.
Like this, get in position ...
And, start!
1,2,3,4,5,6, ...
One more time.
I need to put a lot of strength into it. Ready? - Ok.
And ... start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7, ...
You do it!
And ... start!
1,2,3,4,5, ... - See?
It's in the grip, right?
And ... start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7...
There's no way! You can break free instantly!
Even for an adult, it's difficult to pin down the opponent ...
Even when doing it with an adult, you can break free.
So with a 4 y/o, even if she pins me down, I'll break free instantly!
So you're saying the request she sent us was a lie? - She's lying!
She's definitely lying! A 4 year old?!
What's the truth?
So I'm in the Wakayama prefecture ... ehm ...
... and I don't really know what to say ...
Yes!
Lying is pointless.
Seriously. - I'm over here!
Everyone in this family is a liar! - Not at all! It's true!
Have you seen it? - I have. I've even tried it!
I ... didn't think it was possible for a 4 y/o!
Don't you just want to appear on television? - No, no, I don't!
Can we try? You're definitely weaker than me.
Put a lot of pressure into it.
Not yet, wait for the signal!
Shall we do it?
Not yet! Only when he gives the signal! - But you pressed down already!
Hold on a second ...
And ... go! - 1,2,3,4,5, ...
Can you do it with me? - Yes.
See, even if you press down, I can break free!
But when a 4 y/o does it, it's supposed to be impossible? - Definitely!
It's been 4 years since she was born? - Yes.
In my case, it's been 66 years!
And she can supposedly pin me down like that? That's what you're saying? - Yes, that's right.
Hello ~
Nana has returned from preschool
Hello!
How old are you? - 4 yearth old.
She can't really say it.
4 years old, she goes "4 yearth".
Now you sure have been pranked by mom and dad, haven't you?
You see it now, don't you?
Could you do it with mom?
It starts when I yell "start", ok?
Ready? Start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10!
You're liars, all of you!
How about dad?
Take position, ready?
And, start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10!
You liars! All of you! Nothing but liars!!
Were you serious when you tried? - Absolutely!
Can you do it one more time? When I say start.
Start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10!
Liars, all of you!
This family is starting to scare me!
You know that if you hold me down and I break free, this shoot is over? Then I'll just go home.
Get in position ... like that ...
In position ...
And, start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10!
Hold on!
Hold on a second!
Ready? - Yes.
And ... start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10!
How ... ?
How ... ?!
How old are you?
66.
She can't be that strong!
Her power ...
One of the staff should try as well!
In position? Ok. And ... start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10!
She's strong!
Ready?
And ... start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10!
Hey ... why are you so strong?
Why are you so strong? - 4 yearth old!
Well, that much I know already.
Since when have you been so strong?
Alwayth.
Always?
It's all in that hand.
Look.
Now we've seen that we've all lost to her, but perhaps the viewers at home can't quite grasp it yet.
So should we take a walk around town?
Hello!
Ready? And ... start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10!
She's strong! - How was it?
Why do you think? - Talent?
Isn't that Kanpei?
Ready? And ... start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10!
It wouldn't budge.
All set? Ready? And ... start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10!
I lost.
And ... start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10!
Ah, it's impossible!
Did you use glue or something?
It's like glue? - Yes.
The secret of her strength?
Can you count a little slower? You're so fast!
And ... start!
1 ... 2 ... 3 ... 4 ... 5 ... 6 ... 7 ... 8 ... 9 ... 10!
How ?
... 36 ... 37 ...
Ah, excuse me.
Dr. Tani Hitoshi
Knight Scoop - Medical Supervisor
My thumb won't budge at all.
Please try your best to break free! And ... start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10!
What is this?
What is this? She's 4!
She's 4! - But it won't budge.
It has to do with how human fingers can move.
What do you mean, "how fingers can move"?
If I press it down normally,  I can just slip out.
But this girl goes for this joint.
If you press down this joint, you can't move around freely anymore.
But even if you do it this way, holding down from above, you can still break free to the side!
That's why this girl pins you down in this position here. - Ah, so she does it there?
Here, she wraps her finger around the first joint.
That way, you can't escape in any direction.
So even escaping to the top is impossible?
Yes, just like in that direction.
Did someone teach her this? - She didn't want to lose, so she thought of her own special way.
This little kid ... so much talent!
Amazing! I tremble before you! - I tremble before you!