Subbed by: Otviss
So, my favourite fish tank is in this corner here
Over here
Take a look!
What is that?
It's called a sheepshead wrasse
That fish's forehead is the nicest thing I have ever touched in my whole life...
There's nothing like it
It's stiff though isn't it?
I want to touch it
It's neither soft or hard.
It's an unknown feeling I guess
Is it like touching a boob?
Not really no
So its not...
So if I touch it like this will I get excited?
Oh yeah, if you close your eyes you can definitely reach the limit...
Wanna touch it?
Shall we go then?
Wait, really?
Sure thing!
Are we touching it?
I guess we are
I've never touched the bulge of a wrasse before...
Let's go then, just for you guys
Comfortable thing?
Is the forehead of a wrasse
The most
Wow are we really going there?
It's coming it's coming
Oh shit!
That thing can't be touched!
Look! Go for it now
Go go go!
Wow, that's nice!!
You touched it!
You must be joking
It can't be real..
Haha, that's so nice!
It's really nice!
Wait, I wanna try too
It's coming, do it quickly
OOOOOH!!
It's SO freaking nice!
It's kinda...
What is this thing?
Like a silicone bra
Yeah you're right!
It's a bit too soft though
It feels exactly like one
So why exactly do they have one of those?
This is for their allure​ and longevity.
Both males and females have them though.
But if its bigger then surely...
So if it's a young fish it's not so prominent?
Exactly.
The older they are it gets bigger.
This was such a valuable experience
You kind of want to rub it don't ya?
I do...
However I think you're the one rubbing it am I right?
Are you rubbing it?
I wouldn't be the head chief if I was rubbing it
m -89 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 28 l 38 28 l -89 28