Babyuun M
Super Steel Man
Sang by: Ichiro Mizuki
When the peace on the planet is broken
I will absolutely never forgive
The invulnerable warrior Babyunn M !!
I want to see everyone smile
I wish for everyone's happiness
Today's explosion! Danger Fire!
Babyuun Bike goes at 200 kilometers per hour
Let's go! Showtime! Wheelie Rider!
Super human! Steel Man!
Ah~ Babyunn M !!
Stand up!
Rise!
Ah~ Babyuun M !!
Victory!
Take action!
Ah~ Babyuun M !!
I can't believe it, did you get into an accident?
I will absolutely never admit it
The invulnerable warrior Babyuun M !!
Is this worth it, is it really useless?
As the way things are, should I be motivated?
The invulnerable warrior Babyuun M !!
To continue as things are, it is painful to picture this.
They know it hurts, the kids have seen this all.
The invulnerable warrior Babyuun M !!
Are there difficulties? Are there things to grumble about?
What the hell are you?
Super human! Steel Man!
Ah~ Babyuun M !!
Are you saying that just for the sake of the money?
What are you waiting, the motivation to get up?
Money hungry! Babyuun M !!
Haven't you suffered enough from that depression?
Have you tried to strike it from the inside out?
Why don't you change it all? Babyuun M !!
By the way, do you know how to fix this?
Do you know how to paint the metal sheets?
I will do it, Babyuun M !!
Will the insurance take care of things like that?
Will the insurance take care of that crap?
Don't you think I should have entered automobile liability?
When you are driving in a zig zag like that
It's dangerous and you should have seen it coming!
Super human! Steel Man!
Ah~ Babyuun M !!
In the end you'll make pranks at the garden place
Given the situation, you'll take a shortcut
Go down Kyu Yamate, Babyuun M !!
Don't underestimate the five road junction!
Why did you go down in the direction of Nakamegura Yarigasaki?
If I'm not wrong, that traffic light arrow will fade out soon so it's hard to know
I was relieved that the police box had no one in there!
Did you say I would not be able to hold my liquor?
Ordinary man! Mediocre man!
Ah~ Babyuun M !!
Mediocre! Mediocre!
Ultra mediocre man M