http://jburogu-godzillaradio.blogspot.com.au/
Subtitles by Godzillaradio & Hadin
On this night enveloped by the noises of insects...
...that evening meeting will once again be held.
This show which has reached it's
7th installment due to great reception...
is a very simple program where a group
of speakers lead by Matsumoto Hitoshi
tell of their true but guaranteed funny stories.
The speakers who will be taking part this time are...
(Downtown)
MATSUMOTO HITOSHI
The man who has mastered the art of funny stories...
King of Funny, Matsumoto Hitoshi.
(Chihara Kyoudai)
CHIHARA JUNIOR
He's a story telling specialist who tells
stories from his sharp viewpoint!
Chihara Junior!
MIYAGAWA DAISUKE
He freely controls stories with his ingenious movements.
The conversation expert, Miyagawa Daisuke!
Football Hour
GOTO TERUMOTO
And appearing for the first time, the unique and cool straightman
who tells funny tales, Football Hour's Goto Terumoto!
(Taka and Toshi)
TOSHI
The stories explaining his rage are sure-fire to be funny!
Toshi from Taka and Toshi!
(Drunk Dragon)
TSUKAJI MUGA
He creates funny stories with ease with his varied expressions.
Drunk Dragon's Tsukaji Muga!
(Tokyo Dynamite)
HACHIMITSU JIRO
His slightly bad-ass stories are top-notch.
Hachimitsu Jiro from Tokyo Dynamite!
(Jipangu Jouriku Sakusen)
CHAD MULLANE
A cultural exchange of funny stories.
Hailing form Australia, he's Jipangu Jouriu Sakusen's
Chad Mullane!
Of course, all of the stories told today are...
...all true storrrrriiieees!
Hitoshi Matsumoto's Suberanai Hanashi 7!
So everyone, we're finally starting!
Yeah! Let's do this!
Amazingly, this is now the 7th installment.
Well, the previous 6th installment was a really ground-breaking compilation episode.
We had to retell some of our funny stories again here.
Some people were even retelling another person's story!
What a fresh, new idea!
We had a blast of a time, and after that
we were inundated by comedians
saying they wanted to appear too
and so we have 5 comedians debuting, all at once today!
Everyone on this side is a newcomer.
First of all, is Football Hour's Goto!
Thank you.
And next is Toshi, from Taka and Toshi.
And then Tsukaji from Drunk Dragon.
It's great to be with you! Thank you!
And Hachimitsu Jiro from Tokyo Dynamite!
And finally, Chad Mullane from Jipang Jouriku Sakusen!
Thank you very much.
There's an intense sense of anxiety, isn't there?
Maybe I shouldn't say this but, this show is now on DVD
and it has surprisingly sold pretty well and...
it isn't the reason I do this, but, my bank savings have increased somewhat.
Surely you don't need anymore money!
It's not the aim of this show. but if you do well on this show
you will reap the rewards afterwards.
So 50 billion and how much did you say you have?
50 billion!?
I don't!
Rules are simple.
They toss an 8-sided die with all of their names on it
and the person faced up will tell a funny story.
As long as it's funny, they are allowed to repeat the story as many times as they want.
It's a very simple show, where they spend one hour only using a die!
Well then, let's get to it!
Well here I go! We're starting!
TOSHI
Toshi
Heck yeah....
So, it's me? Ok.
There's a junior comedy duo to me called
Zabungle from a different agency,
but anyway, they were writing jokes
at a family restaurant late at night.
Their skits usually consists of the fool being unreasonable
and the two end up arguing.
Anyway, they then began to rehearse it together
but after a while they got a bit too into it
and their voices became a bit loud.
And suddenly, a gentleman wearing a suit
and a hat slammed his table and said
"You guys are being really noisy there!"
"Why are you fighting at a place like this!?"
"Go outside if you're gonna fight!"
He thought it was a fight.
"There are other customers here, you know!"
The two didn't know what to do, so apologised.
he yelled "Get your act together!",
then stood up and told them to step outside.
Then on the way out he turned and said
"I've been listening this whole time..." and he looked at the fool
and goes "You're the one at fault!"
Of course it is!
He would've been saying stupid stuff a lot.
Of course it is.
Because he only says unreasonable stuff.
Okay, let's go.
Miyagawa
Please wait a second.
Wait, what? You've got 3 books?!
You've written heaps!
I've decided, this is it.
When I was in middle school, I was part of the boys scout
and once you're in middle school,
you become a leader of some cub scouts.
Since cub scouts aren't yet in primary school
they can't sleep in the tents at the campsite
and have to sleep at a ryokan or something, no matter what.
A ryokan is a traditional Japanese inn
So anyway, we hiked for the day, and they stayed at the ryokan.
And at around 9:30pm, I was told to go and patrol the area.
So, I went to patrol, and looked around
where they were sleeping with a torch
when I saw one of them crying in the corner.
I thought, "He must be homesick"
"Homesick on the very first night, huh? I've gotta cheer him up."
So, I crept up to him, and saw it was a kid called Takeuchi-kun.
Takeuchi-kun was all sniveling so...
I asked, "Takeuchi-kun, are you ok?"
"Why're you crying? Are you Homesick?"
and he goes "Nooo".
So I asked, "Huh? Then what's wrong?".
He slowly took his hand from under the blanket
and there was a female stag beetle clamped on his thumb.
Clamped really tight....
Takeuchi's thumb was getting all white.
When I asked "What happened, Takeuchi-kun?"
he said, "I found it while hiking, and put it in my pocket."
"I just remembered about it so put my hand in to check and it....
...OW OW OW OWWWCH!"
As he was speaking the beetle clamped even harder.
Right at that instant?
Right at that instant it clamped harder.
I said, "Are you ok"?
"No, I just cau...OWWWOWW!!"
Poor Takeuchi-kun.
I felt really sorry for him.
Well, very funny stories aren't they?
It's already funny.
Amazing.
GOTO
Errr, this is a story about my mum.
My mum is a bit strange....
...for example, she's 50+ years and used money that I sent her
for plastic surgery to get double eye-lids.
At that age?
She's that kind of unusual parent.
Anyway, when I was in senior high, I brought a girlfriend home for the first time.
My mum seemed a bit agitated.
She was thinking like, "Who the heck is this girl?"
and she said, "Have a seat. I'll cook you some pizza toast."
How stylish.
She was showing off a bit, huh?
Yeah, she wouldn't usually make that stuff.
She said "Eat", so we were just eating, when...
....she asked the girlfriend, "What does your dad do?"
"Oh, my dad is just an ordinary office worker".
Then my mum goes, "Stop talking, and quickly eat".
She was totally agitated.
So I said "Let's go to my room"
and took my girlfriend to my room.
But my mum yells, "Wait! You can't close your door though".
"Ain't ya gonna get up to mischief?"
"Leave your door open!".
So I'm like "Fine, fine...." and leaved it open.
Then my mum says "I'm going shopping".
"But keep your door open!".
Wow!
She wouldn't shut up about it.
So anyway, she went.
But since she went, I wanted to close the door...
...and, you know, do some cheeky stuff.
So I closed the door but, I was a bit scared
since mum told me not to, so I kept it open just ajar.
I couldn't bring myself to shut it completely.
So I was talking with my girlfriend for a bit and...
...the mood became good so I put my arms around her
and was just about to kiss her, when I felt a presence.
I turned to the gap beween the door,
and my mum was peeking in.
Usually when you peek, you peek like this, right?
My mum was like this.
She wanted to see it properly or something!
I got pretty pissed off about that and
yelled "What're you doing mum!?"
and she jerked her head away,
but her glasses were still stuck in the gap.
After a short pause, she grabbed it out.
It was only her glasses for a bit?
It was just her glasses for a bit
Wow! What a powerful mum!
She is powerful.
Well then, here we go.
TSUKAJI
Oh wow, it's going to the newcomers a lot today.
Yes it is.
This is about when I was in 1st year of senior high.
My Japanese history teacher was
very against boys and girls socialising.
Even if a boy and girl were just talking he'd ask, "What are you talking about?"
If a boy and girl were walking home, he'd pull them apart too.
It was so extreme that some students asked  him,
"Aren't you taking it too far?"
and he said "I'm not against relationships".
"I don't care what you do after school
but I want you to concentrate on school while at school".
So I thought "Oh, how admirable".
but the teacher was almost 50 and not married,
so we asked if he had a partner
and he said "I don't have one, and don't need one".
"If I had the time for that, I'd rather
learn more about Japanese history".
We were impressed but, he's still a man and...
...so we asked if he gets frustrated at all
and he said, "If you're passionate enough about one thing,
you don't think at all about dirty things".
So he's like, "I guess you could kinda say,
Japanese history is my partner".
It's pretty lame now that I think about it,
but I thought it was cool at the time.
Anyway, there was a person called Kurisu Yoshihiko
in my Japanese history class
The "kuri" as in chestnut, and "su" as in nest.
Ohh, so he wasn't half Japanese?
Kurisu is how Japanese pronounce Chris.
Yeah, it was his surname.
Yeah some people have that name.
So when the teacher tried to get him to answer a question
he said "Okay, you answer, Toris".
Obviously he was thinking of something dirty!
*Kurisu-torisu, sounds like Clitoris.
He imagined that just from the sound of the name!
He was thinking of the later half.
He must've thought it sounded like something!
It was totally inspired by that!
Yeah kinda sounds like another word
Man, that's horrible. Everyone's faces would've turned red.
The teacher was the reddest, so no doubt it's what he was thinking about.
Oh nice. Nice stories, hey?
Yeah.
MIYAGAWA
Can't you do something about that?
Nope.
Please hurry up!
Stop complaining!
But he does it every time.
Yeah, I know.
It says "Funny Story #7".
You don't need a title!
Just so you don't mistake it with #8.
I'll go with this one.
This is about when I was in 1st Grade of middle school.
My math teacher was a man called Mr. Terao.
He was such a strange teacher, we nicknamed him "Monsieur Terao".
His hair was naturally curly, but had an undercut and....
...he had on coke bottle glasses, while wearing track pants
So, anyway, when he's writing on the board, his ass pops out.
'Cuz he writes like this.
We can't help chuckling when we see that.
And when we laugh, he goes, *clap, clap*, "You there, no laughing!"
He's like, "You there, no laughing".
And we'd see that, and laugh again. So that's what he was like.
I liked that teacher, and enjoyed seeing him.
Anyway, around the end of the first semester
the teacher came to class with a broken arm, cracked front teeth and scrape marks.
And he's casually like, "Okay, let's get started".
But a student asked "Um, err, what happened to you, sir?"
and he said, "Well actually, I stayed at school until quite late last night and....
...it was hot so I decided to swim in the pool before going home".
"So, I went to the pool, but the lights were off and it was pitch black".
"Anyway, I took off my glasses and jumped in".
"I jumped in but, there was no water inside".
What an utter fail!
His eyes are so bad he needs coke bottle glasses so...
...he couldn't anything, so when he jumped in he crashed
What a massive fail!
It was an utter fail!
He dived straight in?
Everyone who heard that, started laughing....
...and he goes, "No laughing!".
It was the day when they changed the water.
Funny stuff.... Here I go.
GOTO
Hooooh, I see.
In addition to my mother....
...my dad is also quite a weird person.
Or rather than weird, should I say, he has no aspirations.
He doesn't give kids things to aspire about.
I was in the lower grades of primary school and...
...on the night of Christmas Eve...
...I was waiting impatiently in bed for Santa to bring presents.
I was thinking, "Surely he'll bring presents, even next to my pillow!".
So, it was midnight, and I had fallen asleep.
The front door slams open and someone yells
"HEEEEY!! SANTA'S BACK HOME!"
and it was dad returning home.
How obvious.
I was like, "Well this sucks".
He screams, "I BOUGHT YA'LL A PRESENT!".
He even gives away that he bought it.
He's saying everything.
And he goes "Oh, sleepin' soundly eh? I'll leave your present here!".
I pretended to be asleep...
...thinking, "Oh well, he got me a present, it's okay I guess."
The next morning I woke up excited to open it up
so I looked next to my pillow, and the present was a library book.
A library book!
He borrowed it!
Yes, and I had to go return it 2 days later!
And the book was also called, "New Years Around The World".
It has nothing to do with Christmas!
He's already thinking of something 1 week later!
It's hard to tell if he has aspirations or not.
It's starting to be a bit one-sided today.
TSUKAJI
This is about my comedy partner, Suzuki.
Urgent announcement!!
Due to rave reviews of Hitoshi Matsymoto's Suberanai Hanashi Episode 1
we've decided to release a 2nd installment!
For more information, visit the show's homepage address!
The DVD this time will again be...!?
Funny stuff!
This is about my comedy partner, Suzuki.
I'm sure many have noticed already but.....
....he's quite unbelievably stupid.
For example, he'd endlessly blow on noodles that are served cold.
And that wasn't only once.
I even told him, "That's cold so you don't have to blow it".
and he's like "Oh yeah!", but it seems like he can't eat it without blowing.
That's how weird he is.
We were with Ogi-Yahagi and ordered some food to be delivered to our agency.
We wanted lunch, but couldn't be bothered going out for it, so go it delivered.
We got Suzuki to call them, and told him to order the curry and whatnot that Ogi and Yahagi wanted.
So Suzuki went off and called a place and said,
"Hello. Mr. Ogi wants curry, and Mr. Yahagi wants a katsu lunch box and..."
Even though the other guy wouldn't know who they are!
How embarrassing.
Also, the thing that shocked me the most happened when we did a show with animals.
We've done work with giraffes several times...
...and at the time me and other staff are on site
but for some reason, Suzuki and the giraffe....
Well, let's say, Suzuki is standing here.
The giraffe would swing his head back and smash him away.
The giraffe does?
Yes. It happened to Suzuki twice and...
...even the zoo keeper was like "I've never seen that happen before".
Apparently, Giraffe's only do that when they perceive someone as an enemy.
For some reason giraffes think Suzuki's an enemy, and they all go and slam him away!
Something's wrong with him, if giraffes think of him that way.
Somethings different about his biological makeup.
That's funny, wow.
Hey Junior, can you toss it?
Chad and Hachimitsu haven't spoken yet?
Hopefully soon, or it'd get harder to speak.
Here I go then.
TSUKAJI
Maybe it's Tsukaji day today?
Well, let's see...this is a story of when I was in middle school.
At the time, Bebop Highschool was very popular and...
...it was a time when everyone looked up to delinquents.
There were incidences like people getting hunted for uniforms by kids from other schools.
Anyway, when I was in 3rd grade of middle school
there was like an uprising of the 2nd years.
Yes, there was a strange time like that.
Anyway, one day after school, I think in summer...
I was changing in the kendo club locker room when...
five of the 3rd year delinquent guys came in.
But they were all friends of mine from primary school...
and they said "We're going to go and brawl with the 2nd graders now".
This was because the 2nd graders wouldn't pay respect to the 3rd graders.
As they thought they were tougher than 3rd years.
They wanted all 3rd graders to greet 2nd graders, or something.
They wanted to gather as many fighters as they could, so they asked me to come.
I wasn't necessarily a fierce guy, but they were all my friends so....
I said "Ok, I'll go", and so I did.
And seriously, there was about thirty 3rd graders gathered near a lake
waiting for the 2nd graders.
Eventually the 2nd graders appeared and...
there were only about 20, but they all had wooden swords and kendo sticks.
The 3rd graders were yelling like, "Hey, those cheaters have wooden swords and stuff!".
When I looked closer, they were all from my club.
They were the wooden swords and bamboo sticks from my kendo clubroom
and since I was kendo captain I was worried about getting in trouble
and peoples' kendo stick getting wrecked.
When I looked at their leader, the stick that he held
was the stick that I use for official bouts, and take extremely good care of!
I used to repair the leather on it...
...and even the tsuba, I went all the way from Osaka to a shop in Wakayama to get it!
The tsuba is the hand guard on the sword.
I knew for sure it was mine!
Anyway, a junior from the kendo club looking sorry over there.
He was my junior, so I was like "What the heck are ya doin'!?"
"I've got a fight in one month, and I was planning to use that stick so....
...I'm gonna be pissed if it breaks!"
But then everyone was going "Let's gooooo!".
and the 3rd and 2nd graders were all out brawling
while I found that junior, and was yelling "Why did ya give it to him!?"
"Why did ya give everyone kendo sticks!!"
While everyone was arguing about who's gonna greet who,
I just kept banging on about the kendo sticks.
Well, that's quite an incident.
MATSUMOTO
So now's, the time?
Well I think you've begun to sense that my mum is also quite strange.
This happened today. Seriously, today.
A certain tv program showed me doing the opening baseball pitch at a game
and my mum called me saying, "That was nice....." and stuff.
She often lies a lot. She said, "It was nice....
EVERYONE in Amagasaki is saying so."
Amagasaki: Matsumoto's home town.
As if they would be.
That's definitely a lie!
She's a strange mother, but when I was about 20 years old...
Well, actually, I'm the youngest out of three children and...
...I had turned 20, so she said that she was lonely.
And she said "You've all become adults, so I want another child."
But it's kinda impossible for her to bear a child at her age.
Anyway, I don't know what she was thinking but
when I came home one day, she was holding a toy baby...
...and said, "From today, this is my child".
She even named it Akira!
She's like "Ain't that right, Akira? Ain't that riiight?"
That's creepy!
And when I come home at night she'd wander out while holding Akira.
She's say "Just heat up that curry for dinner! Heat up the curry!"
"Ain't that right, Akira? Ain't that riiight?"
Scary, right?
Yeahhh.
But 2 months later, Akira was abandoned and lying like this.
She's a really creepy mother.
Here we go then.
CHIHARA
Ummm....
This just happened the other day.
Currently, the Yoshimoto Shinkigeki is visiting all around the country for their national tour.
So people like Imada, Itao, Kimu-nii and others do various stuff
but the practice for that occurs in the Lumine at midnight after all other shows end.
Anyway, I love Shishaku Shisho and always listen
to his rakugo tapes while driving to practice.
Lumine has an underground car park so I parked there and went up in the elevator
to practice with them at night.
Then my manager says "Excuse me, can I please borrow your car keys?"
so I asked why,
and he said that there was nighttime construction going on, and the cars had to be moved outside for a bit.
So they had to take out everyone's cars, including Imada and Kimu-Nii.
I was like, "Okay, go ahead then".
but my managaer, Inagaki, is a paper driver, and has never driven once since getting his license.
So, I assumed he'd pass the key to one of the many other Yoshimoto managers and get them to move my car.
So he went off to do that, and practice finished around 3:30am.
We began to leave, and they announced that Imada's car had been returned to the car park.
So Imada leaved, and then next Kimu-nii's car came, so he leaved.
But mine wouldn't come at all! Even after waiting 30 minutes!
It was strange so I went downstairs, but it wouldn't come
so I walked to the car park where they said they moved it to
when some other guy's manager came and said
"I'm sorry, Inagaki crashed your car".
"Whaaat!? Why did you let Inagaki drive it?!"
But you know how Yoshimoto is like.
Inagaki probably said he can't drive
but his seniors were probably like "I don't give a damn! We're low on help!!"
So he probably was forced to drive for the first time since being licensed.
When I went to the car park, the head lights were off
and it was slightly ahead of the park space, and the doors were wide open.
I look at the front and there's a massive dent.
Quite a huge dent.
I was like, "How did you hit it there!?", it was right down the middle!
Yeah just from parking?
I looked up and Inagaki was there with a horribly sorry face
saying, "I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!"
but from the car I can hear Shishaku Shishou's comedy routine.
Also, he was telling a story was about winning the lottery
and was yelling "I hit it! I hit it! I hit the jackpot!"
I'd never seen people laughing at Shishaku Shishou as much as that time.
Wowww.
Woow, that's amazing.
Maan.
Sure is funny.
When will it not be funny?
I'd like to see when someone's story fails.
TOSHI
Back when I just debuted, I had a senior who was a rakugoka.
A rakugoka is someone who practices rakugo, a type of solo comedic storytelling.
He said that once a month he borrows a tatami room at an
izakaya ands hold a practice show, so he invited us to attend.
So we said, "Oh yes we'll go".
At the time, it was us, that rakugoka, and also one magician.
And we were all changing clothes in a small room before the show.
But you know how magicians have all kinds of secrets tricks?
And since we just debuted, we hadn't seen any of that stuff
and so we were watching in awe when
he put a small umbrella into his sleeve
which shoots out when he thrusts his hands out, like this.
And we were quite impressed with that.
So anyway, it was about 30 minutes until the show starts
and my group, were told to open with manzai for 10 minutes,
after which it was the magician's turn and then the rakugoka.
We were fine with that but the magician said "I'm sorry I've got work after this
so please let me go first".
And our senior was like "Oh what? But we're about to start...?"
but said "Oh...ok then", and hesitantly accepted.
But apparently he wasn't really happy about that so
he said "Hey, why would you tell me that now?"
"Usually you'd say that the day before or,
when you come in, tell us that you're busy so you would like to start first".
"It's common sense!".
We were like "That's right", but the magician was quite strong-hearted and said
"Well, I didn't know either. I got told about it just then!".
and sort of talked back at him.
But the seniors said, "Yeah, so what? You still should have told me earlier!".
"Don't you have any common sense!?"
They began arguing and we didn't know what to do.
Then the rakugoka said "Get your act together!" and shoved the magician.
That made the magician man really angry
and he went to punch, but the umbrella came out.
He then tried to put it back and the other umbrella came out.
It was just a huge mess.
He was trying to shove two umbrellas back in.
Since he had them shoved up there...
What a fine line between nervous tension and hilarity.
He was like "Ahh-ahh..".
HACHIMITSU
I actually go on trips overseas quite often.
Even from back when I had no work and no money.
Once I went to Canada with 4 other people
and they were Japanese, but could speak English
and had traveled around a lot themselves before.
But buying presents is hard right? You can't just keep getting chocolates for people.
Anyway, Canada's got some pretty good drugstores, so I was suggested to buy medicine.
For example, their cold medicine makes you sleep easily, because it's made for Western people's bodies.
The pain killers are also good, and the boxes are quite cute and interesting so
I bought heaps of stuff at this drugstore.
But when I brought all of it to the register, the guy there went ballistic.
He was like "Why are ya buying so much? You can't take all this back to Japan!".
Or that's what I thought he was saying, and I got scared
so I backed off and got a guy that understands English
and told him about the situation, and asked him to interpret for me
and turns out that he was asking if I have a point card.
"If you buy this much, you'll get 3 or 4 free!".
That's such a tiny incident!
He was totally going off at me though.
He turned out to be a really nice guy though, huh?
He must be a really kind guy.
That was a slightly heartwarming story.
MATSUMOTO
I'll tell you a short one then.
Even now I have a column in Playboy...
Even now I have a column in Playboy.
Well it's not like I write anything but
they interview me and they write down whatever I say.
So, this happened to the person in charge of that job at the time. Not anymore.
Anyway, when I was talking in the interview, suddenly.....
His nose started bleeding.
Blood suddenly dribbled out of his nose.
Not snot, but blood?
Yeah it suddenly came out so I was like, "Are you ok!?"
"Maybe we should stop for today?"
"No, no, there's no way we can stop".
"Let's continue. Please let me continue".
"But please allow me a tissue"
and he rolled one up in there.
It was soaked with blood up to half way.
And even while talking more, it was still coming out so
I said "Shouldn't we just stop this?"
"Sorry, let's continue. I would like to continue".
"But please let me lie down".
All the while I'm talking, and he's just lying down.
Why doesn't he just stop!?
Just stop!
That was a shock.
It's going around pretty evenly aside from Chad.
It's about time.
HACHIMITSU
When I was in middle school, my generation totally loved Bebop Highschool.
I grew up in a place called Kurashiki in Okayama, and we were total bad ass delinquents
Now I'm 100 kg, but I used to be 120kg
and my hair was standing up way out here and...
...I rode a bicycle like this.
A bicycle?
Yeah, a bicycle.
And on the back I had those pegs so people could stand on it...
and we used to roam the streets a lot like that.
Anyway, during summer, bats fly past quite low around the residential areas.
You look and think they might be sparrows or swallows, but they're often actually bats.
So one day, we were roaming around in a line of 7-8 people, chatting.
There was a guy that's the best looking, and most popular, called Ishida...
...and a bat flew into his mouth.
But only I managed to see that happened.
So I stopped everyone and said "Hey! A bat just flew into Ishida's mouth!".
But everyone heard that and was just like "Yeah right. As if".
and Ishida likes to seem like a cool dude
so even when I asked him if it went in, he said "No it didn't".
So I was then called a liar.
But it definitely went into Ishida's mouth and...
...when he closed his mouth, the wings flapped out, and it flew away.
I definitely saw it!
But I was called a liar, and no one believed me.
"Bats use sonar and stuff, so no way that'd happen".
It was like I was a big fat liar.
4 years after that, everyone started getting car licenses
and around 5am, on the highway
there's about 4 lanes and nobody is using them.
So we'd fill our cars with bucket loads of water bombs
and we'd throw them at each other while laughing our asses off.
Having water bomb wars and stuff.
We'd close the windows to defend, and when attacking we'd throw again....
...and a water bomb went straight into Ishida's mouth.
Without bursting too!
A water balloon that usually bursts so easily, went into his mouth unbroken.
And from then, everyone's like "Oh that story from 4 years ago about
a bat flying into his mouth must be true!".
Finally after 4 years.
Nice.
Here I go.
CHAD
Finally my turn, huh.
Err, well this is something I've noticed recently.
Something you noticed?
Yes.
So you're announcing something you noticed?
I had always wanted to be a comedian since I was a little kid
and I just happened to come to Japan as a highschooler
when I found Japanese comedy, and was astounded that such a world existed.
I knew I had to be a comedian in Japan, so went back, graduated high school
and then went to Yoshimoto's NSC in Osaka
and without even knowing left from right I....
...I tried and tried my best, but, even after a year, it wasn't enough so...
...I became an apprentice.
So I became an apprentice to Bonchi Osamu from Za Bonchi, who I considered to be the funniest at the time.
Everyday, all day for 2 years I followed him around, learned many things
and basically.....I just tried my best.
I read lots of different books.
I tried lots of different things to try and make Japanese people laugh.
Even working as a dog walker.
I did horrible things like that and...
together with my comedy partner, we'd make just 520 yen each month
which, after tax was 225 yen each.. We had a harsh life like that.
I also had problems, like, not being able to get my visa.
My group's name is Jipangu Jouriku Sakusen,
Means: Japan Disembarkation Strategy
but it almost became Japan Disembarkation Failure.
But I tried, and tried, and finally got the embassy to accept me
and I also finally became able to speak a lot but I recently realised..
...that I used to get more laughs when I spoke more broken Japanese.
I see.
You're too fluent now?
I seee.
My jokes got heaps of laughs back then.
He's saying stuff like "Not knowing right from left"!
Do you know what we call situations like this in Australia?
Nooo we don't.
What?
"It's like, have a look at yourself under the table
you can find some jellybeans there".
And what does that mean?
Have a look at the jellybeans under the table.
Right now, you're a bit like that.
The heck does that mean!?
What does even that mean?
It means you're a useless person.
That's an Australian saying?
Well okay, that was good though.
Well, I don't know if the situation is good but...umm....
Go!
CHIHARA
This is about 10 years or so ago but....
in Osaka there's a downtown nightlife area called Soemoncho and
I went there with a group after work for a meal
and we were walking around there at about 4:00 am
when we heard a lady scream "You freakin' bitch!"
We went to see what it was, and two hostesses were
having a massive fight, but, both of them had
taken off a high heel and....
was yelling, "F**k you bitch!" and attacking each other.
"Sneaky bitch! You stole my customer!"
But since one leg is higher than the other, they both keep spinning around.
I found that sooo funny!
Physics in action, huh.
Ok, here I go.
MATSUMOTO
Ahhh what should I talk about? Ahhh....
I was driving in a car with Imada...
...you know how he likes porn dvd's?
Anyway, he was like "Wanna go to this shop?"
so I said "Yeah, alright", and the outside of the shop was small
but inside, it stretched extremely far out...
...and I was saying "Woaah, the collection here is amazing!".
But I got a huge shock when I went into one of the aisles...
...because there was a corner called "Macchan's Recommendation Corner".
Your first time right?
That was the first time I'd been there!
And they had like a cut out of me stuck there...
...on a spring and it was bobbling from the cooler's breeze!
You've gotta be kidding me!
I totally complained to the shop owner though.
But the products in the corner were some seriously good stuff.
After all.
How dare they just do that though!
MIYAGAWA
Errrr....
This happened when I was in 1st grade of middle school.
I just desperately wanted to touch some breasts.
Well it happens.
I just had to touch breasts no matter what.
And so I came up with an idea...
I have a sister who is 2 years older than me.
So I was like "Fuck it, I'mma touch my sister's boobs".
Maaan, they're all funny, hey?
Urgent announcement!!
Due to rave reviews of Hitoshi Matsumoto's Suberanai Hanashi Episode 1...
we've released the 2nd installment!
For more information, access the shows homepage!
This happened when I was in 1st grade of middle school.
I just desperately wanted to touch some breasts.
Well, it happens.
I really wanted to touch some breasts.
And so, I came up with an idea.
I have a sister who is 2 years older than me.
So I was like "Fuck it, I'mma touch my sister's boobs".
That's desperate.
That's pretty messed up.
So that's what I decided, but...
I can't just go up to her and say "Hey sis, can I touch your boobs?"
There's no choice but to touch them when she's asleep.
Right? And so....
...anyway, my sister went off to have a bath
and it was my chance because mum and dad weren't home that night.
It was just her, me and grandma...
and grandma was in her room, so it was my chance!
After thinking what to do, I decided to lie and wait under my sister's bed.
Eventually, I heard my sister getting out of the bath
and thought "Now's the time!", so
I quickly went over, and slipped under her bed
and breathed quietly as I waited.
Then my sister came up the stairs and...
...was changing into her pajamas or something above me.
But at that point, I had killed my presence.
And was breathing quietly so I don't get caught.
But even though she changed clothes, it takes time before you actually sleep, right?
Reading books and whatnot.
All during that, I was waiting the whole time underneath.
That's amazing, huh?
Then after about 1 hour later...
...I heard some clicking noises, and it became dark.
It might have been a chance, but her sleep wasn't deep enough yet.
So I waited for about 20 minutes more.
After that I decided it was time to get out but
if I made a noise and she heard me, it'd be a disaster so
very slowly.....VERY slowly I....
...spent about 30 minutes to creep out.
How desperately do you wanna touch'em!?
So I got my whole body from underneath the bed...
and then I spent about another 5 minutes to stand.
So my sister was sleeping, and I crept over.
Pretend that's my sister's head.
and I was here hiding and breathing quietly.
But if I just grabbed it suddenly, she'd wake up, right?
So I had to take this slowly, especially since I came this far.
I was wondering what to do but
my sister would breath, and her chest would move as well as her breasts.
Firstly, I realised that I shouldn't disrupt that movement.
If I pressed against the flow and my sister woke up
I'd be in trouble so I first moved in sync with her breath
and went in like this....
My sister didn't wake up. She didn't notice.
I rode that flow for about a minute...
...before I finally went against it.
I went against it.
I was like, "Woah, boobs are so soft!"
But as I thought that, my sister jumped up
and shouted, so I thought "Oh crap"
and there'd be no point making an excuse so I just went straight to my room.
So I went back to my room and was like "Ohhh crap!".
But anyway, I went to sleep thinking "Maybe it'll be ok. Please God, help me!".
The next morning, my mum was home making me breakfast
so I was just eating some bread.
while thinking, "I wonder if mum knows about it yet?"
when my sister suddenly screamed "Waaaahhhh!!".
She came running down from upstairs.
I was thinking "Oh shit, I'm gonna be busted" when she said
"Daisuke! Mum! A ghost appeared yesterday!!".
And my hand holding the bread was just shaking so hard.
"Oh a ghost appeared?"
"Woaah, that's scary"
"That's scary"
and I chucked my bread down
and went to school two buses earlier than usual.
CHAD
My great great great grandfather...
My great great great grandfather was a sheep thief.