THIS PROGRAM WAS PRODUCED UNDER
THE SUPERVISION OF MEDICAL EXPERTS,
TAKING INTO CONSIDERATION THE HEALTH
AND SAFETY OF THE STAFF AND CONTESTANTS.
KITANO
Captain!
Thanks for gathering, brave warriors.
THE CAPTAIN
SUBARU KIMURA
-All right.
-I am your captain, Subaru Kimura.
I love when he says that line.
Our next target is Takeshi Castle's third
fortress, Ichikawa Ennosuke Castle.
THE THIRD CASTLE
ENNOSUKE CASTLE
Many obstacles will stand in our path,
but I believe
that you have it in you
to defeat and conquer.
Let's make it happen!
Fantastic! So you've returned, Mr. Sasuke?
MR. SASUKE
KATSUMI YAMADA (56)
-Yes, here I am.
-Wow, he's 56?
I hate to say this, but...
your track record hasn't been great.
GAMES FAILED: DRAGON GOD'S POND, SLIP-AND-
SLIDE QUIZ, STRONG ARMS, MUSHROOM PLOP
-It wasn't good at all.
-No, not at all.
-I hope you'll score better this time.
-I will.
All right, that's the spirit.
And today, our army goes beyond Japan.
We have warriors
from all over the world, right?
Please raise your hands.
Fantastic!
-From abroad? How lucky are we.
-Wow. That's great.
That's correct. Takeshi's Castle has been
broadcasted in over 150 countries.
We have passionate fans around the world.
This time around, we have
hardcore Takeshi's Castle fans
joining the army from every continent.
You, in the front with the red t-shirt.
Where are you from?
-Technically, the US. Oh, thanks.
-Technically?
-I'm from America.
-America?
How do you feel going into battle?
-I've never been good at sports, but...
-Okay.
-My determination is limitless. Let's go!
-Right!
-He's fluent.
-Your Japanese is excellent.
-Would you prefer English?
-That's all right.
Additionally, the army will have support
from a few star players.
They'll attempt to conquer Ennosuke Castle
with their powers combined.
-We have a superstar among us.
-A superstar?
GOLDEN BOMBER
YUTAKA KYAN (37)
Oh, it's Kyan.
-You there. Aren't you Kyan?
-That's me.
-I've performed at Kohaku four times.
-Wow, how cool.
I usually only accept TV gigs
with my bandmate, Darvish.
But today, I came to hog the spotlight.
Wonderful.
Let's go.
I hope you can work as a team. Sound good?
Let's go!
-Nice.
-Everyone is pumped.
Well now, everyone, our first challenge is
The Border Wall.
I want every one of you
to get to the other side.
Now, charge!
Wow! Amazing.
Gather round,
elite warriors!
THE YEAR 1986
Charge!
In 1986, a colossal battle broke loose.
THE IMPENETRABLE CASTLE
A castle so impenetrable,
only 8 out of
127 battles have ever seen its halls.
8 WINS, 118 LOSSES, 1 DRAW
WIN RATE 6%
That dreadful castle has reemerged
in the Land of the Rising Sun.
JAPAN
RESURRECTION
THE YEAR 2023
Charge!
Takeshi's Castle is back!
Fortified with extravagance and fortitude,
packed with new games,
it's the palace of your dreams!
WHO WILL EMERGE
AS THE BOLDEST WARRIOR?
NO TIME TO FEAR
I'll bring justice upon you numbskulls!
Have a look and see for yourself.
TAKE NO PRISONERS
Victory is ours!
I'm gutted!
Tear it down
to take home...
ONE MILLION YEN
I will destroy you!
I made it!
Here we go!
Fall, fall till you can fall no further.
Struggle as you may,
he has you in the palm of his hand.
DANCE...
The man of the hour
that you've all waited for...
IN THE PALM OF HIS HAND
ARMY VS TAKESHI
Takeshi's Castle!
TAKESHI'S CASTLE
This great battle to overthrow
Takeshi's Castle is the first in 34 years.
Among the three fortresses
that protect Takeshi's Castle,
there first was Ueda Castle
and then Watanabe Castle.
The army had fought tirelessly,
but were decimated
by Takeshi's army in the end.
The enemy they'll face
in this battle is Ennosuke Castle.
On the way, there are seven strongholds
that are meant
to prevent the army from advancing.
BATTLE OF THE THIRD CASTLE
FOREIGN FORCES HAVE ARRIVED
The battle to overthrow
the third castle begins now.
Rumbling onto the battlegrounds
like blustering winds are
powerful warriors that were carefully
selected for this mission.
The army consists of about 104 warriors.
Most of them are
in their teens and twenties.
We have a young infantry on our hands.
Additionally, it's a diverse group
of warriors, who have been strategizing
on how to defeat the castle
from across the ocean.
We're coming for you!
THE THIRD CASTLE
ENNOSUKE CASTLE
TAKESHI'S CASTLE CHIEF &amp; LIEGE
OSAMU SHITARA &amp; YUKI HIMURA
-Here we are in the third castle.
-All right.
-Huh?
-The lord of the castle isn't here.
-You're right. I wonder...
-He's gone. What's happened?
-My Lord?
-My Lord!
Whoa.
My Lord?
-I rushed over from another gig.
-I see.
I'm Ennosuke Ichikawa.
Introducing, Lord of the Third Castle,
Ennosuke Ichikawa.
THE THIRD CASTLE LORD
ENNOSUKE ICHIKAWA
Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you, too.
-Please have a seat.
So, Lord Ennosuke,
welcome to Takeshi's Castle.
-I grew up watching this show.
-I imagine.
Is there any game you remember?
First, there's that wall you climb.
THE BORDER WALL
-I remember Dragon God's Pond...
-Yes.
-...and also Strong Kongo.
-Very good.
That's where he chased after you.
There's one where they threw
volleyballs at you.
-You remember lots of them.
-Of course.
THE 7 STRONGHOLDS
OF ENNOSUKE CASTLE
We'll see many of those nostalgic games.
Nice, I can't wait.
At the moment, it just so happens
that the count has gone MIA.
-He's disappeared?
-Exactly.
But have no worries. We've gathered
all of our technology know-how
-and put together an AI count.
-Nice, an AI count.
-Shall we summon him?
-Sure.
-Good morning. I'm Koji Higashino.
-Here we go, another impersonation.
-Good morning...
-That's not how you talk.
-Pardon me, my mistake.
-Come on, Count!
-The AI is out of control.
-That's not who you are.
-Nice to meet you.
-There's our count.
-This is exciting.
-Well, now,
there's an unruly gang
who's trying to bring down this castle.
-Let's bring them to their knees.
-Agreed, we won't let
-a single person near the castle gates.
-That's right. Great plan.
-There is no way I'll lose!
-All right, that's the spirit.
Okay, everyone, our first challenge is
The Border Wall.
I want everyone to get to the other side.
THE BORDER WALL
DIFFICULTY RATING: 15%
-I'll let them get by.
-Don't you dare.
TAKESHI'S ARMY, DUO TOM BROWN
MICHIO &amp; HIROKI NUNOKAWA
-I meant, I won't.
-There you go.
We'll make it to the end!
We will invade the castle!
All right.
Charge!
-Wow!
-Great!
GET OVER THE WALL
WITHIN FIVE MINUTES
The battle has now officially begun.
The first challenge is The Border Wall.
In the battles of the 1st and 2nd castle,
not everyone made it over the wall.
Let's hope that the entire army
can make it over this time.
Good job, everyone. Stay calm.
REPORTER, NASUNAKANISHI DUO
SHIGEKI NAKANISHI
Bustling sound. Wow, they're already here.
REPORTER, NASUNAKANISHI DUO
AKIYUKI NASU
They're fast. And relentless.
The opponent is trying to blind us.
-Congrats! Well done.
-Yay!
INTERNET ENTERTAINER, USA
AJ ERENDS (33)
Should I speak in Japanese?
I did it! I defeated it!
Good job.
HOKKAIDO UNIVERSITY GRAD STUDENTS
FRANZISKA HEUMANN (29)
&amp; IVAN BALLIANA (23)
That was fun.
While some warriors jubilantly celebrated
their success in getting over the wall...
3 MINUTES REMAINING
-...some continued to struggle.
-Nice, good job.
Take that. And that.
I won't let you through.
Don't underestimate Japan.
-No, he fell.
-There he goes.
It's going up my crotch. My crotch!
Oh no! You have to protect your groin.
That's dangerous.
-Bring your leg up.
-People are helping others up.
1 MINUTE REMAINING
7 WARRIORS LEFT
7 warriors remain.
Come on, everyone.
They're helping each other.
Come on. He's so cool.
-Help each other.
-Go!
-Wow.
-Fantastic!
-That's great.
-Go, go!
Oh no!
I'm sure he hurt his butt.
Just one person left. You got this!
Time is almost up.
-He's running out of time.
-Don't give up!
30 SECONDS REMAINING
ONE WARRIOR LEFT
The army is one person away
from saving the whole group.
Everyone is helping.
Even Yamada, aka Mr. Sasuke, who only
assisted women in the previous battle.
He's not leaving anyone behind this round.
-He's letting them pull him up.
-Keep going!
Yes!
-They all made it.
-The whole group?
Fantastic!
You were a lifesaver, Mr. Sasuke.
Awesome!
NO WARRIOR LEFT BEHIND
-Everyone got over.
-Everyone.
The whole army made it. Amazing job.
Well, they can have this one.
-Really?
-It's fine.
107 WARRIORS REMAIN
Third times a charm. The entire army
makes it over The Border Wall.
This gives us hope for their chances
of overthrowing the castle.
In this battle, the road ahead forks
into four different directions.
The warriors are given the choice
to compete in the task they feel adept in.
-Wow. They chose cooperation.
-Yes. What did you think, Lord Ennosuke?
-The more enemies, the merrier.
-Well, it's only the first stage.
We'll let them have it out of generosity.
-It'll keep them spry.
-This group has good teamwork.
We have many warriors participating
from abroad this time.
Our show broadcasted overseas,
-so most of them are fans.
-Right.
-I'm sure they're elated to be here.
-I agree.
-It's lots of fun after all.
-Yes, let's see what's next.
-Coming up, we have a new game.
-A new game?
-It's called From Right and Left.
-From Right and Left?
AVOID THE BARS THAT STICK OUT
TO GET ACROSS THE BRIDGE
-It'll make sense once you see it.
-From Right and Left.
First, let's take a look at the test run.
TEST PLAYER
TOSHIAKI KASUGA, COMIC
Look, it's Kasuga.
-What's up, everyone?
-Why so loud?
There he goes with that bit again.
Pardon me while I take care of this.
-If he doesn't make it, most people won't.
-You're right.
-I get it now.
-They have to walk across fabric.
-The footing is wobbly.
-I see.
And you have to avoid those bars
from both sides.
-It got him.
-Oh no.
He fell almost instantly.
Damn it!
Damn it.
This is impossible.
The entire army will fail in this round.
-No one will make it.
-There's no stability.
-Wow... it might be impossible.
-Are you sure about this?
No one will make it to the castle.
You've made this game too difficult.
-Okay. Well...
-Isn't that great?
Even the Shanghai Circus acrobats
couldn't pull that off.
-I agree.
-That might be true.
The water underneath is murky,
so we might lose some people if they fall.
I'm pretty sure we'll find them.
At the battles of the second castle,
General Tani was kidnapped by
Kyoko Hamaguchi from Takeshi's army.
He somehow escaped
by the skin of his teeth and is back,
ready to command
the army through battle once again.
Great job making it past The Border Wall,
brave warriors.
GENERAL
HAYATO TANI
-It's General Tani.
-Amazing job. Not to change the subject.
-He's finally back.
-But have you seen this guy in black garb?
It's similar to what I have on,
holding a whistle and yelling "Charge."
CAPTAIN KIMURA IS HAVING A NAP
You saw him? But you can't express
anything beyond body language.
-That's too bad.
-What's going on?
-How are you? You there.
-I'm good.
DATA SCIENTIST, UK
JULIAN ONYALI (38)
-Where are you from? Nerima?
-From Nerima.
-Nerima!
-What?
-Which country are you from?
-I'm from England.
-England?
-Yes.
What made you want
to come to Takeshi's Castle?
-I used to watch it in the UK.
-Really?
-They watch it over there.
-Maybe I should work overseas.
Takeshi's Castle has a great reputation.
The game you'll be competing in is called
From Right and Left. It's a new game.
-True to its name.
-You're done if those get you.
I can't say much about it,
but I believe you can beat it.
I want everyone to try their best.
Sound good?
-All right.
-Oh well.
Charge!
REPORTER, NASUNAKANISHI DUO
AKIYUKI NASU
From Right and Left will keep you
on the edge of your seat.
The Takeshi's goon who will
command this game is...
TAKESHI'S ARMY
YOSHIAKI UMEGAKI, COMIC
-It's Umegaki.
-Nice.
That's nasty. I feel like you blew out
more than a bean from there.
-And here's another secret weapon.
-Hey! Come on!
Here he comes. Why is he acting so cocky?
TAKESHI'S ARMY
TOSHIAKI KASUGA, COMIC
This is no surprise. He was already
introduced in the test run.
Hurry up and do it. Hurry.
It's too hot for this.
-What's up, everyone?
-He's facing the wrong way.
-Turn around.
-What's the point of this?
FROM RIGHT AND LEFT
DIFFICULTY RATING: 97%
Charge!
-So Kasuga gets to aim that.
-Okay.
EX SPANISH EMBASSY EMPLOYEE, SPAIN
ALVARO CAMACHO CRIADO (27)
-Here he comes.
-You got this!
-I'm strong!
-Spain.
CROSS THE BRIDGE WHILE
AVOIDING THE BARS TO WIN
-He shouldn't hurry.
-Slow down.
That was dangerous.
-They come at you from both sides.
-That was dangerous.
-That's risky.
-Only at Takeshi's Castle.
SUPPORT ENGINEER, SPAIN
ERICA MARTINEZ (30)
-I'll try my best!
-Good luck. Come on.
-Okay.
-You got this, Erica.
-She's fast.
-Doing good.
-Now she's taking her time.
-She's doing great.
-Nice.
DATA SCIENTIST, UK
JULIAN ONYALI (38)
I'll do my best.
OPERATOR OF THE BARS
Come and get it.
Kasuga prepares to welcome him to battle.
-Here come the bubbles.
-Maybe he should crouch down.
There's not much space
between the red and blue bars.
-Bubbles...
-Oh, dear.
He tried crouching,
then it hit his face. Smack dab.
He ducks and tries to avoid the blue bar
and is taken out from the other side.
This is the horror of the new game,
From Right and Left.
-Please cheer for me.
-The next warrior...
PROFESSOR TAKESHI'S CASTLE
...to take on this demanding challenge is
a diehard fan of Takeshi's Castle,
Joshua Murphy from America.
A diehard fan?
TAKESHI'S CASTLE
THE SCRIPT
-He owns a rare collection of scripts...
-The original?
...and jackets only given to production
crew members, among other things.
-How does he find them?
-On top of that,
he's memorized events
from all 133 past episodes.
Joshua is absolutely obsessed
with Takeshi's Castle.
JOSHUA LOVES TAKESHI'S CASTLE
-Can you pick a random number?
-23.
It's episode 23.
The Border Wall, The Devil's Domain,
and Dragon God's Pond. Then, Ball Run...
Surprisingly, he can recall
every game that was played
in an episode that was chosen at random.
SWAPPING NOTES WITH TAKESHI'S CASTLE'S
MUSEUM MANAGER, MAEJIMA
Upon learning that his beloved show
was making a comeback,
Joshua fulfilled his lifelong dream
of competing in Takeshi's Castle.
He boarded a plane for the first time
in his life to come to Japan.
RODE HIS FIRST EVER PLANE TO COME TO JAPAN
DIEHARD FAN OF TAKESHI'S CASTLE
JOSHUA MURPHY (31)
-He must be elated.
-I bet.
-This is the highlight of his life.
-With his know-how, he might make it.
Oh no, it's not safe. Be careful.
It's too funny.
That was too funny.
Why do they keep being smacked
in the face before falling?
Takeshi's Castle is painful.
-It was worth waiting for 34 years.
-Wow.
Just then, a superstar walked
onto the scene to support our army.
-Oh, I'm so nervous.
-Hey, it's JP. It's Matsumoto.
CELEBRITY IMPERSONATOR
JP (39)
I was told that I was doing
a different show.
But this is none other than
Takeshi's Castle.
-Wow, Matsumoto came to Takeshi's Castle.
-Seriously.
Hito-hito-hitoshi!
ARMY'S SUPPORT WARRIOR
CELEBRITY IMPERSONATOR, JP (39)
Look, it's Matsumoto.
Matsumoto,
are you up for this kind of program?
JP was supposed to be here today,
but he has other work,
so I'm here as his replacement.
-That would never happen. Never.
-Is that so?
Let's do this. Watch Hitoshi go!
-Good luck.
-Oh no.
I hope he gets past at least one bar.
Whoa, I have to be careful.
-Hang in there.
-JP might be too cautious?
That's good. Okay.
-Good job.
-Keep it up. Oh no.
He went out exactly like we wanted him to.
-How did he not see that coming?
-It was obvious.
-It was right in front of his face.
-Exactly. How?
I was walking...Then suddenly
I'm spinning and splash!
-That's a good impersonation.
-Thanks.
MR. SASUKE
KATSUMI YAMADA (56)
-I think walking like this...
-Meanwhile, the Sasuke legend
was figuring out how to make
a successful comeback.
TEAM YAMADA'S ACE PLAYER
YOSHIYUKI YAMAMOTO (29)
-It makes you stop...
-The guy next to Yamada is very sharp.
-Apparently, that's his best pupil.
-Got it.
This familiar face is our next challenger.
BACK FROM BATTLES AT THE 2ND CASTLE
CHIITAN, ETERNALLY 0 YRS OLD
-It's Chiitan.
-There's no way Chiitan will make it.
Great. I see that you're pumped, Chiitan.
Chiitan, you got this!
-That fabric is not wide enough for her.
-You're right.
-This is a crapshoot.
-How risky.
-This is a crapshoot. There's no way--
-Chiitan...
-Chiitan, your neck...
-Why, Chiitan...
Come on, come on. You're doing great.
INTERNET ENTERTAINER, USA
AJ ERENDS (33)
This new game, From Right and Left,
is giving the army
-a run for their money.
-This is fun to watch.
OWNER OF CAR REPAIR BUSINESS
TORU TANIOKA (60)
-Nonetheless, the daring army...
-Wow.
TRANSLATOR, PERU
DAVID RAMIREZ (30)
...continues to give its best effort.
EX BUS DRIVER
KEIZO NAGAO (60)
PAINT CONTRACTOR
SHUNJI SAKAGUCHI (60)
PRODUCTION RESEARCHER
TAKAZUMI TAMIYA (32)
EX SPANISH EMBASSY EMPLOYEE, SPAIN
MARC AURA RODRIGO (22)
GOLDEN BOMBER
YUTAKA KYAN (37)
Here we go!
We are...Tokyo Theater Girls!
-We're here to win.
-Yay!
The next warriors are...
Mixing together theater and idol-dom,
Tokyo Theater Girls is
a group of performers
who can all act, sing, and dance.
-All right, let's go!
-Yeah!
Charge!
TOKYO THEATER GIRLS
SHION IIZUKA (23)
I'm Shion. Let's get the party started!
She's fast. Look at her go.
Go, Shion!
-Girls are lighter, so they fly further.
-She was blown aside.
I think the red bar got her.
-It got her like, thump!
-Yeah.
One light push and she flew, like "Shoo!"
TOKYO THEATER GIRLS
MONE FUKUSHIMA (25)
After that, the girls continued to push on
with their youth and vigor.
TOKYO THEATER GIRLS
NAGI RINNO (24)
YUI CHITOSE (23)
One by one, they make
a flashy display of falling,
but each time,
they make it a little further.
She was doing so well.
TOKYO THEATER GIRLS
RISA OKUMA (22)
In the end, they hang their hopes
on their youngest member, Okuma.
-You got this.
-Let's go!
THE GROUP'S PRODUCER
KAZUHIRO SHIMOMURA
-Good luck!
-I promise I won't fall.
-You got this!
-Good luck!
-Charge!
-You got this!
Let's go.
No one has more energy than me!
I'll try my best!
-Use that energy. Make it happen.
-You got this!
-I think she can do it.
-Use all that energy.
-Okay, good.
-Advancing too quickly isn't good either.
See, she's skinny,
so she can wait between the bars.
You got this, Okuma.
-Look, she's got the hang of it.
-She might make it.
-Hang in there. She has...
-She's figured it out.
-Yes! She's going to make it.
-Yeah!
You got this. You got it!
-Here come the bubbles!
-You can do it!
-You did it!
-He's been waiting at the end?
-Awesome!
-I did it! I made it to the end!
Hurrah!
-You managed to wait between bars.
-Yes, I ran up to them and then waited.
-That's amazing.
-Look, fits like a puzzle.
-That's the tactic I used.
-And it worked beautifully.
-Yes, I'm so happy. Thank you!
-Congrats!
-Thank you!
-Well done. Fantastic.
Only two warriors remain.
It's finally time
for these two to shoot their shot.
Katsumi Yamada, aka Mr. Sasuke,
couldn't redeem himself
during the battles at the first castle.
Now he's back to try again
along with his sharpest pupil.
He knows what to expect now.
-This time I'll win and prove myself.
-You hear that?
We came shouldering the weight
of these titles on our chests.
We won't go quietly without a fight.
Yamada's back is against the wall
and he can't afford to lose.
The person he brought
to bolster him this time is...
-He's from Black Tigers.
-It's him.
Black Tigers is a fitness group
that Yamada mentors,
and Yoshiyuki Yamamoto
is the best of that crew.
-He's fantastic.
-In the Sasuke race,
he was the first to reach the finals
since the formation of the group.
He is Yamada's
most highly regarded protégé.
He's the best we've got
and is not to be underestimated.
THE BEST OF BLACK TIGERS
YOSHIYUKI YAMAMOTO (29)
Will he be able to live up
to Yamada's high expectations?
You got this!
-Here he comes.
-Good luck.
-Go, but take your time.
-Look how wobbly it is.
-Take your time.
Wait... Really?
Lame. That was lame.
He got ahead of himself,
lost balance and fell.
Yamamoto, the brightest pupil
of Katsumi Yamada...
Things didn't work out for him
like they did for Sasuke.
ONE WARRIOR REMAINING
Only one person has made it past
this stage.
Here to close out this round
is this legend.
Why is this so difficult?
I want to run through it
and get as far as I can.
-I see.
-Approaching it slowly is not my style.
-I'll use momentum.
-Like always.
MR. SASUKE
KATSUMI YAMADA (56)
-Here goes nothing.
-He's up. Go, Yamada.
Bring it on, Mr. Sasuke.
I've been waiting.
He's being cautious. Very cautious.
-Oh no.
-He's wobbling.
-This won't do.
-He can't afford to end there.
-He doesn't care.
-It's like he was walking the plank.
-What was that?
-What's the point?
What a pitiful way to go.
Seemingly prompted by nothing,
he immediately loses balance.
Then he plunges straight into the water
with an awkward plop.
Another unfortunate outcome
following his disaster in Strong Arms.
-I thought we'd have more fun with him...
-Me, too.
-That wasn't like him.
-That was quick even for Mr. Sasuke.
You couldn't get very far.
Yeah... I barely moved an inch, honestly.
-You were barely out the gate.
-I think so, too.
I couldn't make my mark once again.
ONE WARRIOR REMAINS
Only one warrior makes it past
From Right and Left.
-Only one?
-One warrior?
I hope the warriors charging the other
three strongholds are doing a better job.
Only one warrior?
Only one warrior made it out
of From Right and Left.
Everyone won in the first game
and now there's only one. Just one.
What did you think, my lord?
I hope they've realized how strong we are.
We let them have the first game.
Then we kicked them off their stool.
Why did we go from easy straight to
final boss level and nothing in between?
Let's see what the AI count thought.
AI Count!
That girl had the right idea
waiting between the bars.
-Okuma, was it?
-The one with boundless energy.
The entertainment industry works
in the same way.
You have to slide into open doors
before they close.
-Is that so?
-You have to slide in where you can.
-When you really think about it--
-Goodbye now.
-Our next game is Mushroom Plop.
-Classic.
GRAB HOLD OF THE MUSHROOM
AND LAND ON THE FLOATING ISLAND
We've seen it once.
Himura has already tried it.
-Yes, I did a test run.
-Really?
I tried grabbing onto it and
I couldn't even hold myself there.
-You couldn't get on to begin with?
-Yes, so I gave up.
That's how that went.
-It ended before you could start.
-Correct.
So I think this is going to give them
a hard time, too.
This will be the second appearance
of Mushroom Plop since Ueda Castle.
Most of the army met the fate
of being plunged into the pool,
but three brave warriors
won in that round.
However, this game has since been
modified to be harder.
REPORTER, NASUNAKANISHI DUO
SHIGEKI NAKANISHI
I, Nakanishi, will be reporting
for Mushroom Plop.
-What is this? Water?
-Who's attacking?
TAKESHI'S ARMY, DUO TOM BROWN
MICHIO &amp; HIROKI NUNOKAWA
Are you in charge of the hose this time?
-Yes, and we won't make it easy.
-What?
Watch this!
Help me!
MUSHROOM PLOP
DIFFICULTY RATING: 95%
This time, many of the global warriors
will try their hand at Mushroom Plop.
So we decided to host...
The Mushroom Plop World Cup Series.
ANNOUNCER
SHINYA SUGIYAMA FROM TBS
Will these brave warriors
and beloved fans of Takeshi's Castle
be able to defeat the formidable opponent
that is Mushroom Plop?
The Mushroom Plop World Cup Series
is finally under way.
HOKKAIDO UNIVERSITY GRADUATE STUDENT
FRANZISKA HEUMANN
Franziska Heumann, representing Germany.
Last April, she came to Japan
to attend Hokkaido University.
She enjoys kayaking and is confident
in her balancing capabilities.
Charge!
-Standing at 5'8" tall.
-I got this. I think.
HUG THE MUSHROOM AND LAND ON THE ISLAND
She was a fan of the show back in Germany.
-She could just fall, but it spins.
-Will she make it?
She's spinning quickly. She spins out
of control and slides off.
She spins out of control, slides off
and takes the plunge.
It's all about centrifugal force.
The key is to let go sooner
than you think.
Exactly. That's the trick.
The mushroom is spinning.
Her legs miss the island.
She slides into the water,
still spinning from the momentum.
MISSION FAILED
I was a little nervous.
-But it was lots of fun.
-That's good.
HOKKAIDO UNIVERSITY GRADUATE STUDENT
IVAN BALLIANA
Ivan Balliana, representing Italy.
He's proud of his pizza baking skills.
Will he reward himself
with a mushroom pizza party if he wins?
Allelomou!
-Ivan Balliana is off to the races.
-Go! Ivan! Go!
He's being hosed down. Can Ivan handle it?
Oh no, he takes the plunge.
-Here we go. Get it.
-No, too soon.
-I think the water made him slip.
-Got it.
He fell a good distance before the island.
An unexpected fall.
Was Tom Brown's water attack
too much for him?
Ivan Balliana falls well
before the target,
not even grazing its shiny, red surface.
MISSION FAILED
It was very difficult.
That was a good try.
SPORTS MANAGER
MANGO AMER
-Mango Amer, representing Jordan.
-All right!
He holds a black belt in judo.
Today, he's wearing his uniform.
Charge!
-Here I go!
-You got this!
He remembers watching Takeshi's Castle
as a kid in Jordan.
His special talent is that he can play
"Nada Soso". Mango Amer, will he make it?
There he goes, taking a dynamic plunge!
He falls into the pool,
spraying water in every direction.
Mango Amer clung tightly to the mushroom,
only to let go a little too late.
He may have made it if he'd let go sooner.
MISSION FAILED
I swallowed so much water.
SPANISH LANGUAGE TEACHER
DIANA HERRAIZ (34)
Mushroom Plop has been made harder
by adding the hosing attacks.
MISSION FAILED
Diana Herraiz, representing Spain
was up for the next round...
TECH COMPANY EMPLOYEE, SPAIN
JAVIER SÁNCHEZ DELGADO (31)
...followed by another Spanish warrior,
Javier Sánchez Delgado.
Two back-to-back losses.
Sadly, both failed.
No one could beat the new
and improved Mushroom Plop.
Only one international warrior remained.
MISSION FAILED
They're still letting go far too late.
They have to aim earlier.
TOHOKU UNIVERSITY GRADUATE STUDENT
DÁITHÍ Ó HAODHA
Dáithí Ó hAodha, representing Ireland.
Arriving in Japan four years ago, he's now
a graduate student at Tohoku University.
HAODHA'S GIRLFRIEND OF 5 YEARS
MIE SHIMBAYASHI (30)
-Good luck!
-You got this!
He and his girlfriend, Mie, both
came to compete at Takeshi's Castle.
He's trilingual in English, Japanese,
and Irish. Can he make it?
-And he slips!
-How could he not?
He had a good grip on the mushroom,
but he slipped.
He tries to grab hold of the island,
but could not stick a landing.
-We did nice work!
-The hosing attack has proven effective.
He was spinning before reaching
the target, the red island.
He landed on the island,
but couldn't manage to stay on it.
MISSION FAILED
I'm in despair. Seriously.
So far, six international warriors
have tried and none have succeeded.
Next, the Japanese warriors are up.
Here at The Mushroom Plop World Series,
it is now time for Japan
to make an appearance.
JAPAN'S EX SOCCER LEAGUE PLAYERS
MASAYUKI OKANO, SHOJI JO, YOSHITO OKUBO
Hailing from the Japanese
national soccer team,
these three legends are here
to joins us today.
-Really? They'll try it?
-What a glamorous cast.
Team Japan has gained
some powerful reinforcement.
In a last minute decision, we now have
warriors from the actual World Cup games.
They're legendary strikers who have
competed on the global stage,
and now they're at Takeshi's Castle
to land a perfect goal.
Wow, that's Okano.
EX NATIONAL LEAGUE SOCCER PLAYER
MASAYUKI OKANO
I don't care if he's a national hero
or whatever. He's going down.
Only one of us gets to have
luscious locks.
You should cut yours.
Let's go!
Also known as the Delight of Johor Bahru.
It's Okano, who scored the magic goal
taking Japan to the World Cup in France.
-That's amazing.
-Let's hope he takes home another win.
-Looking good.
-Will he bring uproarious joy once again?
The water has him spinning. Okano spins.
Can he make it? He plunges in head first.
-Wow. He had great aim, as expected.
-Masayuki Okano!
He makes a flashy splash as he falls
head first with legs spread wide.
The support warrior falls dynamically.
He falls from the Delight of Johor Bahru
into the pit of the Mushroom Tragedy.
MISSION FAILED
He slips and disappears.
-It's too funny not to laugh.
-I'm bummed.
You went down as if you were hit
by a ball from behind.
I thought I would land perfectly.
He's got a good sense of balance
even while spinning.
-I think so, too.
-It looks like the key is
-to fall forward once you let go.
-I agree.
I hate to say this,
but Jo has gained weight.
EX NATIONAL LEAGUE SOCCER PLAYER
SHOJI JO
Let go earlier than you think you should.
Keep your face
to the right while you're spinning.
Interesting.
-Jo, formerly representing Japan. Now 47.
-Go!
-Go, Jo! You can do it!
-He retired in 2006.
Jo, Jo!
Seventeen years since his retirement,
Shoji Jo is now at Takeshi's Castle.
Shoji Jo. Can he do it?
Can he hit the target?
-He plunges, back first.
-It's just too slippery.
Shoji Jo. He slipped and fell.
We did the same exact thing.
Jo is spinning. Is he too heavy?
He disappeared as if he was
being sucked into the water.
VIEWS OF OKANO VS JO
This made me more nervous
than the French World Cup.
-Really?
-Way more.
MISSION FAILED
That's what athletes tend to say.
-There's no way that's true.
-Exactly.
EX NATIONAL LEAGUE SOCCER PLAYER
YOSHITO OKUBO
-He only recently retired.
-True.
-You can't let go as easily as you think.
-No.
So let go completely and try to land
on your back.
-Okay. You think?
-You won't make it front facing.
You want to land on your back?
-He said so, didn't he?
-Yeah.
Representing Japan in the last round
of Mushroom Plop,
is our hopeful warrior, Yoshito Okubo.
Can he prove his worth
as an ancillary warrior?
-Yoshito!
-The crowd is cheering for him.
The last of three warriors to represent
Japan. He retired from soccer in 2021.
Top scorer, Okubo.
There he goes! And he slips!
-Did he make it?
-Was that a fail?
It's a fail.
He landed firmly on his back. But...
-Wow. That was close.
-So close.
He was close.
For a moment, we thought he'd made it.
Okubo's timing was perfect.
He lands firm and tries to stick
the landing by raising his legs.
MISSION FAILED
-But is dragged into the water.
-What a great try.
-You were so close. You were.
-Wasn't I? I made it onto the target.
What happened after I landed?
In soccer, the ball hit
the goal post and flew outside.
Oh no... People would have words for me.
This concludes
The Mushroom Plop World Cup Series.
The new and improved version
is now mind-blowingly difficult.
Will there be another warrior
to defeat it?
HOUSEWIFE
YUKIKO MATSUOKA
DOCTOR
ATSUSHI MATSUOKA (47)
GOLDEN BOMBER
YUTAKA KYAN (37)
Good try.
ANIMATOR
CHANG SHIN YUAN (31)
Why is he pulling her out like that?
Hang in there.
COLLEGE STUDENT
YUITA (19)
-Hang in there.
-Wow!
GRADUATE STUDENT
MIE SHIMBAYASHI (30)
She's taking too long. Let go.
BAND BOYS AND MEN TRAINEE
TAICHI UTSUMI (21)
So close!
The next warrior to face the new
and improved Mushroom Plop is...
In his third year of middle school,
he was the Nagano Prefecture Champion
in the 100-meter track and field event.
Haru Yamaguchi is currently a high school
student and an athlete in his prime.
CURRENTLY IN HIGH SCHOOL
HARU YAMAGUCHI (16)
My parents loved this show as kids
and I wanted to try it.
HIS SPECIAL SKILL IS ACROBATICS
During breaks, he warms up
with his favorite acrobatic moves
and watches past episodes
with his father for research.
FATHER - MINORU
He's done everything he can
to prepare for battle.
I'll beat this. Please root for me.
-I got this!
-Go get em'.
Will this youngster be the first
to beat the game?
-He might make it.
-I think so, too.
Grab it!
-He might make it.
-I think so, too.
Grab it, grab it!
Stay there. Don't slip. He did it!
He made it! Awesome!
Isn't it great to be young?
He took aim from a spinning mushroom
and landed beautifully.
A high school student, Haru Yamaguchi,
is the first warrior to beat the game!
He's awesome.
-Congrats. How was it?
-Thanks. Piece of cake.
-Easy peasy?
-Totally.
-You landed perfectly.
-Yeah, didn't I?
It's great to be young.
He doesn't mince his words.
What a great age.
Following that success...
HUGE FAN OF EISAKU YOSHIDA
RYOTA YOSHIDA (18)
Ryota Yoshida, who loves the actor,
Eisaku Yoshida, also beat the game.
-Wow. He landed and didn't move.
-And now two warriors have won.
Go, Yoshi!
-Fantastic!
-I feel great.
-Was it easy for you? Okay.
-So-so.
Two warriors beat Mushroom Plop, one
of the most difficult tasks for the army.
Go forth and overthrow Ennosuke Castle!
-We have two warriors remaining.
-Only two. Two people.
There was one warrior last time
and now two?
-How did this happen?
-This is a record.
Now we'll host the consolation games.
-Since we lost most of the army. Right.
-Yeah, down to three. Yeah.
We feel sorry for them.
Is it okay to let them play?
That's fine. Let them think we have mercy.
We'll give them some hope
and devastate them later.
I like that idea.
SIGN-UP FOR CONSOLATION GAMES HERE
Warriors who failed will randomly
be allocated to one of three games.
If you win,
you'll be able to return to the frontline.
You will compete
in the Slip-and-Slide Quiz.
Good luck!
That person was all business.
She couldn't cheer me on or anything?
TOKYO THEATER GIRLS
NAGI RINNO (24)
-I'll catch it. Let's go.
-She's from Tokyo Theater Girls.
You have to catch the ball
that you launched in this one.
At this point, you can't see it,
so you have to rely on your teammates.
Right. So if your buddies... Wait.
-Good try.
-I wanted her to dive face first.
-In the center.
-The center!
-Everyone tries to help.
-Then they dive.
-So close.
-The position was right.
I don't want to get muddy like that.
They supplied some good quality mud.
It's hard to get it to stick
to your face like that.
Now, the Slip-and-Slide Quiz.
-Question.
-You got this.
JULIANA NO TATARI
GINTARO YAJIMA (36)
-When is the Japanese holiday, Dog Day?
-Commit to an answer.
-A. January 11th.
-Okay.
B. November 1st.
-Dog Day is a holiday?
-Which one is it?
-Don't goof off.
-We need an answer, not a performance.
Dog Day?
-Come on, hurry!
-Yajima!
-It's B!
-Go!
CORRECT ANSWER
B: NOVEMBER 1ST.
-Oh no...
-How could you get that wrong?
-I chose C.
-It's Tug-of-War or Splash.
TAKESHI'S ARMY
TOHRU ONOJIMA &amp; KOSHIHIKARI MOCHIDA
-Hey, it's them.
-Now, for a special rule.
I thought it was someone else.
I'm Kato-pan, the news anchor.
Start the Music Festival!
-Kakenukete Keitora is the duo.
-Let's begin.
-He won't win.
-Ready, go!
There's no way... Wow! Be careful!
The winner, Takeshi's army.
Sorry! You're in last place.
-Did you think he'd fly that far?
-There's no way he could win.
DIEHARD FAN OF TAKESHI'S CASTLE, USA
JOSHUA MURPHY (31)
Hey, it's Murphy.
-Next up, he flew in just for this event.
-Good luck.
It's Takeshi's Castle's diehard fan,
Joshua Murphy.
-Hurry, hurry.
-Can he make it back to battle?
-Hurry. Get down there!
-He's too slow.
You'd better hurry.
-Come, diehard fan.
-Good catch!
It seemed he had caught the ball at first.
But the ball bounced back out when he
hit the ground. A painful mistake.
FIGHTING SPIRIT AWARD IS GIVEN TO PEOPLE
WITH NEAR WINS OR WHO TRIED THEIR HARDEST
EVEN AFTER FAILING, YOU CAN MOVE
TO THE NEXT ROUND
But he's given the Fighting Spirit Award
for coming so close.
Good luck in your next game, Joshua!
GOLDEN BOMBER
YUTAKA KYAN (37)
I made it here purely by luck.
I hope luck earns me a win.
-Let's go!
-Good luck, Kyan!
Which historical period lasted longer?
-A. Edo period.
-I don't know either.
-B. Heian period.
-Is it B?
CORRECT ANSWER
B. HEIAN PERIOD
RETURNS TO BATTLE
-He did it. He's back in the game.
-Well done!
BACK FROM BATTLE 1 &amp; 2
CHIITAN (ETERNALLY 0 YEARS OLD)
-Chiitan.
-We hadn't seen her in a while.
TAKESHI'S ARMY
DONGURI TAKESHI
-Thanks for coming.
-Good luck, Chiitan!
Chiitan! I'll eat you like string cheese.
He's that solo act guy.
-Come and get it, then.
-Chiitan is ready to fight.
Ready, go!
-Chiitan is strong. Hold on.
-She's that strong?
Chiitan has muscles.
-Beware of Chiitan.
-Oh no, Chiitan...
Oh no, Chiitan... What are you doing?
RETURNS TO BATTLE
With an unexpected comeback,
Chiitan is headed back to battle.
-Brilliant job!
-Chiitan is back in the game.
-I have a thought about Chiitan.
-Yes?
Couldn't they change the person inside
to suit the game?
True. That is an option.
Has the same person played Chiitan
this whole time?
I don't think so. The Chiitan we just saw
is someone we've never seen.
I guess they're cheating.
This version was way too strong.
-Well, she's back in now.
-I guess so.
-Our next game is the Dragon God's Pond.
-All right, I've been waiting.
A TAKESHI'S CASTLE CLASSIC, USE THE STONES
TO GET ACROSS THE POND
-Here it comes. It's here.
-Look at that.
DRAGON GOD'S POND
DIFFICULTY RATING: 100%
We're Boys and Men from Nagoya!
We're here to take the nation by storm!
-Hey, it's them.
-The idol group from Nagoya, Boys and Men.
-Nice to meet you.
THE TEAM'S AUDITION FOOTAGE
The group made their own decision
to apply to the show.
They won't be paid
and are paying their own expenses.
Their passion for Takeshi's Castle
is unmatched.
TEAM BOYS AND MEN: MASATO YOSHIHARA,
KENTO HIRAMATSU, TATSUNORI TSUJIMOTO
I want to show people what we can do
and hope they come to like Boys and Men.
Boys and Men for life!
SKIP OVER STONES TO THE GOAL
IF YOU FALL, YOU FAIL
TEAM BOYS AND MEN
MASATO YOSHIHARA (28)
-Hang in there. He's making it happen.
-Good job.
-Oh no, he failed.
-He got past the first wobbly one.
What a shame.
TEAM BOYS AND MEN
YUHI (29)
-Nagoya in my soul!
-Go get em'.
-Do it for Nagoya.
-Good luck!
-Two at once?
-Not that stone. It's a trap.
Everyone steps on that one.
They put the wobbly ones
where people naturally want to step.
-I think you're right.
-Hello!
-Go. He's fast!
-Yeah. From that way.
-He's so fast!
-He's doing great.
-Go on that side.
TEAM BOYS AND MEN
KENTO HIRAMATSU (27)
So frustrating.
The Dragon God's Pond is
a Takeshi's Castle favorite,
but it's seen some major improvements.
At the battles of Ueda Castle,
we learned that this game
is now significantly more difficult
than it used to be.
The furthest the army could get
was half way,
and none of them could beat this game.
However, Hiramatsu from Boys and Men,
so far has broken the record
for the longest run.
We hope that someone from their group
can beat the game this round.
I won't stop!
TEAM BOYS AND MEN
YUKIHISA TAMURA (31)
He might make it. Wow!
Oh no. Just one more step!
Just one more step!
That was so close!
-He practically touched the finish line.
-Seriously? He failed.
-With one stone left...
-I'm so bummed.
-I bet.
-So frustrating.
-Did it feel like you had it?
-Honestly, yes.
I thought I could make it.
But my last step landed in the water.
You got this, Honda!
So far, no one from the team has made it.
They've put all their hopes into Honda,
their last warrior.
Go! He's fast! Good.
TEAM BOYS AND MEN
TAKAFUMI HONDA (29)
Looking good.
-He might make it!
-He's close.
-He's got this!
-Oh no!
So close.
-Oh no! So close.
-That's the culprit.
-He's got this!
-Oh no!
So close!
Why, Honda!
What happened in the end?
Well, my leg wasn't long enough.
I knew which way I needed to go.
I saw it clearly. But I couldn't reach it.
-You just missed the last stone.
-It was close.
-If you could've put your foot on that...
-I would've had it.
But these are the limbs I was given.
-My potential was limited from the get go.
-But you're an idol.
But I don't have long legs.
NEXT EPISODE, ENNOSUKE CASTLE
THE FINAL BATTLE
Will someone finally beat
the Dragon God's Pond?
And Kyoko Hamaguchi
will be back on a rampage,
this time, with her dad, Animal Hamaguchi.
Will they overthrow Ennosuke Castle
in the final battle?
Go!
SUPPORTING ARMY
BEHIND THE SCENES
FORMER JAPAN NATIONAL SOCCER TEAM TRIO
-The timing for that is tricky.
-Isn't it?
As a representative of the soccer world,
one of us has to make it.
That would be nice.
THEY REPRESENTED SOCCER PLAYERS
IN THE WORLD SERIES
You even looked nervous.
-It's okay to succeed, right?
-Yeah.
GRADUALLY, THEIR SPORTSMANSHIP
CAUGHT FIRE!
-Yoshito did great.
-Yeah. He did well.
A DISASTROUS DEFEAT BUT
THEY HANDLED IT LIKE CHAMPS
-That was frustrating.
-But we almost had it.
But it's fantastic that we get to be
in a show that we used to watch.
Here I go. Blizzard!
JP WHO ACTUALLY TRIED
MANY OTHER THINGS
HE GAVE THE GAMES
AND HIS IMPERSONATIONS HIS ALL
The winner is Takeshi's army!
I've had enough. I'll take a water bath
on my balcony.
MOOD-MAKER OF THE ARMY,
YUTAKA KYAN
-Let's do our best!
-Sure!
HE DIDN'T PERFORM WELL...
Damn it. I'm frustrated.
HE RETURNED TO BATTLE
THROUGH A CONSOLATION GAME
I made it!
AFTER THE CONSOLATION GAME
-You made it.
-Thanks!
I'm feeling much better now!
I'll do my best! I'll try my hardest!
My battle starts from here.
STAY TUNED TO SEE HOW THE ARMY DOES
IN THE FINAL GAMES
The end is what counts.