THIS PROGRAM WAS PRODUCED UNDER
THE SUPERVISION OF MEDICAL EXPERTS,
TAKING INTO CONSIDERATION THE HEALTH
AND SAFETY OF THE STAFF AND CONTESTANTS.
After 34 years, the battles
at Takeshi's Castle are ready to return.
TAKESHI'S CASTLE
THE COUNT'S TOWER
-No way!
-What? What is it?
What happened?
We're under attack by an army.
OSAMU SHITARA - YUKI HIMURA
An army?
But it's been peaceful
for the last 34 years.
What shall we do? This is not good.
Well, I'm afraid that...
-the count has gone missing.
-He's gone?
COUNT TAKESHI IS MISSING
That must be why they're attacking.
I see. What shall we do?
-We'll be fine.
-We will?
Even in the count's absence,
Takeshi's Castle has a powerful army
of warriors to protect it.
That's right.
They can demolish our opponent.
Matter of fact,
let's visit our first warrior.
-Let's go.
-All right.
Here we go!
Is this a dream, an illusion or reality?
Rugged warriors shake off their slumber
to answer the call for battle.
Gather now, warriors,
in the luscious Midoriyama Forest!
THE YEAR 1986
Ready, go.
Charge!
On May 2nd, 1986,
a colossal battle broke loose
which later came to be known
as the thrilling anything-goes-type show,
"Takeshi's Castle."
THE IMPENETRABLE CASTLE
A castle so impenetrable
it was said to be protected by the Gods.
Out of 127 battles,
only 8 challengers ever saw victory.
8 WINS, 118 LOSSES, 1 DRAW
WIN RATE 0.06%
150 COUNTRIES WORLDWIDE
OVER 34 YEARS
Its dreadful name
echoed all over the world.
And now, 34 years later...
JAPAN
...the castle has reemerged
in the Land of the Rising Sun.
RESURRECTION
THE YEAR 2023
Charge!
Takeshi's Castle is back!
Fortified with extravagance and fortitude,
packed with new games,
it's the palace of your dreams!
From all over Japan...
Nay, all over the world...
WHO WILL EMERGE
AS THE BOLDEST WARRIOR?
Attention seekers, clowns,
athletes and plain fools...
NO TIME FOR FEAR
...the best of the best
have gathered for a chance to taste glory
and endured grueling hours of filming.
So, we're in for a treat.
I'll bring justice upon you numbskulls!
Will it be do or die?
No one can predict
what will happen in this grand battle.
The castle remains lavish,
regardless of the economy.
TAKE NO PRISONERS
Victory is ours!
I'm gutted.
WHAT AWAITS THE CHALLENGERS?
Nostalgia and novelty,
comedy and drama, a show that will toy…
IS IT DESPAIR?
…with your emotions.
My name is Hakuzen Kanda,
and I'm confident...
OR HOPE?
...that there is no bigger fan
of Takeshi's Castle than me.
TEAR IT DOWN
Which is why I've been talking
incessantly in this intro.
TO TAKE HOME
ONE MILLION YEN
Did I make it?
I will destroy you!
I did it!
Here we go!
Take this!
Have a look for yourself and you will see.
Fall, fall till you can fall no further.
Struggle as you may,
he has you in the palm of his hand.
DANCE...
The man of the hour
that you've all waited for...
IN THE PALM OF HIS HAND
ARMY VS TAKESHI
Takeshi's Castle!
TAKESHI'S CASTLE
It's been 34 years since the first battles
to take Takeshi's Castle came to an end.
Three fortresses protect Takeshi's Castle.
An army of 100 people
look to breach its walls.
Thanks to the latest technologies,
the inner citadel has teleported
right next to the first fortress.
The castle is prepared for battle.
Seven gates obstruct the Army's path.
THE FIRST FORTRESS BATTLE
The wail of the horn
marks the start of our first battle.
We opened auditions to the public,
out of which we chose one hundred
of the best of the best.
We cast a wide net,
from junior high school students
to people in their 60s.
We have idols, X-ray technicians,
YouTubers and college students,
all with a burning passion
to take down the castle.
What will become of them?
THE FIRST CASTLE
UEDA CASTLE
Here we are.
-Ueda Castle, right?
-That's correct.
Here he comes!
It's him.
THE FIRST CASTLE'S LORD
SHINYA UEDA
I'm gonna bring down Takeshi's Castle!
Wait, you've got it all wrong.
-No. You're in Takeshi's army.
-No!
-Am I?
-Obviously.
My apologies, I'll do my best
to protect Takeshi's Castle.
Do you really mean that?
Well, this is momentous.
-How long has it been?
-It's 34 years.
I remember watching this show…
That's right.
…every week and wanting to join.
The Dragon God's Pond
is the most memorable for me.
-Yes.
-It was exhilarating to watch.
The way people would fail was dangerous,
thinking back on it now.
Since it's been 34 years,
we've brought back some older games,
as well as prepared some new ones.
And the older games
have also been made more difficult.
-Really?
-That's impressive.
They were
already pretty difficult back then.
Some were impossible to finish,
and now they're even harder.
However, as for Count Takeshi...
he's currently missing.
What do you mean?
-We have no idea why.
-No idea.
No clue.
But we have this AI Count instead.
Shall we try speaking with it?
The Reiwa era castle is a new beast.
Since Count Takeshi
has a habit of disappearing,
we've created
a virtual count using AI technology.
We can now ask him
about strategies at any time.
AI COUNT
Let's meet the AI Count.
What... the heck is this?
Isn't it great?
-Good to see you, my lord.
-Hey, Ueda.
You've gotten better
at navigating prime time TV.
He's full of compliments.
He's praising you.
That makes me happy.
Has AI come this far already?
The AI version
of Count Takeshi is so sweet.
My lord, your team
is having a great year, aren't they?
The Yakult Swallows, you mean?
Well, they...
Are you sure this is the AI speaking?
Hold on.
Please don't derail the conversation.
It seemed like you caught him off guard.
He was struggling
to nail down the impression.
-I'll admit, it was barely an impression.
-Are you sure it's an AI?
-Isn't it just him speaking into a mic?
-No. It's AI.
I'd like to remind you of our premise.
Your motivation is to defeat the army.
I'll protect this castle at all costs!
Your acting is horrible.
NARRATOR: JUN HATTORI
Takeshi's Castle's gates
at the highest plateau
of Mt. Midoriyama have opened.
Look at this scale.
-This is the future.
-I guarantee this is not CGI.
I'd believe it if you told me it was.
They were been built from scratch.
THE BORDER WALL
It's been a long-standing tradition
to start the show
with our first challenge, the Border Wall.
This challenge has seen many iterations.
What will the latest version look like?
It's the Border Wall.
There's a lot of people.
And a wide variety at that.
Here we have the commander of the army.
-Look, it's Kimura.
-It's Subaru.
Thank you for gathering here,
fearless warriors!
SUBARU KIMURA
Here to lead the first army in 34 years
is Captain Subaru Kimura.
Hayato Tani,
the original commander in chief,
recommended him highly.
I'm elated to be given this honor.
-Is everyone excited?
-Yes!
-Will you win?
-Do I look good in this outfit?
-Yes!
All right, I'm pumped to hear that.
Let's bring everyone to the final round.
All right!
I hear that that loathsome Count Takeshi
has gone missing.
So, we will attack
while the castle is vulnerable.
The enemy knows our secret.
You will now overthrow the first castle
in the grounds, Ueda Castle.
THE FIRST CASTLE
UEDA CASTLE
There are several obstacles...
Hey, Yamada's here.
...so bring your best game. Let's go.
To the person in the front row
with the pink onesie.
Yes, Captain.
YOUTUBER
KERUMAI (36)
Wow!
What was the inspiration
for your outfit today?
I look the cutest in this.
Hold on.
Is that Chiitan in the back row?
FAIRY OTTER
CHIITAN (ETERNALLY 0 YEARS OLD)
Can you show me how motivated you are?
Are you ready to throw down?
Thank you for revealing your legs.
Do your best.
-We also have Mr. Sasuke himself.
-That's me.
MR. SASUKE
KATSUMI YAMADA (56)
-Thanks for having me.
-But wait, we're not doing Sasuke today.
I just realized that.
Did you not know before?
Not completely.
Today's enemy is Takeshi's Castle.
-Will you take it as seriously as Sasuke?
-I will. I'll do my best.
Best of luck to you!
The first challenge is the Border Wall.
THE BORDER WALL
DIFFICULTY RATING 10%
We'll take them down!
Bring it on!
KAGAYA MEMBERS
SHO KAGA &amp; SOYA KAYA
Let's get to it!
Charge!
The battle has finally begun.
The first obstacle, the Border Wall.
CLIMB THE WALL WITHIN FIVE MINUTES
Let's hope that most
of our heroes make it over.
This is quite the sight to see.
It's lively.
-Here they come. Watch.
-There they are.
-The Nasunakanishi duo.
-Are you hearing this?
REPORTERS
NAKANISHI &amp; NASU
He's fast.
Nice. Great speed.
He's in first place.
ACROBATICS TEACHER
MONZEN (35)
-Congratulations.
-You're fast.
-Thank you.
-You're in first place.
Really?
-I'm impressed.
-I swallowed a lot of water!
He swallowed water.
-All right!
-He was really fast.
-Look.
-It's Cherry.
As our brave challengers charge the wall,
many buckle
under the relentless hosing attack.
The water makes it too slippery.
It becomes harder the higher you get.
-Kagaya keeps hosing them down.
-It's too slippery.
Mr. Sasuke spends time lending a hand
to comrades that he met today.
He's offering assistance.
I guess that's a good tactic.
This is amazing.
Quite a few heroes
have made it over the wall.
THREE MINUTES LEFT
-They're doing it.
-That's a pretty good number.
BIRD'S EYE VIEW
What is that, a loincloth?
Look, it's Chiitan!
That's one muddy mascot.
What will happen?
-There's no way he'll make it.
-No...
Don't give up!
I've never seen
such a dingy looking mascot.
Somebody please help Chiitan.
Yamada is being a gentleman.
He's trying to help everyone.
Good job. Don't give up.
Congratulations. Where are you from?
REPORTERS
SHUJI AIDA &amp; HIRONOBU KOMIYA
-We're from Spain.
-Spain!
Spain. Really?
Spain!
-That's right.
-Hola!
Did you know about Takeshi's Castle?
Yes, I did.
It was broadcast in Spain
when I was little, and I was hooked.
NAGOYA UNIVERSITY AEROSPACE MAJOR
ALBERTO DE CELIS ROMERO (26)
I see, so Takeshi's Castle
was popular in Spain too.
It's popular all over the world.
However, their teammate
was still struggling to clear the wall.
ENGLISH TEACHER FROM VENEZUELA
GABRIEL FLORES (30)
That's right! You can do it!
Don't give up!
OFFICE WORKER
TOMOKI ISHII (28)
ONE MINUTE LEFT
Five heroes remaining.
Don't give up, fearless army!
NARRATOR
AKI BARBARA (50)
Hang in there.
Chiitan is almost there!
Yamada is right there,
but he's only helping women.
Yamada, help Chiitan!
Chiitan made it!
Nice!
-Great job, Chiitan!
-With no help?
Chiitan, the fairy,
just barely conquered the first obstacle.
Chiitan is soaking wet.
ROCKET NEWS 24 EDITORIAL TEAM
Everyone celebrates a team win.
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
RADIOLOGISTS TEAM
NEIGHBORHOOD BUDDIES
HIBIYA HORIZONTAL BAR CLUB
We will conquer!
We will reach the top.
ACROBATIC YOUTUBERS
AUN
Meanwhile, Mr. Sasuke was trying
to get everyone over the wall. But...
Don't give up!
-Look at that teamwork.
-Ten seconds left.
With barely any time left,
he gave up on saving everyone.
BATTLE OVER
Time is up!
Three of them didn't make it.
-Three people failed.
-Well done, everyone.
THREE DEFEATED
-Only three?
-You never gave up, nice fight!
What a shame.
We did it!
SURVIVORS: 93
Ninety-three brave warriors
conquered the wall.
The road forks ahead
with more battles to come.
It's time to move
onto the next fortress, fearless Army!
Lord Ueda, that was nostalgic, wasn't it?
I'm impressed with Chiitan.
Yamada was there helping women,
but Chiitan did it on his own.
He might be
a surprisingly strong athlete.
-It was impressive.
-In a costume at that.
At first, I thought
Yamada was a gentleman,
-but he only helped women.
-I agree.
He didn't bat an eye for Chiitan.
I'm very disappointed in Yamada.
-I can't blame you.
-With good reason.
-So, three people failed?
-Yes.
That sucks.
Why don't we give them a second chance?
It's sad, but too many people succeeded.
Are you trying to make yourself look good?
Do you want to be like Yamada?
Why are you being so nice?
Should we see what the count says?
Count Takeshi?
You numbskulls! Too many people made it.
-See?
-He's angry.
Don't act like you're such a saint, Ueda.
I felt sorry for them.
The world is unfair
and you should cherish that.
We all saw Yamada helping only women.
What do you think of that,
Mr. Takayuki Nishida?
It's the golden rule to help women.
Why are you taking the bait?
-You're the count, right?
-Why do the imitation?
Apologies, the AI
seems to be malfunctioning.
Are you sure?
It appears to be on its A game.
He was quick to jump on the bit.
The count has range.
The AI needs to stop playing.
The next challenge is Ueda's favorite,
The Dragon God's Pond.
-I always look forward to it.
-Can't wait to see it.
-How nostalgic.
-I want to try it myself.
-Me too.
-It's a Takeshi's Castle classic.
It's the castle's signature game.
-We'll get to see it next.
-Sounds great.
THE DRAGON GOD'S POND
Good job getting yourselves over the wall.
Applaud yourselves!
You did well.
But we are far from being done.
From this point forward,
the struggle will only become harder.
Next up is the Dragon God's Pond.
Isn't it great
to see it again after 34 years?
Great. They seem so happy!
-Are you excited?
-Yeah!
All right. I wish you the best of luck.
Charge!
They're really pumped.
So, this is the Dragon God's Pond.
It's shockingly dirty.
I hope nothing weird is living in there.
Look! I see piranhas.
What? Where? Sorry!
Hey, Komiya!
-Why did you push me?
-Look behind you.
It's a merman!
What?
This is chaos.
The definition of a farce.
What a shady pond.
In conclusion, we, Sanshiro,
will be reporting from this lake.
Leave it to us.
-We can cut that part.
-No, we need it.
-No, we don't.
-It's imperative.
THE DRAGON GOD'S POND
DIFFICULTY RATING 100%
-Just start the segment from here.
-No, keep the sketch too.
YOUTUBER
KERUMAI (36)
-It's Kerumai.
-Here we go.
CROSS THE POND, FAIL IF YOU FALL
Look at him go!
-You got this. No!
-Come on!
There's that YouTuber flair.
It's not as easy as it looks.
APPAREL SHOP OWNER
YUDAI SHIBUYA (44)
He might be 44 years old, but he's fast.
What a shame.
-That's dangerous.
-That's a dangerous way to go.
-Good luck!
-I'll try my best.
Go, Mrs. Segawa.
HOUSEWIFE &amp; WAITRESS
KUMI SEGAWA (42)
Nice try.
You can't even enjoy the scenery.
Momentum is important. He's 51.
SHOEMAKER
HISASHI KATO (51)
-You got this.
-He's good.
You almost had it.
There happen to be eight stones that sink.
Beware not to step on those.
Our next team spend most days
working out on a jungle gym.
HIBIYA HORIZONTAL BAR CLUB
They are middle-aged elites
who work for a major corporations.
-They're seriously strong.
-We got this!
They aren't your average middle aged guys.
-Count Takeshi, root for me!
-He's 55.
HIBIYA CLUB LEADER
TOSHITAKA HOSOI (55)
What was that about?
-Too bad!
-That happened quick!
They're no match at all.
Based on the earlier clip,
I thought they'd do better.
The merman is resting with no interest
to interfere. Now is their chance.
MERMAN SOMETIMES ATTACKS
WITH A WATER GUN
-Come on!
-Let's see.
HIBIYA CLUB
YOSHIO YODA (60)
He's a spry 60 year old.
Look at him go.
So close!
At 60 years old,
he's the oldest member of the army.
He ran the half way, but failed. So close.
Go!
I can walk on water.
HIBIYA CLUB
MARSHALL IKEDA (38)
Marshall Ikeda is a young guy.
BIRD'S EYE VIEW
Not a single Hibiya Club member
makes it across the pond.
What a shame!
34 years' worth of passion
for this tournament,
and it only took one second
for it to all come crumbling down.
Meanwhile, this legend
was gearing up to conquer the pond.
Yamada will put up a good fight.
Is he practicing?
-He's visualizing.
-I think I got this.
Is he talking to the pond?
-We are legends.
-Here's our next dynamic duo.
Both of them participated
in Takeshi's Castle 34 years ago.
Misao even managed
to compete in the last go-cart battle.
-Great stuff!
-I'm jealous!
SECOND APPEARANCE
MISAO KATO (48)
She was 14 then, and now she's back.
-She's our age.
-She's doing great.
So close.
Was it different
from how you remembered it?
It's much more difficult.
There weren't as many stones
back in the day.
That's correct,
compared to the previous pond,
we've increased the distance
and number of stepping stones.
-They upgraded.
-We have no intention of letting you win!
-Wow.
-If you're athletic, it's easy.
And the merman is ready to stir things up.
I'm going to try again!
-Good luck.
That gap is wide, so people steer right.
-Take your time.
-What a cruel game.
COMPETED IN MIDDLE SCHOOL
RIE GRIBOV (48)
-She failed in the same way as last time.
-Did she?
It's exactly the same!
I'm glad someone is having fun.
Let's have a look...
-The frame is the same.
-She's 14 in this video?
-The resemblance is uncanny.
-I can see that.
-Another failed attempt.
-There are more stones.
Would you like to show them how it's done?
Yes, I'm carrying the reputation
of Sasuke after all.
The world-renowned show, Sasuke.
Katsumi Yamada, 56,
has been a participant of that show
since its very first episode.
Though he was never able
to conquer the Sasuke course,
his legacy is filled
with innumerable highlights.
I'm so cold!
What's your goal for this competition?
I want to complete in all the challenges
and become
the very first Mr. Takeshi's Castle.
Will he conquer his goals
and become Mr. Takeshi's Castle?
Here we go.
-Go!
-Come on, Mr. Sasuke!
-Will he do it? Wait, what?
-He barely put up a fight.
What was that?
Hold on, he can't keep going.
-What is happening?
-What do we think about that?
He's acting like he made it,
but he barely got past the starting line.
He was terrible right off the bat.
Mr. Sasuke fell into the pond,
but tried to continue as if
nothing had happened.
He's terminated
after falling a second time.
He cheated.
Can I try again? Is that possible.
No, you can't. Those are the rules.
The army continues to put up a good fight.
But no one has been able to pass.
Will there be a hero
who can conquer this impossible pond?
What a shame.
I see none of you
can get across the pond.
Serves you right.
I won't go easy on you!
Let's up the antics.
RIGHT ARM UNDER CONSTRUCTION
THE ADDITIONAL RULE
An additional rule has been activated.
Another rule?
Contestants will need
to watch their backs,
because there will be
a demon on their heels.
But no one has even won yet.
Who is this demon?
I have arrived. It's Kurochan!
No... They'll need to rush even more now.
You can't take your time anymore.
He'll toss you aside.
-There he is.
-Watch out.
-She fell before he could do anything.
-His presence was pointless.
Unfortunately, the demon is not effective.
Did you notice anyone sneaking up on you?
NARRATOR
SUMIKA KAWANA
-I didn't notice at all.
-See? He was too late.
You didn't see me?
-You have to be quicker.
-My apologies.
-That was terrible.
-You were late.
Here's another duo
with prior castle experience.
HOUSEWIVES
ZAIDA &amp; TOMITA
Who are they?
Chikayo and Masako are former classmates
that competed together when they were 19.
Can they conquer the castle this time?
-She ran right into that wall.
-That's so dangerous.
I got th...
HOUSEWIFE
CHIKAYO ZAIDA
You got this. The demon
is doing a better job too.
What is he doing? Excuse me?
-What was that?
-Why did he fall?
What are you two doing?
Kurochan took the feedback
and tried to attack sooner,
but his opponent fell after two steps
and he had nowhere to go.
-What is this mess?
-What was that?
What is happening?
HOUSEWIFE
MASAKO TOMITA
-And here comes the demon.
-Come on, you got this.
Why did he fall there too?
He had no reason to fall.
The demon seems to be having
no effect on people.
So, after that round, he has been fired.
I've been fired?
-Unfortunately.
-No, you're lying!
-Thank you for your hard work.
-I'm not even tired.
With the demon sent away,
now is the army's chance to attack.
It's time to attack with full force.
-We seriously didn't need him.
-Bye, Kurochan.
Go. He's fast!
LEADER OF TAKAGI BAKUFU
ASUKA TAKAGI (29)
It's scary to run that fast.
TAKAGI BAKUFU
KENYA FURUKAWA (30)
HOKKAIDO NATIVE
YAYOI TAKAHASHI (37)
PARTNER DANCE HOBBYIST
HIROKO MINAMINO
ROCK CLIMBING CLUB LEADER
TORU SAWADA (22)
Good for him.
GRADUATE STUDENT IN ECONOMICS
KONAN SHIMIZU (23)
Nice, he went out with a bang.
UNIVERSITY STUDENT AND PRO MAHJONG PLAYER
KAZUKI TSUJIMOTO (22)
He was close.
Next up, the cute mascot
with athletic skills, Chiitan.
With unmatched physical prowess,
can he conquer the castle?
-Don't hurt yourself.
-It can really move.
-Charge!
-You got this, Chiitan!
-Be careful.
-Take you time.
No, not that stone.
Chiitan…
With limited visibility,
Chiitan couldn't see ahead
and wiped out immediately.
It can't see the ground.
DANCE ENTHUSIASTS
AKINKO &amp; MAYAYA
Who else is confident
in their physical abilities?
The dance-loving duo, Akinko and Mayaya.
Mayaya actually has a personal agenda
for being here.
What is it?
I'd like to get married.
I'm searching for a husband!
-Please, root for us.
-I hope they do well.
DANCE DUO
AKINKO (32)
Here I come!
Hang in there.
-Stay calm.
-Go!
-That's the correct stone.
-Look at her go.
That part is tough.
It's me, Mayaya. I'll eat this race!
DANCE LOVING DUO
MAYAYA (35)
Mayaya!
She went down belly first.
Right in the stomach.
Are you okay?
The next challengers are...
NEIGHBORHOOD BUDDIES
TOSHIYUKI (47) &amp; IMARI HIRAOKA (12)
MANAMI ISHINO (13)
-He's my father and she's my friend.
-He looks young.
Manami and Imari
are close friends from middle school,
who inspired Imari's father
to join them in the race.
-So, it wasn't dad's idea to compete?
-I can do this!
TOSHIYUKI HIRAOKA (47)
-Show your fighting spirit, dad.
-He's going for it.
-Look at him go.
-So close!
-I got this.
-Go get 'em.
-Not that way. I feel bad.
-That stone is bad news.
-I'm bummed for her.
-That gap was too wide.
This is a dangerous zone
where the stones are far apart.
She gave that jump her all,
but couldn't make it across.
Was it a little too far?
-And that was the only stone.
-She's crying.
You didn't have many options,
it must be frustrating.
Manami, can you make
your dad and bestie proud?
MIDDLE SCHOOL BESTIES DUO
ISHINO (13)
Right, good choice.
-No, not that one.
-Great, keep going.
The Dragon God's Pond is too difficult.
She stumbled, but got back
in the game with a speedy recovery.
At her age,
it's an accomplishment to make it so far.
She was so close.
We even have idols in the running.
TWO MONTHS AGO
THE AUDITION
We are Sengoku Resistance.
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you all.
The group debuted in January, 2022,
under the name Sengoku Resistance.
We'll bring the castle down!
Nice. I hope they keep up that energy.
Go for it.
Here I go!
Macaroni is his name.
SENGOKU RESISTANCE
MACARONI
Go. Be careful.
-What are you doing?
-Come on, Macaroni.
-What are you doing, Macaroni?
-That gap is too wide.
-Tough spot.
-It's difficult.
-What're you doing?
-No!
-Superstar!
-Kazu, the Superstar.
SENGOKU RESISTANCE
KAZU THE SUPERSTAR
Here we go again, same spot as Macaroni.
You're right. Why did he jump there?
All speed and no strategy.
I'll do my best. Double cheese burger!
"I'll do my best, double cheese burger"?
SENGOKU RESISTANCE
HI-SAI
-Nice. Good job.
-Go! Keep going!
You can do it!
-No, Hi-Sai!
-Crap!
He had momentum and even resisted a slip.
This idol came very close to the goal.
The final contestant. Will Marco do it?
SENGOKU RESISTANCE
MARCO
-Marco.
-Okay, Marco.
-Good start.
-You got this, Marco.
I got this! No!
-The merman's attack worked.
-It got him.
Nice, Marco!
-They're all out.
-But having fun.
He resisted the merman's attack,
but failed in the end.
However, the last two players
gave a great performance.
-Well done!
-Thank you.
They received the Fighting Spirit Award
for their lively showmanship.
That's great to see.
Grit and perseverance can earn someone
the Fighting Spirit Award,
which allows you
to move on to the next stage.
This is the way of Takeshi's Castle.
Unfortunately, no one completed the task,
but 17 warriors move on
after receiving the Fighting Spirit Award.
We must go on and take down Ueda Castle.
The rules are too wishy-washy!
Seventeen people moved on.
I didn't see a single person succeed.
Yes, no one succeeded,
but 17 are moving on.
I don't get it.
With the Fighting Spirit Award
or with enough popularity,
-you can continue.
-That's right.
I have a few bones to pick with this.
First of all, Kurochan
and that goofy merman,
we can do without them.
No, we need them. They're valuable.
You really think so?
If I'm being honest, no, I don't.
Because it doesn't make sense.
If it's already too difficult to complete,
why add obstacles?
-Where is the logic in that?
-A demon adds fear.
Mr. Sasuke even tried using
some visualization techniques.
-Was that necessary?
-No, it wasn't.
I'm most annoyed that he acted
like he didn't fall when he clearly did.
That was silly.
Apparently, Yamada has always had a habit
of making excuses after he fails.
That is what's great about him.
He's got bad sportsmanship and is clumsy.
That's not a compliment.
It was great to see people
who competed on Takeshi's Castle before.
That made me happy.
It's wild to try the same challenges
on the same show 34 years later.
It's a rare experience that not many
of us get to have. Don't you think?
I agree.
-Shall we call the AI Count?
-Okay.
Yeah, that was interesting.
I also think Kurochan and the opening bit
about the merman were useless.
-That's not true.
-If the count says so, that's correct.
-They weren't necessary.
-They were.
Let's see what fate awaited
the other fork in the road.
The challenge they met is...
BEACH BOYS AND GIRLS
Reach the other shore
ridding the rotating surfboard.
This super hard game is called
Beach Boys and Girls.
Let's see what transformation
has taken place after 34 years.
-Are you excited?
-Yes!
-Do you want more?
I can feel your enthusiasm from over here.
Good job on making it this far.
Our next game sounds like a lot of fun.
It's called Beach Boys and Girls.
-Are you ready, beach boys?
-Yes!
-What about you, beach girls?
Okay! But stay alert,
this game is not be taken lightly.
Prepare yourselves. Charge!
We'll make sure you take a dive!
HOSING CAPTAINS
KAGAYA - SHO KAGA &amp; SOYA KAYA
-This brings back memories.
-It really does.
REPORTERS - NASUNAKANISHI
NAKANISHI &amp; NASU
Just like in the old days.
What are the last 11 digits
of your phone number?
That's the whole phone number, dummy.
And what's with this water?
What is this mist? It keeps hitting us.
If you're going to splash us, just do it.
-Pardon me, miss.
-It's freezing cold!
Please, stop! I'm sorry!
That's funny.
We will now bring you,
Beach Boys and Girls!
Let us see how the battle unfolds.
-Let's begin.
-Cheers.
Who needed that?
-I think it was great.
-It made me laugh.
BEACH BOYS AND GIRLS
DIFFICULTY RATING 81%
-Yeah, let's vibe out, everyone.
-It's Koo.
He has beach boy vibes.
I want to see you jump up and down!
Go!
We have girls in bikinis.
Beach boys and girls, start!
START
Yeah!
Akari, mommy's going to do her best!
Root for me!
HOUSE ORGANIZER
MANAMI (44)
-She's a house organizer.
-Let's go, Mom!
HER HUSBAND
YU (39)
Don't get hurt.
RIDE THE SURFBOARD
WHILE AVOIDING THE OBSTACLES
START - GOAL
Look at me!
-Good luck.
-Great. Good job.
Keep going!
You can't see the board,
so you have to hurry.
-She's good.
-Well done. Very good.
-The water is coming right at her.
-Keep going!
No!
ENTREPRENEUR
YU (39)
You can count on me, Akari!
Good luck, darling!
They're competing as a couple.
Good luck!
Nice, he landed on his feet.
-All right.
-Great job, husband.
-You have to stand up.
-Hurry!
Too bad.
She's laughing.
Go get 'em!
COMEDIAN
CHERRY YOSHITAKE (41)
It's time for Cherry to fight!
He's an athletic guy.
BODYBUILDER
NAOTAKA YOKOGAWA
CYBERJAPAN DANCERS
-Be careful, Cherry. Take your time.
-Good. Keep going.
-Are you okay? Be careful.
-He's a bit bouncy.
-Cherry!
-That's dangerous.
-What's he doing?
-Come on, Cherry.
-What was that? He's in big trouble.
-Cherry...
I'm sorry!
Apparently, it's taking five
or six people to fix it.
Is there anything more embarrassing?
All I've done is cause trouble!
You're shouting,
but look at it this way. No one cares.
I am so very sorry!
-I feel so bad.
-He muddied his own face.
Next up, we have a team
of childhood besties.
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
They came to make the best memories
in their last years of college.
Let's get the Fighting Spirit Award!
Is that them?
Okay, you can have the award.
Just like that?
Let's see
this team's victory dance. Start!
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
MIYUKO ISAKA (21)
Easy to jump!
Yeah!
That was a nice callout to DJ Koo.
You're doing great.
-Good job.
-You got this.
-Stay calm.
-She made it.
-Can she get back up?
-You gotta be quick here.
-Hang in there.
-Be quick.
-Go!
-Nice!
-Good job.
-Good!
-She got past it.
Let's go. Jump.
What happened? I thought she had that.
-She hit her butt.
-Is she okay?
She jumped too far
and hit her butt on the way down.
That must've been painful.
-All right.
-Let's go.
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
RINA HOSOKAWA (21)
-The surfboard slowly speeds up.
-Good job.
-Be swift here.
-Hurry.
Quickly!
No, not there!
-Why?
-That was dangerous.
-That was really dangerous.
-What a scary fall.
COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
MIRI KATO (21)
I'll try my best!
You got this!
-Hang in there.
-Stay calm!
-Jump now. Go!
-Well done, beautiful.
Hang in there!
-You can do it!
-You got this!
They'll spray the water now.
-Quickly, hurry!
-She seems calm.
It hasn't fazed her.
The goal is near. One last jump.
GOAL
-So close!
-She almost had it.
You can do it!
-What a shame.
-She almost had it.
-You were so close. You were right there.
-I know.
I stumbled, so it is what it is.
-How cute.
-The goal was close.
She put up a good fight.
Ms. Kato has gone the farthest so far
and has earned the Fighting Spirit Award.
She was so close.
Next up is nurse Aoi Nakano.
She came without telling her colleagues.
I hope she wins.
I will stay till the end!
-Good luck.
-Make it happen.
NURSE
AOI NAKANO (29)
Are you okay?
Hang in there.
-Well done. Go!
-Get back up!
-Quickly. Nice.
-You got this.
She'll miss it.
It's so dangerous.
-It's so dangerous.
-Truly.
Let's give her the Fighting Spirit Award.
She jumped with such vigor.
-Nakano wins the Fighting Spirit Award!
-What a great fall.
It's so treacherous.
The undefeatable Takeshi's Castle
swallows challengers one after another.
But never give up, fearless army.
RADIOLOGIST
TETSUYA SHIRAKAWA (30)
LIVES TEN MINUTES FROM THE CASTLE
YUSAKU SHIBAZAKI (48)
SURVIVAL GAME HOBBYIST
ATSUSHI OZAKI (34)
DANCER OF 20 YEARS
NORI (36)
SWIMMING PRODUCER
MINA KOBAYASHI (30)
-Good morning.
-Unbelievable, we have a loincloth team.
These are the editors
from the internet news site,
Rocket News 24.
This is easy-peasy!
ROCKET NEWS 24 EDITOR-IN-CHIEF
GO HATORI (42)
-All right, Hatori!
-Go for it!
-Can he pass the first obstacle?
-He missed.
That was quick.
It's difficult to keep your balance.
I slipped. I didn't expect
to slip that hard.
-It shakes too.
-But you still have your teammates.
Yes, they will make it.
But in the end, the whole team…
ROCKET NEWS 24 WRITER
SANG-JOON PARK (44)
-That looked dangerous.
-What happened?
ROCKET NEWS 24 WRITER
TAKASHI HARADA (38)
Great. Nice job.
He couldn't make it.
ROCKET NEWS 24 WRITER
HIDENORI YAMASHINA (48)
The whole team made the same mistake.
None of them made it.
-They're laughing.
-We're all useless!
Not a single person has succeeded so far.
TWO MONTHS AGO
THE AUDITION
But now, we get to meet a promising team.
Popular YouTubers with nearly
one million channel subscribers, Aun.
They'll use their dancing
and acrobatic skills to win this battle.
Who is the most confident
that they'll make it?
Be humble.
-I mean, we're all pumped.
-That's right.
-Can you all make it?
-Sure.
-What if you fail?
-They'll be fired.
-Really? Says who?
-I think they'll make it.
Ready, start!
ACROBATIC YOUTUBER, AUN
ACRE
-Watch me surf and learn!
-Go, Acre!
-I hope they make it.
-Me too.
First up, is the team leader, Acre.
He seems clumsy.
This should be easy for him.
Okay.
Hang in there. Stay calm.
Very good. He's got skills.
-He couldn't get up.
-No, he couldn't.
-Our leader is fired.
-How unfortunate.
Their leader failed miserably.
Our next guy, Ryu, is a confident athlete.
ACROBATIC YOUTUBER - AUN
RYU
So uncool.
He fell before completing
a single obstacle.
ACROBATIC YOUTUBER - AUN
HEIHE1
Will there be no winners?
Our third contestant is Heihe1. Good luck.
He's good.
-Come on!
-He's got the hang of it.
He's quick.
-That water, though…
-It's tricky.
Two more obstacles to the finish line.
-Okay.
-Wow! Look, he's standing.
-He will make it.
-He made it look easy.
Impressive.
CLEAR
Amazing!
-How did he do that?
-Team leader!
LEADER
-Our new leader.
-Team leader!
With outstanding stability from the start,
he reached the goal
with his hands never touching the board.
He became
the very first winner of this game.
-It's great to watch someone make it.
-Yes.
ACROBATIC YOUTUBER - AUN
KANTA
After 20 people failed
to complete this challenge,
we now have two winners in a row.
-Impressive.
-He did very well.
PRO SLACKLINER
REI MATSUMOTO, 36
And the army kept gaining momentum.
He's amazing.
Nice jump!
-Why is he so good?
-He's a slackline walker.
-I see.
-That's why he's good on wobbly surfaces.
That makes sense.
With his pro-level athleticism,
Matsumoto becomes our third winner.
And Sugiyama, a mother of three,
become the first woman to win.
SHONAN FAMILY BESTIES
AYA SUGIYAMA (37)
How cool.
That's great to see.
18 people cleared Beach Boys and Girls,
including the award winners.
At the next fortress,
we'll see a game that's new to the show.
-I see.
-That was quite the challenge.
-It was quite the difficult task.
-Indeed.
I wish we could see
who won the awards and why.
It's nice to see 18 winners, but I barely
remember who they are or what they did.
I think that's on par
with the confusion of a battle field.
-I agree.
-I guess so. Let's go with that.
At this rate,
we're losing contestants too quickly.
There's a chance
we won't have any winners.
They should've all been disqualified
at the pond.
This might be a good time
for a Loser Resurrection.
Wait, what is that
and how is the award system any different?
We don't give away the award that easily.
We gave away tons!
We gave out more than a dozen at the pond.
Please, calm down, Lord Ueda.
Excuse me, AI Count?
Lord Ueda is not happy with the result.
-Should we do a consolation battle?
-Ueda has no clue what he's talking about.
Although, it's not good
to be too forgiving either.
We've been nothing but forgiving so far.
These warriors who wish to rejoin
the battlefield and await instructions.
THEY MUST WIN ONE
OF THREE GAMES TO MOVE ON
They'll be randomly assigned
to one of three games.
LOSER RESURRECTION
REGISTRATION HERE
Best of luck.
The first consolation game
is called You Can't Save The Ball.
OG CONTESTANT
RIE GRIBOV (48)
I'll make sure to catch the ball!
Let's go, Rie!
-Towards the middle!
-You have to catch it as it falls down.
-Right.
-Good spot, stay there.
-Keep you eyes peeled.
-You got this.
That was close.
She was so close!
I'll try my best.
LIVES TEN MINUTES FROM THE CASTLE
YUSAKU SHIBAZAKI (48)
-I like this. This is a fun game.
-I agree.
-He's so slow.
-Can he make it?
-He runs so slow.
-Way too slow.
That was way too slow.
No way he could make it!
-It's the guy from Spain.
-Waiting in the middle is a good tactic.
ALBERTO DE CELIS ROMERO (26)
Nice.
He got it.
I see. It's better
not to jump in the pond.
-Nice catch!
-There's no need to dive in.
RETURN TO THE FRONT
I like seeing it, though.
COMEDIAN
CHERRY YOSHITAKE (41)
-Cherry, I wish him well.
-Good luck.
-Watch the middle!
-He's got it. That looks good.
-That was close.
-So close.
-He can't do anything right.
-Even after being scolded.
He failed, but he was given
the Fighting Spirit Award
for his brave jump.
-He got the award, though.
-Look at that.
The next consolation game
is called Tug of War.
Tug of War.
FOURTH GENERATION SHOEMAKER
HISASHI KATO (51)
I got A.
Who could it be?
PRO WRESTLER
TOMOAKI HONMA
That's some bad luck.
-Isn't he really strong?
-Yes, he's a wrestler.
How dangerous.
He's too strong.
He's tough.
RADIOLOGIST
NORIKO MAKINO (42)
For female warriors,
drawing a strong male opponent…
COMEDIAN
TAKEUCHI PANDA
…can mean an untimely defeat.
Winner, Takeshi's Army!
But Takeshi's Army is diverse.
GRAVURE IDOL
AIRI SHIMIZU
-What a perfect opponent.
-It's a cute lady!
-Ready, go.
-Do you think the idol is strong?
There's no way.
-She voluntarily ran into the pond.
-She didn't want to win.
RETURN TO THE FRONT
Please, excuse my shortcomings.
-She deserves the Fighting Spirit Award.
-How come?
COMEDIANS
KYOHANSHA
The college student
facing an up-and-coming comedian...
-Ready, go!
-Good luck!
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
MINAMI SUDO (22)
...did not make it back to the field.
Her teammate, Matsuzaki,
will compete against...
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
AIRI MATSUZAKI (21)
-Not him again.
-No!
PRO WRESTER
TOMOAKI HONMA
-Seriously?
-That's impossible.
-You got this.
-I'll beat you with one arm.
I don't think
they understood what he said.
-Start!
-Come on, you got this!
Nice. She's got this.
What, really?
He gave her the leg up and lost.
What's even the point?
How lame.
RETURN TO THE FRONT
-That was another Fighting Spirit Award.
-Yes.
I messed up bad.
The third consolation game
is the Slip-and-Slide Quiz.
The Slip-and-Slide Quiz.
First, the warriors bath in slime,
then go down the slimy slide
to answer with either A or B.
What was Hideyoshi Toyotomi's nickname?
ROCKET NEWS 24 WRITER
SANG-JOON PARK (44)
A is monkey. B is racoon.
Okay. Go for it.
Which is the right answer?
He's got momentum.
CORRECT ANSWER
A: MONKEY
-He got it wrong.
-He went with B.
I'll win no matter what.
GRADUATE STUDENT IN ECONOMICS
KONAN SHIMIZU (23)
In Rodin's The Thinker,
which hand under his chin?
A, his right hand or B, his left hand?
Can a current Tokyo University student
answer correctly?
CORRECT ANSWER
A: THE RIGHT HAND
-He's got it wrong.
-They're all failing.
That's not a good look
for a Tokyo University student.
-Isn't it fun to watch?
-That's true.
DRIVER/ACTOR/MODEL
DAI HIRAYAMA (31)
50/50 chance. I'll do my best!
Is Hawaii in A, the Northern Hemisphere,
or B, the Southern Hemisphere?
So where is it?
CORRECT ANSWER
A: NORTHERN HEMISPHERE
RETURN TO THE FRONT
-Good looking guy.
-And he drives a taxi?
You're a true man. Well done!
I've never been on a quiz show
or answered a quiz correctly.
-Yamada didn't received an award?
-Funny that he's in the consolation round.
Which one of the goats
ate the letter first
in the Japanese nursery rhyme?
A, a white goat. B, a black goat.
Don't tell me he can't climb that?
-You got this!
-He's struggling with that tiny hill?
CORRECT ANSWER
B: A BLACK GOAT
-This is bullcrap!
-He got it wrong?
Yamada is hopeless.
I've never seen a black goat.
Is that why it's in a nursery rhyme?
Do black goats actually exist?
They do.
-What's he talking about?
-I'm sure they don't.
He's terrible.
Mr. Sasuke was given an Award
and we look forward to his future success.
No, don't do that!
Don't give an Award to Yamada!
-He got the Fighting Spirit Award.
-For what achievement?
I'll say it, he's a complete fool.
No, he's not.
Starting from next episode,
we should decide who gets the award.
The only person I'm willing
to give an award to is Airi.
Why? She's in our army.
I'd like to introduce a new game that was
specifically developed for this series.
-A new game?
-Yes, it's called Strong Arms.
That's what it looks like.
Fear not and go forward!
-I'll do my best!
-You can do it!
Yu-chan!
Here we go.
NARRATOR
YUYA UTSUGI
This is quite the task.
Don't be afraid, keep going!
-Is he standing on fabric?
-That's right. It's very wobbly.
That was quite high!
-No!
-That's a tough challenge.
On next episode,
Strong Arms will wreak havoc.
NEXT, THE LAST BATTLE
AT UEDA CASTLE
We'll see more classic games
with new twists.
Will the army make it to the final battle?
Also...
WHAT IS THE CAPTAIN'S SECRET PAST?
THE FIRST BATTLES IN 34 YEARS
BEHIND THE SCENES
THREE DAYS OF SHOOTING
ONE HUNDRED PARTICIPANTS
FRIENDSHIPS WERE MADE
IN BETWEEN BATTLES
I'm a YouTuber and also a doctor.
A doctor?
Yasu is so cool!
Ready, go!
THOSE WHO MET HERE FOR THE FIRST TIME
That's crazy!
Rock, paper, scissors!
CREATED DEEP BONDS WITH EACH OTHER
Congratulations!
Takeshi's Castle is the best.
AND THE BATTLES CONTINUE…
Sorry for the wait. We're almost ready.
ON STANDBY
SOUND TECHNICIAN
-Just a second.
-He's changing batteries. Do dance!
-Please, be patient. Sorry.
-Everything is fine.