THIS PROGRAM WAS PRODUCED
UNDER THE SUPERVISION OF MEDICAL EXPERTS,
TAKING INTO CONSIDERATION THE HEALTH
AND SAFETY OF THE STAFF AND CONTESTANTS.
TAKESHI'S CASTLE
THE COUNT'S TOWER
At last, the final battle is here!
We've reached the final battle,
but we'll continue to talk
to the AI count?
Because the count has been missing,
we have no choice.
We call it AI, but we know it's Matsumura.
Don't say that.
Maybe some people don't know.
Is it really okay?
Shall we call Matsumura?
No. Let's call AI Takeshi.
Hey, don't make fun of me.
He's angry.
The count has been missing.
But can we go on like this?
Hey! What?
What's going on?
-Hey!
-The AI is out of control.
-Wow!
-Oh dear!
It exploded.
That's not good.
Now AI Takeshi is gone, too.
What will we call this castle now?
What's going on?
What?
Sorry for the wait, sillies.
Wow!
What?
-Please be careful.
-What are you doing, stupid?
-What?
-Wow!
You've got to be kidding me.
What kind of costume is that?
Count, you're finally here with us!
COUNT TAKESHI'S CASTLE
BEAT TAKESHI
I'm not some singer with a flashy costume.
-What kind of costume?
-What on earth is this?
I'm sorry.
What do I sing in this now?
Whatever it is,
I heard the attacking force was advancing
while I was gone.
It attacked with full force.
We are leading them on deliberately.
-I see.
-That's our plan.
-So the plan is to round them all up.
-Yeah. To round them all up.
-Sure.
To round them all up, stupid!
COUNT'S BODY DOUBLE
KUNIHIRO MATSUMURA
Don't wait for me and say your line.
Omodakaya!
THE ARMY HAS LOST
AGAINST THREE CASTLE LORDS
In the battles so far,
the attacking force boldly challenged
the three castle lords,
but was defeated in the end.
But third time's the charm,
or maybe fourth time's the charm.
The strongest challengers have assembled
for the final battle.
They take aim at the count, Beat Takeshi.
He's the one they're after.
The final battle is about to begin!
ARMY VS TAKESHI
Takeshi's Castle.
TAKESHI'S CASTLE
Ladies and gentlemen,
the army has lost three battles so far,
but God must have blessed them
or Buddha had mercy on them.
What a surprise!
They found a way to the main castle!
They have all assembled
for the biggest battle of our time.
THE DAY OF THE FINAL BATTLE
Let's do this!
Now it's time to gather the challengers
who fought in the last three castles.
It's the Takeshi's Castle water pistol
that was sold back then.
-I heard the games got even harder.
-That's bad.
No one cleared the game.
-What was it?
-The Dragon God's Pond.
How many times have you participated?
-It's our fourth time.
-Perfect attendance.
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
My grandchildren were practicing
their cheering
by watching a DVD
of my performance 35 years ago.
That's fantastic!
Charge!
All the finalists are here!
Actually, this time...
HIBIYA HORIZONTAL BAR CLUB
COMPLETE DOMINATION
OF TAKESHI'S CASTLE
-We made these to show our enthusiasm.
-Nice.
One, ten, one hundred, Raimu Sengoku!
RAIMU SENGOKU (25)
We have two finalists.
TEAM SASUKE
Thank you.
They're some of the best from Sasuke.
Now for some extra training
to prepare for the final battle.
I can't reach my toes,
so I'm touching my knees.
-Seems like you're sweating already.
-I'm losing a lot of weight, today.
This army has the strongest elites ever.
Their goal is the eagerly awaited fall
of Takeshi's Castle!
On the other hand, Takeshi's army
is also putting in extra effort.
THE TOUCH - DRUNK DRAGON TAKU SUZUKI
-It's so hot in this costume.
-I guess so.
It's so hot.
Since they've made this for you,
I don't think you should bad-mouth them.
I didn't mean that.
They didn't mean that.
The first stronghold in the final battle
is the Super Border Wall.
DIFFICULTY RATING: 20%
Spider men moving in all directions
block the path of the army.
In addition, a 40-meter-per-second wind
blows against the challengers.
The wall has become more treacherous.
Will they make it?
The wind's as strong as a typhoon.
-It's Mr. Tani.
-General Tani.
You have done well, my elites.
His face has become swollen.
We'll face many obstacles,
so I want you to try your hardest.
-Do you understand?
-Yes!
You have such a nice body.
Aren't you Kasuga from Audrey?
-What? Is Kasuga there?
-Kasuga.
Toos!
-Who are you?
-He's a spy!
Well, calm down.
Toos!
For some reason, Kasuga,
who has been tormenting the challengers
in Takeshi's army, has now joined them.
I thought it would be much more fun
to bring down the castle.
He betrayed us. He's a traitor.
I thought this was more fulfilling work.
So I joined this side.
What? What are you doing?
Hey, the game hasn't started yet.
Traitor!
-Who are you?
-Who are you two?
I won't forgive you! Hey, wait a second!
Good. They said their line.
We won't let anyone through.
-Be prepared!
-I'll knock you all down.
All right. Are you done?
Get over the Super Border Wall.
Charge!
At last, Takeshi's Castle,
the final battle, is starting.
It's so flashy.
It is.
GET OVER THE WALL
WITHIN FIVE MINUTES
-It's so nice to be that flashy.
-Good luck!
REPORTERS - TOKYO HOTEISON
TAKERU &amp; SHOGO
-It has begun.
-Wow. The sound is amazing!
-He's fast!
-They're coming.
You're the first one. Amazing.
SPARTAN RACER
RYUTARO AIHARA (27)
You were so fast!
Can you get over the wall?
Can you do it?
Now, the gale force wind
is attacking the challengers.
The storm is raging!
Kasuga's the only one who's fallen.
It was much harder than before.
KENYA FURUKAWA (30) - ASUKA TAKAGI (29)
The spider men were in our way.
A handsome guy helped me.
EX-MAID CAFE WAITRESS
MAETEL (28)
They're taking aim at the spider man
who is getting in their way.
There's Chiitan, who has fought
in all the battles so far.
Chiitan's so pumped up.
OTTER FAIRY
CHIITAN
As expected of the elites
who participate in the final battle,
more than half of them
cleared the wall in no time.
EX-FOOTBALL PLAYER
RAIMU SENGOKU
Oh my gosh. That was so much harder.
-It was harder than I expected.
-I see.
We'll have more games after this,
how confident are you?
Of course I'm confident!
ACROBATIC YOUTUBER
AUN - KANTA
It's much more spectacular than last time.
I feel like things have truly begun.
Hang in there!
TWO MINUTES REMAINING
COMIC, AUDREY
TOSHIAKI KASUGA (43)
-What? Is Kasuga struggling?
-Kasuga...
What?
-They help each other, don't they?
-Yeah. From now on.
More and more familiar faces are
reaching the goal.
-Congratulations!
-Congrats!
Thanks!
Are you idols?
We worked very well together
and got through it, didn't we?
-We'll do it again next time!
-Yeah!
No one in Team Sasuke
has been retired, right?
No!
THIRTY SECONDS REMAINING
This is good.
I've knocked down the traitor.
Well done.
Kasuga is the only remaining challenger.
Kasuga is showing off.
That's good. Great.
Everyone got through. Very well done.
I'm glad.
ALL CLEARED
In the first battle of the final round,
the entire army survived.
All cleared.
I see.
You let him through. That's not good.
-I thought we'd all stop him.
-You should've stopped him!
-No. You should've come and stopped him.
-No, you should have.
-You should've stopped him properly.
-What?
-Ouch...
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
The army
made it through the first round.
Next, it will split into two groups
to attack Takeshi's army.
In the early days,
at least five people were killed there.
No! They're not dead.
Kasuga used to be in Takeshi's army,
-but this time, he betrayed us.
-Yes.
He might think he'd be on the air
a lot more than when he was in our army.
Only General Tani has been on the air.
He might be angry because he was
in the pond for a long time before.
Count, the next game is an original one
called Beach Boys and Girls.
The surfboard moves in a circle.
Do you remember that?
-Yeah.
-We made it super hard.
What if we set the rotational speed
up to 5,000 revolutions per second?
No one could ride it.
SUPER BEACH BOYS AND GIRLS
DIFFICULTY RATING: 162%
Excuse me. Thank you.
I'm the producer, Katayama.
Thank you for coming here today.
What? Is he real?
Is he real?
It's a different space.
Please watch your step.
Mr. Toshl is coming.
He could be an impersonator of Toshl.
The second stronghold is
Super Beach Boys and Girls.
For the final battle,
an additional course has been added.
Amazing. Another course.
It has two circles.
If you jump over the balloons and land
on the green mat, you clear the game.
Oh my.
We won't let anyone get through.
It's the Touch.
Super Beach Boys and Girls.
This is the toughest stronghold!
-Okay, let's go! Takeshi's...
-Castle!
-Takeshi's...
Get ready and go for it!
Those college students!
It's the Female College Student Team.
These girls have participated
in all three of the battles so far,
and they are all
perfect attendance award winners.
They're fierce warriors
who have made their mark
during the many battles.
I don't get the impression
you've had any great wins.
We want to show
that we can do it this time.
Good luck!
I'll go for it!
Go for it!
AIRI MATSUZAKI (21)
-This is nostalgic.
-Definitely.
That's scary! Too dangerous!
-She has to clear that one, at least.
-Yes.
MINA SUDO (22)
It's so scary to jump there.
Go now!
She's good.
-Oh no. Hurry!
-Hurry up!
Oh dear!
-Well...
-It's scary!
That's...
It moves fast.
Well, she was too late.
Oh, no.
You have no time to rest here.
-I'll do my best!
-Good luck!
EVE HANIUDA (22)
-This jump is scary.
-I know. That bar is quite high.
-All right!
-That's good!
-The water makes you wobbly.
-Yes, hurry!
-They're getting in the way.
-Right.
Okay. Watch out!
-Good.
-It's slippery.
It's coming. It's so high.
You're doing great.
Wow. Well done.
-Go!
-No, she can't!
That's so mean.
I'm the leader.
MIRI KATO (21)
The last one from their team is
their leader, Kato.
A CHEERFUL MEMBER WHO TAKES ON A CHALLENGE
Can she clear this?
Okay, nice! Leader!
I'll be gentle. Come here!
It moves very fast.
-Her jump...
-The water gets in the way, too.
-Hurry up!
-Keep going!
-Well done.
-It's scary!
-She needs to get to the other side now.
-I can see that.
-Jump now.
-No!
-Why?
-She must be tired by now.
I see.
It was hopeless.
-Because it goes around the opposite way?
-I see.
We'll have a Loser Resurrection
after this.
-We've just got to keep trying.
-I'm a bit scared.
-A tug of war.
-No way.
Up next we have a traitor.
It's Kasuga.
Let's see what you can do!
Toos!
COMIC
TOSHIAKI KASUGA (43)
Here he is.
He also does aerobics,
so he's got toned legs.
He's not as good as we expected.
-He's not good.
-He can't jump.
He can't jump.
He can't jump well.
He fell too soon.
That was fast.
The traitor Kasuga's challenge...
He just can't jump.
...ended in just a few seconds.
What will you do about this atmosphere?
-Well...
-Please do something about it.
Toshl, I made an embarrassing mistake.
Apa!
What is he doing?
It's now a more stern atmosphere
than when I fell in the water.
-He said his gag, "Apa."
-That's good.
Now Mayaya, who is looking for love on
Takeshi's Castle, will take the challenge.
It's a long shot.
I'll look for the god of romance
in Beach Boys and Girls.
She's looking for a boyfriend.
I've heard that this program
will be aired worldwide,
so hi everyone around the world!
I'm Mayaya.
I'm Mayaya. I won't fail!
Mayaya! Mayaya!
You can do it!
She dances. She has good stamina.
Mayaya.
That's good.
-This is scary!
-Is she okay?
Mayaya, jump over this.
-She can't jump at all.
-No chance.
She hit the wall hard.
We didn't expect
anyone to fall with the bar.
Onto the wall...
Jump!
Mayaya!
She fell with the bar
in between her legs. Mayaya.
JOURNALIST
MASANUKI SUNAKOMA
-It's a guy.
-Yeah.
I'm feeling better!
Good luck!
"I'm feeling better!"
This is easy-peasy.
Watch out. He fell.
What is he doing?
-No one can clear this part.
-No.
Wow. It's scary.
Keep going!
GRADUATE STUDENT, IRELAND
DÃITHI O HAODHA
Right in the face.
It's scary. Takeshi's Castle is so scary.
-Hey, the Touch.
-Yes.
Isn't the water pressure a bit too strong?
No one has cleared the course yet.
-He's doing too much.
-No. It's you who's doing too much.
-It's you doing too much.
-No, it's you!
What, stupid?
I'm sorry.
Quotation marks.
IT COMPANY PRESIDENT
YASUYUKI HATTORI (46)
-Team Presidents.
-Yes.
-Go, President.
-He's 46 years old.
What a name they have!
-Presidents...
-That's good.
-He can't jump.
-No.
No!
What is he doing?
Oh, no!
No point in holding on there.
-He can't get over the mat.
-His knees are straight.
-What? He can't get over the mat.
-It's dangerous.
He's got weak knees.
President! President!
MARKETING COMPANY PRESIDENT
MAKOTO TANIMURA (46)
Come on, President!
Friends for 10 years, Team Presidents.
Miraculous synchro, and it's over.
It was exactly the same mistake.
Great skills.
The army is really struggling
against the fast-moving surfboards.
-A junior high school boy.
-Oh no!
YUMA NODA (13)
Beach Boys and Girls,
the most difficult, deluxe version.
The army is in great danger
of being wiped out.
IAIDO PRACTITIONER
SHIHOMI SUEOKA (30)
It's not so easy to succeed, is it?
That's right.
They say I'm not
enthusiastic enough, so...
I'll be more enthusiastic and supportive.
-I'm sorry.
-But you are excited.
Yes. My voice is hoarse.
But they say it's not enough.
-No...
-The producer told me off.
This is where the army must
step up to the plate.
Don't give up. Aim to clear the game!
We can do it!
NARRATOR
SHIZUKA KAWANA
I will make it!
JOURNALIST
HIDENORI YAMASHINA (48)
TEAM TAKAGI BAKUFU
ASUKA TAKAGI (29)
KENYA FURUKAWA (30)
An out-of-body experience!
-Acrobat pole dance!
-Wow!
DANCE DUO
AKINKO (32)
I love girls!
-Are you okay?
-I'm sorry.
Those bars...
They look like iron bars to me.
-They're thin, aren't they?
-If you think of them as iron bars...
-I see. It's all about how you think.
-That's right.
Every day at lunchtime, they gather
in the park to work out on the iron bars.
Hibiya Horizontal Bar Club.
We're finally demonstrating our ability
in the second half.
-Your voice is hoarse.
-Yes.
I lost my voice.
Unlike the younger players, I don't think
we can simply win based on performance,
but I think we can do it
by using our heads.
I'll try my best!
TOSHITAKA HOSOI
The first challenger is Hosoi,
who's 55 years old.
Jump!
Followed by the finalist at Ueda Castle,
Marshall Ikeda also...
HIBIYA CLUB
MARSHALL IKEDA
The power of love gets me going.
HIBIYA CLUB
IPPEI SUYAMA (50)
I'll make the water pressure a bit weaker.
We all failed.
-Useless!
-Useless...
-What a shame...
-I requested a paid day off next Monday.
Next, the Nakamura family
takes on the challenge.
Family?
He has a good sense of balance
because he used to dance.
-There are girls.
-If my dad falls at the early stage...
-Why?
-...I'll be more relaxed.
I see.
That's great.
TOMOYA NAKAMURA
I will do it!
It's Dad's turn.
He might take her home.
He might?
The staff will stop him, though.
-Well done. He's so young.
-Yeah.
Great!
Watch out!
-They know where they're going.
-Yeah.
He landed with a big splash.
I wanted him to succeed, if possible.
Can Tomoki, his son,
settle the score for his father?
-I'll try!
-Good luck!
TOMOKI NAKAMURA (14)
Go for it!
Settle the score for me!
If that shark closed its mouth
all of sudden, that'd be funny.
We'd say, "There was a trap?"
-Watch out!
-He's young. Good balance.
-The mat is bouncy. Hurry!
-Go!
He's good.
Great! Hang in there!
-He's gone to the second circle.
-Take it slow.
-It's very fast, isn't it?
-But it gets harder from now on.
Another jump. That one is high.
-He might make it.
-Go forward!
Go, go, go! You can do it!
I feel like crying.
He will make it!
-He's gonna do it!
-Another one is coming.
Two in a row, but he did it!
-This is mean.
-That's impossible.
That's unreasonable.
The bars are on top of each other.
No way!
-Those bars...
-Like a hot dog on a stick.
-It's tough.
-Toshl is laughing, too.
Tomoki, the 35th challenger from the army,
was the first to come close
to the finish line.
-He did well.
-Yes.
He couldn't get over the last balloons.
He was tired.
He sadly lost.
-They're too high.
-Yeah.
Oh dear...
Don't fawn over the girls!
I heard about you!
I'm sorry.
-You guys aren't wearing life jackets.
-I know.
Somehow, we didn't make it.
AUN are acrobatic video creators
and challengers hoping to avoid wipeouts.
The first challenger is Ryu,
who gave an astonishing performance
at the battle of Ueda Castle.
He's the only one on the team
to become a finalist.
AT UEDA CASTLE, HE GOT TO YABUSAME
We did it!
ACROBATIC YOUTUBER
AUN - RYU
Girl power!
Come on!
Not good at all.
What is Kanta like among the members?
-He's our face.
-Yes, I am.
Show us your best look.
Kanta played an active role at Ueda Castle
using his outstanding physical abilities.
He cleared!
Can he show us
the same charismatic ability he used there
to complete Beach Boys and Girls?
ACROBATIC YOUTUBER
AUN - KANTA
-High five!
-Girls! The best!
Go for it!
He's the last one from the army.
Can he prevent a total wipeout?
You don't have time to wave to her!
You're enjoying this!
-Keep going!
-Go!
Watch out!
Good luck!
He did it!
You can do it!
Wow!
If he gets over the last two balloons,
he will clear the game.
Go! Jump!
Almost there!
Though Kanta demonstrated
his excellent physical capabilities
while giving high-fives to the girls,
he ultimately failed.
You're so good,
but were those last two bars tough?
Yes. They were much higher than I thought.
NO SURVIVORS
-Would you have won without the girls?
-Sure thing.
I feel like I'm dreaming,
being on Takeshi's Castle.
I'm so happy.
When I was living in Los Angeles,
I got video tapes
of Takeshi's Castle sent from Japan.
Takeshi's Castle helped me get through
the hard times.
-Really?
-Yeah.
That's why I'm so pleased.
-So this means a lot to you.
-Yes.
-It brings back memories.
-It does.
Yes.
One of the two sides has been wiped out.
What will happen to the army?
This has become so much harder.
The last two bars on top each other
were not good.
That wasn't fair.
But I'm told that is an order
from you, our count.
Even the most athletic people
are losing their strength.
Indeed.
And he is Toshl himself.
He looks like a piece of pottery.
No, he doesn't.
-You meant he has beautiful skin.
-Right.
Next are two games
which are familiar to you.
The Dragon God's Pond
and Straits of Gibraltar.
I hear our Himura actually tried
to show what it's like.
I went there to try it first.
But you're fat.
-Yes.
-"But you're fat."
Were you okay?
-It's amazing.
-Yes.
-I loved the Dragon God's Pond.
-I see.
He admires the Dragon God's Pond.
How far can 50-year-old Himura go?
Five seconds to go. Four, three...
-Well. I can't wait.
-... two...
-Glad you can do this, aren't you?
-Yeah.
PLAYTEST
BANANAMAN - YUKI HIMURA
Very nice.
Nice.
Those are actually quite far.
-You can't jump there easily.
-No.
You made it quite far.
-Oh, no.
-He fell.
Hey, you!
I was scared.
You were.
-You can't get out on your own.
-You're pathetic.
My body is too heavy.
Why don't they edit this clip shorter?
There. That's the problem.
I don't think anyone could clear
this game. Stop worrying. Sure thing.
-You were too slow, anyway.
-Right.
It's more fun to watch people
running across the pond quickly.
They'll either laugh at you for falling
or watch you get it right.
-You have to play the odds.
-Right.
If you don't do either of those properly,
you don't get much airtime.
-I apologize, sir.
-Not much airtime...
SUPER DRAGON GOD'S POND
STRAITS OF GIBRALTAR
DIFFICULTY RATING: 140%
MASARU HAMAGUCHI
This is costing a lot of money!
It's Hamaguchi.
I used to watch this on TV. It's awesome!
What an amazing set! What is this?
I don't want to fall,
because I'm scared of water.
-It's Obayashi.
-I have no choice but to clear the game.
EX-VOLLEYBALL PLAYER
MOTOKO OBAYASHI
I'm afraid of water.
For the next game,
two games have been combined
into one much harder game.
Two additional huge rotating bars
were set up in the strait.
In addition, standing up
to the challengers is...
WATER MARSHALL
MASARU HAMAGUCHI
Let's go, everyone!
I started working
as a Takeshi's Castle reporter!
-It's AMEMIYA.
-He's here, too.
I'm AMEMIYA!
The other reporters are in Tokyo Hoteison!
-We are Tokyo Hoteison!
-Did you hear how AMEMIYA speaks?
The Super Dragon God's Pond
and Straits of Gibraltar.
The first challenger is...
Didn't you come here to cheer for me?
You aren't doing that at all.
The way he performed last time,
it was hard believe he was 62 years old.
He's actually a great challenger
who made it to the final 35 years ago.
Wow. Mr. Tani is so young.
I lost in the kart game
and failed to bring down the castle.
I want to succeed this time.
It's amazing to see those
who have taken part before.
Grandpa! Go for it!
Let's go!
HIROAKI SHINGA (62)
-He's amazing.
-He is!
He's going. Go! Keep going!
Wow! Great! How did he do that?
Keep it up!
-He can do it! Go!
-Fight!
Good luck!
Good luck. Stay still there.
-Catch this ball. Okay.
-All right!
You need to move forward
while avoiding two rotating bars.
It's much harder than before.
He's calm. Keep shooting!
It's Makabe.
PRO WRESTLER
TOGI MAKABE
-That's too hard.
-That's impossible!
No way!
No chance!
You can do it!
Almost there!
Makabe! You did it!
Masaru! Masaru!
No one can get through this.
In Straits of Gibraltar,
water marshal Hamaguchi's attack
and pro wrestler Makabe's bouncing attack
wreak havoc!
Plus, there are those obstacles.
No mercy.
Grandpa!
I'm sorry.
Grandpa fell into the water.
They are hit with water and balls.
DATA ANALYST, SPAIN
RUBEN BARRENA (34)
It went straight at him.
All right, let's go!
EX EMBASSY EMPLOYEE, SPAIN
MARC AURA RODRIGO (22)
Next, traitor Audrey's Kasuga
takes on the challenge.
When I was little,
I was crazy about Takeshi's Castle.
-To be on the show at 43 is deeply moving.
-It's Kasuga.
I think so, too.
Mr. Takeshi, wait for me.
-For what?
-I, Kasuga, will be there for sure.
What are you talking about, silly?
-What will happen to Kasuga?
-He's likely to get through.
I hope a ball will hit him hard, now.
Toos!
Come on, Kasuga! Hurry up!
-Run!
-Run quick!
When a ball hits him,
he doesn't make the slightest move.
Why is Kasuga looking at us?
-He's got it.
-It him in the face.
What a hit!
It's so funny.
Kasuga, defying the flying balls,
passed through the Dragon God's Pond.
-He did it.
-Will he get through easily?
No problem.
He was just strolling through the pond.
-Please run, Kasuga!
-Please run.
Take it easy.
Come on, Kasuga!
Wait for me.
Can you go now?
Good luck.
-Are you ready? Catch this ball.
-Sure.
Okay!
Let's go.
That's tough.
-Even Kasuga...
-He's amazing, as expected.
He made it.
He's holding on.
Is he gonna fall? It's a tough spot.
They're shooting water at him hard.
-He made it over. Now, he's falling!
-Watch out!
-It's not looking good.
-No!
He fell with it!
He can't take that rock with him!
That's impossible.
-What are we gonna do?
-We'd better fix it.
Yes.
Oh my gosh!
Hey!
That was the most exciting thing ever.
Did you enjoy it?
Yes, this is Takeshi's Castle,
which I used to watch on TV.
I know!
Kasuga, they say it'll take 20 minutes
to fix the bridge.
I'm sorry about that.
The next challenger is
former national volleyball player,
Motoko Obayashi.
I'm scared.
Which makes you more nervous,
the Olympic Games or this one?
I feel more nervous here,
because I had confidence at the Olympics.
I don't have any confidence here.
How will she do?
-I hope Obayashi gets through.
-I hope so, too.
Obayashi, 55 years old,
cleared the Dragon God's Pond brilliantly.
Now she moves onto Straits of Gibraltar.
Will she make it to the end?
I'm scared.
-Obayashi can get far in one stride.
-Really?
Why?
She hit it back well.
Don't bump it!
I usually mustn't catch a ball.
I understand that.
I want you to catch it in this game.
-Okay? Let's go.
-Yes.
I wish her good luck.
Crouch down!
That's good.
She's good.
Bouncing is another problem.
That rock is hard to get over.
Makabe shows no mercy.
She straddled it.
It's because she has long legs.
No.
-That rock is tough.
-Yeah.
Oh, no!
-You were so close.
-Yeah.
That tall rock was hard to get over.
-But you mounted it in one go.
-In terms of height, yes.
Because of the volleyball team and Makabe,
I've started improving my coordination.
It's impossible to withstand us together.
I think the attack will be stronger now.
We have been able to work together better.
-Good luck.
-We'll do it now.
The force is struggling against
the vicious attacks of Takeshi's army.
NURSE
EMIKO KANNO
-Wow.
-But she went that far.
EX-EMBASSY EMPLOYEE, SPAIN
ALVARO CAMACHO CRÃADO
-It's so wobbly.
-Oh no!
Okay! Okay!
We haven't done anything good so far.
We came all the way from Nagoya.
-Today, too?
-Of course.
We drove a van from Nagoya. Yes.
Yeah. By car.
Boys and Men, who almost reached the goal
at Ennosuke Castle's Dragon God's Pond,
and were given the Fighting Spirit Award,
are taking on the challenge next.
We came here from Nagoya.
I will clear this for sure!
BOYS AND MEN
YUKIHISA TAMURA
-You've got this!
-Yes!
Was it good? Yes!
Let's go!
Keep calm and just relax. Go for it!
-Come on!
-I'm taking you down.
-Go for it!
-Thanks!
Let's go!
We have an additional guardian,
Kurochan, just before the goal.
YASUDA DAI CIRCUS - KUROCHAN
Fall down!
Okay!
I made him fall!
I did it! There you go!
Go home! Go home!
He's so hard on good-looking men.
Boys and Men couldn't withstand
Kurochan's merciless bouncing attack.
BOYS AND MEN
YUHI (29)
Kurochan has no mercy.
BOYS AND MEN
MASATO YOSHIHARA (28)
Good luck!
What's wrong with you?
I did it!
Are you called "Ugly Men"?
No. They're "Boys and Men."
Kurochan is so harsh towards Boys and Men.
I know. He called you "Ugly Men."
-He called us "Ugly Men"?
-Yeah.
I'll think about what to do with him.
Yes, you'd better.
He was nasty.
Mr. Takeshi!
TAKESHI'S CASTLE MUSEUM DIRECTOR
SATOSHI MAEJIMA
Mr. Takeshi, we're coming see you!
Ready?
Bubbly!
-Are they still active?
-Yeah.
Shoot me!
JULIANA NO TATARI
YAJIMA GINTARO (36)
I won!
OTTER FAIRY
CHIITAN
BOYS AND MEN
KENTO HIRAMATSU (27)
Fall down!
Good luck!
EX-JAPANESE NATIONAL FOOTBALL PLAYER
RAIMU SENGOKU (25)
ATHLETE AND TV PERSONALITY
YUME MOSES (34)
I'm so sad!
IDOL
RISA OKUMA
Bring down Takeshi's Castle!
Next...
Team Sasuke, which has been successful
in past battles, finally appears!
-It's Team Sasuke!
-Here they come!
Will there be anyone clearing
for the first time?
He's amazing.
We will conquer Takeshi's Castle
as a team!
They're quite tough.
First, Sato, who is the chairman of Japan
Parkour Association, takes on a challenge.
I'll try my hardest!
-He's great.
-I hope he goes through.
CHAIRMAN OF PARKOUR ASSOCIATION
JUN SATO (30)
-He's fast!
-Fantastic!
It's like he's running on normal ground.
-Did he fall?
-He did.
-You were doing so well.
-I know. I thought I was gonna make it.
Then suddenly, I couldn't see. I failed.
-In the end?
-Yeah.
Dad. If you clear this,
we'd call you Mr. Takeshi's Castle.
-If I clear this?
-Yeah.
Hioki has tried hard with his family
and played an active role
in the battle of Naomi Castle.
Will he be the first person
to beat this game?
I'll try my best!
KITAGAWA ELECTRONICS, STORE MANAGER
MASASHI HIOKI (41)
Dad, go for it!
Take it slow!
That's all right.
-He did it!
You can do it! Keep going!
Ready?
Okay!
It's wobbly.
Ouch!
Wow.
It hit him in the face.
-But he's gotten quite far.
-That's good.
-Over that rock?
-He failed...
We did it!
Next, Yoshiyuki Yamamoto, a pupil
of Katsumi Yamada, Mr. Sasuke,
will take on the challenge.
His master, Yamada,
finished Takeshi's Castle
without performing well.
I didn't show you
anything good at all, again.
Mr. Sasuke is absent
from the final battle.
Mr. Yamada has given up
on Takeshi's Castle.
I will do my best to fulfill
Mr. Yamada's wishes,
and bring him good news.
We're counting on you!
YAMADA SQUAD
YOSHIYUKI YAMAMOTO (29)
I'll show you what Mr. Sasuke is made of.
He's good.
Wow!
Hey!
You were giving us hope!
Even Team Sasuke is struggling.
Sasuke fans all over the world
are counting on you.
I know.
I want to beat this game.
Yusuke Morimoto, Sasuke Jr.,
is the toughest player on the Sasuke team.
He has won a compete victory twice
and is a super hero among athletic men.
Sasuke Jr. cleared Straits of Gibraltar
at the battle of Naomi Castle.
I did it!
Will he be the first challenger
to clear this much harder version?
What are you doing now?
I'm climbing over the rock
in the middle of the bridge.
I'll try my best!
COMPLETED SASUKE, SASUKE JR.
YUSUKE MORIMOTO (30)
Fight!
-He's the toughest one of all.
-Yeah.
-Keep going!
-How can he do that?
Fantastic!
-Nice!
-He stayed on.
He did.
Go!
-He's amazing. He's the champion.
-Yes.
They could make it. He nearly fell,
but he is Sasuke Jr., after all.
Okay.
You can do this better!
This is a hard one.
-He might clear this.
-I think so, too.
He has excellent balance.
That's good.
-He got through.
-He made it over.
Even on that wobbly bridge,
-his upper body is still stable.
-Indeed.
-Watch out!
-Seriously?
-He did it!
-Amazing!
Hang on!
Fantastic!
All right! I did it!
Damn it!
He did it again.
-He's amazing.
-Yeah. He's great.
I lost.
Sasuke Jr. withstood
Makabe's bouncing attack
and reached the goal beautifully.
He's incredible.
-He's fantastic.
-That's why he's won Sasuke twice.
Next, this man takes up the challenge.
Haru Yamaguchi,
the finalist at Ennosuke Castle.
He's a super high school student
who has cleared every game he has tried.
Following Sasuke Jr.,
will he be able to clear the game?
I will clear this!
Good luck!
HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
HARU YAMAGUCHI (16)
He's awesome! Fantastic!
-Stay calm. Let's go.
-Sure.
All right!
You're great!
You can do it!
Keep going!
All right!
Awesome!
Wow!
It's not my fault!
Fujitaka, who holds the world's
best cheerleading title, also cleared.
Only three survived.
-In total, three challengers...
-From 300 in total down to three.
...from the army survived.
THREE SURVIVORS
Miraculously, the army avoided
a total wipeout and will move forward!
Count, how was it?
Some people got through.
Like Morimoto, also know as Sasuke Jr.,
who has won a complete victory twice.
He has an amazing sense of balance.
-Did three challengers go through?
-Yes.
We need to prepare
three lunch boxes for the evening.
You're stingy. Just a lunch box.
Our staff was worried.
Don't worry. We have enough money.
Now, we have Loser Resurrection.
Do we?
Yes. Otherwise,
we wouldn't have anyone left.
Loser Resurrection, in which the army
tries to return to the front line.
Kasuga has had a poor showing
with his consecutive failures.
Will he be able to return
to the front line?
I'm so sorry about earlier.
-I'll do things right next time.
-I see.
He must've been sorry
for finishing too soon.
Kasuga! You've got this!
Can Kasuga get back to the front line?
This is the way, right?
This is what I'm supposed to do?
Looks good. Go!
What a shame, Kasuga.
I'm having the most fun.
Meow!
COMIC
HIROSHI NEKO
Don't pour that on my head.
DANCE DUO
MAYAYA (35)
EX-EMBASSY EMPLOYEE, SPAIN
MARC AURA RODRIGO (22)
-Don't throw it away!
-Don't throw it!
TOHRU ONOJIMA &amp; KOSHIHIKARI MOCHIDA
I'm Kato-pan, the news anchor.
GRADUATE STUDENT
MIE SHIMBAYASHI (30)
We came here to cheer for them.
What are we gonna do?
This'll be our memory of the summer.
Ready, go!
PRO WRESTLER
TOMOAKI HONMA
We did it!
All right!
YAMAGATA PREFECTURAL OFFICE WORKER
TATSUYA TADA (30)
For justice!
PINUP MODEL
NANOKA ITO
-This way!
-To the right!
TV PERSONALITY
NATSU
Let's begin.
AEROSPACE ENGINEER
ALBERTO DE CELIS ROMERO
EX-MAID CAFE WAITRESS
MAETEL (28)
I'll win Slip-and-Slide Quiz!
NARRATOR
SHIZUKA KAWANA
Those who fail to return
to the front line after these games
are out of the battle altogether.
The winner is Takeshi's army!
Well done.
ACROBATIC YOUTUBER
AUN - RYU
I'm done.
JUNIOR HIGH STUDENT
IMARI HIRAOKA (12)
-I'm gutted.
-I know. You were so close.
Loser Resurrection should be
a little harder.
-Were they quite easy?
-Yeah.
-They weren't any good?
-No.
But we need them
to return to the front line, right?
We can't have more losers
in the loser's games, can we?
You're right.
THE FINAL BATTLE
FIRST DAY AFTER SHOOTING
Thank you to everyone
who participated today!
SECOND DAY OF THE FINAL BATTLE
QUALIFIERS
You must've enjoyed the stages
and spending time together this summer.
Those who will be back tomorrow,
please continue to do your best.
-Thank you so much!
-Thank you!
NEXT, TAKESHI'S CASTLE
THE FINAL CHAPTER
Are you really up for it?
Go through it if you can!
UNBEATABLE GAMES
PUSHING THE LIMITS
Takeshi's Castle reaches
its final chapter.
We're also pushing
the limits of the games' difficulty!
Plus, that super athlete
will also make an appearance!
I think it was because of your cheering.
-Was it my fault?
-Yes.
-That's why no one cleared?
I wasn't enthusiastic enough.
-Please try harder.
-That's hard.
It was so close.
Mr. Makabe,
you aren't wearing a chain today.
Me? I forgot.
-Why not?
-I forgot about it.
-Because it was too hot.
-Sure.
-Do your best.
-You don't sound sincere.
In this heat?
Of course I'll try my best, silly.
I'll do it!
We can see your human legs, Chiitan.
How many costumes do you have?
You're scary.
Did you watch Takeshi's Castle
-when you were little?
-It was my absolute favorite.
Look at this. Am I here for a work?
I used to watch it every week.
I wanted him to say to me,
"You have survived well, my elites."
Also, "Charge!"
I grew up hearing those words.
I did it.
I'm sorry. I did it again.
Good luck!
-Do you go to Shonan Beach?
-It's great.
-It's a good place to pick up girls.
-You don't do that anyway, right?
Go for it!
This is so '80s. We shout, "Girls!"
-You'll try losers' games, Boys and Men?
-Yes.
I hope you try hard and fail!
-We've finished shooting. Thank you!
-Thank you!
All right. Thank you!
The water pressure was
strong enough to push me backwards.
-It was so much fun.
-Thank you!
Takeshi's Castle is the best!
I'm losing my voice.
We're sorry about your precious voice.
-Thank you.
-Thank you for coming.
They're leaving now.