Welcome to Wednesday Downtown
Let's get on with our first presenter please
Welcome to Oda
Oh my god
It's the glasses duo!
You're right.
-We are not copying anyone
There are others
There are a lot
Enough is enough
-Enough is enough
So what are we here for?
This time we bring you this:
The 2nd edition of the theory from last year
It is this:
The 2nd "It's impossible to cry while doing the Matsuken Samba"
I don't feel its worth doing this again
Hasn't it already been proven?
Do you remember?
Of course, super hard to do
As you know
We did the project before of trying to cry while doing the Matsuken Samba
It was a little hard to understand though
He's very nervous right now
At times like this, you don't make a joke at all?
What is there to say?
There's no script so this'll happen
Well, while singing and dancing...
-Difficult
I'm wondering if I can ask to do it
You're so noisy
-What are you talking about?
So scary
The 2nd "It's impossible to cry while doing the Matsuken Samba"
This time
The challengers are dancing the Matsuken Samba
57 seconds from the beginning of the second verse to the chorus
Will they be able to cry?
So
This one won't work
The first challenger is
Diane's Tsuda
Little things make me cry easily
No way
I cry whenever I think about certain things
I am very confident about this
A crybaby
What kind of combat strategy will you use this time?
No such impression
-No
Battle strategy...
The Rugby World Cup 2015 in South Africa
It was a long time ago
At that time, they photographed the audience who came from Japan to support the team
There was someome that looked like a retired rugby player
Looking at their faces, even now, will make me cry
I can cry already, seriously
There's one in the audience with glasses
Really?
I'm going to cry when I think of that person
Maybe it will work
Although I have never played rugby
Really?
Tsuda, who has a tear switch
Obviously never played rugby
Will he succeed?
It's perfect.
-It's a perfect match
A joyful appearance
Bang the bongos, play the samba, dance the southern carnival
It's a good song.
-Indeed
Whoever you are, let's party, let's sweat and shine
It's hard, can it really work?
In the hot wind, I give my body to dance until my heart is satisfied
The waves also sing the samba of love, the rhythm of the chest is full
Remember, remember
Go for it!
Ole ole, Matsuken Samba! Ole ole, Matsuken Samba!
No way
That's pretty much it!
Just a gloomy expression
To dance is really a little
The emotions are off.
-Yeah
Impossible
Ah, come to love, my friend, come to dance, my lady
Out of time!
-20 seconds left
Sleepless and restlessly dance until dawn
Samba Viva Samba Matsuken Samba Ole!
Hurry up!
-There's no time. There's no time
Get in the mood.
-It's not working
No tears at all
That's the end of it.
-What are you doing?
It's not the time for "Ole"!
Can't cry at all
I'm trying my best to remember that scene
But the lyrics are too positive
Indeed
The one that nullifies all but the "joy" of happiness and sadness
Devil's song "Matsuken Samba"
The Devil's Song, this is awesome
The next challenger is
Takahashi Minami
This one is different
I feel like I probably
Can dance and sing and cry more beautifully than any other challenger
Indeed
-She has that impression
I cried especially hard when I graduated from AKB
It all came to me
All of the happy and sad times in AKB
I'm going to go back to those scenes in one fell swoop
Indeed more likely that Tsuda
I think it will work
Songs, dances, and tears are all part of the job
Arguably the strongest challenger in this project
What will happen?
The atmosphere is not depressing
Good dancing
Very brisk movements
Bang the bongos, play the samba, dance the southern carnival
This piece is still cheerful
The lyrics are awesome!
Whoever you are, let's party, let's sweat and shine
In the hot wind, I give my body to dance until my heart is satisfied
Here we go. Getting into shape
Remember
The waves also sing the samba of love, the rhythm of the chest is full
Ole ole, Matsuken Samba! Ole ole, Matsuken Samba!
Feels like it's coming soon
Feels good
30 seconds left
Eyes already wet
Ah, come to love, my friend, come to dance, my lady
Is there no problem here? There is a phrase "my lady"
Sleepless and restlessly dance until dawn
Will all the work be lost?
Time is almost up.
-15 seconds
Samba Viva Samba Matsuken Samba Ole!
Can do can do
There is no more time
Still not working?
The end
It's too hard
It's really disheartening
If I have another 10 seconds, I may be able to cry
Although it reminds me of the past of AKB
Jumping and jumping Mr. Akimoto and Mr. Matsudaira Ken mixed together
Now the tears are flowing
-Too bad
How to put it ... now I can cry a lot
It's confusing.
-Pity
And now you are in the state?
-Yes, I'm in the state
Although I was in the state the dance is too intense
Another 10 seconds
So close
I wish I could have another 10 seconds
Just a little bit
The next challenger is
Forget about this guy.
-Bad guy
Yasuda Dai Circus's Kuro-chan
Last time I cried
That's right, when it comes to Kuro-chan
He completed a challenge of crying during the chorus of a song
The first successful winner of the chorus crying contest
The singing style is terrible
To eliminate your demons
After all, it is this kind of music
I'm also getting drenched today
Sad
This time the song is not the same
I think I was asked to come because the project was too difficult
I've experienced a lot of nasty things so far
In this program especially
That's right, he has experienced a lot of things
So I can cry
So Kuro-chan tackles the challenge
Will he succeed?
Scary
What'll happen?
It's scary when he laughs
A bit like Kuwano
Very similar indeed
Bang the bongos, play the samba, dance the southern carnival
Whoever you are, let's party, let's sweat and shine
Pretty good
Start from here
Can he do it?
In the hot wind, I give my body to dance until my heart is satisfied
The waves also sing the samba of love, the rhythm of the chest is full
Already in the zone
Come on!
-There's still a chance here
There are still 40 seconds left
Ole ole, Matsuken Samba! Ole ole, Matsuken Samba!
The singing is really bad
There's no way around it
A distorted expression
The expressions are great
It depends on what happens next
Ah, come to love, my friend, come to dance, my lady
Sleepless and restlessly dance until dawn
This won't work, will it?
Oh, no.
-Not good
Samba Viva Samba Matsuken Samba Ole!
Last 10 seconds
Running out of time
Impossible
It's really hard!
Kuro-chan can't do it
Just a sad expression
Good work, everyone!
What are you talking about?
Although I was sad, I couldn't cry to this song
Even the strongest challengers are powerless
The impossible crying son Matsuken Samba
Who can do it?
The next challenger is
AMEMIYA
I cry quite easily.
-Is that so?
At child abuse and stuff like that
When I see news like that, I cry out of anger
Also cry when I watch "Crash Landing on You"
I understand
The last episode of the "4 o'clock" program, I also cried after watching it
You have a very wide range of crying points
How to say, my emotional ups and downs are still very intense
This expression is too terrible
Can't even recognize who it is
A bit scary indeed
This expression is great
Eyes wide open, no problem, right?
Bang the bongos, play the samba, dance the southern carnival
That's a good one.
-Indeed
Whoever you are, let's party, let's sweat and shine
The action is a little scary
Too stiff, the body is shaking
The singing is good but not the dancing
In the hot wind, I give my body to dance until my heart is satisfied
The waves also sing the samba of love, the rhythm of the chest is full
Seems like he'll cry
Getting into the mood
Ole ole, Matsuken Samba! Ole ole, Matsuken Samba!
What kind of emotion is this?
Can it be done?
What's this?
Ah, come to love, my friend, come to dance, my lady
Sleepless and restlessly dance until dawn
Can't do it
No more time
Samba Viva Samba Matsuken Samba Ole!
There's no time
-Not good
Just a sad expression
No tears were shed
Didn't cry
Not crying?
No
The next challenger is
It's too hard
Mr. SASUKE Yamada Katsumi
You guys really love using Yamada!
But he seems like he might be the type
I'm confident I can cry
We've seen it a hundred times, everyone is familiar with Katsumi Yamada
You don't have to say 100 times
SASUKE is my everything!
When it comes to SASUKE, I can cry easily
Just cried a week ago
Really?
What'll happen?
Bang the bongos, play the samba, dance the southern carnival
Why is his face so colorful?
Singing is quite gentle, really unexpected
It's awesome!
-Singing and dancing well
Whoever you are, let's party, let's sweat and shine
In the hot wind, I give my body to dance until my heart is satisfied
The waves also sing the samba of love, the rhythm of the chest is full
Not dancing
It's okay to fast forward
Ole!
This is too much.
-What the hell?
Sorry
It's too much.
-Really?
The next challengers are
Kintaro
Since becoming a mother its been very easy to cry
Yes
People who have had children should be able to understand
It's really easy to cry compared to before
Do you have a battle plan?
My two years old child is in a difficult rebellious period
Its tough being a mother
So I want to express my gratitude to my mother
Seems like a good way to cry
But now that mom is gone
I should be able to cry while thinking of my mother
Should work
Indeed, you'd be moved
Now remembering her late mother, she wont be fooling around
What'll happen?
Does this remind you of your mother?
Its just too funny
The expression is too terrible
Bang the bongos, play the samba, dance the southern carnival
Singing and dancing are good
True, although not yet in the mood
Whoever you are, let's party, let's sweat and shine
Got it all figured out.
-Great!
In the hot wind, I give my body to dance until my heart is satisfied
We're in the zone.
-Here we go
Koroke!
The waves also sing the samba of love, the rhythm of the chest is full
A small Koroke
But it does get you into the mood
Memories of Mom
Ole ole, Matsuken Samba! Ole ole, Matsuken Samba!
Remember
Tears are coming out
-Amazing
It's already flowing out, right?
Ah, come to love, my friend, come to dance, my lady
Amazing! Amazing! Unbelievable!
Sleepless and restlessly dance until dawn
That's awesome!
Samba Viva Samba Matsuken Samba Ole!
Crying like crazy!
-Really crying
Tears are flowing
-Seriously!?
Perfect
-Terrific
Awesome
-Scary scary scary
Impressive
It's like Kabuki!
Thank you. You've did it.
-Great!
Both eyes are tearing up
Thank you so much!
Really great
7 seconds into the second main verse of the crying section
It's fast
Tears were already shining in the corners of her eyes
Only 7 seconds in
It's really fast.
-Amazing
It's out! It's out!
14 seconds later, she succeeded in shedding tears
Awesome
After that there were also tears from the other side of the eye
-This is really awesome
So, she completed the Matsuken Samba crying project
Really?
I'm betting all of 2022 on this
Finishing the year on this, it was worth it
What are you talking about?
Thank you
In Summary
If there is a sequel, it will be a Genghis Khan tear project
This really does not work
Genghis Khan is too far
Awesome
It's over. Someone really did it
So, how do you feel?
It was really a big surprise
Yes
-A big surprise
It's true
She was so cool at the end.
-Indeed
It was like Kabuki
You wouldn't be able to do it, right?
-No way
But I do feel that the longing for one's mother can really overpower "Matsuken Samba"!
What are you saying here all of a sudden?
-It's too sudden
Mr. SASUKE, you fast-forwarded it, wouldn't cutting it be better?
He was invited at least
Let's welcome the next presenter
Magical Lovely!
We are Magical Lovely
Magi-Love
We are Magical Love
It's not short for a Magical Love
Yes, I'm in Magic Haruka
Magic Haruka?
The name has become strange
-Opportunities like this don't happen too much
Magic Haruri?
Have people ever said bad things about others or talked badly about people behind their backs?
Yuuchami, have you?
If I have anything to say I generally say it directly in person
I see
So I don't really say bad things behind people's backs
A typical gyaru
So this time we have a project about badmouthing
The King of inducing people to talk badly behind the backs of others
Induction King
Senior comedians will be the setters
And will attempt to induce junior artists to speak ill of them behind their backs
I see
I drank with Kubota of Toro Salmon before
He kept bad-mouthing Kyojin
Everyone in Japan knows this.
-Is that so?
That's not backbiting anymore.
-So it's not backbiting
The King of inducing people to talk badly behind the backs of others
This time, the contestants are four comedians
The first one is Cunning's Takeyama
The next generation of comedians to be targeted are these four
But one of them
Higuchi
Is an accomplice controlling the direction of the conversation
So there are spys
He's controlling the situation
My idea is to intimidate them directly at the beginning
But it's somewhat unnatural to suddenly intimidate them
So I'll just be unpleasant from the very beginning
And i'll focus on one after another
Slamming their character and attitude towards their work
I'm prepared to do this but here's the problem
The people's styles etc
I don't even know what kind of work they do
But since none of them are popular i'll just focus on this
Only by imagination
By the way, this time at Misaki Fishing Port in Kanagawa Prefecture
They are recording the next morning in a location shoot
As the group came to the local accommodation one day in advance for the shooting
Then on that night
At the dinner invited by the seniors
The backstabbing challenge takes place
Although these words wont really help you...
I'll say it. I didn't want to do this job
Ah really
I spoke to my agent
That guy clearly said something like "Okay, I get it".
But still added me to the job
With you unpopular guys
Eh?
-What kind of location shoot is this
Just like Takeyama stated before, he is immediately angry from the outset
At this point in time when the atmosphere is heavy
The game begins
Matsu, you...
It's been a long time since we've seen each other, but I'd like to say something
-Ok
Tomorrow's Sun Music Live is a first-tier live performance, right?
How long have you been there, but you still aren't leading it?
You can't say you're at my level, right?
Yes
-You also said that you "rehearse the segment every day"
You also said "we can't go to the sauna together today"
How is Nori doing these days? Still not gained popularity?
Indeed, not much movement
Didn't you start in this business with Kazlaser?
Aren't you contemporaries?
-Yes
Really?
And Kaz is super popular now, right?
Aren't your frustrated?
I don't pay attention to him
Even if you say "I don't pay attention", I can't help it
Its hopeless if you're just choosing to ignore it
Anyway, giving up being a comedian isn't the same as dying
Pretty convincing
Going further
Already on board?
Yes, I'm an official member now
You're a member of Sun Music?
-Yes
Done any Lives?
-Yes, I did
What if you get more work?
I'm on paid leave
With this attitude you can't make it
-Indeed
I think you should not stay in the company with such an uncertain attitude
It will cause trouble for others
Do a good job. Be serious.
-Okay
After preaching precisely to the three juniors like this
I'm going first
They don't know what I said for my comment "sorry, I forgot" they said
What do you mean by "forgot", you bastard
Don't oversleep for me tomorrow!
I won't oversleep
Really if you oversleep I'll kill you
After dropping his final harsh comment, he retires for the night
At this time
So annoying
He really has something wrong with his brain
I can't watch, too scary
I can't stand this type
He's so pretentious
Just now also when coming in
That walk, what is he acting like?
Wants to walk with the aura of an entertainer'
-What entertainer!?
But that guy is usually
"Hehehehehehe" just sitting there laughing
Come on, someone stop him!
They don't want me to laugh like that?
Scary
"Hehehe hisshisshiss"
Badmouthing the seniors when they are not around
They sure know how to talk!
Only stupid people smoke
Then
Looks so happy
He must have felt the same way when we traveled to Kyushu together
So suddenly got angry then too
Did he start to get angry when he left Tokyo?
This sentence is super laughable
Is it because he's nervous?
-No, it can't be
The bad things being said behind the scenes are not only about this time, but also previous times
Bad
It is difficult to say bad things about seniors
I said, "I'm going back to Osaka," but he was mean to me for three hours
I was asked, "What did you do the next day?" I said, "I went back to Osaka."
He said, "Why? Everyone is working so hard."
Three hours of lecturing like this
Yeah, with me
At a barbecue place I just asked for a bowl of rice
He shouted "What the hell are you doing eating rice at barbecue!?"
Went on for six hours
What a way to talk! These guys have poison tongues
Then the conversation goes even deeper
Although it may not be appropriate to say this, but I think the guy really
I think if I really argue back I can absolutely win
I just have that feeling
His last words
Its not like that
Like a high school student
I had the same feeling when I was his driver
I thought "I could just drive straight off the capital highway at any time"
Straight off of the highway
I want us both to die right now, like this
This is the first time I've heard of such an thought
He wants to kill me!
So sad
Doesn't he always ask for people's help? It's confusing
What do you mean by "Come with me to the shoot"?
Always something unreasonable
I've probably done the same
Once I was told to "wait in the car"
I would deliberately smoke cigarettes in the car
This guy. This guy
This is no longer a backstabbing, its a secret revenge plan
When I worked for him as a driver
In his Toyota Alfa, I XXXX loads of times
Really?
This is bad
They really don't deserve to be popular
Right at that moment
Scared me
-We'll be done in a minute
Everyone sat down at once
The sudden return makes the targets panic
Everyone's stiffened all of a sudden
Anyway, you must be saying bad things about me
No, no, no, not at all
-How can we say anything bad about you?
Unveiling the whole thing under a clichéd lie
You guys are really bad
You all said a lot of bad things
The moment I left, you started talking bad
And what did you do to my car when you were my driver
-Ah, well...
Uh... what did i...?
What's going on here? Where did it start?
-I heard it from the beginning to the end
Is it limited to this venue? You heard the bad things from just now?
What do you mean here only?
-Did you hear the bad words in the car over?
You talked bad about me in the car?
That was close
The next challenger is Impulse's Tsutsumishita and the target is these four juniors
Sloppy members
The next challenger is Impulse's Tsutsumishita
How old is Satake?
-39 years old. The same age as us
I'll be 40 years old this year
What about Mr. Half?
Mr. Half?
What does that mean?
He's split in two
When did this happen?
It's not for anyone's sake
I just wanted to be more eye-catching
They are just talking about the strange tricks of unpopular artists to receive attention
Why don't you put more effort in comedy?
I thought about trying.
-No, no, you didn't
More than just a thought
It feels like you didn't make any action
You're 46 now too, right?
-Yes
What'll you do when you're 50?
Okamoto is the same way
This guy has been in the industry for a while but look at him now
You don't even know what you want to do, do you?
You're too half-assed when it comes to comedy
Half-assed?
-Completely
So true
This approach will also bleed into your daily life
You'll lose your way
You think this about my comedy?
-Your comedy as well as other things
I guess all of you are not very motivated
Good way to criticize
I don't really think thats the case
Why don't you just quit your jobs?
Seems to be angry
When drinking just now, I asked "What do you want to eat?"
He's angry
And also said "this is really delicious"
None of this is funny
You're all just saying "what's delicious?"
Obviously I want to joke around
But you guys don't even pick up on it
After his stern rebuke
Everyone is holding back
I'm bored really
-Sorry
I'm going
What a clever induction
Leaving after dropping 30,000 for a dinner party
What will happen?
They are holding back
That
I haven't been out drinking for a long time,  is this the atmosphere now?
Does this happen often?
Or just when he's in a bad mood?
It's possible
But there's nothing you can do about this stuff
Just simply venting their frustrations, right?
First of all, what did he just say?
I thought "Who are you to say that?"
Like when he said, "What are you going to do from now on?"
He's concerned
Although he said a lot of things out of concern
But I'm also very concerned about that guy's situation
Called me "that guy"
Already started
The juniors who have entered the rhythm of badmouthing have started to call him "that guy"
So fast
Gradually showing their aggressiveness
Really angry
He seems to think that eating just a little is
Very cool
Yeah yeah
But I don't know what he's pretending to be
He's showing off
Talking about some very serious topics to make himself feel cool
He himself does not even know that his ability is the lower-mid level
What lower middle level, his ability is right on the edge
His look is also bad
-It's a disaster
Fat and ugly face with a ghostly appearance
Pure stupidity
They won't stop
I've come to hate these guys really
Throws the money down and says "I'm leaving"
There were times when the money he drops isn't even enough to settle the bill, right?
-It's true
Pretending to not know the price of something
His brain is messed up
I'm an idiot, right?
But that stupid pig?
These two shiny titles
Isn't it tough being such an idiot?
Saying i'm a stupid pig is too much, right? It's tough
A real character attack
When comedians get together
He always starts with this seniority stuff
He thinks he's on top
When really, he's the worst
How can he still stand on the head of others?
At this point, one member continues to unleash an unstoppable tirade
He's really quite a loser
Completely
Because he used to work for NSC
Everyone hates him
He really makes people angry, that piece of shit
Frankly speaking, we hate him from the bottom of our hearts, right?
My two-year-old daughter is more obedient
A no-go is a no-go
Hello
Scary!
I don't want to look
Still drinking?
Drinking and chatting happily
Drinking and talking well?
-Yes
We were talking about how to change ourselves starting tomorrow
And talking about tuna
Tuna?
Talking about this kind of stuff the whole time?
-Yes
To the juniors clearly did not talk about any of this
We revealed the truth
This is too much to bear
Super difficult
What the hell is this?
Then, the content of this project was conveyed to them
Wow!
Wait, what is this situation?
I heard it all when I wasn't here!
About 40 minutes of badmouthing me without stopping
But I also know your nature
Scary, what to do now?
I'll apologize afterwards
I will apologize to you solemnly afterwards
It's really too much.
-Ah, this... this...
The next challenger is the Nichokenju' Kobori
The target is these four junior artists
Always feel a little messed up
Not that it's perfunctory either
Its like eating up your savings
Do you mean we aren't challenging ourselves to do something new?
He is sure to be badmouthed
"You're too comfortable with the status quo," Kobori said to Keishi and Murakami for about an hour
That's a great choice.
-The scene must be very confusing
Then
I really think you're unacceptable
After dropping a simple "You're unacceptable" to New Okabe
He retreats as before with an unhappy look
Did he get weird from halfway through?
Yeah, really
There really are some seniors that our concerned for our wellbeing
-Some
I thought he didn't even take us seriously
No, don't compliment me
But
What did he say to you, Okabe?
Honestly... unacceptable
Although it is a small thing
Didn't I give him some cigarettes?
You did?
He only smoked a tiny bit
It's true, so I can't say its badmouthing
Look, look, look, look, it's still long, right?
All of the finished ones are the same lengths
This is really not good, right?
Same, same.
-It's very even. It's completely consistent
He's only smoking the tip of it!
Not ingesting the nicotine at all
So why is he even smoking?
-The look
It's over for him
He's pissing me off. What a statement!
What do you mean by "the look"?
A fake smoker
All for appearance?
Smoking to look cool
Not to be a cool comedian but a musician
He definitely pretends to be like that
They're looking down on me!
And
Jun as well
I'm always being lectured by him
I don't think it's a problem at all.
-That's not possible, is it?
Won't there be "question marks" in your head when you are being lectured?
There will, but, how to put it...
Even if we talk back he doesn't understand
Oi!
That's the worst!
Then
Totally looked down on
Although it might be a bit much
I've always thought i'll never lose to him
This is not good!
Never thought of losing to Nichokenju
No, not Nichokenju, just Kobori
When Kobori returns to his seat as before
The truth is revealed
The mood is heavy
It's getting heavy
Oh...
This is Wednesday Downtown
Good face
You said, "i'll never lose to him"
That sentence hurt me the most
What do you mean by "i'll never lose to him"?
Look at the wristband
He's pretending to be a musician
It's not like that!
So the final challenger is
This candidate is a little dangerous
Nagano is assisted by a junior at his firm
What will happen?
This is a good opportunity to convey the facts
For them
They wont say something they've never thought
To incite them hard
I'll start with the psychological aspect
And then just let them talk bad about me, right?
-Yes
I usually scold them
Do you usually tell them off?
-Usually
I've scolded all of them before, yeah
Really
Although Nagano is confident about this project
What will happen?
If you know which artist is badmouthing you behind you back, they'll be sent away as soon as possible
What do you mean "sent away?"
Never work with him again
I'd like to think that I would accept it with an open mind and move on
It's rare for these members to get together so why don't I just say it
It's really impossible for you, right now
How long ago did you decide to be comedians?
If something happens, the office will fire you
First Nagano lectures the helper
Making the atmosphere worse
Then
Isn't Shinichi very strange lately?
Will you get the trophy again?
Get the R-1 trophy by playing dumb?
I think so
I've always wanted to get it back
-That!
But now its like "is it ever gonna happen?"
The staff thinks so
Everyone is tired of your act
You're just playing the fool
In fact, only Nagano-san thinks so
The trophy has passed by so many times
Shinichi almost got it
I've pretty much had enough
Already starting to get angry
Shinichi's stuff is just not funny anymore
Although you seem to be fine with it, what are you going to do in the future?
This will not work
You've also made a lot of enemies because you have been badmouthing others
With Nagano's natural sinister look
Don't say it's natural!
This session differs greatly from the previous lectures
As expected of him
Straight to the core now
Fujiwara too
The final of King of Conte?
-Yes
How many times have you been in the final?
-3 times
3 times to the final?
-Yes
In the final 3 times but still not popular, such a waste
Indeed
Isn't it awful?
It still depends on the audience, if they don't like you its impossible
Speak for yourself
Does anyone like you guys?
Not many fans, no
No, right?
-Yes
Feels like it's about to explode
You also
I don't even know what your purpose is
You're writing more
On various programs
Although Shinichi's stuff isn't funny
They're used at least, despite not being funny
Angry?
How to put it...
Aren't you a big guy?
It's really disgusting
There are loads of entertainers over one meter seven
In this way, he vents his usual outrageous words for an hour
Terrible
Drink what you want. Here's the money
Dropping a 3,000 yen dinner fee, which was not even enough for one person, he leaves
Too cheap, right?
He's gone
He's really gone
What a guy
Isn't tomorrow's shoot going to be awful?
Not great
Isn't he jealous? Because Shinichi got there first
Saying all that about Shinichi
His complex seems clear
Really bad, he said such a lot of strange things
You really don't need to care
-You don't need to care about what he said
They're all very kind
Mostly because no one at R-1 takes him seriously
Because you won, he has an inferiority complex
He's a bundle of low self-esteem
And his popularity is now gone, too
So he's become neurotic
The devil
So he hurts others with his words
Because of Nagano's tone of voice
Shinichi is really upset
The juniors did not mix any funny elements and instead just bad-mouth seriously
But Shinichi, you've been on set recently
Aren't there a lot of times you perform with him?
-Yes
I'm super wary of him.
-Ha?
Super wary
What happened to make you feel like that?
Everything, literally everything
It's so tiring
-You're lying, right? I thought we had a good relationship
I think he has too much pride
In the end, he has no charisma at all
He thinks he does?
-I used to think so
So serious!
I don't think he has charisma
I just pretended to respect him
Really?
He's always said that before... eh?
That guy is just a drag.
-A drag?
It's a big drag.
-What do you mean, on set?
He's the type that just wants whats best for himself
So because I also hope to do well, i've been desperately trying to please him
But on TV
He drags everything down
This is also too hurtful
Looks so sad
I really feel like keeping my distance from him
I've gradually understood everything
I can't stand that guy right now
Can't stand me?
Good and true bad words
It was tough from the start but right now its really impossible
So that's what you thought, Shinichi?
I thought he was a very cool and interesting person
But a part of his character makes him impossible to like
I really think so
If he wants to go to dinner together I definitely will not go
So that's what you think?
So real
You know what? He never takes the lead
He absolutely must take a back seat
He himself said that "playing the fool is really a skill"
But instead he just acts like a big shot
Hiding in the back, not wanting to be found
He also always wears a hat, but even if he doesn't no one will recognize him
You wouldn't recognize him if you ran into him on the train, right?
Unstoppable
With a strange hat
-Really weird
Gross, a gross dude
Can't even tie shoelaces
So he probably can't even live a normal life
From now on, I really can't work with him on set
Same with live shows
Either is impossible
This project is really difficult to top
I really hope he can work more carefully
And he's also stingy as hell
Seriously, does he ever treat anyone?
The money he gave is not enough at all.
-Really?
What can you do with 3,000 yen?
He probably doesn't understand the price of goods
And he can't count
Because he only goes to cheap izakayas
Doesn't know the price of anything
Just drops 3,000 yen as a token of appreciation
This is bad
I really think he's not thinking straight
Its so frustrating
What do you guys hate most about Nagano-san?
I don't like his scruffy look either
-Ha?
It's really disgusting
Only wears lame shoes
Dirty socks, dirty underwear too
When he's changing you can see his wrinkly underwear
That old "Grape" logo
Ultimately, lots of bad things were said from various angles
Like search engine keywords
At this point, he returns
And we reveal the truth
What's going on?
Who?
What program?
Which show?
Shinichi's?
I really don't understand what's going on at all
This is Wednesday Downtown
Seriously!?
So after informing them of the content of the project
So you heard everything?
It's not true, Nagano
It's not true, what I said
The worst... really bad
Look at Nagano's face
I really think this is a project that should not be done
This expression
This is not an expression for a variety show
This time, really...
-It's really bad...
This relationship... we have...
Well...
Our relationship is over
-No, no, no
It's not like that, it's really not like that
It's already irreparable
This is the end
In summary
Nagano is the King
This is embarrassing
How about this project?
Matsumoto, do you think this project should not be done?
This is really bad this time
I also think Grape Company is done for
It was already struggling
Before the company was stronger
-Now it's bad
After all, the juniors were wound up
That's why they are cursing
The juniors are more fired up than usual
Why do they have to make so much effort to rile them up?
So true
Let's not do it a 2nd time, then
It's too harsh
-Let's do it again
Regardless of whether to do it again or not
It shouldn't have been done the first time
I drink with my juniors all the time
It's great, and everything is said with respect
Even so, when you leave they still say
"So annoying"
What is that response?
It is better not to say bad things behind others
How to put it
I don't want it to end yet
You want to end on a lighter note, don't you?
I would like to talk more
Just let it end
I don't want to go back to the lounge yet
Let's all hold hands and go back together in a friendly manner
Let's live in harmony, after all, it is a funny show
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03