Timers: SilverDOA, Riddell, Otviss, Gestalt, Phantom Translators: Hikarii, Jump4r, Xueshi, Zebestt
m 0 0  l 1800 0  1800 140  0 140
WDT Project
Welcome everyone to Wednesday Downtown.
Let's move on with the first presenter if you would please.
Mr. Hakata Daikichi!
Teacher. Teach.
Weren't the fan girl screams for Teach impressive?
Thank you.
Okazoe-san, if I may ask suddenly, have you ever found money
you had forgotten about in your clothes?
Quite often actually.
- Often?
What, really?
You forget about it often?
It's natural, isn't it?
Huh?
Natural?
With money it's like second-nature to just stash it away when you find it.
I feel like she's not very good at holding this conversation.
Since that money is yours you can do that, right?
Exactly.
Right?
With that, this time I present you all this.
When you find money that you don't know about in your pocket, you will most definitely stash it away.
When you find it in your own clothes of course you think,
"Isn't this my money?" and put it away.
It would seem that's the case.
Right?
That's something you'd normally do, right?
Well, when it's like 1000 yen (~$10)...
It depends on how much.
It does depend on how much...
You definitely wouldn't find a large amount.
In terms of the amount, it does matter and that's why...
Yeah.
This time, it's 50,000 yen (~$500).
I see.
With $500 I'd definitely wonder if it's mine.
What do you think, Ebisu-san?
If it's from my pocket then it's mine, isn't it?
It's not about whether it's yours or not, just that you find $500.
Who would put money in my pocket?
That person can only be me (so it's mine).
Coming up, planting money into pockets secretly! An observation
Did I win it from the slots..?
After that, "Caricatures of scary customers will be greatly weakened for some features"
Then, "The rewards on a point card system become far more ridiculous towards the end" as well as
The first Ghost-Bicyclist Championship!
There he goes! He strikes a winning pose!
When you find money that you don't know about in your pocket, you will most definitely stash it away
The first target is Viking's Kotoge.
With cooperation from Television magazine,
a photo shoot featuring fashionable comedians will take place.
The magician playing as a cameraman will plant $500 in Kotoge's pocket.
How will this play
out, I wonder?
The accomplice Shoji waits for
Oooh! I see!
There he is.
the unsuspecting Kotoge to enter the studio
Immediately, the photo shoot featuring fashionable private clothes begins
They're wearing their own private clothes?
That's right.
Could you do something like this please?
Stand a little closer together.
It's better to have people standing close.
While Kotoge poses, the magician begins to make his move.
Yes, exactly. Bring your chin up-- perfect. Just like that.
First, he uses his finger to make the pocket accessible.
Whoa.
Turn a little this way, please.
Wow...
Then face the front, please. Angle your arms forward.
Whoa, really?!
He's fast. Really fast.
He's nimble.
He makes a blind spot using crossed arms
from which he easily plants all five $100 in one go.
And then...
Excuse me.
Could you please put your hands in your pockets?
If you have like a cellphone please take that out.
You put money in there?
No...
You the type to go without a wallet?
No, not at all..
That's a lot to keep in a pocket!
Huh? What's this?
Did you perhaps forget you had that there?
I would know about $500 though...
Huh...
I really don't know
You seem scared!
This doesn't feel right
Upon finding money he doesn't remember having,
Kotoge feels uneasy.
(Manager) What's wrong?
I don't know why but this is here..
To entice him, his manager brings him his wallet.
This feels bad...
This doesn't feel right at all!
He doesn't seem to be pocketing the money
Here we reveal ourselves
Good work today.
We're from Wednesday Downtown.
You've come.
Ah!
It's this, isn't it?
It seems you didn't put the money you found away. Why?
If it were $100...
I would think that MAYBE I left that in there.
But finding $500?? That's a little...
There's no such thing.
That kind of money is scary isn't it?
I see!
It just doesn't feel right at all.
Would you want to put dirty money in your wallet?
We kind of felt you would though.
He's great.
What, really?
Did you know about it, Shoji?
I did.
YOU KNEW!
Why the hell do YOU know!?
The next target is Sanshiro's Komiya
This time, disguised as a group of three fans,
one of them will place $500 in his pocket.
Manager
While waiting for his partner, some fans call out to him
Komiya's fan huh?
As they distract him, $500 is snuck into his clothes
That is something else.
Just like that?
That easily?
Without suspecting a thing,
Komiya moves to the next location
Please change your clothes first.
Put your valuables away in your bags.
Here at that moment...
You would
be surprised!
Komiya finds the $500
He's putting it away
- Huh!?
He double checks the amount of money
There he goes!
He kept it, dude!
and stashes it away in his wallet!
With that, we now approach Komiya
Good work today.
Huh?
What is it?
We're from Wednesday Downtown
Huh? What happened? That you've come?
In your pocket, there was $500 wasn't there?
Right, my pocket--
Yeah.. Why do you know? How much?
It's just as you said..
Damn it...
You mean it really isn't mine?
Nope, not at all. We put it there.
Why did you do that?
No, see, 'cause it was there I felt it was mine.
I mean, of course it wouldn't happen. $500!?
Right? That's too large of an amount to find suddenly.
I mean, if it was like $10 or $20 maybe it'd make sense.
He's talking so
freaking much
Or even some coins. Yeah.
He totally is
You have a lot to say
Yeah... Sorry
How embarrassing!
With that said, the fact that Komiya stashes the money away
That's embarrassing.
That is SO embarrassing.
does not necessarily make Komiya a bad person
We leave that as a disclaimer
With that, our final target is Kuro-chan
He will TOTALLY
go for it.
Will Kuro-chan
do it I wonder?
Just like with Kotoge, we set up for a fake photo shoot
Yes, just like that. Great.
Could you raise your arms a bit? Perfect.
Using the same tactic with he blind spot, $500 is slipped into the pocket.
That's incredible.
Then...
Could you check your pockets? They're bulging out a little.
Manager
They're close.
Make sure your wallet or cell phone aren't in there.
Don't involve him!
Why is this money here?
Huh?
Is that from the slots?
Did I win?
Wait, wait
That's quite an amount.
Yeah.
Did I get it from the slots?
(End of the photo shoot)
If you would please, thanks.
Does it belong to the stylist?
Nope, it's mine
so I'm gonna put it away.
Into the wallet goes the $500
His image is
in danger.
Without a doubt, the money is stashed away
Unlike Kotoge and Komiya, he was
adamant about the money being his
This guy...
Before the experiment can end, there is one more thing to be verified
TBS has called him out for a fake DVD interview
During the photo shoot, the staff will infiltrate Kuro-chan's dressing room
There they will put 100,000 yen (~$1000) in his bag, twice the former amount.
How evil
And then...
Thanks for buying :3
Wa wa waaaaa!
Hmm, it's kind of weird without some confetti
I think adding the confetti would give us a solid ending.
It'll be smooth
Yeah
Then, could you go get some for us?
Ok
Kuro-chan is sent back to the dressing room to get him to look in his bag
Ah, he noticed...
He noticed the 100,000 yen, but just put it back...
and returned to the set
Thaaaaaank youuuu!!
Wa wa waaaaaah!
With that, the shooting ends...
...and Kuro-chan returns once again to the dressing room.
He takes out the money he placed earlier
He checks the amount
And then...
Without fail, he stashes the money in his wallet
and then...
Wooo
Ooo OooO
He starts humming a cheerful tune.
Suspect: Kurokawa Akihito, AKA Kuro-chan, Age 39
Of course, we must investigate further (2 days later)
This time, we are placing hidden camera's inside the target's home...
...And placing 1 million yen (~$10,000) in his doorstep.
Will Kuro-chan pocket this money as well?
That shit is wild.
2 hours later
Kuro-chan returns without knowing anything
The result is...
Oh you put it there.
Eh?
Wait, is someone here?
He must be scared thinking someone's there...
Hello?
Umm..
Uhh, what the hell? What the hell??
Eh??
More than the 1 million yen, Kuro-chan is more afraid that someone was in his home.
And then...
What's he doing?
For some reason, he eccentrically rings his own doorbell.
What is he doing
Someone is here right? Someone is here right??
That's pretty scary
Right? Right??
They wouldn't come out!(even if someone was there)
What's up
Someone is here right?
Right?
Answer me!
Hold up...
What is this, seriously!?
Am I being loud?
You gonna close it?!
H-Hello?
Hello?
Hey, someone is here right?
I won't do anything, I promise!
Ok!? Hello!?
"I wont do anything, I promise!"
No one!?
This is scary!
Super scary, what the hell!?
Right?? What??
Why didn't he just leave?
With that, it's time for the reveal
So scary
Eh?
It's scary but...
Ah, he covered it
Good work today.
Eh, for what?
We're from Wednesday Downtown.
Eh, what do you mean?
Eh, what do you mean? What?
Hold up hold up hold up
I don't get this at all, hold up, what? what?
Has anything strange happened to you lately?
Strange things...
Well, when I was in a meeting,
Umm...
...there was nothing but extremely sexy people there. Are you talking about that?
Uhh, no...
He doesn't notice what happened, so this time we have to explain it to him.
And then...
What's that you're hiding there?
No, you're mistaken...
Do you mind lifting up that bag for me?
No... you're mistaken...
No he's not
There's no way that I would pocket this money. Seriously
Damn I was super scared.
That was freaking terrifying.
There you have it, having 1 million yen placed in your house while you're away is super scary.
That was pretty interesting.
Downtown, what would you guys do in that situation
if you opened up a drawer and took out 1 million yen.
If I found it in my drawer then I would take it.
Hmm, a drawer...
Well, at their level, they would just say "Oh, just 1 million?"
First of all, the price of me versus Hamada is way different
About 8:2
Really?
8:2
You've done really well for yourself then.
You're pretty successful
Moving on, our next presenter, please come forward
It's Sanshirou!
Thanks for having us
You came as a combination?
Yes, this is my new consort.
We'll do our best as the main and sub of Sanshirou.
You have a dirty body don'tcha?
From the previous scene right?
Pretty sure you're both filthy actually.
Me too?
Of course you too, no matter how you look at it
You're pretty livid right now aren't you?
Do I get yelled at that much?
You must've thought "What a pitiful body" from looking at my back.
Pretty shameful yeah.
Well then, this is sudden, but everyone please take a look at this.
This is from a manga called Gorillaman, "Ghostriding"
Did you guys know about this?
Yes
I learned about it from the manga.
While riding a bike, you first let go of the handlebars...
... and due to the momentum as you get off...
...it appears as if a ghost is riding the bike.
Just with bicycles though
So with that, our theory is this...
Theory: A Ghostriding Tournament will be reasonably exciting.
We've gathered some people who seem like they would be good at ghostriding.
Due to their image
And we were thinking "Won't this be interesting"
So we wanted to try this.
"Theory: A Ghostriding Tournament will be reasonably exciting" investigation.
We've gathered 4 challengers to take part in this tournament.
Our first contender...
BMX Pro Rider: Ikeda Takahiro
Oh, he seems really good
2016 BMX National Runner Up
Currently holding 4 Guinness World Records, he's a bike expert.
He's also performed in the Cirque du Soleil
I feel like there are a lot of people
who used to do this when they were kids.
I also did it when I was a kid
It ends up curving left or right.
It'll be important to try and make the bike go straight
Our next contender...
Former Women's Keirin Athlete, Shimano Reibin
She just retired from the sport 2 months ago, after winning the Girl's Championship 8 times.
Holding the weight of those accomplishments,
she suddenly decided to take part in this contest.
Moving on,
Wow, her ass is sticking out
Competing on behalf of the entertainment world, Yasuda's Big Circus's Danchou
That's not it
He's competed in numerous road races and triathlons.
He's also passed the corporate team's entry test.
For Wednesday Downtown
Basically all they use is Kuro-chan right?
He always gets super excited
and in the end he is always just being deceived
Kurokawa
You take a good look
Lastly
Gymnastics Athlete Ozeki Shingo
His power is in maintaining balance
When thinking about ghostriding ,the most critical point would be balance
Placing his faith in his balance, he joins the competition
In all, these four are the ones competing
Ghostriding Championship
Eh, that seems fun
The rules are simple: As soon as you throw the bicycle
The bicycle which goes the furthest shall be declared the winner
The recorded distance is not based on the path taken
but the straight line distance from the starting point
Unfortunately for us, the day begins with rain
We decided to hold the bicycle championship indoor instead
The contestants have three choices
Woah, amazing
Impressive
* A family bike
Mama-chari Bike*, Mountain Bike and Road Bike
By drawing lots, the first contestant is chosen
Yasuda Dai Circus : Danchou
So his choice is the mama-chari bike
We witness his first ghost bike try
He has begun
140,000 yen is the cost of his beloved bicycle
He is good enough to be employed by a business team
And so, Yasuda Danchou
How will his first throw turn out? It is rolling but..
It is making a large right turn
As expected of Danchou's bicycle
It makes a right turn and ends there
Distance: 14m 60 cm
Isn't this good?
Amazing
I won't be overshadowed by Kuro-chan
Up next, is Former girls track cycling team Shimano Riimin
As expected of a former
8 times Champion of women track cycling
She places her weight on the left side and throws the bicycle out
Its heading straight forward
But as feared, it veers towards the right
As expected, it does turn
Distance: 22m 50cm
She managed to break Danchou's record
A rare expression of self-pride
Amazing, it really took off
Following that is our 3rd contestant
Ozeki Shingo
Nihon Creed Gymnastics Team
Director and athlete
He's got good speed and posture
He jumps off the back!
His landing was decisive
Impressive..
It appeared to be straight for a while but
It went quite straight
It is still continuing on its path but
In the end, it has veered towards the right
His was the best out of the contestants
Distance: 31m
Wow, Amazing
As expected
The trick is in cleanly letting go
By cleanly letting go of the bike from the back
He managed to clinch the best record of 31 m
topping the previous record holder
Lastly, our fourth contestant is BMX pro rider: Ikeda Takahiro
Surprisingly, everyone else is quite serious about this
So I am a little nervous
In 2016 iBMXff BMX Flatland World Championships 2016, he finished 2nd place
He has also appeared in the Cirque du Soleil
and possesses the 4 Guinness BMX records
He lifts his left leg and attempts his 1st throw
If only he had thrown it more properly
Throws
Ohh, what a blunder
He is holding his head
So this type of things happen as well
That was really unexpected
That was damn embarrassing
Distance : 8m 10cm
It doesn't work just throwing your bicycle
After the 1st try, the highest record is Ozeki
Ikeda Takahiro, the one favored to win is in last
What an upsetting turn of events
And so begins the fateful 2nd round
There goes Danchou's 2nd throw
Its still going
Amazing, its still going
Its looking good
Still Impressive
It makes a large turn but he managed to get good distance
RIGHT ON!
His record is 34m 30cm
Taking over Ozeki , he is now the top record holder
Following that, is Track cyclist Shimano's 2nd try
She wasn't able to improve her record
The result is 18m 40cm
It definitely turns towards the right
You can see everyone's record up to now
Everyone does seem to end at the right
The remaining two are Ozeki the gymnast and Ikeda the BMX Pro
Who will prevail in the end!?
Dark horse Gymnast Ozeki begins his 2nd try
Will he come out on top?
The crux lies in maintaining speed when you let go
Here he goes
How will it turn out?
Good,He did well
Its so good that it looks like a ghost is really riding the bicycle
Well done achieving such a distance
It isn't turning still
Ahh~ It hit the wall on the other side!
Splendid
Distance : 51m 80cm
Once again, Ozeki achieves the top with an immeasurable big throw.
The last contestant BMX Ikeda takes the spotlight
With his pride which brought him to the World's BMX Championship
His 1st throw surprisingly turned out to be a failure
Even with his 1st throw,it looked like it was going to go well
He doesn't want to feel like a failure again
When he's cornered
Here goes Ikeda's 2nd try : how would it turn out?
It's going straight forward
Wow that's amazing!
BMX
Ikeda's 2nd try
How would it turn out?
It's properly rolling straight
This is truly
ghost cycling
It slid and crashed into the wall
Wow, this is truly the worst
Distance : 50m 40cm
Amazing
Can't we just call that a home run?
In this case where two contestants have hit the wall
We shall now conduct an extended round
Luckily for us, the rain has cleared and we have shifted to an empty parking lot
Gymnast Ozaki VS BMX Ikeda in the 1st round tiebreaker
How is the distance looking from here?
It looks interesting
We can throw however far we want to
The ground is bumpy
We have to "read" the line the bike is gonna follow
Into the extended round
By lot drawing again, Ozaki is to be the first
Okay, going for it
The Ghostriding Tournament's first throw in the outer field
In front of him, there are no longer any walls to stop him
In the end, what kind of record will he be able to show us
Ozaki's challenge
He has successfully fallen from the back and thrown out his bicycle
The ghost bicycle is moving but
it has ended up making a really large right turn
and it has stopped, the ghost has stopped
Distance :  37m 70cm
Ozaki was unable to extend his past record
Following that act is BMX Ikeda
If he manages to break Ozaki's record, his win would be set in stone
Who will be our 1st ghostriding champion?
Ozaki or Ikeda?
He's lifting his left leg and has let go
He made a winning pose
He lifted his left leg and has let go
Its heading straight forward
He made a winning pose
Its smoothly pulling ahead
It's truly a ghost riding the bicycle
It's still making distance
And finally it has fallen
How is his record?
Distance: 53m 30cm
And with that, the crowned champion for the 1st ever Ghostriding Tournament is:
BMX Pro Rider: Ikeda Takahiro
In conclusion:
Ghostriding competitions are somewhat exciting but
good kids should not follow in their example
I see
Yes yes
How was it?
It was interesting
That was underwhelmingly soft
Unbelievably softspoken
I can't believe this
When you were talking to me, you stared intensely
Therefore, when I replied, it became a half-hearted response
Surprisingly, the gymnast
performed better than anticipated
What he did: Jumping off the back of the bicycle
Why didn't the bicycle flip upwards?
Yeah, yeah
When he let go, it went smoothly
Please do your job properly
I think its due to the fact that he jumped off from the back
Wasn't there a moment where he needed to flip upwards from the handle?
Well...
He probably didn't flip it and just let go like this
Do you understand?
This is tragic
This situation is wretched
Hey Joker, he let go like this
Therefore it could go straight upon release
What's happening to you, ghost comedian
That's one hell of a nickname
Moving on, proving and disproving common theories from our audience
The viewer's theory corner
Tonight's presenter is:
Tamura Kenji
Nice to meet you
Everyone, this is kind of sudden but
All of you are celebrities in the show business
Have you been requested to have a portrait of you done?
Yes
Downtown-san right?
What about you, Degawa-san?
I have appeared a lot on magazines
which are mostly made from user submissions
Oh I see
There are a lot of types of portraits
There are those who specialize in exaggerating
Yes,Yes
So here's a exaggerated caricature of Hamada-san
Okay
Here is how it turned out
This is amazing by the way
You get it's him instantly
Isn't the caricature weak?
What do you mean weak! I don't have fat lips like that!
Yeah I wonder how it is
Is it really exaggerated?
Why did my lips become like that? Look look! They're normal!
But you...
They really are!
The eyes look like they've been pushed to the middle!
Yeah the eyes right? The parts on my face are gathered in the center so it's becomes that way
The eyes...
But if you're asked who this is, you definitely answer Hamada-san
Instantly
Ah maybe
This time right, I have brought with me a theory about this type of drawing
Here it is
Theory : A caricaturist's exaggeration will lessen if the client being drawn is scary
Yeah, right?
Being careful like "Will it be okay? His nose is kinda big but..."
Won't they be careful?
Yeah that's a tough situation as a professional isn't it?
Yeah...
A person who looks kinda scary...
It's because angry people will get angry
It's fine if you kill a person instantly but...
Uhm...if you just...break their precious right arm...
You mumbled your words so I didn't get what the hell you're trying to say
You can't mumble
Ah you're scary...You comedy-yakuza!
Even if its a little,won't you let up
We're testing the theory that a caricaturist's exaggeration will lessen if the client being drawn is scary
This time, with the help of an owner of a portrait shop
We will investigate with hidden cameras
Our first target is...
Waah, it looks like him
...a portrait artist...
Isn't the exaggeration too much?
...who has drawn these portraits
And our helper will be this man with a scary look
But this guy is kind of scary right?
His hair can be called a "bar code head"
I mean yeah...
Now we get our guy inside with an over the top yakuza feeling
Over the top!
Will he be able to draw an usual caricature with a scary man as his subject?
Will he? I want him to...
Hey don't fucking sit down
What kind of touch would you want?
Just draw me as I am
With a bar code head?
Now that we've shown the strong look, the portrait drawing starts
You really can't draw here
But it'd be weird if he drew thick hairs
And it's done
What kind of portrait has it turned out to be?
He's probably stressed out...
There is a little bit of exaggeration but...
...the hair should've been drawn even less however...
It's definitely like that
...in this portrait it has reversely gotten thicker
He put more hair on it
There is zero exaggeration of the bar code-head
As expected,
has the exaggeration gotten weaker? When we ask him...
It's a bit hmm...
How was the drawing process?
It was hard to draw him
Why is that?
Because he was a scary man
Was it scary?
Yes it was
So it WAS hard...
It was to test if when a scary person comes...
Oh what will happen?
...will you hold back a bit?
You definitely hold back!
The hardest ones to draw are the scary people
Oh really?
With that, here is the result when we make him draw holding nothing back
I wonder how different it'll be
He of course draws the receding hairline...
...but also a very round face and pronounced eyes
We can easily see that he was really holding back before
He almost looks like a foreigner
How about this scary man?
The features that stand out are...
...the big nose and his underbite
His chin sticks out
And our next artist is...
...this man
He already has drawn people with protruding chins...
...to an extreme, but what will happen?
It's about a person's characteristics so...
...it becomes a minus for the exaggeration
He's saying it!
The exaggeration?
He's pushing forward
We can display it as a good point of that person
That person is a person of his own so...
...if you ask which it is...
...we think of it as a plus
He's really freaking out
Quibbling along trying to insure his safety
What kind of drawing has it turned out to be?
In the end, how did the caricature turn out?
That's handsome!
Even though there was alot of material...
...it seems that he was holding back
I feel bad for Shohara-san
Asking him after we explain the prank...
You can't do that right?
We're from a program called "Wednesday Downtown"
Yes...
Was there anything odd that happened to you today?
One of the customers uhh...
He seemed to be in a special line of work
Yeah I kinda thought of him like that...
What was all that guaranteeing safety
If it were for real, would you exaggerated a little bit more?
Honestly I would yeah...
He has quite a unique face
There are alot of high-potential parts but...
...they don't really stand out with what I've drawn
With that, when we have him draw no holds barred...
I wonder how it'll turn out
...here is the result!
Certainly when you compare them, the size of the nose, the look of his eyes...
Aahh...His nose and...
The teeth are showing
...and also the size of his chin makes it easy to see that he was holding back
The size is completely different
It is...
When we continue with our investigation...
We can't really find any caricaturists...
...that actually do their job when faced with a scary looking man
Lastly, we will use this man for our experiment
He isn't scary at all!
The comedian (Einstein's Inada)
Why is there a...
That's put on there isn't it?
This ugly ass comedian from Kansai...
If you made it that far...
...will be taking on the role of a yakuza underling
Impossible!
It's really made him scary
With an already extremely protruding chin...
...and a head with signs of a weird kind of balding.
It's amazing
But also with a giant fake mole
If they really made it like this what will happen?
What will happen when a person with a face completely full of exaggerated parts shows up?
Where are you from?
Do it fast I ain't got time
They're not letting him talk
Yes sir
We pushed his scary character
Scary! That kind of mole is definitely scaring him
What has that face been made into?
The fact that it's on the side is scary
Somehow his unique chin has been clearly drawn
Does that mean that the fear factor was not enough?
He's..scared..right
It was a bit scary yeah
A little bit scary?
Since he was a scary person...
...if you go all out...
...alot of things can go wrong
He's not gone full force
There are some points where I held back
He was holding back
This was actually held back
How will it become?
Actually when told, the balding, the nose and the chin are clearly visible but
It doesn't actually look that much different from the real thing
It is different!
The real man was too amazing
So there was an illusion of exaggeration
If it were a person who laughed a bit more...
...I could've probably gone all out
If I think to myself "This man is OK" I can go at it hard
He can tell that...
Here's the version we made him do afterwards...
Oh okay...
He's sticking out goddammit!
I'm not fitting in
You really held back didn't you?
His hair is also...
I'm sorry you had to be careful because of me
That means, even professional caricaturists
will hold back with their exaggeration
And also the exaggerated version looks more real
Yeah everybody...
The quality seems to disappear a bit
Ebisu-san, can you draw portraits?
It happens from time to time actually
The hardest parts are when a female customer comes...
...even when a weird woman comes...
...I try to draw them pretty
Do you actually want to draw them ugly?
Yeah...actually...yeah I want to
He's an honest guy isn't he?
Do any of you own any point cards?
I do own some
The bakery near me has one...
Really?
They don't do it do they?
Isn't she looking to up her popularity with that kind of move?
Please stop doing stuff like that...
Then, do you know how much you pay for a cabbage?
Cabbage?
I don't know
You should know a cabbage's price
That means you're not looking at how much it is when you're buying it right?
I DO look
I do look at the price but since I want cabbages I buy it
It wouldn't be 1000 yen for one cabbage would it?
She's really staring me down
You were smiling when talking to Matsumoto-san
She got excited and really stared me down
This time I have brought a theory about those point cards
Here it is:
Theory: There are plenty of point cards that set goals that are impossible to reach
Ones that make you think "Can you really save up from that?"
"How many times will I have to go there?"
There are plenty like that...
Oh really...
We will investigate some point cards that are hard to accomplish or are plain weird after this
We will investigate the theory that there are plenty of point cards that set goals that are impossible to reach
Now, when we search for them...
...we found a car parts shop that gives you 10000 yen discount if you spend 2 million yen at their shop
Spending 500,000 yen will get you a 5000 yen gift certificate
at this store specializing in bags
Oh it's that kind of package
That's pretty strict isn't it...
Of course, we found numerous ridiculous point cards here...
...but within that, this is the one that beats the rest
In Osaka, there's a maid cafe
called "Nadia"
They have a system where if you spend 500 yen, you earn one point
There's a option for 500 points
They have various prizes from 5 points to those with special privileges starting at 200 points
Basically, if you exchange 100,000 yen worth of points
You get a photoshoot with the maids
Furthermore, 150,000 yen will get you a lunch date with a maid.
250,000 yen and you can hang out with a maid for an entire day.
And the prices continue to rise.
That's pretty cool
There are still goals which require more points
Taking a maid on a vacation in a foreign country will require 3000 points.
Vacation to a foreign country?!
(14.000 USD or 10.000 Pounds)
In actuality, you need 1,500,000 yen in points.
So expensive!
However, you will not be able to go alone with a maid,
The store owner will tag along with you.
He comes along??
In addition, all travel expenses
and accommodation charges will be covered by the customer.
Who would wanna do this??
Even though these rules being so strict, is there anyone who would take this trip?
Has anyone ever saved up for the trip to a foreign country?
What is this...
Yeah, there have been a few
I've tagged along to places like Hong Kong, Hawaii, and Paris.
There have been 10 people so far that have earned this trip.
By the way, of the customers currently in the maid cafe today
How many points have they saved so far?
We asked them to let us see their cards
Noooo....
308 points
I see
With a cost of 150,000 yen
he's saved up over 300 points
What can you get now that you've saved 300 points?
I can go on a lunch date
together with a maid to a store I like.
What do you think? Are you gonna do it?
I was thinking about it before, but now I'm reconsidering
Because I can go to several places if I use 500 points.
He's so serious
I see, so these 300 points
If I use them once, they'll decrease
How much have you spent so far?
(9 350 USD or 6 650 Pounds)
Close to 1 million yen.
Do you feel satisfied with your purchases?
Very much so
Really?
The cost is high...
They are used to the high price point
but the customers seems satisfied with paying it.
Furthermore, as we continue our investigation,
We have discovered a number of genre specific point cards.
To begin with
at a West African traditional drumming practice course for "Djembe"
1000 yen is equal to 1 point
Their sensei sure is convincing
If you save 100,000 yen worth of points...
You receive a big Djembe drum
However, the course is only once a week
and one lesson is 2000 yen, so it will take 50 weeks to save the points.
Which means if you go to every class without skipping a week, it will take 350 days.
In addition, the expiration date on the offer is in 2 years.
A limit...
With this ridiculous setting...
...no one has been able to obtain the prize.
You should have the points...
by May of next year right? If you keep saving?
Yeah, if I keep at this rate.
Moving on, our next point card comes from this cemetery
Our point card is called "Mairi Point Card". If you go around the cemetery once...
You get 30 points.
"Mairi Point". Combining the names "Mairi" and "Mile"
(To pray)
(Pray mile points)
It comes together to form a hilarious name.
Don't bully them
If you go around the gravesite 40 times...
You can receive flowers worth 1200 yen.
A point card that will truly make your ancestors happy.
Others: A candy store which will give a 50 yen off coupon if you come 20 times.
A cycle track and bike store which
will give you a "beckoning cat" if you come 240 times.
Furthermore, a snake cafe
which will let you touch the snakes as much as you want if you come 20 times.
There are many special point cards indeed
And there is one within those that is even more special
Or rather, more like an insane point card
An everyday goods shop in Saitama prefecture, Cosucoji
C-cosu?
In this store, 1000 yen equals 1 point.
And 60,000 yen will allow you to
That's going to be quite difficult
exchange your points for various interesting choices
They've got a decent amount
I have a beard right now right...
There's an option where you can shave my beard
Oh really... is that it?
Yup, that's it.
There have been a few people who have done it.
Oh really?
Yeah, just a few people.
Ibaragi Dialect Lesson
Have people saved up for this one?
No, not at all
No one has exchanged for this option, but you keep it on there?
Yeah, I'm leaving it on there just in case someone does want it, I think it'll be interesting, you know?
Ahahaha
A store owner who naturally laughs at his own jokes.
I have a dad
One of the prizes is a life consulting session with my father.
He's really an amazing person. Very meticulous.
How many points is that?
Umm
120 points.
120..
Looking at it from the other side, would you take this prize?
Absolutely not.
Furthermore, there is the option to do "Ghost Calisthenics" with the owner's mother.
Or force the owner to cross dress for a day.
There are many options that make the owner incredibly nervous.
And lastly
An overnight tour of the Asahiyama Zoo.
(84.000 USD or 60.000 Pounds)
It costs 9 million yen
An inconceivable amount, this is a hellish privilege.
This is so stupid...
There you have it
There are plenty of ridiculous point cards,
as well as point cards that fall short of success.
That was pretty interesting don't you think?
You think so?
Is it ok for the maid cafe to be doing that?
What do you mean?
Legally speaking is that even allowed?
You mean them taking a trip with the customer?
Doesn't it feel like human trafficking?
Human trafficking..
No way...
I wouldn't go that far...
That was too much huh..
Next week, an "Audience Theory" special!
Check out our Facebook and Website for more Wednesday Downtown! This video was subbed by a community run project called the Wednesday Downtown project. Thanks for watching!
m 0 0  l 1800 0  1800 158  0 158
"Given a single bean every 10 seconds, you can continue eating forever".
"Being the winner of a race show...
people you don't know will contact you."
"If you drag someone around with a blindfold, they won't notice that they've returned home"
Furthermore, "It's better to wash a Panda "
"Pa-ko is the weakest stare-down player",
"Small Saving" Theory, and more to investigate next week.