Welcome to Wednesday Downtown
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Who's there?
It's Fujimon!
FUJIWARA's Fujimon
Monfuji
-I am Monfuji
People love Monfuji
I am the most beloved
-Monfuji senpai
Today I bring you the second edition of a competition project
-What is it?
Please take a look
The 2nd Street Bingo Competition
The first edition was 3 years ago, do you remember?
I guess so
You do?
-Yes
Last time my subject was age
Sanshino Komiya's was weight
Morita's was rent
It was these  themes
Morita was wasting away
Morita finally got bingo after finding a 800,000 monthly rent
It took 18 days
Wasn't it 18 hours?
Long-term shoot
-18 days
Bingo finally after 18 days
Street Bingo Competition!
Everyone seems slightly tired already
That's for sure.
-Yes
We all know that it will not end for a while
Is a long time a bad thing?
You mean, like a lot of time to get footage?
-Yeah
That's really putting it mildly.
-Is that so?
Grip Strength
Phone battery
Residential Floor
This time we have prepared 3 themes for 3 people as above
They need to find passersby who match the corresponding number of squares to complete BINGO
Ready?
-Let's go
Whoa!
-Great
Yes, I phone battery power
Not bad
Grip strength
Ok, Minamikawa is Morita this time around
It's you. 18 days.
-Please, not 18 days...
It could be longer
No, no, I won't exceed it.
-Maximum number of days
So, this time also they can't go home until they achieve bingo
Can't go home?
-Yes
The staff arranged a hotel
Fujimoto, what is your plan?
First of all, the first stop, let's see
Go to Sugamo
I'm in "Pressure Battle!!!", and popular for haiku
Many older people in this area like my haiku
So it'll be easier to do this sort of location shoot there
Shoji went to Shinjuku, where men, women, and children gather
Minamikawa went to Omotesando in search of wealthy high-rise apartment dwellers
The three men were divided into three groups
Sugamo, i'm coming!
Its Sugamo
Everything's going smoothly so far
The first one is the best
First, we found this man
The clothes fell off
We are surveying everyone's cell phone battery
Can I see your phone?
-Yes
Let's take a look
75% 75 75…
No
-No
Sorry, thank you
78 and 72 are available
3% difference
Pity
Ah, come here, come here, come here, come here
Can you be on camera?
-Yes, no problem
Your voice is so high pitched!
Who cares?
I get mistaken for my mother on the phone
-A misunderstanding
We are asking people about their cell phone battery
Can I see yours?
- Yes
69, it's there!
Surprisingly easy
Thank you
Next is this lady
Here we go. Okay, 85, there we go
In addition
88%
-88
The one right in the corner!
It can be done!
Super fast
I'm very confident
I want to get as many as possible so I need to hurry
Its still the morning so people wont have used their phones that much yet
On the other side in Shinjuku is Shoji
Can I measure your grip strength?
Please start
Oh!
Rule：Decimal point is omitted
Awesome!
Corner! Thank you!
Adult men are generally in the 40s
-Yeah
The next one found was this father and daughter
The target is the only single digit 9
Seems like a 9
What is the result?
How much will she get?
Good
9.
-Yes?
Thank you
Is it 9?
Oh, great!
Next is Dad's grip strength
Come on, let's measure
About 40
42. Great. Thank you
So, Minamikawa
Where do you live?
Meguro
What floor do you live on?
I live on the 7th floor
There you go. A good location
In one hit!
Oh yeah
In the next few days
Rule：Only confirmations count
Is it possible for the staff to confirm you live on the 7th floor
Is it possible?
-Yes
Yes, yes, thank you
Sorry, we're playing BINGO
Please take a look
This is the 2LDK on the 7th floor of the Meguro area that we took afterwards
The house is so nice
Next are these three young people
What floor do you live on now?
2nd floor
What floor are you on?
I live in a single house
Rule：Detached don't count
But yeah, it's pretty good
What floor are you on?
-3rd floor
3rd Floor 3rd Floor
Awesome! Faster than expected!
Here we go
3 in the first 15 minutes
A good sign
Subsequently
What floor is your home on?
I live on the 2nd floor.
-2nd floor
I live on the 4th floor
4th floor
Minamikawa smoothly covers the low floors
5th
Everyone agreed to shoot
Is he faking this?
A fake location shoot?
After 1 hour, the bingo stands as is above
Initially, Minamikawa is in the lead
At this point, Fujimoto is eager to obtain big numbers
We are surveying people on their cell phone power
Can I see yours?
-My battery is quite full
Full charge... that's a good thing
Quite full is good
Is it time?
This one is also fine
Don't say it first!
Looks like a full charge
What's wrong with these people? They don't do anything
Not only that
What percentage
-100
100... don't you use it?
Why?
100%. Sorry.
-What the hell?
I'd want to ask why
You can use it a little bit, Saito-kun
On the other hand, Shoji in Shinjuku
Please start
There's 22
Got it, great!
So lucky!
Shoji's begins to obtain numbers one by one
At this time, Minamikawa
Met 2 girls coming out of a Mercedes
Where do you live? Tokyo?
Right
-Yes
Do you live in Tokyo?
Is it an apartment or a detached building?
Apartment
What floor of the apartment do you live on?
-Great!
31?
-Yes
31st floor
Sorry, how old are you?
12 years old
-12 years old
Where's mom and dad?
-Over there
Can the staff film your house in a few days?
Can I ask?
Thank you for your help
Just 3 minutes of shooting
Go go go!
OK？
Go go go
No problem
OK!
Nice people
Thank you
This is the 4LDK on the 31st floor of Minato Aoyama
Rich
13 and 19 would be very realistic
Indeed
That's a win
And Fujimoto is one step behind
Only got 3
What percentage
-55%
55 55… it's there!
Yes, yes, yes
Oh, yes!
What percentage
-92%
Here we go!
At this point he gets several numbers
No problem.
-Great!
On this side, a group of 6
Out of 6 people I should get at least one, right?
What percentage are you?
88% 46% 80% 62% 90%
None, what's going on?
6 people
-How can it be?
The last one, please!
What percentage are you?
Got it!
It's almost there!
After 2 hours and 45 minutes, Fujimoto is the first to be one step away from a line
Still got a 5
I've asked a lot of people, but there's no single digit yet
Have to wait until the evening
5 is indeed difficult
Sorry, hello
Then please start
Mikitty!
Making fun of him
Say something instead
Got 50!
Yes, 50, great!
Line!
10 minutes later than Fujimoto, Shoji is also one step away from a line
Can you find 63?
Hello, we are Wednesday Downtown
What floor do you live on?
1st floor
3rd floor
7th floor
2nd floor, 1st floor, 2nd floor
The floor bingo's difficulty suddenly becomes apparent
As Shoji gets numbers non-stop
Triple!
This is the status after 5 hours
At that time, Fujimoto came to Akihabara
Lots of cell phone users
Fujimoto is so smart
-Smart, right?
I'm here
There are a lot of people in Akihabara who use cell phones, right?
Looking for low power, Fujimoto soon found his target
He seems to be quite addicted to cell phones
He locks on to this backpack wearing man
We are investigating the phone power, what percentage are you?
I am 7%
7%?
This is close to 7
My God, it would be nice if we could wait a bit
More than that
I am 15%
I'm at 19%
I am 23%
As expected, there are many people with low power
But he just can't find the right number
On this side, Shoji needs big numbers
Can I go to the gym?
Okay, let's go to Gold's Gym
That's the top place in Japan
There must be a lot of people there who can get over 50, right?
A bit crafty
What's wrong with that?
At the same time, this man's bingo game has halted
I'll go directly to a high-rise apartment neighborhood
Smart
Go to Toyosu. Toyosu
A bit crafty
It's still a street. It's fine
Each of the three men rush to their destination
Hello, I'm sorry to bother you
We are surveying people on their cell phone power
Do you have a cell phone with you?
-Yes, I do
A flip screen!
You use the flip-top one?
Yes, I bought a new one
A new flip-top?
-Yes
Why not use a smartphone?
-This is more comfortable to use
Smooth. Always used it
-Yes
How much power is left?
Wow, flip-top 47!
Totally unexcited
Did my excitement not reach you?
Two different temperatures, these two
I'm so excited that I got the number
Do you know me?
-No, not at all
Not at all?
And do not know what my profession is?
-No idea
Do you know Downtown?
I'm sure you know!
I think I know
-Just "I think I know"?
Do you know their names?
The straight man is
Not so sure
Don't know?
Hamada!
You don't know the idiot either?
-Yes, I'm not familiar with them
Not familiar, even familiar with me
-Yes
This Galapagos man breaks new ground
※The Galapagos phenomenon is a Japanese business term that refers to the phenomenon of isolated market environments in which adaptation optimization is carried out alone and interchangeability outside the region is eventually lost.
I am 22%
-22
The following three numbers were obtained one after another
Fujimoto is now waiting on these 4 single digits
Want single digits
But it's going well enough
I've arrived
Gold's Gym East Tokyo
And so
Hello
Looks strong
A muscular man appeared as if he came out of a painting
How old are you?
-52 years old
52 years old, you have a good body.
-No, no, no, no
Doesn't look like 52
Beautiful
So, please start
It's coming. It's coming
What's wrong with you?
Probably just finished practicing
-I see
Only the muscular comedians understand
-Who?
At this time, Minamikawa arrives at the new location
Now living on the 15th floor
After arriving he gets 3 middle floors in a row
More than that
Hello, we are Wednesday Downtown
What floor do you live in the apartment?
I live on the 32nd floor
No 32...
What floor do you live on?
-42nd floor
As he expected, all he encountered were high-rise apartment dwellers
At this time
What floor do you live on?
I live on the 43rd floor.
-43
So high, you live so high
It's on there!
I never thought i'd get numbers like this
7 and a half hours into the game, Minamikawa finally almost has a line
And the 43rd floor 1LDK looks like this
And has a great view of Odaiba and Rainbow Bridge
At this point they are all very close
One moment, please
Why did you take it off?
Then please start
What's happening?
Quite high
Wow, there it is. 57
Great. Look at this. 57.
-Good
5 lines!
Can you come over here?
-Yes
Excuse me, come over here and line up
How much power is left in your phone
-59
What percentage
-41
-49
49 also, what happened?
What percentage
-66
66, no
Similar battery of these guys
How much power is left
-8%
There's an 8
Didn't expect it
BINGO!
8 hours after the start of the location shoot, BINGO is achieved!
Hello, this is Minamikawa
I'm done!
You did it first!
What're you eating?
Crepes, I'm eating a strawberry banana crepe
Really tired...
I'm super tired
Ok, bye bye
Thanks for your hard work
I'm home!
Remaining power is too easy
He's shit talking now
Anyone can find
Looking for 52
Sorry
Can I measure your grip strength?
Come and see these hands
I'm expecting a lot now
The goal is 52 60 or 63
Then please start
More than 60 is quite remarkable
What is the result?
Looking strong
Hasn't exercised yet, right?
What, why?
You lying? Stop it!
Sorry, we're Wednesday Downtown
What floor do you live on?
-50th floor
Eh eh eh?
It's really the 50th floor
Thank you so much!
The view from the window of the 50th floor, the highest floor of BINGO, is like this
So great!
The Rainbow Bridge under the twinkling lights, the beautiful Tokyo Tower, a great view
More than that
What floor is your home on?
18th floor
-18
Really?
-Yes
18, there's also a 22
Minamikawa now also gets 4 almost-lines
Let's end it right here. I mean it
However
A call came in.
-Give me a break
Is it possible...?
Hello?
What're you eating!?
Hmm? Chicken breast
Muscle care
Protein
I'm done with BINGO. Thanks.
-Wow! Damn!
Actually, 15 minutes ago
Gold's Gym, good choice
Grip strength...
-Eh? Uh, Japanese not so good
Grip strength
-good
Power
-Good. No problem
OK? Short interview？
-No problem
63, great!
Wh-what?
A punch would be great
Dammit!
It's dark
I thought I could do it
Victory was in sight!
-4 in a row
I lost
Yeah, it was close
However, whether we win or lose, the planning rule is that we can't go home without BINGO
Look, there's almost no one left
Places where there are people + rich people
Roppongi and Azabu, let's go!
So Minamikawa went to Roppongi
What floor do you live on?
2nd floor
-2F
What floor do you live on?
-4th floor
-2nd floor
5th floor 4th floor 4th floor 10th floor 3rd floor 3rd floor 4th floor
What's up
-What's going on
Residents above the 20th floor are hard to find
It's been 13 hours since the start and already 11:00
It can't be ended
People are going home
The crowds have become thin. Will he have to go the route of accommodation?
However, at this time
Excuse me, do you live around here?
-Yes, I do
Please, what floor do you live on?
28th floor
It's done!
Thank you 28
There are dogs
What's wrong with having a dog?
So i've finally got BINGO
-BINGO
After 13 hours and 15 minutes, Minamikawa finally gets BINGO
Awesome
What do you think?
There's not much to see here.
-Please don't say anything unnecessary
Not much to see but still very interesting
Also interesting? I can be satisfied then?
How about other themes?
Sight?
Sight
Too detailed, right?
-So much trouble
Take that C-vision chart
How many teeth are left?
Yeah remaining teeth
It was exhausting, they edited it a lot
I asked more than 200 people
So hard
-Exhausting!
It has a bit of a fake feeling to it
What do you mean?
How is that possible? Don't say that
The excellent point of this program is not to fake
I have not faked anything here, not even once
Not even 1 time?
Just once
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Magical Lovely!
So, without delay, this time we bring the second edition of a theory about duos
The 2nd 'The person who doesn't write skits has no right to complain no matter how boring the segment written by his partner is'
I see, that's true
We verified it last time
This is really a combination of things that will happen to those who write skits and those who don't
Relationships
-The relationship between people, but there are no rules about who should write the paragraphs
No contract
-Because there is no contract to skits its essentially done for free
That's true
Why must we write skits?
That's true. That's true.
I watched Matsumoto's manzai talent in the previous "Legendary Day" show
After the end of the skit was there no discussion about thoughts on it?
No, no, no. After that, there was no dialogue.
Also, I have never felt the feeling of having done something just myself
But Hamada is actually thinking "Thank you, Matsumoto" in his heart, right?
When its a good performance, certainly I think so
But as far as that performance is concerned
It's just a few random words
After it was over, he left without saying anything
Left immediately, right?
Not even any pillow talk
When performing manzai
When Matsumoto shares the ideas
What were your thoughts?
Would you just go along with it or...
I basically just told him all of them verbally
Have you ever had a conversation like "this doesn't feel right"?
No no
But I think there was a "huh? reaction
A "huh?"
Did I say "huh?" Did I?
Yes yes, you have
People who write the skits should be able to feel it
The feeling that the other person wants to say something
You'd have to be very careful and say "I feel that the line here isn't quite right"
Ah, that happened
I've been told, "Well...I do understand, but..."
"The audience may not be able to understand it."
It was said with respect, right?
-Yes, yes, that's what it is
After that, 3 duos will be tested to see if they have respect for the partner who writes the skits
The person who doesn't write skits has no right to complain no matter how boring the segment written by his partner is
So the initial duo is
M-1 Champion Magic Lovely
Hey, stand up. Stand up
Known for their unique segments
I didn't take your umbrella
-This seems to be going round and round
Are all penned by this man
After writing skits, Murakami is the first to hear them
Because it is the initial audience will observe the reaction
If it doesn't seem interesting
He'll say "well, let's not do this segment first," and then propose other segments
Murakami is not very direct words?
There will be a little grunt like "Hmmm..."
Same as Hamada
But won't say anything directly
Because he doesn't want to shoulder the responsibility of after the change
Like Hamada, super happy
It's a case of not saying
-Can't say, and although he can't say it he'll make a noise instead
Let's see Murakami's reaction to Noda's boring skit
The show "Best One" wants us to do some new segments, and short ones are fine
Seems very real
A few minutes
-2 minutes
For example, I start by saying, "I've started using dating apps," and "Oh, yeah?"
With that, Noda immediately verbally explains the content of the segment as he had done before
This time, Noda wrote a boring skit on purpose with the theme of registering for a dating app
Which will allow Murakami to perform super exaggerated retorts
The most annoying
"First enter your name and birthday"
"Oh, that's right... you have to state these."
"Then enter your body fat percentage and your calorie intake for the day."
"Oh, you have to enter this?"
The theme is that that the dating software is actually workout software
Murakami, who has been listening quietly
Then finally write the exercise history
"Workout Software!"
I hope you can move a little more
Then on the contrary, I will not move at all
Hmm...
-Your side keeps moving, that's all
In light of the super exaggerated retorts were not suggested until now
No particular opinion is clear
So, they start rehearsing
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
This
It's not a dating app, it's a workout app!
Ah, it's so boring...
Murakami, whose face was slightly red, retorted with all his might as requested
Became very red in a flash
Also
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
It's not even in their style anymore.
-What is this?
You! You!
That's not dating, its workout software!
For no reason, he is told to do it while lying down
He said "do it like a fish"
Yes,like a fish
Super hard work!
At this point, the skit develops even more fascinatingly
More?
I said you. I said that... Hey...
Not a dating app!
I'm hungry, I'm going home
And so it ends with a naked tirade that seems to reignite the "talented manzai" debate
But... can deal with undressing?
-Deal with it?
I don't think it's necessary to undress
Ah, he said what he thinks!
Here he shows resistance to nudity for no reason
But Murakami still basically accepts all of it
So, we reveal the truth at this time
What?
No... great
This is not a real skit, right?
Not like our style, it feels...
As expected, the content of the skit felt incompatible
No complaints. I'm really disappointed
Eh?
It's not ok to do just anything
Exactly
I think it is better to be grateful
So, the next one is
A threesome that has been together for 15 years
This is going to be messier
Jungle Pocket
A group who is a regular finalist in the King of Conte
This time its Ota, who is in charge of all skit creation
We asked him about his partners
Surprisingly, Saito is the type to go along with everything
The randomly written lines, he memorizes them exactly as they are written
Otake though, he's basically not interested in skits
This is not "good", right?
It's all "bad"
So I don't think Otake will say anything
This time, Ota wrote the following skit
A cheesy set-up in which someone falls suddenly in on a plane
With absolutely no chances to "play the fool"
This will definitely be said, right?
Immediately, the two of them read the boring script
Then
That's it
This will still be said, right?
Hmm...
Is there anything you care about?
It's just like a skit, right?
Well, although it's a corny beginning
There are still some...
Can't find any funny parts at all
Saito immediately shows hesitation
This will definitely scare you
Must be a little strange
As expected, Motake feels nothing
Already started to memorize it
Where are the parts to get a laugh?
A place to get a laugh?
The jokes
What do you mean?
To say where, including the wording...
Sure enough, because he hasn't written it, there is no way to forcefully express an opinion
Instead, Saito shows a little bit of "what the hell is this?
Are you angry?
Although its a bit cliche there are jokes
Is "intestinal obstruction" the funny part?
Yes, "appendicitis," "peritonitis," and finally "intestinal obstruction"
Using of the 3 diseases inferred from the patient's symptoms as jokes
A difficult order
The name of the disease is a little nasty
There is no discrepancy
However, the language sense of the words
Because "appendicitis" and "peritonitis" are the groundwork
Otake, what do you think?
"Appendicitis," "peritonitis," "intestinal obstruction."
-Yeah
To put it bluntly, "intestinal obstruction" is the final push
"Appendicitis followed by intestinal obstruction."
What does it mean?
The idiot next door, however, is motivated
Saito's dilemma is clear to see
Saito will say it of his own accord
Then, the rehearsals reluctantly started
In this area, there are 3 possibilities
3?
Appendicitis, peritonitis, or intestinal obstruction
Intestinal obstruction?
Finally
No, this is not quite right
He's said it
No, Ota, there's not really any joke here
He said it
That's it, right? This new...
That's not true, and there's no such new...
Don't you feel its a little off?
Otake has completely accepted the awful script
But Saito's irritation could not be concealed
Intestinal obstruction can not make you laugh
I wouldn't be amused by intestinal obstruction
Working in Tokyo, for example, here is...
Intestinal obstruction, its not the right feeling, right?
Well, not at all.
-It's not like that, is it?
I think it's just plain speaking with ordinary lines
And just like that, the intestinal blockage session with Jungle Pocket begins to heat up
Thank you for using Gibbon Air Flight 482 today
Always memorizing
Otake, its a mistake
Otake quits the meeting in the middle to learn the laughless lines
Is there a doctor, please?
You don't need to practice yet
We're talking about here, not your part
This guest seems to have a very painful stomach
This is too different from the skits you've written so far
-3 types? 3 types?
Even in the past, there are obvious jokes, but here there isn't
Although it may not be appropriate to say
But this skit will also cause you to suffer because you wrote it
This time, Saito, who has never complained about a script
Explicitly negates the content
Here we reveal the truth
Still practicing
What?
What's wrong? You two were both in on it?
Eh? I don't know. What?
Seriously!?
-I really don't know what's going on
I really don't know what... what's going on
What, what, what, what? Wait, I don't get it.
-Okay, you don't have to say anything
It's too hard to understand what it means
What's "too hard to understand"? It's super easy, right?
-What? What? What?
Beautifully done
And then finally
Although it is often forgotten, a former winner of King of Conte
Korkochikichiki Peppers
This is dangerous
Staff, come here!
As opposed to Nadal, whose job is mainly to show a bad attitude on TV
So nostalgic!
All the skits are created by Nishino
What'll happen?
If we did this sort of thing
Jiro would become silent
This time, Nishino created a skit
With Nadal playing a variety of roles at a festival
Performing multiple low quality fake-outs in a row
What'll happen?
A little acting?
It'll be performed in 4 days time
This time is the preparation for a looming live show
It was a marriage proposal skit
But I want to change it
Are you listening properly?
So annoying
From the very beginning, there is no respect at all for skit creation
It's Nadal!
If you want to drink, drink it properly
Instead, its a music festival
Shout "Arena!"
Like Ayumi Hamasaki?
Good evening, I'm Koda Yumi
Like Koda Kumi
Koda Yumi means...
"Good evening. I'm Koda Yumi"
Good evening, I'm Koda Yumi
Thumb, middle finger, pinky and ring finger, index finger will be coming out soon
It's coming out! It's coming out! The index finger is coming out!
It's a thumbs up
What does this mean? I'll just show my head, right?
-Yes, yes, yes
So, they sing about Koda Yumi's fingers and perform each finger with expressions
Somewhat difficult conditions
Difficult is indeed quite difficult
That's how I come out, right? And then what?
-Yes, yes, from behind the table
My knee hurts!
I'll try it
Then
Thumb, middle finger, pinky to ring finger
I don't know what expression to use!
Suddenly said a thumbs up expression
Just now the ring finger expression is the little thumb, right?
What do you mean?
Then you try it. I don't understand
Here Nadal is right
"What do you mean" indeed
What is the middle finger? What is the little finger? I don't know
I don't know, that look
Not at all like the tone of the duo that does not write the skits
Nadal starts to complain
The other one i've done before
This is too much trouble.
-The one about the proposal?
Eh?
-Proposal skit?
Yeah
-No, but...
I don't understand this one
You wrote this at night, right?
Not at night, but on the road
You sometimes just write some super boring skits
This guy is terrible, they're gonna break up
When they're good they're good
At those times I can trust you completely
But in times like this
This time...
If I wanted to do it, I wouldn't say anything
-Because I have to plan 6 segments
Although Nadal still at least has respect for Nishino who wrote the skit
I don't get the thumbs up expression
What is the correct answer... you say what expression to do
Perform the thumbs up expression
I don't know it
Feels like it's about to get interesting
In the end what is the expression, you do it, I do not understand
What the hell is that expression? I can't understand it!
I said you do it cause I don't understand it
Fury mode begins due to discussions about a thumbs up expression
Then I'll do it, won't I?
-Let's do it again
The thumb, middle finger, pinky and ring finger, index finger...
What about the index finger?
This is already a paragraph skit
It's a type of skit
At this point, they move onto other characters
I'll try it, but I don't think it'll be very funny
Where are you going?
Then you come out
I am Nadal A Dream
-Nadal A Dream?
Flashlight
-Eh?
Hey!
-Ya!
Then your crotch has gotten smaller.
-It's too bad
See you next week
Where's the fun in that?
Straight criticism
It's good to evolve this together, right?
I think it is quite interesting
But I don't want to do it
Then change the Nadal A Dream
Because the bad mood can't be stopped
We reveal the truth here
Always drinking water
The theory is will someone complain about a super boring skit if they aren't the writer
I will
Sometimes they're really not good
Of course I trust you. Of course
But occasionally they suck
I don't get it, let me make the thumbs up face
Is a thumbs up expression so cramped-looking?
That's it. Is this the little thumb?
This is the little thumb
-Where is it?
In summary
Nishino's tolerance is unusual
What do you think, Matsumoto?
Comedy is incredible
Even this became somewhat funny, so humor is difficult to understand
I actually think it's okay to act like this, a new genre
Jungle Pocket's one could become somewhat interesting
Nadal must have drunk 2 gallons of water
It's a gallon, right?
That one can be measured in gallons
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03