Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Who is it?
It's him.
-It's him, the competent man
It's Kawashima
-Hello everyone
Thank you all, today we bring you a special episode
This is it
All Counter-Prank Special!
What is this
All?
When it comes to Wednesday Downtown, there have been a number of prank projects that can be called masterpieces
This time, we have chosen some very popular style pranks to perform some counter pranks
Counter prank?
-What masterpiece projects of Wednesday Downtown come to mind?
Masterpieces...
You're taking too long to think
Is it impossible?
I don't even watch it
-You must have seen some of it
By the way, the target of these counter pranks are those who have been the instigators in the past
I see.
-Yes, we called them in again to re-do old projects
They will think, "It went down well, they asked me to do it again," and come to participate
They'll be more energetic than before.
-Thinking "Yes, let's do it!"
Then they'll be metaphorically punched in the face
In other words, for Hamada-san, it's a great VTR.
-Why?
One full hour
-It's true!
It's like Hamada-san's children's meal
Today is all stuff Hamada loves to watch
And so, the All Counter-Prank Special!
What will happen?
"I'm coming over now, wait for me!" If an angry person turns up, no matter how strange they look, the other won't say anything
A very interesting one
Last time was
Even thought you're a junior, you say bad things about me, I'm angry!
Diane's Tsuda ranted on the phone to Rice's Sekimachi
I'm coming to find you now, dammit, i'm so pissed off!
Tsuda acted quite well
With such anger, he went to Sekimachi barefoot
Hey, what the hell is wrong with you?
-How are you?
What do you want?
Why do I have to hear this stuff from you?
-What's wrong with you?
You're barefoot
Don't worry about barefoot, damn you!
It's over in a flash
Failure in just 13 seconds
So,
Thank you for having me
He said it
This time, Tsuda will attack Yojou in a strange costume
But he will be waiting for Tsuda in an even stranger costume as a counter prank
So that's how it is
What is your relationship?
I have a Tsuda Legion
He is a member of the Osaka Tsuda Legion
Tsuda Legion?
-Tsuda Legion?
-Tsuda Legion, yes
Tsuda Legion...
The disguise that this Military Chief will use is...
How many times does he have to say it?
Ah, all wet, all wet, right?
Last time the soaking wet Yamauchi was a success!
So this could be doable
And more extreme than a full layer of moisture is Yojou's disguise...
A doppelgänger doll in the style of the Hall of Civilization, famous for its "honey cake first"
Waiting like this?
-Just like this
It is difficult to ignore
So, it begins immediately
I'm calling him now
Here we go
Calling
I'll take it
Hello?
-Hello?
Hello
Tsuda
-Ah, hello
I was in Osaka last month, around the 10th
He starts lecturing about ignoring an invitation to drink
Are you looking down on me?
-No, no, no, no
Because it is me it doesn't matter, is that it?
No, I don't think that, really
Why do I have to be so embarrassed by you?
I'm sorry
-The alcohol doesn't taste good anymore, you bastard!
Not knowing that the other side has diverged, Tsuda's angry reaches its limit
Well played
Where the hell are you? Where are you now?
I'm at Yoshimoto headquarters.
-Headquarters?
I'm going over there now, you wait for me!
Hey, wait for me, you bastard!
-Yes, I'm sorry
He's scared to death
What the hell is this guy doing?
So disgusting looking
It will work. This will work
So, on the other side the body begins to be soaked
Why is it cold water
He departs
Can Tsuda maintain this anger even in front of the doppelganger?
The expression is very good
Very good, very good, the expression should be maintained
What will be the result?
He does seem to be reflecting
Oi!
What the heck are you doing?
I'm sorry
What the hell are you?
Ah, that...
Today I came to Tokyo to attend the meeting of an event and shoot a VTR
This kind of thing does happen
Yoshimoto really has such jobs
You damn...you damn, why...
Don't give up!
Why couldn't I get in touch with you?
Said it, said it
-Sorry
Already laughing!
All out to apologize
What the hell?
You'd want to say, "What the hell?"
I'm sorry. I'm very sorry
Why couldn't I contact you?
Go, go, go!
With the appearance of the junior exceeding expectations and the weird situation
Both sides seem to be reflecting each other
Tsuda couldn't help but laugh out loud
Why the hell are you dressed like this, ah?
It was really not intentional
Why are you dressed like this ah?
I'm sorry, it's because to shoot the event VTR
Why couldn't you be contacted until today?
I'm sorry
Three people apologizing together
You look...look down on me, right?
No, there is absolutely no disrespect
Already looking down
What the hell do you want to do?
-I don't want to do anything
I'm so angry
-I'm really sorry
In the face of the trio's total denial, Tsuda was completely KO'd
Laughing out loud is not an option
The truth is revealed
Three on one
What is this...?
Enough! What is this?
Do you understand what's going on?
Who can understand this?
This time, it is a project to counter a previously tested theory
I couldn't figure out what happened the moment I came in
But I thought I had to go on
I was really looking forward to this project!
Once in a while, let me be the undercover person
I'm sorry. I'm really, really sorry
That's enough of you, you piss me off
I see.
-Indeed
But it's true that there are cases like that, as a comedian
Being scolded when having dressed up and waiting to shoot
There are really cases when the other person comes over when they are free in between work
I'd still want to say "Why are you wet?
Just another sentence
-Yes
The great thing is that Tsuda gradually dried up
Because he was weaker, right?
Probably went home like that
What I find particularly funny is that, at the beginning, Tsuda was so happy to be chosen
Even happier than last time
The difference was very clear
He's really a very good object to make fun of
So, the rest is even more enjoyable so let's watch the next VTR
What is it this time
Next on the All Counter-Prank Special is...
Celebrity family members can accidentally be fooled by a bad impersonation of the artist
A very old project, this one
The last validation performed was...
Hello?
-It's me
What's wrong?
-My phone number has changed
You can save this number
You're not buying a smartphone, are you?
The quality of the imitation is very high at first, but
I got offered work as father and daughter
I was wondering if I should take it, I'm thinking about it
What do you think?
Father and daughter on stage together?
Um, no...hey?
Wait a minute. Something doesn't seem right.
-What's wrong?
The topic of "father and daughter on stage together" arouses suspicion
This time, the counter-prank is targeting Haraguchi
IMALU, who supposedly thinks the real Sanma is calling her, says something that cannot be revealed
And this matter is...
I am going to tell him that i'm having an affair
Hello everyone, i'm Haraguchi
Haraguchi thinks he will be taking revenge for the failed verification
The "It's me" mimic phone call beings
I'm going to call
Here we go, here we go, here we go
Hello?
-It's me
Oh, okay.
-I've changed my number. Save it
I've changed my number again, please.
-OK
This is a new number?
It's a new number. You can save it
Ok
-And...
What do you want for your birthday?
Ah, I'm still thinking about it
IMALU, of course, acts as if there is no suspicion
What are you hesitating about? Tell me
Thinking either a stereo or a vacuum cleaner
Why these two?
Pretending to be father and daughter for five minutes
Great. Very similar
Vacuum cleaner...
Dyson ... buy a Dyson
As the other believes the trick has been completed, the counter actually begins
That... sorry
Although it was you who called, this is a bit bad
There's something I want to tell you
What's wrong? I don't have much more free time
That...
There is a person, I often talk to this guy
What...what are you talking about?
The relationship with him slowly changed
I started to become attracted to him
-Oh
That...
It's a little hard to say
It's really the same expression that Sanma would have
That person actually already has a family of his own
Oh... oh...
Well...that...
Get off the phone!
Well to be honest it's an affair, right?
Danger, danger
It's better to hang up, right?
Upon hearing the word "affair", he quickly informs the staff of the emergency situation
But the staff didn't give any instructions, so Haraguchi continues the call
Is everything okay?
No, um, it's fine
Nothing at all
That...that...how...how...where...
Ah...
In the end, he couldn't even say anything
It's not right to give advice
At this point, IMALU adds another piece of info
Not only has it become an affair, but that person is also a bit strange
He said that if he broke up with him, he would expose it
If he says something bad, it'll affect you too...
You don't want reporters to start sniffing around
So I thought it would be better to talk to you first
I'll do something, don't worry, it is not a problem
But I still have to consider everything
At this point, it becomes impossible to reveal the truth
Can't discuss this!
And so, Haraguchi continues to maintain Sanma's manliness
The smile from a few minutes ago is nowhere to be found
And he's become distraught
Now... now... now is not the time to talk about this
So what should I do?
What should we do? Hang up the phone first, then we can talk about it
You wait first
Ah, I see
Then I'll contact you if there's anything.
-Okay, okay, okay
So, he hangs up the phone forcibly
This can not be broadcast
Is it the end?
Should I have said it? That I wasn't him?
An evil smile
As he failed to realize, there's more
So bad
The agent will go and explain what happened
Could you please wait a moment?
No matter what...
-No matter what we have to confess
Absolutely not to broadcast it
I feel like it's over...
Can you hold on a second? I'll make a phone call first
After the staff leaves,
I'm screwed...
Ah…
What's over?
He feels responsible
Yes, he's heard things he shouldn't have heard
IMALU's agent has talked to her
She's a little annoyed
She may complain to Yoshimoto and Sanma
Yeah... talk to Sanma...
It's a problem
Haraguchi has become super depressed
That's for sure
Normally such a cheerful person
I'll take full responsibility for it, and that's how it should be
But I still have to consider the worst case scenario...
We're being contacted. Please wait a moment
A big shock!
Damn
Teeth, at the dental office
Holding the teeth
-Incisors
"Are we going to be separated?" He thinks, looking at the dentures in despair
Farewell to the teeth
And so, the truth is revealed
Do it!
Whoa...
Worked it out?
Thanks for your hard work
-Thanks
How do you feel?
Ah wait a minute
Wait a minute!
What does "how does it feel" mean?
Haraguchi hadn't understood the situation, so we explained
Haraguchi's counter prank
Relaxed all of a sudden
That's great!
Finally tricked you!
Seriously...
I really thought it was over
When did it start to feel like it was all over for you?
Don't remember anymore
But maintaining the imitation until the end...
I wanted to say right away that it was me
I also thought you'd say it
But it becomes harder when you hear things you shouldn't
I really wanted the staff here to carry the burden too
Ah really too frightening, don't do this
You took out the teeth like this
Kept staring at the teeth
I just had it serviced.
-The teeth?
First job just after maintenance
"Oh, it's all over."
I was thinking "I'll never get it serviced again"
His teeth require a lot of care
Can't imitate him for the rest of your life
-I'd never imitate him again
Next on the All Counter-Prank Special is...
A person who is angry won't be corrected when using non-existent words
It is also the benefit of Soho, right?
But how? I still hope you can make an effort
In the end, it will not become a graveyard of the earth, no matter what happens in the end
This theory was tested by Morita last time
The next set of people are...
Thank you for having me
He seems the type to do it
Viking's Kotoge
He will lecture Darlings' Oda, a junior who he is close with, by using words that do not exist
But little does he know, the other will counter with non-existent words
What'll happen?
It's like aerial combat
It begins
Don't laugh!
King of Conte
Have you started yet? Or not?
First stage was probably at the end of June
How's it going? Are you ready?
-Well...
No sense of "this is it" yet
So what, it's not going well?
-It's not good. And there's anxiety
But everyone's familiar with your work
What about now?
Everyone thinks "Ah, Darlings are so funny"
Just a little
So you have a bit of "naked armor", I think
"Naked Armor"
You're not a frog at the bottom of the well anymore
You definitely have this kind of "naked armor"
But to not have anything prepared at this point is...
-It's true that...
It's not good
It's not like you have an "old woman's killer weapon"
What's that?
No, it's not.
So you have a bit of "naked armor", I think
It's not like you have an "old woman's killer weapon"
At the beginning Kotoge uses fancy words
Interesting is important
But in addition to interesting, you have to have impact
You have to have a grave-eating joke to do it
-Well, it's true...
Otherwise it's impossible
You have to shake it up like an "apache's earthquake"
Otherwise you can't do it
You'll just stop in the semi-finals
All the way to the semi-finals, semi-finals, semi-finals
But just can't get into the final
That's like a "three-and-a-half gauge struggle"
-Yes
At worst, you have to reach the final
Didn't your parents say anything? About this
-On the parents' side...
Haven't said anything to them for a while
They don't oppose, but originally didn't really support me
Neither for or against
"Hachigaya riot," neither opposed nor supported
Indeed
What about your wife?
She's always supported me
What a good woman.
-Yes, I'm really thankful for her
A "pero"-like woman
She's really a "pero"-like woman
If this was a real verification, Kotoge's weird words would surely arouse suspicion
At this point, the counter prank begins
Oda also begins responding with non-existent words, what will happen?
How do I put it? It feels like your style
It's "traditional Mexican", you know?
Talking shit
Speaking of which,
The skits, there aren't many highlights, more down than up
Now it's become a case of "not taking the lid off the pot", I'm kind of feeling that
-Yeah, yeah, yeah
When we were on "Golden Sma" before
We had good conversation with Nakai, right?
-That's right
We chatted back and forth
There weren't any obvious laughs, right?
I felt I was a bit lax
It was a bit tingly too.
-We can't give up though
It's a rung on the ladder, right? A step up
Now it's become a case of "not taking the lid off the pot", I'm kind of feeling that
It was a bit tingly too
Darlings Oda's two counterattacks slip by unnoticed
In my own words...
Because i'm rarely called, so no matter what the program is
We went with the mood of "three years of killing ghosts", and if we had any chance, we'd go
This sentence is also ignored
"Three Years of Killing Ghosts"
But,
Because i've been around you all this time, I also feel...
That awareness is not enough
-Well, awareness isn't enough
I also want to be able to "nail the heart" to move forward
-Yeah, yeah
Is it about to be exposed?
It would be nice to be more "commitnation"
-Hmm...
I won't be able to deal with myself if I become a "jackson sermon"
-Well...yeah...
"Jackson sermon"?
With three consecutive rounds of strange words, Kotoge seems to be suspicious
But this state is basically...
"Technocut syndrome"
-Indeed.
Indeed it's exactly the same
When I returned home and reflected, I also felt
It's just "technocut syndrome"
-Yeah...
Copied for use
I also think it's "American bike syndrome"
-Well...
As the saying goes, "mackerel are the same when fried"
-They are indeed the same
Frantically thinking
It's like "sucking on a ribeye"
-Yeah, it is
Frantically thinking
It's like "sucking on a ribeye", and it's like "eating a ribeye"
It's a "bone marrow bath", right?
-Yes, it is
Bone talk
Kotoge's words today are really very
Not even making eye contact anymore
"Cranial nail"
It's like "skinning a hot girl"
-Yes
The theme has changed
As they both exchange non-existent words, Kotoge has obviously come to a realization
This is a good thing
I'd like to "steal a stone like I did at the fire station and hold on to it"
It's become a game of who laughs loses
"Dumpling Festival" is working!
-Yes, it is
Thinking about what to say now
It feels like if that's all
Just making up words and saying them
Then, as a man, "I'm turning into a jellyfish"
-Hmmmmmmmm
It is true that there will also be a zombie escape
I agree
There will be times when "you can't see your back when you look in the mirror"
It's so nice to talk to you in such a heartfelt way
-Yes, thank you very much
Really a surprisingly constructive day
-Agreed
It's no longer working
Already obvious
What was that, seriously
What the hell
So painful
How do you feel?
-How do I feel...
I really did not realize with the first few words this guy said
But halfway through I suddenly thought "huh!?"
When there was a few a row, I thought, "Ah, this...must be it"
But I can only keep attacking, as can he
What could I do to end this?
No, it was really terrible. It was really terrifying
Terrifying?
-Terrifying
Next on the All Counter-Prank Special is...
Tough work
It's impossible to avoid being thrown by a sound engineer
Kasuga, please come over here for a moment
How can this be countered?
A fighter with judo experience pretending to be a sound engineer
Sorry, I'll adjust it a little
Can you lower your head a bit?
What?
This theory was thus exhibited
After that, the inescapable theory was repeated
The move was verified in different settings
This time at a social dance, the target's inner thighs will be attacked
However, the opponent will instead receive a counterattack
And this time the object of the counter prank is
Thank you for having me
A week before this shoot, she won the Rizin championship belt
And was a top three finisher in the national judo collegiate tournament in high school
Female Mixed Martial Artist Izawa Seika
It's not long been long since the match ended
But my body was recovered well
And my stomach's not bulging today
So i'm lucky
To challenge the reigning queen is...
Hello everyone
This guy practiced judo
Jungle Pocket's Ota, who was the judo champion of Aichi Prefecture in high school
No matter how I think about it, I think i'm in a good position
I'll be on the alert that it's coming, right?
I will throw even the current champion
This is almost like a match, right?
Afterwards, we rehearsed carefully to confirm the angle of attack, the timing of the attack, etc
Rizin Queen Izawa vs. Ota, the counter prank is about to begin
Golden Sma's Social Dance Department
So, he pretends to be a new dance partner for Golden Sma's social dance project
The two first practice the dance steps seriously
Finally, the official start of the counter prank, what will be the result?
So here we go, please
1 2 3
2 2 3
3 2 3
Will it work?
4 2 3
5 2...
Can't do it!
Locked firmly
It didn't go as promised
The result is completely different
Dangerous!
It's not at all what I thought it would be
Damn it!
Scared the hell out of me
Damn
Are you okay?
Worthy of being Rizin's current champion
Although the inside of the thighs were opened, she immediately put her foot in front of Ota to prevent him from throwing
Ota struggled
Then, when attacked by Otazato, she fought with beautiful body balance
Wonderful
Finally, a flying guillotine
Flying guillotine
Another roll and Ota was locked up perfectly to end the match
What is this theory again?
Gave up
Why'd you give up!?
Awesome
So interesting... awesome!
Winner
Eh?
You ok?
So strong
Sure enough
Even if you don't know anything, you can still do the guillotine
You ok?
No, no, no. How can I be okay?
He's gone crazy
Seriously, like the old TVs
My eyes are flashing when I look at things
At this time, Izawa explained the real plan to the target
I was supposed to counter your attack by going for your inner thigh
Inner thighs...that's why you resisted so hard!
Seriously, people who don't know anything shouldn't start a war like that, right?
However do you remember? A few minutes ago
It must be a subconscious reaction
You came and locked my neck
Great
So awesome!
These three counter pranks all became impressive duels
Three good plans!
-Impressive duels!
Kobayashi, what did you think?
The one with Kotoge
-The angry one
Oda's words are quite, how to say,
For example, "I can't see my back when I look in the mirror" and so on
They're all pretty much the same thing. I can understand their meaning at all
It's quite impressive.
-Kinda touching
It is true that when you look in the mirror you can not see your back
And Haraguchi was very professional from start to finish.
-Very good
※Yamaguchi Momoe placed her microphone on the stage at the end of the concert to signal her retirement.
Took his teeth and put them down like the microphone of Momiji
Moving on
-Retreated
That part was quite tough, I wanted to cry
After all, staff are important but you can't hurt family members either
He showed Sanma's manliness
In the middle, he clearly said "I will protect"
How are you going to protect?
If the confession was actually to Sanma it might go a different way
Possibly so
I think that's how he removes his teeth, too.
-Why?
His teeth can't be freshly maintained, right?
Next on the All Counter-Prank Special is...
Can you eat a lot of food when you are on a serious phone call to discuss something
This, this
Last time
My wife doesn't want me to go home
Please let me stay at your house for a few days
It's not impossible...
-Is it possible?
Nadal made a phone call to his senior Fujimoto while eating throughout
What are you doing?
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. What are you doing now?
-I'm not doing anything. I'm not doing anything. What's wrong?
No. What is that clicking sound?
This guy is so stupid
Exposed in a flash
This will definitely be exposed
So this time, Nadal will again make a phone call to Fujimoto
But in fact, Fujimoto will be on the other side of the phone also eating a lot of food
Please finish everything here during the call
Wait...eh?
Simply eating and talking at the same time
A little too much, isn't it?
Is this another counter prank?
No, no, no, no, no. Wait a minute
The rule on Nadal's side is he also has to finish everything
So finish it before he does
Finish first, before Nadal
Will Fujimoto be exposed faster than Nadal can eat all the food above?
Hello everyone
Nadal, who knew nothing, finished preparing in another studio
What if I succeed?
Do you have any requests?
I think success should lead to a little something
This is him asking for money
The motivation to work well... is completely different
I want...
We have prepared a bonus
-How much? How much?
50,000 yen
-Yeah!
50,000, yes!
A bonus is at stake
I will do my best to avenge my disgrace
It's mostly about money, right?
Wow so boring
So annoyed by this
Fujimoto is able to observe Nadal throughout
So, the two-way telephone feast begins
Will this work?
Hello
Thanks for your hard work, Fujimoto
-Hey, what's up?
It's Nadal. Sorry
-Yes
The tone of voice is so angry
What is it?
Fujimoto takes the tuna and onion sushi just like Nadal, and then
Fujimoto can see the other side
I'm gonna go to Bunshun (newspaper)
-Eh?
What what What's up? Were you caught doing something?
Matching the timing of each other's eating
A strategy to make the other side not know whether the chewing sounds are their own or not
In the theater
Fujimoto has the advantage
Yes, can see the other
Well, I cheated on my wife
What did you do?
With whom?
Who?
Mikitty
Seriously?
What a load of nonsense!
Fujimoto almost laughs at loud at the unexpected cheater
Seriously?
But
Recently
They're not even talking
After 20 minutes, Fujimoto takes the lead
The food is also out of sync
Tell me what you think
I want to apologize to Shoji... and to my wife
What the hell?
Both sides use the strategy of eating whilst the other talks
I'm sad, really
Really sad
Answered with the sound of chewing
I'm really sorry
It's sad
This man is stupid, right?
And then
What should I do?
-Hey, it's really sad
Both sides are waiting for the other to speak and freeze together
But just at that moment
How come you don't listen to people at all?
Nishino just cheated
-I'm the one who wants to cry. Don't talk about Nishino
Eating?
Silent protest
Eating
Nadal sensed that Fujimoto was also eating
I just said it, didn't I?
Completely exposed!
The performance is too bad
However, it appears he doesn't suspect a counter prank
As Fujimoto realizes
He takes advantage of the opportunity to sprint ahead
He can really eat
It's hard to eat so much
Sorry
Are you listening to me?
Listening
You're not even listening
Crying crying crying
Wait a minute. You're being weird
So, one hour after the start
Fujimoto is so powerful
Hey
Simply eating
No matter how loud the food is, the other party does not mention it at all
Nadal also accelerates
It has completely turned into a big appetite competition with one hand being an inconvenience
Ah, that's bad
That hurts
Nadal you can not do this, call someone else
What is this horror movie
The winner of this competition is
Finished
Fujimoto wins
-Good...
Impressive
I'm happy, but it was a tough win
So the truth was revealed
I really don't understand
I won
WIN
Confused
Okay, okay, don't do that
No one remembers your curry rice ad
It's a counter prank
Counter prank?
-Yes
Did you eat it too?
Eating the whole time
Always... eh?
Why didn't you say anything?
No, I thought it's okay for my senpai to help me while he eats
It's not good for a 51-year-old person to eat this amount you know
Was it the same amount?
-The same
It's so pathetic.
-What's "pathetic"?
You don't feel shame at all, do you?
It took a long time to realize
But in the end it became an eating contest.
-Yeah
Those that watch it will surely feel sick
Even though its just two people on the phone eating a lot
Next on the All Counter-Prank Special is...
As long as your appear polite, you can say anything and get away with it
So far, Kasuga has challenged a variety of greetings, starting with "Thank you for your hard work"
Its success rate was a staggering 89 percent
Hello
Thank you so much for your help earlier.
-It's okay
Yonagashima is the southernmost island of Kagoshima
-Yeah
It's Hamada that has the problem, right?
And so
Hello
-Thanks for coming
Thank you
Bye (please)
The theory that will be challenged is...
You can replace anything with "good morning"
"Good morning?"
So the first sentence is
"I'm going to take a shower"
"I'm going to take a shower?"
This is the first sentence?
-This is the first sentence
Level 1 is already high
And the target of this challenge is
A bit scary
Kimura Yuichi
This time, Kasuga will greet with "I'm going to take a shower!"
However, Kimura will by asking about what he said, and thus countering it
This can't fail, it's only level 1
Yeah, let's go
How will it turn out?
Excuse me
I'm going to take a shower. Please take care of me.
-Why?
Please take care of me today
-Why? Why? Why?
Ah, today...that show together...
-Hey, is it always like this?
Eh?
What floor is it on?
How many floors?
-Didn't you just say
You said, "I'm going to take a shower."
No, no, no...
-Said it
No, no, that... Good morning
No, you said "I'm going to take a shower", right?
No, no...
-I was wondering why you were taking a shower now
Well, that... recording the show together...
-You said, "I'm going to take a shower."
No, I said "good morning"
No...you said "I'm going to take a shower"
No, good morning...good morning.
-Then say it again, like you just did
"I'm going to take a shower."
-See, "I'm going to take a shower."
No, good morning...I said good morning
Stuttered?
Well, it was...right...yeah
You're not going to take a shower, are you?
I'm not going to take a shower.
-I was surprised when you suddenly said, "I'm going to take a shower."
Yeah? Go take a shower. Take a shower
Eh?
Hey...shower...hey...
-Sorry, sorry
How does this feel?
-Huh?
Failed? Failed?
As Kasuga didn't realize it was a counter prank, we explained the plan
Thought it had failed
That was scary.
-Is it scary?
Yeah, it' was really scary.
-You're scared because you were exposed?
Because I was exposed and also suddenly asked "why?"
It's the "why" question about something...
-That's it!
It is very rude to say hello like this as a junior
That's why he asked "why"...
But you don't usually ask "why" in return, right?
Then followed by
I was also asked, "What floor is it on? The bathing place"
Only at that point did I realize "i've been caught!"
I asked you if you were stuttering, and you said, "Yes, I was stuttering."
Too cunning, right?
-It's so embarrassing...
I see
Nadal and Fujimoto's matchup, both sides knew the other was eating, right?
-Yes
Sometimes the two sides only use chewing sounds to communicate, grunt grunt, that kind of thing
It would have been nice if someone had made it clear first
Yes, if Nadal had said, "What are you eating?
Then Fujimoto would be disqualified
But after all, you're calling, and the other party just happens to be eating
I think it's okay for seniors to eat and talk on the phone at the same time
But no matter what, this type of thing would only go one way, right?
Is it true that Nadal and Mikitty had an affair?
How would it be possible
If it's true, we'll all have to bear the cross together
We all know
So what does everyone think?
It's like a stalemate
However, the supposed instigator can't bring everything to a halt
Yes
-They can't give up halfway
In the end, it can only become a stalemate
Instead of counter prank special, it's more of a no defense sparring special
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03