Welcome to Wednesday Downtown
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Who?
I'm here
-Jinai Tomonori!
I am Jinnai, thanks for having me
Today I bring this theory
The 2nd " Verify that comedians' ranking increases the closer to their hometown"
The second time, last time was Kaminari
They ranked 42nd in national popularity
Then the survey area was narrowed down to Ibaraki Prefecture and Tamada
And also 1046
The results showed that in Ibaraki Prefecture they were in 4th place
And 1st in their city of Hokota
-It's the same as the hypothesis
So, this time we interviewed about 2,000 people
And compiled a national version of favorite comedians
-Got it
Here's the top 10
Impressive, right?
Sandwichman is clearly first, right?
Must feel good
Both of them have cheated on each other
Yes, these two people have cheated on each other
Never heard such a thing
Weird
So, the first group is
Thank you for having us
Saga Prefecture's DobuRock
Not like Saga people
The two of us are childhood friends
Kindergarten, elementary school, middle school, high school, and college all together
Never separated
These two people have been together since the start
We lived in Kokura, Kiyama-cho, Miyaki-gun, Saga Prefecture
The area codes are different
-Yes
Then which area will you choose to investigate?
Yes, which to choose?
-Definitely yours
Mine?
The scope of this survey is gradually reduced as shown in the figure
There are not many comedians from Saga, right?
To verify where they are number one
Your place in the national ranking is 86th
86th, so low
I can't argue with that.
-Yeah
I hope to get more votes than other entertainers from Saga Prefecture
First of all, we have to defeat Hanawa
So... a few days later
Hanawa is not very active in Saga
We approached DobuRock again to inform them of the findings
The ranking of Saga Prefecture
First, we conducted a survey of 20 municipalities in Saga Prefecture
Better here is the first
-Right
10th
On Youtube, he makes a special effort to introduce Saga Prefecture food and so on
I really like his efforts in this area
He always comes to the summer festival
His hosting left a deep impression on me
Hanawa
10th
Speaking of Saga Prefecture, we must mention him
After scoring a hit with "Saga Prefecture" in 2003
He's still popular in the local area
6th to 8th are shown above
The Hanawa Family's 3rd Son is also firmly in 8th place
Can DobuRock crack the top 5?
Next, in 5th
Interesting, just interesting
IKKO's imitation
We like Choco
Chocolate
-Chocolate
5th is Chocolate Planet
Next in 4th
They're work is very impulsive, and I like the feeling of fear and trepidation
They're Saga, the pride of Saga people
They do dirty jokes
I think dirty jokes are fun
DobuRock
It has to be DobuRock
They're awesome
I've already forgotten about DobuRock
Why?
DobuRock is 4th
Higher than expected
We are only ranked 86th in the country
Every year at the festival, the two of them shout "everyone together"
Men and women, young and old, all come together
Their dirty jokes have the support of all-age residents of the old Saga family
They've successfully jumped from 86th to 4th place
Although not in the top 10
Egashira 2:50 was in 11th
We beat Egashira!?
-Indeed
Local comedians all have the love
-Love!
We all have the same love from the place
-I'm so happy
This is a pleasing result
The ranking of comedians that are from Saga Prefecture in the area is shown in the picture
Who's first?
By the way, Orakio and Cherry Yoshitake both have 0 votes
So redundant
So, we narrowed the scope even further
Can they be first?
Possible
An investigation was conducted in Miyaki-gun, Saga Prefecture, which has a population of about 50,000
5th and up is shown above
DobuRock is 4th in Saga Prefecture, will they be 4th here?
Whatever program they're on they are funny
Downtown
I like Matsumoto, but I like Hamada the most
Thats fine
My first choice will always be Hamada
This is not necessary, no need to emphasize
Why are people still being asked this?
Next in 3rd place
Interesting, the way they get along is interesting
And their dirty jokes are funny
A little awkward to watch with the family
Balls and stuff
DobuRock
And so, DobuRock is up 1 spot to #3 in Miyaki-gun
Slowly rising
A little improvement
Higher than Downtown!?
I can't believe we passed Downtown
As expected of their home
It's really a pleasure to see this
Yes, wow
The top two are shown in the chart
Strong
Although they are not in first place, it is still within reach
Yeah
Next is the area with a population of about 17,000 people, where DobuRock are local ambassadors
Almost there
-Yeah
Kiyama-cho, Miyaki-gun, Saga Prefecture
So
I am good friends with Eguchi's sister
I've been supporting them since their debut
DobuRock is my husband's junior, my senior
Since childhood, DobuRock and I grew up and played together
I've been watching their Youtube and TV shows
After the survey was narrowed down to the town, it appeared that many people knew DobuRock directly
So, the No.1 favorite comedian in Kiyama-cho is
Which comedian do you like?
DobuRock
They're my dad's friends.
-They are?
Which comedian do you like most?
Of course from Kiyama
DobuRock
DobuRock's roots are surprisingly stable
As they pulled almost triple the amount of votes of Downtown to secure 1st place
Yeah!
-Wow, that's great
Happy
-So great!
They and my youngest son are classmates from elementary school
Has an especial good relationship with Eguchi
Watching them on TV
We were so excited when they won a contest we shouted hooray!
There's was the best sketch i've ever seen
We are classmates
You know them?
-That's right.
We have been together from elementary school to college
At that time did they do dirty jokes?
-Not at all
Eguchi always did a lot
Mori was also very serious
We rarely hear friends and family say they like us
So I was quite nervous initially
I guess I'll have to give out a lot of autographs
At least 10
The second group is
Good morning
-Hello
59th in the country
Tochigi Prefecture's Ujikoji
Best in Tochigi at least
-That's right
We are popular there
But we... No. 1 is a little tough
Strength...
-Not very stable
Where did you two meet?
-High School
I'm from Otawara
I am in Nasu-Shiobara City
What's wrong with your neck?
Whose hometown will we investigate this time?
Do you care?
We often go to Nasu-Shiobara for events
Indeed, there are more performances in my hometown
Nasu-Shiobara has a better chance of winning!
So, this time, we narrowed the scope from the prefecture to Fukuda's hometown and surveyed them in turn.
First in Tochigi, right?
And so the verification to see if they can reach the topspot begins
Wow
These people are all really funny
We are still so far away
What?
-Its not like that
Good morning
-Good morning
These are the county rankings
County is tough
No problem
Tochigi residents favorite comedians 10th to 4th are as above
They are in the top 10
But where are Tochigi's future ambassadors in the top 3?
3rd
What attracts me?
I like the way they use their dialect
Dresses like a gangster
Sushi Ni-gan
I really like Chidori
Chidori are 3rd
Next in 2nd
Hometown characteristics
The style is very warm
Everyone has passed away
What are you referring to?
For example, Yasushi and Eigaku
Ujikoji is a bit further down the list
This sorting is awesome
I'm sorry. I'm sorry
What a long list of comedians!
Tochigi Prefecture is very special
Ujikoji
Not surprisingly, Ujikoji's work enjoys high popularity in their hometown
Loved by the elderly, they rank 2nd
But 2nd...
That's very satisfying
Who's in 1st place?
The first is Sandwichman
-Sandwichman!
Its like prefectural high school and the top four has made it to the Koshien
Next, we survey in Nasu-Shiobara City
10th to 3rd are as shown
Can Ujikoji reach 1st place?
2nd is...
The clothing and their topics are interesting
Their lines are funny
Funny look
I like Sandwichman
That means
2nd is Sandwichman
They're 2nd
So, 1st is...
Because they're local
Ujikoji
Treasures of the north
And so, Ujikoki get 1st place in Nasu-Shiobara
Thank you!
That's great!
So close, so close
Oh, Kaminari's on the list.
-Yeah, came out of nowhere
They have their own program in Tochigi on Tochigi TV
That must be the reason
Don't want to lose them?
They have their strengths
But they're not to everyone's tastes
And finally, this guy
Hello everyone
39th in the country, Kano Eiko of Miyagi Prefecture
Sandwichman are also from Miyagi
-Yes
106, Sanjin-shita Sakuraga, Kurikoma, Kurihara, Miyagi Prefecture
Said it all
The division of Kano's hometown address is above
We conducted a survey in these 3 areas
My hometown is a shrine area
Festivals and New Year's Eve and other times
I go home to work then leave
I return home to work for the shrine and contribute to the local community
However, in Miyagi Prefecture
There's also Sandwichman
That's right, Miyagi Prefecture is the domain of the kings, Sandwichman
A tough opponent!
How close to home does Kano have to be to become No. 1?
First, Miyagi Prefecture
I think i'll be in the top 3
The first is the ranking of favorite comedians in the 35 cities, towns and villages of Miyagi Prefecture
10th to 6th are shown above
NON STYLE's always there
-Awesome
In fifth...
I've been watching his game channel on Youtube, its good
His sense of nonsense is good
-That's right, that's right
Ramen noodles, dipping noodles, Ichi noodles
Kano Eiko
Kano Eitaka
He made the list
And so, Kano Eiko jumps from 39th to 5th place in the prefecture
5th? Really, 5th?
There's still some hope left
Above Kato are these comedians
Sandwichman has 306 votes
Sandwichman 306 votes, 2nd is Chidori with 49 votes
Sandwichman is such a tough hurdle to overcome
How close to home does Kano Eiko have to be to be number 1 on the list of favorite comedians?
Next, a survey was conducted in Kurihara City, Miyagi Prefecture, with a population of about 64,000 people
10th to 3rd are above
And in 2nd with an overwhelming number of votes...
His words and responses are fun
I like his eyes
I support him because he is a local comedian
Kurihara City's
Kano Eitaka
The only comedian who lives in Kurihara is Kano Eiko
Only 2nd though?
1st is those two, right?
1st is Sandwichman with 132 votes
Close, close
Getting closer to #1
The next level is Kurikoma, Kurihara City, Miyagi Prefecture, which has a population of about 10,000
10th to 4th is shown above
The 1st and 2nd place finishers have a huge gap in comparison to others with overwhelming votes
Yes, that is to say that our Kurihara's
Kano EIKO
Kano Eiko is my classmate
But I don't like him
I like Sandwichman
As expected, the fight is between Sandwichman and Kano Eiko
He is a hometown hero
Kano Eitaka
They've done a lot for Miyagi Prefecture
Sandwichman
Kano Eitaka
We are cousins
What was Kano-san like when he was in school?
I think...
How should I put it
The type that would be bullied
I heard that he fainted after being beaten up
So, the top two in Kurihara are...
Seriously, can Sandwichman take a break?
Still no?
So, we narrowed our investigation again
Finally, we arrived at Kurikoma Sakurada in Kurihara City with a population of about 400 people
That's about right
Only 409 people
-Real hometown vibes now
The range is much smaller
Is it small?
The "Kano Family", our shrine is authentic
And there are many people with the surname Kano in the Sakurada area
I have a lot of people in my family
They are all relatives
If i'm not first this time... they're nothing to me anymore
Do you know each other?
Yeah
I still have tapes of him singing at home
The lyrics are all love-themed
When I look at it I get embarrassed so I close the box.
We're surveying the neighborhood about which comedians the locals like
Only Kano Eiko
And so, the top for Sakurada residents is...
Shoveling snow at the shrines and junior high school
Shoveling snow while chatting with us, I liked it
Sandwichman
But you were talking about the shrine!?
So, even this close to his home with just 400 people, the unbeatable kings still hold the throne
Double the score
No, really?
-Really
Wait wait
Take a breather
No kidding?
-No kidding
A big blow
The votes, what is the number of votes
Starting with me
-Okay, and Sandwichman?
It's double!
Why didn't you choose Kano?
-Why...
Sandwichman chatted with us like normal people
But Kano doesn't care about us
He is completely different from TV in real life
I remember this
Date was there
And he came with snapper and other gifts for the young junior high school students
What's to dislike?
Buying peoples' hearts with stuff is just despicable
So, the investigation was further narrowed down
To the local shrine
There are 4 households with a total of 7 people living here
Sanjin-shita, Sakuraga, Kurikoma, Kurihara, Miyagi Prefecture
Sanjin is...
-Sanjin is...
You can see it from my house
When I was a child, the elders there would educate me like my parents did
A real family
In fact, here
Can you tell me your name?
I'm Kano Musaki
All the residents are named Kano
It's okay, right?
-I also think so
If i'm not 1st here then it'll be humiliating
Indeed
There are 7 residents in this area
Except for one who is too old to be interviewed and Kano's mother
We asked the remaining 5
This isn't M-1
M-1 Grand Final
Initially a clear winner was not clear
And so, the result will be decided by the last Kano
It's up to him
And so, Kano Musaki's favorite comedian is...
We met during the recording of a program at the shrine
What did you think?
Certainly a superstar aura
Who is it?
Who is your favorite comedian?
Sandwichman
Despite all the participants being Kano's, Kano Eiko is still unable to achieve 1st
Shouldn't it be unanimous?
It's a lie, right?
Really?
-Really
Why not Kano Eiko?
Sandwichman has introduced Miyagi to everyone through many programs
But Kano Eiko doesn't even mention Miyagi that much
So, we ended up at Sakurada Shrine, Kano's old home
1 person
-Just 1
We went to the house
Also known as the shrine
-Right
Wait a second
I'm so scared. I'm sorry
With all these rankings of 2nd
I'm a little afraid of what my mum will say when I go back home
The other party agreed to the interview without being told the name of the project or program
Let's get right to the point
We're a TBS show that's investigating people's favorite comedians
Which one do you like the most?
Favorite comedian...
That's...yeah
Sandwichman
No way
-Why?
Leave me alone for a moment
Turn on the air conditioning
Getting hot
Is this Kano Eiko's hometown?
-Yes, it is
Why not your own son?
I do like my son, yes
But considering the parent-child relationship
Our project allows family members to vote. Do you still think...
I still think Sandwichman is the funniest
If you were to ask me which comedian I like the most
I wouldn't hesitate to say Sandwichman
This questionnaire is so hurtful
I'm gonna have heart problems
In summary
Kano can't get 1st anywhere in Japan no matter what
The results are amazing!
-Interesting
An unexpected result
-Yes
It's not Kano's fault, Sandwichman are just too good
Indeed
You can't not like them
Can't not
-They're personas are great
Their personas, especially Date who is super cheerful
Very gentle and will chat with anyone
Really great
Honoka what do you think?
The range is so small, but he still couldn't get 1st
Is it a problem with the person himself?
You should wear a normal hat when snowplowing, otherwise the locals won't be happy
Who wears a Chaplin hat while snow plowing?
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's A Masso
A rare guest!
Thank you for having us, we are A Masso
Thank you everyone
It's your first time here, right?
-Yes, the first time
So, this time, whether its theater performances or commercial performances
There's bound to be some interruptions at some point
Such as children suddenly crying
Or an old man making noise
Has Downtown ever encountered such a thing?
There were several times, but the first one that comes to mind is
One time a drunk shouted "Speak seriously!", a drunk old man
Hamada replied "Ahhhh!"
Scary
He even shouted at the audience and said "How much are the tickets?"
"3,000 yen." "I'll give it back to you!"
"Get the hell out!"
Such a thing did occur
This is an issue, is it not?
Then on the side I said "Oh, you shouldn't say that."
To make people think "the old man's just talking to much"
But it lightened the mood
-That's it.
Exactly, interruptions can be overcome
In fact, it can make things even funnier
This time we have brought this project, please take a look
Unexpected Occurrence Incorporation Championship
This time, it is not a test of one's ability to deal with an unexpected occurrence
Instead, its to add the occurrence to the performance
A contest to get a laugh from adding an unexpected occurrence to the performance
Unexpected Occurrence Incorporation Championship
The first to challenge are
Hello
A Masso
You're going to perform a sketch later
-Yes
How do you feel?
There is a very strange sense of tension
Because unexpected things are going to happen
We won't be able to finish our sketch properly
This is already established
Feeling a little unmotivated
Back two weeks ago
It's difficult
To conceptualize a sketch
Or determine the occurrence first and then work out a sketch around it
You should be used to it, right?
Don't I always forget my words?
No, that's an issue of our own making
-Is it?
This new mode of writing leaves the writer at a loss
But on the sixth day of writing the sketch
How's it going?
Ah, it's finished at least.
I thought of many kinds of unexpected situations
As I wanted to include the kind of unexpected occurrence that could actually happen
That's how I was able to finish
At this point, the content of the sketch is confirmed for the first time
It's a sketch that reeks of desperation
-It is desperate
Bravely facing a difficulty
-It's pretty brave
What difficulty will A Masso face?
Hello everyone
Hello everyone, we are A Masso, thank you
First time seeing these friends
Don't fart!
Why did you fart at the start?
-Sorry, sorry, sorry
Stop farting.
-Sorry everyone
Sorry, my name is Kano
The one who made the sound is Murakami
Thank you
Don't mention it. Anyway, the temperature difference is really big lately.
-Yes, it is
※Shinobu Sakagami, an fiery actor and host
Sometimes it's as hot as Sakagami in the morning
※Kenshu Furuichi, a social scientist, a writer, and a frequent critic of variety shows with calm venom
The night is as cold as Furuichi
I get it. I get it.
-It's true
So it's hard to adjust the body temperature.
-It's hard, indeed
So i've come up with a great idea.
-What idea?
Wearing a cardigan is good
Isn't that brilliant? Isn't that super brilliant?
No matter what the weather as long as there is a cardigan it's all good
-It's too strong
The weather bureau should make good use of her
Superb!
-Cardigans are good, right?
The best thing is, in terms of cardigans
There are different kinds of cardigans, right?
How about a cardigan like this one?
-Is that one a cardigan?
Isn't this a little thick? Thicker, right?
But the color match is very good, right? The color of the cardigan
-Color matching...
When going to TSUTAYA
※TSUTAYA Niaoya Bookstore
Black
Black cardigans feel great
Everyone look at this black
-Yes, this black
This black color is good, right?
-Indeed, this black cardigan is very good
But how can I say it, there is still a bit inadequate
The feel, right? Black is a bit earthy
Kir~
What are you angry about all of a sudden?
Can you stop saying "not good enough"?
-Sorry, sorry, sorry
I didn't expect you to be so angry
Talking of "inadequate"
I hate second generation comedians that look down on young artists
Who does? Which second generation comedians?
Let's not talk about that, what kind of cardigan do you think is good?
-What kind of cardigan?
Let me think
Liquid cardigan
-What's that?
How long are you gonna talk about this!?
Please leave, you who are not feeling well.
-Get out, get out!
Thank you for reminding me. I forgot to mention that if you feel unwell, please leave
Seriously, if you don't feel well, please go
-You guys are so boring
Of course, of course, you will leave if you don't feel well, you will leave, right?
Boring as hell!
Everyone, if you have something important to do, please leave
Sorry, I just forgot to say thank you very much
So boring!
※"Boring" and "clogged" are similar in pronunciation
Those who have clogged noses, please leave to unclog your nose
I'm sorry, I really appreciate it. So let's continue
As I was saying, about cardigans, which cardigan is better?
The liquid cardigan is best
-What is liquid...
Get off!
-It's weird, right? A cardigan is a jacket, right?
A cardigan is a jacket
Liquid cardigans are not acceptable
If a cardigan is liquid
It can't be folded into this sort of shape, right?
In the end, cardigans need to be carried around...
Liquid cardigan...
Eh? There's a typhoon today?
What a mess!
-It's so windy today
Staff, please close the door.
-The door is open
Sorry, this isn't a backpack flea market
Sorry
A a cardigan with that shirt would look good
This type of shirt is a good match
The cardigan is very versatile
No, I was asking "which cardigan is better"
After thinking about it, I still think
A cardigan as big as this is good
What are you talking about? That's enough!
Awesome
-Very good
Thank you
How did you feel about the performance?
Not bad
The concept wasn't bad
Maybe we're good with unexpected occurences
-Seems so
I think we now have more confidence to perform like this in the theater in the future
In addition, this time, in addition to the crowd of actors responsible for creating accidents
The general audience knows that something unexpected will happen but does not know the details
The next challengers are
Hello
Punk Booboo
Never done it before
I wonder what will become of it
It is true that you have to do it once to know
And there is still that little feeling of embarrassment
Shame
-Shame indeed
When your partner makes a surprised expression
Inside you're thinking "You know what's happening"
-It's true
What will happen in Punk Booboo's sketch?
Hello everyone, we are Punk Booboo
Thank you very much
Not everyone is willing to wave.
-Indeed
Thanks for coming, and I hope you'll remember us, Punk Booboo
If you remember, please go
-Please don't go. There's more to come
Please remain seated
I've been thinking lately.
-What's going on?
Japanese society has become really unsettled
Oh, there is indeed a lot of terrible news
It's really annoying. A lot of things have happened
So, you'd better practice that
That? What does that mean?
Yes, pray for mercy
Praying for mercy must be practiced, if you don't your life will be threatened
-You don't need to practice it
This kind of thing comes naturally
-No one does it, right?
I haven't.
-Its good to practice then
Can you pretend to be a murderer?
-I'll play the murderer
I'll beg you to spare my life in order not to be killed
Ok, I'll just say something like "I'm going to shoot" and so on
Hey, you, I'm going to shoot you
Wait a second
Ne ne
Ne ne ne
That's not going to work, is it?
Why do you only say "ne ne ne"?
Neh neh neh
-No, no, no. That's the same
Nu?
-That's not the point
What's with this line anyway
-Then what line is allowed
No, no, no, you have to talk.
-Say something?
I have to talk. "Wait, please listen to me."
-Oh, "Please listen to me."
Yeah, you have to let him hear you out. Come on
Hey, you!
-Wait a minute, please listen to me...
Wait a minute. Let's wait for the announcement in the museum to finish
Attention all guests in the venue
A wallet has been found near the men's room, can the owner please collect it from the front desk on the first floor
You guys didn't drop your wallets, right? No, right? Then it's you
Wait a minute, please listen to me
Mama...
-Anyway, listen to this kid before you listen to me.
Ask this child first
What's wrong, boy? What's wrong?
Mama is gone...
I can't find my mother!
Then what's your name?
Kouji
-Kouji
Kouji can't find his mother
Is Kouji's mother here?
Ah, I found Kouji's mother!
The child is standing here crying and the mother isn't coming to get him, really kind-hearted
A bit embarrassed, right?
It's okay, it's okay.
-Children are fine
It's the parents who are in the wrong.
-Don't say that. It's not allowed
So anyway, this is the perfect way to beg for mercy
-It's not perfect
The child was saved
-Not saved at all!
Only the child was saved. You have to be saved too
Add a little more pleading.
-Pleading?
"Wait a minute. I'll do anything."
-"I'll do anything."
Yes, and then they'll say, "What can you do?" That's fine.
-That's it.
Hey, you!
Wait a minute. I'll do anything.
-What can you do?
I'll quit smoking and I'll eat more vegetables...
Well, I will quit smoking and will eat vegetables.
And will say to the lighting technician to turn on the lights
-Hey turn on the light!
What's going on? Ah the light is on now
It's a perfect save
-It's not perfect
It just got darker then and brighter. You're completely hopeless.
-That's it
You don't know how to ask for mercy.
-Don't I?
You have to appeal to their sense of sympathy
※"sympathy" and "dojo"are similar in pronunciation
How about ask him if he wants to practice karate together.
-No, no, no, no, no. Not dojo
is to elicit sympathy
-How can I elicit sympathy?
"Wait a minute, I have a wife and children that I love very much."
-"I have a wife and children that I love very much"
Then the other party may stop
-So that's how it is
Hey, I'll kill you, you son of a bitch!
-Wait a minute, I have...
Hey, why haven't you contacted me lately?
A good occurrence
Well, I'm still working.
-You said you'd marry me, right? What happened?
Did I say that? Did I said that?
-You said it
Did he say he'd marry you?
-Yeah. Were you lying to me?
Wait a minute, this guy already has a wife and kid he loves.
-What are you talking about?
Is that so?
-No, it's not
Scum
-No
I'll tell the press about you.
-The press...ah, it hurts.
Wait a second
She hit harder than I expected
I said "wife and children who I love so much."
-Why say that to her?
What's wrong? What's that sound?
Nobody move!
-Be quiet
Wait a second
Na na na na na na na
I can't believe it really worked.
-That's enough!
Thank you very much
How do you feel after the performance?
I'm not sure
Whether it went well or not...
-Unsure
But the audience laughed more than I expected
-They did laugh
What exactly is the reason for them laughing?
We are also still figuring it out
But it went smoothly
Although there were unexpected occurrences
We knew what would happen
So we reacted a little then moved on
Maybe going a bit deeper would be better
There are still some places to explore
Introspection!
So, the final challenger is
Thank you for having me
ZAZY
I've had audiences laughing in strange places all the time.
I can't solve it at all by myself
So I have to take advantage of such
Halfway through the bit
-End it quickly
Isn't this just a project aimed at me?
During the R-1 competition last year
The flap on the results wouldn't flip over
I said "Ah..." for the first time in a live competition
There is such a sad past
So I am very sensitive to accidents
Now that I can control such issues I'm very much looking forward to
What kind of skit will ZAZY, who is said to be immune to accidents, produce?
Hello, everyone, I am ZAZY
Please just take a moment to get used to the ZAZY look
Looks like everyone is getting used to it. Thank you very much
Today, when I was in the lounge.
My hot pants ripped
So I had to use the raw ham that comes with the free meal to make some more
Can you tell? No problem, right?
What the hell!?
Raw ham with your meal?
It's best you get used to seeing it, okay?
Anyway, let's check out ZAZY's e-comic: Shibuya "Sushi Restaurant"!
Welcome
Hello, one
-Ok
We only have a set menu. Is that okay?
-Yes
Okay, let's start with sushi, please
It's corn
Corn?
Next up is...corn
-Corn?
Corn
Apprentice
Apprentice?
Foreign apprentice
Bucktooth apprentice
A single buckteeth apprentice
A five buckteeth apprentice
Foreign lower five teeth buckteeth apprentice
Hello?
Hey, I don't get it!
One tooth apprentice
Two teeth apprentice
Three teeth apprentice
One Tooth ISSA
One tooth
Binge eating mints one tooth
Mukkus with eight teeth
Toothless
Get off!
Love you!
What the hell...
I can't read it.
-Get off, get off!
Love you love you~
-Get off!
Get off!
3, 2, 1 GO
Hi, Hyokkorihan
Hi Hi Hi Hyokkori
Hi HI Hi HI
Ah, what do you want?
Is this Saito's room?
This is the stage of ZAZY
Excuse me
What is this!?
Messing around!
Please wait a moment
Please...
Ah, thank you
Please take care.
-Thanks
Love you!
It's almost time to wrap up
Spring, the distant spring
Close your eyes and you'll find her there
Bringing you my love
Your voice is ringing in my ears
Hi, Hyokkorihan
What?
Thank you for your hard work
Hmm
He's changed suddenly
No...a little confused, I guess?
Feels like the least funny performance of the past six years
So true
He knows it himself!
I just want to say "what is this?"
But it was a performance with unexpected occurences
So its tough to know where to end it
Don't know what to focus on
It's better to make the rules clearer
It's really too free
-That's it
This tournament can be done
But there's no need to play it back on TVer
Hey, why?
-Why do you say that? You can rewatch it!
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03