Tonight is...
Even if locked up
If you can get the "Lucky Item of the Day
You'll be able to escape - 1 hour SP
Trapped in a small, isolated house in the snowy plains of Nagano Prefecture
Patapatamama
Need two keys to escape from here
One hung from a ceiling 4.5 meters high
The other is tied around the neck of a rat indoors
History Books
-History books?
This is no use for escaping
In addition to whether the two can make full use of the lucky items that appear in TV horoscopes
To obtain two keys
And escape from this room
What about their final return to Tokyo?
So, hello again everyone
Same as last week, its Nanamagari
Thank you
Looking forward to the rest of it
This week's episode follows last week's episode
The first day's lucky items have been delivered, what do you think?
That's really...
-All useless
That history book is too thin, right?
If they get more then they may be able to get the key
More of the world's greats, indeed
That history book is too thin.
-That's true
Sweater could be slightly useful
But they probably don't even know the sweater will come in handy
Yeah, they both don't know what's going on out there yet
If they don't know, maybe they'll sell the sweater
They even said it was hot in the room
If they don't get enough items, it is impossible to escape, right?
Its like Abashiri Prison
※1965 Japanese film set in Tsunago Prison, the most famous prison for felons in Japan
Its jailbreak level
So, please continue to watch
Day 1
They received the lucky items of the day
And learned about the cash exchange system
They will sell them all, right?
Anyway, let's sell this first
It's warm in the room. You don't need it at all, right?
No need. It's warm inside
The two also have no way of knowing the weather conditions outside the room
Do you really want to sell?
So, they sold the important sweaters and history books
They can get a bit of money
Total 5,000 yen
Great!
It's good, 5000
This store's conscience...
We've got 5,000, right?
Hurry up and buy something!
"Lucky Chance, Small" Buy it?
I kind of want toilet paper
Wow... that's an amazing price!
After a long time of deliberation, the two purchased...
Sure enough, the same as you two
They both smoke
Balance
Cigarettes (one box)
Lighter
Toilet paper
m 0 0 l 274 0 274 60 0 60
Ah, they bought a box
Really addicted
In addition, they get dinner
Based on the horoscope ranking of TBS "HAYADOKI!
So, third place on that day, Aquarius, Shimabata, had sushi for dinner
Tenth place, Virgo, Kinoshita's dinner was rice balls
So delicious!
Are the rice balls good?
-Mmm
This sushi is also very delicious!
Afterwards
Just jump up
Can't reach it!
Ah, it's in
Ah no no no no
Ah! It hurts!
It's in!
The key is control
Rose  Fragrance
Ah, I hit it! I hit it!
Yes, you can
Its so steady!
Seems to be connected
They must reach the first key at a height of 4.5 meters with their hands
And the second key stays in the nest and doesn't come out at all
Give it a name?
What is the best name?
Since it has the key hanging
Call it "Nanking", right?
※In Japanese, "padlocks" are called "Nanking lozenges" from the Edo period, when it was customary to call exotic and small objects "Nanking".
"Nanking"
It's not a pumpkin
※"Pumpkin" is also known as "Nanking" in Japanese, and by the way, potatoes are also known as "Nanking taro" in Japanese, and groundnuts are also known as "Nanking beans"
Nan, come here
Nan is very cute
You just said it was disgusting
I'm used to seeing it now
Just an ordinary rat
Not a hamster or something like that
In the midst of their prayers for Nan to come out soon
The first day ends
It's so long!
Day 2
Here it comes, here it comes, the golden slot
"HAYADOKI!" is almost ready to start!
They can already get up on time!
Model prisoners
This is the most important part of our day
Get a "ladder"!
Ladder...
Here comes the lazy egg horoscope
Bad morning
Ladder probably wont come up
The best luck on this day of the holiday is...
Please
Come on come on
Scorpio
Ah, Scorpio first
Scorpio ah...
Wow, that's dangerous
Wow, not at all
The lucky thing is the picture at the top of the mountain
Luckily not the first
After that, they will all come out at once
Virgo second
Lunch box?
Lunch box...
Down undershirt, sheet music, balloons, couples things...
Beige
Calculator
Copy Paper
Crafts
Purple
Toothpaste
Ah, ninth place
Ninth place - hat
Hat...
Hat?
You should keep your hat. It's cold
Next, Asahi TV's Good Morning!
Antiques
Balcony
Essay Collection
Headphones
Headwear
Oil painting
Photo
Sugar-free chewing gum
Vegetable Soup
Wooden Spoon
m 0 0 l 0 43 l 370 43 l 370 0
Here we go
Sesame Tofu
m 0 0 l 0 43 l 370 43 l 370 0
There it is, Aquarius is Sesame Tofu
What's all this?
Why is there a balcony?
Don't need it
None are needed
Today's are so weak
So busy just at this moment in the day
Fine Arts Museum
MV
Milk-flavored Candy
Recent Selfie
Same Item as a Friend
Sportswear with Logo
Supermarket
Toothbrush
Yoga
m 0 0 l 0 43 l 370 43 l 370 0
Virgo is coming, library book
Book again!
Can be sold
Aquarius is coming, recliner!
Recliner
m 0 0 l 0 43 l 370 43 l 370 0
Can this be used?
Good
Wow, Aries is a toothbrush
Maybe you can straighten it to get the keys
Oh yeah
Toothbrush... so jealous
I see
Books
Hat
Lunch Box
Recliner
Tofu
Vouchers
Today they got 6 items
Later
The recliner is very high class
This feels useful, right?
Yeah
The two have finally obtained some bigger items
And thus begin looking forward to the possibility of getting the far-off key
Still too low, right?
It won't work
It's breaking down, it's breaking down, it's breaking down
You hold the top
It's dangerous.
-Looks like it'll break
It will definitely happen!
Whoa whoa whoa
Yeah, for sure
Ah, it hurts...
It was hard to climb here, but now it's so easy
No way
Ah, I feel like I can reach it
Ah, not enough at all
If you could climb up, you could reach it
Can't climb that high yet
After the two people realize how far they are from getting the key
Smoking again
This shot is very unattractive
Balance
Bath Set
Bath towel x2
Items purchased on this day
Toothbrush set x2
m 0 0 l 274 0 274 60 0 60
m 0 0 l 413 0 413 47 0 47
Where can you go in five hours?
Its really like a bathhouse
Should be able to pass Nagoya, right?
Through Nagoya?
-Yes
Then go to Tomei
It is in Mie?
I have no sense of direction, I don't know...
Five hours indeed
Maybe Lake Biwa?
Shiga Prefecture
I see
It may really be Lake Biwa
Once they leave the room, they will face other problems
What the hell are they going to do?
Anyway, the 3rd day begins
What will they do?
Seems like they'll never escape
Café
Food bags
Sweet Wine
Veg Juice
The lucky items for both of them today are the above four
5th place
Athlete's picture
Desk
Earmuffs
Sneakers
Suits
Sneakers and desk
Desk
Desk might be enough to reach
Desk?
Not bad!
This is very important
The desk is great!
This may be enough
Not available
Coffee shop
Desk
Sneakers
Sweet Wine
Vegetable Juice
They acquired sneakers that they'll unfortunately need after leaving the room
Sneakers absolutely needed
And a table that they hope can be used to reach the key
After all, they don't have shoes
The horde for the 3rd day
However, Nan remains in the nest
But will they be able to use the table to get the first key?
Is the height enough?
The table legs are so thin
-Unexpectedly
Upright on top of this should still be safe, right?
Feel much closer!
Is it close?
It's close!
Seems a bit far still
Is it enough to add this?
Really?
This is really enough
Be careful. Be careful
Good
Ah this really can really work
Stacked?
Exactly...
Be careful!
What is this?
Come on!
Eh? Seems possible
Please.
-Oi!
Did you get it?
Ah
Please!
Eh, what's wrong?
40cm away
Not even close
Out of reach...
Damn
Gimme a break!
Day 4
Same as before, on the 4th morning
Totally old men!
What was delivered to the two today was
Artificial fur coat
All are needed after leaving the room
This is very necessary
They only have tops
But...
What is artificial fur?
It's almost spring!
There is no need for this kind of jacket!
You need it!
This is not necessary
Even after escaping
Need it!
The two people, completely unaware of the situation outside, immediately sold the warm clothes
Ah, they sold it
And
Doorbell
This sound will definitely stay in our memories
It will be when we open it, right?
-Exactly
This is the last thing you need, right?
This will become our goal
Ok
Artificial Fur
Balance
Cigarettes(1 box)
Doorbell
Home wear
Keeping
Lucky Chance Small
Manga
Overcoat
Purchased goods
Selling
Toilet paper
m 0 0 l 298 0 298 150 0 150
m 0 0 l 298 0 298 172 0 172
m 0 0 l 310 0 310 85 0 85
Using the money they saved today
They finally purchased the long-awaited lucky item - small
Its content is
Here we go
5000 yen
Hey wait a minute, this is completely useless
What is it?
Magazine
This magazine is for us to pass the time?
These are the five magazines that were delivered
And
Please choose a favorite magazine and you can get the lucky items in the magazine
Oh
I see
Most of the lucky items in this book are female items
If its cosmetics and so on then we're done for
It's true
So, the magazine they chose was
We chose "The Television"
So
Winning and losing at once
It's coming. It's coming
High cocoa chocolate
Full Body Mirror
Full body mirror is that...
Can this be used?
Show me too
Wow, I have grown a lot of beard
Full Body Mirror
Recliner
Table
It doesn't matter, right?
Using it like that?
Clamp it
Can you pull it?
No...
Can't pull it?
Completely ungraspable
Being locked up for 20 days a month and playing at the theater for 10 days
Seems pretty good
No way... they are broken
By now, the two have gotten used to the situation
And have even begun to enjoy this life without freedom where they don't have consider their livelihoods
They're having fun!
Indeed
It's out!
Nan
Nan is out
It's out. So cute
Hey!
Hey, Shimo
Ah, its moving
Day 5
What was that just now?
I feel like I can buy a winner
Yes
Cardboard
Reserved
Album
Balance
E-Reader
English
Conversation
Not available
Lucky Chance
Medium
Purchased
Products
Romantic Comedy
Thermometers
m 0 0 l 1310 0 1310 485 0 485
m 0 0 l 310 0 310 185 0 185
Today, they sold a high-priced e-reader item straight away
And bought a lucky chance item for the second day in a row
Finally, this'll be a winner
That's three times the price of Lucky Chance Small
It costs 15,000 yen so it should be useful
They are trying to convince themselves
15,000 yen is expensive
The contents of the lucky chance is...
What is it?
The lucky chance
allows one to select a
specific horoscope for the next day
to get the selected items for that sign
This is also by luck
So that's our Aquarius, Virgo, and one more
This is awesome!
So, the two people use the cards they got to randomly select a constellation
They also have playing cards
This is the one to choose
① Aries
Will this choice be bad or good?
Playing poker
m 0 0 l 1310 0 1310 485 0 485
Open!
They're having a good time!
You have a flush!
-Flush
Even the hair on my ass is being plucked
They were gambling cigarettes
Thank you!
I've run out of cigarettes
That's not good
No way!
I was set up!
So crafty, you cheat!
This is prison, right?
Showa-era prison
Day 6
Can it been done today?
Aries is also counted
Yeah
Thanks to buying the Lucky Chance
Lucky Chance
m 0 0 l 1310 0 1310 485 0 485
Although they are pinning their hopes on yesterday's purchase
Here, something unexpected happens
What's going on?
No "HAYADOKI!
Ah, yes, because it's Saturday
Not on at the weekend
No "HAYADOKI!" on Saturday!
Playing something like a music program
No other programs on?
Indeed, it was a Saturday
So that's what happened
Thus, they realize the horoscope segment is only broadcast on weekdays
What about the others?
It is not on at the weekend
Once again, the search was extended to all TV stations
It's gotta be done
The first weekend
Oh, isn't this one?
It's "ZOOM SAT"!
Seems right
It should have a horoscope segment, right?
Ah, there it is
I think there is
It's there!
Aries
Ah, but it does not seem to say lucky items
What is this?
Aries, ah No. 10!
Ah, but... there's nothing
No mention of lucky items
No lucky items?
Ah, its here coming!
It says, "Don't be too greedy now!
The irony... so ironic
Next: On Fuji TV
Okay, come on
Ah, here we go
Here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go.
-Okay, okay
Aries is also useful
Virgo is the third
-Virgo is the third and then...
Jogging?
Aquarius, surprisingly, is a soba restaurant
One by one, all useless
So, the item from the lucky chance for Aries is...
Come on, come on!
What's this?
Wow what is this?
Lucky person!?
What the hell is "People who wear light clothes even in winter"?
This isn't us!
Unfortunately, their luck failed to materialize
Why did you choose Aries?
-What a waste
Cheated!
The staff knew that there was no horoscopes on Saturday, right?
They must know it!
There is no concern for the mood of those who are locked up
Because they've never experienced it
They've only ever imprisoned others
I'll complain to Downtown
You two are so annoying
The two of them must be laughing at us together with the staff
They're just a gang, or rather, the bosses of the gang
Getting ruder and ruder
And then, all they have to look forward to is dinner
Dinner
Ice Cream
Pizza
m 0 0 l 1310 0 1310 485 0 485
There is no dinner because there is no "HAYADOKI!
Too cruel, right?
Ahhhh
Adding fuel to the fire
How could you do such a thing?
Looks like an old man
An old man who fainted from the heat in the bathhouse
Oh
Lucky Item Escape Life
Not only that, but their misfortune continued on Sunday as well
Sunday there are no horoscopes
-None
Not a single one!
Nothing can be done about that
So none of them on the weekend
That's it. No new items, no dinner
The duo had a hell of a weekend
This is too tough
Only sleep
Whoa, this could really work!
This TV show is unbelievable
Lucky Item Escape Life
The duo who had a weekend with nothing to do
At this rate
Simply waiting for time to pass also feels a little redundant
The only thing we can do now is to catch Nan
Nan, right?
Indeed, there is a key
So, they spend their free time to seriously capture Nan
I think the cheese method is still the best
-After all, they like cheese the most
Just try putting cheese?
-Try to place it in a row
They purchased the cheese on the item list
Cheese
m 0 0 l 1310 0 1310 485 0 485
Bought
Then broke it up into small pieces to try and lure the rat out
And then Immediately
Here we go, here we go
Really will eat the cheese
Nan is reacting
So cute
And really likes cheese
Close the distance, hold your breath
Getting ready with the book
It would be better to put it out again, right?
Then step forward with your right foot
Make sure you use a capture method that can be broadcast on TV
It feels like it knows
-It's gone
It knows
But cheese works!
That's it. The two of them continue to hold their breath
Trying to become part of room, and three hours have passed
This is too much to bear
At this time, the opportunity came once again
Nan must be hungry
Don't rush
It's out!
Nan
It should also be a bit more familiar now
Not yet
Just want the key
It's out, right? It should be out already
Now now now
-Go go
Hurry up!
Great! Great!
Hurry up and block it
Well, well, well, this should be the best thing to do
After a week, they finally succeeded in blocking the exit of the cage
They have almost captured Nan
So
Should be able to just pick it up directly
Friendly!
Should be able to pick it up directly
Well, it works. It works
Just get the key
Be gentle
Great! Great!
Oh, nice!
Take it off
Got it!
Great! Great!
Nanjou is also quite happy, right?
Finally got it!
Finally got the first key!
This guy is already married
Other sorrows have arisen...
Lets use this key to open the first lock
It took a whole week!
It's in, isn't it? It's in.
-It's in
Its going
Ok
It's open!
Great! We did it!
So happy!
Great!
The only one left is this guy!
All that's left is this guy.
-Wait for me
Making progress ups the confidence
Finally got one!
It's been a week since they started, and they've finally made substantial progress
Married!
What awaits the hopeful pair?
Is it simply...
Despair?
Really the middle of nowhere
Infinite snow
Still so far
Finally got a key
The real problem comes after getting the key
-That's true
Opening the door is just the beginning
-It does start there
We were out in five days, and they've been in there for a week.
-Yeah
Since we had a task it felt like we had something to do
But the part of us finally being free was all cut
It was very tough
They didn't sell the cards and other stuff so they had something to pass the time
It's been a long time since I heard on TV that "even the hair on my ass is being plucked"
Lucky Item Escape Life
On the day when the mandatory house life entered its second week
"Today's Lucky Item" will make waves
Really?
Come on, please
Looks like Izumiya
Quite similar
Izumiya
Ok
It's here, Monday!
The lucky items appearing after three days causes the duo to applaud
Books
Brooches
Food Site
Notepad
The lucky items for each TV station were as follows
Among them, the most lucky item from Fuji TV is...
The lucky items given were
Aquarius
m 0 0 l 0 343 l 370 343 l 370 0
Is this...
What is it?
Wow, we got it!
Key!
-For what?
It says "TOYOTA" on it
Isn't this the key to the mobile vending cart?
Vending Cart
m 0 0 l 0 343 l 370 343 l 370 0
Is it a car?
Vending Cart
m 0 0 l 0 343 l 370 343 l 370 0
Isn't it great?
A lie, right?
Can drive back in a car?
Does that mean it's already here? The mobile vending cart?
I think it's already here
The two of them expected that the mobile vending cart of lucky items would be parked on the other side of the door like a miracle
Awesome
However
Because of the snow, it was not possible to drive it to the door
Ah, I see, I see
It's stopped there!
It was parked about 300 meters away from the snowfield
Going back to Tokyo in this?
Isn't this a jailbreak?
Do they do stuff like this on TV?
It's really a miracle
This TV show is unbelievable, right?
So
Lucky Chance
m 0 0 l 498 0 498 167.5 0 167.5
A big chance
Going for the big one?
Try to save up 30,000 yen
Must endure
The duo has immediately gained realistic confidence in reaching their goals
We also feel relieved
A one-two punch approach
Lucky Item Escape Life
So good luck brings good luck
Once again, they acquired unimaginable items
Coming
It's quite pleasing. Hopefully it will be done this week
Aquarius
The best luck today is
First...
Here we go
Oh, number one. Great
The first time the first
Big Tree
-It's a big tree!
A big tree?
-Isn't that good?
Surprisingly, they've bagged a big tree
Surprisingly, a big tree
Wait!
Oh, here it is
A big tree
Ah, a tree
A tree!
The big tree has arrived
Its a big tree
If we put it under here and stand on it
It's awesome
It should work just fine
On this day, they also received something useful for the cold
Big Tree
Jacket
Weather Forecast
That's important too!
Its the luckiest day since the beginning
Meanwhile, Virgo gets...
T-point card
Spring Tune
Grape Juice
Reward Card
Spring Songs
Yumi Matsutani: "Spring is coming"
Nostalgic. It's a CD single
So, they tried to use a large tree with a length of 3.5 meters and a weight of 150 kg
Incredible
150kg
They initiate an attempt to retrieve the key
Ok, on two
Don't get hurt!
Heavy, right?
-It's heavy.
I'll lift it
-I'll push
Just a little bit, just wait a little bit
Put it back first, put it back, put it back
-Put it back, put it back, put it back
Looks dangerous
It's tough to get it up
I see, it's because it's too long
It's too heavy
Is it not good to lean?
So, they fought with this big, heavy tree for an hour
Yeah need some support
Table
3rd Day Item
m 0 0 l 0 343 l 370 343 l 370 0
Using the lucky item desk they got at the beginning
They were able to put the tree against the wall
Even so, can you get it?
It's up?
Sneakers
Will the two be able get the final key and escape?
Wearing shoes now
Can they climb up?
Grandpa
Encouraging an old grandpa
Okay, wait a minute
Be careful, looks scary
It feels good.
-I'm holding it still
It won't suddenly fall, right?
From the top
Because it's a big tree
Lean on the side first
Ok ok ok
Impressive
Should be able to get it now
Go for it!
Be careful! Be careful!
Be careful indeed!
Wow, this is really a bit slippery
There is no place to hold on to
True
What about the wall?
-I can't reach it with my hands
Just a little further
Need to climb a little higher
One more step up
I'll go up a bit more
I'm up i'm up
Shouldn't be a problem
I'm up!
-At the top!
Looks scary
It should work. It should work
Like watching a documentary about escaping from prison
No way!
Oh, he can reach it
Finally, the moment has come
Okay, its possible
-Did you get it?
Great!
Got it! Got it!
After 215 hours they finally got the key
Great. Got it before the weekend
And then, the moment they'd been looking forward to for 9 days finally came
Let's open it!
But they both still think this is the end
What kind of expression will there be?
It should be ok
The time has finally come for the escape bell to ring
Indeed
Great!
They thought this'd be the end
Let's open it together
Its just the starting bell
Ok, one, two
The time has finally come for the escape bell to ring
Great!
Let's open it together
Ok. One, two
Great!
What is this?
One-two, great!
Thought the staff was already waiting outside
Still one step behind
What is this?
Eh, wait
Playing DEPARTURES
Isn't this all snow?
Wow, it's cold!
My breath is white!
Close the door quickly
Where is this place?
Season 2 has started
Wait a second
-An endless field of snow!
Eh, where is this?
Isn't it spring already?
I don't even have shoes
Barefoot
Ah, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm wearing it
These are the comments of people just released from prison
Go in first, go in first
Went back
Wear the jacket?
Indeed, it's great to have a jacket
Getting equipped
What have you done? What the hell is this?
What's going on here?
Hey, what's with the snow?
Also using a drone like thing to shoot!?
What the hell is going on here?
Barefoot!
Can someone please come out?
Where is the mobile vending cart?
We're not being lied to, are we?
-Fooled?
We can't escape yet
Failed escape?
Because of the snow
Snow everywhere
This is impossible
Can't walk barefoot!
Really can't, barefoot
What should we do?
Throwing a tantrum now
Don't want to see this
The chair is taking a beating
Broken heart
What happened?
Thought it was the end
We can only be on TV if we have to go through this?
We really can't be on TV unless we're being punished huh?
Both crying
Wedding ring...
What the heck
His words are a little hard to top
Why do we have to go to such lengths to be on TV
I've never seen him in such a state before
He went berserk
Crazy!
Punched the chair
He hit the hinge part
Really pissed off
They are so desperate to get home
The expression of joy after opening the door
Ok, open!
He's half a beat late
The momentary freeze is the most real response
Frozen in place
What do you think so far?
I think, if they stay one more day
Get some more lucky items
And go back in the car with no problem
But I just don't know if their mental state can still hold up
But even after working so hard to get back to Yoshimoto headquarters
They don't have any more work
Just back to the real world
Lucky Item Escape Life
Spending the night in despair
Only departure remains
It is impossible to escape without cold clothing and shoes
That's true. That's true
Today's lucky items are
In the beginning, they won a lot of prizes!
Car Recorder
Flower shape mould
Headphones
Poached eggs
Yoga
Items such as headphones and flower-shaped molds
Nothing useful for protection against the cold
Yoga?
-Poached eggs...
At this time
Although we don't know what it is
You can only bet on a good chance of luck, right?
Saving money is better
I hope we can get winter clothes from here
Right?
Car Recorder
Doorbell
Flower shape mould
Full Body Mirror
Headphones
Literature Books
Office Desk
Outerwear
Poker
Recliner
Retention
Selling
Sneakers
TV Series Manga
m 0 0 l 298 0 298 150 0 150
m 0 0 l 298 0 298 50 0 50
m 0 0 l 398 0 398 50 0 50
In this way, they place everything on the lucky chance items
So far, including the items exchanged
No need indeed
They sold everything but the sneakers, jacket, and doorbell
Sell the doorbell
Successfully raised 35,000 yen
Really all sold
So next
Lucky Chance Big
m 0 0 l 298 0 298 67.5 0 67.5
Please grant me a great chance of luck!
-Give it to me!
Their hopes are high for the lucky chance
What's inside?
What exactly is it?
30,000
Lucky chance is big
Choose any one program tomorrow
and get the full horoscope lucky items
Get it all
-12 of them
Oh, so that's it!
It's a big opportunity indeed
In other words, we must wait for tomorrow's show
Just like that, the possibility of escaping today is reduced to a wisp of smoke
Which program will they watch?
Lucky Item Escape Life
Day 11 is upon us
The two put their money on Asahi TV's Good Morning!
This time we can get 12 in one go.
-Great chance of luck
Get all 12
Great! Get all of them!
Some good ones, please!
Coaster
Editorial
Electric Bicycle
Green Fish
Massage Chair
Postcard
Speckled pattern
Sportswear
Tableware Mat
Ticket Office
Web Release
Writing Brush
m 0 0 l 0 927 l 1115 927 l 1115 0
So, the 12 lucky items obtained are as follows
Successfully got a jacket
Here we go, here we go, here we go
-Here we go, jacket
Sportswear
Virgo
m 0 0 l 0 927 l 1115 927 l 1115 0
Actually, it's a Virgo lucky item that Kinoshita would have gotten anyway
Anyway, they finally got the clothes they have been waiting for
Haunted by sadness
The duo begin to see the hope of a successful escape
Great!
They then confirmed the situation outside of the house during the day
So
Oooh, blinded
It's too harsh
Snow blind
I can't see at all
Incredible!
-The snow is too reflective
Coming out barefoot?
No one around either
Look! So many mountains!
It's all mountains as far as the eye can see
So many mountains
Where the hell is this? Seriously
Barefoot on the snow...
Let's go
Wait a minute. The white balance of the eyes has not been adjusted back
It's been too long since I've seen the sunlight
O the light of the sun
Yeah, haven't seen the sun in over a week, right?
The eyes must have been hit hard
Emotions are running high!
Nice!
And so, while the mood was high because of the long-lost sunlight
Both smiling now
Both relearned the importance of protecting their feet in the snow
What to do then?
Coaster
Massage Chair
Notepad
Postcard
Tableware Mat
Writing Brush
m 0 0 l 398 0 398 70 0 70
m 0 0 l 448 0 448 70 0 70
Among the items purchased from the Lucky Chance opportunity
Ah massage chair is quite expensive
They again sell the unwanted items
And then
Oh, here we go
Three pairs
-What three pairs?
Three pairs of socks
m 0 0 l 298 0 298 67.5 0 67.5
Oh, slippers.
-Ohhhh this is good
Three pairs of socks
m 0 0 l 298 0 298 70 0 70
拖鞋
Slippers
Three pairs of socks
m 0 0 l 298 0 298 70 0 70
Slippers
Three pairs of socks
m 0 0 l 298 0 298 70 0 70
m 0 0 l 298 0 298 72 0 72
Slippers
Three pairs of socks
m 0 0 l 298 0 298 70 0 70
m 0 0 l 298 0 298 72 0 72
Slippers
Three pairs of socks
m 0 0 l 298 0 298 67.5 0 67.5
m 0 0 l 300 0 300 75 0 75
I thought I would get cloth slippers
Not the one with the hole at the front?
-Yes, yes, yes
I thought it would be a problem if it was like that
If this is the case, it will work.
-Because there is no water seepage
This should work
Okay, we can use this to go down the mountain
That's it, they bought socks and slippers to protect our feet in the snow
Finally, they're heading for the end of the line at Yoshimoto's Tokyo headquarters
The moment has, at last, arrived
Really ringing the escape bell for the last time
Please
Ok
Okay, let's go!
It's cold.
-It's a little cold
Oh 43,500 yen, still got some money
Looks like a criminal
What a shitty place!
The wind is really harsh
Just jailbroken?
-Jailbreak sense is too strong
The first goal of the two people who came out of the hut was
Parked at a straight line distance of about 300 meters, the lucky item mobile vending cart
What will happen?
It feels like watching the life of condemned men
Time and space are distorted
Still haven't left yet
Try to step in my footprints, will you?
-Ok
So caring
-Wearing slippers, right?
Feet are sunken in
It's a little cold
So cute
Ah, feet are really cold
Keep going!
Is everything okay?
-Oh, I'm stuck
The snow is indeed very deep
Go back?
Feet are really not working
Also wearing shorts
Are you okay?
-My foot was hit hard
Although there are slippers, right?
Cold, really cold
Emergency evacuation?
This snow is too difficult to top
What the hell is going on here? Where are we?
Why is the snow so thick?
Too tough
Head back
It's that bridge over there, right? Go that way, right?
Seen it? You seen it?
Ahhhhh
You can do it!
I'm stuck
All the snow is pouring in and my socks are soaking wet
My feet hurt~
My feet are already in a bad state
Can't walk like this
Sure enough, in the snow where your feet can sink in
Isn't it reckless to walk in only flip-flops?
Soon the cold turned to pain
Only a little better than barefoot
Crouched down on the spot
But they've come so far
Ah can't stand it!
Aah! It hurts!
Have gone too far to return
It hurts~
What to do?
Pour some pee on it, right? How about that?
Seriously, it might be warmer to pee on it
Humans are incredible
The two who have no means to warm their feet
Stay there for a total of 15 minutes
Okay, you go first
Leave me behind and you go
What program is this?
Let's go back together
I've had enough of this
There is only one last stretch of road left
He'll die if he stays, right?
Film-like scene
Can you do it? Can you still walk?
Can't leave him there
How are your feet? How are they holding up?
Cold feet
It's like they're eloping
Any car going there...
It is no different from escaping
Keep going!
Slippers are hard to walk in
What is it?
Go back
Is Wednesday Downtown this kind of show?
It's freezing. Frozen into a popsicle
Can't feel my fingers anymore
I can't feel my feet anymore.
-Feet are done
Arms are also starting to lose a bit of feeling
Ahhhhh~
Still a long way to go
Still such a long distance
Is 300 meters this long?
It's getting colder and colder
I can see the car!
I can see it now
Just a breath away
Really like a movie
We can do it.
-We can do it!
We're doing it!
Just 300 meters of untrodden path
They walked for 2 hours
Indeed, if the road is not good
There's no more snow in front of you
It's cold... my feet are cold...
Finally
The car's here
Great, we're in the car
Okay, let's go
Let's go!
We're gone!
OK
-Ok
OK OK OK
Still don't know where they are
Seriously, where is this?
Where is this?
-It's too remote
It's good to be able to leave
Which way is Tokyo?
I can't tell at all
Yes, there is nothing around
Ah, there are many private houses
There may be several households
There are several houses
They look too suspicious
Isn't it scary? Such a person suddenly coming to the door
Coming to the door in slippers
Surely suspicious
Sorry to disturb you
We are filming a program from TBS
Don't do it!
Can we talk for a little bit?
Super scary
By the way, what county is this?
Nagano Prefecture
Nagano Prefecture ...
Where are we in Nagano Prefecture? What is the name of this place?
Hakuba
Hakuba?
Sorry i'm a bit confused
Thank you
Sorry
The kid is a little frightened
Eh?
Where did they say we are?
-Here...
Hakuba in Nagano Prefecture
Hakuba?
Hakuba...
Okay, let's go back to Tokyo
It's finally over!
-It's finally over
8 km from Hachioji! Almost there! Almost to Tokyo!
-Great!
We're almost in Tokyo!
-Awesome!
We're in Tokyo!
Yes!
Yes! Back to Tokyo!
Spring... the distant spring...
If you close your eyelids, there will be
Run out of gas!
We're here!
Arrival Kabukicho
A familiar place.
-Kabukicho!
We've arrived at Kabukicho, where Yoshimoto headquarters is located
Wow, what a relief!
Civilized society
It's been so long since i've seen women
And then
That's a bit...
Will this line be used?
After 12 days
A total of 268 hours, they escaped and returned with only the help of lucky items
How was it? Lucky item life
What kind of question are you asking? It was obviously awful
But it's not like there's another job tomorrow, right?
In terms of comedy jobs, this month there is just one more
One live show
-Only one live show
That live is on January 11
And?
-Eh? Is that the end of it?
A sad ending
But they finally came back
A grimmer reality awaits them
It'd be better if something happened after escaping
The car broke down or something
By the way, you were saying that very loudly.
-You've been saying it a lot
Run out of gas!
In a very loud voice
"Gasoline disappear!"
When they arrived in Kabukicho, he said, "Ah..."
The feeling that this is the end?
And the Hakuba kid
You shouldn't open the door so easily
-Indeed
So true
Absolutely wrong, wearing shorts with flip-flops
An older man with a cape came knocking on the door
At least put the chain on
To prevent crime
So then, everyone
Please welcome them onto the stage
Oh!
-Awesome!
Thank you all
We're back!
Thank you for your hard work.
-Welcome back
Yeah, it was too hard, really
It's a relief to be back
-Finally, we're back
The end of the VTR was too unpleasant
I thought you had passed away
We are alive
-Alive and well
How do you feel? You must have a lot of questions you want to ask
When did you first notice the mobile vending cart?
When we came out to let off steam during the day
Did you see it?
-So far in the distance
Walked out with the feeling of "that should be it"
But weren't sure when you actually left
Yes. Also the staff
Wouldn't answer any questions
Is that it? Wouldn't even answer even when asked that.
-I see
No one would say anything
Should we go that way? They you won't answer even if you ask
We just had to try
Well, the staff here have communication problems
Is that so?
Really?
They are people who have not learned to speak
You were the same as Nanamagari, right? Just wanted to smoke
It's better to quit smoking
Just for that you wasted time and money
Yeah, but I can't do it.
-Why
If you do not have a cigarette, you will go crazy
Really?
I really looked forward to smoking a cigarette or two every day
But honestly
You may be suddenly put on live or something
-True
You'll be banned from TBS
It's really possible
They're on parole now
We did it to get on TV
All we have to offer is time
To appear on camera
Please feel free to use us more in the future
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03