Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let's get on with our first presenter please
First?
Who is it?
It's Kendo Kobayashi!  -Hello everyone
This time, I bring you the second instance of a project that was very popular
Really?
-Yes, it is this:
The 2nd survey on the best comments made by comedians to date
So its that
-This is it
This is highly anticipated exciting
-Do you remember it?
We've got some great participants this time
-Really?
They took part in a survey, so please take a look at the VTR
-Okay
So, a survey on what comedians think are the best comments made by other comedians, and,
No matter how much you don't like a certain food, as long as it is the best version of it, you'll acknowledge it's deliciousness
The 2nd survey on the best comments made by comedians to date
The first is Yamauchi
What is this photo!?
When I used to be on "Ametalk"
There was a section about artists who came to Tokyo but felt that they couldn't fit in
We were participating as a party that had integrated into Tokyo
I think I remember
The ones that couldn't fit in were Seshita and Plus Minus
The program made things difficult for those involved
Like suddenly asking them to eat very spicy dishes
To exceed the supposed limit of spice they could handle
Plus Minus's Iwahashi made an extremely accurate analogy about Seshita
So precise even that I would say it should be passed down by future generations
In my heart, it is the absolute first
Is that so?
-Told by future generations
Iwahashi's extremely accurate analogy is as follows
I saw this one
Go for it!
-Chance!!!
Chance!
Seshita's experiencing a crisis
What a weird face
He's become Sakurai!
This
-No, no, no, no.
Certainly accurate
It really was so precise
Indeed, it's exactly the same
When he made that face
Everyone laughed because the expression itself was funny
But when everyone was laughing, only Iwahashi-san
It adds another layer of meaning
Spoke up and said "He's become Sakurai"
Is it that accurate?
And indeed, he had become the same as Sakurai
He did become the same
In that moment when everyone was laughing
Someone piped up and said "He's become like Sakurai"
Everyone thought "That's true," and it made the atmosphere even more lively
In all honesty, because everyone was laughing so hard
Hamaya (his partner) thought he had said it
What happened?
He thought "Seeing the Sakurai-looking face caused the analogy to just come to me"
He thought he'd done a really good job
I'm scared, what is this?
-Scary, scary
I don't really know why, but when I heard him say that,
Why?
I thought "No, no, no, wasn't it me that said it?"
That's what everyone was thinking
After hearing the line "He's become like Sakurai"
I was also thinking "He's become like Sakurai"
An amazing phenomenon
Because it fit so well
So I thought I had said it too
Scary!
What an amazing phenomenon
But after watching the broadcast, I told Hamaya:
"Oh... Iwahashi said it..."
"Oh yeah... it was Iwahashi"
I see, I guess it's possible
I said "I'm really suprised it was Iwahashi..."
Can such a thing happen?
-Impressive
Next is the comment that Morita was most impressed by
About a year ago, on Wednesday Downtown
There was a theory called "The first B in BKB is 80% Super"
It involved me going out on location
In the studio part of the theory, Matsumoto said something
It made me think "Ah! As expected of Matsumoto Hitoshi!"
I don't remember at all
Morita was impressed by the following quote from Matsumoto
I remember
-Really?
The theory is...
BKB- Ah, sorry
-No problem, please
Hamada-san, is it okay?
-Of course, it's yours, after all
Is that so? I'm sorry
The last dumpling?
Can I eat this?
That's the one
This was really awesome
That's it!
I can understand this one
First of all, the speed at which he says "the last dumpling?"
The tone is very good
Such a quick retort
It's too fast
There's also the conciseness of the phrase that makes it so much more effective
This is essentially, to put it mildly
A bundle of politeness (over-politeness)
But if you just said "a bundle of politeness" straight
It could be a little confusing
Instead, he just said "the last dumpling?"
In such a concise sentence, a perfect interpretation is offered
And included "dumplings", as everyone knows the phrase "dumplings are always in abundance"
With this compact turn of phrase, there's a sense of speed and quality
This guy is so talkative!
Indeed, I think it's perfect
This is so embarrassing
It's a shame that its embarrassing
If you think about it, Matsumoto does this type of thing as much as possible
He provides these sort of statements in all sorts of settings
Not just on Wednesday Downtown but also Downtown DX
Even if the room has a weird atmosphere
All of a sudden he's able to cut in with a comment and lift everything
He's very strong in general fields
Strong in general fields
It may be rude to say, but regardless, it's the way I feel
What are you talking about?
Also, some of the guests in the same theory also left other strong comments
Say three words along the lines of the three initials: BKB
Junior, please let us hear your BKB
Eh?
-Say something that BKB stands for
In the face of Jinnai's sudden prompt, Junior's instant reaction is as follows
Junior, please let us hear your BKB
Eh?
-Say something that BKB stands for
Starting with BKB
-What the hell do you think?
At the wedding (bridal), I sang "Bitter Coke" and made people laugh
-Isn't that me?
How dare you do such a thing!
-That's awesome!
That's beautiful
-Amazing
Hey-ya!
-You can't end on "Hey-ya!"
Isn't that what happened? Isn't that when you say "Hey-ya"?
Junior's reply is also a real powerful
His reply was also very fast
I'm impressed he came up with the word "bridal"
I doubt BKB himself would think of the word "bridal"
Even the creator couldn't think of it
Next is the comment that Hamaya was most impressed by
I saw it on TV about a year or two ago
On "God Tongue"
Daian appeared in a segment on the show
About after coming to Tokyo things were supposed to get better
Why is it always like this? That sort of segment
While everyone was giving their own opinions
Gekidan Hitori made a comment
It really made me laugh
It was so funny that I went back and watched it several times
Its the sort of thing that only Hitori could say
A very, very enjoyable comment
The comment by Gekidan Hitori that made Hamaya go back and watch it several times is as follows
Tsuda didn't think of using Nishizawa, did he?
You only care about yourself
I don't only care about myself
-You only think about yourself
No consideration at all for Nishizawa
That's true
-It's sad
What's "too sad"
You really have this all for me look on your face
That's not it!
-There's the long-awaited look
You've never felt he cared for, have you?
-Never
It feels like your struggling alone, right?
-It really does
Sometimes it really feels like I'm struggling alone
It's hard, isn't it?
-It's hard
Forget it, let's just kill Tsuda
Why!?
Why do I have to be killed on this show!?
This was really funny!
The phrase "let's kill him" really shows a complete lack of consideration for Tsuda
"Forget it, that's it, let's just kill him while we have the chance"
This sort of vibe is just too interesting
Its really frivolous, right?
As a proposed suggestion its just too frivolous, right?
"Why don't you sit down first?" It's this level of frivolity
"Why are we all standing? Let's sit down first" It's this level of emotion
It is indeed frivolous
This feeling really makes me laugh
Forget it, let's just kill Tsuda
Why!?
Why do I have to be killed on this show!?
Next is the comment that Hollywood Zakoshi was most impressed by
About 20 years ago
TBS had a show called "Gachikno!", right?
※A documentary variety show broadcast by TBS from April 1999 to July 2003
One of the projects was called "The Way of Sincere Manzai Talents"
All Kyojin appeared as a lecturer at one point
His comments were really unforgettable!
You're choosing such a well-known thing?
Eh, is it?
We all remember this
I don't remember
Really? It's that famous?
It was really like a bolt of lightning
It really was like rolling thunder
The comment, which struck like lightning, was as follows
It was indeed a shock
Take it from me
Unscrupulous people
I don't want them to become famous
I don't want people with bad attitudes to become famous
I just want some good people to get ahead
To remain
If you keep going this way, even if you stay until the end, nothing'll happen
You'll lose face
I guess you don't really know me
If you were my student
I'd PAN PAN ya!
※All Kyojin wrote in his book: I actually didn't mean to say that, I said "PAN PAN" because I meant "I want to beat you up" "if you don't do a good job I'll do it" and so on, it was probably a result of my own anger and excitement
This sentence is really too famous
So this is the source of the parody
-Yes
This, this is really great
I can basically understand the meaning of the words
"If you were my student, I'd PAN PAN ya!"
But the "PAN PAN" thing is...
The actual meaning is a total mystery
It can be considered to be incredibly imaginative
Indeed
I do think All Kyojin said it in this way deliberately
What the heck is PAN PAN
"Please use your own imagination to understand it as you see fit"
This sentence has infinite imagination, does not it?
If he had just said "If you were my student, I would have beaten you up"
It would contain this one connotation and that would be the end of it
"If you were my student, I'd PAN PAN ya!"
What he intends to do, until now, is still unclear
I really don't get it
What're you gonna do? Beat the face until it's round like a pan?
Or do you mean PAN PAN, like beat it?
He didn't say, and he didn't do it, right?
Subject to interpretation
To what extent and how much he wants to PAN PAN is also unclear
PAN PAN, indeed...
What constitutes a PAN PAN is also unclear
There's a saying "If you were my student...i'd forgive you"
Which is the way it is because, after all, you're my student
Instead, I think it should be "If you want to be my student, I'd PAN PAN ya!"
So that's how it is
We also asked Zakoshi if he had his own version of this comment
Is there an exaggerated parody about this
-Yes there is
It's a good thing you asked me, there is
Really?
-Can I perform it?
So, here is Hollywood Zakoshi's "If you were my student, I'd PAN PAN ya!"
If you were my student, I'd PAN PAN ya!
That's the normal one
The exaggerated "If you were my student, I'd PAN PAN" is:
If you were my student,
I'd po-PAN po-PAN-ya
It's like that
It should be po-PAN po-PAN
What is he doing?
So, Hollywood Zakoshi's favourite comment from All Kyoin is...
If you were my student, I'd PAN PAN ya!
He's been storing this up for a while
-This is too cheap
Right?
Bang bang be be is just PAN PAN!
There's also a Ba
And stored up for quite a while
It's really a golden line
Matsumoto was also mentioned
I also think the phrase "the last dumpling" is very strong
Still though, its embarrassing to being commented on so much
If it continues...
I'll PAN PAN ya!
No, no, no don't use it here
I have a feeling you're gonna keep using it
Is it for here?
Does anyone else have any favorite comments?
I think Iwahashi's line "He's become Sakurai"
The fact that it made people think they said it was really an interesting phenomenon - A phenomenon indeed
It is
-It's incredible, isn't it?
It also really shows how accurate the statement was
The most interesting thing is that, after the "He's become Sakurai" line
Seshita became more interesting
-True
Okay, we also have more comedians that have been asked
-Oh really?
Please see the next VTR
-OK
Next is the comment that Chocolate Planet's Osada was most impressed by
What left a deep impact on me was...
On the 2020 edition of Dream East-West Neta Battle
Hamada's comments have stayed with me ever since
The most recent?
This program was for the New Year period
So it made wonder why he said what he said
It was really shocking
I really think that only Hamada would say such a thing
It was a pure reflection of Hamada's singular style
The words of Hamada, which do not fit the New Year setting, are as follows
Weekly Ferrari
There is such a thing
How's the assembly going?
-I'm just starting to work on it
There's just one more step left until I complete the Ferrari of my dreams
-I'm looking forward to it!
For this week's issue #4
Please allow us to take a week off from publication without notice
Don't just decide that yourself!
Is there a hiatus for this kind of stuff?
For Jinnai's performance based about Deagositini
Which was the grand finale of the western army
Hamada was constantly muttering during the performance
What were you saying, Hamada?
Isn't this unfunny?
Scary
This is where it starts
Hamada, you shouldn't say such things, right?
No, the audience was more or less laughing
-Yes
But this group here, completely still and silent
What a way to start the New Year!
This is the hardest part
Up until this point there has been some unfunny guys, right?
No
-No no no
But not to this extent
Isn't what this guy said even harsher?
Indeed
Seriously, unfortunately its not the same as Deagostini, the laughter will only come later
Matsumoto's comment is also very strong
Indeed
The audience was indeed laughing
Very impressive indeed
But the performer side was certainly a bit...
This guy is too much
Not so much laughter
From that point on, their team lost a bit of energy
Even if this is the case, it does not matter
But regardless, I think it's very impressive to be able to say it so bluntly
Everyone can have this kind of confused feeling at times
Correct
But in this type of big new year show, most people wouldn't say this sort of thing
However, in my opinion
Being teased can also be considered a chance for redemption
Its possible to be able to tell that the comedians on set aren't really laughing
After all, you can directly see their reaction
You weren't laughing?
The feeling of "Wow, the comedians aren't smiling much"
It can indeed be felt
But in this case, instead of ending on a whimper
The situation can be improved with a bit of teasing like this
I think, in a sense, this helps save the misfire
I see
Next is the comment that Yoshimura was most impressed by
Yoshimura
It was about 8 years ago on Shikujiri Sensei's program
We shot a different kind of project than usual
Which was about common people
Focusing on a reclusive self-sufficient artist living in the mountain
Sawabe went to interview him
How do you live?
What do you do? How do you stay up to date?
Due to the lack of money, he was interested in what the person ate
And the analogy used for a certain food was really awesome
It's a perfect statement
I watched the VTR in the studio with a few other guests
And until now those words have stayed with me
Sawabe's metaphor that Yoshimura will never forget is as follows
It occurs when the program crew are shown the food which the individual has stored for long term preservation
Is it stored here?
Regarding hand-salted mushrooms...
Is this a chunk of The Predator?
Its like you're collecting and storing pieces of The Predator
Wonderful
If it were me, I'd say "Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait"
"Wow, it's scary, it's disgusting," and so on
And I would definitely add a phrase like "it stinks" to fill the blank time
It's more likely someone would say "this is so and so and so"
Or say something beforehand
Like "this can't be shown" or something like that
It'd stop at the level of "something is wrong with this person"
But without any assistance, he just shot off a line instantly
"Is this a piece of The Predator?"
You can only do something like this with strong comedic sense
If it was me, I would have dealt with it normally
"That's disgusting," "Wow..." and so on
Which would most likely hurt the other person's feelings
And that old guy almost certainly doesn't know what The Predator is
"You seem to be saying something but I don't understand what you're saying"
But when we look at it, we think, "Wow, it's a piece of The Predator"
Look at the way the hand reaches in and takes it out, the way the thing shines
Isn't it just a piece of The Predator?
The more you look at it, the more it looks like it
It's subtly brilliant
If there is prior rehearsal or pre-rehearsal
I don't think it'd be possible to come up with it
Only without these it is possible to make such an off-the-cuff comment
This is really a person who can react quickly!
Really strong explosive power
Yoshimura not only admires Sawabe's talent but also...
There's really a lot...
For example, something that Ariyoshi said
This was also a TBS program
A variety show that aired on TBS from October 2008 to February 2009. The main theme of the show was to help a celebrity get his or her wish, but if the wish was not granted, the celebrity had to pay all the expenses and other responsibilities
How many years ago was it? Hm, it was a long time ago
It was called "Pact with the Devil", right?
Oh, I really miss it
Although I don't remember it completely precisely
According to Yoshimura, the comments in question were extremely subtle
13 years ago
An exterior scene between Ariyoshi and a political mobster
Scenes like this just don't exist anymore
Its incredible to think Ariyoshi once did a scene like this
Once again, I think he's great and I'm sure I couldn't do it
Its a scene in which he's going around collecting questionnaires
It's really awesome
The moment that Yoshimura was moved by Ariyoshi's youthful and heroic act is as follows:
Excuse me, Hama-ko
It's already a strange start
Can I talk to you for a second?
-What do you mean?
We are the "Pact with the Devil" program
What are you doing, bringing a camera with you
Wait a minute
-What are you doing?
Ouch, we just want to know about a questionnaire we asked you to do for this program
You did not fill it out, right?
I don't even know about any shit like that
You don't know what?
Aren't you being a little too rude right now?
You're the one who's being rude, you bastard!
So impressive!
I was paid... eh, that's not true, dumbass.
That being said
-I don't have the ti-ti-time to deal with your questionnaires one by one, you idiot!
You're the one who's the idiot!
So harsh
This is the questionnaire
-Shut up you're so annoying!
What's the problem you old fart?
Hamada, wait, ow ow ow!
So messed up
I'm talking about a questionnaire, a questionnaire
This is my car!
So where's my car?
Why is the car I was in not here?
You're getting too excited!
Do you have dementia?
Hamada, can we talk a little more?
I've had enough. Don't open it
So awesome
Just a bit longer
-You're so annoying!
Ariyoshi is too awesome
Driver, please wait a little longer
Old fart!
After that, Ariyoshi also visits his office for the purpose of the questionnaire
You are still young, don't be so reckless
I understand what you're saying, Hamada
Calling me an stinky old fart is too much
Indeed, because you aren't a stinky old man
Just an old fart  -Not an old fart either...
And
Mother died, want to go to see mother in heaven to rub her shoulders and back
There's no way you're going to heaven!
Hamada can't go to heaven, right?
-But I'll probably to go to hell when I die
Absolutely
-Right?
Next is the comment that Razor Ramon RG was most impressed by
So awesome!
It was the 2013 edition of King of Conto (Sketch)
Kawahara's comments after a certain performance
In the history of this competition, i'm not sure any other comments really surpass this one
After the score comes out, Downtown speaks before the break
I thought "Is this really the time to play dumb?"
The quote from Kawahara that RG admires is as follows
Okay, let's take a look
The score for the second round of contestants...
Is 946
So the ranking after adding up the scores of the two rounds is
Awesome!
With 1825 points they are now ranked temporarily first!
That's pretty good
So, Panther!
No, no, no, sorry, sorry, sorry, this is what Hamada is supposed to say
I'm sorry, please don't beat me up, I'm sorry
Why did Seshita get beaten up?
Calm down, please
Watch it again
To begin with, the set was quiet for a moment
Yeah, there was indeed a moment
For a second, everyone was wondering "what's going on"
Yeah, indeed, it took some time to understand
After this, Downtown both start to react
This should be considered the highest honor
In this kind of competition
It's tough to make this kind of thing happen, right?
-Indeed
There are indeed a few famous instances of this in the past
For example, Laughing Rice's "It didn't turn out how I thought it would!"
※In the first round of M1 2008, Audrey, who came in ninth place, won the highest score of 649 points and eliminated Laughing Rice, who was in third place, from the top three. When Imaeda asked Laughing Rice about his feelings on the provisional table Nishida replied with this now classic quote.
But in Kawahara's case, it wasn't like that, usually you're asked "How do you feel?" after you take your seat
But instead, he came to the front of the stage after the performance, and before Hamada asked
"So, Panther..."
Kawahara has always been, so to speak,
A man who only responds by playing dumb
So all of this culminates in his "So, Panther!"
And the choice of Panther is great
To say "So, Jarujaru!" wouldn't be right
It has to be "So, Panther!"
So, this is RG's favorite comment of Kawahara
So, Panther!
No, no, no, sorry, sorry, sorry, this is what Hamada is supposed to say
Not a single opportunity missed
I'm sorry, please don't beat me up, I'm sorry
Don't even know why you're angry
Okay, that's all the quotes for today
-There it is
What do you think?
Although each of them is very good, the last "So, Panther"
-"So Panther"?
Kawahara-san didn't say "So, Panther" straight away
First he read the autocue
Because Hamada also reads it before saying his lines
Kawahara joined in on this action completely
Yeah
-Very detailed
So it appears even more like Hamada
-So it is
Mine was just speaking for everyone
It's not much
-"Isn't this unfunny?"
Yes, yes, yes, after all, that's what everyone thought
-Matsumoto what do you think
Well, Jinnai is not usually known for such making unfunny jokes
But as we said, because of the teasing Jinnai was saved somewhat
But he's been experiencing hell ever since
Since then, every performance is unfunny
I feel that in the two years since that day, he's been a little uninspired
Indeed, he hasn't redeemed himself
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's Chocolate Planet
-Thanks for having us
It's choco's
Chocolate's is okay
-Why do you have to make it plural every time?
Do you really like the sound "'s"?
You two come often!
-Thank you
So, what is the theory this time?
This is a theory about "NOM NOM NOM"
You really dare make a joke at this time?
Please acknowledge his courage
I was surprised myself
Although a bit sudden
About 5 years ago,
There was a "Even if the food is disgusting, after 3 days of fasting..."
"You will eat it" theory
Do you remember this hypothesis?
-I vaguely remember such a thing
Concerning the final verification results:
The food that Ungirls' Tanaka hates is cilantro (coriander)
In the end, he still couldn't eat it
-Couldn't eat it
The food Sugi hates is sea squirts
After fasting it proved to be very delicious
Viking's Nishimura hates figs
And although he ate it
This thing doesn't have any flavor at all!
No flavor!
What's with this stuff?
Nishimura ended up losing his sense of taste
What the hell!?
So the results were ultimately confusing
Three people with three different results
-What the hell happened?
That's just how it turned out
So we also don't understand what happened
Isn't it true that the taste sensitivity of the tongue becomes higher after fasting?
In the end, it turned out to be a mysterious verification result
-Nishimura is really an odd guy!
So this time, we bring a new theory about disliked food
This is it:
No matter how much you dislike a type of food, if you eat it at its peak quality, you will think it's delicious
Yes, I'm sure all of you here have tasted the best food
Just saying meat alone
If you compare cheap meat with the highest grade of meat
You'll surely think it's not the same thing.
-True
Incidentally, what food do you hate, Matsumoto?
Sushi with the silvery white type of fish, that type I can't stand
-Oh
Like those square sushi
※A square of sushi with mackerel slices on it, made in a mold in Kansai
It is similar to mackerel sushi, right?
That thing is no different from a Zippo
-Zippo?
That stuff is not for human consumption at all
A gasoline zippo lighter?
This guy judges whether food is good or not from its appearance
No, no, no, no...
Is it the appearance that's not good? Or is it the taste?
It can reflect your own face
So it's not so much the taste as it is a point of dislike?
Because its as smooth as the surface of a mirror
Is it that smooth?
Has there ever been a situation where you can see your own face?
You can't see the face so clearly, surely
No matter how much you dislike a type of food, if you eat it at its peak quality, you will think it's delicious
That's it
This time, the target was a trio of people who each had a type of food they would absolutely not eat
First is...
Hello
-Hello
Jungle Pocket's Ota
He has been called out on the pretext of working for a fake food show
Do you have any favorite food?
Eel or something
Also meat
Following along with this topic
Conversely, do you have anything you absolutely hate to eat?
Well...yeah I do
-What is it?
Cucumber
Oh, cucumber?
I am completely unable to eat cucumber
I haven't eaten a piece of cucumber in almost 30 years
Even if there's some in a salad, you can't eat it?
Even if there's small pieces in potato salad, I will avoid all of them
So, Ota's absolute NG food is cucumber
How did you come to hate eating cucumbers?
There was a teacher in elementary school
The kind of teacher who didn't allow us to leave anything uneaten
At that time there were cucumber slices in the lunch
I tried to prevent the teacher from finding out i'd left some
By hiding it in the desk drawer as if it had all been eaten
But in the end, it was discovered
The teacher said, "If you don't finish these, you can't go home"
So although I tried really hard
I just couldn't eat it
And a large pile of it on the table looked absolutely disgusting
So I threw up
So,
After this we're going to record a promo for the show
-Okay
So please come with me
Under false pretenses
He is lead to another room in which the best cucumber can be found
This is probably going to be bad
Ah this is a shock...
What's this all about?
What kind of project is this?
It's really scary
No matter how much you hate a certain type of food
You'll think its delicious once you eat the best version of it
Oh...so that's it
This time, the best version of cucumber tasted by Ota was...
Compared to the average cucumber, it is about twice the price
So straight!
This is specially selected Chichibu cucumber
Sweet, umami and crisp
It must be delicious
I am really not sure
Whether my body can accept it or not
After all, I have childhood trauma connected to it, and I really hate it
Its not the level of "oh I can't stand the smell of it"
Is it possible for you to eat the best cucumber?
No, I don't think I can eat it
Since this instance is not on the level of "just muddle through and eat it"
It can't be eaten in its natural state
So, we instead make a dish to change its state
If this is acceptable, then we will use a two-stage system to verify
The first thing Ota was told to eat was
Korean Style Salad
Ah I see...
It's not as refined a cuisine as I expected...
Putting a raw cucumber in front of me to eat...
My heart is really beating fast right now
What will be the result?
It seems he really can't eat it
Can't eat it, right?
What a nuisance!
Seriously a nuisance
Is he eating it?
Ate quite a lot
He's chewing
Eaten with lettuce
Yes
There is also seaweed in it
Yes, so the taste is still there
I can eat it
This is no problem
At its highest quality, do you acknowledge its deliciousness?
I'm sorry, I really can't say it's delicious
Its just the taste of Korean salad
I can't say i'm feeling that the cucumber is delicious
It just tastes like a Korean salad, so it's good enough to eat
But still, you chewed and swallowed it
-Yes
If this is the case, it can be eaten
The taste is still acceptable
After that, it was time to challenge the raw cucumber
After 30 years, can he overcome the inability to eat cucumber if its peak quality?
Not eaten it in 30 years, impressive
It should be okay to dip it in some salt, right?
-It's OK
Waaaaaa...
This is now pure cucumber flavor
I genuinely haven't eaten it like this
I'm going to do it
Too fast!
Don't you think it's too fast?
This is true resistance
Please wait a minute, I'm really...
Eh, wait?
What's going on?
-I don't know
The moment I put it in my mouth, I started to vomit
Definitely psychological trauma
You can also take a little break
I'll try again
First drink some water to rest a little
It's okay, it's okay, I'm scared that if I wait too long i'll be more afraid
What do you mean by "afraid"
It means his hate has already reached the level of fear
I'm going for it
Don't dip it in the salt!
Ah, he's chewing
Eh?
I said don't dip it in the salt!
Hasn't he finished?
It's not that good to eat
However...
It's not impossible to eat
Success!
It's not as bad as my recollection of it
I still don't understand my body's reaction to it
But the feeling of "It's not what I thought it would be" prevailed
And I was able to swallow it by accident
So, from now on, Ota
What will you think of cucumbers?
I have the type of "I can actually eat it" confidence now
Despite still not feeling that it is "delicious"
By experiencing it at its best, he was able to eat cucumbers after 30 years
Next is...
Gushiken Yoko
What can't I eat? The things I can't eat are few
When I was young, I used to catch sea urchins to eat
But after eating so much of it, I began to feel a little strange about it
In the past, you thought it was delicious?
Ate too much and became disgusted by it
It was delicious because, how can I say... because I was hungry
What aspect is it that you hate?
Its slippery so its unpleasant
Do you mean the texture of the food?  -Yes, and
It also smells a bit unpleasant
And the color of it also looks like poo, which is a bit off-putting
So i'm afraid i'm not really willing to eat it
He's really cute
He's still a kid
What is this man saying?
When was the last time you ate sea urchin?
When I was in high school
Gushiken's absolute NG food is "sea urchin" which he has not eaten for over 50 years
So
Ah, there are a lot of people here... hello
No matter how much you hate a certain type of food
You'll think its delicious once you eat the best version of it
Ah, I can already tell its not possible even before i've seen it
Sea urchin, I really can't
The peak quality sea urchin prepared for Gushiken is...
About seven times the price of average sea urchin
One box costs about 25,000
Sea urchin of Ezo horse manure from Nemuro, Hokkaido (gold quality)
Gold quality
It is characterized by a strong sweetness and aromatic richness
Can't even look at it
Evil ... it really fills the nostrils
The smell is really strong
This is way stronger that what i've experienced in the past
Is it the fragrance?
It is the smell of sea urchin
This time, the first challenge is sea urchin steamed rice
So, please enjoy
The food I can't eat is raw oysters
I can't stand the taste
I can't stand the soft feeling when I bite down
So it's probably been about 10 years since I've eaten it
So, please enjoy
Trying to pick a bite with no sea urchin
So... sorry
That...
Every grain of rice is covered with it...
That's for sure!
Wait a minute...
If he doesn't want to eat it then nothing can be done
So, after this
It took this long?
It's still quite difficult
So tough
This is really tough
Is it ok to just not eat it?
The struggle and refusal to eat the sea urchin lasted 20 minutes
But at this point, finally,
Uwa, this is really too much
Placed deep in the throat
To avoid the taste
Avoid the tastebuds
Deep in the throat
Wasn't chewed at all!
It's impossible
Ah... i'm sorry
Can't even chew a mouthful
Can't eat it
Although it was of the highest quality, he could not eat the sea urchin
Ah ... sea urchin is still sea urchin after all
Saying this type of flavor is delicious, I just can't
The final challenger is JOY
Foods you dislike are...?
Mentaiko, tomato, eggplant, red bean filling
For JOY, who is a very picky eater
Which is the worst out of all of these?
Probably tomato, I threw it up in the past
It's tomato
How long has it been since you've had one?
-A tomato?
Tomato...
I haven't had one since the early years of elementary school, I think
Even a single bite is just impossible...
Taking a bite of it will probably kill me
And so, JOY is lead to his final resting place
Hello
Thanks for having me
Ah!?
Eh!?
No matter how much you hate a certain type of food
You'll think its delicious once you eat the best version of it
Can't do it, can't do it, can't do it
I don't think I can do it, so let's just not
This is not just a simple dislike of mine
Please sit down first
Hey... the GoPro has been shooting for 11 minutes already
So you were already preparing this when we were talking back there!
For JOY, who hates tomatoes so much
The price of this variety is 5 times higher than the normal variety
This box of small tomatoes costs about 5,400
And its sugar content is twice as high as the average variety
With an elegant sweetness
Certainly not the same as a standard tomato
The first item to be challenged is marinated tomatoes
Marinated Tomatoes
This is completely raw
So, please enjoy "the highest quality marinated tomatoes"
Please wait a moment...
Can you give me a countdown or something?
If it's not mandatory, I can't eat it
I don't think I can do it otherwise, its like a bungee jump
-Okay
Is it okay to count down from 10 seconds
Please start from 15
10 isn't enough?
Okay, so let's get started
15 14…
Just count down from 5
This is bad...
Does it make any difference?
Ah ah, i'll show you my power
Let's do it, eat it!
Awful!
These are the highest quality tomatoes
Super disgusting
JOY can't even eat it at its highest peak quality
It must be absolutely delicious
On the contrary, because the quality is high, the flavor is very strong, right?
The tomatoey taste is too prominent
It's probably more difficult for me to eat the highest quality one
For those who can't eat it, the best quality one is the worst
This should be the answer to this theory
This proved, once again, that I really can not eat tomatoes
Incidentally, what is your least favorite food, Saito?
Huh?
-What's the food you hate, most, Saito?
Whoa... eh?
Tomatoes...
This was known in advance and that's why they asked him, right?
We got this information
-Oh, this is bad...
How resistant are you?
Raw is definitely impossible
I probably haven't eaten it since elementary school
Same as JOY
Eh, wait a minute... Oh, so that's how it is...
This is how it is
Today happens to be the first time that Saito has hosted a variety show
His reaction will probably be really bad
The tomatoes that JOY challenged are now presented "raw"
Everyone takes a deep breath
After 14 years, he'll try a tomato
Eeeeee! This is bad!
This kid is really spoiled
It's a very high class tomato
I guess it'll turn out like this
Oh wow, it still stinks after throwing it up
The taste of the core is really awful
3 out of 4 people couldn't even swallow
Only Ota ate it
After one week
Eh? A follow-up?
Hello
-Hello
What's the show?
-Wednesday Downtown
Before this you ate the highest quality cucumber
-Yes
How did it go after that?
I bought cucumbers at supermarket and took them home
To challenge myself
Unfortunately it's still not working
After all, I ate the highest quality cucumber, right?
In summary,
overcoming food you hate is extremely difficult
I see
The result is that it is very difficult to overcome
What do you think?
If it is the highest peak quality of something, the smell is probably quite unpleasant for those who hate it
The speed that everyone spat it out is abnormally fast
Its true, they threw it up instantly
-Indeed
So they really do find it extremely unpleasant
It's usually rare to see so many people continuously vomiting
I hoped Gushiken would try harder
-Yes
It might be better to start the challenge with poop
Have you ever seen anyone picking up poo with chopsticks?
And don't put a trash can next to them, so they can't use it to escape the challenge
I see
-It's making it too easy
Or stuff poop in Gushiken's mouth while he's asleep
-It's not about poop
Sea urchin is enough
How has the food that Gushiken dislikes become poop?
It's sea urchin!
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03