Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Tonight we have several presenters
It's the usual one, right?
Here we go
Kotouge, Takahashi and Kasuga!
Twoos!
-A very loud voice
Exactly the same!
Who?
-Where?
Exactly the same
You have a problem with your eyesight
So, all of us today
Bring you the semi-annual "Everybody's Theories" special
Yes
So, the first theory is this
If you see a skinny bald guy in blue leather jacket in a TV station, you'll presume its Kotouge
I guess you do have that style
You do!
Very much so
It's the changing of the seasons
-I understand
It's autumn!
Seeing my leather jacket
-Yes
It turns out that the staff of this program called him "thin blue leather jacket bald head"
Well said
I can't believe i'm thought of like that
Skinny bald head
If you see a skinny bald guy in blue leather jacket in a TV station, you'll presume its Kotouge
Therefore, we prepared the blue leather jacket that Kotouge loves to wear
This will be verified by a similarly bald-headed man, Hyouroku
What a skinny bald guy to get
So, Hyouroku is placed in position
It's Kotouge!
Kotouge
The 1st target is
What are you doing?
Diane's Tsuda
What happens?
Good morning
"Who are you?" is written on his face
A greeting was offered
And
A beautiful double-take
It's Kotouge...
Everyone... everyone will fall for it
You can't walk pass Kotouge...
The next target is Asahi Nao
Didn't look
No such impression, right?
She walks straight past
Why does he look so despondent?
The final target is
Looks like he's asking "why!?"
A direct junior from the same firm, Nishkikoi's Watanabe
What happens?
Its possible they'll realize something is up
True
Good morning
-Ah!
Sorry
-Good morning
Sorry. Good morning
Good morning. Sorry.
-Good morning
Wrong person, sorry, sorry
No, no
Thanks for your hard work
-Thank you
There's nothing to be sorry about
There is another such person in the world!
No, right?
I mistook him for Kotouge
"I'm sorry for thinking of you as Kotouge just because of your baldness."
I apologize profusely
Seems he's not...
Background
We don't need him in the background!
I don't want to be that kind of person
In summary
Comedians will say hello
Watanabe and I know each other very well
I didn't expect him to fall for it
I'd love to see the fake Kotogue!
What would happen if Kotouge saw it?
-What would happen?
Of course I wouldn't think "This is Kotouge, right?
You'd ignore him?
The next theory chosen by Takahashi is...
The sound effect of cracking bones being played during an orthopedic won't be noticed
Under this massage bed are speakers that will play the effect of sound to verify
It's close
The target is
Sanshiro Komiya, who think this is their private time
Komiya is very perceptive
So dirty
Enough!
So much whining
Next is the orthopedic treatment of the lower back
Will he realize?
I'll shake you gently
What is the sound?
Please breathe in
Very real
Please turn over
We'll do the same as just now
Please breathe in
Please tilt your head
Here we go. Please exhale
Go back
Seems to have missed it completely
The next verification is even bolder
Please relax
Please breathe in
1  2
Now the other side
Please relax
1  2
Okay
No, no, no
Is everything okay?
Eh?
Did it make a noise?
Certainly didn't feel anything
Eh, huh?
-Is everything okay?
And
Here we go
1  2
You'd surely realize
Eh?
Is everything okay?
What was it just now?
Eh?
Hmm?
What's going on?
Did you realize?
Don't use noises!
The next theory chosen by Takahashi is
Blueberry Farmer Vision Test 2.0
We came to this blueberry farm in Hachioji
Sorry, we are from TBS
Ok.
-Ah...
One wearing glasses!
The next theory chosen by Takahashi is
You can't complain if you  ordered the kaki set and was served persimmons
※Both Japanese oyster and persimmon are pronounced as "kaki"
With the assistance of this canteen
We called out an unsuspecting male as a target
Welcome!
Would you like to order now?
The fried kaki
-good
So, he orders the recommended dish of the day, the fried kaki set
But the dish served is made of persimmons cut into pieces
Coated with wheat flour, egg wash, breadcrumbs and fried
A fried persimmon set like this
Although the appearance is difficult to distinguish
The content is completely different
Sorry for the wait
Here's your order
Please take your time
And then...
First he takes photos
Then beings to eat
Very brittle, right?
Looked at the blackboard
It's time to eat
Then took another picture
Uploaded to Instagram
Fried kaki set: 800 yen
I can't believe it's the kaki of persimmon!
Sees it as an interesting accident in daily life
And then...
Persimmons also have a unique flavor
One after another
All 4 pieces were eaten
The 2nd target is this male
Looking first
It's different with Chinese characters
If the writing is Chinese characters you'd complain
It is written in Katakana
It does make sense
He reads the board 3 times to confirm that the writing is true
Also eaten completely
Sorry to interrupt
Kaki means persimmon?
Yes
Also not complaining about the writing of kaki despite thinking it meant oysters
I didn't think it was a persimmon, which is rare
But...
Also quite delicious
The next theory chosen by Takahashi is
Nowadays, elementary school students do not know the word "sewer"
Do you know dobu?
No idea
What do you think it is?
Is it a type of container?
Do you know dobu?
I don't know
-I don't know
Not anymore?
Plant?
No idea
What do you think it is?
A fish
As expected, no one knows
Do you know dobu?
Mobile App?
The final theory chosen by Takahashi is
Suzumi Muneo is the strongest of reaching-out-of-the-car
What does strongest mean?
Candidates are not obligated to wear seat belts during the election period
And they can wave to voters by poking their body out of the car window
And Suzuki Muneo...
Presents his body in a very unique fashion
And
It can be said that this exceeds the concept of reaching out of the car
So, there we go
Is it possible to do that during the election?
Yes, you can
Does it influence the vote?
If they do it badly it wont help
No problem if its the "head extension party"
Everyone who stretches out of cars
Next is a theory chosen by Kotouge
So, the theory I choose is this...
It's hard to crack shells with a stone on your stomach like a sea otter
That's for sure
Must be a lot of work
This time we tested whether humans can do the same as sea otters
A realistic sea otter tournament was held
Realistic Sea Otter Tournament
I didn't hear about the registration for this tournament
If you heard would you have signed up?
If I heard about it, of course
Realistic sea otter tournament?
But I wouldn't really want to do it in the morning
There is no difference in the afternoon, right?
It's the same in the morning and afternoon, right?
It's hard to crack shells with a stone on your stomach like a sea otter
Realistic Sea Otter Tournament
Participating in the challenge are these 3 comedians
The first person to crack open and eat 5 clams wins
First each choose a stone to crack open the clams
This... will my stomach be okay?
These are very dangerous to use to smash the stomach
Realistic Sea Otter Tournament - Start!
It's begun!
Ogata is going for it!
Smash failed!
The stone hit the stomach
What will happen?
Clams are flying!
Micho smashes!
Ogata is in pain!
This hurts!
Unexpected blows to the stomach
All 3 people lose their spirit in the first move
Not only is it difficult to hit the shells accurately
A slight deviation and the stomach will be hit hard
Michio completely hammered his stomach on the first attempt
And has not yet started again
But 2 minutes after starting...
Success!
Minamikawa hit the center of the shell with a sharp stone and succeeded in breaking it open
Minamikawa opened the 1st shell
How about Ogata? Can he catch up with Minamikawa?
This one... one is out!
Minamikawa gets the 1st piece of shellfish
Then the clams are sent to the iron plate
For safety, the clams are cooked first before being eaten
Really considerate
As Minamikawa eats a hot clam he's one step ahead
Minamikawa is burnt!
Can Ogata catch up?
Cracked open!
Ogata has also succeeded!
He's catching up
How about Michio?
Wait a minute...can't fix it at all
The stomach is no good
Does a flabby tummy absorb the pressure?
My stomach is no good
Ogata is also covered in clam juice
Minamikawa gets his 2nd
Ogata is still trying to get his second one
I have the talent to be a sea otter
Oh, got it!
What is "the talent to be a sea otter"?
The gap between Ogata and Minamikawa is gradually lessening as the competition is fierce
Opened the 3rd one!
And Michio has yet to open one
And then...
On this side, both have just one left
1 more 1 more
Will Ogata be the winner?
Ah! It hit his face!
A flying clam hit his face!
Next to him
It's open, but not quite
Its cracked!
It's cracked. It's close.
-It's already cracked
Then
For some reason, Ogata now places the clam very low
Oh, it's open!
Smashed open!
Ogata smashes the last clam by sheer willpower alone
He's finished eating 5 of them
So the winner of the Realistic Sea Otter Championship is Ogata!
Great!
Damn
It really hurts. I have dark skin so I can't see it
This... should not be broadcast
This is also my own work
Not smashed by others
Yes, although some want to
There's no reason to be hit b y others
Yes, no reason
He's turning red
And then...
Want to see the sea otter model?
Want to see
Want to watch, want to learn!
So lets take a look
The location is very close to the bottom
Eh, wait...
-Hey
Isn't the stone on the bottom?
The stone is below
It's the opposite of us
The stone is placed underneath
It uses the shell and smashes it downwards
Surely more efficient
Sea otters are so smart
No pain either
What is it?
-I don't know
Tell us in advance!
You only said "like a sea otter"
You are the ones who decided to do the opposite
Don't say that
But we should be reminded how to do it
In summary
The sea otter's practice and the imitation is the complete opposite
That is, sea otters are smarter than they are
But Ogata...
-Yes, yes, yes
Very forced
Instead, it's a bit of a buzzkill
Putting in the crotch seems very dangerous
There was no interest here at all
The next theory chosen by Kotouge is
The order of popularity of Robert's members's full names should be Yamamoto Akiyama and Maba
The most well-known surname is presumably Akiyama
With the the most well-known full name presumably being Yamamoto Hiroshi
So, a survey was conducted with 100 people who knew about Robert
Baba, Akiyama and Yamamoto
Do you know their full names?
Well... I know Ryuji Akiyama
Don't know the remaining two?
No idea
Akiyama Baba Yamamoto
Hiroshi Yamamoto
Only know Yamamoto's full name?
Yes
Akiyama always called him by it
After that too...
Ryuji Akiyama
Others I don't know
Hiroshi Yamamoto
Akiyama... eh?
Ryuji Akiyama
Hiroshi Yamamoto
Baba...
I don't know the name of Baba, sorry
The survey results are shown in the figure
The full name of the popularity is shown above
The theory is verified
What is the full name of Baba?
Baba Hiroiki
That's the right answer.
-Really?
I guessed
The next theory chosen by Kotouge is
People whose game of shiritori ends with "n" definitely say "ah"
By the way there is another verification
-Okay
Thank you
Anyway, two person shiritori
2 people?
-Yes
So Asahi will go first.
-Ok
kuruma (car)
-marimo (green algae)
mozuku (sea foam)
-kurumi (walnut)
mikazuki (new moon)
-kitutuki (woodpecker)
kiiro (yellow)
-roba (donkey)
tomato (tomato)
-toire (toilet)
renkon (lotus root)
Ah...
What is this atmosphere?
Before doing a double jump with a jumping rope, you have to first jump normally three times
Equivalent to assisted running
There is another theory that I would like you to test
Please use this jump rope to do a double jump
-Double jump?
At your own pace
-OK
Please.
-I'm ready
First, the normal jump three times
-Three times
End of verification
-What the heck!?
The last theory chosen by Kotouge is...
A "small but heavy item" can be held for about the same amount of time as a "large but light item"
To help us test this theory
What's up!?
We called Westland's Inokichi for a fake program
The fact that its Wednesday Downtown doesn't matter
What the theory is what matters
Anyway, can you take this first?
So scary!
No problem, right?
Wow, it's heavy!
This tungsten block the same volume as iron, but is 2.5 times the weight of iron
It's a rare metal.
-It's very heavy
This is a challenge project to see how long you can last holding it
Oh right
Can you convey to the audience that this super heavy
I don't know if the audience can understand
Because this size of it makes it look very easy to hold
We also didn't tell him about the additional verification of holding a large but light item
So, we set up a fixed camera before leaving
Physical strength is no problem, right?
What's the meaning of this?
Left him alone
This is seriously heavy
Putting the heavy object on one's chest or stomach
Using body parts other than the palm of the hand is prohibited
A good rule
Very painful,  the edge of the metal block is so sharp
And so, an hour and 30 minutes passed
I should eat
Wait a minute, so heavy, ugh
It's too hard to hold the top when you hold it with one hand
My wrist hurts
My wrist is starting to hurt, seriously
The complaints are mounting
This guy can really complain
Even if you try to hold it again, it will be edited out, right?
Last time I searched for chess pieces for so long
Outside on location for 10 hours
Why do I have to spend 10 hours just to be cut out?
Why can't I go to a "Love it!" location shoot and eat delicious food?
Three hours have passed since the start
Complaining so much but still trying hard
This 3 hours is not easy
Ah...
My back hurts too
Not only wrist pain but also finger pain
This is now full-body pain
It's hard, isn't it?
-It's been 4 hours
Ow ow ow
Getting more screen time than expected at least
-Keep going!
OW!
Ah! Ow!
I can't, it hurts!
It really hurts!
Can't hold on any longer
Ouch!
Reached his limit
From start to finish in 4 hours and 2 minutes
A very simple way to end the challenge
It hurts so much...
Isn't this project the most boring Wednesday Downtown project?
If I don't need to bring my manzai clothes can't you just tell me in advance?
Bringing clothes with you is a real pain
A hundred complaints a second
Not knowing there is a follow-up, he returns home for now
Tsk, what the hell is this?
After 3 days
Have to test with the same subject to make it fair, right?
Oh!
What is it?
Enough already, right?
This time, he'll challenge a large and light cardboard box which is half the weight of the tungsten block
It's hard too, isn't it?
What position should I hold this in?
As before, touching with parts other than the palm of the hand is not accepted
Can't use your head
Its so hard to get a hold of
Unbearable...
This seems to be even worse
He tries various positions to hold the cardboard box
Looks like a sculpture
Whoa whoa
But still can't find a suitable position
He brought his clothes with him again
This pose must look really weird, right?
But now only this position is slightly more comfortable
An hour later
Oh no. Tsk!
This is the worst
His manzai clothes got wet, right?
The table, and his stuff, are now soaking wet
It's not going to work
Afterwards
Must want to drink water too
This is the position
Found it?
Like this... but still can't rest
It hurts
The record is 1 hour and 23 minutes
Sadly, the challenge is over
It hurts...
It hurts... tsk
The verification result is that the small and heavy item can be held for longer
So what?
So strict
-Angry
What about my manzai clothes?
You don't need them
-Tsk
In summary
An inefficient location shoot
Interesting
So pissed off
-That guy was making a lot of noise, talking about his clothes
If he's not even willing to bring his manzai clothes, he shouldn't even do manzai
Really doesn't want to bring his performance clothes
What happens if you have to hold poo?
Fresh raw poo
Raw poo?
You have to hold raw poop.
-That's too hard to top
Contrast it with holding a heavy object
Depends on who's it is
Yes, it depends on whether it is yours or your partner's
Partner's poop would be awful
What do you mean by raw poo? Is there such a thing as cooked poo?
It's unprocessed.
-All stool is raw, right?
What does raw poo mean?
-Pure green natural GMO-free poop
What the hell is that face!?
You wanna fight!?
You listening?
Next is the first theory chosen by Kasuga
So, Kasuga's gonna finish it off
-He's finally speaking!
It's true, apart from "Twoos" at the start he hasn't said anything at all
Indeed
-You aren't doing some kind of verification on the sly, are you?
No, I'm not doing a verification, i'm just quiet
I just simply can't think of anything to say
Couldn't think of a single thing to say the whole time
I'm the strong-silent type
So, i'll continue
The theories I have chosen are these
Sons must be able to understand the type of women their father likes
Is that so?
-That's right
Do you know?
-I don't know my father's preferences at all
My father and I don't get along, and we basically don't talk to each other
So it's a mystery to me
That man is more of a mystery to me than anyone else
Can people understand that?
-Absolutely not
How about women?
I know
He likes women who like to carry heavy-looking luggage
What are you talking about?
-What's heavy?
Even if you offer a helping hand, they'll say "no, it's fine"
This low-key kind of vibe
Low-key?
Sons must be able to understand the type of women their father likes
The relationship is a big part of this
So
The challenger this time is Miyashita Kusanagi of Miyashita
My father is a bit special
He is an underground fighter
Underground fighter?
-Yes
At this time, his father...
Sakurai Mac Hideki is 54 years old
He was married once before
And divorced my mother and got married again
So he must have a lot of energy
Is he very popular?
-He should be very popular
Your son Miyashita got married recently, right?
-Yes
Do you know your daughter-in-law?
-Yes, I do
She's a pretty and cute girl
Incidentally, can I ask if your daughter-in-law is your type?
If my daughter-in-law took the initiative to approach me
I'd like it, after all, she's pretty
Stop that!
Isn't that what men are like?
Miyashita's father walks the path of the man
From these five different types of women
He will be asked to choose his favorite
It's hard to choose
For example, the type of woman you like
I mostly find women's eyes to be very attractive
Such a gross scene
You don't want to see your father doing this
-After all, it's your dad
Who's better, I wonder?
Have you chosen?
I've made my choice
After the father has chosen his preferred type of female
The next step is for the son to predict his father's choice
Wow, this is tough
Oh, I'm worried
Which one is it?
What is this vibe, watching his son guess
I personally like D, this kind of innocent feeling
And B, the formal look
I get what he means, sophisticated type
My father should be the opposite of my preference
It should not be the two of them
I think my father likes gyaru type
So I think either A, C or E
I see
In terms of figure, I think E
She's similar to my mother when she was young
My mother used to wear boots like this
She did, it was popular then
I feel like A is also the type my father would like
She has similarities to my mother
Good point
Because the face is the type that my father likes, its possible
But E is also very similar to my mother
What to do?
Which one...?
For the women in the gyaru category
Two have similarities to his mother
So, its time to reveal the results
The female your father chose has his signature on the back of their tag
If there is nothing on the back, the choice is wrong
Go for it!
So which one do you think is your father's favorite type?
The type of women my father likes is...
A
So, please can A peel off the tag
What will be the result?
Please!
Is there a signature?
Right answer!
So happy!
Yes, so happy!
This is a good one!
I got it right, super happy!
You must be super happy!
What kind of feeling is this?
Dad.
-You got it!
She seems like the type found in high class hostess clubs
Where are you manners!
In a place like that?
-Like a club in Ginza
This is a key point
My mother also worked at a hostess club
In summary
He likes hostess clubs
What a rough conclusion.
-But guessed right
Guess correctly
This is the father-son bond
It could also be seen as a very touching theory
Seriously
Indeed, it is still difficult to guess
How can I put it? I don't have such a good relationship with my father
Halfway through I felt like I wanted to cry
But once he said, "Nice, right? Feels like a high-class hostess"
I couldn't help but think "this guy isn't great"
What do you think?
This...
Was it the type of woman that Miyashita likes?
No
-It wasn't? It was the father's?
Miyashita's father
-Huh?
Did you watch it carefully?
I watched but didn't know who was choosing
Because Miyashita was on screen choosing more
So you thought he was picking his own type, right?
-That's right
That's not good.
-I know I'm sorry
It has nothing to do with me, there is no need to hit me, right?
Why is it that the closest to you has to be hit?
The next theory chosen by Kasuga is...
No one really uses the deciliter as a unit of measurement
One tenth of a liter is one deciliter
After learning this point in elementary school, it's rarely heard of again
Incidentally abroad
Juice in Sweden
And Swiss instant soup, etc
It is still used in Europe and other places
Also in Japan
I heard that the unit of measurement this store uses is "deciliter"
Mixed grains here are sold by the "penny"
Really
Here it is used to calculate the amount of small beans sold
Why is the unit of measurement "deciliter" used?
Previously, it was sold as 1 in 2
※The volume unit in Japan is 0.180 kg per unit.
But the shakuhan method is not used anymore
※The Shakukan method is a traditional Japanese metric system derived from Chinese weights and measures
So we had to use the metric system
1 is a little under 2 deciliters
Metrics are very carefully observed
So we use the 2 deciliter
Yes, the Shakuhan method was banned in Showa 34
In terms of the amount sold, the unit of measurement such as the combined and liters can not be used
※The liters mentioned here are the liters of the shakuhan method, and one liter is equal to 1.8039 liters.
So stores began to use sub-liters to measure
So with this kind of container
We made this kind of container of 2 deciliters for trading
Incidentally, deciliters are also used for medical reports and in the medical field
The next theory chosen by Kasuga is...
The 2nd Before doing a double jump with a jumping rope, you have to first jump normally three times
Please do a double jump
Sure enough, the first three jumps
He can jump
The next theory chosen by Kasuga is
It's awesome! Not a single word!
Nothing to say
Drawing Hotei Tomoyasu's face in the same way as Hachi no Hemoji is possible
So, following the rhythm
Let's have a drawing song
Like drawing the old man
Let's draw the face of Hotei
Use these characters twice
Let's draw his face
First, write a "Ho" on the right side
Then write a "Te" in the middle
Write an "I" on the left side
Falling into madness
"To" is his nose
"Mo" is his ear
"Ya" is his hair
Use "Su" to draw eyes
Hug tightly
Hotei Tomoyasu
Like drawing the old man
No, no, no, no, no
We drew the face of Hotei Tomoyasu
Good drawing skills
The best!
This painting can be anyone, right?
The final theory chosen by Kasuga is...
How many points will Shimizu's new imitation get from Noriko Awaya speaking through a psychic?
She used to tell him off a lot
It is already a fixed process
Thank you, friends and viewers!
If you have any theories, please feel free to submit them
We will do this project again in about half a year
This is "Everybody's Theories" special
How many points will Shimizu's new imitation get from the departed Noriko Awaya speaking through a psychic?
Vulgar imitations and dirty imitations
She'd usually score at least an 8
As shown in the theory
Psychic Medium Mikami
No specific explanations were given
First, we ask the psychic Noriko Awaya to get into the body
Three minutes have passed since the spirit was invited to the body
Is it Noriko Awaya?
-Yes.
Here we go
Sorry to trouble you
Today I want you to
Look at someone's parody and score it
Can you help?
Me?
-Yes
I would like to ask Noriko Awaji to rate it
Okay... got it
After receiving permission
We asked her to take a seat at the judges' table
Preparation is complete
What are you feeling right now?
Thanks for letting me be in the spotlight
You are welcome
Who are the other judges?
Then show it quickly!
Shimizu-san's new segment is a parody of Piko Taro-san
Please
POOP
P O O P
I have a pen
I have a ass...
Asspen
I have a pen
I have a boobs, an~
Boobspen
Asspen
Unh! Pen boobs ass pen
Seems like she's in a bad mood
Pen boobs ass pen
Pen pen pen pen pen pen pen
It hurts! It hurts when you slap the butt!
Thank you Shimizu
How do you personally rate your performance today?
I think it's full marks
Then let's start scoring
-So nostalgic~
Shimizu's score is...
10分 10分 10分 5分
10分 10分 10分 10分 10分 10 分
Total 95 points
5 points?
My first time to get 5 points
The lowest score I've ever received was a 6...
Why 5?
I think Akira-kun's imitations used to be more spirited
Did Awaya always call you Akira-kun?
It was always "Shimizu-san"
Today was "Akira-kun"
In summary
Awaya's scoring has become stricter since going to heaven
That's what happened.
-She's gotten stricter
What do you think, Shigemori? Which ones did you like the most?
I like the one about the deciliter
Eh?
If you ask an idiot "What unit of measurement do you prefer?" The answer is usually deciliters
What makes you say that?
-Because it sounds cool
What appears in exams is also generally deciliter
Are they usually divided into liters?
-Questions about capacity
If you want to get tattoo, you'd get one of a deciliter, right?
-Yes
Woman!
-Sorry
What is this angry mode?
It's because of this woman that I got beaten up
Woman!
Kotouge has problems too!
-Don't do this
Don't call people by their gender
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03