Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let's get on with our first presenter please
It's Koyabu
Yoshimoto's guy
Yoshimoto's guy, aren't everyone around you?
Ok
Today involves the names of people on the street
It's a brand new project.
-New project!
Please take a look:
Street Passerby Name Cooking
Sounds interesting
The program team provides food corresponding to the name of a passerby to carry out a culinary duel
For instance, you meet Kakimoto-san, then you have to use Kakio (persimmon)
-Understood
Ebihara
-You'd have to use shrimp (ebi)
The project involves two teams follwing this rule to make three dishes each with the collected ingredients
Finally, the uninformed judges choose which team's is more delicious
Personally, I think this project can be made into an actual show
BS Yoshimoto
Don't put us in the same category as such a casual TV station
※Yoshimoto's satellite TV station has programs such as "Tetsuo Laughing Rice's Interesting Temple Tour" and "Wakayoshi Sekishiro's Aimless Walk"
Inexplicable young entertainers chattering away all the time
Street Passerby Name Cooking
This must take a while
Everyone is divided into red apron and blue apron teams for the cooking competition
Fukuda is the red team's leader
That's why i've got a hat
Very good cook
The blue team is led by Beppu
I used to be a chef, I can handle it
Worked in a hotel before
Hotel staff for 4 years
The red and blue team members are shown above
10 hours from now
10 hours?
After 10 hours?
Way too long!
It's too much!
10 hours?
As if 10 hours is normal
It would take that long.
-Yes, yes, yes
After 10 hours, they'll have made three dishes with the collected ingredients
The uninformed Lady Devi will decide which team's is better
What kind of ingredients does Fukuda?
-Yes, yes, yes.
Commonly used ingredients such as fish and meat, and then the rice
Don't ask too much, okay? We're the ones in charge of finding the ingredients
I want seasoning
Now there's only sugar and soy sauce
Only sugar and soy sauce
What do you want most?
-Touban (soybean) and sweet pasta sauce or something like that
No one calls it "touban", right?
-No
Do you have water? Here?
Only sugar and soy sauce
Water is usually a given
Gotta look for water?
So the two teams first went to areas with a lot of people
The difficulty is quite high
They can make something if they have seasoning at least
Let's go!
Ask one by one and win by numbers
It's all about quantity
The first one found was this bicycle man
Please tell me your name
Hidehira Fujii
No food
In this way, it feels as exciting as gambling
Hello, can I interview you?
-Yes
What are you doing?
What high school? Omori Higashi High School.
-Not the name of your high school
Please show me your name
My name is
Hayashi?
No good
Thank you. Excuse me.
-Thank you
Thank you
He hit it. He hit the post
A nice guy
Please tell me your name
Maiko Akabane
"Feather" isn't doable, right?
Chicken wings have "feathers"
-No
Please tell me your name
My name is Sei Sato
A very rare name
My name is Morigami Seirena
Pears
There you go. Great. There you go
Cooking with pears
-Can you?
Has "pear" in the name
Great! So quick!
How do you plan to use the pear?
It's rare that pears is used for a dish
Dessert?
It can be used as a side dish for cold noodles
But pears must be used
Yes, it is not always good to get one
Food obtained must be used
Have I ever cooked with pears in my life?
Do you have to use them all?
On the blue team
Please tell me your name
Junsei Nozaki
Cool name
Kitani Ryousuke
Tomoya Yoshida
None
None!
In fact, we are comedians
Comedians? Really?
My stage name is Kitani Curry
Stage names don't count.
-Can't be counted
Stage name doesn't count
Is there anyone named "Ushiyama Dolphin"?
So, please reveal
-One... Two...
Okay, there's nothing in these names
What is your name?
Is it pronounced "Nouzei Hiroshi"?
"Nose"
Hello, Nose Hiroshi
The part of this character, can I use it for ise lobster?
One, two
Not easy
Rice
-We have rice
Wow, here we go!
Komeda
-Komeda? Great!
Just the second group i've asked!
If you have rice, you can at least make a rice ball
So, as soon as the project started, both teams received one ingredient each
What is your name?
Rice would be very advantageous
Shuya Shoya
Water!
Water, water is there!
Mito
-This reaction is funny
Yeah, water
Fukuda said he can't cook without water
So this is a great result!
Also
Also?
Shigono Momo
Got peach, and salt!
Two ingredients in the name
Double get, great!
Please tell me your name
My name is Haru
Great!
This character
Canola?
Canola? Only canola?
-Yes
Isn't it a baby bok choy?
Canola only
-Canola only?
In addition, Fukuda found..
Sakashoma
Thank you
Horse meat sashimi?
Got horse meat!
Great, that's... that's a big step!
You can make a raw mix if you have pears
Yeah, right
After two hours, the red team have obtained six ingredients
Fukuda is awesome
The blue team is also in a good poisition
Kazuhiro Takezawa
Bamboo shoots, OK?
Great! Thank you!
Soma, soma-kun?
"Ma" again
-A lot of horse
Yes, i've got another!
What is your name?
Ochiai Shiina
Ochiai Shiina-san is great, there you go!
Look, there is there is there
Please!
Rina Shiiba
"Fu" is in there, "hana" too
Does "hana" count?
OK
-Okay, okay, okay
Vegetables with "hana" (leaves) can be used
Can you choose any kind of leaf?
Sorry to bother you, but I have a question
Which kind of vegetable with leaves should we choose?
Can you choose any of them?
-Any of them?
Yes, both.
-Which one do you prefer, Beppu?
Green perilla would be best
After two hours, the blue team have 5 ingredients
Not enough to make a dish
At this time
A fellow comedian happens to wander past
Matsuo Atoomae Police Station
A junior
What is your real name?
Tell me your name
My name is Matsuo Toshiji
Sushi
What? How do you pronounce this?
Toshiji
Toshiji?
-Yes
Must be an ingredient
Ah not usable
Meanwhile, a similar situation is happening here
We are Wednesday Downtown
Hello
Koda, can I interview you for a while?
What? Really?
Yes, Koda, what is your name?
Tell me your real name
No way!
None
No what?
-Not so good
Yes, not a single one
There is nothing
-There is only a "field"
What are you talking about?
Why's he got his hat just half on?
Little blue hat
3 hours after the start additional competition rules are introduced
Thank you for your hard work!
From now on, not only the people you meet on the road, but also the words on the door and signboards count
Company names such as "○○ Shop" and "Kuriyama Business" are also acceptable
So
Ogata, you should go to a residential area to look at the names on the houses
Why me?
-You have the spirit!
How come I'm the only one who has to move?
-Because you are more suitable
No, I look like an errand boy
I can't just show up to people's houses unannounced
Ogata, you have a gentlemanly nature so it'll be easier for you
Ugh, how come I have to go to find door signs... to the residential area...
It's wrong
Each of the two teams select the member responsible for doors and signage
The first is Ogata
Kaji
Plum
If they confirm with the people, they can get the ingredients, what will happen?
Go for it!
Noone there, gotta keep looking
Chestnut!
However
No one home
Hello?
Again, no one is home
At this point, the man in charge of signs
Signage is good
Salt
Good, good!
We've got the important seasoning here
But we need to confirm with them, right?
Hello
-Please come in
Sorry, i'm coming in, sorry to interrupt
Hello, I'm a comedian
-Hello
Hello, how are you?
Please show it, thank you
Good! Good!
On the other side, Beppu is in charge of door signs
Oh, wait a minute
Look, the sign is "Sakemoto"
Sorry to disturb you suddenly
Can be used for cooking
Wine is good.
-Very useful for fishy things
I am Beppu, a comedian
Afterwards
Please tell me your name
Shinya Sakemoto
Wow, here we go. Good job. Thanks
At this point, 4 hours have passed
Please tell me your name
Kaiko Sakaguchi
Seafood
And
Kumasaka
Bear
Wild game
Do we have bear meat?
-Yes
Yes, here we go
Horse and bear
"Got bear"
The stench is super strong, right?
In that case, the meat must be steamed with wine to make it softer
It smells bad, doesn't it?
-You need wine to remove the smell
Next, Nishimoto found this couple, one of whom is a foreigner
Nakano Daichi
Please tell me your name
Niel Khon
※Khon sounds like 'corn"
Corn
Where are you from?
Cambodia
-Ah, Cambodia
In this case
I guess so
The rules were originally limited to kanji only
Corn is ok
Corn is ok?
-Yes
Corn is great!
After further discussion, it was decided that katakana ingredients can be obtained from foreigners
She's called corn
Then, we continued a interview in Shinjuku
Met so many!
Because of the proximity to Yoshimoto's theater
Magical Lovely's Murakami appears
Bound to happen being outside for 10 hours
So they asked him
Suzuki Takahiro
Yes, his name is not Murakami
Murakami, your real name is Suzuki
Its a bit complicated
-Overcomplicated
Sorry
-No no no
Also
Oswald
Lets ask
What is this?
I don't know your full names
You don't know?
-Yes
Shunsuke Ito
Ito Shunsuke, then you are
Yu Hatake
Hatake Yu?
Sounds like a male actor
You two get out of here
How did we let you down?
-Just go to the Lumine
Wait a minute, I'm so curious
What is this?
-That's my line!
Please show them one by one
Please tell me your name
Ebi Yasufumi
※Ebi - shrimp
We got shrimp, a good one!
The best target of this project has appeared. Thank you
Please tell me your name
Umeda
Umeda! (ume - plum)
Kikuchi Ginga
Kikuchi
-Ginga
Ginga, what a name
Is chrysanthemum (kiku) okay? Great!
Kin (gold)! Kin! Can sprinkle the dust on top
Really really!
Please tell me your name
Isogai Yu
Kai! (shellfish)
Can any kind of shellfish be used?
Can choose shellfish
Thank you, if its shellfish, I choose scallops
One by one, the two teams get the ingredients
Ogata got none
Only Ogata has yet to get anything
Hello, hello, hello
Do you live nearby?
-Yes
We are shooting on location
Can I ask your name? Don't say it yet!
You'll never guess
I'm not guessing, rest assured
"You'll never guess" must be a good opportunity
Please tell me your name
Cow!
Really?
-Really
How do you pronounce it?
-Gorai Hayato
Gorai Hayato?
A miracle!
-Terrific
Hello?
-Hey, its Ogata
What's up?
I got cow.
-Eh?
Cow
-Cow! Thanks!
You're too muted in your response.
-Wait a minute
I tried to hard to find something
Is this really the attitude you should have toward getting a cow?
7 hours after the start
The red team has gotten 14 ingredients, including horse meat, bear meat, beef and other meat-based ingredients
But not all of these can be used, right?
-Yes
And the blue team got a variety of ingredients such as rice, shrimp, a total of 19
Everyone, we have enough ingredients for 3 dishes
That's great.
-Yes
But the only thing I really want is oil
Oil ah no oil ah
If there are more ingredients, I can't handle it
Try not to look for new ingredients
-Easy for you to say!
You can't talk like that. We're almost dead looking for this stuff
-Indeed
We can't control it.
-It's not good for you to say that
It's not nice to talk like that
-We're working hard
I'm almost ready to go to the kitchen
I'm off to do the dishes
Here the two groups of culinary leaders have gone to the kitchen to prepare the ingredients
Finally, it's time for the cooking session
Okay, this is Beppu, here we go
Finally only 2 hours left
2 hours is very short
The rest of the members will look for ingredients until the last moment
At this time
Hello, this is Beppu
I got pork without any problems
Pork? Good, good, good
Pork can be used for oil
-Pork
Yes, actually
Dad's name is
Butakku Ryan Akira
Acquired pork in the name of a foreigner
※Pork is pronounced Buta
In addition
Butakku Mia Cola
Shinichi unexpectedly also gets Cola
Cola can be used with meat
In addition
Beppu
I got chicken
Chicken? Chicken?
That's tough
That's about the end of it
That's enough, don't look anymore
That's right.
-Too much is not good
At the same time
i got yellowtail
-No way!
Buri, who is called buri?
Buri!
They also succeeded in obtaining yellowtail from foreigners here
In addition
Wow, they really got it!
What is your name?
Yuuki
Great!
The desired oil!
There is not much time left for the cooking showdown
Tastes good
What kind of dishes did the two groups make?
After 10 hours
The ingredients were found and cooking complete
Ingredient search and cooking complete
The final showdown takes place in this restaurant
The other members watch the showdown in a separate room
Thank you
Lady Devi thinks she is attending a regular food project
Serious comedian cooking duel!
The showdown finally begins
A serious duel between 2 professional chef-level comedians without laughs
The judge for both dishes is Lady Devi
Separate 3-course meal from both teams Comprehensive evaluation
Professional level?
-Yes
No way!
First is Fukuda's first course
Okay, come on, Fukuda, show your confidence
Wow, I'm looking forward to it
Please see the first course
What is this?
Raw Scallop and Horse Meat
Here it comes
-Scallop and horse meat
Do horse meat and scallops go together?
Horse meat?
-That's a big deal
-What does it mean?
Made with raw scallops and horse meat
Horse meat
-Right
I topped it with a fruit sauce, and I used pears in the sauce
Eat it raw, please
Not bad
Can it be considered delicious?
It's delicious.
-Great
I'm really happy
I'm amazed!
-Great
I just underestimated you.
-Underestimated, so straight forward
Devi is very strict
Delicious
Right? Look, it's good, right?
Appetizer standard
The first course just right
-Lighter in taste
Perfection
This is the taste that adults like
Chrysanthemum is a big help
Next is the first course for the blue team
Please take a look
Looks good
Stir-fried shrimp, clams, chicken breast, bamboo shoots, cauliflower and plum meat
What is this? Shrimp. You got shrimp!
Too many ingredients
Shrimp was mine
However
It looks like it's all dry
Super dry
No moisture
Looks all dried out
The situation is already bad just by looking at it
It tastes good, right?
How does it taste?
Sorry, it's not good
Very direct
Not good?
It's not good at all.
-Really?
Sorry
It's delicious.
-Especially delicious!
Taste is also very good
It's good.
-Yeah
It's delicious!
-Suitable for bento
If my dog smelt it they'd walk away
Harsh
Dogs wouldn't like it either?
The first course was an overwhelming victory for Fukuda
Next, the second course
Please take a look
What is this?
"Greetings from the Land of Bears."
Please be ok
The rare ingredient bear meat
Was stewed together with bamboo shoots and cauliflower
How does it taste?
The meat is soft
That's a compliment.
-Good impression
Did you use only salt for the seasoning?
-Yes
Next is the meatball made with yellowtail, however
So salty.
-Is it?
I only taste salt
As she said, the only seasoning used was salt
Next is the blue team
Please take a look
Just now criticized as worthless
Boiled pork and bear cutlet with fruit sauce and gold shaving
Bear
-Right
You got bear, too.
-Yes
Just had bear, now another bear
Bears, horse and pig.
-Horse meat at the beginning, right?
An unusual combination of horse and bear
Not a fan at all
Unclear theme
Just now the bear meat was a big hit
So hard
The tone of voice
100 points for "so hard" tone
Next is the last course for the red team
Golden peach sauce sirloin
Cow
-Cow?
Used peach
Not bad
Not bad, not bad at all
This is the highest rating
Ok ok ok
Cows are good!
So came the last course for the blue team
Here we go!
Aromatic fish and snapper super rice ball
Aromatic fish, I love aromatic fish
Wait. Aromatic fish?
-Great!
Who got that?
-Me
That was mine!
A favorite ingredient appears
The blue team got the snapper
Can choose the type of fish
There's fish! We've got it!
What is the result?
What?
More snapper?
It's not bad.
-Really? Thank you
Not particularly tasty either
But it's not bad. It's good. It's good
This is the end of the tasting of the 6 dishes, what is the result?
Your first course was very good.
-Thanks
Beppu's last rice ball was also good
-Thank you
Do I have to choose one?
-Yes
Please!
Please, please, please, please
It won't end if you can't choose
Then I choose the last
Rice balls
In Summary
The winner is the blue team
What do you think?
Lady Devi is really straightforward
Despite them having to cook for her she still said what she thought
Its very difficult to still be able to taste when trying lots of different food
Was the meat really that hard?
The phrase "so hard", it's like she was eating a stone
The tone of "so hard" was too funny
I'll have to rewind and watch it again when it comes on.
-I do want to watch it again
Next is everybody's theories
Tonight's presenter is...
It's been a long time!
It's Kenji Tamura
Hello everyone, long time no see
It's been a long time.
-Yes
I thought you were snowed in
Indeed
If I have offended you, please say so!
Why would you have?
I'll surely apologize
So
-Reorganize your mood
Yes, do you know the singer Yutaka Oe?
Yes
Have you ever been on stage together?
-Yes
Yes? Of course, Hamada-san...
Yes, he came to our show
Was he nice?
A nice guy, yeah
What is it?
Today we bring you this hypothesis about Yutaka Oe
If Yutaka Oe turns out to be bad in private, people will be accept it without much discomfort
What does it mean?
Even if he's very scary?
His whole person seems to be that of having a wild aura
Not really...
He seems like a normal person
That's why there are contrasts
Why is this program aiming their sights at him?
Take for example manga, they often have a kind of smiling monk
But in private, they are actually very bad
-I guess
The real Yutaka Oe is such a monk
What?
So even if he's scary in private
You may also think that this person is really like this and believe it
Don't understand
But the acting and singing world does have some scary people
People in the enka circle are especially bad
What're you talking about "bad"?
If he is very, very scary
Unimaginable
Parking wherever
Parking is pretty bad
If you park wherever, your license will be revoked
If Yutaka Oe turns out to be bad in private, people will be accept it without much discomfort
Therefore, Yutaka Oe was brought in as a helper to play the role of a very scary person
And the target who will witness this in a fake show is
The man who is prone to encountering scary people Chance Oshiro
Hello
Our first meeting
I am Yutaka Oe, a singer and actor of Kitajima Music Agency
Looks like a nice guy
I'm not very good at talking
I'm sorry if it's a problem for you
No, no, I'm the one who isn't good
Very humble
This is the normal Yutaka Oe
However, soon...
Please welcome the singer who is going on a journey with us today
It's Yutaka Oe
Our first meeting
This is out first meeting, I'm Aerosmith
Hello, i'm so happy
Yutaka Oe completely ignores the Aerosmith joke
The 1st bad thing is...
Yutaka Oe, this is Choshi, Chiba Prefecture
Have you been to Choshi?
Oe, brackets, answer
1st Bad Thing
Can't read the teleprompter board
Very interesting
You are very interesting ah
No, no, that... Choshi
I asked if you have ever been to Choshi
Have you been here?
Oe, brackets, answer
Ah, uh...
Well, this is his first location shoot
That... it seems to be the his first location shoot
This is where the staff comes in to explain the meaning of the teleprompter board
Ah, I see, so I answer
Yes, yes, just answer Chance's question
Answer... ah sorry
I'm sorry, 'll say it again
Ready Chance, countdown 5 4 3 2
Oe, this is Choshi in Chiba
Have you been to Choshi?
Oe, brackets, answer
Why?
Let's move on to the next topic
A little angry
Therefore
Festival, festival, festival
Oe is set up so that he only sings without mistakes
Sings as soon as the situation arises
2nd Bad Thing
Thus the scence is forced to end
Ok, cut, thank you
What a great song!
Awesome
Unusually thirsty after singing
3rd Bad Thing
To hear so... so close
Too close is scary
You can't get a ticket this close, right?
Coming over like you want to hit someone
The pause is also scary
From the start, Oe makes frequent and strange actions
Chance who saw these...
He's probably in some kind of trouble
Looks strange
There must be something going on with him
Nice people
Something appears to be wrong, but he is unsure what it is
The next strange thing is...
Chance's Lounge
Pretending to be an agent
Hey, you!
Is this a joke?
Fierce to agent
4th Bad Thing
Do you want to do it?
What are you thinking about?
Chance will also think I'm a fool if I don't do it right
Do you understand?
He's scary when he's angry
Sorry
Are you kidding me?
Because of you, it's a problem for everyone
In the tense atmosphere, Chance holds his breath and the tea in his mouth
Do you want to do well?
-I want to
I'm asking you if you want to do a good job!
I do!
How many times have you said you're sorry?
I've been saying it all along, right?
Hey, I'll kill you!
I'll kill you
It's really rude to everyone
It's really annoying
But also quite protective of Chance
Finally gone
Only just swallowing now
Seem to have been waiting for a while
Just now...
What's going on?
Oe...
He seems to be angry with his manager
Eh?
Super angry
So scary
I think he was born in Kishiwada
He must have been in a gang in Kishiwada
A real Kishiwada punk
Ah, that's right
Is Kishiwada such a place...
Kishiwada 9 is full on gangsters
No its not!
Because of the fury, he begins to think of all of Kishiwada as a dwelling for gangsters
Later outside
Several different terrible scenarios have been prepared
Hello, this is our first meeting
I am a singer and actor at Kitajima Music Agency
I'm Yutaka Oe
Memory loss with each break
5th Bad Thing
Scary, scary, scary.
-It's scary
Many different terrible aspects
5th Bad Thing
Memory loss with each break
But Chance did not specifically retort and instead ignored this fact
Afterwards, Chance begins to think that Oe is acting strangely because his heart is troubled
On the location shoot...
Also sharing an umbrella
Can I say, Oe
There's shit there
If you step on it like this
Just wash it off and you'll be fine
Although at that time, dog shit will be on the sole of your shoe
Like this
You don't need to actually do it!
Right?
What are you doing?
But what I'm trying to say is...
What's he trying to say
Just wash it off and then everything will be fine
Right? It'll be clean
What is this?
That's what I'm trying to say
Eh? What do you mean?
Just that...
The meaning is unclear
But it was clear that Chance was trying to do something to encourage Oe
Just act like a normal person
Just trying to do something
He wants to help out
Here too...
Here we go again
With cutting trees
Singing is good
Hey hey ho, hey hey ho
What is it this time
Ok, cut
Drinking after singing is the most important
6th Bad Thing
This is scary
Drinking and crushing at the same time
The same as drinking jelly
You sure sing very well
Especially powerful
Once again, it was time for a break...
Have you washed your shoes?
Do you have towels?
-Ah!
Not now
Wet wipes are fine
No wet wipes either
What are you thinking? Are you sick?
I'll beat you up!
Sorry
I'm gonna beat you, come outside
I told you to come outside!
Excuse me, can I interrupt?
Fine
Sorry
Okay I got it
Oe-san was so angry
He's fired up?
Super scary...
So annoying, he was so angry
Really angry?
Maybe it's not a problem, he may just be a nasty person
What kind of expression is this?
Sorry, sorry
Sorry I'm late
Hello, its our first time meeting
I'm Oe, the singer of Kitajima Music Agency
Memory loss with each break
7th Bad Thing
Ah, yes, hello, hello
Every break he gets angry and then starts shooting again with no memory
This is the enigmatic cycle of Oe
In the next food review section...
After eating the crab in the seafood rice bowl with his hands
This should be eaten quickly
This is a family meal, right?
Eats with his hands
8th Bad Thing
Only eating the crab
What's wrong with that guy?
Tsk. Ha-
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk
Because of the pressure, Chance keeps ticking
It's going bad
Ha-
To calm down he smokes 3 quit sticks
Is this magic?
What is this little magic trick?
Suddenly 3 sticks appear
Finally, the last shoot of the day
I'm Oe of Kitajima Music Agency
Memory loss with each break
9th Bad Thing
Ah, its not the first time
Not the first time
Finally said it
Ah...
What'll happen in the closing scene in the middle of a beautiful view
We found a good location to shoot
Go back a little more
Don't push me. Don't push me
Eh?
-Don't push me
Symptoms of delusions of victimization
10th Bad Thing
Don't push me
If you try it, I'll do it first
Scary!
Face this way. Watch the distance
Look at the camera
Don't push me
What do you mean by "don't push"?
Of... of course I wont
Of course
Even if it is a joke, do not say so
Can you take a step closer to Oe?
Don't push me
You cannot push me
You touched me
Oh, sorry.
-You touched me
What do you mean? If you want to do it, just come on!
Countdown 5 seconds 4 3 2
Okay, everybody, the view is beautiful.
-Yes
I feel like i've lived until today just to see this view
If the sun comes out
Don't push me. Don't push me
You trying to kill someone?
What?
I will not die alone
I'll definitely take you along
That guy is really dangerous, this guy... really scary
He's gone crazy
He's really that type
Terrible, terrible
Super scary!
I'm not listening to that guy's songs anymore
In summary
The possibility that he's scary can't be ruled out
Who knows?
The theory was tested
Is this how a verification works?
What is this? What have I just watched?
Of course, Oe is not that kind of person
He took it so seriously
No, that's who he is, isn't it?
Yeah, right.
-Yes
He's too good at it, right?
Yes, yes
The performance is too good, very scary
After playing that character, Shiro Sano was also treated as that kind of person...
※Shiro Sano played an Oedipal character in the TV series "Always Love You"
Acted too well
It's drama, if you will
He was following the instructions of the program team to act like this
It's an act
But
He's actually that kind of person
No, no, no
Let me be clear, he's not
Although I know this is an act
I can't listen to his songs anymore either
Please listen!
Everyone please keep listening!
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03