Translation: royaltree1204
Additional translations: Oolong, GakiDave
Timing and typesetting: GakiDave
Let's welcome our next presenter.
It's Mr. Maric!
We have... We have an unusual presenter.
I'm very interested in this presentation though!
What are you possibly going to present?
Since I'm a magician, it will be about magicians.
Ah, yes.
When I say "magician," what do you all think of?
A person who deceives.
That is probably the most common, a person who deceives.
Someone who is very dexterous.
That is my specialty so I'd like to bring a theory related to that.
If an evil magician decided to go all out, they can shoplift without security guards noticing.
In a way, this has mixed rules.
For example, from this distance, as an example...
...here's a gold necklace. See the gold necklace?
Let's say I shoplifted this.
And we're the security guards.
A magician can do this with a necklace like this.
Put it in my hand like this.
It's in my hand, are you watching?
And it's gone. It's gone.
It's nowhere to be found.
If you seriously do not know what happened...
...and if we were in a big grocery store, I could steal all I want.
You're right, if he were an evil magician though.
T/N: The word for narcotics is "mayaku" while shoplifting is "manbiki" so Matsumoto accidentally mistakes them.
But if narcotics... Wait, we're not talking about narcotics officers.
ARE YOU STEALING NARCOTICS?!
No, he's supposed to be the security guard.
We tested the theory of if an evil magician decided to go all out, they can shoplift without security guards noticing.
With that, we turn to a store that is worried about shoplifting in the Adachi ward in Tokyo.
Then don't do
it there!
We conduct a magician vs. security shoplifting showdown.
Even though
they're worried,
you do it there?
The rules are two teams of two.
If security can catch the two magicians...
...among ten random customers, they win.
Tonight, Mr. Maric chooses to enlist these two magicians for the project.
First up:
A veteran performer for 30 years...
Ken Masaki.
Although he doesn't show up in the media much, he is known in the industry as a hidden genius magician.
And the other:
Female magician Mayuko.
An expert magician whose sleight-of-hand work...
...even Mr. Maric considers the best in the business.
How confident are you tonight?
Our specialty is to reveal things.
I am a little uneasy, but...
...we are still magicians.
I believe I can make things disappear without getting caught.
Mr. Maric...
challenged me to do magic that can be seen 360° around me.
Whether security or regular customers are watching...
...viewing from anywhere - I'll work my magic.
Whoa, cool.
Their opponent:
Security Guard Ito Yuu.
Fighting against all shoplifters in various media...
...he's a top security guard.
Scary, scary!
How many shoplifters have you caught?
I've been in my career for 16 years.
I would think over 4,000 people.
Staff: Tonight they'll be magicians.
I don't know what kind of tricks they'll use, but...
...they still have to take the item and hide it.
So we don't get tricked...
...for us, we fight with our eyes.
One hour before the showdown.
Both teams get 10 minutes to scope the place.
Kiwis.
I like round things, even in everyday life.
Normally I use white balls.
Making them appear and disappear is my forte.
If I can take this, that would be nice.
Something like this is OK.
You can make this disappear, just like that, with your custom device.
This would be easy.
Custom device?
It appears they've found a number of items they can use their magic on.
Meanwhile...
I kind of have a bad feeling.
Staff: Bad feeling?
I have a bad feeling.
Bad guys like dimly lit areas.
This opening also concerns me.
There's three ways, but...
...you can only see it from here.
Tonight we set up 20 cameras to get every angle.
One of the security guards will watch the monitors.
The other will be deployed on scene.
We should be able to tell.
If we don't get this...
...I'll have to quit my job.
Let's review the rules.
Among ten random customers...
...two will be magicians, and one a security guard.
The competition starts with neither knowing what the other looks like.
During the 30 minutes only magicians will steal items.
At the end of the contest...
...the security guard will accuse the suspect...
...who he believes is a magician, of shoplifting...
...and call out what items were stolen.
If at least two items are correct, the security guards win.
However, if at least two items aren't correct, the magician wins.
We thought the incorrect items will then be given as a prize...
...but that would just be stealing, so dismiss that idea.
Tonight will just be for self-satisfaction.
Was it necessary to say that?
Who will win this showdown? Magicians?
Or will it be the security guards?
Here they come.
Everyone looks the part.
Everyone? Do they look
like shoplifters or magicians?
That old man is suspicious.
He thinks the old man
is suspicious.
The security guards suspects something about the magician's movement...
...as soon as he walks in.
But it's meaningless
if he doesn't see
him take anything.
Follow him.  I'll look elsewhere.
Already marked.
The male magician is being closely marked by security.
My heart is pounding.
This guy? Maybe this guy?
No, he's yawning.
Throw out the guy in beige.
What about boy with headphones, that guy. No?
No...
Kind of rude!
That's true.
Security narrows down the targets one by one.
However...
I can't make any headway.
Staff: Maybe they haven't stolen anything yet?
I don't see anyone moving suspiciously.
Ten minutes into the contest.
She has something.  She's got something.
Candy! Candy! Candy!
Behind you.
Maybe gum? I didn't see what she took.
Security reacts to the female magician's movements.
But couldn't get proof of what was taken.
It looked like she put
it in the basket.
However, afterwards...
Her behavior is suspicious. This one.
They continue marking her.
I don't think I'm wrong about this one.
They conclude this is one of the magicians.
But can they correctly identify what was stolen?
And how much is the other magician getting away with?
Staff: How was it?
It was harder than I thought.
Staff: Do you know who the magicians are?
I think I know who the magicians are.
Time to prove their claim.
As the customers leave the store...
...they stop the ones they believe to be a magician.
The result?
How well did security observe the magician's acts of crime?
That's the first guy
he threw out.
He did say "throw out
the guy in beige."
You're a magician, aren't you?
Yes.
They got the first magician correct.
But here's where the real battle starts.
If two of the stolen items are accurately declared...
...the security guards win.
So, what did she take?
I think it's a cup of noodles and a Kewpie mayonnaise.  A small one.
And the result is?
Cup of noodles?
No, I do not have a cup of noodles and mayonnaise.
What?! Wrongly accused!
With that said, under these circumstances the magician wins.
What did she take?
Indeed, what did she steal?
What came out of the special costume was...
Rice seasoning
Furthermore...
Chocolate
Rice seasoning
This is what I thought was mayonnaise.
A small one.
Chocolate
Ramune candy
Rice seasoning
Chocolate
Kiwi
Ramune candy
Rice seasoning
This girl took a lot!
Chocolate
Kiwi
Ramune
Rice seasoning
Chocolate
Kiwi
Ramune
Rice seasoning
Yōkan
Afterwards, more and more items
kept coming from her clothes.
Chocolate
Kiwi
Lime
Ramune candy
Rice seasoning
Yōkan
Chocolate
Kiwi
Lime
Ramune candy
Rice seasoning
Yōkan
Chocolate
Kiwi
Lime
Ramune candy
Rice seasoning
Yōkan
Candy
Chocolate
Kiwi
Lime
Ramune candy
Rice seasoning
Yōkan
Candy
Chocolate
Kiwi
Lime
Ramune candy
Rice seasoning
Yōkan
A cucmber?!
Candy
Chocolate
Cucumber
Kiwi
Lime
Ramune candy
Rice seasoning
Yōkan
Amazing!
Here is that technique.
It just went in.
In her sleeve.
Did you notice?
Pretending to reach for one cucumber...
...the other is put in the sleeve.
The average person cannot pull off this technique.
The magician continues putting things in her clothes, one by one.
In there there's also this.
A fish!
Wow!
A total of 15 items stolen without one being detected.
A complete victory for the magician.
And the second...
You're a magician, aren't you?
You're wrong.
Ah...is that so?
What?! This one didn't give away he was a magician!
Actually my name is Ken Masaki.  A magician.
We were debating.
Staff: How do you think he did it?
I don't know his method...
...but he looked puffy, so I was marking him.
The security guards noticed the puffiness in his stomach.
What did they find there?
I have potatoes, carrots, and onions.
My goal was curry.
You have three hands.
This is magic.
I see!
That's right.
Having an extra hand
is an advantage.
What is this?!
Scary! Scary!
The right hand pushing the cart was a dummy.
With his real hand hidden from the cameras in his stomach...
...he is calmly able to commit crimes.
This was also inside.
You did well to fit that in.
We only check to see both hands.
You win.
In conclusion, shoplifting is a crime.
You could serve up to ten years...
T/N: At the time of translating, 500,000yen is equal to $3,611USD.
...and fined up to 500,000 yen.
Perfect!
Although I don't think there will be anyone who would try to imitate this after watching.
You won't be able to pull it off this well.
I repeat, this is in the context of evil magicians.
But the one who took 10 or so items...
...Mr. Maric was so amused, you'd almost cringe.
But she took a fish! A fish!
Is it something only relatable to magicians?