Let's bring on our next presenter.
Original subs: royaltree1204
Additional subs: oolong
Updates and QC: GakiDave
Who's coming?
Who is it?
It's Daikichi Hakata!
It's Mr. Daikichi, the teacher who looks good in a V-neck sweater.
I wanted to dress up like a person on a supermarket ad.
Has anyone heard of the term, "homing instinct"?
Ooya-san, what do you think?
It's people who can get home even though they're drunk, right?
Like, they somehow are able to get home.
Yes, that's essentially what it means.
I never thought that Ooya-san would give the correct answer.
There are many animals who have it, but...
...if you say, "homing instinct," then pigeons may be the most famous for it.
Yes, yes.
The most famous would be the messenger pigeon.
It is said that even if they're 1,000km away, they're able to figure out their way home.
T/N: 1,000km = 621.3 miles
1,000km is approximately the distance from Tokyo to Hokkaido.
It seems that distance is pretty easy for them to find their way.
Once you hear this, you think, "pigeons are amazing".
Mad respect for pigeons
This time, I have brought this kind of theory.
The theory that humans have a better homing instinct than pigeons.
Even if it's amazing for a pigeon to return home to Tokyo from Hokkaido.
For example, if you were abandoned in Hokkaido, what would you do?
T/N: Hokkaido is the northernmost island in Japan and known for the harsh cold temperatures.
Well, I'd get back home one way or another.
Futo-san, how about you, if you were abandoned in Okinawa?
T/N: Okinawa is the southernmost island in Japan and known for the warm tropical weather.
I'd relax and take my time.
We're talking about going home!
Though it depends on the season.
We verify if humans have a better homing instinct than pigeons.
Tonight we enlist the help of a pigeon coop in Saitama prefecture.
Roughly 500km from Tohoku's mountainous region...
...we hold an exhibition race.
Who will get home faster: human or pigeon?
My first thought is that the pigeons will come out on top.
(Question: Can pigeons win against humans?)
Really?
I'm confident.
And so the person they choose to go against the pigeons is...
Why from here?!
Excuse me.
Yasuda Dai Circus
Kuro-chan
Wait...
Eh?
It's the awful staff again!
Where are we going?
Staff:  You'll know when you get there.
T/N: Inoki Kanji (aka Antonio Inoki) had a famous saying about how even if you wonder about what will happen if you go down a certain path, you'll know when you get there.
That's something Inoki Kanji would say
With that said, we put on the eyemask...
...and begin our journey to the starting line.
I can't predict anything.
Staff: Were you able to predict things before?
Oh, definitely not!
With this, the car travels down the freeway...
...roughly eight hours to the starting point.
7:00 the next morning.
We arrive at a mountain in the Tohoku region.
Staff:  Good morning.
Staff: We've arrived.
Wasn't that kind of long?
This time we start from...
...Iwate Prefecture, Shimoheigun, Iwaizumi town.
No station, and practically no roads nearby.
An area with nothing in sight.
Incidentally, the temperature today is -3C.
It's cold!  So cold!
It's really cold, isn't it?
In shorts and short-sleeves...
...Kuro-chan is perhaps underdressed for Iwate.
This is absolutely in the minuses.
Both participants take their starting positions.
To make things fair we confiscate his phone and wallet.
As the pigeons aren't privy to knowing where they are, we start without either one knowing.
As a result, will the human win?
Or will the pigeons?
Scary...he doesn't know.
(Rule: The pigeon that returns earliest out of the ten pigeons will be their time.)
What was that?
What's going on?
It's started!
What was that flying?
You're not going to
tell him it started?!
I don't get the meaning of this.
What is going on?  Really?
It's freezing!
Kuro-chan doesn't realize the race has started.
So tell him!
This time there are others besides Kuro-chan...
I just followed my friends...
...so I don't know.
I even had them buy my ticket.
An old man who has never ridden on the train by himself.
Are you confident?
Can you do this?
Even an 8-year old is going on their first errand alone.
All start roughly at the same time.
Ten minutes after the pigeons took flight...
...Kuro-chan shows no signs of starting.
How long do I stand here?
It seems the frequent blindfolding has
trained him not to remove the eyemask.
He doesn't remove the eyemask until he's instructed to do so.
He is very disciplined in that sense.
Seriously, one hour later...
But then...
Excuse me, I have to go to the bathroom.
I think I'm going to leak!
Staff-san?
We did start from
the bathroom.
Hey...
Seriously, I don't understand.  What is this?
Did it start?
Can I take off my eyemask?
Hello?
HELLO?!
Anyone?
Can I take it off?
Can I take off the eyemask?
It's ok, right?
Where am I?!
Where am I!?
Even if he asks this
one question, they
can't answer it.
This is amazing.
"Take the camera and go to the next location."
Where is this?!
What is this?!
"Page 1?"
"Saitama Prefecture, Koshigaya"
I don't know where this is?
Am I supposed to go here?
This is different than usual!
I don't really understand, but...
...really, what is this?!
As a result, who will reach the goal first?
One hour since the start of the race.
The current situation is...
I'm currently heading towards Route 45.
To get the help of local people...
...the old man heads to the station.
His mother told him, "if you're in trouble, ask someone for help."
Ringo-kun, for the time being, looks for a house.
Maybe this way.
And Kuro-chan, who started an hour later than the others...
Just a minute, what is this?
Seriously, what is this?
With no knowledge of what is going on...
...he walks into the mountains.
At any rate I have to go this way, right?
And then...
Oh, there's a car!
An Iwate Prefecture car?
He looked at the plate.
Eh? Is this Iwate prefecture?
Kuro-chan managed to get a significant hint...
...from the plates of the passing car.
I should have talked to that car just now.
After walking another ten minutes...
What's this?
This looks like a workshop.
Ah, there's someone there.
Excuse me...
Eh? Are you Kuro-chan?
Amazing!
Do you have a second to talk?
Sorry, can I get you in the shot?
Can you tell me where I am?
This is... Iwaizumi town in Iwate prefecture.
Iwate prefecture?!
Tohoku's Iwate prefecture?
Yes, Tohoku.
By the way, from here I have to go to Koshigaya in Saitama.
I have to get to Saitama.
Saitama?
There really isn't much in the way of public transportation here.
No?
Not really.
Eh... what should I do?
He is able to find his current location, but there are no stations around.
There aren't any freeways around either.
Quite a hopeless situation.
There's a car here.
Would it be possible for you to take me somewhere by car?
If it's to the station.
It's ok?
For now, with the generosity of a local...
...he is able to get to the nearest station.
He got lucky.
You really are in a tough place.
This is too much.
Other shows aren't like this.
They're messed in the head!
Meanwhile, Ringo-kun was looking for a house.
Not able to find anyone and tired from walking, he sits down.
As for the old man...
Excuse me, good morning!
Would you mind giving me a ride to the station on the way?
Is Komoto station ok?
Yes.
Hitchhiking for the first time in his life...
...he is the first to arrive at a station.
And as for the pigeons?
(※ - Stock footage)
They are likely making good progress.
Right, filming them
was impossible.
Two hours since the start of the race.
As the old man waits outside by the bus stop...
...Kuro-chan also arrives.
So from here I go...
From here, go to Miyako.
That's the fastest?
Yes, fastest.
Then from Miyako go to Morioka.
Then from Morioka...you can get there by bullet train or whatever.
Based on the suggestion we would aim for Morioka, but...
...Kuro-chan currently has no money.
Furthermore...
Right now you are at this place called Omoto.
That's way too late.
This might be the fastest way.
There is a two-hour wait for the next train.
But with no money, there is also no train.
While this is going on...
Kuro-chan!
Thank you for your hard work!
Locals who recognize Kuro-chan come to talk.
Seems you don't have enough for the train fare?
I have nothing.
They left him with an eyemask.
Ah...
Not "ah...", this isn't normal!
Look how I'm dressed.  Isn't this strange?
By the way, how long would it take by car?
From here to Miyako, probably about an hour.
About an hour?
Do you have any plans after this?
If it were to Miyako, the three of us could ride together.
It's ok?
We can take you as far as Miyako.
We are heading to the Miyako site anyway.
He gets a ride to Miyako station.
Thank goodness, really.
I don't know what's going on.
Meanwhile, Ringo-kun discovers a house.
Hello...
Who are you?
I'm kinda on this errand by myself...
Ah...
(Shows the paper) Here.
That's Saitama prefecture.
Ringo-kun gets a ride to the station from a kind stranger.
So many nice people!
Three hours since the start.
Itadakimasu!
He accepts a bento from a local shopping street.
His first meal of the day.
Sorry about that, thank you.
It's hard filming, isn't it.
With zero funds, Kuro-chan gets this suggestion.
I wonder if you get get home with 5,000 yen.
I wonder if I can.
Offer to have your picture taken at my job site.
Say, 1,000 yen per shot with five people is 5,000 yen.
Could you kind of give me a ride there?
A dangerous schemer appears.
He's Kuroda Kanbei.
T/N: Kuroda Kanbei was a feudal lord known for his quick wit.
With that said, they stop at their job site...
...annd raise funds with pictures.
Pose, please!
It's Kuro-chan!
Thank you so much!
Sorry for accepting this.
I will use this money wisely.
He gets 6,000 yen total.
With everyone's strength I'm able to return home!
Since you're getting on the bus at Miyako station...
...to Morioka will be 2,030 yen.
2,030 yen...
From Morioka, take the bullet train for 8,230 yen.
8,230 yen?
Their research indicated that to get to Saitama...
...it would require 10,260 yen.
Currently short by 4,260 yen.
And so...
This is the always-happy Kuro-chan!  Wah-wah-wah!
Seiji-san, thank you so much for the 2,260 yen.
Recording individual messages to the local townsfolk.
With this, the goal of 10,260 yen has been reached.
Amazing!
This is incredible!
Looks like you'll get home.
Yeah, looks like it!
But when I get back, I'm not sure if it's finished or not.
I'm really not sure what I'm actually participating in.
That's right, Kuro-chan has no knowledge of what's going on.
Tonight's challenge is Humans vs Homing Pigeons.
Surely the pigeons are having a nice flight.
Currently among them, the old man is in last place.
After failing to get on the bus, he now aims to get to Morioka by hitchhiking.
And then...
Pardon me, which way are you heading?
Umm...Morioka...
He gets a car heading to Morioka...
...suddenly coming up from behind.
Meanwhile, Ringo-kun arrived at Miyako Station before Kuro-chan.
Just as he was directed: onto the bus to Morioka station.
However, perhaps exhausted from his first trip alone...
...he falls fast asleep.
And Kuro-chan, who got a ride to Miyako...
Is it alright?
Is this ok with everyone?
...got a ride with a family going to Morioka.
Why didn't you laugh there?
With this, all three are aiming for Morioka at roughly the same time.
And the first to arrive at Morioka station is...
I'm sorry, everyone.
Kuro-chan.
What?! It's Kuro-chan!
All that's left is to get the money collected earlier...
...and get on a bullet train.
The goal is close at hand.
But, as one would expect, a situation arises!
Kuro-chan is the first to arrive at Morioka station.
But a situation has arisen!
Excuse me...
...I'd like to go to Koshigaya in Saitama prefecture.
To Koshigaya would be a total of...
...a total of 13,170 yen.
13,000 yen?
13,000 yen, eh?
This is the cheapest price?
Yes, it is.
It looks like the researched price was wrong.
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no...
We made a mistake.
The calculations were completely off.
With that said...
Ready, and...
Congratulations on your marriage Manabe! Wah wah wah!
He sells wedding congratulation messages.
And in just five minutes, he's raised 6,000 yen.
You can make it with this!
With this, he acquires a bullet train ticket and taxi fare.
What a crazy journey!
From the funds, a bullet train ride and a regular train ride...
...for two and a half hours ends in Saitama's Kasukabe station.
Made it to Kasukabe.
After that, get to the goal destination in a taxi.
Thank goodness, I really made it!
I finally made it!
And then...
Ah, this is it!  This is it!
Mister, thank you so much!
Eleven hours and twenty seven minutes since the start...
...Kuro-chan reaches the goal.
Is here ok?
Staff: Well done.
Staff: You reached an admirable goal.
Oh, I don't do something here?
Staff: This is the goal.
I made it!
This is the end? It's over?
Staff: But Kuro-chan...you lost.
Eh? What? What do you mean?
I lost?
That's right.  Five hours earlier...
Ah, they're here!
The pigeons came in first place.
Faster than in a car!
Incredible!
Also, 30 minutes before Kuro-chan arrived...
...the old man arrives.
Good job everyone!
Also, Ringo-kun, who arrived 15 minutes before Kuro-chan.
I lost?
Staff: You lost.
What's "yes"?
Lost to who? I didn't lose to anyone.
I wasn't up against anybody!
Staff: Pigeons.
Pigeons?
What are you talking about?
Kuro-chan's face looks like he's been shot by a peashooter.
Here at last we explain the project.
Staff: By the way, this time...
Staff: We released ten pigeons...and two came back home.
And the other eight?
Isn't that the bigger question?
With that said, pigeons will return faster from Tohoku than humans.
However, most never came back.
I see, I see.
Well, unfortunately, humans lost, but...
...wasn't that clever of Kuro-chan to get back the way he did?
Clever or maybe devilish.
His method seemed very simple.
And there's also...
...they didn't show even one heartwarming moment by Ringo-kun.
I think there were a lot.
Would you just gloss that over?
An 8-year-old who does his very best.
They didn't show the kid's uneasiness.
I think we should change that background music. I feel sorry for the other show.
T/N: The background music they used for Ringo-kun comes from the show, "My First Errand", a show about young kids running their first errand all alone.
Like the mother's tears and everything.
Kuro-chan can make that much money...
...how much could Matsumoto-san make?!
I personally can't use Kuro-chan's sort of simple methods.
But really, his worth...
If Matsumoto-san were doing photos on the spot like that, he could probably get 10,000 yen per!
T/N: 10,000yen was approximately worth $82.61USD at the time this episode aired.
Yeah, that's right!
Definitely!
Let's see how much we can earn!
Please go try to see how much you can earn.
And then please come back by helicopter or something.