Hello everyone, welcome to Wednesday's Downtown.
Today's presenter is this person!  Welcome!
It's Viking Kotouge!
I'm not a pin mic!
I'm not a pin mic.
I thought my pin mic was standing over there.
What kind of system is this?
Today we have that annual series, which is:
2018 Advance Prank Notice
This series has become a staple at this time of year.
We investigated who was pranked the most throughout the year...
...and told them in advance that we would prank them over the course of a week.
At the end of the week they tell us what they believe to be a prank.
Doesn't the person who gets pranked the most usually present this segment?
That's how we've done it every year.
But...enough of that.
So in 2014 and 2015 I was first place in back-to-back years.
And one of the pranks they did on me was all the way in Nagoya.
We were waiting at a traffic light when my own car passed in front of me.
Who are the most-pranked entertainers in 2018?
This year we'll be doing the Advance Prank Notice with "that" comedian!
We'll be starting the Scream-1 Grand Prix! Get points with screams and laughter!
Getting screams is rather easy.
As well, finding the guy with the longest hair in Japan!
And a chanting competition with Nakamori Akina's DESIRE!
The most-pranked entertainers of 2018...
Three people are tied for 8th, having been pranked seven times.
Karina Maruyama, who become popular last year.
Nadal from Korokoro Chikichiki Peppers...
...and Kotouge from Viking.
By the way, Kotouge is the only one...
...to have made the Top Ten rankings for five years in a row.
7th is Otake from Jungle Pocket with eight times.
6th is Okarina from Okazu Club with nine times.
Most Pranked in 2018 Rankings
Next at number five is...
Viking Nishimura, with ten times.
Instead of having a "pranker" and a "prankee"...
...they both end up being pranked a lot.
The two of them are in the rankings.
They're a weird Combi right?
It's pathetic, isn't it.
Next, two entertainers are tied for third.
Ganbareruya's Yoshiko, with eleven times.
Even with a long break at the end of the year...
...the popular entertainer secured a third place finish.
Tied for third is Fujiwara from Fujimoto.
So far, all the faces we think of when we think "dokkiri".
Next is number two...
Ogata from Panther with fourteen times.
The man whose career started with the help of "dokkiri"...
...is getting "a second break" thanks to dokkiri.
He has been pranked on shows on every channel...
...leading to a respectable second place.
Finally, the one who rose to take the number one spot is...
Sanshiro's Komiya, with fifteen times.
He just barely missed the top spot in 2017...
...but this time it was he who won
by the slimmest of margins.
Our most-pranked entertainer of 2018 is Komiya!
Tecchan, you don't really get pranked any more?
For me nowadays it might happen two or three times a year...
...right around the time when the seasons change.
Occasionally it happens.
So Komiya was number one for 2018, but...
...Komiya already did this challenge last year.
So this time we got this man to take the challenge instead.
This time, the man stepping up to the Advance Notice Prank challenge is...
Second place in the dokkiri rankings, Panther's Ogata.
Staff: Ogata-san...
Staff: In 2018, out of all the entertainers who were pranked...
Second place? Is that so?
Is that a good thing?
I'm not quite sure.
There was only a one point difference between Ogata and the champion, Komiya.
As someone who was pranked 14 times throughout the year...
...Ogata should be able to tell when he is being pranked.
If we prank Ogata seven times throughout the week...
...will he notice all of them?
One Week Advance Notice Prank Investigation.
Honestly I think I'll be ok.
I'm quite sensitive.
Staff: Sensitive?
Yes.
Compared to the previous challengers...
...of Kotouge, Saito, and Komiya...
...he is, by far, the most obtuse.
I think I will realize right away, to be honest.
For the extremely confident Ogata, we have the following pranks:
#1 - Slightly far-away Kan (one of Ogata's partners in Panther) is not really Kan.
#2 - Car navigation audio recording is fake.
#3 - Setsubun (end of winter holiday) event demon is a very tough opponent.
#4 - The living room at home is a little smaller.
#5 - Anmika with no makeup is really somebody else.
#6 - Squid (instead of octopus) inside of takoyaki.
#7 - Walk past the same scary man every day.
Cameras are following Ogata around all week.
We will execute each of these pranks during this timeframe.
After one week, Ogata will tell us what he believes was a prank...
...out of the things he experienced.
As someone who is sensitive to pranks (according to himself)...
...will he be able to point out all of the pranks?
One Week Later
Good morning!
I was constantly searching and looking. Yeah...
It was tough.
Staff: Are you confident?
I am!
Ogata wrote all of the suspicious events that he experienced in his notebook.
Will Ogata manage to call out all of the pranks?
The first event he thinks was a prank was...
First off, this one has to be a prank.
I went to a bean-throwing event at a preschool.
At this event, I would throw beans at the demon.
When I threw the beans, the demon would fall to the ground.
However, no matter how many times I hit him with the beans...
...he kept getting up!
When I did this, he was smirking under the mask.
I thought to myself, "this has to be a prank."
But I pushed through to the end.
Demons, get out!  Good luck, come in!
He ran out of beans.
For 10 long minutes Ogata would continue fighting this formidable demon.
We're both huffing and puffing as we're tussling.
He hit me so many times with the stick.
Such a thing...
If it was, that school is sick and wrong.
If that's real...that's one messed-up preschool.
The second incident Ogata thinks was a prank.
We used my house one day for work...
...my house was the location...
...and the director for that...
...had the smelliest feet!
It smelled SO bad!
He had the face of a man with smelly feet.
You could see yellow fumes coming out like in a comic book.
It was so bad I thought it had to be one of the pranks.
It was just a staff member from one of his regular shows.
Ogata unnecessarily insulted him.
Ogata's hopes for 100% are already gone.
The third incident Ogata thinks was a prank.
There's a bathhouse I go to frequently...
...about four times a week.
The water at the bathhouse...
...was a little bit slimy.
The employees looked a little nervous, too.
This is the first we've heard of this type of hot water.
Ogata, supposedly sensitive to pranks, gets two wrong in a row.
...and then...
I have a junior called Ichikippurin.
He tells me, "there's this really good ramen place."
So I went.
And it was really bad.
My wife...
She was snoring so much...
...like an old man.
If this isn't one of the pranks, then I seriously...
...it would turn me off from my wife a bit.
Ogata continues to insult the people around him of his own accord.
The sixth incident Ogata thinks was a prank.
I bought a car...
I converted my Land Cruiser 80 to a Land Cruiser 60 body.
I was very particular about the details.
It's a car that I cherish.
On the right side, by the handles, there was a 10 yen punch mark.
Do you know the 10 yen punch?  It leaves a scratch.
I definitely think it's one of them.
That was really vicious.
It's right up Wednesday Downtown's alley.
As if!
Isn't that really sinister?
Even we wouldn't go that far.
At the end of the day, the notebook was full of issues from his daily life.
Finally, the seventh incident Ogata thinks was a prank is...
I had a job where I walked around town.
Just around the town...
There was a meat store with lots of fried things, like croquettes.
The person who worked there...
...previously worked for Wednesday Downtown.
I was pranked like, "what if a weirdo was disturbing your job?"  Do you remember that?
This is the dining room "Solitary Gourmet" comes to.
...excuse me...
Everyone becomes more energetic with... the fish...
...we're filming for TV right now, I'm sorry... YES...
The employee was that weirdo, definitely.
Yes, during the fake walking around town filming...
How long have you been doing this? 40 years?
46 years.
Dressed as the owner of the meat shop was the weirdo that Ogata had previously encountered.
I see...
His face is like,
"No way right?"
His energy is so low!
That face left such a strong impression on me. It's like - I still have dreams about it.
I will never forget that face.  Ever.
A regular person I wouldn't have noticed, but THAT guy...
I'm already looking...
...that guy was definitely one of the pranks.  Yes.
However, this time...
The prank wasn't just at the "walking around town" gig.
Even if it was just a moment...
...he passed by this man every day.
Ogata's answer that the owner of the meat store was the weirdo...
...was close, but no cigar.
So, here we reveal the pranks to Ogata.
Staff: You only got one correct.
Only one?!
We told him which one we got correct.
Wait, what about the slime?
Staff: That was wrong.
Ehh, that's scary!
Fact: The bathhouse has slimy bath water.
What was that slime?
That's so disgusting!
Staff: The director with smelly feet was real, too.
Oh no...I was so rude...
The 10 yen punch on your Land Cruiser is also real.
Who does that?
Does that mean someone is messing with me?
Ogata, who could only identify one out of seven pranks...
...is about to find out about the other six pranks.
Is it the handshake event?
Staff: What handshake event?
Yoshimotozaka.
Staff: It's not the handshake event.
Oh, it's not?
Staff: Didn't you have another job at Yoshimotozaka?
Wait, is it the car navigation?
We're going to have someone handle one prefecture each...
...and provide the voice for the car navigation.
Ogata-san, we're going to have you do Hokkaido.
Staff: The car navigation recording was all fake.
That was fake?
I was saying normal things...
Turn left, thank you.
"Turn left, thank you!"
"Up ahead is a dedicated left-turn lane, thank you!"
Could we get "continue straight" in the four different variations?
"Continue straight for one kilometer."
"Continue straight for ten kilometers."
"Continue straight for 100 kilometers."
"Continue straight for 1000 kilometers."
Oh yeah, I guess if you think about it...
...that would mean you're driving straight for 1000 kilometers.
"1000 kilometers ahead, turn right."
"10,000 kilometers ahead, turn right."
Wow, he doesn't notice with this?
This guy's a moron.
He doesn't realize with this!
Next we're doing some destinations.
There are some kanji I can't read.
"Shimukappu." (a real place)
"You have arrived in Shimukappu!"
What's this next one?
Katocha. (a fake place)
Katocha?
"You have arrived in Katocha!"
There's more...
"A bear has appeared."
It's Hokkaido...
Bears come out, don't they?
"A bear is causing this 10 kilometer-long traffic jam."
Next, please.
You're kidding me!
"You ran over a bear."
Could you lower your tone a little?
Kind of like you feel bad about it.
"You ran over a bear."
He treated every demand very seriously...
...completely ignoring the weird things he had to say.
Rurururu...a fox has appeared!
A crab has appeared!
For the next prank reveal...
Staff: Did anyone come say hi to you in the green room?
Do you know what show this was for?
The King's Brunch.
Anmika-san?
Anmika-san?  What about her?
Excuse me...
I'm Anmika, nice to meet you!
The person who came into Ogata's green room was "Anmika without makeup"...
...but in reality was a completely different person.
She came in with no makeup.
I was thinking to myself, "she looks pretty old."
I did think her face looked a little different.
But isn't that what the entertainment industry is like?
An acquaintance of mine...
...gave me me a bunch of these new dog treats.
I've been handing them out to other dog owners.
Oh, is that so?  Thank you very much.
Excuse me for not having makeup on.
Anmika-san? That was really Anmika-san?
So that's Anmika-san...
The voice seemed like her.
Yes, this time the face is completely different, but...
I'm Anmika, nice to meet you!
...we recorded her voice beforehand.
We put a speaker in her mouth and played the audio.
Going on...
Arinkurin brought me some takoyaki.
Staff: Those were filled with squid.
It wasn't octopus?
What kind of prank is that?!
As for his living room...
By making part of the wall 10cm thicker...
...we made the room slightly smaller.
Staff: We made the wall 10cm thicker.
Eh...
...what kind of prank is that?!
Ogata didn't notice the slightly smaller living room through the whole week.
Next...
Staff: Didn't you go to the Yoshimoto offices?
Yeah, I did.
Staff: Did you see anyone there?
Ohh, like Mukai and Kan...
Kan-san (fake Kan)
standing in the distance.
Ogata-san!
Ogata-san, what time do you finish today?
Mukai is real...
...but the person next to him is not their partner Kan.
...but an artist who looks a lot like Kan:
Keiji Muranaka from wacci.
What time do you finish?
Around 11 for me.
Ahh, someone was saying they wanted to grab a drink with you.
What?
Someone was saying they wanted to get a drink with you.
What are you doing?
Filming.
He doesn't know
his own partner?
Who the hell is this?!
Ehhh!
So that wasn't Kan?!
Finally, we have the weirdo that Ogata partially noticed.
Staff: For seven days, you crossed paths every day.
Ehh?
The whole time?
What do you mean?
Seven times?
Every day?
Ehh?!
So scary!
What kind of ending was that?
He got so many wrong!
Is it really that hard to tell?
Seriously, with the car navigation - what's wrong with him?
It means he thinks that kind of situation is realistic, right?
That if you run over a bear, your car can detect it...
...and let you know you ran over a bear.
If you run over a bear...
...your car would be destroyed.
He thinks today's car navigation systems can let us know these things.
But isn't it crazy he didn't recognize Kan-san?
It's someone you work with every day.
Kan is one of the partners in your group!
Yeah, but if you lined up our staff here with a chimpanzee...
...I might think it was Hamada.
If it was behaving like this..