Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
It's Jinnai Tomonori!
Good relationship, right?
Let's get to the point
Please take a look
2nd Among the people you know, if you confess in the order of how much you like them, and you'll find someone within 100 people, no matter who you are
The ending of the 1st edition previewed the 2nd
But what happened the first time around?
Please see the review
The last to test this hypothesis was...
Papa's Hoshino Disco
Who confessed to he liked in the order of how much he liked them
At the 16th person...
Please go out with me
Eh--?
With Miyuki...
I have discussed the matter that I like Disco
It came out
A succesfull coupling
Or so it seemed
As expected... Ito...
I like you
But we haven't been out on a proper date yet
He was told "i'll consider it after a date"
Indeed
As he couldn't give up on the 13th person, Ito Chinami
He ultimately didn't choose Ami
And after a few meetings with Ito
He confessed again
If you can, please go out with me
However
I can't get into a relationship with you
Unfortunately, he failed
On the other hand, Ami, who clearly confessed but was rejected
Didn't Disco do this project?
So...
Can I try it too?
I want to have a boyfriend, really
With all my heart
Volunteered?
And so, the 2nd edition follows suit
Ponloop Ami's 100 person confession project!
So, Kanda, this theory
If you did it, there'd probably be no problem
No, I don't think so
It's 100 people, after all
I don't even know 100 people
Ah right
What do you think, Shibuya?
Well, honestly...
-Confident?
Confident
For sure!
If its 100 people, it should be possible
To validate this theory
Now is not the time to be indecisive
With 5 years of experience, Pon Loop's Ami, 28 years old
By the way, how has your love life been so far?
Couldn't have dressed up a bit?
So far... the number of years without a boyfriend equals my age
Neither confessed nor been confessed to
The majority of students at her high school were girls
And in college she became passionate about comedy
That's how Ami has never experienced love head-on
I kind of think it's time for a relationship
Seems like a good girl
So, she was asked to seriously consider the person she wanted to date for a week
The day of confession arrives
Only the thought of a relationship is on my mind
Ami's first choice is...
Determined
Not bad, not bad
Oswald's Ito
The first time we met was about 3 years ago
Really?
Picked him as number one?
It was love at first sight, so to speak
So
"Hello"
-You've worked hard
Want to meet
"Hey, what? What's wrong?"
Called Ito to TBS
Her first confession in life begins
Looks kinda nervous
Thank you for your hard work
Hey, what's going on here?
No, that...
The wind is so strong
Could you please have a seat first?
Sit?
On the bench?
-Yes
Although it may be insignificant to you
When recording a show with you
With your group and mine
In the backstage, the atmosphere was pretty cold
At that time, only Ito came to our side
Really, that...
"Don't worry so much about whether this works or not. It's okay."
So gentle
This is what you said to me
You probably don't remember
Hmm...
I was really saved by those words
The bangs
Gradually, that...
A handsome vibe appeared
Think I like Ito
The back is flowing
What kind of haircut is this?
Hmm...
Like a character actor
I like you
I like Ito
Would you go out with me?
Very clear and direct
Well, that...
So, um...
Ah, I'm very sorry
Ami is unfortunately rejected by her first choice
I just see you as a junior
A close junior
Is that what you think of me?
Yes, that's for sure
Well that also makes me happy
To be honest I think it's quite suspicious
The phrase "cute junior"
It's fine to be a "cute junior"
And he said it casually
As its just the first person, I'm starting to realize
It's starting to get a bit scary
But i'll continue with a positive mind
So
Awesome
The second place is Shogo
They're all comedians
Really
Well, I think it's not possible
It is better to have a good relationship but also distance with juniors
Ah...
-That's what I think
She's still a "cute junior"
Then
Another comedian
"I just see you as a junior"
"That's all I've thought up until now"
That is, as a fellow comedian
Youtuber？
"I think of you as an interesting senior"
Comedy writer
"I think of you from that perspective."
-Hmmmmmmmm
And
"I have a girlfriend at the moment"
Ahh...
College junior
I thought none of them have girlfriends
I took this into consideration when making the list
Indeed
From her first confession in life, Ami is rejected by 6 people in 3 hours
In 7th place is...
Timon D's Maeda
We have a good relationship
Unexpected choice
And we go out to eat
This is a different thing from falling in love
We also go to concerts together sometimes
The closest male so far, Maeda
Thank you very much. Sorry
If you can
Would you be able to go out with me?
Ahhh so
Yes, that, yes...
Did you say "I like Shogo"?
I still remember you said "I still like Disco"
Did I say that?
Don't remember?
He knew...
Have I told that many people?
I'm surprised by myself
I'm not feeling so good about myself
I really like you as a person
Really?
-Really
It's true... I feel like I like you
-Is it true?
Well, I have a girlfriend now
Why are you a little angry?
After that, she also contacted former college seniors, comedians and staff members
16 people
So tough
Successive confessions in order of preference
Is her mental state okay?
Mental state must be not so great
I think of you as a sister
After 9 hours
She's been rejected 17 times
Too strong
Honestly, in terms of Mimori...
What do you think of me?
"Eh? No, eh... the feeling of people of the same age?"
We are indeed the same age
"Yes"
"It's the feeling of a close male classmate"
Eh?
I get it
"Eh, no, that..."
Thank you very much, really
Sorry to call you so suddenly
The mood became very bad
Please continue to look out for me
Thank you very much
"Is it that awkward? What's going on here?"
Thank you very much. Sorry
Just wants to hang up the phone quickly
"Eh, what is this?"
Hurry to the next
Indeed, such a situation, it can become...
It's dangerous. It's really dangerous
I was just about to confess
This is no different from confessing...
Seems very petty
At 9pm
The 19th male
Juicemans' Yojiro
Juicemans?
A comedian?
-Comedian
Loads of comedians
Calling unexpectedly at night
Long phone calls with him
If you don't like someone, you wouldn't do it, right?
Why?
Indeed
That's what I think, at least
Maybe
A seemingly obtainable goal
The 19th man
How exactly will it develop?
Very handsome
Thank you for your hard work
Yeah pretty attractive
So urgent, what's wrong?
In regard to you
I like you
I just want to get it out there
So I invited you here today
To date?
Yes...if you can
He said it straight
If possible, I would like to go out
Although I think it would be good if we could play together as before
I really like baseball
I know
Although I would like to be with someone
But that...
I need my own space
Need time for your own interests
-Yeah, yeah, yeah
Time to watch the game
I am also the type of person who needs their own space
I see
Don't want to be tied down
Is that ok?
Hesitating
What do you think?
Is there any other factor that you think is necessary?
I didn't know before
Didn't know that Ami liked me
So with that in mind
What comes after
I think its possible
Considered
To be honest, it's not an immediate "I like you too" feeling
I see
But we can go out on a date, that's no problem at all
Eh, really?
It's okay to go on a date
If I had to decide today
All I can say is sorry
OK
A possibility
To wait until after the date... although leaving the possibility
Ami was told a relationship straight away is not possible
How do you feel now?
I really don't want to expect too much
Although it's a bit of an understatement to say that
But I want an "on the day boyfriend"
On the day boyfriend
Why?
This kind of thing will not happen!
So into the second day of confession
This kind of thing has to be accumulated over time
What'll happen on day two
I feel like I'm back in the right frame of mind
I'm approaching today with the feeling of starting afresh
Very positive mindset
The 20th male that such Ami wants to date is
Ultra Boogies' Sasaki
He is very gentle
To be honest
If pressure is put on him
He might go out with me
So
What is she saying!?
Can you go out with me?
I don't think of you in a romantic sense
Although rejected once...
The strategy changes to apply pressure
What's going on?
But really...
Do you have a girlfriend now?
No girlfriend
Anyone you like?
No
Really...
No, it's...
This isn't how you should confess
In any case, the precondition of something first
Precondition？
Just do not have preconceptions
Eliminate the concept of fixation
-Hmm
Don't say you can't date me because I'm a second generation female comedian
Don't worry about such factors
I think there is definitely
That... because
What are you talking about?
In a relationship sense?
Yes, relationships
Yes, but...
But I can only answer what I think
Indeed
But it may not be accurate
No, that's my decision
Pressure confession strategy failed
That's a sure failure!
She had a vicious look in her eyes
Things are getting worse and worse
After confessing to more than 20 people
Ami is becoming stronger
Is it possible in the future?
"No, no, no, no, no, no, no."
Answer too fast
The 25th place is
Former comedian, Ochimori's Ochi
All types of people
I have feelings for Ochi
The feeling of like
Really?
The tone of voice is kind of different now
Ah, so
Well, as a junior, you get a perfect score
Ah, okay, I don't need to hear the rest
I think what you're gonna say afterwards will be very annoying
Not so good
As a girl.
-Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. I said, "Okay."
Don't be like that!
As a girl to see
-Dangerous, okay, okay, wait, what, what, what, what?
What do you mean by danger?
Wait, really don't say it
Hey, what? I don't know what you mean.
-No, I really...
Wait a minute. What? Okay, stop it.
-No, in the future...
Okay, okay, okay, okay, why?
This is not a confession
Don't know what you mean
In the future...
-All right, all right, all right, all right, stop it
What's going on here?
Impossible, its impossible
What kind of conversation is this?
I can't do it, but I hope you can...
-No, no, that's not what I meant...
I'll cheer myself up, okay?
Please don't say it.
-What do you mean?
What kind of conversation is this?
Next in 26th place was 2nd place Shogo's partner Takeru
What just happened?
I like your personality
His partner
Not just personality, how to say it...
I like you
In terms of dating
Can you tell me if it's doable?
No, this is the one...
It is possible, right?
No, no, no, no, no, no
It's okay, right?
-No
Sorry, no
The theory is that you can find love within 100 people if you confess in order of your preferences
I see
Which place am I?
-No, it's so low...
It's too low
But really...
-What about Shogo?
2nd place
Not good
I just shouted
Don't get both members of a duo involved!
Really, don't do both
You should just choose one, right?
It can't be helped
You just happen to be a duo
-Don't go for both
Just like the two people themselves form a combo
It can't be helped
Indeed
That's the reason. I understand
So many comedians
Why are you angry?
This is what it looks like
I'm really sorry about this
I am the type of person who considers male comedians as the opposite sex
After that, she continues to confess to the "other sex" of comedians
How many more people does she like?
I also have strong intentions
I also want to go out with a model or an idol
Good point
If you become popular you have a chance, right?
Is it okay to say the opposite?
Men not replying in kind did not appear
Nothing you can do about that
On the 2nd day she confessed to 14 people
Too much
Total 33 consecutive losses
Anyone else you like?
There are
Still?
Still...
-Sorry
So, we entered the third day of Pon Loop Ami's confessions
Go for it!
First on this day is
I hope you can go out with me
Takashi's fine, right?
With Ami?
Takashi is okay, right?
With me
Doesn't get it
Me?
With Takashi, yes
No, no
You don't like me, do you?
Eh? I do!
Didn't you say "Disco is good"?
Didn't you say, "Disco is best of comedians"?
As expected
Everyone knows it
Did I say that?
Don't you always wear a T-shirt that says Disco?
Really likes him!
Next, in 35th place is a junior comedian Isayama
A very innocent look
He awakens a maternal feeling in me
Really very cute
I like you as a member of the opposite sex
Eh? Ok
Cute, so cute!
Wow, i'm surprised
Is there a chance?
But, um...
What does "um" mean?
No, this is not the place to laugh
Not the place to laugh
What's wrong? What's wrong?
What's going on here?
I am very sorry
No way!
I am very happy
It's best not to laugh when you reject someone
If this is still the case
-Sorry
Why's she being like this again
Afterward, she confesses to two monk-looking men
Impressive two
Welcoming the 39th
Really?
A comedian again
Kakaroni's Kuritani
Never heard of him
That... Kuritani has never had a girlfriend either
I don't think he's very good with women
This type might be good
I have not had a boyfriend either
So this common ground feels quite appropriate
Two inexperienced people seems like a good idea
Indeed
I feel that you are very self-restrained
And have a serious outlook in terms of comedy
The advice you give is very helpful
Makes me think I should listen to you
And made me notice a lot of things
Like, I took the liberty of going to the shrine where Kuritani often goes
Yes yes yes
I'm on my own
And i've gotten somewhere
If I could become like Kuritani
I think it would be good and interesting
Also, as a man, I like Kuritani
So, will you go out with me?
Oh...oh oh
Hm...
How to...
Thinking
Thank you so much for saying that!
Thanks
I have never been confessed to
First time!
Although there is no right to refuse
-Rights?
Currently
All I can say is sorry
I am very sorry
I'm really, really sorry. I'm so bad. I'm sorry...I'm really sorry.
-No, no, no. I'm sorry, too
It's the first time, right?
Although it is the 39th person
Sorry for suddenly saying such a thing
Ah, I'm sorry. I'm really sorry
I'm really...sorry.
-No, no, no
Super nice guy
Wow, I'm really sorry.
-You don't have to say that
It's someone else's first time, sorry...I'm really sorry
Are you crying?
No, not crying
What kind of scene is this?
Because I understand the weight of the first time
Sorry
Good boy
Confessions are such a courageous thing to do
He himself is touched, seeing Ami take such a huge step
And so, Kuritani sheds tears
But
This is the Wednesday Downtown
The theory involves whether its possible to get a relationship by confessing to 100 people in the order of preference
You're gonna say it?
Don't tell him the truth, right?
How many?
-39th
That's a lot of people
39 ah
I'm crying. I was 39th
I'm sorry because it's the first time I've been confessed to
Seriously
39…
Crying
Because Ami often asks me to go out
I also felt there was something going on
I thought you might like me
But that's not true at all
Really, please don't do that
Don't cry
What the hell is going on here?
I thought I could get on
Why're you saying it like that
"Get on"...
Weird way to say it
It's true that the phrase "get on" is not great
This kid's an idiot, right?
I feel that Kuritani is really a good person
He thought very seriously
Really did
I feel a little bit uncomfortable...
But what next?
Can I continue?
Seriously!?
Still going
To continue
Her spirit is too strong
So, with more people she likes
The confessions move into the 4th day
Day 4
Incredible
From now on
I just want to get along as seniors and juniors
Keep up the good relationship
But
In fact the next will be the last person
If it doesn't work, i'll give up
The number of men she has confessed to so far is 70
But not even Ami has 100 people she likes
To be expected
The number of people I know
Of course there are many more
It's not great for the person to know the number
Indeed
Although there have been many
Objectively, this situation has been formed
So far
All are carefully chosen
In terms of people I really like
You only want to confess to those you'd actually date
According to this standard, there are 71 people
So, the last one is
The 71st is a former member of her agency
Shinichi
If you can, I hope you can go out with me
"Wait"
"No, it's definitely not me."
"It's not me"
"No...no no"
"No. Ami should be very popular, right?"
Popular? What are you talking about?
"No, no, no"
Angry
How can I be popular?
- "There are others..."
There's no one else
This is no longer the attitude of confession
And thus ends the testing of the theory
Is that a confession?
Ending with anger
But
The results
In terms of same-day relationships
No one could do it
But with Juicemans' Yojiro
Oh yeah
Can I talk to him on the phone again?
Back to 3 days ago
The 19th confession, Yojiro
Dating
Dating is perfectly fine
Eh, really?
It is possible to go on a date together
Because he said so
He is contacted
Like this...
Well, I still think
Only Yojiro...
"How dare you say that now"
So true
In terms of a relationship
Confessed to 71
There is no one else to like
Can you, that, dating...
Can you go on a date with me?
"If you really feel like you like me"
Yes yes yes I do
"If you really want to go out"
"With this in mind"
Yes yes yes
"If you really think so, we can."
It's true, it's true, it's true.
Thank you very much
So irritating
I did it
Why are you so irritated?
Got on!
So, Ami's challenge is extended
Will this work out?
Good
I'm tired already
So Ami confessed to 71 men she likes
But she wasn't successful
But she was serious
She really wanted to get a boyfriend on the same day
But there was no way to do it that day
What's this?
-Impactful words
Same-day boyfriend
She wanted it on the same-day, but couldn't
So, with Juicemans' Yojiro, and the promise of going on a date
Things were getting heated
Ami did start to get angrier and angrier
Gradually more and more angry
It became a bit like trying to emotionally pressure people to borrow money
There are situations where she was surely angry
So, now, Ami
Is going on a date with Yojiro
By the time this episode airs
It'll be clear whether they are in a relationship or not
So the results will be stated in the broadcast
Which ranking was Yojiro?
Yojiro is the 19th.
-19th place
Not bad, not bad
It's okay.
-It's okay
So a week after the confession
Ami and Yojiro travel to the zoo for their first date
Then
After that, they met a few times
What the hell is going on here?
I'm scared
One month from the start of the confessions
Finally it's time to confess again
We've had frequent contact, we've met frequently
More than before, I like you more now...
I think I really like you
Although its nothing new
If you can, can you go out with me?
Please
Well, well, well, that...
Ami who wants her first boyfriend
And Yojiro who had a girlfriend once 6 years ago
The answer given is...
At the beginning of the confession, the first time, to be honest it was a little...
I felt a lot of pressure
Did I apply pressure?
Yes, unsurmountable pressure
But in terms of dating, it felt good
You seemed to be really happy
And i've been very happy being with you
I've felt really happy
Its made me happy
So that's why...
I think, if we were to be together, I think we'd both be very happy
So, I'd also like to ask you to be with me
-Eh?
Eh eh eh eh?
Eh eh eh eh, what!?
Does that mean I've become Yojiro's girlfriend?
Yeah that's the case
※The BGM is Disco's song... yeah
Awesome!
Please take care of me
Too awesome!
I hope you'll delete Disco-san's contact information immediately
I will talk to Disco
Ami is mine
We're doing a joint performance together, so we'll have to meet
If I meet him, I'll definitely beat him up
Please don't
Congratulations!
Thank you very much
I really though it was hopeless
It really didn't seem like it was going to work out
I was rejected by 71 people!
I never thought this would be the result
What kind of date do you want in the future?
Hmm, how to put it
Go once to... go to Disneyland once
I'm gonna go book it now
Next is everybody's theories
Tonight's presenter is
It's Tamura Kenji!
Isn't that Tam Ken?
I'm Tam Ken, thank you for waiting
So guys, let me ask you a question about curry
If you hate curry, please raise your hand and explain why
I don't think I hate it
No one, right?
So this time, I bring you the second part of a certain curry theory
This is it
The 2nd - If the smell of curry wafts in from the next room during a meeting, you'll surely go eat curry afterward
Ah yeah this was done before
That's it
The plan is to keep sending the aroma of curry to the next room during a meeting
And then fellow the target on the street to see if they eat curry or not
What is this?
This did happen
Five out of six people ate it!
Yeah
-It was pretty impressive
Only Noda Crystal did not eat
Because he hates curry
It can't be helped.
-It can't be helped. After all, people who hate curry will definitely not eat it
Basically, we can say that the theory has been proven, right?
But... those people last time
They're all simple-minded guys, right?
It varies from person to person, right?
As soon as they smell the curry, they wanted to eat it
So, the next step is to re-examine curry in a new format
The 2nd - If the smell of curry wafts in from the next room during a meeting, you'll surely go eat curry afterward
This time, we called our targets to the Green Mountain Studio under the pretext of a fake location for a TV show promotion
In the middle of the discussion, they will smell curry coming from the next room
Then they'll choose their lunch from three possible menus
Curry
Omelet
Ramen
Incidentally, in front of the curry cart, we set up a trap
What a mess
-Why?
Although perhaps a bit unreasonable for people attracted by the smell
We'll let them fall regardless
Why?
Really unreasonable
So first of all, the first target is
Good morning
I'm Plus Minus' Iwahashi, thank you
Plus Minus' Iwahashi
And
This is a "medical examination for comedians" program
The meeting to discuss a program begins
Sorry
Appeared
-His ticks
Scary
Twice
Sorry
It's fine. It's totally fine
It's totally fine
After he unleashes his ticks as usual
It happens
Is it common?
The curry battle begins
Do you use your eyes a lot?
Very often
I often watch Youtube and Neftlix
Then
Took off the mask to smell it
Seems like there's a strong smell of curry
He's quick to respond to the scent
This is curry, right?
Hey? Very strong curry smell...
I have a bit of nasal congestion so I can't really smell it
Really?
It's really strong
This imprinted the aroma of curry in his mind
Weird
Then, the opening of the fake show is shot
Hello everyone, i'm Plus Minus' Iwahashi
My interest is to go to hotels for breakfast without staying overnight
Okay, OK, thanks
This will be fine for the opening
-Thank you
It just so happens that the TV series team is not here yet
So you can here for a while
-Oh, really?
Are you waiting for the actors?
-Yes
Ah yes, I understand
This time we prepared three food trucks
And gave them a voucher and to choose one of three
Can I go?
-Yes
Ok
What will happen?
Which one will he eat?
What is this way of walking?
He's heading...
Eat curry? Eat curry?
Will you go for curry?
Is it curry?
Going to the right, he's not eating it?
It's curry, right?
Attempted to eat curry
Why does this have to happen to him?
So the truth was revealed
Carried away by the aroma of curry
What the hell?
Oi what's this?
Hey, what's going on?
What is going on?
Hey, I don't get it, why this hole?
Iwahashi, what were you going to eat?
Curry
Why do you want to eat curry?
Because the smell of curry was very strong
During the meeting
So you want to eat curry?
Well... that...
If the aroma is so strong you will definitely crave curry, right?
Hey, wait, hey, what, hey?
What is this? What is this?
So, the project is explained
What is this?
I like curry
If I smell curry of course i'll eat it!
This prank is way too simple, right?
Iwabashi, by the way, you have to go somewhere else now
Go elsewhere?
Unfortunately you have no time for curry
Oi!
At least let me eat the curry!
I can almost taste the curry
Iwahashi already looks like he has curry on his mouth
It's dirt!
So this is the end
Loads of dirt
The next target is
Who is this?
Here we go again
The 2nd appearance, Viking's Nishimura
Is that the smell of curry?
Last time, he went to eat curry after the meeting
Will he fall for the same trick this time?
Then
Do you smell it?
Vague smell of curry
I think it's probably curry
Despite being relatively minor, it still made an impression on him
So, the same as before, an opening scene is shot
Then it's time for lunch break
Will the same thing from two years ago happen again?
Which one will you eat?
What will happen?
Ramen is also available!
Ramen is an attractive choice
Looking at the signs
A little hesitant
Yeah
Still going for curry?
Surely eating curry!
Hello-
Also said hello
The truth is revealed
Hey what's going on here?
Nishimura, this is the second time
Ah, did he forget?
Do you remember? Don't remember?
The trap? If you fall into a trap...
No, it's not about the trap, the curry
Curry?
Ah!
Ahh..
The one in Akasaka.
-Yes
Now I think of it...
Didn't you have a curry then?
I did!
He forgot
That time also had the fragrance of curry!
What a strange way to talk!
Like a moron talking
-Like a moron
This is the second time
This way of speaking
Whoa
Curry is so awesome!
Emotions are so high!
So...
You could use this to commit a crime
What kind of crime?
What if this causes a crime?
What is he talking about?
The next target is
I'm Tom Brown's Michio
Tom Brown's Michio
Without further ado, we immediately feed in the curry aroma
Looks so delicious this curry
During the meeting for the fake health program
Ah, I like curry rice
Like curry?
Yes
Katsu curry and stuff like that
Whether its the smell that influences the conversation or not, the topic naturally turns to curry
I also make my own curry at home
But
How many times a week do you eat curry?
How many times...?
Haven't eaten in a long time?
No...I feel like I can't remember
But in any case, I often eat it
I also often go to Coco and also make my own
The curry is pouring in
But i feel that maybe I don't eat it that much
Eh? How much is it?
Eh... do I eat it?
Scary scary scary
With the smell of curry filling the whole room, is he becoming dizzy?
Michio's words seem to be muddled
Sorry
I feel that, in terms of food... I suddenly can't remember anything
Next
Hello, I'm Tom-Brown' Michio, the presenter of the TBS Spring Drama Festival
The curry sauce is sucked in through the nose
As expected of someone who has inhaled curry
His opening joke is curry-related
Okay, OK. Thank you very much
He got carried away
With this opening
Unconsciously in front of the camera...
The word "curry" came out of his mouth
His brain is already full of curry
So surely he will choose the curry?
It's curry
The truth is revealed
Eh? This is... eh?
I don't understand... why did I fall into a trap?
Why do you want to eat curry?
There was a meeting before this
There was a very strong curry smell
During the meeting?
Yes
If you smell curry, you will definitely wanna eat it
Eh, then why...
What does the trap have to do with this?
Falling is funny
What the hell are you laughing at?
The next target is
I'm Jimmy
All strange people!
Jimmy Onishi
Why ask this guy to be the host of a TV drama festival?
So true
That's weird. That's weird
Surely he'll think its strange
I smell curry
And he has a good nose
Smell the smell of curry rice
Ah, you mean here?
Ah no, the cafe is also quite close, I can't tell the difference
So, the same approach is used to verify again
The café is also quite close...
What'd he say for the opening?
What'll happen?
It got cut out
It must have been awful
I guess so
Walk straight through!
Excuse me
And said "excuse me"
As expected: curry
I'm sure I'd choose curry if I smelled it
So far, the curry battle has gone perfectly
What's up with that smile!?
The last target is...
I am Shoji, thank you
A muscular comedian who considers curry as an enemy to maintain his body shape, Shoji Tomoharu
If the other person next to me makes a little, if you bring curry, I'll also do it
You mean you won't eat it?
I don't really get what you're talking about
A little harsh
Curry Battle, the final target is
I am Shoji, thank you
Shoji Tomoharu
Here he is also asked some questions about diet and lifestyle
I eat basmati rice and stuff
I'm careful not to consume carbohydrates when I eat
I am also very careful to control what I eat at night
Shoji is quite serious about it
Sure enough, he's limiting his carbohydrate intake to stay in shape
That's not the same
Curry and the like is a no-go
So, we've added chicken just for him
This time there's chicken too
Chicken
Curry
Omelet Rice
Ramen
I see
It'd be great if he still chooses curry
A high level of difficulty, will Shoji choose the king of carbs?
Indeed
If so, the theory will be completely proven
Completely and perfectly confirmed
I don't think he'll eat ramen either
What'll happen?
Ah, chicken!
Going to the chicken side
Is it chicken?
Is it?
Still chose curry!
He chose curry, what about carbohydrates?
A perfect score
What for? Why the hole? What's going on here?
What the hell is this for? What the hell is going on?
This is Wednesday Downtown
Yeah
So, we explained the project to him
Because you are more concerned about carbohydrate intake
Ah-
We also prepared chicken
Other muscle comedians are gonna criticize me
You usually pay attention to sugar, right?
Yes
But I'll usually eat curry
I see
In summary
Curry is pretty much a drug
So, the theory was completely confirmed
This is really impressive
Then there will be no more complaints, right?
That's true
The participants all seemed to have something to say about it
These people are too unique, right?
They are all simple people
Aren't they the ones who will go for curry even without the smell?
No, it's not because of the aroma
To get up from a hole and go to eat curry is really impressive
It's a good thing, right?
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03