★Subbed by fmck fansubs★
reddit.com/u/fmckfansubs
patreon.com/fmck
We're doing something different today.
Why are you so tired?
Well, you know, I don't know
what's happening on today's show
We've been watching those
Obon Kobon guys until recently
Obon Kobon
I'm so tired
It's like I've been made to do
40 laps around the track
Because it was two weeks long
Really, that was...
Well, yeah, but it ended well
traumatic, wasn't it?
My emotions are still
running high
Well, this is something
completely different
Well then, she we call them out?
Who is it?
Presenter, come in!
It's Viking's Kotōge!
Kotōge?
Hello!
No no, definitely at this point...
Obon Kobon are going to come out
No they won't!
That's impossible
They definitely won't come
out now. Definitely
We've given up on you
I didn't expect to be rejected
Really? Well, Kotōge...
Thank you
welcome to today's show.
What have you got for us?
Today it's the 3rd installment
of something we haven't
done for a year and a half
And here it is:
Panelist's Theories
Investigation Special
I'm sure you already
remember what this is
Yes, yes, yes.
It's when people here are talking
They talk a bit at the start
But we don't use that much do we?
When we record this show, during the opening,
this is what the panelists are doing:
Every time at the start of recording, the panelists tell us their own theories but this is cut from the show
We ask them theories
they'd like investigated
But we don't air it at all
Why not?
Why not? I think it's strange
Sometimes it's funnier than the rest of the show
Sometimes
I put so much effort into it
sometimes too
Once again we've ammassed a collection
of theories presented during the opening talk
So tonight we will introduce and investigate some of these theories
Panelist's Theories
Investigation Special
First, Nonomura Yukiko's theory
I, um, love movies and
After a movie has finished, you know the end credits?
It seems like..
If you leave the cinema in the middle of them, you're not a movie lover
Doesn't it?
That's the impression
But sometimes,
if they're really long→
and in English, it feels like all I'm doing is just searching for Japanese names.
Ah, yes.
So if there's a personality who's
professed to be a movie lover,
If the end credits are as long as the actual movie, they will leave before they're over.
(Nonomura) Don't you think?
I want to try it
Theory: If the end credits are the same length as the rest of the movie, even a movie lover will leave in the middle of them
As long as the movie?
I want to try it. I want to.
That'd be quite hard
It'd be fine if we looped it.
I want to try it
Next is JOY's theory
You know those otakus who support an idol?
They really hate when the idol they like has a relationship with a guy or a male acquaintance, don't they?
They'll get angry, won't they?
But I think if an otaku could get involved with their own idol, they'd do it without thinking.
Theory: Even an otaku who hates their idol associating with men wouldn't mind if it were them
Ah, yes
That's true
They'll get so angry won't they?
To someone else
Well yes to someone else
But if it were them,
they'd do it straightaway
You've told us something extremely obvious
Huh? Really?
I'm kind of surprised
Wait a second, Matsumoto-san
Is this your first appearance?
Next is a theory from Kirin's Kawashima
Someone who's angry
can get away with using words that don't exist.
Ah
Theory: Someone who's angry can get away with using words that don't exist.
Like when someone's being lectured
and apologizing like this,
if ithe person lecturing them is being pretenious and says something like...
"You don't have enough pollination"
They'd probably just say "Yes. I'm sorry"
Even if they don't know the word
Like a loanword from English
An English word?
If someone says to them a word like that,
they definitely won't say
"What does that mean?"
If someone told them jibberish like "dobengasongeka" they'd just think it's a regional word
They'd probably think you meant "We have to do something" ("Dogyankasentoikan")
Next a theory from Masuda Okada's Okada
My theory is one that I can think
all men will understand.
Everyone here has been to many tourist spots both for work and privately
And according to my data often these will be...
Shrines and temples
And the toilets they have there,
when you're peeing in the men's room
you can almost be seen from outside.
Theory: When peeing in the men's room at temples and shrines you cam almost be seen from outside
It's like "Can't they see me?"
What do you mean?
It's true. There are just
some dead plants there
It's like "From this angle, if a bus arrives now,
"everyone getting off will see me."
Ah, so it's surprising how people aren't more defensive
Ah, yes.
Yes, that's the theory
Next, Horan Chiaki's theory
Sometimes, on this show, you broadcast a collection of theories that panelists have introduced during the openings, right?
So I have one that I've always wanted to tell you
and I think it could be investigated too.
If you replaced the caramel part of a custard pudding with cough syrup, no one would notice.
(Horan) Yes →
Because it's kind of sweet, right?
Theory: If the caramel in a custard pudding were replaced with cough syrup, no one would notice.
That sweet,
kind of bitter taste
Doesn't caramel-flavored
cough syrup taste the same?
I love it.
I don't really know anything about cough syrup
What?
"It's kind of sweet"?
It's gross that you know that, Hamada
Why? It's sweet, isn't it?
Because I've drunk it
But why do you know that?
When?! Why would you be drinking
cough syrup at your age?
It's because he's that age that he's drunk it
Everyone's had it
Really?
Next, Miyagawa Daisuke's theory
I've been
thinking a bit
You know André the Giant?
André the Giant
His hair, during his prime--
Well, no one here knows him
A pro wrestler
He was a huge person
At that time,
in his heyday, his hairstyle
If the amount of hair on his head
were yakisoba,
What the hell?
it'd be about 14 portions.
Theory: If the hair on André the Giant's head during his heyday were yakisoba, it could feed 14 people
What are you talking about?
What kind of theory is that?
I was thinking it's about that much
You've thought that?
I have, yes. I'm sorry
What are you thinking here?
Theory: Even an otaku who
hates their idol associating
with men wouldn't mind if it
were them
Theory: If the caramel in a
custard pudding were replaced
with cough syrup, no one
would notice.
Theory: If the end credits are
the same length as the rest of
the movie, even a movie lover
will leave in the middle of them
Theory: If the hair on André
the Giant's head during his
heyday were yakisoba, it could
feed 14 people
Theory: Someone who's
angry can get away with using
words that don't exist.
Theory: When peeing in the
men's room at temples and
shrines you cam almost be
seen from outside
Out of these theories...
the one we will investigate is...
this one.
Theory: Someone who's angry can get away with using words that don't exist.
And so,
(Staff) Good morning
Good morning
Our challenger will be Saraba Seishun no Hikari's Morita.
I think that he will think they're just words he doesn't know
And our target is...
Invited to appear on a fake show in which comedians have revealing talks about senpais they're close to,
it's Pumpkin Potato Fry's Tani.
What kind of..
Do you have something to talk about? Like, what topic?
What should we do?
I'll probably be talking about you Morita-san, right?
So... well...
Hmmm
You've been on TV how many times?
This will be my 10th
Yes
Your 10th?
So at this point, you should be getting results
Yes, that's right
Right?
and that means...
So to put it simply
You need actually do some preparation in advance
Yes…
You came in today saying "What should we talk about?"
Honestly, I just think that's ridiculous.
Ah, I'm sorry.
Using his approach to work as
an entry point,
Lecture Mode is turned on.
Then, without delay...
So, today, when I called you here,
that means you've been licked, doesn't it?
Ah, it does. Yes.
And when you've been licked, then
at the very least you need to have thought about
what you're going to talk about.
I see... I'm sorry.
First he hits him with a quick jab,
in the form of a short word...
That means you've been licked, doesn't it?
Ah, it does. Yes.
It's completely ignored.
Then...
It's not like I'm ordering you to get excited here but
I call you because I want you to get excited.
I see. Thank you very much.
If you turn up, but →
it all comes to nothing,
the attitude you've brought with you...
It's probably sogo's profit.
I want you to try your best
Yes
It wastes my time too if I appear with you like this
Is wasting my time something you enjoy doing?
No. That's not ... really
Right? No, if we appear with this, it'll just be...
Jizō's grave, right?
a\And if that happens, what then?
There's no point in doing it
No no, It's like I'm also wasting my time here
That's right
It's probably sogo's profit.
It'll be Jizō's grave, right?
Two unfamiliar idioms in a row also get ignored
After that...
I'm really wondering what you do when you're with other comedians senior to you
I keep telling you this
It's probably Tengen theory but...
It wouldn't hurt to try, right?
In the end...
You just think I'm nothing but a sparse youth
That's how I see it
Yeah
Something like that, when it happens, I won't think
with the Breck Effect, "ah this guy is good", will I?
It's all →
Murasame Koji and that's not alright
This is too much
This one is too much
You're overdoing it!
(Morita) Honestly, yeah.
Yes...
Huh, what? Got something to say?
No...
I think it's as you say
And asking "How many jokes do you write a week?" or thinking "Just writing one is enough" just won't do
You think you're going to M-1. You want to, don't you?
That's right. Of course, yes
Because it's like doing manzai on the Tengu stage
A young person like you
needs to do it right
I like this kind of thing
And the other day you competed in the Kansai competition but didn't get anything right?
That's right.
That's right. It wasn't good.
So you got nothing, didn't you?
Correct
So it ended super flat
(Morita) If you do it, do it right
I see...
It'll always be like that
You'll end up as just a scoop saint
People who keep doing that don't get treated well
No... that's right
Right?
If you don't do it right...
it's going to be over for you, as a scoop saint
Wh- What...
It'll be over?
Yeah
If I keep messing up, it'll be over for me?
Well, if you don't have the skills...
Right. I understand.
Don't you think?
I think so, yes
"Scoop saint"
In reaction to this word,
it seemed as though Tani was going to
ask for an explanation for the first time.
It'll be over?
Yeah
It's going to be over for me ...
And then...
I guess you don't know
what to do
Of course I do
No, you don't. Seriously
I think I just don't have a stung face
("have a stung face" = to feel uneasy)
Huh, what does "stung face" mean?
You're the one saying things people don't know
Now he's doing it
What you said ... stung
I know what that means. Did it sting or not?
It didn't, did it?
No, it did
The gyōtan is not good enough,
so I don't think so.
"Gyōtan"?
The gyōtan's not good enough, is it?
"Gyōtan"...
No, the words stung, but my face is probably...
No. If they had, I'd feel it. That's what I'm saying, OK?
I'm sorry, you're right
Safe
People who make it in this world, definitely have something, right?
They hold on to that something and succeed
All of them
They all have some →
King Venus On, so they-
Is that like a weapon?
Is it a weapon or something?
Seriously
That's...
Hold on. Sorry. This is unrelated but...
Wh- what is...
What?
There was a long word I don't know
And so, because he clearly asked for
an explanation...
we end it here.
Prank Reveal
(Tani) Is that a weapon?
(Staff) Thanks for your help
I knew it...
(Staff) Good work
Ah, it has to be...
(Staff) That went well
I think so, yes
Wh... What was it?
The wrong words?
I thought I just didn't know them...
So you're not really angry?
I'm not worried about the words
The words were all I cared about
(Tani) Really?
You're not angry?
Seriously,
I was thinking this guy is so full of himself, maybe he's made his own company
Because he can't get along with others
Next is a theory from Knights' Hanawa.
'For the last 20 years, Naitō Takashi
has played only detectives' is my theory
Theory: For the last 20 years, Naitō Takashi has only been doing detective roles
I'm currently co-starring with him as one too
Slander…
I've only seen him playing a detective
Oh really?
Always, without any interruptions?
for 20 years.
He's done almost nothing else
For the last 20 years, really.
He's said it himself
"I only play a detective."
So because of that,
I was thinking I'd like for it
to be properly verified.
I see
His shoes are probably as worn down as much as a real detective's
Even if he commits a little crime, he won't get caught
Next, a theory from Ogi Yahagi's Yahagi
I'm not really picky when it comes to food
so if it's some stirred-fried vegetables,
if there's something weird inside,
someone like me would still eat it
What do you mean?
Don't you look at it a bit?
Theory: People who aren't picky eaters will eat something weird if it's in a vegetable stir-fry
I'll just eat it without checking
Unlike a picky eater
Someone who
hates onions will check
Or bell peppers for example
I don't need to check,
so I'd probably eat anything
What if there's some excrement in there?
Excrement?
Well... probably
Why?!
Next, Ahn Mika's theory
You know, if all toilets in the world now
were made to have swinging saloon doors
everyone would definitely use them.
Theory: If all toilets in the world had saloon doors everyone would definitely use them
Sorry but could we stop with the toilet talk?
That give me a shock
Talking about toilets is still banned
You just spoke without thinking
I'm surprised
I think if you think about it, it makes sense
So it would be like this?
Yes, yes, yes!
For many reasons
Because it'deters you, right?
Yes, it puts me off using them
I'm a person who hates
touching doorknobs
Are you teasing me?
(JOY) You're too sensitive
No, I'm not!
Next, a theory from Untouchable's Yamazaki
My theory is that the general public
think that all comedians
work for Yoshimoto
Theory: The general public think all comedians work for Yoshimoto
That can't be true!
They don't!
I don't want to
dig up the past but
there was a big fuss 2 years ago, wasn't there?
Ah the so-called Yoshimoto scandal, yes
At that time, when I was shooting in public
people started telling me
"It must be hard but keep it up!"
And for me it was a hassle
to keep saying "no, you're wrong"
because it had nothing to do with me.
So I'd just say "I'll do my best!"
I wasn't telling them I'd do anything about it
So anyone in the comedy industry --
I work at a place called Jinrikisha
We may work for
Jinrikisha or Sun Music
but the general public will
just think we all work for Yoshimoto.
Next, Hotta Akane's theory
If you go to somewhere like
a big hardware store or airport,
the car park will have sections from A to Z won't it?
So if you park somewhere like section L...
when you say it alphabetically
Can you say it normally?
Huh?
What do you mean?
If I don't sing in my head...
If you don't start from A...
Are you able to say it?
Theory: You can't say the alphabet without singing the ABCD song
Well, I kind of get it
If I don't sing
A-B-C-D
If I don't say it, that melody
is definitely playing in my head.
At the Disneyland car park,
they have the Goofy section
I don't know where Goofy is
Are you visiting Disneyland?
There are times when I go there.
Why wouldn't there be?
And when did this occur?
What's with the sudden ambush?
No, when was this?
I was under the impression→
that you hadn't been there
when you were growing up.
So this Goofy story,
when did it happen?
I am
Is anyone interested in this?
In my being interrogated by Hamada on whether I go to Disneyland or not?
We are interested
We are. We are.
I'm extremely interested
I'm interested. What's wrong with that?
I'm just asking you
when this happened.
This is too much trouble. Can we do it tomorrow?
What is this?!
Actually I'm going tomorrow too
No! You're definitely not
Next, Nishno Miki's theory
The first boyfriend a girl gets after graduating from AKB is almost always a bad one.
Theory: The first boyfriend after graduating from AKB48 is almost always a bad one
I can tell you. It's not a good story but
in my experience,
I got stuck with two bad guys in a row
No, it's too gross
What kind of bad guy?
Isn't it just you?
No, it's really nasty
(Fujimoto) It's just you, isn't it?
But it's not only AKB...
Idols can't date →
It's idols
so their expectations are too high.
They fall for a guy who looks good
Were you tricked?
and get tricked.
Yes...
How were you tricked?
It's so gross
(Fujimoto) Tell us!
Was it money?
No, a woman.
When I looked at his phone,
I saw him ******* with another woman 3 days prior
That's enough! Quiet, you!
Out of these theories,
Theory: For the last 20 years,
Naitō Takashi has only been
doing detective roles
Theory: If all toilets in the world
had saloon doors everyone
would definitely use them
Theory: People who
aren't picky eaters will eat
something weird if it's in a
vegetable stir-fry
Theory: The first boyfriend
after graduating from AKB48
is almost always a bad one
Theory: The general public
think all comedians work for
Yoshimoto
Theory: You can't say the
alphabet without singing
the ABCD song
the one we will actually investigate is...
Theory: For the last 20 years,
Naitō Takashi has only been
doing detective roles
Theory: If all toilets in the world
had saloon doors everyone
would definitely use them
Theory: People who
aren't picky eaters will eat
something weird if it's in a
vegetable stir-fry
Theory: The first boyfriend
after graduating from AKB48
is almost always a bad one
Theory: The general public
think all comedians work for
Yoshimoto
Theory: You can't say the
alphabet without singing
the ABCD song
Out of these theories,
the one will investigate is
this one:
Theory: For the last 20 years,
Naitō Takashi has been
doing only detective roles
And so without delay we will start going back from 2021,
investigating all dramas he has appeared in.
First, this work, which aired
this year from April to June.
Tokyo MPD, Chief of Investigation 5
What?
Murdered because the cake was too different from its photo?
What's this?
I'm curious
Regardless of what the murder motive was, it's a detective role
Continuing, in this work too..
MPD Violent Crime - Higuchi Akira
Kikuchi, the cuffs!
Here
Detective role
Full-body Detective
And in this one too
Out of the stalkers I arrested three years ago...
Detective role
Estimated time of death
Inspector Totsugawa Series 8
(The woman who disappeared on the Sotobō Line)
Detective role
Inspector Totsugawa Series 8
(The woman who disappeared on the Sotobō Line)
Kyoto Taxi Driver Case File
Tokyo MPD, Chief of Investigation
(Special)
Forensic Woman
(New Year Special)
Recurrence
(MPD Violent Crime - Higuchi Akira)
Inspector Totsugawa Series 7
(The Lake Hamana Murder Route)
Forensic Woman
(Special)
Inspector Totsugawa Series 6
(Nikkō - Love and Betrayal at Kinugawa River)
Tokyo MPD, Chief of Investigation
(New Year Special)
(Special)
Tokyo MPD, Chief of Investigation
Holy Ground
(MPD Violent Crime - Higuchi Akia)
Tokyo MPD, Chief of Investigation
(Special II)
(Special I)
Unsolved Woman
Tokyo MPD, Chief of Investigation
(Special)
Forensic Woman
Tokyo MPD, Chief of Investigation 5
MPD Violent Crime - Higuchi Akira
Will-O'-the-Wisp
(MPD Violent Crime - Higuchi Akira)
\Memory Search 2
Forensic Woman
Binding Spell
(MPD Violent Crime - Higuchi Akira)
Unsolved Woman
Tokyo MPD, Chief of Investigation 2020
Full-body Detective
Going back 4 years...
2021 to 2018
A total of 104 works. All detective roles
all dramas he appeared in up to
autumn 2018...
But in this drama
aired in August 2018,
Funakoshi Eiichiro Murder Case
I told Ayano-san→
Wh- why?
to bring you here.
What are you doing?!
As usual, another detective role
Or so we thought...
Performing the duties of MC in a talk show
Naitō Takashi appears as himself
But because playing oneself
is an irregular situation,
we decide this doesn't count
and continue our search.
Naitō-san
What?!
Forensic Woman (Special)
Special Crime Division - Hanashima Wataru 2
Inspector Totsugawa Series 3
Then in 2017...
we finally discover a non-detective role.
And it is...
Firstly, we only managed to collect a tiny amount of blood from the area where the body was found
Public Prosecutor
However, even though this isn't a detective role,
it deals with catching criminals and is extremely close.
Thus, for the time being we continue our investigation.
Tokyo MPD, Chief of Investigation 2
New Inspector Totsugawa Series 2 (The Ikaho Onsen Murder Case)
Special Crime Division - Hanashima Wataru
New Inspector Totsugawa Series 1 (The Izu-Shimoda murder route)
Forensic Woman (New Year Special)
Conflagration
(MPD Violent Crime - Higuchi Akira)
Public Prosecutor Asahi Nayōko 18
Forensic Woman
Uniformed Investigation 3
Surgeon Hatomura Shūgorō 4
Forensic Woman (Spring special)
Tokyo MPD, Chief of Investigation
Public Prosecutor Asahi Nayōko 17
Uniformed Investigation 3
After that...
aside from occasionally
playing a public prosecutor,
Naitō plays a detective repeatedly.
Tokyo MPD, Chief of Investigation
Forensic Woman
Beat (MPD Violent Crime - Higuchi Akira)
Then, in 2015,
we at last find a role that has nothing to with a detective.
Naitō Takashi not playing a detective
And it's this:
Mito Kōmon (Special)
In Mito Kōmon,
Naito was the second
actor to play Kazaguruma
no Yashichi
And with that,
Theory disproved
By the way, in movies,
Naito regularly plays
non-detective characters
such as this main role.
Naito Takashi's drama detective proportion from 2015 to 2021
Period drama: 2 roles
Himself: 1 role
In the last 7
years,
Detective: 205 roles
Public prosecutor: 3 roles
out of the dramas
he starred in
an astounding 97.16%
were detective roles.
Isn't it?
That's really amazing
But Kazaguruma no Yashichi,
in the modern version...
He kind of is one, yes
He fights evil
He really only plays good people
That's the impression I have
Amazing
Definitely
Great
That wasn't bad
No, it wasn't. Also,
what did you think of Morita?
Ah, I think it was good but
the bit at the end...
So many words came out,
I can't really remember much of it
Definitely
Not really, no
Base something...
He said something about a base
I only remember bits and pieces
Next, Tsuchida Teruyuki's theory
Often in the comedy industry, a senpai will say
"Live somewhere where you can barely afford rent"
They say "if you push yourself,
you'll definitely get work" don't they?
So the kōhai will listen
and do what the senpai says but
my theory is that of the ones
who do that, a majority fail anyway.
Theory: The majority of the comedians told by their senpai to live somewhere unaffordable still don't succeed
They just suffer
Well...
Because only those who
succeed are considered?
Yes. At their workplace,
all the senpais will be doing well
If they weren't, you'd
stop seeing them there
So you listen to senpais doing well
But what the unsuccessful senpais say
doesn't really get listened to
Because they don't admire them
So my theory is
If you do what others tell you,
you'll probably regret it.
I see, I see
Next, Kondō Chihiro's theory
My husband's
Ōta  from Jungle Pocket and-
Didn't know that
Really? Hamada-san you've
done a lot to help him
Ah, thank you
He appears so often so
You do?
we do know that
You know that? I'm glad
Well, we have two daughters. And my theory is most comedians' children are daughters.
Ah, surely
Aren't there a lot?
Theory: Most comedians' children are daughters
(Kondō) There's so many, right?
I think it's reality rather than a theory
The comedians my husband knows...
Fujimoto-san has
two daughters,
FUJIWARA
Fujimoto Toshifumi
Nelsons
Wada Manjū
Wada Manjū-san
has a daughter too
Hold on!
You need a bit...
There's quite a gap
between them
Because lots of comedians
are womanizers,
they're more likely to have daughters.
... is what I was about to say, but then you mentioned Wada Manjū and now that theory's iffy too
It doesn't apply to him
You think so?
Next, a theory from Kis-My-Ft2's Nikaidō
It's about Miyata from my group
Kis-My-Ft2
Miyata Toshiya
He really never gets angry
Ah...
No wonder what you do, he won't get angry
No matter how tired he is,
or if plans go wrong
He doesn't get angry at all
So, I'd like to know just how much
he can take until he gets angry
Theory: Kis-My-Ft2's Miyata won't get angry no matter what happens
I want to try
You'd like to make him angry?
So it's like you can do this much
Hamada-san is like that too
He doesn't get angry ever
Right?
No way
Isn't Hamada-san like a T-Fal kettle?
Both heat up instantly
Next, a theory from Harisenbon's Haruka
When I'm riding the bullet train,
I'll be there for a while, so
I take off my shoes to relax
While they're off, if those shoes
got a little bit smaller
I wouldn't notice but rather
think my feet had swelled.
Theory: If the shoes you took off on the shinkansen got a bit smaller you wouldn't notice
If they'd been switched?
Yes, if swapped in secret,
I think they wouldn't notice
What a simple prank
Next, Kazlaser's theory
Lots of famous people
like manga, right?
Yeah
Deciding which manga is the best always causes arguments. But when I debate it,
it's always with people around my age.
So I really have no idea what manga
young people would find interesting
To find out the best one,
I'll have everyone bring the first volume of the manga they think is most interesting
And we'll leave them all in the green room.
Then we'll call a young model
for a plausible-sounding job
and make her wait for ages there.
She'll have nothing to do
so she'll read them
Then she'll do the fake job
and go home.
If on the way home she buys the second volume of your chosen manga, you win
Theory: A manga is really interesting if you buy
the second volume on the way home
How about it?
Well, it depends if they want to read it
It'll be like buying 2 volumes of "Ashita no Joe"
and then going home
Next, Jinnai Tomonori's theory
If Downtown were
newcomers now,
they wouldn't be this successful.
Theory: If Downtown were new comedians right now they wouldn't be so successful
(Jinnai) You wouldn't, right?
We wouldn't be
We would not
You're sure about it?
Of course I am. With a guy like you...
So...
No, no, no. It's nothing to do with me
So if you were young now, Downtown...
Yep, totally impossible
would probably not be possible.
Well, I'd do my best.
But even if I did,
this guy's sexual harrassment
would ruin it all.
(Cookie!) For sure
It's awful how he holds me back
I watched something
from when you were about 24
Hamada-san with sunglasses on
and Matsumoto-san in slip-on shoes
What's wrong with that?
With a long stick like Iwaki Masami
That's totally fine
held in his mouth
Are there any 24-year-old
comedians like that now?
Hey, it's strange
It's weird
No no
Then at the teppanyaki restaurant
The owner had just had a baby so
was like "Macchan, hold my baby!",
but the moment he took it
he pretended he was trying to grill it on the hot plate
You can't talk about that now
A scary joke
We can't even use that as a topic now
Then Hamada-san was
screeching with laughter
The mother was too of course
That was the plan,
to put it on the grill
No way, you can't have done that
Because I was totally against it
In that case...
Theory: A manga is really
interesting if you buy
the second volume
on the way home
Theory: If Downtown were new
comedians right now they
wouldn't be so successful
Theory: If the shoes you took
off on the shinkansen got a
bit smaller you wouldn't notice
Theory: Kis-My-Ft2's Miyata
won't get angry no matter what
happens
Theory: Most comedians'
children are daughters
Theory: The majority of the
comedians told by their
senpai to live somewhere
unaffordable still don't succeed
And so, out of these,
the theory we'll actually investigate is...
Out of these,
this one:
Theory: A manga is really interesting if you buy the second volume on the way home without thinking after reading the first
And so, we will take 3 mangas recommended
by these 3 manga-loving entertainers,
and leave the first volume of each in the green room.
High school student and popular model
Hinata Maru is the target.
Manager
I want plastic surgery
I keep saying that recently
You can't do that
Hinata has no idea at all she's being recorded
Kendō Kobayashi
First, the manga chosen by Kenkoba is...
"Asahinagu"
34 volumes, published from 2011 to 2020 in Big Comic Spirits
As you can see
from the cover,
it's about a high-school girl who's
in the naginata (pole weapon) club
It's a sport manga, which
is quite rare nowadays.
At the start of chapter one,
Even when
weird stuff
like this
happens
What...?
a weird guy on the train
You're cute
so I'll show
you especially,
shows her his crotch. And then,
because It's the first time she's seen one,
she starts hallucinating that an UFO is taking her away.
As for what that has to do with naganata,
it's saying you'll meet all kinds of people.
That's what the first volume's about. I hope you read it
Throughout the whole thing I cried at least 20 times
Rereading it now, the part most likely
to make me cry is that flasher
Next, it's Kamaitachi's Yamauchi, whose chosen work is...
Here it is.
Wayama Yama's
"Onna No Sono no Hoshi "
2 volumes published so far from 2020 to present in monthly magazine "FEEL YOUNG"
It's already been nominated
for pretty much every award.
It's always ranked high.
It's about the daily life of a girls' high school teacher called Hoshi-sensei.
A situation arises where he has to keep a dog in his classroom
*CLICK*
One day, the dog→
has someone draw eyebrows on him.
... drew eyebrows
on Setsuko - I
mean Tapioca,
or is an
accomplice,
He asks "who drew eyebrows on the dog?",
raise
your
hand.
and nearly all the girls were involved.
This much is about the dog being drawn on.
It's not laugh-out-loud funny but
it's the kind of humor that'll really make you chuckle.
And the manga chosen by the theory's proponent, Kazlaser, is...
I've thought about it and it's this
Kawaguchi Kaiji's "Boku wa Beatles"
10 volumes published from 2010 to 2012 in "Morning"
A Beatles tribute band
travel back in time
to before the Beatles' time
so they start releasing
Beatles songs.
But they're not just using The Beatles' songs
What if
we released
"I Want to Hold
Your Hand",
"Please Please Me",
and "Yesterday",
then made them
big hits all over
the world?
What
would
John and
Paul do?
to make money or become famous. Rather,
it's to reach the 4 people who should've been The Beatles.
Don't you
think those
two would
come up with
songs that
are even
better?
with songs
that we've
never
heard.
They think that perhaps
it'll cause them to make new
Beatles songs they don't know.
New
Beatles
songs...
That's
what
I want to
listen to
It's like a great experiment
There's also a bit about how the Beatles' songs didn't resonate with people at the time
It's like it's too new to get a reaction
It's like the first time everyone saw
Madical Lovely-san's manzai
If a girl who's probably never listened to The Beatles enjoys this,
then it must be really good, right?
That's why I'd like to try this one
And so, with three very different choices...
The first manga Hinata picks up is...
Ah, this looks good
"Onna no Sono no Hoshi"
Yamauchi's "Onna no Sono no Hoshi"
Then...
she starts to read
while eating a bento
She has a nap along the way
Maru-chan
She finishes the 3 mangas in 2 hours
Then, after a fake 10-minute interview, the preparations are complete
I have to buy a book for work.
Do you mind if we stop by the book shop on the way to our next booking?
Sure
Guided by her manager, they pay
a quick visit to a local book shop
(Manager) We're buying together anyway, so I'll pay
Yay
Then I want this
(Manager) Ah, this?
15 minutes later, Hinata comes out having bought something
So, which manga did she buy?
Prank Reveal
We go check
Huh?
What?
Huh, what is it?
(Staff) Could you show us what you just bought?
What?
It's "I Tried Drowning in a Swamp"
(Staff) What is that?
It's like...
Numa de Oboretemitakeredo
by HIRARISA
A collection of essays looking into women's money and desire
Now everyone knows I read this kind of thing
And the other books she bought
weren't manga either
Otsukare Joshi no Fuchō wo Kaizen suru Iyashi Zukan
by Shinoda Hiroaki
Otome Roppō,
by Kamitani Sakura
She purchased in total of 3 books
containing essays for girls
(Staff) We thought you might buy manga since you went to the book shop
Ah, I liked them but I thought not today
Huh?
(Manager) How about more of those mangas you read earlier?
Ew, no thanks
I didn't really want to read them
Asahinagu
Onna no Sono no Hoshi
Boku wa Beatles
Despite that, here's how she ranked them if she had to choose:
Next, Takahashi Maasa's theory
The first person to go home
when we do All-Star Thanksgiving is →
Theory: The first person to go home after All-Star Thanksgiving is Katsumata
Katsumata-san.
Really?
We don't know that
There's around 200
people there, right?
I also try to go home quickly
So you're looking?
Katsumata Kunikazu
When I manage to slip out quickly
and think I must be first,
as I'm getting in my car,
I always see Katsumata-san in his car
That's amazing. Really?
leaving ahead of me.
I want to catch it
on hidden camera
To always be first, out of so
many entertainers, is impressive, isn't it?
I wonder what his secret is
Next, Kanda Sayaka's theory
I think a manager wouldn't notice if a really good lookalike of the personality they work for got into their car
Theory: A manager wouldn't notice if a lookalike got into their car
Ah, that's probably true
Ah...
Now especially,
because of masks
If you just say "good morning"
They don't really look that hard
trying to imitate their voice
We could investigate that,
couldn't we?
I think ours wouldn't
Even if Dowsotowso got in
Next, Ichikawa Saya's theory
I love sumo and
I often go to see it and
report on it too
TL note: "dosukoi" = word often used in sumo songs and as a chant
But I've never heard a sumo wrestler
say "dosukoi"
Theory: Sumo wrestlers never say "dosukoi"
Ah, they just have that image
It's in sumo songs
Or in training
so they might use it there
I think they never say it
how we imagine it
I've never heard an octopus make kissing sounds either
TL note: referencing a children's game called "chuuchuutakokaina"
Right, it's just the shape of their mouth
It's just how we imagine it
The expression
It's like I thought it up for no reason
Dosukoi? For sure
I feel like they don't say dosukoi
But they do say "gocchan desu"
I've heard "gocchan desu"
Next, Katsumata Kunikazu's theory
Mothers will often
Sing a lullaby to make their child fall asleep
They're sleeping
only because of the melody
I think the lyrics don't matter
Theory: No matter what a lullaby's lyrics are, a baby will fall asleep
with that "go to sleep"
melody
even if the lyrics
are really weird
They'd never know
or badmouthing people.
A kid'd just fall asleep anyway
Next, Chihara Junia's theory
When I'm watching talk shows
during the day
I won't watch anything specific
but just channel surf
Miyane Seiji from "Miyane-ya"
To a panelist, he'll be like
next up it's you!
Mr. So-and-so, this is like this, this and this
I think for a panelist to pass a question from him
if he's on good form, can take over a minute
Theory: On "Miyane-ya" Miyane can take over a minute to pass a
panelist if he's on good form
First he says their name
quickly, right?
Taka-san, you know this?
It's like this, that and this
But there's this view too,
saying this
And you may think it's like this
but it's actually that
So it's that but this too.
What do you think?
He does
It's true
Then Taka-san finishes saying something harmless and inoffensive
And that's pretty much the whole package
Next, Suzuki Fuku's theory
Ever since I was young, people have told me
that their son,
or grandson
or friend,
or they themselves
look just like me. All the time.
I've already been told it 100 times
So I'd like the theory that there are
1,000 people who look like me,
Theory: Over 1,000 people look like Suzuki Fuku
to be investigated.
In the past we were looking
for people who look like Hamada-san
and Thailand was full of them.
It's true
About 20 in the airport
There were so many
Guys working in farms
looked just like me too
Ah, yes. Really
Definitely
And at Abashiri Prison
There's that doll
Yeah
Exhibition at Abashiri Prison Museum
Like this with a shaven head
Sitting like this on the floor in the prison
Exhibition at Abashiri Prison Museum
That's me
No matter how you look it
Exhibition at Abashiri Prison Museum
That's right
That was his style during high school
Theory: A manager wouldn't
notice if a lookalike got into
their car
Theory: No matter what a
lullaby's lyrics are, a baby
will fall asleep
Theory: On "Miyane-ya"
Miyane can take over a
minute to pass a panelist if
he's on good form
Theory: Over 1,000
people look like Suzuki Fuku
Theory: Sumo wrestlers
never say "dosukoi"
Theory: The first person to
go home after All-Star
Thanksgiving is Katsumata
And so, out of these,
the theory we'll actually investigate is...
Theory: A manager wouldn't
notice if a lookalike got into
their car
Theory: No matter what a
lullaby's lyrics are, a baby
will fall asleep
Theory: On "Miyane-ya"
Miyane can take over a
minute to pass a panelist if
he's on good form
Theory: Over 1,000
people look like Suzuki Fuku
Theory: Sumo wrestlers
never say "dosukoi"
Theory: The first person to
go home after All-Star
Thanksgiving is Katsumata
Out of these,the theory
we'll actually investigate is...
this one:
Theory: No matter what a lullaby's lyrics are, a baby will fall asleep
For this we will have
two entertainers
think up some lullaby
lyrics for us.
First it's...
Let's say good luck. Good luck!
"Good work"
Yes, thank you very much. Excuse me
(Staff) What was that?
No, it just reacted on its own. Sorry
(Staff) Siri?
I think it might be. I'm sorry
Cookie!
Yasei Bakudan
(Staff) "Nen-nen kororiyo"
"Nen-nen korori yo", yes
(Staff) We'd like some new lyrics. Is that alright?
Oh, totally totally. Super easy
New lyrics are easy, so easy
Yeah, easy, easy
"Nen-nen kororiyo"
Time for bed, roll over easily
Good boy, go to sleep
Where's the little one's souvenir gone?
I went over those mountains and
villages to buy a souvenir for the boy
I got some souvenirs from the village,
a denden drum and a shō flute
Wake up Koboshi with a hand drum
To think up some new lyrics for "Nen-nen kororiyo"
takes him 20 minutes
Done
I think what I've written will work
I think they'll sleep. I do
With the cooperation
of this nursery school
Ukima Kizuna Nursery School
we'll be investigating on 1-year olds as they still don't understand words
OK, time for bed Mei-chan
Nursery staff
Asahi-san
Will it work?
Mei-chan
Mei-chan good night
Four, five, six silver-capped molars
Seven, eight teeth in total
What if she remembers it?
Kids do...
Gather them up and melt them down
Just enough to make a Zippo
The front teeth fall out
She's asleep
Even a song about silver teeth worked
The next person who'll be writing lyrics for us is...
Shooo!
Yeah! Yeah!
Hollywood Zakoshishō
Schubert's Lullaby
Sleep, sleep, sleep, in Mother's arms
Sleep, sleep, sleep in Mother's hands
To the sound of a good song
In the joyful dream
Sleep, sleep, sleep, in Mother's arms
Sleep, sleep, sleep in Mother's hands
In the warmth of her sleeve
Sleep in her arms
And the lullaby this time
♬～ Sleep, sleep, sleep
is a song that has been putting
children across the world to sleep:
Schubert's Lullaby.
I'm done. Yeah
This is good
I thought about the baby and
put my feelings into words
It's a soothing feeling
And so...
Hiroto-kun, time for bed
Hiroto-kun
OK then, I'll hold you
This time the difficulty level has been raised as we investigate with a crying baby
Let's see what happens
(TL note: Hollywood Zakoshishō's usual jibberish)
Ambaran Kambaran Hanmakanma Hanmakanma
Bonboron Dondoron Hanmakanma
She succeeds in calming him down by doing
Hanmakanma while holding him
Can she keep going and put him to sleep?
Jonjoron Beronberon Hanmakanma
Atatata Atetete Tetetetei Atatetete
Result: the baby didn't fall asleep but became Zakoshi-like
He's been hypnotized
I see
That's how it is
The teacher learned the lyrics well, didn't she?
She did, and without laughing
We can laugh but as Matsumoto-san
said earlier
What if they remember it?
A child saying that
Such strange lyrics
It's scary if they start singing it at night
Yes, but...
if they fall asleep to "a tooth fell out!", that's perfect.
It'll just roll out
It would be
Just right, timing-wise right?
And Kazlaser's?
Also
She didn't take it, as expected
Theory: A manga is really interesting if you buy
the second volume on the way home
I wanted to hear more of the high-school student
and her manager's conversation
She's stopping the plastic surgery
She's like "I want surgery!"
We had a glimpse of reality
The manager's stopping it
It's like "No way!"
Per the company's rules
OK well,
Next time the theories pile up,
I didn't really remember much of it
shall we do this again?
I couldn't tell you one if you asked me
Really?
I can't remember even one
Not even one?
I think it's your brain that's the problem
Hamada-san did you?
Kacchan's was...
Huh, what was it again?
I totally forgot
You forget that?!
No, Kacchan's was...
What the hell
I was thinking about
what he said
The lullaby, right?
Yes that's it
Don't act more stupid than me
I'm not
It's awful, really
Your stupidity's starting to exceed mine
★Subbed by fmck fansubs★
reddit.com/u/fmckfansubs
patreon.com/fmck
Next week
Did I need to fall so far?
This hole's so deep!
A hole over 3 meters deep that
can't be escaped without help
An extremely evil prank
When are the staff coming? So lazy
Have they forgotten about this?
After falling in a hole,
the Prank Reveal doesn't come
If left there until sunset,
can they stay sane?
Hey! Help!
What's the point of this?