Coming up: "Everyone's theory corner" - where various theories from around the world are presented and investigated.
And tonight's presenter is ...
It's one half of Saraba Senshuu no Hikari - Morita!
Thank you for having me!
By yourself?
Yes ... today ... yes, by myself, ... well ...
It's just that I don't think you, as a performer, can really ...
Don't reject me already!
It's just you're usually not funny at all.
I'll be quiet.
I didn't hear you, so I'll just laugh over it!
I didn't understand it ...
Well ... anyway!
Is everyone here a morning person? Nakai, what about you?
I'm not a morning person at all. - Ah, you're not?
When I have to get up, I get into a really bad mood.
You get into a bad mood?
But you can still talk to, say, your manager?
Sometimes I can't stand him.
Should you really be saying that on TV?
Probably not too loudly.
So this time, we put the following morning-related plan in motion. Here it is!
Early morning new discipline simulation!
When you think of this program, you're probaby familiar with the "early morning" series.
This is a new installment.
"New disciplines". - Yes, new disciplines!
Is what I've brought you today.
Yes.
Your pacing usually also isn't on point at all.
I'll just laugh over it a little more.
Early morning new discipline simulation - what will be the first contest?
Straight-out-of-bed vs spinning-around-the-bat: a beach flag contest.
In other words, on a certain day in May, at 10:30 pm.
Who is the contestant to be woken up, lured in by the prospect of a fake TV show?
Yes?
We're with Wednesday's Downtown.
Wednesday's Downtown?
Could you come with us for now?
Please put on this eye mask for us.
Isn't this what you do with Kuro-chan all the time?
The clueless Nishimura is taken along ...
The air here is different!
... to the location of the contest: the beach.
And then, after changing clothes, ...
... he's put into a futon.
At 0:30am, late at night ...
... Nishimura has fallen into a deep sleep with the sound of the sea in the background.
WIth this, all preparations for the sleep-contestant are set.
Who will be his opponent, and spin around the bat?
Kasuga from the comedy duo Audrey.
Kasuga is told everything about the contents of this bout.
So am I gonna crush him or what?
He immediately set his eyes on the goal.
4:00am. Everyone has arrived on the beach.
He's completely gone. How can he sleep so well in this kind of place?
No way I'm going to lose here.
If he's sleeping so soundly, he can't get straight into it.
Who will win? Kasuga, spinning around the bat, or Nishimura who is just about to wake up?!
Who will it be?!
First of all, Kasuga has started to spin around the bat.
They will both start, once his preparations are complete.
And with this, Kasuga has just finished his 4th lap around the bat.
Nishimura will be woken up the moment Kasuga finishes his preparations.
Now Kasuga is at 9 laps ... just one more to go!
Wake up! Wake up!
Kasuga is off to a good start, but he can't run straight!
Meanwhile, Nishimura ...
It's a game of beach flag. Please run. - Beach? Where?
Where is it?
He doesn't know where the flag is!
Over there?
But now that Nishimura has found the flag, he's catching up! Who will reach it first?
And Kasuga takes the flag!
How was Nishimura that fast?
In other words, in a straight-out-of-bed vs spin-around-the-bat contest, the bat contestant wins by a narrow margin!
Good morning.
I did it.
How can you talk like that just after waking up?
I wasn't sleeping. Only you were.
What did you have to do?
What I had to do? Spin around the bat.
So it was that, compared to someone who had just woken up?
That's right. - Ah, come on!
But it's funny when you think about it.
What is the next contest in our early morning simulation?
A pair contest! Early morning three-legged race!
Who are the unaware sleeping contestants for this bout?
Razor Ramon, as well as ...
... Kaminari.
We let them sleep for 4 hours, without even knowing that their partner is right next to them.
Which pair will come out victorious?
Please wake up!
And with that, the early morning three-legged race has begun.
The staff will not only wake them up, but also tie their legs together this time.
It's a three-legged race! Please wake up!
It's a three-legged race! Please get up. - Huh?
It's a three-legged race!
Please run for it.
Ah, Takumi is also here?
Razor Ramon off to a good start!
But Kaminari is also on the move!
One, two, one, two, ...
But Razor Ramon is too fast!
Can they keep going?
And just like that, they cross the finish line!
But it seems they haven't noticed the finish line and keep running ...
Where to? How much further?
They couldn't explain the rules like this after all.
And just like that, Kaminari stays in pursuit of Razor Ramon.
And they, too, have already passed the finish line!
It's so far ...
... the goal ...
Where is the goal?
The white line over there was the goal ...
Are you kidding me?
So we didn't have to run a full lap? - We ran 400m.
Ah, so that was the goal?
Why didn't you stop us?
What is the final contest of our early morning simulation?
Early morning futsal!
The rules are as follows: At the sign of the kick-off, the captains of both teams, who are sleeping outside the court, will be woken up.
The captains will then start the game, as they continue to wake up the rest of their team.
And to add to the competition, the time limit for the match as well as waking up every team mate will be 3 minutes.
Who are the captains of this game of early morning futsal?
Two gentlemen who went to school with very strong soccer teams - Penalty's Wakki, as well as Panther's Ogata.
They both fell asleep late at 1:00 am.
And one after another, their team mates were also laid to sleep here.
What kind of match is about to unfold?
And with that, the whistle signifies the beginning of the match!
Wakki, wake up! - Ogata, wake up!
Please wake up! Wake up!
We're playing futsal.
Futsal ... ?
Yes, please wake up! We're playing futsal!
Wakki, you're in the blue team!
The time limit is 3 minutes!
Sorry, my contact lens ... is out of place.
We're playing futsal. It's already begun and the time limit is 3min!
Please do the kick-off!
What should I do?
And finally, both captains make their way to the court!
What kind of match will unfold here?
Who are all these people?
Who are we supposed to wake up?
The two captains are starting off a game of early morning futsal, but since they were woken up, 30 seconds have passed already.
What kind of match will unfold here?
Who are all these people?
Who are we supposed to wake up?
What will they do first?
Do they both understand the situation?
Sorry. - He's blue!
It seems that Ogata has woken up a member of the opposing team!
We're playing futsal.
Good morning Ogata.
Ah, Nakamura!
Wake up, wake up!
Meanwhile, Wakki is waking up his team mates.
This puts the blue team at 3 members already! Meanwhile, Ogata has kicked off the ball!
He enters the penalty zone, shoots, and gooaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaal!
Everyone but the captain is asleep on the red team, but lucky for them, the keeper of the blue team is also sleeping!
Get up!
Wake up! - We're playing futsal.
We're playing futsal. - Wake up the blue team!
It seems both captains have now understood the situation and are increasing the number of players on their team.
Come on, wake up!
The game has resumed, with all 5 players awake on the blue team.
Meanwhile, the red team is leading by one goal despite two players being deep asleep.
Time is running out ...
I'm red ...
But for some reason, the game has slowed down significantly.
Notice the ball at least!
Get up, get up!
Only 25 seconds remaining!
What is the blue team doing? - Wakki with a shot, but it's saved!
Wakki with another shot ... but the keeper saves it!
The ball ... is out of bounds, so a corner kick is awarded!
Will this be the final play of the game?
The kicker will be Regular's Matsumoto.
But there's no power behind the kick!
And with this, the game is over!
We will continue to look into early morning disciplines.