This is 'Suiyōbi no Downtown'.
Welcome, everyone
Hamada Masatoshi
(Downtown)
Bakarhythm
Matsumoto Hitoshi
(Downtown)
Nonomura Yukiko
Yahagi Ken
(Ogi Yahagi)
Hello
I can do it for you
So, here's our first presenter. Come in!
Are they there?
Hello
Yes, it's Mitorizu!
Lily
Moriyama Shintarō
Presenters
(Mitorizu)
(Lily) Hello
(Moriyama) Hello, we're Mitorizu
Back from defeat at M-1?
Hold on a minute,
we don't know yet
There's a second-chance system
We're aiming for victory through that
By the time this airs, we might already be champions
So then, everyone...
You're all already
super-successful legends here
So you don't go out
on location anymore, right?
(Lily) You used to
but not anymore
You're hardly ever...
No, no, no.
That's not true at all
Everyone...
What's the most important thing when on location?
Well, of course, you have
to speak louder, don't you?
Also, people will talk to you
Make your voice a bit louder
Members of the public
Right, you have to handle them
And when you're eating,
you need to have a big reaction
Wrong, everyone!
The most important thing on location is...
The camera
It's the camera
The camera...
No, well, that's...
That's true for TV in general, no?
That's too obvious. The camera...
There's no doubt about it.
So, today...
We've brought you a theory related to cameras on location. Here it is!
Theory: Even on a crazy on-location shoot where there are no cameras anywhere to be seen, it is possible to proceed without the guest pointing it out
Huh?
No camera?
So...
What are we going to be looking at?
We were recording from far away
You wouldn't just
interview them later
I was surprised
I thought we'd just be listening to audio
★Subbed by fmck fansubs★
gaki-no-tsukai.com
reddit.com/r/GakiNoTsukai
patreon.com/fmck
So, today...
Amusement park
Food report
Transit bus
we'll be taking over these locations
for camera free on-location shoots
First, our plants facilitating
the shoot at the amusement park are...
(Both) Hello
(Staff) Hello
These two
Jinnai Tomonori
Main Guest
Sakashita Chiriko
* TL Note (pause to read): Jinnai's first name, Tomonori, kind of sounds
like 'Wants to be friends' shortened ('TOMOdachi ni NARItai' → 'Tomonari')
There's someone who wants to be friends!
Tomonari!*
In this fake show
a celebrity who says they want to make friends will appear halfway through a shoot
That means
even if it's a weird shoot with no camera
if Jinnai and Sakashita have
started filming as normal
the target joining them halfway through won't point it out
Or so we hope
Staff) So we're doing a shoot with no camera...
Yeah
So there's no cameraman
So it's 'will they notice?', right?
Staff) Like, will they just let it happen...
No, they won't
They'll say
"What's going on?" is what I'd say, immediately
Like "There's no cameraman! What's going on?"
Even I'd say something
Right?
At this point...
Cameraman
We change to a camera-free formation
Wait a moment
Is this the camera...?
(Jinnai) You mean
this person is following?
Yes, on a normal shoot...
the crew make this formation,
with the camera at the front
Camera
Audio
Director
Mic
but this time...
in the cameraman's position, there's an empty-handed mystery man
Mystery
man
So they can just talk at the mystery man?
So, from this point...
Audio mixer
Bag
Chest pocket
Gun mic
Makeup bag
Using hidden cameras in places like
the audio equipment
we will capture everything
Hold on...
What if someone says 'look at that'?
No no no no
No, this is too much
Wait, just wait
I won't be able to not laugh
That movement's annoying, right?
The camera's like this, right?
Yeah
Wait a minute...
They're going to say something
And so, the crazy shoot in which this guy acts as though he's a camera begins
Staff) Jinnai-san, in 5 seconds
We've begun!
There's someone who wants to be friends
Hold on, I'm going to laugh
Hey, this is no good
We're making eye contact
Hold on, it's no good, I'll laugh
(Sakashita) Hey, Jinnai-san→
I'm making eye contact, with this old man
So...
I can't. Where should I look?
Wait a minute
Please don't look at my face
Don't look into my eyes
So, with the opening scene complete...
the old man with a built-in camera
moves from behind them
to a position in front of them
Staff) When we go inside
Staff) The guest will be there, so let's switch over
OK
And so...
Person number one will come in now
It's this person. Come in!
Wanting to make friends today, it's Tokyo Hoteison
Nice to meet you
Welcome
Our first target, who wouldn't have much experience with on location shoots
Shōgo
Takeru
Tokyo Hoteison
is Tokyo Hoteison
Nice to meet you
We're Tokyo Hoteison. Nice to meet you
Yeah, from Mayweather's hand!
Mayweather held this in an interview
(Takeru) Sorry
Get it right
Thank you for letting me do it
By the way, for this...
Shōgo already knows what's going on
Only Takeru is the target
So, what do you think Chiri-chan is like, Takeru?
Well, really...
I've never had a celebrity tell me they want to be friends so
Ah, that's good
I'm really really happy
It seems like he still hasn't noticed
that there isn't a camera in the film crew
Next, a walk around the park
(Sakashita) Wow
(Shōgo) Wow, it's really pretty. Look
This Ferris wheel
(Shōgo) It's really pretty
Which?
(Jinnai) This Ferris Wheel?
(Shōgo) It's really pretty. Look
(Takeru) Which?
(Shōgo) It's really pretty
Anticipating the movements of
the camera-free cameraman
the crew continues acting as though
they need to avoid blocking its view
Oh, a merry-go-round?
I want to go on the merry-go-round first
I'll get nervous if I'm suddenly in a locked room
Definitely
Right
OK, let's have some enthusiasm
Some enthusiasm please, Takeru
How will we become friends using the merry-go-round?
Definitely
It'll make us as close as best friends
(Jinnai) Ah, I see. Good luck
For a moment, he seems to be
looking for a camera but...
Definitely
He gives a quick one-liner in no particular direction
This is going really well
It is...
Huh?
How come?
Huh? No way
Why is it going so well? Who and what was he talking to?
Where was he looking at for that comment?
He was lost for a moment
(Shōugo) Yeah
(Jinnai) For a moment
Who's he showing enthusiasm to?
Then...
Very good. Hey, could you give us a wave?
(Jinnai) Could you give us a wave?
Who's he waving at?
Who's he waving at? What's he waving at?
He's glancing around
He's searching for it
He's definitely searching
But he doesn't know it's that person
That that's the cameraman
Next, we try something even more audacious
Because he's focusing on the game
the scary, head-swiveling
old man goes unnoticed
However...
(Jinnai) Isn't it 2-1?
Ah, Chiri-chan, tough luck→
Takeru, Takeru, bad luck Takeru
(Takeru) This is hard
(Jinnai) It's over! So, the result is...
With a score of 3-1, Chiri-chan wins!
Wow!
At this point Takeru finally notices how strange this situation is
(Jinnai) No but Chiri-san,
you're young
And your appearance
(Sakashita) Hey, Takeru-san's...
Takeru, is something wrong?
No, not at all, not at all
You seem a little troubled...
(Sakashita) Something was wrong
No, no, no. Actually it's...
I'm too happy
However, because the other members are proceeding as normal
He doesn't point it out, despite being suspicous
(Jinnai) Where to next?
(Sakashita) This way
So, for the last spot, we do something even more bold
I'm a bit nervous. How about you two do it?
I want to go on a roller coaster!
Well, have a look at this
Navel Coaster
Looks like a roller coaster
Having one camera is strange too
For sure, at a shoot like this
That's right
And so...
The empty-handed old man with a built-in camera boards in front of them
So he'll turn around to film them, right?
Then...
Woah! Scary, scary, scary
Seriously, who is this person?
Finally, as you'd expect in this situation...
He finally points it out
(Sakashita) Here we go! →
Eeek!
Woah, hold on a second. This is too much for me
Woah, wait a minute! Agh! Wait!
Hold on a second...
And, who the hell are you? Seriously!
Whoooo?
At this point...
We reveal the prank
Staff) Was there anything strange about today's shoot?
Well that person was looking at me so much
Like during basketball and on the roller coaster
I was like 'Ew!'
Staff) Who do you think he was?
Huh?
He was among the staff so I thought he must be someone important's son
Like he came here to see the shoot...
Was there a camera?
Ah, there wasn't
Then, after we've explained today's plan...
You missed it
No... Well, I'm sorry. I wouldn't say 'missed it'
But the weird guy bothered me more than the lack of a camera
When the crew's so big, you don't wonder who's filming
Right
There are already GoPros, right?
I thought maybe they can make a contact camera now
So. for our next target we try a...
Camera-free food report
Here's who'll be appearing for us today. Welcome!
(Both) Hello
Hello, welcome, in the middle please
With almost no experience with
variety show shoots...
Okuhara Hinako
Tokunaga Remi
it's these two AK48 members
Nice to meet you!
They don't notice at all in the opening
Sure enough...
I'm a 9th grader, aged 15, Tokunaga Remi
And so...
From here...
We add another human with a built in camera
A-cam
B-cam
The food report starts in a 2-camera formation
But first...
Staff) Is it okay if we calibrate the white balance now?
Excuse me
"Calibrating the white balance"
Action of calibrating the color of the image
White balance
means to adjust the color of the image
by doing something like this
Of course, in this shoot too...
But the two beginners to on-location shoots...
Ignore it
Then, we go with something bold for the food report
(Both) Itadakimasu!
I think I'll eat this first
Like Spiderman
Together with the lighting,
he closes the distance at once
It's really elastic, and very tasty
Safe
Next...
I think I'll have this now
These grated vegetables are really cute
Really, every single one
B-cam old man leans down over the udon
Perhaps because she's built up a tolerance to be stared at by old guys from her work
But, surprisingly,
this is also safe
Safe
It's really stretchy
Staff) OK. Now, we're going to stop for a while
Staff) I'd like to do some inserts of the food first so
Staff) It's okay if you eat for real now
Okay
So, in the corner of the room
The crazy insert filming begins
Staff) Could you pan down please?
Staff) Turn down in 5 seconds...
1 2 3 4 5
6 7 8 9
Staff) Alright, thanks
Staff) Now with the chopsticks held up please
(Staff) 3 2 1
B-cam) Hold it still
Staff) Sorry
B-cam) Now stop
Staff) OK
(Staff) Is it okay if we do it again?
As the strange men complain while gazing at the udon...
the pair look away instinctively
Then...
Staff) Jinnai-san, Sakashita-san, I'd like reshoot you walking outside
Staff) You two can stay here and eat while you wait
We try leaving the two targets alone for a while...
It's probably okay to sit cross-legged for a while
Ouch
I don't know which one the camera was
Where's the camera?
I don't know
Where were you facing?
Like, the light...
was really...
was really... close
That old guy who got really close...
I didn't know
I don't know.
I said earlier
I didn't know at all
What was that? Was he filming with it?
Huh... I don't know
Anyway, let's eat all of this
It's good
This is really tasty
It is, isn't it?
It's like 'well, whatever' isn't it?
Last, we're investigating
on a transit bus shoot
Camera-free transit bus
And to go with it, we've
added some plausible plants
Kojima Natsuko
Main Guest
Mieharu
And...
The target is...
(Mieharu) Hey
Oh, good morning!
Mieharu-san!
Michio
Tom Brown
They get on the bus straightaway but...
at this point...
(Mieharu) Kojima-san, why
are we on this bus with Michio-kun?
In contrast to the two targets before him...
He starts trying to confirm the camera's position immediately
However...
The two people he's meeting for the first time continue as normal
So he didn't point it out
The autumn leaves and that bridge...
But...
(Mieharu) The leaves
And the red torii gate
Michio-kun, it's better on this side of the bus
Ah, over there
The view, yes
(Mieharu) Aren't the autumn leaves nice?
Now he's noticed the old man
who reacts to their comments
Michio gets agitated
(Mieharu) On the mountain road there are...
And, after 30 minutes since the shoot started...
That bicycle shop's really good. Look, behind us
(Mieharu)
That bike shop's really good, isn't it? →
It's so stylish→
Yes...
I'd have thought by now...
For some reason, there seems to be
something physically wrong with Michio
Are you okay?
Oh, I'm fine
I can make this normal
But...
After that, the madness continues...
(Kojima) Michio-san,
are you alright?
(Mieharu) Your jokes and tricks...
At this point...
We reveal the prank
Staff) Good work
Staff) Was there anything weird about today's shoot?
Ah, yeah...
There was no camera at all
It was so scary, my head started to hurt
I was so scared...
These two were calmly talking throughout so I got really scared
I thought they were insane
What is this?
Staff) This is Suiyōbi no Downtown
Wow, what a relief. I was so scared
Thank God!
I thought it was a scary show...
Like I was thinking that old guy had a camera in his eye
And so...
Investigation Result
They get scared but
they can't point it out
I see, I see
That was funny
Everyone, how was it?
Not good! Not good
You even damaged Michio's health
Tom Brown
Michio
His headache
Not good
But it was funny, wasn't it?
Compared to the missing camera...
The impact from the old man was greater
For the whole thing, they
didn't know what he was doing
If it were Hamada-san,
he'd be like this for sure
If an old man goes near him like that,
he's like 'who are you?'
You get physical?
It makes the footage shaky
Because that old man isn't being filmed
(Lily) So why believe him?
Ah, I see, I see
Our next presenter
is this person. Come in!
Hello, hello
It's Viking's Kotouge!
Koutouge Eiji
Presenter
(Viking)
Hello, everyone
So, I have a question for you.
Do you know "Mother's Song"?
"Mother's Song"
"Mom's been working all night", right?
Yes, "Knitting you gloves". That one
It's often used in police dramas, when they're interviewing someone
True
When they're tugging at the criminal's heartstrings
In old dramas
In the past, though
It's got an old feeling
but stirs something up
I've brought with me a project that uses "Mother's Song". Here it is.
Theory: No matter how much you tug at someone's heartstrings, it's difficult to make someone cry by finishing with "Mother's Song"
Ah, I see
Especially with that 'sesseto andadayo' line
("worked hard knitting" in a regional dialect)
I think it'll make them wonder "What's 'andadyo'?"
Like 'what dialect'?
'Andadyo' is...
In the style of Shimura-san
Investigation
Theory: No matter how much you tug at someone's heartstrings, it's difficult to make someone cry by finishing with "Mother's Song"
all night
♬～My mom worked
My mom worked all night.
Knitting by hand
She knew the cold wind would blow
So she worked hard knitting
The letter from my hometown came through
I could smell the fire
♬～Knitting by hand
A song that makes you think of
your mom and your hometown
and a big hit in
the '60s
"Mother's Song"
♬～'andadayo'
Today a senpai comedian
Tearjerker story
will lay the groundwork with a tearjerker story
and attempt to make their kōhai cry
while singing "Mother's Song"
"Mother's Song"
Tears
And so...
Our first challenger is...
(Staff) Good morning
Good morning
Cookie!
Yasei Bakudan
And the kōhai who'll be his target is...
Ah, umm, by train
Poko
Target
What are you doing for New Year's Eve?
I'm staying at home
Can't you visit your parents?
I'm going there soon
But since it's so close, you can't go home in between?
I don't think so
I haven't seen my mom and dad at all
You don't take care of your parents, do you?
I don't, no
Right
But couldn't you just make an appearance?
They'll be happy just to see you, really
He naturally changes the
subject to talking about parents
Your dad...
Your dad and your mom...
Ah, yes
Here's the wagyū steak
Eat some steak
Thank you very much
I really love steak
I grew up poor so...
If someone asked what I wanted to eat, I always said steak
Once when I was in middle school, my mom got a part-time job
She started working part-time
They were building in the Shiga countryside
Apartments and condos
So they'd dig a hole and boom
My mom was like a worker to check if the ground was solid or not
You know? She'd look inside and go into the hole and sweep at the dirt with a brush
You can do it like that?
So it was like...
If they found any pottery, they'd report it
It's to, like, report back the strata had changed
So when I'd cycle home with friends in middle school
Mom would be right there digging holes
I hated it so much
"Kuu-chan! Welcome home" she'd say
I'd be thinking "stop that"
So in the end I told her
"Seriously, can you not do that kind of job? It's embarrassing"
Then my mom looked sad and said
"Alright, got it"
And she really quit
I felt so guilty about it
Then, I don't know if it was because I felt guilty but...
I started delivering papers
You did that?
It's a good story
It's good, this story
When they're healthy you don't think about your parents
Yeah
I don't know if they're getting weaker or not but
For some reason I've been thinking of mine a lot lately
I mean it's not like I'd feel it if the worse were to happen
But I feel like if they're unlucky they might die soon
That's how it feels
That's right
But at the most it's going to happen in the next 20 years
Because they're already 80
Not like the next 10, or 5 years?
You're right, within 10
When the time comes, all they've done for me these last 45 years...
It's like, how can I pay that back in the next 5 years?
Oh man
That's tough, right? Like what should I do?
You've already paid them back
I haven't! I've done nothing
I don't even visit
Look at me. Mine are in Tokyo and I still don't
(Cookie!) Well...
Now, with the sad mood established...
It's finally time for "Mother's Song"
How about you go meet your mom?
Yeah
Since she's close, you can visit her a lot
Because moms are important, you know?
You're right. My mom...
My mom worked all night, knitting by hand
She knew the cold wind would blow
So she worked hard knitting
The letter from my hometown came through
I could smell the fire
He didn't cry
And so...
My mom spun the hemp yarn, spun it for a day
He throws in the unfamiliar 2nd verse
♬～Working the straw
Do your best as well
I miss my hometown in winter
At least let me listen to the radio
You're laughing now, come on!
Kuu-chan laughs so easily, doesn't he?
Because the 'let me listen to the radio'
line made him start laughing...
We reveal the prank
At this point...
Wow...
Cry!
No, I won't cry. I definitely won't
I mean you're laughing already
Staff) Investigating the strata?
It was a lie
Jeez
Staff) Delivering newspapers?
A lie
Jeez
And so, the next challenger is...
Anthony
Matenrou
And the kōhai comedian who'll be his target is...
Thank you very much
Jumbo Takao
Target
Rainbow
Once again, after the groundwork has been laid...
It's time for "Mother's Song"
That's so true
My mom worked all night, knitting by hand
She knew the cold wind would blow
So she worked hard knitting
The letter from my hometown came through
I could smell the fire
Fantastic!
No, well...
Based on the mood, he's accepted the song but...
Jumbo does not cry
At this point...
My mom is...
He starts verse 2
But then...
She knitted...
He unexpectedly joins in
♬～knew it'd be cold
She worked hard knitting
The letter from my
hometown came through
I could smell the fire
But, as expected...
He didn't cry
So, our last challenger is...
Harisenbon
Kondō Haruna
And...
Ogawa Haruna
Target
Spike
I don't need to do it to know it'll be hard for her
She's really honest and pure, a really good girl
I think she'll cry. Ogawa-chan will
So you haven't visited them at all?
I haven't, no. Ever since coronavirus...
About 2 years
Here too, she naturally changes
the subject to parents...
Mothers, you know, they notice changes like that
Yeah
Like in the finals of THE W
Mine as well, when I'm in the final of a competition
I get really worried and nervous
At a time like that...
She doesn't really know anything about my work
And I don't talk about it
But it's like she can sense that tension and anxiety
She made me a lucky charm
Wow!
And gave it to me
She's so kind
So, like...
My mom worked all night, knitting by hand
I'm going to cry
She knew the cold wind would blow
So she worked hard knitting
Laughing senpai
Crying kōhai
So, here's the...
Prank Reveal
Huh.. what...
Huh, what?
What is this?
Staff) "No matter how much you tug at someone's heartstrings...
Staff) it's difficult to make someone cry by
finishing with 'Mother's Song'" is the theory
Definitely
Despite that, you cried so much for us
Seriously, it was a really good story
What made me feel like she understood was that story about high school
Ah, yeah, yeah
I was like "Wow". And also that lucky charm she gave you
The lucky charm
The lucky charm was fake
Investigation Result
We had intended it for it to be
an impossible theory instead of a difficult theory but something unexpected happened
And with that...
Definitely
One person succeeded
She cried
Amazing. But now...
I have to ask.
At a time when you're making someone cry...
Why did Haruna
order a sushi boat?
Sushi boat
2 of them
That caught my attention
2 people ordering a sushi boat's pretty rare
It's massive
2 people ordering a sushi boat...
And also, when Cookie!-san
was talking about his mom
Yasei Bakudan
Cookie!
When Cookie!-san said she's
80 so she has 20 years left
Poko
Habu-san was like
"well, 5 or 10 years at most"
Shortening her life expectancy without asking
You know,
I was wondering about that one
Yasei Bakudan
Cookie!
Poko
Like 'why say that?'
If it were reversed, I'd get it
'5 to 10 years'
'No, she could last
another 20 years'
I'd understand then. But when he said
Right, right
'another 20 years', he was like...
No, at most 5 to 10 years, surely
You can't say that if you're not related
Here's our next presenter. Come in!
Are you there?
Yes, it's Kirin's Kawashima!
Kawashima Akira
Presenter
(Kirin)
Hello everyone
Thank you for that
"Love It!" theory, really
Ah, really?
We were on that show, right?
Theory: A female guest on "Love It!" remotely
controlled by an army of comedians can get more laughs than the regular members
It's a live
morning show
It was insane,
you know!
You really got me
I really was
Were you shocked at first?
I was seriously
worried
I thought she
was on drugs
But...
You're right
We have no proof
Ano-chan doesn't do drugs
Hey, that's enough
She doesn't!
So, since today's show is a special
I've brought with me the 3rd
installment of a special project
And that is...
Real Prank
Ah...
So, this time...
"Advert" Real Prank
"Scandal Article" Real Prank
the theory I've brought with me about
something that turns out to be true is this!
Theory: If someone happily accepts the offer of an MC job on an 'obi program', even if the show turns out to be about introducing kimono obi, it's hard to say "in that case, we won't do it"
(Note: Obi means belt or sash)
I'm done
You don't have to do that!
We definitely have to make sure
Normally, when you say 'obi program'
it means a program airing from Monday
to Friday, covering the schedule like a belt
Yes, that's right
But it turns out...
It's a special show about kimono obi
That's harsh...
How about it? Yahagi-san,
if this happened to you
Hmmm
"You want me to do it?" is what I'd ask
Like "I'm not familiar with them!"
If it's about obi
When you discover it's about kimono
But, everyone, the main
point is still to come
Today it's a Real Prank
We actually recorded this obi program
And we'll really broadcast it
Broadcast it?
TBS kindly gave us a slot
for our obi program
to air as a special
As a different show?
It's not just on this program
You're doing it properly
So it's the same as before, isn't it?
That's right
The ones who are positive about it→
If along the way they start doubting it
are the ones who get it
or saying "what's this?" too much
then they get disqualified
Who's going to watch a show like this?
In fact when it comes to the kimono obi program...
The quality doesn't matter at all
No, no.
Do it properly please
We just have to make it happen
We can't do more than that
Some people will watch it
without knowing about this
I hope it's funny
Of course, whoever is our target
will do everything they can
I want them to do "obi snapping"
Investigation:
Theory: If someone happily accepts the offer of an MC job on an 'obi program', even if the show turns out to be about introducing kimono obi, it's hard to say "in that case, we won't do it"
(Note: Obi means belt or sash)
Today, the targets for our
obi program Real Prank will be
These 3 groups
Magical Lovely
New York
Saraba Seishun no Hikari
And the pair that shows a positive attitude
towards the program right to the end
will be invited to what is, without a doubt, the first variety program specializing in obi in history:
"Wonderful Obi Life"
(Suteki ni Obi Life)
where they'll be participating as MC
And so...
in the first week
or so of November
their respective managers inform them that they've received an offer to be MCs for an obi program
The first group were last year's M-1 champions
Magical Lovely
Murakami
Noda Crystal
and very popular
in variety shows this year,
Magical Lovely
Manager
And we've got one more thing from TBS
It is going to be at night
They'd like you to be MCs for an obi show
An obi show?
What kind? Comedy?
Well, I still haven't been told any of the details
It seems we'll be meeting them in the next few weeks
We set it up as if the manager
doesn't know the details either
Daily from Monday to Friday?
(Manager) That's right
Well, I still don't know what form it's going to take
This is incredible
Manager
Next, it's...
New York
Shimasa Kazuya
Yashiki Hirosama
We've had an offer from TBS about a late-night obi show
Obi? Really?
Yes
We'll do an obi show?
It'll be at night
For TBS
Wow, great
Something like "Wonderful"?
I don't know about that right now
But we've got a meeting about it next week
It seems like it'll be with the production staff
Wow, TBS
A late-night obi show for TBS
Manager
Higashi Bukuro
Morita Tetsuya
Saraba Seishun no Hikari
with you two as MC
Huh? Obi?
Obi...
Monday to Friday?
It seems we'll be meeting very soon to discuss the details
Both of us?
Yes, both
Bukuro too?
Bukuro too
What do you mean, 'too'?
So they're fine with Bukuro?
What's that mean?
That's great
Bukuro too?
How many times will you say it?
And, of course, they mistake it for what's known in the industry as an obi show
It's clear the 3 groups are happy
It'll be like a night version of 'Love It!'
In that case...
They could let us use the 'Love It!' set with some changes
Wouldn't it look good with, like, smoky colors?
But with the same set
And on-location shoots too. Maybe a vomit search
Searching the town for vomit
'Here's a problem for you, Uekami-san'
'What on earth is this round green thing?'
He's really talkative, isn't he?
He's getting really excited
He's already getting carried away
And so, Magical Lovely start dreaming about their late-night obi show
And then, when it comes to Saraba...
What I'm worried about is you
In what way?
You and your scandals
It doesn't matter
No but if we start an obi show, a scandal would end it
No, I don't know anything about anything like that
I don't know about that
You "don't know"?
Saying "don't know" isn't going to cut it anymore
We'll do the obi show and ... I don't know about that
No, don't say that to the staff
That's why we'll have a meeting and umm...
It's probably better to say "I don't know!", right?
In that case
So then I can say "I already told you that"
Yeah
Is there something else?
What's wrong with you?
Well, there isn't but...
There isn't but I don't know about something like that
I don't know what might get exposed
You should say that
"I don't know what might get exposed" is what you should say
So after they say "you're definitely doing it", I'll say that
Once they say that
"We're going with Saraba"
After they say "you'll do the obi show"...
Once if feels like they can't back out anymore
What do you mean back out?
So after it's gone that far?
They discuss underhanded strategies to
make sure they don't lose the MC job
Is it best to say that as we're leaving the meeting room?
In a sort of lighthearted way
No no, like... I don't think that counts as telling them
Is that really going to be okay on a professional level?
If we go back into the room it'll be bad
But if it's near the elevators, we'll go down, and it's done
We would win then
With all 3 pairs having high hopes for their first obi show MC job...
it's the end of the day.
Obi...
Obi MCs
And so, about a week after their
manager told them about it
Mid-November
the 3 groups are invited over under the pretext of meeting the staff
Director
Producer
At last...
It's time to announce it's about kimono 'obi'
So, this nighttime show, we've put a lot of effort into it
and with New York-san's participation
I think it could be a really good show
Thank you very much
Looking forward to it
Well then, shall we discuss the program's content?
If you could just turn to page 1?
(Yashiki/Shimasa) Sure
So, this show...
is called "Wonderful Obi Life"
Modern people have almost forgotten
about the beauty of Japanese clothes
so this is a program to "delve
into and rediscover the obi"
It'll air from 12.26am at night, for one hour
Ah, for only 1 day...?
That's right, yes
Ah, it's a one-off?
Yes, a one-off. Just 1 episode
Ah, I see...
So it's a special
So it's not an obi show
That's confirmed
That's right, it's a special
It's scheduled for Wednesday 22 December
The obi show...
Is it... this?
Ah...
Ah, I see
Ah, I see, sorry
The obi show's a show about obi...
A show about obi, yes
Is something wrong?
No...
It's...
It's... nothing
Is it okay?
Yes, totally
Would it be alright if we were to proceed?
Yes
Calling a show about obi an obi show...
I see
It's a kimono obi, you know?
You call this an obi show?
Because of the unbelievable "obi show" mix-up...
Yashiki pokes fun without thinking
Is it okay?
Yes it is
Is it okay
if we continue?
Excuse me, please continue
We're going to stay focused now
So it's an obi program
Just obi?
Just obi
They're thinking "we can't mention this on radio"
Program TBA
Suiyōbi no Downtown
And so, after this...
starting at 12.26am
A whole hour about kimono obi!
The first obi variety show in history
Wonderful Obi Life
a fake-looking but real program
"Wonderful Obi Life"
will actually air on TBS
Here?
Yes
Today, after this, for an hour
Amazing
An hour!
Who on earth will the MCs be?
TL Note: I'm not translating the obi show but you're really not missing much. Search for 'Suteki ni Obi Life' if you want to watch it
Could you please turn to page 1?
So, this program's name
is "Wonderful Obi Life".
By delving into obi, we'll discover things like
what it is to be Japanese person
A late-night show about obi
Ah, an obi show...
Ah...
It's not an obi show but about them
Yes? "About them"... what?
(Murakami) Ah, the...
The... obi is
L-
L- Late night...
Yes, it's late
So, there's only going to be one episode?
Yes, that's right
A special?
A special, yes
(Murakami) Oh
On second thought, there's no way it's an obi...
In comedy... well...
In TV terminology, "obi show" means
Right...
We probably got a bit carried away, you know
It's too early for us to have an obi show
And so, Magical Lovely's hopes are replaced with an equal amount of disappointment
And, as for the Saraba pair...
You're OK with this guy too?
We are
So I can do the obi show too
Thank you very much
Will it air live?
No, it won't
Ah, it's not live
For now...
Please look at the project booklet...
The program's called "Wonderful Obi Life"
Ah...
Huh?
Ah... oh?
Ah
Ah yes...
Huh?
Huh? Yes...
Is there a problem?
About... about obi
Obi from Japanese clothing
Yes
This is a show focusing on those kinds of obi
Ah
Ah, obi show...
It's a show about obi
What's wrong?
No, we're grateful, we're grateful
Ah, obi. Yes, yes...
What? Is it okay?
It's fine...
No, it's fine...
We must have misunderstood
It seems there's a lot they want to say...
Well, we've got 3 main projects in mind
There'll be...
Yamamura Momiji-san's on-location shoot.
Obi, right? Obi
We're thinking of having her go shopping
You two will watch that in the studio
and add some commentary about it
As for when it'll air, it's after "news23" for an hour
After "news23"?
It's like, we want to keep the "news23" audience levels intact
So we'll take over from that?
Then, once the staff have left the room...
What?
Well, I suppose it's technically an obi show
No way... would they put this after "news23"?
Well, I guess it's like a joint production of serious shows
Could he be possibly thinking that
"Wonderful Obi Life" doesn't exist?
Morita seems to be suspecting something
Then...
For cameras?
He's searching
It's done
Stop it!
He looks around...
and searches for hidden cameras
Because it's strange
Why not kimono? An obi needs a kimono
Why didn't they say kimono show?
Why obi?
Magical Lovely
New York
Similarly, for the other two groups, the staff leave the room so we can hear their true thoughts
I'm sorry, I said obi show. Um...
Sorry
I must have not heard them say "about"
I'm really sorry
This doesn't need us at all
Wouldn't Suehirogarizu be better?
But I'm happy if we've started getting jobs like this, about things that we don't have a connection to
So, at this point, we would probably be able to say no
It's fine, isn't it? Like, even if we flop
It's like "who could make this funny?"
So, like, it's alright. If that's the case
"Why don't you try it!?"
We'll say "Why don't you try it?"
I mean, who can make it funny?
Obi show...
I'm sorry. I, um, misunderstood too
Well, let's chat later
about the obi show being an "obi" show
It's not confirmed yet, including the schedule
Well, if the schedule works
It seems funny, actually
Totally
Wow, an hour on terrestrial TV as MCs
And so, there are two groups who considered the obi mix-up a funny mistake and are positive about the show
Early December
Yet another week later...
We invite the 3 groups to a meeting to
discuss the specific content of the program
Real!!
From this point...
To make the most of the "Real!!" at the end...
We daringly add more tricks to make it seem fake
So, first...
Excuse us. Sorry we're late
Sorry, hello
The meeting staff wear kimono
Trick to make it seem fake
Thank you for coming
Not at all
I'm looking forward to working together
(Murakami) Thank you
I like the kimono
We thought we'd get into the spirit of it
(Staff) The staff thinks it's a good look
Ah, totally
Yeah, it's cool isn't it?
(Murakami) It's good isn't it?
It keeps us focused, kind of
Of course, as MCs, you two will also wear these
Ah, really?
I'm glad
I'm so happy
Next, it's the ones who were already suspicious
about the program at the last meeting, Saraba...
Ah, hello. Sorry we're late
Sorry
Hello
I just want to say...
I'm looking forward to working together on this obi show
Yes
Ah... yes...
It seems as though Morita's
doubts have been confirmed
Moving onto New York...
Excuse us. Sorry we're late
(Yashiki) Good morning
Sorry we're late
Good morning
Hello
Sorry. Thanks for coming
Thank you
Good morning, hello
Well then, would it alright if we started the meeting?
Sure
Faced by a gang of kimono wearers...
for some reason, both of them give no reaction
Trick to make it seem fake
During the meeting, there's matcha tea and teacakes
After that, while they're being treated to matcha tea and teacakes...
Would it be okay if we moved onto the script?
We'd like each of you to do various one-liner obi gags
Trick to make it seem fake
Unreasonable request for obi gags
(Murakami) Obi gag? Obi gag?
How about it? Do you think you can do some?
Obi gags...
I see. Well... hmm
Some gags related to obi
Ah...
Ah... something...
Ah... something... yes
We'll think of something
Yes
We'd like to have a few scattered around
Obi gags?
Gags related to obi
Do you have anything right now?
Now?
(Staff)
Does anything come to mind?
Now? About obi?
He looks angry
He's already in a bad mood
He's got angry eyes
I see. Like...
Y-you have to wear an obi
Oh.. the obi...
Hello, I'm Obi Ologun. Something like that
Personally, I like it a lot but...
It's good, right?
No, it is good
I think it's really good
Furthermore...
Just before VTRs, it's different from the obi gags but...
This gesture, like pulling an obi
Ah, like in period dramas
And Noda-san will be like "Aa-ree!"
(Staff) Like you're entering the VTR.
Something like that
Trick to make it seem fake
Being compelled to do an unfunny VTR intro
Will you do it?
You don't have to
Aa-ree!!
VTR
Ah, other way
The obi is the other way
Counterclockwise
It's fine.
It's fine. Got it
Just one more time then
Aa-ree!!
VTR
That's it, that's it
This way, this way, this way
Could we turn the "Aa-ree!!" into Harley?
From, like, the second time
"Harley", like the motorbike?
The motorbike Harley
Aa-ree!!
First, Aa-ree!! then
Harley!
Couldn't that be an obi gag?
As an obi gag?
You've already made one really good obi gag
Aa-ree...
Harley
Magical Lovely are already showing a high amount of adaptability towards making obi gags
Next...
Thanks for filling in this questionnaire for us
I was wondering if we could review...
Trick to make it seem fake
A super-long preliminary questionnaire about obi
Sure
your answers to these questions now
We don't have much to say about obi
(Shimasa) For sure
I was hooking up with a girl wearing a kimono
Are there any obi you'd like to wear in future?
Has anything funny happened to you while wearing an obi?
I was hooking up with a girl wearing a kimono
I'd like to try on some high-end classic ones
Please complete this questionnaire for TBS Special "Wonderful Obi Life"
We kindly ask for your cooperation in creating material
What do you think the obi industry needs
When I did karate, I didn't really get past white belt.
Wonderful
Obi
Life
Yashiki's answers
Young girls like Meruru and Yuuchami
and popular gyaru-style girls...
and I had a really hard time untying it
to thrive in future?
Why does that happen? Seriously
Picking up girls wearing yukata or kimono
Thank you very much
We appreciate your writing so much
No problem
I see you've done karate
Do you have any sad memories related to obi?
Has anything funny happened to you while wearing an obi?
Higashi Bukuro's answers
It was in karate but I liked black.
I think firework-patterned obi are pretty
It was in karate but,
I remember struggling hard going from purple to brown belt so
I don't like purple obi
My classmate Takahashi-kun couldn't reach black belt so
everyone teased him, calling him the eternal brown belt.
He was brown belt for so long, it started to fade
and gradually become a white belt.
On the other hand, what colors and patterns do you dislike?
Please complete this questionnaire for TBS Special "Wonderful Obi Life"
We kindly ask for your cooperation in creating material
What are your favorite obi colors and patterns?
When I was a 3rd grader and couldn't tie my obi yet...
Ah, yes...
Yes, I did
In contrast to Higashi Bukuro,
who surprisingly answered
this puzzling questionnaire
in great detail...
Morita-san, are you not a fan of questionnaires?
It's fine
I'm sorry. I'm a bit...
Has anything funny happened to you while wearing an obi?
Bright colors
Do you have any sad memories related to obi?
I don't think so
Morita's answers
None at all
None in particular
On the other hand, what colors and patterns do you dislike?
Please complete this questionnaire for TBS Special "Wonderful Obi Life"
We kindly ask for your cooperation in creating material
What are your favorite obi colors and patterns?
When it comes to obi
I don't really have anything, sorry
that comes to mind...
Could it be that Morita thinks Wonderful Obi Life doesn't exist and so didn't fill it in?
Has anything funny happened to you while wearing an obi?
The obi you'd like to try on in future
Are there any obi you'd like to wear in future?
Noda's answers
Overlapping circles
Please complete this questionnaire for TBS Special "Wonderful Obi Life"
Tatsumura Kintai
We kindly ask for your cooperation in creating material
What are your favorite obi colors and patterns?
Wonderful
Obi
Life
Tatsumura Kintai
Did you already
Well...
Did you already know it before this?
Well... like...
I think I'd like to try it sometime
Oh, man
30 minutes before the meeting
This is so hard
We've got to write something
This is so bad. There's a script already
There's no choice but to search it online and write that
I don't even know what my favorite color obi is
There's no choice but to search
It's a bit unrelated but do you two have...
belts on right now?
Well, I don't
I do have a belt on, yes
Like this, yes
Since the belt is kind of a competitor, to the obi
Competition?
Trick to make it seem fake
Belts are competition for the obi so they can't wear them
To the obi?
Belts?
Because it's wrapped around you
Just for the day we're recording it, please don't wear one
Belts are competition?
Competition?
Yes
It's totally different though
Like, sweatpants...
They'd be useful
You don't usually wear one?
I don't...
I don't really I guess
I'm sure those in the obi world will be happy about that
If you could mention that
People in the obi world
They regard belts as something of an enemy
Is that so?
You're perfect for an obi MC
And then...
If you get an offer from a rival channel for a show about obi
We'd appreciate if you could refuse it
Trick to make it seem fake
Banned from appearing on rival networks' obi shows
Well, there won't be
Well, there won't be for sure
There won't be any, will there?
We don't think there'll be any but
Sure
If you could just let us know if you do
(Staff) Thank you very much
Sure
No problem
And now it's time for...
The final check
As before, after the meeting the staff leave them alone so we can hear what they think
Why did they wear kimono in today's meeting?
Well, because they're obi people
That's what it means?
Is he totally convinced it's a prank?
This time too Morita starts searching for cameras
On the other hand,
Magical Lovely...
They suddenly started the "Aa-ree!!" bit
"It's this way" "No that"
Was that on purpose to try to get a laugh?
We had to laugh more
Offers from another network...
There won't be any. No way
Those people are so weird, aren't they?
They're weird, no doubt about it
It's because they're weird that they said "do this belt show"
They get excited badmouthing the staff
This is something else too
This set too. They're really overdoing it with all this
It was tasty though
It was really delicious, right?
Really delicious
And, as expected, since he feels suspicious...
He starts looking for cameras too
But in this midst of
all this, New York...
What do you think? Does this program seem OK?
I wonder what it'll be like
I really have no idea
It seems they're uneasy but
there's no sign of suspicion
And so, the MC role for
"Wonderful Obi Life"...
go to the pair who were positive throughout.
Wonderful
Obi
Life
New York's
We select New York!
As for the 2 groups who
unfortunately searched for cameras
We tell them it's Real!!
Here...
Staff) Good work
Well we did think it was a bit suspicious
That's true, yes
I was already a little suspicious from the start
Staff) The start?
From when the 'obi show' turned out to be a 'show about obi'
But after that, when this didn't happen, I was like "is it real?"
After being approached by
staff holding a sign
they're totally sure it's a prank, but now we tell them it's real
Staff) The story was that you'd be obi show MCs right?
Yes
Staff) Actually
Real!!
Wait, what?
It exists?
Staff) Yes
"Wonderful Obi Life" exists?
Staff) Yes, it does
You're making it?
Staff) We are. It's scheduled
You've been doing this prank for weeks now
I don't get it. It's confusing. I'm not sure which it is
So you're saying this isn't a prank?
Staff) That's right, it's Real
It was Real?
Staff) It's Real
When you think it's a prank
(Staff) Yes
It's like the opposite of an opposite
Then we tell them they're disqualified...
So we'll be the ones who just complained about it
Staff) You did complain
Without a doubt
Staff) So how do you feel about having lost the MC job?
I feel like it's always going to be in the back of my head
What happened with this show
It was quite a burden
I felt a bit of pressure
There is a feeling I've been released
Next,
the Saraba pair
Prank Reveal
What the hell?
Staff) Good work
What the hell? What the hell?
No no no no no
I'm so annoyed. So annoyed
Staff) How was it?
What do you mean 'How was it'? What is this?
Well I already...
I was really suspicious from the previous meeting
Huh, huh? So it doesn't exist? 'Wonderful Obi Life'?
Staff) Just to make sure
Staff) The story was that you'd be obi show MCs, right?
Yes
Staff) That story...
is Real!!
Staff) So it's Real
Real?
(Staff) And because it's Real...
What do you mean? What is this?
Staff) "Wonderful Obi Life"
Staff) "Wonderful Obi Life" really will
Staff) "Wonderful Obi Life" really will be broadcast
Wha?
What? It exists?
You're making this?
It exists?
Staff) We are
Staff) Just as scripted, we'll be recording it but
Huh, seriously?
Yes
Staff) Because Morita-san was suspicious last time
Staff) and today as well...
Of course I was, in such a weird meeting
After we explain today's project and their disqualification...
Do things right for once!
No no no no no. We could've done it! See, they're doing it
Huh? You're really doing it?
Staff) We really are
Huh, what are you? Which side are you on?
Which side?
No, I didn't know either
So we weren't positive enough?
Obviously not
I was just thinking I could do a show on terrestrial TV
No one normal will think this is real
This guy wants to be on TV so much he just couldn't see it
He was just like this
So first I lost the Monday to Friday show
Then, I was like 'I'll do this 1 thing'
And now I've lost that too. I've lost 6 things
What? You wanted to do it?
Well, I did
I thought I could do a show about obi and was excited
(A kind of traditional textile↓)
Because I've already been researching Nishijin-ori
Ah, "There's no area in Kyoto called Nishijin...
That area is roughly called Nishijin."
I learned all that already
So you'll air it on Suiyō?
Staff) Yeah
After that? I'd want to do it then
(Staff) After that
Staff) No no no, but you can't
If it there's no Suiyō, that show would be awful
I see
So then...
So it's New York
That's right, as obi show MCs
We selected
New York
After that...
I really want to watch Obi Life now
I hope they do it right
I know, right?
By the way,
We've actually already filmed it
Really?
Wow!
Great
You have?
But New York still...
haven't had the prank revealed
They don't
They don't know we're involved?
Only that they've been introduced to kimono obi
And that they've recorded a strange program
But of course, at some point
we've got to tell them. So...
Today, we've called them to the studio
What do you mean?
(Bakarhythm) Ah, like that
(New York)
Shimasa Kazuya
Yashiki Hirosama
(Yahagi) I see
Yes, we brought them to TBS just like this
Well, you'd have to
Yes. Actually, 1 hour before recording this...
1 hour before recording
Yoshimoto Kōgyō Tokyo HQ
We captured New York
as they were finishing work
Ah, this is so scary
What? I'm scared already
Where are we going? What is this?
We don't even want them to know their destination is TBS, let alone what the program is...
So we bring them to TBS without telling them anything
So, then...
OK
Please take off your blindfolds
Good morning
Huh, so what is this?
Good work
Woah
Huh? Ah... huh?
This is "Suiyōbi no Downtown"
Yes
No, this...
doesn't make sense
Is that so?
Well, probably not
Well it's not like...
You were just going about your lives...
we're going to do
anything to you here
It's all already done
We already did something?
Finished?
It's already finished
Huh, what is it?
Yes, really. Good work
(Bakarhythm) Really, well done
Does anything come to mind?
(Shimasa) Finished it?
Huh, what?
Ah, that.
Could it be...
The 9-hour on location shoot for "Love It!"
(Shimasa) That...
That was a prank
Ah, it was. In Nikkō
From the end of the live show until 11 at night
Please don't think
that's something weird
Yashiki-san, lately,
have you had any strange jobs?
Right
Yeah
Yes, Yashiki-san?
That light-night TBS show.
The one we recorded at night
That!
What was the program called?
I forgot the name
TBS
That one was so so weird
That's the question!
(Shimasa) It was that, that one...
That one!
Yes! I've got it
Shimasa-san?
Wonderful Obi Life
Correct! Very well done
Was it that?
I get it now
I thought I was going to die recording that
Really? We still haven't seen it
So we don't know
So, that was...?
That was entirely
a "Suiyōbi no Downtown" project
That was close!
So the project you two have done is this:
Obi Show Real Prank
Yikes
Ah, but... yes... huh?
Yes
Do you get it now?
So...
That was a prank then?
It was so bad
Ah, but the set...
Yes?
It was, it was. Totally
was so fancy!
And there were so many people in the staff
Read it properly. Obi Show Prank
What's "Real Prank" mean?
The Real Prank is that "Wonderful Obi Life"
Huh?
really will be broadcast
What do you mean?
I don't get it
Well, because it's real
Apart from New York, we also targeted Magical Lovely and Saraba Seishun no Hikari.
But, even after learning it was about kimono→
the ones most positive and willing to continue→
That's right
were New York so that's why
you were chosen as MCs
So it's recorded, and
later, really...
We will of course broadcast it
Like an hour later
When will it air?
After this airs
Huh, it's going to air on TV?
A whole hour about kimono obi!
The first obi variety show in history
Wonderful Obi Life
Suiyōbi no Downtown
After "news23"...
After this show, there's "news23"
It's really going to air?
it's "New York's Wonderful Obi Life"
Well, it is Real after all
Ah, wait. Knowing it's a prank...
Ah... but
It's probably fine even if you don't broadcast it
Matsumoto-san, what's great is that...
This morning's TV guide had it as "TBA"
Program TBA
When this show airs...
The digital guide will change to
'New York's Wonderful Obi Life'
A whole hour about kimono obi!
The first obi variety show in history
Wonderful Obi Life
I see
This is something...
A whole hour about kimono obi!
The first obi variety show in history
Totally unprecedented
Because it'll say "New York's", right?
Yes, "... Wonderful Obi Life"
It was really bad
That's not true at all
How do you mean?
What was so bad?
It's really too specialized, about obi
Well, it's an obi show
Really though
It's really not funny
As a show
Whoever doesn't watch this "Suiyōbi no Downtown"
and only watches "Wonderful Obi Life"
Will think New York are extremely boring
No no... this is wrong
No... that program...
Oh no
They're probably just being modest so...
So we've prepared a compilation VTR
To watch now?
Sometime in December
Wonderful Obi Life recording day
On the day of recording 'Wonderful Obi Life'
Excuse me. I'm looking
forward to working with you
10:00 PM
MC meeting
I'll be working on the floor as well
Yes
First, in preparation for the show,
the performers and staff
Trick to make it seem fake
Of course, the floor staff are wearing kimono too
have a kimono-filled meeting
Staff) Regarding the "VTR Aa-ree!!"s
Staff) I'd like for us to roughly sketch out where they'll go
Staff) Later, when we get the chance
Staff) We can do it when you check where you'll stand
Alright then, we'll do that later
10:30 PM
Rehearsal
Then, right before the show
They enter the studio
for the rehearsal
Just a basic karate posture
Staff) Yes, please stand like that
Staff) It's alright if you sit during the VTRs
Understood
Staff) By the way, your position for the opening gag
Staff) Could you look at the camera?
Ah, now? Is that better? Sure
You'll go there? When doing the gag
Yeah
Is here fine?
Staff) Wherever's easiest
I think it's better
Staff) Hold on a second
Sure
Staff) For the size on camera
It doesn't make sense to change it during the show
Ah definitely
If you look at the size of the shot
(Staff) Will you move around a lot?
That won't be funny later
Actually I won't move at all. I'll do it all like this
I'll do the show
I'll just stay like this from now on
Is it OK? We'll keep that one as a backup
Instead let's do one that's definitely funny
Ah
Sorry if it's not funny
(Staff) Not at all
You're raising the bar too high
Raising the bar too high?
Then finally, the unprecedented obi show recording starts
Serving as MCs for this noble program
,We're too short for an obi but too long for a sleeve. It's New York!
Welcome
Yes
I see
Ah, oh...
What an atmosphere
It is
We'd like you to brace your obi and yourself
(Yashiki) Of course
Everyone, please join us for the next hour
Please join us
With the filming proceeding smoothly...
Japan's 3 Biggest "Obi" complete
and the 1st
segment finished...
They take a break
Break time
Guest
Iwashita Hisafumi
Did you do a lot of research before this? About obi
No, not at all
None
I thought not
I didn't know anything about the round obi
At the moment, I don't think we're getting much usable footage
Trick to make it seem fake
Lecture from Hako-chan during the break
Really?
(Iwashita) I'm just saying
I'm not saying this for the sake of you two
Huh?
This affects me
I went to the trouble of coming here so late
Nothing good is coming of this
I'm just thinking "these guys aren't a big deal"
I'm saying because it's bad for me
This is a complaint
I'm sorry
The others are thinking it too
You're not sincere
Staff) Sorry, we're about to start the second half
Staff) Could you please make your way to the studio
Thank you
Just keep that in mind
Thank you, yes
Excuse us
All the others are too important to speak to you
So I'm going to be the hated one
Thank you very much
Staff) The second half is about to start
After being put into a bad mood
by a puzzling lecture...
The second half of filming starts
Shimasa, how do you choose your obi?
Ah, well, I've never chosen one
You've never bought one?
No, I haven't
This is hell...
Then...
1:30 AM at night
Have a wonderful obi life!
Staff) Alright, that's OK. Thank you
The recording of the fake-seeming but real program is complete
And then, like this,
they record promotional messages
To everyone watching King's Brunch, 'Wonderful Obi Life'
Watch it!
Simple!
Staff) Alright, OK! We're done. Filming over
The long-term
Obi Real Prank is complete
Do you think it'll be okay? Like that
It's strangely funny
How will it look on air?
I know, right?
What about the next episode...
There won't be one
I think there won't be another
We should watch it for sure, to see what it's like
Yes, good work
The staff didn't laugh at all
Well it  wasn't very funny, was it?
No no, what?
What kind of jokes did you do?
For the VTRs, it was like this
Ah, isn't it the other way?
Ah, it's backwards. This way
This isn't good, this thing
You spin against the obi
The sponsors are watching
You're winding it backwards
That's it
VTR
Aa-ree!!
It's funny though
(Bakarhythm) Not bad, not bad
It's getting
more and more funny
We did it maybe 3 times
According to the staff, during recording
there was a lot of going in circles
Well, that's accurate. Seriously
If an obi's going in circle's that's not good
Right
No, the staff were weird
Now...
Even Matsumoto-san's not funny
Obi are unfunny
If it's about obi it's unfunny
New York's Wonderful Obi Life is after this from 12.26am
Some areas excluded
So, 'New York's Wonderful Obi Life'
will air today, 1 hour after
this 'Suiyōbi no Downtown' ends
From 12.26am
it really is a hour whole long
It's really 1 hour?
We're going to air it
Please watch it
Wow
I think if it were like 30 minutes
I'd watch it but not an hour
★Subbed by fmck fansubs★
gaki-no-tsukai.com
reddit.com/r/GakiNoTsukai
patreon.com/fmck
I think it's really bad.
It really is bad
I hate that atmosphere
Well, there's that but also
After this,
the three of us, me and New York
are going to record a commentary track
For 'Obi Life'?
For 'Obi Life'
I see
We'll have no viewers left
if it's too awful
So we'll watch Obi Life together
with Kawashima-san?
The three of us, yes
That's probably going to be the most painful
thing for us
New York's
Some areas excluded
Starting 12.26am
Wonderful
Obi
Life
After this
'Wonderful Obi Life'
It's the Obi!
Please watch it! Thank you!