No matter how obvious the prank is, a comedian will play along
The target is Viking's Kotouge
How far will he play along with this bad prank?
The first hint is
A suspicious cable coming from the room
He appears to notice something, but still enters the room
You didn't notice this?
No I didn't
When he enters the room, inside are
Some unnatural magic mirrors & plants
Very suspicious
It's already kinda scary
Everyone disappears
Yeah they leave you alone
He doesn't look at towards the magic mirrors
And shows no reaction
You must've noticed
something around now
Please excuse us
Suddenly, police enter the room
Sometime yesterday morning
This lady's wallet
Was lost somewhere on this floor
We're searching around each floor
We'd like to search this area, we appreciate your cooperation
Sure
Thank you
Inside TBS, a woman's wallet was stolen
and fake police begin to search the room
These guys are really fishy
Lastly, we'd also like to check your bag
Alright, please excuse me
It's definitely in there
Uh... Huh?
What color wallet did you say it was?
It was a glossy red one
Huh...
Inside Kotouge's bag is the victim's wallet
Hey that's mine
This is it, isn't it?
N-no, I don't anything about this
That's right, actually-
When Kotouge was taken out of the room
Staff placed the wallet into his bag
There's no mistake right?
Yes
This guy's the thief isn't he?
No no no, uh... this is a mistake
Kotouge suddenly realizes what's going on
And starts playing along with the prank setup
We'd like to collect the evidence
Well it was found inside the bag
No no, I didn't take it
No I didn't take it, I didn't take it
Well it didn't walk in there on its own
Well, we can take our time listening to your story
It's 14:45
Get up
No, I didn't do it
,14:45 the suspect is arrested
,Arrested under suspicion of theft
,No no I didn't do it
,When told to get up, he stands
,When told he's under arrest, he extends his arms
,To both the police and the prank, Kotouge is very compliant
The press are already here
You're laughing!
Of course I would laugh here
No no, I didn't take it
Is this for real
In reaction to the unbelievable event, Kotouge unintentionally laughs
While thinking "This is a prank right?" he says
There's no way I'd do something like that
He once again plays along
But with his "There's no way" laugh
His playing along isn't very convincing
If you play along, then play along seriously
If you Tsukkomi, then Tsukkomi seriously
We wanted a clear answer but
Do you always perform your crimes in the dressing rooms?
No no I didn't do it, there's no always
How many times have you done this?
No this is my first time
"First time" I mean I didn't do it though
You just confessed right?
No that's not what I meant...
Where are we going?
Court
Instead of the police station, it's court
Court?
And so they take Kotouge to a house studio with a court themed set
They skip the interrogation and go straight to trial
Defendant Kotouge's theft trial begins
Defendant, take the stand
Prosecution, your opening statement
The prosecution states that
In Minato Ward, Akasaka 5-3-6, TBS HQ's 7th Floor Meeting Room
A wallet containing ¥15,000 belonging to a Iroha Fumiko was stolen
by the defendant
Criminal Theft under Penal Code Article 235
That is all
Defendant, do you dispute these claims?
Well I mean I didn't take it
In this case
The victim's wallet was discovered inside your bag
This is true is it not?
Well it's true that the wallet was inside my bag but
I didn't take it
Did you ever think "I did something bad"?
No I didn't, because I didn't take it
Even with these absurd developments
He does not deny the events, instead
He insists on the single point "I didn't take it"
The defendant's actions were extremely malicious
He completely denies the crime and shows absolutely no remorse
We seek a death penalty
Death? Isn't that too harsh?
Theft receives death penalty
Death?
Defendant
be silent
Defense, any objections?
None
Why are you even here?
What are you even here for? Seriously
"I'm Sorry" "I apologize to the victim" If you said something like that
There could have been some consideration
But you have done none of that
So if I apologize I avoid the death penalty?
So you admit your crime?
I don't know if I admit, but I'd like to apologize
You confess to stealing right?
If pleading guilty will avoid the death penalty
then I'll take it
Alright then
I am ready to give the sentence
Sentence is
Death
It's still death?
In the end it's still death?
It's still death
Let's go
"Let's go", you mean to die?
I don't want to die
Who'd want to die?
Don't tell me to "be quiet" if it's death
I don't want to die
Death? Hey!
Death Row Inmate Kotouge is transferred to a prison set
There's still more!?
This is so long
Your execution is tomorrow, wait here
Tomorrow!?
How long is this gonna go...