Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Hello everyone
It's Shimofuri
Amazing!
This is Shirofumi's first time, nice to meet you
Isn't this the declining-in-popularity-Shimofumi?
Wait, Matsumoto
What the hell?
Matsumoto, where did you hear this?
Never heard of it.
-Seems wrong
We're on the rise.
-We're still on the rise
I was wrong
We're just getting started!
Stop this, Matsumoto!
So, this time
When it comes to Wednesday Downtown
There are horror-oriented pranks
Among these, Hamada's favorite is
The "Somebody Series"
Ahhhh interesting
I heard that Hamada enjoys this the most
Really likes it!
He watches it with his whole mouth open
That wide?
Previously, it was said that the most frightening thing is to open the door and find someone
Indeed
"Someone in the back seat of the car"
"Wake up and find someone"
And others like "someone's in the bed"
Every time Hamada smiles very happily
But there should be none left
Well
This time, the "Someone Series" is twisted slightly
It will be used to validate a relatively novel theory
Even if a foreigner has lived in Japan for a long time, the first words that come out of their mouth when they are surprised will be their native language
What is this?
They'll react
A slightly different scenario
"GOD DAMN" or something like that?
Eh?
"GOD DAMN" and the like
Seriously, just leave
Takada really made us nervous too
This volume is the that of the ring announcer
Sorry
Shortly, a verification involving foreigners
Also
How long with Rossy go along with suspicious things?
Little girl selling matches?
Men with scary faces have been told "I won't give you my daughter"
Even if a foreigner has lived in Japan for a long time, the first words that come out of their mouth when they are surprised will be their native language
So, this time, we are testing foreign people who are active in Japan
With an approach that has a 100% rate of scaring people
The dependable "Someone Series"
The initial target is
Girolamo has been here for 32 years?
This time the setting is
A locker room in the lounge
Japanese still isn't great
This is the man
It's this guy every time
I Love you baby
I Love you…
@%#$!!!
Seems like he said something
What did he say?
I Love you…
@%#$!!!
Asshole, what the hell!
The second sentence is "asshole" but
The first sentence sounds like Italian
What exactly did he say?
There's a strange man here, a stalker
We confirmed
There was a particularly... particularly strange person in...
How are you feeling?
It was a shock!
What did you say when you saw this male?
Ah, it's "die!"
Ah... Japanese...
Not his native language
Yes, Japanese
Will it change back to speak Italian when you are scared?
You usually speak Japanese.
-But... but...
I really like "die!"
From time to time, i'll say it
What should you have said in Italian at this time?
Mamma Mia would be better, right?
But, for me, the usage of "die!" is the same
Die!!
Asshole, what the hell!
Why "die!"?
So, the next target is
Who would say "die!"?
Wrong way to use it, right?
In Japan for 23 years: Caiya
Caiya is really scary
The setting is "someone is in the back seat of the car"
Might get hit
While a fictitious interview was in progress
The person is placed on standby in the back seat of the private car she drove in
Preparations complete
Really could be hit in the chaos of the situation
After this
Caiya, who was talking to someone while returning to the car
Definitely not in a happy phone conversation
It's true, a lot has happened
Who are you talking to on the phone?
Already in English
If she is scared like this
There should be a sound like "Oh my God"
What'll happen?
OK  see you soon  bye
A simple reaction
And due to too much fear
She escaped from the car with full force
Here we revealed the truth
How are you feeling?
I'm sorry, I'm not thinking straight right now
Seeing someone in the car
This is already trauma, trauma!
Oh my God, I'm scared to death, oh my god
When calming down, she spoke English from time to time
But the first reaction was a horror movie-like scream
The next target is
In Japan for 13 years, Nwala
This time, he was set up to sleep in a hotel and "wake up to find someone"
So
We first confirm he's asleep
Before an older man enters
This guy is awesome!
This is so scary
Oh wow, this is so bad
This would definitely be scary
The next thing to do before he wakes up naturally is just to wait
This job is also not easy
Then after two hours
So
This is a normal reaction
Who?
So scared that he fell out of bed, but the first sentence was in Japanese
Scared the hell out of me!
No English at all
Give me a break, really
Authentic Japanese
Definitely won't sleep tonight
Indeed
How could you do this? Seriously
I can't sleep. He's still here!
I have to get up at four o'clock to go to "Good Morning Studio"
This program is live!
I can't sleep anymore
Angry
And I locked the door
How could you still come in?
Do you know what a master key is?
Master Key
What kind of timing is this?
The next target is
In Japan for 33 years: Dave Spector
This time it was in Dave's dedicated cloakroom
Where the man with a high success rate is lurking
So, we start immediately
Terrifying
Eh, what's this?
What? Who is this?
Completely in Japanese
What? Who?
Who the hell is this?
Scared the hell out of me
It's really "oh my godou!" this one
He even says "oh my god" in Japanese
33 years of living in Japan were not in vain
It's really "oh my godou!" this one
Not even here
The last target is
Really want to here them speak English
Yeah
21 years in Japan: Bobby Ologun
Bobby is also very timid
The set up is "someone in the bed" trick
This time we let the family go out first
A verification of an isolated single person in his own house
When he gets home, he first performs the daily task of checking stock prices
Now he's ready for bed
So
Unbelievably he doesn't notice there's someone next to him
Will he sleep with an older man he doesn't know for a whole night?
Bobby didn't notice the man hiding under the blanket and went to sleep
However
What the hell--
Bobby who felt a sense of dissonance from his back when he turned over
The first sentence was clearly in Japanese
Immediately after
He fell into a state of panic with the dramatic effect of frantically pressing the wrong switch
And
Who!?
It hurts...it hurts...it hurts
He knocks down the sliding door in one move
The truth is revealed
What the hell?
Crying crying crying
Someone has died
I... I don't know anything
Did you sleep in the bed?
I got in
Did you not pay attention at all at that time?
Yeah
I was sleeping on my side the whole time
By the way, what do you say when you are frightened in Nigerian?
In summary
Japanese pranks will always end in Japanese
The result turned out to be this
Yes
-No native language spoken
This is too much, not good for the heart
It's scary to watch
But, how to put it?
They'll calm down eventually
Then they'll speak their native language
Yeah, at the time they won't
They must be dreaming in Japanese, right?
Stayed too long, have become completely Japanese
Are there such people? Only dreaming in the native language
If you live too long, your dreams become Japanese, right?
I want it to keep going like this until Bobby speaks his native language
Poor thing
-Its enough for him to hit the door
The doors of their house will be all gone
Incredible, the energy
The lights in the living room also flickered as if they were about to break
Lights and doors are running out
The light is the same as lightning
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Savannah's Takahashi
This time, I bring a project about the world's most innocent and gentle man
He is literally the most innocent and gentle man in the world
Please take a look
Rossy's acceptance of everything has gone so far that its scary
You must all know Rossy, right?
He is really gentle, innocent, and tolerant of all things
Totally non-angry, non-doubting
A man who feels nothing is out of place
Indeed
Do you still remember the "Strange Man Contest" project that was conducted for him?
In a project such as, persuading a child to continue to be a shut-in
On the way, he suddenly became furious with the mother of the child
Loudly scolded the mother "how can you do this to your child"
This is also a reflection of his gentle caring nature
The ending was that Rossy became shut in the room and couldn't get out
Even at that inexplicable point, he accepted it without question
He's really an incredible man!
That part was scary
We did all kinds of tricks on this gentle Rossy
To what extent will he accept them?
This is worrying
Rossy's acceptance of everything has gone so far that its scary
So, we first asked the person who knows Rossy best
His wife
He tolerates everything, basically
I think it will be incredible for everyone to witness
I really feel like that
Have you encountered any strange things lately?
Recently...
For example, the entrance to a convenience store
The ruler they measure the approximate height of a thief
※It is also available at financial institutions, amusement parks, etc. It is used for witnesses to recall the approximate height of the possible culprit.
Rossy he...
He thought it was normal to measure his own height and happily did so
And also
He has very bad eyesight
If he doesn't wear contact lenses, he is completely blind
Sometimes he will forget to take off his contact lenses and go to sleep
And still put another pair on the next morning
Won't even notice he's wearing double contact lenses
So, we spent several days watching Rossy closely
The first day
Rossy, he is really gentle
Help with incredibly heavy luggage
Feels like it will be very interesting
What happens if he's told, "Please can you take this luggage that cannot be put on the floor"?
Uh, well, I think...
He will always hold it
They'll say "Don't put it on the floor", right?
-That's right
Then he won't put it on the ground
So, we called out Rossy for a fake job
So at this point
Sorry
Can you take this for me, please?
I forgot something, I need to go back quickly
Wow, so heavy
Sorry, this can not be put on the ground
Because inside are very valuable things
Is it okay if I leave for a little bit...for a little bit?
I'm very sorry.
-No problem
Sorry, obviously you're so busy. I'm very sorry. I'm sorry...
It looks so heavy!
As you can see, Rossy calmly agreed to carry a full 20kg box of sand
There is no difference with the sand on the ground
We also inexplicably added a requirement that prohibits putting it on the ground
Normally you'd put it on the ground
So far there is no doubt that the luggage was not put on the ground as agreed
Are not curious about what'd happen if put it on the ground?
Then
Sorry, sorry.
-It's okay, it's okay
Thank you very much. It's a big help.
-Don't mention it
Where are you going?
I'm going to go around to the back of the area
Because this luggage is very heavy
Does it mean...?
We'll walk a little bit, there might be a place to take a cab
If the pick-up point is close, you might as well take one
Let me walk you to the cab
So gentle
Thank you so much!
Kindly helped to carry the sand to the loading point
Next is
The cab drives to the wrong destination but charges as normal
He wont get angry
When paying...
Well...probably will hesitate a few times
Thank you
Um... please send me to TBS
TBS？
The one in Akasaka.
-Oh, it's in Akasaka, isn't it?
Ok
-Okay, thanks for the ride
The work destination from Shinbashi is Akasaka, about 3km away
However, the cab went to Shinagawa,  the opposite direction of Akasaka
The result?
You'd surely be angry
Mr. Driver, excuse me?
-Yes.
I'm wondering if we're going in the right direction
The wording is so gentle
I'm driving in the direction of Akasaka, TBS, so its fine
Really? What...
I feel like you are driving towards Shinagawa
Can you drive towards the centre?
If you drive in the direction of the sun
I think it will be closer to TBS
Relying on the afternoon sun and the position of the sun, the driver was directed to drive west
It's over there, over there
In terms of direction
No...that...
-Hahaha no no no
He's not angry
It's that way
I can get off here and transfer if you don't know the way
No need to...
Please stop for a moment
We're heading to Shinagawa now
Too gentle, right?
Uh... I don't think there's anything wrong with that
If I don't arrive, it's not good
Rossy started to get anxious about being late because of his serious personality
Now we are in the direction of TBS
No, no, that's not the right direction, although I'm taking the liberty of making that judgment
Maybe it's my fault
Please let me off here
I will get to the destination in some other way
Can I get out of the car now, please?
I can't say this
Here?
Just drop me off here. It's close to Shinagawa
Here, a little to the side
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
-We've already passed Shinagawa Station
Excuse me, can you let me out?
Mr. Driver, you've already driven past Shinagawa Station
Is this the direction of Akasaka?
No, no, Akasaka is in the opposite direction
You've got it wrong, Mr. Driver
However, this time the driver is determined not to let him off
What the hell is this setup?
So
I may have to do something not so good
I may contact the police
If you don't let me out
You may be held criminally liable
Hearing these 3 numbers the program team immediately softened
So we stopped here
I'm sorry I made such an arbitrary request
Arbitrary request?
Sorry, the fare is 2010 yen
Thank you
Despite being pulled further away from his destination
He is nonetheless thankful and paid the fair
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
-It's okay, it's okay
I'm sorry for making arbitrary demands
Sorry about making arbitrary demands?
What is this?
Day 2
Verification ③ Stranger asks to borrow his cell phone
A request from a complete stranger to "borrow a cell phone"
You'd surely want to refuse
He rightfully lends it
Hello?
Hey...
Hung up?
What is your unlock code?
Unlock code? What is it?
Is there an unlock code?
Can I call again?
-Yes, of course
Sorry about that
Doesn't even know of the existence of the unlock code and the phone doesn't have a lock screen
What about personal privacy...
3rd Day
Cookie asks him to look after his son for a while
If strongly requested
Probably would agree
During a meeting
A staff member leaves momentarily
Where do you live? Have you moved?
Is the room very spacious?
No, the room is not very spacious. 2LDK
You have two children?
-2, 2
Can the toys be packed up to make room?
Hmm?
-Can you make room by packing up their toys?
Toys can be packed to make room for almost one person's space
Can it sleep two children?
Two children?
Yeah probably
My wife always had a dream to study language abroad
But I don't have time to take care of children
Uh-?
Really?
When the time is confirmed can you please
Take care of my child for about 3 months
It is not something that can't be done
Because of a variety of reasons its not impossible, not impossible
But for example, going to school
And stuff like that
Taking them there and stuff
I don't mean transferring them my child's school
I mean parents and such
There are still many things that need to be adapted
If its stable then its fine
If the child is not given a happy experience
If they just suffer
So you can't take care of them?
-I'm not saying that
Although it is not impossible to take care of, but I can not go to your home to take care of them
But since you entrusted me with the care of a life
Rossy, who is very sensitive about human life and children's matters
Unexpectedly and carefully thought out and answered carefully
Well you can look at it as just an extended sleepover
No, 3 months is a little...
3 months is a bit... uh
Probably because someone else's kid is staying here
You'd feel a sense of responsibility, right?
You wouldn't say yes so easily
If the mood is "ah yeah fine"
It's just like borrowing something
"Then you can borrow it next time" or something like that...
3 months is a bit...
-I don't understand you, for example
3 months is a bit too long
1 week and 2 weeks is quite manageable
Then help me look after them for two weeks
That's perfectly fine!
2 weeks is perfectly fine!
But 3 months is a bit...
You take care of them for 2 weeks and then I pick them up for a day and then give you them back for another two weeks
It can be up to 3 months repeatedly
Eh?
Why does he look accepting of the length all of a sudden
Yeah... yeah
He is successfully convinced thanks to Cookie's sophisticated argument
Slowly ground into agreement
He is really gentle with children, no matter what children
We added something for Rossy, who is very gentle with children
Then I will contact you when I have the chance.
-Ok thank you
Thanks for your hard work
Big brother.
-Scared the hell out of me, yes?
Do you want to buy some matches?
The little girl who sells matches
Verification ⑤ The little girl who sells matches in 2019
Please.
-No, right?
Can you buy it?
How much, how much, how much, how much, how much, what to say?
How much? What should I say?
I can buy one
Okay, then 1000 yen, please
A little expensive
Just buy one, one
Here, here's your money. Give me the matches.
-Thanks
Go for it!
-Yes
Although a high price
He still accepted the scene with equanimity
Normally you'd be looking for a camera here
The unreasonableness of the tests slowly escalate
4th Day
Abandoned dogs on the roadside
Please be kind enough to take her in, she's a little bitch named Mocha
However this dog is
AIBO？
AIBO might be adopted by him
I'm not sure about that either
Would he be afraid?
May say "what is this?"
As you can see, after a short glance, he walks past
However
Immediately after this, he sent his wife this LINE
Do you want AIBO?
If you do at XX elementary school there's one, we could take it
AIBO? AIBO is the robot dog! Haha
There's an abandoned AIBO dog in a box named Mocha
It says "AIBO"
The kids will probably like it
Because of rushing to work
Although not personally taking it
As the abandoned dog is an electronic dog his feelings are less strong
Next was a verification as part of a fake health program
Firstly
Sorry, this microphone
The micro-mic has changed to coin operated
Coin-operated?
-Yes, coin-operated...
Verification ⑦ If you don't use a 100-yen coin the microphone wont work
How is this possible?
Rossy-san, could you please put in 100 yen first...
I know, I know, I'll get the money.
-You have some?
I'll go and look
Should have change, right?
His acceptance has reached ridiculous heights
How long does it last?
-How long does it last?
100 yen will last about an hour.
-That's great!
The more words you say, the faster the battery drops
Haha new type of microphone
It's perfectly fine!
No suspicion at all
Finally Rossy's over-acceptance is at the point of being frightening
Regardless, he puts on the micro-mic with 100 yen invested first
First of all, the physical strength test
Then
Ready ~ Start
The sound of 100 yen completely affects the important sound recording of the program.
Putting the cart before the horse
End
56th
There are so many?
-Yes
Ah, really?
However, Rossy did not care about this at all
So tired
-Well done
Thanks for the compliment
After this also
Round trip running
Above average
Accompanied by the sound of the mic he completes the seven physical tests
Next is the health diagnosis
So, without further ado
Let's have a health check
Yes, please
So please strip down to your underwear
Okay, understood
Then put your clothes in this basket
As you can see, Rossy took off his shirt
Now lets start the vision check
Please look at the table over there
Verification ⑧ Stripping isn't necessary for the tests
Please stand in the white line
This
What? Ah, its a little hard to see it
To the left, ah, sorry
After that, these tests that had nothing to do with nudity
Finally, he gets dressed and goes to receive the results
The x-ray image is done
-Ok
Let's take a look.
Can you see this part?
-No
You have a seed sprouting in your stomach.
-No, really?
Verification ⑨ Watermelon seed germinating in stomach
I presume its a watermelon seed
You've been...
-I've been eating watermelon lately
Do you swallow seeds?
Ah that's really watermelon seeds
Yes, two days ago
Karateka Yabetaro asked Rossy to eat some watermelon
Yes, i'll be careful in the future
I'll have to take all the seeds out in future
It's very rare
I'm also worried about Yabe, I ate it with him
He is still worried about others
Watermelon seeds sprouted in the x-ray image
I think he'll believe it
He still quite likes this kind of fantasy things
Has there been anything before? Something fantastical?
Fantasy - well - for example...
Isn't there a knife skill called "Chikiri" that cuts cabbage?
He felt that a more superior knife technique, "Ten Thousand Cuts", also existed
Another example is the Romance Car, which he thought was a train for the elderly.
※Romance Car: The term "Romance Car" was originally used to refer to a train with a Romance Seat, i.e., a couple's seat in a group of 2. In 1991, Odakyu Electric Railway registered the term as its own trademark, so it now refers specifically to the special trains operated by Odakyu Electric Railway
It's sprouting
It's like a bean sprout. Will it grow?
If there is enough nutrition in the stomach, it may grow
Although it was the first time I saw
This will not be a problem if left unattended
But what if?
If it grows into a watermelon fruit in the stomach, it's a big deal
This is really amazing, if it'll grow into a watermelon
There is medicine to make this bud wilt. I'll bring it to you now
This bottle is the medicine that makes the buds wilt
This bottle is the medicine that will destroy it
Please pay attention to the order of taking the medicine
If you don't germinate and drink this bottle of blight medicine, your stomach will be perforated
This is the end of the shoot
However, there is one last thing
The last verification is?
This is our first meeting
I'm the new AD Shino
Ah, the same last name
What?
-My name is Shino too
Is that so?
-Yes
Ah, sorry, my name is also Shino...
Which characters?
The city and vegetables
Yasei?
Yes, Yasei
I would say the "word" town with "wild" in Nogahara
Same word, same word, right?
-The same word!
Verification⑩ Received a request from AD to borrow money
The fake AD has been present all day
He puts forward a request for money
Will Rossy lend money to someone he has just met and has no relationship with?
How much do you need?
I need 3 million
This is a little tough, and I don't have that much money
3 million, I can't get it by tomorrow
Tell me your contact information
I'll let you know if its possible
If you give up because of this it'll be difficult for you
Although he could not immediately come up with the loan because of his own financial problems...
Rossy nonetheless listened gently and carefully to the AD troubles
Work hard
We have to work together
And for some reason he makes the promise to "work together"
What the hell is working together?
At this point, we move to ask him about the strange events over the past few days
So, we got him in under the guise of a fake program
Have you encountered anything unusual lately?
Recently? Is there a limit to what kind of thing?
Did you encounter any strange or unbelievable things in your daily life?
There are a bunch of them
The year number changed, something like that?
Say the watermelon thing!
I see.
-Different from the past
Within the last week
Something unusual, anything?
The weather is colder than expected, right?
I recently went to the dentist
Now I have dentures and need to get a new tooth or something
It's not about those things
Just 30 minutes ago things like this happened
Completely ignored
As we fear he will be unable to realize it himself
This is actually Wednesday Downtown
Oh-
Ah, scary!
Rossy's acceptance of all things is scary
No way
You accepted a lot of strange things
No, no. Is there someone else named Rossy?
-No, no, no
In summary
He's really scary
What's going on? What's going on?
Did you see the final conclusion?
-What's happened?
Sorry, I'm a little confused
He thinks there are a lot of Rossys, thinks its verifying different Rossys?
He didn't think anything weird happened to him, did he?
-That's probably it
Ah... I see
What did the other Rossys encounter
He himself hasn't encountered anything
-Thinks he hasn't
So other people named Rossy experienced lots of weird things
This is what he thinks it is?
So he thinks that nothing happened to him
To Rossy...
-He thinks it was all normal
You are now the closest to Rossy's mindset
Is that so?
-Seems like it
What do you think, Matsumoto?
The driver
This part is good, he didn't get angry at all
Using Rossy as a comparison
I would like to see the Hamada version of this same scenario
If it were Hamada...
-I'm sure he would have been furious
He'd probably kick the kid selling matches
Next is everybody's theories
Tonight's presenter is
Tamura Kenji!
The theory I have brought this time is this:
Men with scary faces have been told "I won't give you my daughter"
Won't give them
This is about people with scary auras meeting parents
Yes
If they go to meet the parents, they'll will be told that they won't give their daughter to someone like them
What do you think, Matsumoto? You have a daughter, right?
Me in the position of parent?
If someone with a scary look comes
Well... definitely not if they have swastika on their face
It's not really that far
Well, if the attitude is not good, it'd be impossible
Did Hamada meet the parents?
Of course
What happened? Did they say, "I won't give you my daughter"?
No not at all
Did you go with a fake pinky finger?
-No pinky?
It's very convincing
You tug it, it won't fall off
It will come off
-You tug at it!
It will fall off
My dad is also a strange man
So I was curious to have them meet
Why?
What will be the reaction?
What would your father do?
Men with scary faces have been told "I won't give you my daughter"
The first interview was with this man
Both arms embroidered with tattoos and huge ear lobes
His head is also full of tattoos
Its Bam Bam Bigelow!
Not caring about being poor
Would someone be fearful that their daughter was going to suffer?
Do you have new tattoos?
This one
A large piece
This is it.
-That's it?
It's a "gout" tattoo.
-What?
It says gout
You had gout?
-I had gout
And then got a gout tattoo?
-Got the tattoo
Why?
I drank too much, so I got it to make sure I don't forget I had gout
This scary-looking guy is controlling his purine intake
Have you met a girlfriend's parents?
Twice
Twice?
-Yes
How did it go?
She told me that "my father is very strict" and "be aware of it"
I went there and was ignored
Ignored?
-Yes, ignored. Didn't say anything at all
How did that meeting with the parents end?
Nothing, I couldn't say anything, I was completely ignored
Have you ever heard the words "I won't give you my daughter"?
Isn't being ignored the same?
Next is this tattooist
Have you met a girlfriend's parents?
Once, I did my hair nicely and wore a smart suit
Neat and tiday
But the tattoo...
-You could see the tattoos still
I also shaved my beard
They said "Are you a drug addict, are you a gangster, do you have a relationship with that kind of people?"
The door was closed
They said "Don't talk to me, get out" and "Get out of my house"
Despite the closed door, they had a child and married
Super opposed to me, still are
And this fierce-looking man too
It is possible that the tattoo wasn't seen as it was covered
Why is it hated?
Did you wear long sleeves?
No, this is the kind of tattoo that will show even if you wear long sleeves
The other party said, "Are you kidding me?" "That's ridiculous"
It's true that the parents' generation still has a strong aversion to tattoos
In the midst of all this, this tattooed guy
"Please let me marry your daughter" like this
I said, "Please let me marry your daughter"
Then what did the other side say?
The person said, "Well...okay," and that was the end result
I was told to "pay the insurance properly"
Isn't there a national health insurance and an insurance certificate?
Something like "just make sure you pay that"
In such a way, occasionally someone hits the jackpot and meets a low threshold family
This next guy
Didn't like my appearance
How did you dress?
Wore a suit, but my hair color and earrings were the same
Told me "dye your hair black and take out the earrings"
But I don't want to do things other people tell me
So we argued
My father-in-law did not come to the wedding
It seems that it is not only the appearance that makes an old man angry
Next is this red-haired man with earrings
The other party is a single-parent family, only her mother
I was welcomed very warmly and
After meeting me she also began to wear earrings
She originally did not have ear holes, but them pierced her ears and became funky
My own parents are very strict
I can't go to funerals on my side
I was shocked to be refused
And this fierce-looking man sipping whisky on the street
This one's interesting
Is this still Japan?
Where do you want to get a piercing next?
Here
Why do you want it on your forehead?
-Because it's cool, like this on the center line
I like the kind of left and right symmetry
This man has a total of 20 openings on the left and right side symmetrically
My mother-in-law doesn't like this
I was told to "take them all off" so I did when we met
Did the parents of the other party say anything?
No, they were very nice, didn't say anything in particular
Quite understanding, I was a little surprised
So how do you deal with your piercings in front of your mother-in-law now
Although I was told to take it off, I still have them
That's me
I told her that piercings is not makeup but my armor
And I don't want to be judged by my appearance
Although no tattoos and no piercings, this one has a strong sense of weirdness
Have you met a prospective wife's parents?
-Parents?
When meeting the parents, did they say anything about you?
Well, said the hair is so long
And it was pink
One of em seemed to be a teacher or something
One of em?
I got pushed down the stairs
Really?
-Yes
They said "I won't give you my daughter" and then bang, I was pushed down
Probably feeling words were useless, he was rejected physically
Then this senior fierce-looking man
He said something really bad to me
They said "What are you doing here?"
He said, "First of all, look at the way you're dressed."
I said "I'm a musician"
Then he said, "It doesn't matter, just shave it"
"Why would I give my daughter to you?"
Then I said "yes"
It was like that
How about it? Do you want a more exaggerated story?
How about "How can I give my daughter to someone like you? Come back tomorrow when you're shaved! What?"
How to say... tell the truth is fine
In summary
Daughters wont be given to people who like to exaggerate stories
This VTR is a with a lot of piercings and tattoos
Fierce looking
It's true...
-The kind of type that will get rejected
It is true that the degree of tattoo coverage is also a determining factor
The first few people are very impressive
They should just have have a tattoo on their backs, like Hamada
This way you can't see it with clothes on
-No, that's wrong
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03