Welcome to Wednesday Downtown
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Who is it?
Anyone there?
Welcome Miracle Light
-Hello everyone
What a rare guest!
I can't believe you're the presenter!
-Yes
So this should be a hypothesis about imitation
It is indeed related to imitation
Do you remember the previous one...
Eh...
You forgot?
You can't forget it!
You're supposed to be explaining it, right?
You love to switch roles
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Do you remember the project about imitating the teacher?
In the school, right?
Went to the school to imitate the teachers
Very moving
-That one was very well done
It think it won an award.
-Yes, it did
Got the Galaxy Award.
-Really great
This time we bring a project that can stand alongside it
Please take a look
"No one has done it yet" King of Imitation Showdown
No one has done it?
-What does it mean?
We generally choose people to imitiate
After year and a half of practice, those imitations are performed
But the project this time
The program team will select the topics to be parodied
And they are things that have never been imitated
They will be imitated in an improvised way
Sorry.
-Yes
I can't quite understand what you're saying...
Thank you for speaking up for us!
I also didn't understand
Absolutely awful!
In any case, the parody stars will start an unprecedented parody battle
And
They think they're shooting commercials
But really, they're being pranked
This event is an impromptu imitation of an object that no one has imitated yet
Impressive
The list of the much-anticipated participants is as follows
A serious competition
Hello
The pressure is very high
Feeling scared
If no one has imitated these things before, it means
It's difficult to do
If this passive approach to unlock your unknown potential
Then I think its very exciting
On the one hand, although it is disturbing
If you can win here, you should be invincible
I should say I'm a head-in-the-sand type. So I hope I can excel
I think Kanazuki will be a strong opponent
In my case...
After all, I quite often do some far-fetched imitations
After all, he did JB
I should be ready for it
Notoriously rough
I'm looking forward to exploring my unknown self through this
Because i'm competing with many legendary seniors
I feel like... am I really qualified?
And my work is subpar in comparison
For example?
"A girl becomes a dog when she agrees" or something like that
It has nothing to do with seniority...
I think it will be a very fair game
I am quite confident
What is your area of expertise?
Is there a certain aspect you focus on?
Yes, there is
Such as?
I can imitate people with protruding chins
"Slippery is also golden"
This is Midori Ito
※World Hall of Fame Women's Ice Skater
After all, it's my old job to do imitations that no one has ever done before
Compared to others, my psychological construction should be the most sound
Bring it on
I think it's a good opportunity to test my ability
The matchup combinations are as follows
Men and women will be divided into three groups and the theme of the parody will be decided by drawing lots
Both sides will face off in the same role
Each group will be tested until there is one winner
It's really awesome, this group is incredible
And they're parodying the same thing
So you can clearly see the strength of each person
Plus, this time, it's the impersonators scoring each other
I see
-The professionals are doing the judging
The system is the same as the first King of Conte
That's true
In the first round
So interesting
Looking forward to see what the topic will be
Akima Haraguchi vs. Masahiro Ehara
It's all about technique
First, let's decide which theme you two will imitate
The theme is..
Who is it?
Yoshiharu Doi
It's Doi-sensei!
Wait wait
Wait a little bit
Although it's basic Japanese food, it's still quite high quality
Very fine
The performance is very good
Really no one has ever done it
What do you think?
Wow - I never thought of imitating Yoshiharu Doi!
Eh ... but the Kansai accent seems to be more favorable to me
They have only 90 minutes of preparation time
What kind of Doi Yoshiharu will the two of them present?
A parody of Yoshiharu Doi, brought to you by Akima Haraguchi
The preparation is actually all cut out
Using chopsticks is so much faster with four of them
To say it is boiled, with water boiling, its not that simple
Recipes often say something like two to three minutes to be ready
The tone of voice
Two and three minutes are completely different I tell you
So you don't even know if it's cooked or not
When you don't know, how can you do it?
Eat it and you will know
Okay, it's done
Very impressive
The imitation is spot on
Now for the opponent, Masahiro Ehara
Today, I'd like to give you a taste of autumn salmon
What is the best way to eat autumn salmon?
Speaking of fall salmon, in the summer, they go upstream from the river
Very energetic, and last through the winter
So they are very active in the summer and winter time
The same as Gachapin
※Fuji TV's children's program mascot often appears in the weather forecast segment
Gachapin spends his summers surfing, and his winters skiing
As for the method of cooking
No need to fry or boil
After all, the ingredients themselves are very tasty, so just a little searing will do
The same as Gachapin
After all, Gachapin is also very tasty with just a little searing
Why?
What are you saying? Gachapin is not for eating
So skilled!
Just eat it with white rice. Thank you all
Impressive!
So strong even from the start!
It took only 90 minutes for the two to reach such a high level
Next, we'll let the rest of the participants in this event do the scoring
Each person will cast 3 votes for the ideal candidate in his or her mind
Will the first person to progress by Akima Haraguchi
Or Masahiro Ehara?
The results are as follows
Akima Haraguchi with 10 votes and Masahiro Ehara with 14 votes
Masahiro Ehara is advancing to the next stage!
Great competition
Scoring isn't easy
What a pity to lose in the first round
Miracle
Ah, how can I put it...
It was a struggle
I like Mr. Doi very much, he said a lot of quotes
"No need to do extra things." "The taste of the ingredients is the most important thing
He has a pure insistence on the taste of the ingredients themselves
I think he caught this point
So whether it's Gachapin or the other one, i'm voting for him
I see, the performance was accurate
-It was accurate
It's really hard, but... I enjoyed it
"No one has done it yet." The King of Imitation Showdown continues
2nd Match is Hori vs Yoshiaki Hanaka
The theme is
Noda Crystal
Noda Crystal, a very current choice
A champion
I've had a bad breakup with the master.
-You've had a bad breakup with the master?
Master, your magical performances are out of date
What the audience wants to see is more luxurious magic
Arguments between masters and disciplines would all go like this
Your magic is all superficial stuff
Well, how to put it
Noda's body movements are relatively rich compared to most
One of his characteristics is that he will pause in the middle of a sentence
What kind of Noda Crystal will the two present?
Even the pectoral muscles are done
A parody of Noda Crystal brought to you by Hori
Great! It's Noda!
Super similar
This is awesome
This is really awesome
A person who wants to make you laugh no matter what, I am Noda Crystal
Please take care of me
Awesome
We're going to eat fine French food!
Advanced French cuisine ah, great
Imitating both of them
I'll do it now, if its wrong, you have to say
No, no, no, no
Are you a sous chef? Are you a sous chef?
This guy is crazy
What do you mean "it's over?"
Emi-chan--!
Even Murakami's part is similar
Close to a perfect imitation
Both of them imitated
Hori, who imitated even Murakami, is up against against Yoshaki Hanaka
So alike
A person who wants you to taste no matter what
Noda Crystal's Three Minute Kitchen
To make a roasted whole chicken oh-!
The first thing is to put a chicken...
Chicken, wait. Chicken
Chicken... Chicken...!
Chicken he... chicken chicken
Chicken
Chicken-!
Ok
Flutter, flutter, flutter
In this way, the cooking is done
Now i'm going to take this in the gossip kitchen direction
※Emiko Uenuma's program
Emi-chan, wait for me...!
Wonderful
Thank you for the performance
This is so difficult to rate
Hori, who recreated the M-1 segment in its entirety
And Hanaka who used the person's characteristics combined with an original segment
Fully integrated into something else
The results are as follows
16 votes to 8, with Hori taking the lead
Hori even imitated the partner's part in such a short amount of time
This is something I'm not happy about but I voted for him anyway
Hori was able to include everyone
He touched upon everything
In this way he is really the best of all imitation artists
This puts a lot of pressure on me for the future
"No one has done it yet." The King of Imitation Showdown
Matchup 3 is Miracle Light vs Rei Maruyama
Miracle is also very good at this kind of it
The theme is
Harue Okada
-I see
A cultural person
Top TV appearances during covid
The most seen
-Very true
Appearing throughout 2020 on popular TV news programs, Harue Okada, a professor
Is there a wrap dress?
What kind of imitation will be presented?
Please enjoy Miracle Light's Harue Okada impersonation
# This year Where should I
go from here ~ w
Okada
I'm Harue Okada
Last year I made a lot of statements about covid
Where do I go from here this year?
A little malicious
What can I do to make Japan a country where everyone has enough to eat?
Ramen Burger 24-hour Convenience Store
Anything you want to eat at any time is at your fingertips
But 6,000 years ago, on the great plateau of Mexico
Aborigines ate chili and bean curd in a pie crust
Talking nonsense
That was the origin of tacos
All I can do this year is to make tacos a reality in Japan
And for the second encounter with Jijohnen
※Economic commentator has criticized Okada's remarks as irresponsible
I put on a mini skirt
Thank you all
Thank you Miracle for your performance!
Very similar
And a surprising ending
Miracle, who ended with a surprise, is up against Rei Maruyama
Rei change will put up a fight too
Is it my turn?
I'm Harue Okada, a professor
In the end, what is this covid?
It is transmitted by droplets
And suspended particle infections that are smaller than droplets
Then there are contact infections, which are roughly divided into these three categories
It would be good if this came first
That... I like Sakanaction the most
After the epidemic is over, I really want to go see their concerts
"Let's take covid away like this"
※Lyrics of "New Treasure Island" by Sakanaction
"Wash your hands carefully, carefully, carefully." I hope you can do this
Please pay attention to prevention measures
It's so hard!
It's really hard...
Really hard
The imitations of Harue Okada captured characteristics in a short time
Is this the same person you are imitating?
The results are as follows
11 votes to 13 votes, the winner is Rei Maruyama
You fell in the first round!
Let's talk to Miracle first
Looking at everyone
They use a standard approach
You are slapping yourself in the face!
With a basic look and a bit of imagination, people can win
So it makes sense that I would lose
I lost convincingly
I'm really shocked that I beat Miracle
Match 4 is Mikan vs Kintaro
The theme is
Michopa
No one has done it
This is really hard...
But it's true that we have to start from the public's impression...
Despite her popularity, no one has imitated Michopa
What kind of performance will the two present?
Michopa's parody brought to you by Mikan
Michopa's "Michopa in the small window while watching Kuro's Love Confessions VTR"
Good details
Oh nice
You can't be talking about me
It's a lie. It's disgusting, okay?
Next
Michopa's delusions of grandeur while watching "What if I were to go out with Michopa?"
What does it mean to want to be NTR?
This is correct
Thank you Mikan
Next is the Michopa imitation by Kintaro
What are you talking about?
Looks like an LA American
Is it really true?
Are you stupid?
That cake is a birthday surprise for me, right?
I've seen it all. You guys are lame
That's so basic
Are you stupid?
Magazine shoot
Thank you
This content is all guess work
No, its all out now, it's really lame
At least hide it, so basic!
This prank was a big success... this is where it is!
Never seen such a Michopa
It's so hard!
It's so hard...
-Two different styles
Can Mikan advance?
Or will the short-legged Michopa win?
The results are as follows
What'll happen?
13 votes to 11 votes. The winner is Mikan
Kintaro-san, your neck is more and more like "Lu Bu"
From the Three Kingdoms
-Too mean
Too much
The comparison is correct
She should imitate imitate "Lu Bu"
"No one has done it yet" King of Imitation Showdown
The 5th round is Koji Tomita vs Razor Ramon RG
The theme is...
Morley Robertson
So hard
It's hard even from a professional point of view.
-It's super hard
A parody of Morley Robertson brought to you by Koji Tomita
Hi everyone, I'm Morley
First time meeting, please allow me to introduce myself
I am Morley, Morley Robertson
Born in America and raised by Takarazuka
Just kidding, JOKE JOKE
I love the country of Japan. Morley is good at Kanji
Occasionally someone will say to me, "Morley, you're too arrogant."
Then I'd say back to him, "You're giving off a bad vibe (kanji)."
Who is this an imitation of?
Thank you all
Thank you Koji Tomita for your performance!
The "Yutti" system
Gentleman's YUTTI
The opponent is Razor Ramon RG
Morley Robertson will put on Koji Tamaki's "Field" and sing it to you while impersonating
What's this?
How will this score?
Is this a Morley imitation?
I want to say that Morley Robertson impersonates
He is imitating Tamaki, right?
You who want to listen to Morley Robertson's impersonation?
The guy who wants to hear Morley Robertson's impersonation
The girl who wants to listen to Morley Robertson's impersonation
Stop pretending. I want to get Morley Robertson's impersonation out of the way
Don't pretend to do all the work for impersonation every day
Live strong to do impersonations
In the end he's pretty similar
I'm conveying Morley Robertson's impersonation
Morley Robertson likes the pasta the most
Who?
Thank you all
The judges looked like they were in an uproar!
Too smooth
I shaved myself
Any hair left?
There was before
You really got ready
-Yes
I will live as Morley
Do you want to live as Morley in the future?
The verdict of this very different style of Morley parody is
10 votes to 14, the winner is Razor Ramon RG
That's KOJI Tomita!
The most difficult imitation
Think it went pretty well
I should continue this one in the future
So, the final match of the 1st round
Mr. Shachuhoko VS Kanazuki
Shachuhoko is very serious
The theme is
Nobuko Iowaki
A woman?
Energy, vitality, Inowaki!
An old friend of the program
Wearing the trademark pink suit, the former politician
This person is always used
It is not easy to be so polite
The clothes are a great help
Indeed
What kind of a duel will be presented?
This person is too distinctive
Lets see Mr. Shachuhoko's Nobuko Inowaki impersonation
Energy, vitality, Nobuko Inowaki is at work!
Speaking of education, recently
Enough is enough, I'm tired of hearing how many times
Have heard it hundreds and thousands of times
What?
What is it?
What's going on?
Zakoshi
Energy, vitality Inowaki
This...
Thank you
What just happened?
Added a lot of unexpected elements
Really surprising
So strong...
Why was it added?
Take your time to ask afterwards
Interrogate, I should say
Mr. Shachuhoko, who embarrassed the whole audience, is up against
Really did
What the hell is going on?
Kanazuki
Energy, vitality, Inowaki!
Same as before
Already won, right?
It's not your first time, right?
Energy, vitality
What should we order?
Sorry, let's start with a pork chop
Energy, vitality, Inowaki
Airplane
Flight attendant, please come over
Please give me the newspaper
Ninkan
Energy, vitality, Inowaki
Inowaki, golf course
That's great, President
Energy, vitality, Inowaki
Thank you
What an impact!
What was the outcome of this chaotic first round final battle?
What a surprise!
11 vs. 13 Kanazuki-san's victory
What a close win!
Surprisingly, not much difference
Everyone was shocked too
Mr. Shachuhoko
Why did you do such a thing
In such a short amount of time
It's not easy to make such a decent sketch
So I thought I better exaggerate
Afterwards, I realized i've been watching a lot of Zakoshi's videos
-This is not good!
That's the worst thing for an imitation artist
Infected
I wondered if it would be funny to imitate it
Kanazuki is very good at this kind of thing
You said something like "any theme is fine", right?
As long as it is something alive
As long as it is a living organism
A famous quote
So cool
So, the six people who advanced to the semi-finals are the above
Who will be the winner?
What do you think?
These are not seen on parody programs
Is it true that Kanazuki has never played Inowaki?
Honestly, this one...
This level of proficiency is amazing
Very skilled indeed
Razor Ramon's finish is also very strong
What a shock!
-Shocking
It's great to leave it to the end
-His back was always turned
It makes you want to see it quicker
"No one has done it yet" King of Imitation Showdown
Semifinal Round 1 Masahiro Ehara vs Hori
The semi-finals will be songs only
Ehara is used to doing song segments, right?
That's great.
-Maybe it will be very strong
Hori has done some?
Basically, no. Not on TV
Mikidozan
Don't know it
But a strong character
Isn't it quite high?
It's hard...
The title is Lifetime Respect
Mikidozan, who made reggae music No.1 on the public records chart for the first time
So nostalgic
Does Naomi know him?
I know, he was popular when I was in elementary school
I won't lose at singing
I must win this one
No confidence at all
Seems like it'll be hellish
It's terrible
How will they do it in just 90 minutes?
First, Masahiro Ehara
I have no strengths
And hate meaningless betrayal
I also want to grow with others who respect me
hear whe mi say
Stay with me forever
So similar
Watch my talents!
Please look at me with love
Now you are my whole world
Stay with me forever
No need to fight and no need to be brave
What's this expression?
Please love me, please believe me
come again
Thank you for performing
Good singing
Strong style
Great!
The person facing off against Ehara is Hori, a stranger to songs
What a face!
I have no strengths
And hate meaningless betrayal
I also want to grow with others who respect me
Stay with me forever
Watch my talents!
Now you are my whole world
Stay with me forever
No need to fight and no need to be brave
Please love me, please believe me
Thank you for performing
This is also quite good
Both sides are really evenly matched
An unexpectedly high-level duel
Which side is the winner?
Yeah...
It's understandable
So, please, Kendo Kobayashi, cast an additional vote.
-Really?
Is it ok?
The winner is...
Hori
Is it me?
Hori did well
Really?
Although I am an amateur
I vaguely remember the scene of him sitting on the sofa and reading
In the music video
So, the one that evokes the deepest memories in me is Hori's performance
Sorry, Ehara
Thanks
Next, match 2 in the semi-finals
Maruyama Rei VS Mikan
The theme is...
Please tell us
AiNA THE END
The one from BiSH?
-Yes, BiSH
Her singing voice is now in the limelight
Her video is now a hit
I haven't heard it
I'm stuck in the era of Ayumi Hamasaki
BiSH's AiNA THE END, who has been gaining attention for her distinctive husky voice
Must be tough if you haven't heard it
Two people that are also not used to singing
How will there improvisation pan out?
Also have to memorize the lyrics
So similar
The eyes are super similar
The lies you made up at that time
What a resemblance!
Haven't had a chance to ask
Just crying on the ramp
Just a glance is all it takes
Let me see it again
Time is quietly and angrily watching
Clasping hands with each other
The sound of laughing together
I will never forget
Uncountable tears that have been shed
The character is captured well
Now the only connection with you is the same sky
And a little bit of nonsense
Thank you for performing
The semi-finalists are very strong
Really similar.
-Awesome
The next one is Mikaan, a parody artist who doesn't know AiNA THE END
Mikan also looks great
So similar
Also doing actions
Can you dance?
The lies you made up at that time
Haven't had a chance to ask
Just crying on the ramp
Just a glance is all it takes
Let me see it again
Time is quietly and angrily watching
Clasping hands with each other
The sound of laughing together
I will never forget
Uncountable tears that have been shed
Now the only connection with you is the same sky
The face is really similar
Makeup also very good
Thanks
It's hard to choose
Just so you know, this is how the semi-finals should be
Have your brain waves return to normal, Shachuhoko?
After returning to the lounge, I was comforted by so many people for the first time in my life
So, please rate them
The results are...
Surprisingly, again
Awesome
Such a duel will indeed lead to this result
It is so hard to choose
So, Kendo Kobayashi, please cast your vote
Sorry, I'll cast this vote
Winner: Mikan
Congratulations to Mikan for winning!
The details are spot on
For me, a layman, this breathing technique
I thought, "It's great to be able to notice such details"
I was quite confident
But looking at her breathing technique
When she made the sound
I thought "ah"...
A surprising performance for such a short period of time
I think this is my blind spot
The 3rd match in the semi-finals is
Very interesting
I'm looking forward to this matchup!
Razor Ramon RG VS Kanazuki
The theme is...
It's true that no one has ever done this one
Never seen it at all
-AMEMIYA
The third game of the semifinals is to imitate AMEMIYA
On December 20th, my ramen store finally
Started selling cold noodles
First is Razor Ramon RG
Prepare for summer, start in spring
Try again and again before the taste passes the test, today
On December 20th, my ramen store finally
Started selling cold noodles
Although during the process of development and production, the wife fell in love with a cowboy
I still started selling cold noodles
Too similar
The unexplained fires that occur from time to time are also unknowingly insured
Still I wanted to start selling cold noodles
A strong level
Thank you
Thank you for performing
A very serious performance
Awesome
Up against RG is Kanazuki
Prepare for summer, start in spring
Try again and again before the taste passes the test, today
On December 20th, my ramen store finally
Started selling cold noodles
Although in the process of development and production, the wife fell in love with a cowboy
But still started selling cold noodles
What is interesting about this?
The unexplained fires that occur from time to time are also unknowingly insured
I still started selling cold noodles
Thank you for performing
Not bad, you guys
Although they were both great its not a tough decision
Not tough?
As opposed to RG, who sang an unexpectedly earnest imitation here
Kanazaki unexpectedly did a lot of face art
The result is
15-3 Razor Ramon RG wins
How can there be so much difference?
RG really did well
In such a short period of time
But compared to Kanazuki
Who did you study?
AMEMIYA!
This is not sure who it was supposed to be singing AMEMIYA's song
It's been about seven years since I last sang on stage
So the three finalists are the following
This time, the theme is...
This
TKO Kimoto
So hard
And I have no advantage as a woman ah
-Very unfavorable
It's a lottery, so there's no way out
Is it ok to finish on Kimoto?
Unexpectedly, Kimoto is the final
I don't intend to disappear from everyone's view
So it's "people think I've disappeared"
Heavy topics that are not suitable for the finale of the competition
Three people have 90-minutes, what will be the result?
I don't think you're complimenting me
I wish I had more time, but it's not too late
The first time i've ever googled Kimoto
How to start...
Focus on the facial resemblance?
So, up first is Hori
The atmosphere is quite similar
Thank you for today. Thank you. Thank you
This is very good, very good, eat it
It's good, isn't it?
The place we went to the other day was also good, right?
Speaking of the other day
Did you say you wanted to praise me, praise me for being careful?
I'm getting the vibe
I am not angry at all, really not angry
I don't mind at all. I don't mind at all
But that's not quite right, is it?
Because I don't mind you saying it to me
But it would be bad if you say that to Matsumoto and Hamada
Really, I'm saying all this for your own good
I really don't mind
Eat!
Thank you for performing
I see
The angle of the neck and the upper body twisted over
This is the Kimoto I've seen on TV
Thankfully he's still got some energy
Recovered already
Can the next contestant overcome the gender barrier?
Mikan can do anything
A bit pathetic
Very strict with male junior artists
But exceptionally gentle with female artists
Good morning, please give me more advice today!
You, didn't you do a food review?
I really can't watch it anymore
You will really be out if you do not learn more...
Good morning
So cute. Cute today also!
Eh, first time doing a food review?
It's okay, it's okay. Just say it's delicious
That's pretty spot on
Very good
Last is Razor Ramon RG
Here we go again
Because it was hard to find memorable jokes from Kimoto
Can it be that similar?
I'll be singing Thrill by Tomoyasu Hotei
Because the earlier ones are too similar
A bit of anticipation
Raised the difficulty instead
Kimo Kimo Kimo Kimo Kimo Kimo's Imitation
I want to sing quickly
Please hurry up
Kimoto's Imitation
I want to sing it quickly
Thrill done like a Kimoto imitation
Kimoto's Imitation
I want to sing it quickly
I told you to hurry up!
Kimoto's imitation is okay
Kissing you on the count of three
Kimoto's Imitation
Yes, I just want to hold you
Yes, without hesitation
Kimo Kimo Kimo Kimo Kimo Kimo's Imitation
Always likes to use nasal sounds
This is no good
Three completely different TKO Kimoto appeared, what are the results?
The results are in
Here are the results
The result is
Why is it like M-1?
The winner is Hori
Thank you all
Thank you
Hori, how do you feel?
Really happy
Just simply happy
Yes, thank you all
Also scared of being shouted at by Kimoto
Please be told off
I think he will say "I don't mind but this can't be done"
What does everyone think?
This is a parody program
That's what I call a parody show.
-Don't say that
You will be scolded by Fuji and Nihon TV for saying this
Competitions should be like this
Other places will say its been done before, and will copy it
Who?
You talked about this when we were drinking before, right?
To sum up, the winner is Hori
So the first champion is Hori
Wonderful
Will it happen again?
I also want to participate in this until I die
No one loses in this competition
-Everyone benefits
But, Shachuhoko...
Accidents happen
The only thing I'm a little concerned about is
KOJI Tomita doesn't seem to have much energy
The longest-running player was eliminated in the first round.
-Lost to Razor Ramon
Overall, that is
Let's welcome the next presenter
Hello everyone
It's Sanshiro's Komiya
In terms of me on this show, you tend to think of pranks, right?
-That's true
Hora
-Yes?
Do you remember any of these?
You wont detect the sound of jingle bells when you enter a coffee shop
It's a very unimpressive trick
-Yes, it is
It was over in a flash, okay?
But it was enjoyable
-Thanks for the compliment!
Why're you drinking now?
Don't start drinking water when we're in the middle of talking
I'm really counting on you
There was also a real prank, does anyone remember it?
Some information getting leaked in a gossip magazine
About going out in Atami
They said there would be an article about it
I was super scared
And I was told by an agent that it'll be really bad
Then they said with a very poor acting skills, this is actually a trick, do not worry
I was so relieved
Sure enough, a staff member and photographer barged in with a sign
I was like, "It's that one, right? I know, I know
On the sign that was held up, it said "Real"
What the hell is "real"?
It was all another layer of the prank
It was actually published after that
It'd never been done before.
-It's true
This time, we have another "real prank" project
This is it
Real Commercial Prank
With the full assistance of Coca-Cola, one of the sponsors of the show
The participants were able to appear in a commercial for Lemondo
-Eh!?
That's the one that Hirosi Abe also starred in?
-Yes
They're gonna act?
This is a super happy "real"
-That's for sure!
It's very different from the "real" one you had, Komiya
What's up with that!?
Real Commercial Prank
Here's what happened
With the full assistance of Coca-Cola Japan
This is really awesome!
We carried out a "real prank" of being able to act in a commercial for Lemondo
This one's super popular
That must be great
But, of the five
Some will be mislead
So, the targets of the pranks were these five people
It means that someone will be able to act in it
If in such a situation
If you're doubtful then its obviously a prank
It would be very disrespectful to the sponsors, and therefore out of character
Only the last person left believing it will actually appear in the commercial
Coca-Cola is really good at this
That's what it's all about. First, each come to a meeting
The project begins
Thank you for coming all the way out here today.
-Thank you
We really wanted to create a perfect advertisement
So we'd like to ask for your help
Aren't you cold today?
I'm fat and hot, so I'm perfectly fine
Actually a little sweaty right now.
-I see
Incidentally, what are you doing in terms of the product?
I've been drinking it a lot.
-Yeah, thanks
I drink it
-Ok
Yeah, it's good
This time it's a product called Razor Lime
※The previous commercial had was a play on words using "very sharp razor" as an analogy for "Lemonade that refreshes you after drinking it."
I'm sure it's going to be tempting. I'm tempted now that I've seen the packaging
This guy's a real pain in the ass
Seriously, this is the kind of work I'd appreciate the opportunity to do
Thank you very much
He's a good liar, isn't he?
You don't have to be so obvious
There will be six tricks thrown into the mix during this deliberation
Nadal looks like the kind of guy who would love to do commercials
First
This time, we're talking about the product that we want you to endorse
The person in charge can't read the kanji for "Lemon"
It's now being endorsed by Abe
Uh...
That...
It's called Lemondo
It's a brand of lemon drink called Lemondo.
Uh-huh
That's not possible
Kotouge: I'll just leave it
This time, Mr. Oda, the product you're going to advertise?
Hmm...
It's Lemondo.
-Oh!
It's a brand of lemonade called Lemondo
-Ok
This... that...
Doesn't think it's a trick at this point
It's Lemondo
Yes, it's a commercial for Lemonade, and I'd like to cast you, Nadal
-Yes, of course. No problem at all
That's not a problem at all, is it?
At this point, all five of them choose to ignore it
Next
Since you're going to be in this commercial, I'd like to confirm a few things
Recognizing that alcohol-related matters are completely unreasonable
I hope you can answer truthfully
Have you ever been so drunk that you lost your memory?
I don't know if it's possible to drink to the point of amnesia
This is turning into a quiz
Well, I don't know, maybe once
Ah, you have, haven't you?
-Yes
That's pretty honest
Just once in a while, I guess
Ever drive after drinking?
-No, I haven't
No, right?
-No
I don't drive
You can rest assured of that
A hell of a sales pitch.
-It is
Ever been drunk and then posted on social media?
Ah, that doesn't happen.
-No way?
My predecessors have gotten into all sorts of trouble because of that
Like Kubota or something
※At the celebratory dinner after M1 2018 Kubota atweeted verbally abusive words at reviewer Emiko Uenuma
Let's not talk about this kind of thing
It's like that thing with Ichi
We've already had one incident, and we're still making the same mistakes
What are you doing? You could've kept your mouth shut.
Like Shizuru's Murakami
Always tweeting in a drunken state
It's like they are the opposite of what they should be
That's why I'll never do it
Basically, it's best not to behave like this
It's never gonna happen. It's never gonna happen
I've been really paying attention to that
Now I'm all about the money
Seriously
Ever experienced drunken violence?
No, I haven't. Not even once.
-No? Sure?
Not even the domestic violence stuff
In 2019, Yoshimitsu Tokui was found to have evaded 138 million yen in taxes over a seven-year period.
Same with, tax evasion stuff like that
Not at all
No one asked you that, did they?
Dad did use violence against mom
But i've never used violence
This guy's really honest
Mogura speaks lightly of his hard family circumstances
This part also went by unnoticed
Yeah, so far
The next one is...
Here's the contract for the performance. Please take a look at it
I can't see page three, article eight.
-Article 8...
Yeah, that's an important one
For the duration of the advertisement, you can only drink Lemondo
They were forced to sign a contract saying that they could only drink the Lemondo product for the duration of the advertisement
What do you think?
This...huh?
So that means drinking beer or something like that is a no-no, right?
-Yes, it does
And it's not okay to drink at home even if you're drinking something else.
-Not even at home
That's pretty harsh
As for the duration, it's about a month
That's ok. No problem
No problem at all
I don't drink much anyway
I'll just have this
I'll contribute to sales
-Thank you
It's perfectly fine. That's what I'm drinking at home
There's no problem at all
Oh, no problem, no problem. I think I've heard that somewhere
Don't drink anything else even at home? There's no such thing, is there?
Compared to the four's unexpectedly oblivious reaction
For the duration of the advertisement, you can only drink Lemondo
What's going on here...
In terms of content?
Just anything with alcohol in it...?
Ah, I think we found someone. Do you think there's something wrong?
Oda, he began to suspect something was wrong long ago
Hold on a second. What's going on here?
What's wrong with you?
Yeah, okay, okay
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Is something wrong?
No, no, no, no. There's nothing wrong with that
Hold on a second. What's going on here?
Showing a little bit of skepticism, he nonetheless quickly retreated, just scraping by
But it's getting dangerous
And the rest of them, even in the face of this unreasonable contract
Finally, they all signed the contract
How could this happen?
Using the fingerprint and everything...
This time, the role I want you to play
It's an office worker role
Well...
It's called Lemondo
The setting is, after a long day's work
The guy in charge still can't pronounce the word "lemon."
The feeling you will be evoking
Is that all you want is drink after work
Which progresses to you ultimately drinking the lemonade
Ok
So far, only Kotouge, Hashimoto, and Mogura have not suspected any of the three traps
After all, they're gonna be shooting a commercial
And then there's Oda, who's beginning to suspect that it's a trick
Whereas Nadal is bending over backwards to please them
Later
Although its rare since you've only just agreed
We will shoot the commercial now
Despite having just had the meeting the filming starts immediately
That's obviously impossible
Yes, it's impossible
Totally, uh, totally fine.
-Is that so? Thank you
I'm glad you are so motivated
It's not something you can shoot on a whim, okay?
Just ten minutes after, the commercial is shot
The director's attire is too bizarre
Bizarrely dressed CM director arrives
Hey, this is too weird
They do come around once in a while
Thank you
As the situation accelerates in an outrageous direction
That's a lot of staring
He can't help but stare
Not only that, but ...
Didn't they make a set for the last commercial?
Uh-huh
Why don't we shoot it at an izakaya this time?
The location hasn't been decided until the day
Really?
Like in Ebisu or something. There's probably a lot of them there
No problems with the car or anything like that?
We've got a car coming now.
-Really? Really? Okay, I get it
What do you think?
Well...
I think it's OK if you go with that momentum
As we've been talking
I think you're going to be very busy
If there's no problem, you can head for the car...
What is this!?
What's wrong with you? What's wrong with you?
He said it.
-And very clearly
What's going on here?
Hey, no
This... is too fake!
Oh, come on. There you go
It's so fake...
What is this?
How dare he say that!
Instead of going with it, he couldn't help but shout
That's why Oda is hereby disqualified
Mogura, he's like the type that never knows what's going on, right?
-Aah! Aah!
Kodoki's a veteran, so even if he finds out, he'll just go with the flow, won't he?
Even if he knows what's going on
That means that even if you know it's a trick, you still go along with it, right?
What is this?
-Huh? What's wrong?
Although Oda is disqualified at this point
This... is too fake!
Hey, it's not fake
I even told my wife
Coca-Cola commercial
You'd be happy sure
I was so happy for me
Lets continue, then
Your passion comes through loud and clear
I think it's a good idea to shoot this now
So, he was taken to an izakaya
After all, it's a rare opportunity. Let's keep him with us for a while longer
I can't believe it didn't end after him shouting like that
Your mind is already broken, right?
Incidentally, the other members
Despite having just had the meeting the filming starts immediately
You can book the venue now, right?
-No problem
I can't believe you can still book it.
-Yes
There are plenty of izakayas in Tokyo, so I'm sure its fine
Oh, really? That's pretty fast
Just like that. Hashimoto has started to comment subtly
So we're actually going to shoot at the place?
-Yes
That's perfectly fine
Ahhh it's totally fine, anything...
Its impossible to tell what they're thinking
After this
As for the costumes, I think they're ready
We were give your measurements beforehand, and you're supposed to wear a suit
So now it's being prepared
I think there's a store for that. Let's go there first
Okay, that's a good point...
Thank you...
Unsure if its a prank or not
Nadal's excitement is noticeably lowered
After all, I want it to be the best-selling drink in Japan
Thank you
It's really appreciated
Yeah, I'll do my best
A man like this, who was so excited just a moment ago
Okay, that's a good point...
Thank you...
It's only been 30 minutes
The tone of his voice has now plummeted
All in all, there are five of them, including Oda, who's already disqualified
All embark in a car in search of an izakaya to use as a photo location
And that's when this happened
Ah, looking for the camera
Looking for the camera properly
He's found it
You've found it!
As soon as Oda gets in the car, he starts looking for hidden cameras
After that
Ah, there's an izakaya with a nice atmosphere
Ah, it's okay.
-It's got a nice atmosphere
Looks comfortable
Go to the place to get permission
After finding an izakaya with a nice atmosphere
The staff get permission from the store
This isn't a venue for a celebration party, is it?
This is unbearable
What's going on?
I'm sure that's what happened
Well, that's certainly the way it's going to turn out
It's not like, "Can you please shoot a scene here?"
It's an advertisement
Seemingly having made up his mind
Even in this situation, Hashimoto decides to go with the flow
And what about Nadal, who already thinks it's a prank?
No good
I'm sorry. No permit
First of all, the owner of the store wasn't there, and secondly, the request was too sudden, so they refused
Looking at the camera!
Surely looking for the cameras
I guess we'll have to go to Ebisu after all
Like Oda, this man confirmed the existence of the hidden camera
After that, they moved to the 2nd location
Is this place a bar?
-Is that a bar?
I wonder if it's open for business?
Well, I'm gonna go see what's going on
He can't help but laugh at this stupid conversation
It's true, you'd have to laugh
Already pretending
Not only that, but ...
Oh, oh, oh, coming out
Uh-oh. OK?
OK！？
Really? That's amazing
How can that be possible?
Looks like it's okay
Oh, oh, that's great
As this place agreed to do the shoot, it was chosen as the location
So, they've finally arrived at the izakaya where they'll be shooting
I'm sure you're thirsty now
A little bit
Would you like some tea or something?
-Well...
Is there an AD around?
-I'll drink anything
Third AD (79 years old)
Advanced Age AD
Thank you
So old but only 3rd AD still?
Is this the AD?
Third AD, 79 years old
Well...it's an AD
Been doing this a long time
How much do you like being an AD?
A living fossil
Meanwhile
Oda, who was disqualified while still in the conference room
You're out, why're you still here?
Is there an AD out there?
AD?
Oh, there is
Do you have any tea for Oda? Tea or water is fine
There's nothing here. See if you can get something to drink
Eh? ...AD?
-Yes, AD
No thats just weird
What is this scene!?
Shouted clearly
What's all this!?
It takes a little guts
What!?
It's a commercial...
No, no, absolutely no way
What the hell is this?
It's a weird commercial shoot, but it's a real commercial shoot
It's a real commercial
It's just that Oda doesn't want to cooperate at all anymore
It's not his fault
It ends here
And we tell him it's all true
You've worked hard
What's this?
May I ask what you are working on today?
I was going to... come and do a commercial for Coca-Cola's Lemondo
I don't know what it is
Ready?
-Yes
I don't know exactly which program...
Yes you do
But it's been exposed for a long time, and we've been filming it all along
"It's been exposed for a while"
That's why we're here to reveal the project to Oda
Actually, the commercial shoot thing that's going on today
It's real
Can't make any sense of it
Too much, its too much
What? What? What? What are you talking about?
No, it's not. It's not. It's not
It's real
No, no, no
It is true
That's not true. That's not true
Eh? Eh?
No, right?
No, no, no, no
So, this whole commercial thing today, it's really...
He's done for
You were asked to do a commercial.
-No, no, no
By the way, who are you? May I ask?
What... what is this? What do you do?
We're from Wednesday Downtown
No, no, no, no. You guys, wait
Wait a minute. Wait a minute
You say that like its nothing
Eh?
Wednesday...
So, we carefully explained the project to Oda
And the sad fact that he's out
It'll take a while to figure it out
As a result
It's impossible... it's impossible for me to ignore this situation
I've been holding back
I was going to kick off
But then I thought, what if it's true?
This is the "what if?"
Seriously, no way!
I've told everyone. I've told my wife everything
I said, "I got a Coca-Cola commercial."
This is the worst
So far there are four left
Who exactly will end up starring in the commercial?
It's Oda first
I'm simply disgusted to see Hashimoto trying his best to get this commercial
It does feel a little bit like that
It's a bit overshadowed by Nadal, though, and Hashimoto's got his hands full
In terms of roles
The tsukkomi people might be more likely to say something
You can't help it, can you?
I can't help it
If someone couldn't pronounce "lemon" i'd definitely say something
So, excluding Oda, there are four left
From now on, it's officially time to move on to the shoot
The content of this advertisement is
After ordering lemonade at the izakaya
The result is a bitter or sour drink
Content that requires a quick retort
The content of the ad
So, let's start with the Lemondo scene
So big
Huge
The board is unusually large
Are you okay, Kotouge?
I'm fine. It's too big for me
It's always been like this.
-All the time?
You always use such a big one?
-Yes.
It's in the way
Already complaining
I think it's redundant
Faced with an oversized board
Kotouge can't help but comment
And Hashimoto did the same
Seems like he's gonna say something
I haven't even said "ready--" yet
"Ready, set, go" is followed by the board, remember?
That's the first time I've ever heard a command for a board
Ok, start!
I'm sorry
When should I start?
You can still see it. The board
It's too big
Is it okay to start when the board is moved?
-It's fine
Because its a little big, and when it's moved out of the way...
It's moving slowly
"Because its a little big" he says...
Its impacting the shoot badly
By the time Nadal gets here
The look on Nadal's face
Please go faster
"I can't"
Ok, start!
Laughing
The usual
Here you go
You were laughing a bit at the start
Can we get a new marker board?
That... board
That one's a little too big. And the AD is a little old
That's not very polite, is it?
AD (72 years old)
That's all we've been using, it's all we have...
What do you care about his age?
He's too old
Don't say he's too old
Wait...
Everyone get ready
Still ready to act?
Ok, start!
The usual
Here you go
I don't think they're going to be able to shoot this scene
Uh...
The AD is in the shot
In light of the screw-up
These three all couldn't help but comment
Impossible not to
What about Mogura?
Next up, Mogura says, "The usual"
And then the shopkeeper says, "Here you go," and passes the drink over
Concentrating
Ok
We'll start as soon as we're ready
He probably thinks that's how it's done in commercials
Ok, start!
Maybe it is
The usual
Here you go
Not bad at all!
Mogura is great
Ok, cut!
So, only Mogura performed naturally
Ah, not bad
Has he realized the prank and is simply playing along?
Or has he just presumed everything is as it should be?
Can't tell
At this point it's impossible to confirm which
Not thinking about anything, is he
Yeah
A further trap for these four men is now set
Let's take a little break
Ah, okay
It's break time
I'll take one
Oh, I see
The staff start drinking
That's bad
There's no way that's gonna happen
Absolutely not
I don't think i'd be able to hold on now
This isn't going to last, is it?
It's already a mess
That's kind of...
Yes
They're drinking between takes
It's mainly targeted at young people
I see
Eh...
It's okay if we all let loose and drink?
Despite being just a break
The staff start drinking
Though it was a little light, they commented
Comparatively
Ah, that's good
Come on, its too much
Not a word is said here
He might even be thinking, "I'd like to drink it, too."
Really?
Mogura stares with envy at the drinking staff members
Yeah
Mogura is good
Among them, Kotouge, basically switched to tsukkomi-mode upon arriving at the izakaya
Looks like he's ready to fight
Thank you for your hard work
What's the point of talking about hard work at this point?
Isn't this a break?
That sound
Anyone would laugh at that, wouldn't they?
It's still working hours, isn't it?
They're all drunks
It's just a break from work now, right?
I've never seen anyone drink on the job
He said it
It's over. It's over. The commercials done for
Bad work environment
Everyone's tired
He's doing it
No, no, that's not the problem
You shouldn't drink just 'cause its tiring
So true
That's why everyone's drinking though, isn't it?
They're still shooting after though, right?
Yes, of course
It's gonna be bad, right?
Can they still work?
-Yes
Something bad's about to happen
A bit disorganized and undisciplined
A powerful statement
He's said it
So
I don't think we're going to be able to get away with this
This is really...
I won't say anything, of course
Well, well, well, well. That's it, I guess, isn't it?
It's not like that, Kotouge
As strong words have been spoken
Kotouge is eliminated here
You have to look past it!
Who can look past this?
Who can!?
So, here we tell him everything
You've worked hard
Well, well, well...
Well, that's how it is, isn't it?
"That's how it is" What is it?
They all look pleased with themselves at the start
The look of a winner
After that, they'll become a loser
Its Wednesday, right?
It's Wednesday, right?
You are correct
Of course it'd be Wednesday
Kotouge recognizes the staff
First of all, I've never seen such a spontaneous commercial shoot
Indeed
Sure enough, he mistook the commercial shoot for a prank
Today is actually a shoot for Coca-Cola's Lemondo product
What?
The biggest trick of all
Eh?
It's true
Eh? True?
Eh? Really?
Really
So, what was filmed today will actually be on TV
It's a real commercial
Eh? Really?
Getting angsty now
However
You suspected it was a prank
So you're out
Out
-Yes
Out...
Why?
I'm a little confused by this prank
He didn't know there was anyone else
So, Kotouge is now also qualified
So, the joke is on the remaining three contestants
Next up is a shot of the owner mistakenly serving another drink
Yeah, that's it
So bitter! Not this one. The usual one
Ok, cut
It's a second over...
I'm sorry.
-No, no, no. It's totally fine
Wow, it's really that strict
Let's go ahead and get another one
Yeah, that's fine with me
It's still the same board
Ok, start!
Yeah, that's it
So bitter! Not this one. The usual one
The timing is still not right.
-The timing? Ok, got it
Half a second over.
-Half a second
Have to drink repeatedly
Like any other commercial, the director just won't let it go
This development forces the individual to taste the unpleasant drink repeatedly
Cut!
Super bitter
So tough
Compare to the two who don't complain...
Little scary
Get ready
Ok, start!
Yeah, yeah, that's it
It's bitter. It's not that. The usual!
So bitter! Are you serious!
He's angry
So bitter!
It's an uncomfortable thing to say
Better for it be real...
-No need
Tastes like medicine
No need for it
I can act without this
We wanted to make it as real as possible
Not speaking politely anymore
I can't drink this more than a couple of times
He's really pissed off
Nadal complains and asks to change the drink
As a result
Second AD (84 years old)
The second one is older than the third one
Get ready
Ok, start!
Yeah, yeah, that's it
So bitter...
That... director...
It's the same as earlier.
-The same?
Is it that bad?
Honestly, I don't need to suffer so much. I can do it without this
I'm really shocked. I can't even say my lines
Because it's too bitter
Is this one okay?
This one will do
Is it okay if I try it first?
Yes, yes, yes
Testing
It's still bitter
Hey, AD!
I don't mean to sound harsh
But its really bitter
Her sense of taste must be failing her
What a foul mouth
The AD's tastebuds have deteriorated
How dare you!?
AD?
Don't refer to them as "AD"!
You're the one who hired them
It's not their fault. It happens to all of us when we get old
This is not the right mood
He blames the senior AD one minute and then speaks up for her the next
Nadal has his hands full
Yeah, yeah, that's it
So sour! Sour!
AD!
Our AD works hard
Please be generous. I apologize in advance
We'll do better
You've worked so hard
I can't support myself on just my pension alone
Ah really...
Can you ask the AD not to talk?
"I can't support myself on my pension alone."
What's he doing?
I'm being talked to through the board
Really...
What are you doing?
It makes me feel bad about myself
Ah, I'm sorry
What's going on here?
What the hell are you doing?
Really? What's going on here?
His suspicion is now clear
Ah, it's over
Can't do it anymore
Nadal loses here
There's something wrong this guy
What the hell are you doing?
You've worked hard
I know everything
I can tell
It's like interrogating a criminal
You can tell?
Pretty much figured it out
Got it?
-Hold up the sign already
Are you sure?
By the way, do you know what this is?
There's no commercial at all, is there?
Eh?
-There's no commercial at all, right?
So cool
And what makes you feel that way?
He's like a detective
It all started with "let's film here"
That was enough
It was a real mess, right?
I shouldn't have been so hopeful all along
I thought this might be a trick!
It's so messed up!
I really love doing commercials!
To Nadal, who has cut off the last vestiges of hope
We reveal that it was all, in fact, "real"
What's wrong?
It's obviously your own fault
Eh?
It's true.
-Really?
It was true, but...
Nadal, you suspected since the midway point, right?
You made the odd comment here and there
I knew it was a trick.
-And sometimes you laughed
What's wrong with that?
Eh, why am I disqualified?
Why do I feel like I'm out of the race?
You're out
I feel like I'm out
I don't get it. I really don't
They want to work with artists who can be more active in filming
That's what the sponsors think
-I was going with it! I was cooperating!
Lemondo Coca-Cola!
Please let me do the commercial! Please!
I've lasted this long!
I've been working on it for a while now with a glimmer of hope
No, no, no. Not enough
So, you're out
Did I do something wrong?
He's back to his old ways
So, only Mogura and Hashimoto are left
That means these two survived the second AD
Now, we reach the final stage
Song and dubbing recording
Lets do the voice-over for the product summary at the end of the commercial
And then there's the recording of the theme song
Lemon lemon lemondo lemonade~
Eh? Wait a minute
It's delicious to drink, lemon lemonade~
Awful
The advertisement song is a complete copy
Lemon lemon lemondo lemonade~
Should say something
This tune is the tune
Lemon lemon lemonade~
Gotta dance too
It's delicious to drink, lemon lemonade~
It's not being filmed, but it's got dance moves
That's a lot of excitement
Lemon lemon lemonade~
It's all good
Impressive
Thank you. It's not a hard song to sing, is it?
Uh, no, it's not
This won't be filmed, will it?
This one's off camera
Don't shoot
It's better not to be filmed
It has that "Demai" feeling...haven't you seen it? The Demai commercial
Couldn't help it after all
Is it plagiarizing?
It was inspired by that
Its a little embarrassing
It's better without images
I'd be perfectly fine without the video
Then it's fine.
-Yeah, it's totally fine
Next
"Lemondo is popular!" Say it in 2.5 seconds!
Lemondo is popular!
30 versions of one line
A little more calm
Lemondo is popular!
That's a wide range of voices
All kinds of recordings
Lemondo is popular!
Takeshi Kitano?
OK
-Thank you
Thank you
Which to use?
A prevailing feeling of "something's up"
But the final duo persevere seriously
Mogura is trying really hard
Therefore, the final outcome will be determined by the reaction to being informed
See what the response is?
Its up to the "I knew it!"
You've worked hard
How're you feeling?
No way...
Something's not right
Is that so?
No, it's very wrong
He doubted
That's too bad, it really is...
My heart is so tired...what is this?
In fact, today's commercial shoot
So it's all fake?
-Well...
It's real
Wait a minute. I don't know what's going on
It's all true
Indeed
Dumbstruck
It's too out-there
I still don't get it
In that case, you don't have to come and talk to me, do you?
What? "Real" What?
What are you talking about?
That means it's all true
So it's just a fun day of work...
There's actually no commercial, right?
There is
It's real
Eh?
Eh? Will it really be aired? Eh?
Is it really possible to broadcast with the way you're filming it?
That song too?
-Yes
Is the song also true?
Ah, but isn't that the one from Demaican?
At this point, Hashimoto started to strongly doubt "reality"
Ah, still skeptical
In contrast
No response so far
Mogura, the man who still doesn't know his true feelings
You've worked hard
Saw the board?
No no no no
It feels like he's just reacting
How does it feel? Today
Eh? No way...
Still believed it!
Really?
No way this... eh?
This is a prank?
What do you think? Today's work
So shocked
It's a Coca-Cola commercial
Is there something wrong going on?
There was some strange things
Undoubtedly felt something was wrong
That's for sure
It's okay. It's okay
But I thought maybe this is just how commercials work
All the documents were signed
In fact, the commercial shoot that took place today
Was real
Eh!?
Really?
-Really
Not bad
Very refreshed
Eh? Really?
-Really
You're happy, aren't you?
Really?
Who're you asking?
So happy!
Eh? What's going on?
If it was real, there'd be no need for this
It's all true
So we're here to tell you it's true
I've been treating it like a real job since the beginning
I've always believed it to be true
You didn't laugh much during the whole thing
I feel like if I laughed or said, "That's not right," or something like that...
The company bigwigs are there
Maybe they'd replace me
Very serious
Thought it was real
Mogura, who shows his heart for his sponsors to the very end
Is confirmed for the Lemondo commercial
Great!
How about that song?
Well, it's Demaican.
-Yes, it is
I just don't feel like it goes well
It's the same as Demaican
Ah, Demaican!
Ah the take-out one
Didn't realize at all
Ah, indeed
A little naive
Wow, it's the one with Mr. Hamada
It is
Wow, really?
Eh? Demaican is red clothes, right?
-Yes
It's true that if you have money in your eyes, you are blinded to a lot of things
That's it
Congratulations
It turned out to be Mogura
Indeed
His reaction when the board was lifted
It's a total comedian killer, isn't it?
My fellow warriors, who have fought many battles
They all ended up tilting their heads
So will any be aired?
What's going on? Do they have to do another commercial?
It was planned beforehand
So regardless it was still a serious shoot
At the time of the shoot, Mogura just didn't know what was going on
I see
So he was later informed that he is going to be in the commercial
We can have a look now
So, Mogura was informed that he was confirmed for the commercial
Hello
Eh? Is the advertisement finalized?
The commercial will be featuring Mogura
Super happy
That's great!
In retrospect
That's great. Is it true?
-It's real
Good job
Wow!
It's true now, and it was true before
Ah, yeah
So, here it is
I'm looking forward to it
The usual
Here you go
Yeah, yeah, that's it
Really using this music
So sour! Not this one. The usual one.
Here you go
Yeah, yeah, that's it
So bitter! Not this one. The usual one
Here you go
Yeah, yeah, that's it
Delicious!
Full marks for freshness!
Lemondo, hugely popular
This will be on the air
Really using this?
Wow. So happy
It's awesome
So there's a paycheck or something, right?
-Of course
Payment for advertising, right?
Wow!!
That should be a lot
Yeah
It's Coca-Cola, after all!
Lemondo is a big seller, too
The look in his eyes when faced with gold
That's something to look forward to
Have you thought about what you're going to spend it on?
I have a second child on the way
Really?
Around the end of March
I need to buy the crib
I'll watch my kid sleeping in the crib while drinking Lemondo
That's a great use for it
Yeah
That's good
Will it really air?
Starting today, even though it's limited to TBS
It's about to go on the air
So, the staff at Wednesday Downtown is a little bit out of their minds, too
But it's probably Coca-Cola that's the craziest
Demaican also agreed, right?
That is unclear
Don't be unclear about that part
I'm not sure.
-Don't be unclear about that
I don't know about these things
The circumstances of the trick might change a bit
What do we do after that?
It's bad if you're unsure even at the point of the commercial being out
What if I'm asked to sing "Soft, Soft, Softbank" later?
I'm not sure what to do
By the time this program airs, there'll probably be commercials on the air
I think it's gonna be on after this, so please watch
The usual
Here you go
Yeah, yeah, that's it
So sour! Not this one. The usual one
Here you go
Yeah, yeah, that's it
So bitter. Not this one. The usual one
Here you go
Yeah, yeah, that's it
Delicious!
Full marks for freshness!
Lemondo, hugely popular!
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03