Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Kamaitachi!
The theory we bring this time is a second edition
I see
It is this:
The 2nd If someone close by is dishing out good gossip, you'll forget work and be stuck in place
Had to do a 2nd one quickly
-Yes
Yeah, the first one hasn't been aired yet
Indeed
If it had been, then no one would fall for it
Your explanation is very accurate
But that said, the first time this guy really sat there completely motionless
Really
The show's AD had a relationship with an actress
The topic of the relationship between the AD and the actress of the TV drama without saying the name to keep him there
We tested how long he'd stay there listening
He listened especially carefully
Really listened very carefully
With program staff waiting for him to join a meeting
Unbelievably he was there for 16 minutes
I waited for so long, but they did not say the name
Who was it? It was hidden in such a roundabout way
Don't sleep with ADs that talk like this
What does everyone think?
If you encounter this situation in a cafe
In the TMC lounge, there's a kind of curtain that separates
You can hear everything the person next to you says.
-Yeah
Once an idol asked her agent "Please let me stop blogging"
No, right?
"I really want to stop" like that
I did listen there without moving a muscle
On a side note
Hamaye mistakenly entered the women's room at TMC
Screams of the Hinatazaka46 member's could be heard from outside
This is really off-topic
Off-topic indeed
The gossip challenge returns again
Also
I want to be a "Troublemaker" YouTuber
If a child says "I want to be a YouTuber who gets into trouble"
No parent will say "Since it's your choice..." and show their support
This theory will be tested
Once again, if someone close by is dishing out good gossip, you'll forget work and be stuck in place
This time, we also called the verification target to the coffee shop inside TBS under the name of a fake meeting
While there, the meeting location changes and they are informed they need to get there as soon as possible
Will they continue to stay and listen to the neighboring gossip?
The first target is...
Okubo
Will definitely listen
What kind of gossip do you plan to use this time?
A classic topic like female ADs having sex with celebrities
Let's cut to the chase and start the gossip
I went to a hotel with a comedian some time ago
Comedian?
It's bad, right? What should I do?
Who is it? Which comedian?
Still considered very popular
Which one?
Seems to be listening a bit
Do not tell anyone!
I won't
Gradually approaching
-Sitting position changed
To tell you the truth, it was cheating
That's a problem!
Head up
After hearing the keyword "cheating", her eyes change
This time the tactic of naming the person is adopted
Don't tell anyone!
Like I'd say anything!
It's Hitori
Eh?
Hitori!
Ah, wait a minute I'm a little confused
Gekidan Hitori?
Don't use my name without permission!
Eh? Eh?
It's bad, isn't it?
Look at her face
Really, Hitori?
Yes
This is clearly a sigh
Obviously shocked
It was a blow
Probably thinking, "Even Hitori?"
Now it is especially troublesome
Why?
Because he has more than one lover
Eh?
No way!
I've heard some rumors
It seems that the relationship with his wife is not great now
This is annoying
She makes a sound as if to say "don't say such things out loud"
Who is the other person?
How can I put it? It's a big name
If it's a big name, is it also an artist?
A look of "stop it!"
Yeah, yeah, it's bad, right?
Okubo is a good person
Wait, slow down. Who is it?
I'll tell you later
Using the name of the cheating partner as bait
Okubo is really a good person
And so, the manager calls
Sorry, the staff just contacted me
The meeting has been changed to the 4th floor of TBS
Please come here
The 4th floor?
Yes, we'll wait for you on the 4th floor
Now, she must get to the new location as soon as possible
But will she instead stay and listen to the gossip?
The challenge begins now
Good-looking?
Not really like a gyaru type, more like "clean" type
Clean-cut
Hitori seems like he likes that type
-It's true
Indeed, seems like he doesn't have a preference for gyaru-type
But aren't you a gyaru?
Am I a gyaru?
No?
Seems kind of obvious you are?
Maybe an age thing
He likes young ones?
I don't want to do this... bad-mouth Shogo
※A member of the same troupe whose real name is Kawashima Kengo
What? This is cheating?
But he's been especially kind to me
Looking to confirm who they are
Looks a bit annoyed
Once the name "Shogo" came out she seems even more annoyed
Angry?
Angry at the rude woman
You're so gentle, Okubo
She listens for 5 minutes as the other cheater has not yet been revealed
5 minutes is quite a long time
The woman is also dating someone
She's married too?
So it looks like both sides are cheating?
-Yeah
Unexpectedly, the topic turns to "both parties are cheating"
And Okubo's features become squeezed together
So emotionally invested
But
Stood up!
Ah, although its a bit sudden pretend to start saying the name
I'll give you the name, then
Eh, really?
Never tell anyone, ok?
-I won't!
So, although she left her seat and got up
She is stuck in place in order to get the answer
A few more hints
How can I say it? If the class is analogous, the number of students is about 1~15
No phone call
The name is "a"
The name starts with the "a" column or row of the kana syllabary
Say it quickly!
Non-existent phone call
That's too broad a scope
So its the "a" column or row of the kana syllabary
"A" column or row of the kana syllabary?
Eh? "A" column or row of the kana syllabary?
An "A" column or row of the kana syllabary person
Why did you stand up and not go?
If you want to go, go
Sit down, sit down, its better, right?
Yeah!
Unwrapping wet wipes
Ah but the person i'm thinking of is not married
What will happen?
Yeah, they're married
Moreover, her husband is also a famous person
Both sides are in the industry?
Her husband still has a lot of fans
Giving up?
Who is it?
Although stuck for a while
She eventually leaves the store
So, we reveal the truth
Okubo
Both sides cheated on the other one, do you know?
Aibu Saki, right?
She got that from the "a"
I was really angry
This is inside the TV station!
Talking out loud about cheating!?
It's really not right
So you coughed to remind them
"Don't say this." "People can hear you."
It doesn't matter if she's a TBS employee or a production company employee
She's probably stupid and a bad person
Really stupid and bad
She looked a bit like Osawa Akane
Not sure how but just seems a bit similar
So, we explained the project
Ah, I see
Talking about comedians
Such an excellent person
Hitori is such a nice person so I really couldn't stand it
I had the feeling of regret
So nice!
That aspect was conveyed
-You got it, right?
You had the look of "Not Hitori too!"
There's so many talented people that get mixed up in this sort of thing
It was Watanabe all over again
Yes, it really gave me the feeling of another Watanabe
So, Oasis Okubo's record of 7 minutes and 11 seconds temporarily ranks first
7 minutes is still quite long
The next target is
Nadal
He loves to gossip
This is cheating-realted news
Ugh, no good
What's going on?
I was just contacted by a published
They sent me the article
Hasn't been released yet
Its cheating news
Eh... cheating?
Yes
This time it's a really big deal
Quite a surprising person
Eh, who is it?
You absolutely wont tell anyone, right?
Tell me, I won't tell anyone
How to put it...
Mikitty
Me this time?
Eh, Mikitty? Is it Miki Fujimoto?
You're too loud.
-Sorry, sorry, sorry
Yes, Miki Fujimoto
Uh, really?
I can't believe it! Poor Shoji!
Listening
Really? Even Mikitty would cheat?
The eyes are moving
Black eyes are wandering
Really listening!
A sudden shock for a famous couple
Nadal consumes the gossip wholeheartedly
Then
It's not impossible if the people are similar
This kind of thing can happen
Yes, indeed
Put the headphones on
This is a gimmick, right?
Wearing earphones as if not listening to other people talking but is in fact eavesdropping
Everyone is doing it!
Letting one's guard down here
But the cheating partner is also unimaginable
Is it a problem?
Eh? What's wrong?
Who was the cheating partner?
Took the right earphone out
So, as the name comes up, the phone call comes in
As usual, he is told the meeting location has changed
Now, the challenge begins
Who is the other one?
Big name actor?
Almost... an actor
Famous? Someone I know?
Listen carefully
I'm certain you know them
Eh, who is it...
Recently been in comedy shows
Oh, oh, oh, that means they're on variety shows too, right?
Really listening carefully!
Thinking about who it is
No intention of leaving at all
Such a serious expression
This time
Excuse me
Can I have an iced coffee?
Only wants to drink now
He should only be wanting to hurry up and get to work
In this state
Ordered an iced coffee
Ordered an iced coffee!
Seems like he'll be here for a while
But if you order a drink
So 6 minutes passed with his iced coffee and gossip
You can stay very naturally
Then, the agent calls again
It is difficult to do press conferences
It's almost 8 minutes
Needs to be done formally
He hung up
Its not good to just hang up
Here comes a LINE message
Sorry, my stomach hurts a little. I'll be right there when I get out of the bathroom
He said he's in the toilet
Speaking as if he's in the toilet
That's too much, why the toilet?
But 8 minutes into the process
Is it really a name I would know?
Absolutely. Famous
Surely not
Then tell me
Ok, i'll tell you
You'll really tell me? Who is it?
Let's just say the initials are T
-T?
He's stopped
This posture is not normal, right?
Who stands like this?
Is it a last name or a first name with the initial T?
Yes, yes, the initials of the surname is T
Who is it... can't guess
A few more hints
No, you guess
T... first name initial is T...
It looks like the answer will not be given
So he leaves
It's been 9 minutes, so people are waiting
Thank you for your hard work
You were called, right?
What? What's going on here?
I'm completely confused about what is happening
What is this?
You really do care!
Of course I care
But he didn't say anything at all
Has your impression of Miki Fujimoto changed?
Aren't all idols like this?
So Nadal's 9 minutes 07 seconds record is temporarily ranked first
The next target is
New York's Shimada
Probably because of drug arrests and the like
This guy is interested more in the dark side of show business
I'm in trouble this time
You know the show I'm working on, right?
The one that has just started?
-Yes, yes
I told you there would be idols in the show, right?
A male idol
Just a little while ago, during the shoot
One person didn't show up.
-Late?
No
They were arrested
Arrested? Handcuffed?
Handcuffed and taken away
Really?
It was so bad
Who is it?
I'll tell you later
So, as a rule, the name is again used to keep them hanging around
As usual, he is told the meeting location has changed
The challenge begins
Now the other members of the group seem to have been told
That the police are "watching them"
This multi-person group
Not only the one who was taken away, the other members were also being looked at
But they don't seem the type at all
Innocent-looking boys?
More that type, yeah
You're blatantly listening!
Look a bit naughty though
Rather than being naughty
Turn your face a little better, right?
They're not actually innocent
Basically facing that way
He's not even hiding that he's listening with this posture
Its like three people talking
A TV drama scene
Three people in the same frame
Here's a big tip for you
"The person who sang this song", and take your iPhone and pretend to show it to him
Okay, here's a hint
This song, this song
If you look like this, you'll be found out
Really looking!
Don't look so freely like that
You can't look like that!
You're really looking!
So obvious
Everyone will want to see
Start humming
Please hum it in a very low voice
You got it?
-Well... not really
A little more, a little more humming
Thinking about it
Hurry up and go to the meeting!
Just a melody with no right answer
While thinking about what the song is, another 3 minutes have passed
At this time
Let's go, give up
Ah, he's stoop up
Please say "The girlfriend was arrested too"
The girlfriend was also arrested together
She's an actress
It should be worse for her
Of course it's bad, because there are in a lot of commercials
Will he go? Finally gone?
Ah, he's gone!
Wow, he's really gone!
The truth is revealed
What is this?
Don't you care that the girlfriend was arrested too?
It was an actress
I don't care if it's an actress, but...
It would have been good if the information had come out 30 seconds earlier
Did you listen to the humming?
I listened to it
What song do you think it is?
How can I know that? Just from humming
Not at all!
So, the final target is...
Panther's Ogata
Ogata
The topic that will most draw his attention
I think it also has to be about his wife
That's right
He has an abnormal sense of jealousy
If its about her cheating
Affair-related topics
I think he will definitely be stuck in place
Is that ok?
It's scary. It's scary to say that
Heard something from a weekly journalist
Wait. What's the news?
The report is not yet out
Hmm?
Cheating-related
Cheating?
Shh-
The performance is really natural
But this time is different
Good performance
Not from the celebrity themself
Oh...
It's the celebrity's wife who cheated
I see...
It's bad
Just a moment ago he glanced over
Its like the fishing rod bobbing slightly
Now he's definitely hooked
So, he's informed of the location change
And the challenge begins
This lady, how to put it, is about thirty-something years old
Thirty-something years old
What a great way to act out a conversation
It's really good, like the real thing
Previously did clothing-related work
What kind of person is the lady's cheating partner?
Because that person is a comedian
As a comedian...
Comedian?
Sometimes shooting takes place at their home
Moved
Look how he's shifting in his chair
Just shifted to the side
Recording takes place in their home quite a lot
So there are directors who have been there many times
So that's how it happened
Good performance
Wait a minute, wait a minute, who the hell is it?
I'll tell you later
You have to tell me
Already looks like he thinks they're talking about him
To be honest, at this time, he is probably sure in his head that it is him
That said, it is a comedian who reacts in a funny way
How can I tell from that?
Not a lot of information
Moved again
Gradually moving to the corner of the frame
Is it Abareru?
Ah...
It would have been nice if it was Abareru
It seems not. You're reacting in the wrong way
Yeah
Is that Saito from Jungle Pocket?
Ah, the reaction type, huh?
Since there seems to be absolutely no intention to go to the meeting
He's thinking it's him!
He is called again to remind him
They also have a young daughter
The daughter is still at home...
He hung up straight away
No way, just hung up!
Angry
You can't do that. Call again. Please call again
That's no good
Really no good
Work is waiting!
Is it Degawa?
No, not Degawa
That's right, it really shouldn't be
I feel wrong after saying that
Wow, seems painful
Ogata seems almost completely sure they are talking about him
There's no one else
With the conversation carefully avoiding names for now
After 6-minutes he has reached an almost catatonic state
That's impressive
So at this time
A devastating occurrence
Fill-in-the-blank type hints
The husband, the comedian
He is super bound to her
Bound?
This completely confirms it
Head is buried
Already think "it's me, it's me"
There is no longer any doubt
Its confirmed
That person is particularly excessive
Unlikely to play away, that type
Oh, really?
So
Is that a man like an artist
Excuse me
He talked to them!
Sorry, what you're talking about
Can't stand it anymore
Sorry, are you talking about me?
Eh... eh?
The person you are talking about, its me, right?
An unexpected result
No, no, no
Who would have thought this'd happen
Couldn't help it!
No no no!
No, I want to know...
Who is the director?
No, I just heard about it too...
Who did it come from?
So scary
Is it true?
-I think you've misunderstood
Please tell me the truth, okay?
No no...
Hurry up and go to your meeting!
Its long been forgotten
Starting to interrogate them now
Please tell him "Sorry we have to go to a meeting"
Sorry we have to go to a meeting
Please, before you go
Can't get away otherwise
I just can't accept it
I'm right here, please just tell me
But, I... this...
Its what you're talking about, right?
Sorry, we're being called. We're being rushed
Please wait, don't go!
Sorry, sorry, sorry
Then I'll leave too... I can't take it
Going together?
Don't go, I really can't take it
Sorry!
Going together
Wait a minute, wait for me
The truth is revealed
Calm down a little.
-What's going on here?
Calm down a little
Calm down
Following people isn't right
Poor thing
Do not follow people
What's the program?
You think about it. What do you think the show is?
Wednesday Downtown?
Correct answer
The worst!
This is really unethical
My heart, can you guys come and feel it?
My heart is pounding!
Great! Thank goodness it's not true!
What is this theory, can you guess?
Having an affair will make your heart pound?
There is no such theory
What kind of stupid theory is this?
Great! Thank goodness it's not true!
This is not true, of course, great!
But it's more important to hurry up and get to the meeting, right?
Sorry...
You turned your phone off so there was nothing we could do
I'm really sorry...
So, in first place was Ogata
With over 9 minutes
And probably had no intention to go to the meeting
What do you all think?
Ogata's developed very unexpectedly
Yes, indeed
Ogata's wasn't finished
He followed them out
We should have kept it going
The next theory could have been
How many kilometers will he follow them for
But I have personally heard these rumors about Mrs. Ogata
Eh-
That's a big problem!
There aren't any, right?
Ogata will pursue you!
Yes, indeed
-Constantly following Matsumoto
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's Koyabu!
So let's get right to the point
Does anyone watch Youtube?
The sound is too loud to hear anything
Is there still a ceiling for hearing?
I just hear "bang!"
What do you think?
I will watch comedians
Their online shows
-Yes
I also watch some YouTube channels
Hamada doesn't watch YouTube, right?
Well, i'm the same, I have a look from time to time
To see what other guys who have retired are up to now
That's what you like to watch?
That sort of thing
Social type
What "social type"? He's the "anti social" type
The theory I bring today is about YouTube
No parent would say "Since it's your choice..." to support a child who says "I want to be a trouble-making YouTuber"
What do you think, especially those of you with children?
You won't support it, right?
It's strange, isn't it, to emphasize "troublemaker"?
I'd just want to ask "why"
Imagine your child looking at you with a straight face, what you would say?
Blunt eyes, right?
-Yeah
Since it is your choice...
I don't know if I can say it.
-No, no, no, no, no
No parent would say "Since it's your choice..." to support a child who says "I want to be a trouble-making YouTuber"
The first parent-child pair is Saito and his 18-year old son
I see
The parents divorced shortly after birth
It's been a long time since they saw each other
He lives with his mother in Aomori and is in his fourth year of high school
Some things are better to say directly
It's been a long time since I've seen a live skit.
-Yeah?
It's been a long time since we had a separate live
-Last year?
Yes, yes, nothing since then.
-Ohhhh
Very interesting.
-That's great
No sound at all, my throat was so dry
After a long absence of father and son alone together, Saito speaks in his home dialect
After this they'll start talking
This time to see a live show
Saito is called to the hotel where he was staying on the pretext that there was something important to discuss
What do you want to talk about, then?
I'm in fourth grade now.
-Yes
I just think it's time for me to...
It's time to think about the future.
-Yeah
I want to talk to you about this
With me?
-Yes, yes, yes
If you want to work, you have to come here.
-It's true
So, what I want to do is
Be a trouble-making YouTuber
Straight to the point
Don't, seriously?
Really really really
Are you serious?
-Serious, serious
Why?
You may think that being an ordinary YouTuber is enough
Why don't you be a regular YouTuber?
Why a trouble-making one?
Tell me why you wanna be a troublemaking YouTuber specifically
If you do ordinary things...
There are a lot of YouTubers now, right?
-Yes, a lot
That's why they say, "is this channel like so-and-so's"
But its the same for troublemakers, right?
Has anyone been arrested recently for being a troublemaker?
I don't know. I  haven't seen much YouTube
Haven't seen much?
-Yes
Especially troublemaking YouTubers, I hate them the most
I can't tolerate making money by causing trouble to others
So, to be honest, now I'm very, very shocked
In response to his son's declaration that he would "get into trouble in the future"
A dependable father
Saito is very shocked
Very good, very good
I don't understand. Let's say for example
You're going to do it after you graduate?
No, I think it's fine to start now
Not going?
You're not going to school?
-Yeah
Come on, it's not worth it. I mean it
If it is necessary to do immediately
If you have to do it in Tokyo, I understand completely
What does that mean?
Can I come here after I graduate from college?
I won't support you
I'm saying it straight it up front.
-Ok
To convince Saito
At this point, a specific plan to cause trouble is proposed
For example?
You know that type of exposure fetish?
I'll go out wearing that kind of long coat
Then suddenly open it
But inside i'm actually wearing ordinary clothes
You can just do that as a skit!
I know
Scaring people is bad
Hurting someone is something you can't afford to do
Although there's actually nothing bad going on in the end
Watching from the side might be funny
But from the perspective of the woman
You are scaring her either way
Young women or children, right?
Never do it to children
Absolutely not
The father will definitely be worried about this
Sexual pranks against children is not a good idea
Even if you're not a father, you'd be right to say that
Sorry, I need to reply to an email... Oh, no, a LINE
I'm really worried to hear you say this
What a cut!!!
So boring
But I want to become this troublesome type either way
Hmm...
The son is very strong willed
How about it?
Good or bad?
It's bad, i'm very hesitant
I don't want to see it, and don't support it
Saito said no completely
At this point, we revealed the truth
What? Really!?
What is it?
What do you think?
So annoying, I said such embarrassing things
Kid says "I want to be a trouble-making YouTuber"
The theory is that no parent would say "Since its your choice..." and show support
That's for sure!
Who would support it?
I really wanted to beat him up
But I'm divorced and separated again
So its unconvincing
It's great that I was denied
Because I did not expect a refusal to such an extent
That's great. That's really great
For sure!
-From the bottom of my heart, I feel glad
The next parents and children who participated in the verification were
A good kid, actually
KUDOU MIKIKO, an entertainer, and her father
KUDOU went to Waseda University and started to work as a comedian at the same time
But she didn't tell her father about becoming an comedian initially as she thought he would be "absolutely opposed"
A father who seems to be against even "comedy"
What will be his reaction to "trouble-making"?
It's time to consider employment.
-Yeah
I've thought about what I want to do so this is not really a discussion
Informing me?
-Yes
What?
Troublemaking YouTuber...
Want to be?
-Yes
But still calm
Are you serious?
-Yes
Gentle Dad
Is that the "troublemaker" type?
Eating in the supermarket but not paying for the food, stuff like that to attract attention?
No
Will not do criminal things
Are you going to live on this for the rest of your life?
I think its pointless
A bit sad
Is it good for others and society?
That's the reason you want to go for it?
Or is it just because it makes money?
If the audience finds it interesting, it's good
I can't support it
I can't support this kind of thing
As expected, he was opposed
Then
I thought you would support what I wanted to do
Why don't you let go and support me?
Facing the father who does not support her dream
She can't help but shed a tear
This is a bit off
You want to make it your life's work?
Yeah
You only live once.
-Yeah
Dad's heart is softened because of the tears
Well...it's not bad to try
Yes, I will try it
Surprisingly, he reluctantly agrees to her becoming a troublemaking YouTuber
Mixed emotions, right?
At this point, the mother and sister come home
Here, she explains the specific project she intends to do
Isn't there a live camera of Enoshima?
Shooting the beach of Enoshima
The one that was on the weather forecast.
-Yeah
I'll draw a big poop on the beach there like this
Are you stupid?
What?
I'm still trying to decide whether to paint it or write it
Cute project
Painting is better
-Is it better to paint?
Why not draw a dog too?
Making recommendations
Pooping dogs and poop
Eventually, even advice is given from the "troublemaking family"
At this point, we reveal the truth
So bright!
What is this?
Is this a prank?
You'll agree if they want to try it
Well, it can not be helped
If you don't let her do it, she'll regret it, right?
I don't want to give her such regrets
After confirming that the father "wants to support his daughter's dream"
She decides to disclose her comedy activities
Still needs to say this
Comedian
-Want to be?
Would love to be
Now I have an agent
From time to time, I also participate in live events
Really? You've become busy
That I would totally support you in
-Really?
For sure!
Really?
-Funny?
What a fool!
What to do if you don't do what you want to do once in a lifetime
Dad is so nice
Kudou shed tears of joy in the face of her father's tenderness
This technique
First leading with "Troublemaker YouTuber"
Of course you'd be relieved to hear "comedian" afterwards
Being a comedian isn't such a bad thing
Very happy
Have a great pair of parents
Next is Honahonami, who has 2 years of experience, and
What kind of name is this?
Her father, who also doesn't know that his daughter is a comedian
Haven't even told your parents!
Huh?
Getting into trouble, you'll be scolded, right?
And you'll be called a criminal, right?
Won't do criminal things
Then you are really in the abyss
No matter how she tries to persuade, he does not approve
That's for sure!
Being a comedian will be talked about at the point of the reveal
I started working as a comedian 2 years ago
After graduating from college, I want to live as a comedian
This is even scarier
Is it okay? To be a comedian
Well... if you think it's your dream
As long as it does not cause trouble for others, its fine
The standard has dropped a lot
This side also reluctantly agreed
The final parents and children who participated in the validation were
Nichokenju's Kobori and his son
Won't Downtown open a Youtube channel?
No
You can detail your daily lives
Hamada wants to do one about driving his wife, right?
That'd be weird!
There are also couples who drive together
That's crazy
Have you heard?
Well, I heard you have something to say
Here's the deal
What? Whoa, what is it?
Want money?
-Not money
I don't have the money
It is about the future
I found what I wanted to do
I want to talk to you about this
Didn't you say you wanted to be a teacher at school?
Previously, yes
Now I want to be a troublemaking YouTuber
No... eh?
Why do you want to be that kind of person?
Want to be a YouTuber I can still understand a little
Eh? What... uh...
Troublemaker?
Facing a big turn in direction from "education" to "trouble-making"
Kobori is very upset
You'll be scolded and arrested?
I wont do illegal things
It is to get popular by causing trouble
Why do you want to cause trouble...
Why do this kind of thing?
Working as a teacher is good
What is a YouTuber who causes trouble?
Even this trash who is well known for his cheating and debts
Does not approve of activities that cause trouble for others
First of all, why do you want to be that?
Why not? There's nothing wrong with it, right?
You should know...
I've been called "scum" and "trash"
And then my son is causing trouble everywhere
Originally?
I wonder what else will be said
But I just want to do it
First of all, although there are many YouTubers
They don't have love!
No love?
Yeah, those guys
Saying that all you need is popularity
The troublemaker type means you don't care what happens to others
Not funny and no love
This kind of thing ... there is no need to do it
What type of things do you want to do?
Now, some examples of projects are given
For example, if it's related to a comedian
-Yeah
I buy all the tickets of comedian's live show
Then on the day 0 people show up
Very bad
What's funny about that?
What do you think?
Who would find it interesting?
Its a prank to see the reaction of the person
And then does the comedian feel they benefit too?
Its publicity for them too
In the end, it is a win-win situation
There's nothing funny about failure to comedians
Why?
Do you understand the feelings of a comedian when they are pranked like that?
No, I don't understand
YouTubers ignore many rules
They think "it's good to be scolded"
I hate people like that!
He sounds like he's just talking about himself
He's mad at his own company
-Why?
Who are you trying to screw, for example?
For example, COWCOW
No
Why COWCOW... we are the same generation
Because we're the same generation we have a good relationship
That Tada can't take a joke
He's always having a go at me
Tell me to "go and talk about Manzai".
Tada will be furious
Tada takes good care of me too
Kobori does not look like he is going to agree at all...
There are also seniors in the university doing this
They did something over the top and are now super popular
Can earn about 1 million a month
Non-pro?
-Yeah, a million
Interested
Talking about money...
1 million, 1 million
I'll give you half, or more
Half for Dad?
Say you don't need it!
The wind direction has changed
Getting motivated
If I have 1 million a month, I can give you 600,000
College tuition will be paid for, too
Now he's thinking
Of course, I can also supplement the family
Now just 1 million
Doing YouTube, 2 million 3 million is also possible
Eh, want to do it together?
Together?
You have a reputation
You being in it it'll surely be popluar
Eh...
-3 million
What will you do with the 3 million you earn?
Shaken by money
The 18-year-old has lured his father with enticing potential
You can also come up with ideas, it'll surely be popular
In that case, its the same as your comedy, right?
Trying hard to convince!
You're also doing music
Trying to DJ
-Yes
Isn't it the same?
What did Kobori ultimately conclude?
Can't you do it?
Not…
I can understand a little if I am a YouTuber
But causing others trouble and controversy like this
I can't say I agree. Sorry
Disagree?
Disagree
Kobori stopped at the last step
So, the truth was revealed
When it comes to money he almost agreed
What what what what?
Eh, this is fake?
Eh?
You've already got staff?
A team is formed? What's the deal?
At this point, we explained the project
Wednesday?
Theory?
You're working with Wednesday?
-Yes
With Downtown?
Yes, Wednesday Downtown
He's so shocked
Fooled by my own child...
In summary
I want to see what the parents of trouble-making YouTubers are like
Awesome
The examples of troublemaking are still relatively cute and mild
There are also fathers who agreed
If you give bad kind of examples then they will certainly be opposed
Indeed
But this show itself is a trouble-making variety show
If a child says, "I want to be a staff member of Wednesday Downtown"
The parents will certainly be worried
"Are you okay?"
"Can't you just go to a regular variety show?"
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03