THIS PROGRAM IS THE RECORD
OF A "BATTLE" AMONGST COMEDIANS.
IN ORDER TO PRESERVE QUALITY,
IT IS MOSTLY UNEDITED.
AS SUCH, VIEWERS MAY ENCOUNTER
EXPLICIT CONTENT.
-Hello, Mr. Matsumoto.
-Hello.
As the creator of this show,
could you tell us what Documental is?
Well...
HITOSHI MATSUMOTO
I had a few ideas for the title.
But long story short,
this is a documentary of sorts.
I wanted to focus on
the mental battle between comedians,
so it's a "Docu-mental."
From "documentary" and "mental"
I ended up with Documental.
DOCUMENTAL
What drove you to create this show
in the first place?
Well, how should I put it?
When you think about what I've done,
I've devoted my whole life to comedy,
ever since I was in elementary school.
This is the train wreck
at the end of the line.
THIS IS HOW FAR COMEDY HAS COME
We've all seen a variety of formats
for comedy.
Sketches, funny stories, funny quizzes,
duo acts, solo acts, stand-up...
There are probably more.
But the one format
that hasn't been done is
a "no-holds-barred" show.
A JOURNEY THROUGH UNCHARTED TERRITORY
"THE NO-HOLDS-BARRED SHOW"
The comedians can do whatever they want.
What also makes this unique is:
Comedians usually take turns at making an
audience laugh within a given time frame.
But on this show,
10 comedians are confined to one room.
They have to make the other nine laugh.
But they have to do it
without laughing themselves.
This might actually be the simplest way
and the best way to decide who truly is
the funniest person.
THE RAWEST AND MOST DEFINITIVE BATTLE
THE MIGHTIEST
I must admit,
this is sort of an experiment.
A BIG EXPERIMENT
You scared me! Good morning.
THE CHOSEN WARRIORS
Mr. Oh.
-Good morning.
-You have an invitation.
-I do?
This is for you.
-Here you go.
-Oh, thank you.
Good morning.
What is this?
What's going on?
Good morning.
-Good morning.
Yes?
This is for you.
Does it say "Event"?
-It says "Invitation."
-"Invita-ton"?
Dear sirs,
Now the autumn breeze blows,
the summer heat is but a fond memory.
Have the seasons been treating you well?
I send you this invitation
with my best intentions.
I sincerely hope you will join me
with one million yen on your person.
I am hosting a Documental.
"With one million yen on your person"?
One million yen?
One million yen!
-I have to bring one million yen?
-That's right.
The winner will receive
a 10 million yen reward.
To play or not, the choice is yours.
That's too expensive!
One million yen?
If I win, I'll get 10 million yen.
That would be nice.
But I don't really need it.
More importantly,
I don't want to pay one million.
If you don't win, you lose the entry fee?
That's right.
I'll have to think about it.
If you would like to participate,
I will inform you of the time and venue.
I look forward to hearing from you.
The mornings and evenings
are getting chillier.
Please keep yourself in good health.
Yours sincerely,
Hitoshi Matsumoto.
No thanks.
There's no way I could win it.
I'd never win. No way.
This is some grand plan devised
by the comic genius Mr. Matsumoto.
If I just showed up,
they'd tear me to shreds.
Hear that? The sirens are ringing already.
This is like some new kind of scam.
You never say no to Mr. Matsumoto, right?
There are 10 people,
and everyone brings one million.
That's right.
And the winner takes 10 million home...
I think I'll laugh right away.
I don't get it.
What's he trying to do?
One million yen?
Wait. What should I do?
This is really going to happen, right?
-It's not a prank?
-It's not.
Another thing is,
I do the TV show You Mustn't Laugh
at the end of each year.
It's become a highly entertaining show
for all ages.
That's great, but it can be limiting.
THE ULTIMATE FIGHT
I wanted to get rid of all the shackles.
AN EXISTENTIAL WORLD OF COMEDY
You know those moments
when you laugh the hardest?
It may be something trivial,
but it hits your funny bone.
I've been wanting to create something
based on that for several years.
THIS IS THE FRONTIER OF COMEDY
There are a tremendous number of
comedians in Japan now.
THEY ARE THE CHOSEN BEASTS
It's really like a jungle.
Some comedians do well in the water.
THEY'RE BEASTS IN THE JUNGLE
Some just hang around in trees.
You know what I mean?
Some of them live in swamps.
Some are fast runners...
This show puts a variety of beasts
all in one room.
THE STRONGEST IN THE WILD
So, which of them is the strongest?
I'm sure this won't get
high ratings on TV.
Unless you watch pretty carefully,
you won't grasp how funny it is.
You could say it's aimed towards
a very specific audience.
I wouldn't say it's a show for
older people, women, or kids.
But I think those who like it
will be glued to the screen.
So, I think it's not a bad idea
to narrow down our target audience.
After all, it's not easy
to watch videos on Amazon, right?
It's too hard for geezers, right?
Subscribing to Amazon is too complicated
for them, right?
Geezers can't do it.
Early elementary kids can't do it, either.
Those people can go elsewhere...
Yeah.
By the way,
I just said comedians were like
animals in the jungle,
and this show is on Amazon, right?
That was either a good joke,
a little confusing, or I got it all wrong.
I'm not sure.
THE COMEDIANS ARRIVE AT THE BATTLEFIELD
Am I the first one?
I'm the first?
Really?
So this is the place.
Where should I sit?
I'm Daisuke Miyagawa. Nice to meet you.
One million yen is a large amount.
I had to think about it at home,
but in the end,
it sounded like fun.
The only problem is,
I don't have any trademark jokes.
I don't have a killer technique.
I don't know how I'm going to fight.
He's an innately happy guy.
How can I put it?
He loves to be around people.
He's the type of guy who always has fun,
whatever he's doing.
HE ENJOYS WHATEVER'S
IN FRONT OF HIM
I think he'll stir things up a lot, but...
Unfortunately, he probably laughs the most
out of the whole group.
QUICK TO LAUGH
I'm scared of the guys who are weird.
I'm not worried about any joke
or gag that's been prepared.
But I'm scared I'll find something funny,
all by myself.
Especially when I'm not supposed to laugh.
I'm worried what will happen when
I start to find some trivial thing funny.
That is his weak point.
Do you think he can win?
In terms of making other people laugh,
I think he does have a chance.
It's interesting when you think about it.
If you were to categorize his abilities
and put them in a hexagonal chart,
he excels in one or two areas,
but, overall, it's not well-balanced.
I don't have a strategy to be honest.
I'll see what happens.
It depends on the participants.
I'll sit here.
Wait a minute.
Okay. I will sit here.
Who is it?
Excuse me.
It's Ohchi!
-Good morning.
I'm Yosuke Ohchi, from the duo Dienoji.
I'm 44 years old.
I have a wife and two daughters.
Nice to meet you.
My wife handed me one million yen
this morning, and now I'm here.
ASKING HIS WIFE FOR THE CASH
Remember that one million yen I mentioned?
Yeah, I do...
Can I have it?
Seriously?
Where will I get that?
My daughter warned me,
"Don't waste our money."
It's Ohchi!
You're gonna sit there?
-Where should I sit?
-Over on the right.
If each of them had to do something
all by themselves,
it wouldn't be funny at all.
Apparently, he's an air guitar champion.
AIR GUITAR WORLD CHAMPION
There's no way he'd win a contest like
that if he was truly a funny comedian.
It's like showing the world
he's not funny.
But he is a go-getter.
It'll be fun to have one guy like him.
However, Ohchi may be
Daisuke's Achilles' heel.
-This is insane.
-It sure is!
-The day has come.
-This is insane.
-Know who's coming?
-I have no idea.
-Nobody's said anything.
-Nothing.
I can't believe Daisuke's here.
Someone's coming.
Yes?
Hello?
So it's you?
Someone else from Yoshimoto.
This guy's so annoying.
We're all from Yoshimoto.
Hello.
-Nice seeing you.
-Howdy.
I'm part of the Toro Salmon duo.
I'm Kubota. Nice to meet you.
This guy is...
He's a little...
scary.
He has a bit of a unique style of comedy.
Seaweed. Seaweed. Seaweed.
Is "Seaweed" a palindrome?
No, in reverse it's "Deewaes!"
I don't get it!
And he has what you might call...
a psychopathic streak.
The one million yen?
I paid the entry fee from my savings.
And I borrowed some.
And I participated in a clinical trial
at a university.
Before meds are sold at drug stores,
they're tested out on human subjects.
I made 200,000 yen.
I think rich people will laugh more
because they have fewer worries.
Poor people are defensive,
so they don't laugh much.
To earn one million at Yoshimoto means
I could earn double that elsewhere.
That's enough to retire on in North Korea.
I checked the rules,
and we can use living animals.
ANIMALS ARE PERMITTED
I asked them to bring me
three stray dogs...
It's Kubota...
They're all actually quite happy people.
Why are you wearing a tank top?
I heard we had to wear a collared shirt.
A collared shirt?
Did they prepare one for us?
No, you had to bring your own.
Why did he choose a tank top?
I don't know if I'm hot or cold.
I've thought about this show too much.
He looks like a rickshaw man.
So I stripped.
Kubota is...
He could be dangerous.
-We're all in danger.
-This is dangerous.
No way.
This is bad news.
This is really bad.
Fujimoto makes it a different story.
I'm Fujimoto from Fujiwara.
I will try my bestest!
I simply thought it sounded like fun.
That's all.
In his case,
for every single thing
anybody says or does,
he chips in as the straight man.
-I want your eyes to cave in!
-What the hell!
What kind of insult is that?
"Caved-in eyes"?
His presence could be a problem, too.
The thing is, he plays the straight man,
but he makes funny quips, too.
I think he may cause trouble
for the others.
I'll just deal with whatever unfolds.
That's my only plan.
Yeah.
If Ohchi does something silly,
and Fujimoto starts to play with that,
it will be tough for the others.
My wife said,
"You wanna be on the show, right?
Then go for it."
She was supportive.
And she's the breadwinner anyway.
In fact, it's like...
I can hear a little devil saying,
"It's okay to laugh and lose.
Your wife is rich!"
Right here.
-Is that all you brought?
-Yeah.
How much did you bring?
That's what I brought.
-What did he bring?
-A pouch.
RULE 1: YOU MAY BRING PROPS
-Is that all?
-Your bag is huge!
-You're gonna make us laugh that much?
-No, that's not why...
-What's inside that?
-Isn't that too small?
-What's in it?
-Well...
That's not a bag people take to work.
But, it's...
And this is what it's like
with only four people.
You're not scared of me.
-I didn't expect Daisuke to be here.
-Right?
-I didn't think so, either.
-I thought you were abroad.
I get that a lot.
-You should stay there.
-What does that mean?
Doing overseas reports and eating.
Those jobs suit you.
-What's your problem?
-Go overseas, or to the countryside.
-Look. It's him.
-Uh-oh.
The monster's here.
It's turning into a heavy-weight match.
A monster has arrived.
For real?
I'm Kukky, from Yaseibakudan.
The reason I became a comedian was
I wanted to steal money from
the general public.
I never thought someone would steal
from me.
I said,
"Dude, can you lend me a million yen?"
I borrowed the money from a place called
Yoshimoto Finance.
I signed a lot of papers.
They gave me the loan without any hassle.
It's a very nice company.
The payments get taken out of my salary.
A MILLION YEN LOAN FROM YOSHIMOTO
-I have to pay back 100,000 yen a month?
-Yes.
Well, he is even more of a psychopath.
YET ANOTHER PSYCHOPATH
He has a butterfly knife?
If he sets up some kind of trap,
they'll be in trouble indeed.
He's a war veteran!
-Is that a tent?
-Look at Fujimoto's small bag.
I brought 18 robot model kits.
That was a forced punchline.
I think he will do pretty well.
Every time he does something
that seems random,
you start to imagine
what led him to do it.
He can be incredibly funny.
I'll laugh.
I'm already laughing. See?
That's the type of guy I am.
I even laugh at my own jokes.
I'm in trouble.
I'm like canned laughter.
Call me "Can-ghter"
-He means trouble.
-For real? Damn it.
Just make him laugh first.
I'm in trouble.
-These guys crack me up.
-I have a bad feeling.
-I don't like this...
-It feels like we're backstage at Lumine.
Here's another one.
-We got another one.
-I'm done for.
That's the face you'd expect.
-It's him.
-Another dangerous one.
Hi. I am from Japan.
I'm from Trendy Angel.
I think my name is Saito.
Nice to meet you.
I'm this year's "Biggest Hit Comedian."
I've starred in 11 commercials this year.
But I only have 700,000 yen in my account.
I think Saito is the most well-balanced
out of this group.
In many respects.
-He always makes me laugh.
-Stay over there. Next to Ohchi.
-Don't come here.
-Don't say that--
-Oops!
-We haven't started yet.
There are many disadvantages for Saito.
The other nine will never laugh.
at his bald head.
HIS BALDNESS IS LAME
That's a key point.
Women and children might find it funny,
but being bald won't cut it here.
There's no way I'll lose.
-How big is his bag?
-Show us.
-This is it.
-Are you kidding?
-Is that all?
-Look at Fujimoto's.
That's too small.
-What's with that pouch?
-That's your weapon?
New shoes come in bags like that.
Everyone's really happy and smiling now.
The atmosphere's nice and relaxed, but...
For now, they can enjoy themselves,
but soon...
-That's just wrong.
-I was told to wear a collared shirt.
-Then you need a collar.
-Mine has one.
Here's another twisted one.
Too many weirdos.
He's twisted and knotted.
I'm Tenjikunezumi's Kawahara.
I'm looking forward to it.
I went home to think about this properly.
I tried to figure it out.
But even then, I couldn't really get it.
And now, I still don't get it.
He's got peculiarities.
I hope they're not my juniors.
If they're my seniors,
I can give them all I've got.
-We're done for.
-He never shows any emotion.
-Kawahara never laughs.
-You're right.
He's a tough opponent.
He's not the type to pull
a lot of punches.
I don't think he will be dismissed
in the first half.
I can't picture him splitting his sides
with laughter at something somebody does.
Every now and then you'll find
a comedian like that.
Like Itsuji Itao.
THE "ITSUJI ITAO TYPE"
I would like 10 million yen.
But more than that,
I want to leave my mark.
I want to leave a mark worth
one million yen.
You brought enough for a camp.
-All I brought was one big sausage.
-That bombed.
-That bombed as much as your 18 robots.
-No, mine's funnier than a sausage.
He's incredibly expressionless.
Good morning.
I'm Jiro Hachimitsu.
I'll try to take myself into
a state of emptiness.
As empty as possible.
-Good morning.
-I've never seen him laugh.
-He never laughs.
-He does, but...
Yeah, he's not really the type to laugh.
Simply put,
his comedic aptitude is very high.
MR. HIGHLY PROFICIENT
Don't talk about Thomas and Friends now.
There's a subway below us.
He's a straight man who makes funny quips,
but he's different from Fujimoto.
Whenever something happens,
he'll quietly mutter a witty remark.
That's what slowly creeps up on you.
He is a strong opponent.
I was honored.
I accepted the offer right away.
The biggest problem was,
I didn't have a million yen.
My motto is, "Money is not something
you keep overnight."
I have a lot of confidence,
but at the same time,
I laugh easily at the corniest jokes.
I'm in the middle?
Has anyone ever seen Jiro laugh out loud?
-No.
-Never.
All he does is smile.
Now that you mention it,
I've never seen him roll in laughter.
-I laugh at Mr. Bean.
-Mr. Bean?
-Only Mr. Bean?
-Stop trying to make us laugh.
This is an amazing group.
Is it a female contestant?
It's "Thony-An."
We're all from Yoshimoto.
Hello...
Hello. I'm Anthony from the Matenrou duo.
Right now, I'm full of dread.
And this guy...
I think his career is a lot shorter
than the others.
If he doesn't hold back
in front of his seniors,
he might do well...
But, Anthony?
I think he might hold back a little
out of respect for his seniors.
Last month I earned 220,000 yen.
I borrowed 500,000 yen
from my senior colleagues.
Thank you so much, BKB.
I don't want to regret lending you this.
Make me glad that I lent it to you.
-Certainly.
-Keep that in mind.
-I'm sure you have the money.
-I don't.
Stop acting poor.
Thank you for lending me the money.
I borrowed from my mom as well,
and I finally raised one million.
He's the only one not fully Japanese,
so it'll be interesting.
But when it comes to these guys,
it's like what I said about Saito.
They won't laugh at his usual jokes.
Not when he only looks a bit different.
When I first got to quit my part-time job
after becoming a comedian,
I was so happy.
I never want to have
a part-time job again.
But if I lose this,
I'll have to find a part-time job.
You look like a backpacker.
Where'd he come from?
-Stop making funny quips.
-Why? We haven't started yet.
He looks like a hitchhiker.
So there are nine.
We have nine participants now.
That means there's one more.
One more.
Who is the last participant?
I'm sure it's someone from Yoshimoto.
-No way.
-The worst participant!
-Oh, no!
-This is terrible!
I'm Jimmy Onishi.
I'm just going to try my best.
He is a monster.
The nine others are not going to like it.
Not with him here.
The consumer loan officer told me
I can't borrow a million yen.
Because my annual income is only
six million.
It really hit me how low
my standing is in society.
He laughs easily.
All it would take is one
really simple dirty joke.
He's that stupid.
Well, you see...
Dumb luck always plays a part in comedy.
I'm going to aim for dumb luck.
He's already won.
Look how grey his hair is.
-Stop saying things like that.
-Why?
Stop it.
This is really going to be something.
They are quite an elite troop.
THE ELITE TROOP
I think this will be great.
This is not good.
-With him here...
-Jimmy is too much.
It might be over before we use
any of our props.
Are you laughing because he's black?
That's wrong.
What's so funny?
He's here.
Good morning!
He looks very angry.
-He's scary.
-Why?
-He's angry.
-Why's he so mad?
Look at his muscles.
He's nice and pumped now.
He gets more buff every time I see him.
-Good morning.
So, gentlemen...
Did you bring it?
-Have you brought what we promised?
-Yes.
-Of course we did.
-Then put it on the table, please.
This is truly your own money, right?
-You all raised it somehow?
-Yes.
One million yen.
I can't believe you're doing this to us.
This is crazy.
Spending money is easy,
but making it is...
Yes. You are right, but...
Damn, that's worn!
His is amazing.
Which country is this rubber band from?
Who looks at things like that?
Would you mind passing the money?
Our staff will confirm
it's all there later.
I am sure there are no mistakes.
Please start from there.
Okay.
-I just pass it around?
-Yes, please do.
-The cameras are rolling.
-You're not handing out homework.
-I've never done this before.
-What a nice chunk of money.
-I can't believe we are doing this.
-It looks beautiful.
That's how tall the pile gets.
-I've never seen 10 million yen before.
-It's huge.
-Yeah, now that you mention it.
-Wow!
Goodness!
-Awesome!
Is this for real?
Is something wrong?
He's trying to make you laugh already?
Cut it out.
DAISUKE & HANAKO
"TOGETHER FOR 35 YEARS"
It's not a joke. It's a good luck charm.
-It's more like a bad luck charm.
-It's their 35th wedding anniversary.
-It's a bad luck charm.
-No, it's not.
-Stop saying they're bad luck.
-That veteran duo isn't "bad luck."
Stop making pointless jokes.
They're irrelevant.
So, here is the money you brought.
There is nine million yen here.
I mean 10 million yen.
The 10 million yen is in this bag.
And now...
Allow me to explain the rules.
Rule 2:
There are 10 participants in this game.
You will spend the entire time together
confined in this room.
Rule 3: At the end, the person who hasn't
laughed will receive the reward.
10 million yen.
Rule 4: There is a time limit.
It is displayed up there.
You have six hours.
As soon as I call start,
it will begin counting down.
Before the six hours are up,
I would like to see one of you become
the champion.
Okay.
-You can do whatever you want.
-Okay!
You can do absolutely anything.
The funniest person wins.
Think about it. This is an amazing event.
We simply have to be funny.
-It's worth being a champion here.
-Yes, winning here will be like...
It could mean even more than
winning the M-1 Grand Prix.
-It's not a comedy sketch.
-We're fighting with our bare fists.
Things like, "The mechanism of laughter."
And, "What is laughter?"
"What is it that we find truly funny?"
I think this program will make us consider
concepts like that.
I still haven't found answers
to questions like that myself.
How did you get your one million yen,
Anthony?
I borrowed it from many people.
Anthony has a lot more work recently,
but a million yen is still a big amount.
I asked Akebono, the sumo wrestler,
for a loan.
He said, "No damn way."
Why did you ask him?
Akebono, right?
-But a million's nothing for Jimmy, right?
-That's not true!
I went to loan companies,
like Promise and Acom,
but they said, with my income,
they can't loan me one million.
Really?
-But your paintings are popular.
-You could sell one.
I'm on a break from painting.
What does he do?
At the moment,
he's more interested in sex than painting.
-My sex drive's winning at the moment.
-Your art is losing?
-And now...
-How old is he?
-Nowadays, I stop.
-Stop what?
When I'm about to cum.
When I'm about to cum, I stop.
What the hell is he talking about?
-Why do you stop?
-We're done for.
-Why not just cum?
-The time's too expensive to waste.
-What time?
-I pay for two whole hours.
-Are you talking about sex clubs?
-Yeah, at the sex club.
At the sex club?
He's doing it himself.
Jimmy's not the best storyteller.
He's difficult to understand,
but please make an effort.
So, at the loan company, they said,
"With your income,
we can't loan you one million yen."
-Really?
-Is that so.
He is my only senior colleague here.
Senior by a few months?
A few months... Two months.
What's funny about that?
So, gentlemen,
you have a kitchen there,
if you ever feel hungry.
We're not here to see you
battle with hunger.
There's alcohol and such
in the refrigerator,
if you would like to drink some.
The staff will not come in at all.
If something comes up, ring me.
RULE 5:
MATSUMOTO MAY CALL TO GIVE ORDERS, TOO
That's how things will go.
-You have six hours to find one winner.
-We won't need six hours.
You're right. You won't need six hours.
-No, we don't need six hours, do we?
-No, we don't.
Really, you can do whatever.
Truly, you can do anything.
Nothing is off limits for broadcast?
-There must be some limits.
-Apparently not.
You say we're free, but...
You have six hours!
-It may seem long, or the time may fly.
-I'm scared.
For the next six hours,
good luck to you all!
This is scary now.
-When do we start?
-Will they tell us?
I will let you know.
Smile and relax until then.
Jimmy, please wipe off
your eye mucus first.
Please wait a second.
Eye mucus first.
He is getting older.
-You're clear.
-He's at that age when you get eye mucus.
Even with all this, look at these two.
-Kawahara and Jiro haven't laughed at all.
-You're right.
-It's not fair.
-They don't talk either.
-They're tough.
-No, they're just missing something.
-They forgot how to feel.
-They're missing something inside.
So, are you guys ready?
Documental,
start!
Here we go. The game has begun.
May the best player win.
This is my first time meeting Jimmy.
-I'm Jiro Hachimitsu, from Tokyo Dynamite.
-I'm a great fan of your work.
Thank you.
-Do you have something to say?
-It's my first time as well.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Kyojin, from All Hanshin.
-No, you're not.
-He's not.
Hey.
-Which of the duo are you?
-Kyojin.
Jimmy?
-You're Kyojin?
-Yes.
-You're not Hanshin?
-But you're short.
Jimmy is very close.
Kyojin is the tall one.
Jimmy...
Jimmy?
Excuse me. I'm going to stand.
Can I go outside?
Hold on.
This can't be right.
-Who's out?
-Don't joke like that from the very start.
-Is it you?
-No, I laughed after the buzzer.
RULE 6: LAUGHTER IS PERMITTED
WHILE PLAY IS SUSPENDED
-Who was it?
-Wait.
-Who laughed first?
Hachi, I can't believe you did that.
Pretty much everyone laughed.
So, this is really...
I will let this one go,
but almost everyone was laughing.
-You consider that laughing?
-This is going to be tough.
Almost everyone laughed.
-Where does a "laugh" start?
-You can't have your mouth open wide.
-Okay?
-Are you serious?
-You all laughed.
-Jimmy, that's too much.
-Am I the best so far?
-You were really good.
Hey, it's just the beginning.
Can't we slowly ease into it?
-No.
-We can't. We started.
Look. Only 18 seconds have passed.
-That was quick.
-Jimmy, that was way too quick.
I didn't want to stop this.
Can you stop the timer for me?
-I didn't want to stop.
-This is impossible.
But you were terrible.
Everyone was laughing.
Let's make it clear.
We have to keep a normal, natural face.
-That's right.
-Otherwise--
Then let's check what our normal
faces look like.
To be precise, Jiro was laughing a bit
when he introduced himself to Jimmy.
RULE 7:
SMILING WILL BE RULED AS A LAUGH
-He smiled.
-We can't even smile?
No, you can't.
Then we have to see everyone's
normal face first.
No, we don't.
There's no need to.
Why do you want to see it?
You won't get any more chances!
-We're not the judges.
-No more chances!
Fujimoto, stop coming in so fast.
You're relentless.
He's killing me.
-I'm serious.
-Wait a minute!
This is my normal face.
This is my normal face, okay?
Yes, that's your normal face.
Just keep that.
But Fujimoto's face is kind of smiling.
Put on a more neutral face.
-Like that.
-I have to stay like this?
-That will do.
-This is going to be tough.
So, you guys gave me no choice.
Everyone was all smiles.
I think we'll be done in about 18 minutes.
We'll finish really quick.
-We won't last that long.
-It's no fun at all.
Jimmy, that face is great.
-Like this?
-Yeah.
Keep that face.
Wait!
You're making us laugh!
I'm allowed to laugh.
Sorry.
-Don't attack us from the side.
-Sorry.
I'm done for!
We're about to start.
Let's put on neutral faces.
Let's keep a neutral face.
-Jimmy, you're smiling.
-I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Daisuke, stop that.
Stop saying that.
Play's still suspended, right?
This is my normal face.
-You're smiling.
-I'm not.
You are smiling.
Yeah, he's smiling.
-You call this smiling?
-Yes. You are.
You are. Look at your nose.
-Your nose is laughing.
-I don't think so.
Here we go. Start!
It's because I blow my nose too much.
-Should we put our things in a locker?
-You're right.
He said he blows his nose too much?
-Where are the lockers?
-In the back.
THE ROOM COMES WITH A BATH,
SHOWER AND TOILET
Kawahara looks dangerous.
-I didn't know we could smoke here.
-You can have some of mine.
Put that envelope away.
-Oh, sorry.
-Give it to Fujimoto.
Give it to him.
Cut it out.
Oh, Fujimoto...
Where are the lockers?
Fujimoto has sort of been smirking.
-We have sushi, too.
-Look at this.
Oh, I can...
-He can make us sushi.
-Lucky us.
I'll make some later.
I don't want any of yours.
-I don't know about your sushi.
-But my parents own a sushi restaurant.
Put those envelopes away.
Why is he roaming around?
-Where did you get the envelopes?
-I bought them.
You stole the envelopes from
Daisuke & Hanako's dressing room?
You think I stole from them?
What would they have to steal?
-I'm sure there's something.
-They have nothing but great jokes.
What a square.
-Stop fighting.
-We're not here to fight.
Stop following me.
Let's take turns at smoking.
Jimmy's making a move already.
This set is amazing.
Fujimoto looks suspicious.
This is a nice kitchen.
It's amazing.
-We can go over here, right?
-Yeah.
-We can spread out.
-Anything goes.
Really?
You brought heaps.
-Is that wine?
-Yes.
-Drinking already?
-From the bottle?
-You're cool.
-I'm going to drink wine.
Just like Julie's song.
Do you want some nibbles?
Do you want something to nibble?
-No, thanks.
-Okay.
No nibbles or giggles?
-Stop it.
-He's like a bartender.
At a bar.
-It's hot in here.
-This is a nice frying pan.
Is the shower this way? Oh, it's here.
Wow.
They brought one in.
Stop roaming around, Anthony.
You're in my line of sight.
Right?
-We still have a long way to go.
-Yes.
-It hasn't even been 10 minutes.
-Really?
-We have six hours here.
-Those 10 minutes went by quickly for me.
I agree with you.
It's faster than I expected.
-10 minutes have passed already?
-Not yet. It's been six.
It's only been six minutes.
Ohchi?
-Are we allowed to smoke?
-You can smoke over there.
Well, wherever.
-Is that really alcohol?
-It is.
It's red wine.
-Red wine.
-Wow.
You'd rather be drunk?
No, I just like alcohol.
-Were you born in Spain?
-What?
This polo shirt is from Spain.
I have the exact same shirt.
But I bought mine in Okinawa.
-As a present on a holiday.
-I got mine at the mall.
I bought it on a family trip.
At the hotel.
The hotel's boutique.
We didn't ask about your shirt.
Do you have this shirt?
I saw a homeless guy wearing this.
The old guy had the very same one.
The polo shirt.
We all bought one.
So, my wife has one, too.
She has the dress version.
-She has the dress version.
-Who does?
-We all decided to buy the same one.
-Your wife, too?
Do you mean your giant wife?
It's not like she's Giant Shirota.
She's not Giant Shirota.
My "giant wife"?
She's not Giant Shirota!
This tastes great.
Ohchi is very close. And here's Jimmy.
They're mother and child.
Are you hungry?
Ohchi laughed.
Who is it?
Who laughed?
Who was it?
-Was it Jimmy?
-It's not me.
-Seriously, who was it?
-Not me.
-Who was it?
-Who?
-Phew!
-He's been laughing for a while.
-He was laughing a fair bit.
-Yes.
He'd actually been chuckling
for quite a while.
He was soft on you.
-What happened?
-He was laughing the whole time.
What was it?
-We can laugh now, right?
-It's okay now.
You laughed, right?
You were chuckling, right?
Because everyone was funny.
We haven't said anything funny yet.
It was nothing special.
You guys are wandering around too much.
-To muster up the courage.
-I want you to calm down.
It's too early for things like that.
He set me up.
It's too early to set us up.
-What are they?
-They're mother and child.
-Mother and child.
-Are you still going?
-So what if they're mother and child?
-She was hungry.
Enough, please.
Gentlemen...
We're going to watch a replay,
just to confirm that Ohchi laughed.
I think you know already,
but we'll play it here.
We have video evidence.
He was so quick.
Let's watch the replay.
Let's not hide our laughter with
cigarettes or drinks, okay?
He looks like Al Capone.
He's Al Capone.
He's Yoshimoto's Al Capone.
The cigarette tasted good.
You were laughing a lot before this, too.
Which means,
you get a yellow card.
You only get a yellow card for that?
-Look.
-He's laughing hard.
Well, I know, but...
We've really only just started.
-I'm safe. But if I get a red card?
-You're out.
If he laughs at something like that,
he'll be out in no time.
-You'd better start getting serious.
-Yes. Absolutely.
-I got it.
-It's one million yen.
I definitely won't laugh.
Ouch!
What the hell was that?