THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
What's the most difficult thing for
the players in Documental?
Well, you see...
You get lost.
It's not like you're playing in a theater,
where you have a live audience before you.
There's no laughter.
When you have the audience's laughter
taken away from you,
it's like having the light switched off
in your lighthouse.
Kawashima, that's no good.
-It's no good.
-Yeah.
You start wondering,
"Exactly where am I swimming to?"
So I'm sure there are moments
when they feel quite insecure.
But the opposite happens, too.
Even if nobody laughs,
sometimes you're sure something is funny.
And you keep pushing it.
Then you watch it later,
and realize it wasn't funny at all.
It's me.
I'm Master Hamburg!
Now, I'll offer you hungry folks...
HITOSHI MATSUMOTO
Presents Documental
Pengin Shokudo? Who ur that?
Pengin Shokudo.
Remember "throwable dumplings"?
-It's the whole family.
-Wow.
Young actors pose like,
"What's going on, dude?"
During a shoot?
Fujimoto did that?
Why would I?
Did I?
Who was it?
-What's wrong?
-Ouch.
Wait a minute!
Why hide it like that?
What a big load.
Hang on. Isn't Kurosawa laughing?
Oh, honey! How could you?
You're so drunk!
-You can't sleep here.
-Ahh, I'm so drunk!
Orange?
Nipple beams. They point outwards. Heart.
Ah, Straddle Time!
Ah, ah, Straddle Time!
Straddle Time!
Yellow, I guess.
Yeah, yellow.
The new ones are...
Now you're on the ropes.
-You got orange. No more chances.
-Okay.
Won't this get you in trouble?
I don't know.
They haven't said anything yet.
It's probably just that Master Daisuke
doesn't know you've been dissing him.
-It must be a lot of work.
-Yeah.
-It took ages.
-You do it on your computer?
-Yes.
-Amazing.
I cut the parts out, alter them,
then I paste them back in.
It's shrunken here...
Then it grows.
Why is he doing a Kameda impression?
The close-ups are good.
I've got something along this line.
-I bought some phone cases.
-Really? Phone cases?
-Show us.
-Tell me which you like.
-Hang on. Nishizawa's phone cases?
-I break them all the time.
-I'm scared.
-Me, too.
For example...
-We can see through the case.
-You spoiled it.
-Hm?
-Was that a smile?
No... Look...
The light made it...
-It's not a funeral portrait.
-It's Master Yoshio.
Who's that?
It's Obitani.
"The Pot."
Wow. You can buy these?
-Does Yoshimoto sell them?
-Well...
-They make Obitani's merchandise?
These are amazing.
-Who'd buy Obitani's case?
-That's a super cool ducktail.
"Obitani Part II."
-From a different era?
-Is that Obitani?
-He looks laid back.
-He was in the lobby.
He looks like the Baystars' Daisuke Miura.
-There's a resemblance.
-The haircut.
They're from different eras.
See the glasses?
Yeah, different frames.
-"Master Osamu: The Simple Version."
-I like how his teeth are so small.
That's not the point.
And his ear cuff.
Master Sakata.
I can't choose between them.
Is this a termite seen through
a microscope?
It's Master Sakata.
-That's a bit rude.
-That was disrespectful.
Master Osamu has an elevator
in his house that's super slow.
-He has an elevator?
-In his single-family house?
-Have you been to his house?
-I've been.
-Have you seen the elevator?
-I have.
Isn't it amazing? It goes like this.
It's that slow?
-By the time you get to...
-Huh?
-That must have been Nishizawa.
-It's him, right?
-Why did he let out such a noise?
-He chuckled, just a bit.
He laughed the moment you started
going up slowly.
It's Nishizawa, right?
It was Nishizawa, but...
I couldn't see it very well myself.
Okay.
-Let's take a look and check.
-Okay.
-Have you been to his house?
-I've been.
-Have you seen the elevator?
-I have.
It's amazing, isn't it? It's like this.
You laughed.
That was the most natural one so far.
It was really...
-Yellow.
-Okay. Sorry.
It was such a natural laugh.
Sometimes I forget what's going on
for a moment.
-His elevator is so slow.
-It's that slow?
His wife walked up and down four times
before I got to the second floor.
-Four times?
-If I'd heard that I would've laughed.
That was close.
If I heard, I would've been out.
No, no, no! We're still safe now.
-What a waste.
-Nearly a red card.
I almost overlooked it. That was close.
-Let's resume.
-Okay.
-I'll go pee.
-This is tough.
-Do you want to pee first?
-Go ahead.
Let's go.
Nobody would buy these,
even if they were for sale.
-Obitani would be popular.
-No way.
-What if they were 300 yen?
-Not even if they were free.
I have gifts for everyone, too.
-Really?
-Gifts?
-What are they? Photos?
-May I?
Are they photos?
Photos?
-Can I open it?
-Sure.
Okay, we will.
Ready?
-It's his mother.
-His mother-in-law.
-His ex-mother-in-law, actually.
-That's right.
This I want to see.
-I'd like you all to look.
-He bought so many.
Why?
I want you to know.
-Know what?
-Huh?
-About your mother-in-law?
-Yes.
For real?
That is nasty.
-She's beautiful.
-She is.
Look here.
You don't often get to...
She's really showing the goods.
She's the one who gave birth to
that daughter...
She's beautiful.
She was about 60 at the time...
-She's over 60?
-Really?
I understand why she
wanted to publish this.
When you're this beautiful, yeah.
What was the target market?
It was a pretty big seller.
I'll bet.
No doubt.
-Nobu, this page is really good.
-I'm fine, thanks.
Here.
-I put a bookmark in there.
-It's okay. I have my own copy.
Ahh.
-The page you bookmarked?
-Yeah.
Start looking from that page.
Hey.
This is...
-Did you find a mysterious page?
-Mysterious page?
They're stuck together.
Oh, that's...
Look.
Yuck!
Please.
-He jerked off.
-He spanked the monkey!
To your mother-in-law?
-"Don't pity me. Fap for me."
-Classic quote.
It's stuck? Damn.
-Are they your favorite pages?
-You jerk off to that?
-What was her dog's name?
-Ryu.
Tissue.
Guys, I, um...
I got a tattoo.
-What were you thinking?
-How could you?
I think it's time comedians were
allowed to get one.
-You really think so?
-Bad move.
But I wanted one.
I just think it's time they were okay.
But you still have gigs
that require you to get naked.
-You are...
-I wanted one.
You'll be banned from pools.
-It's not on your back?
-Where is it?
There's nothing there.
-Very well drawn.
-Who gets their partner in ink?
What a bromance.
This is the face he makes after
he's said a joke, right?
After he's nailed one.
-That's when he says "It's me," right?
-No.
It's when he says "Hand, hand."
That's when his face looks the best.
-That's permanent.
-You okay?
Sorry, but I have a confession too.
I got a tattoo.
-Really?
-You, too?
-Hey, he's your partner.
-For real?
-But Nobu doesn't seem the type at all.
-Yeah.
That makes it more interesting.
-It's fire.
-Fire?
Flames?
Yes, flames.
I was thinking...
-I needed to challenge myself more.
-I see what you mean.
Fire?
It may help you focus.
I actually got them on my armpits.
-They're three dimensional.
-Wow.
-They look like birds.
-Black flames?
Black fire.
-Amazing.
-You don't say.
To be honest...
-Me, too.
-You got one?
I became the first in Asai Kikaku
to get a tattoo.
That wasn't a smart move, Iio.
I haven't shown it to anyone,
not even Sekine.
Will you be okay?
He doesn't like tattoos.
-Of course he doesn't.
-He'll hate it.
-Can you take a look?
-Seriously?
If you don't like it,
I'll get a skin graft.
-You'll remove it?
-But it's not like you.
It's not like me, or the agency.
However...
I needed to move forward, so I got two.
May I?
-Give me your honest opinions.
-Okay.
If you don't...
If you tell me to remove them, I will.
-May I?
-Sure.
-Really?
-Where are they?
I may be old,
but they're like pink sapphires.
That's a tough one.
-They're tattoos?
-They are not tattoos.
Did you add pink to them?
-You tattooed them pink?
-Pink pigment?
Amazing.
-Really.
-They're 48 years old.
-They truly are pink.
-Beautiful.
They're pink sapphires.
Do nipples represent the entire person?
Are they the same as a person's face?
I heard the diameter of your nipple
is the same as your pupil.
That's bull.
-That would be a nuisance.
-Right? You'd be all pupils.
They're too big for pupils.
You have the same nipples as Morio Kazama.
Ah, the color.
In Fall Guy?
Yeah, they're the same color.
What do you think?
You don't need a better look.
Everyone saw them.
Excuse me...
-If only you'd told me...
-Excuse me.
I've lost my wallet.
-Your wallet?
-Yes.
-Where?
-Around here.
-Your wallet?
-We haven't seen it.
You have an abnormal volume of hair.
-Are you a student?
-Yes.
My wallet...
-What a small forehead.
-Have you seen it?
We haven't.
I lost it somewhere around here.
-Shall we look for it?
-It's around here.
-What does it look like?
-Well...
It's a Puma wallet.
Puma?
-Are you in middle school?
-Yes.
Puma, with velcro.
-The ones you peel open?
-Right.
-The ones you rip.
-What color?
It's checkered.
I've never seen a checkered Puma wallet.
-Checkered Puma wallets are rare.
-You have an awful lot of hair.
-Your hair. There's an awful lot of it.
-But I had a haircut yesterday.
Yesterday?
It grew right back.
Just a little...
It's like a beehive.
-Are you on a school trip?
-I had a trim.
-On a school trip?
-No.
-You live nearby?
-Yes.
You have a small forehead.
Your wallet's not here.
-Why...
-My wallet's gone.
-We didn't take it.
-We didn't.
-We didn't do it.
-Are you suspecting us?
You should just go home.
I'll go then!
That's scary. You can't be like that.
-Go home. It's not here.
-I'm going!
Doesn't your mother say anything
about your hair?
What?
Doesn't your mom say anything
about your hair?
-She does.
-Right?
-She tell you to trim it?
-Yes.
Go get it trimmed.
Have it trimmed, then come back.
At least tell us your name.
Minoru Saji.
Saji?
-Your last name is Saji?
-Saji?
How do you write it?
You write the Kanji for "left"
and then "oneself."
I mean "temple."
How can you mistake it?
You must be lying.
To make a mistake like that.
-"Left temple."
You pronounce it "Saji," not "Hidaridera"?
-What was your first name?
-Minoru.
-Minoru?
-Yes.
You write that normally?
It's the kanji for "jitsu."
Jitsu?
-One letter?
-"Minoru."
-Then you add "noru."
-"Noru"?
In hiragana?
-"Noru" is in hiragana?
-Yes.
-Have you ever seen "noru" in hiragana?
-For Minoru? Never heard of that before.
We got it.
He has so much hair.
And a small forehead.
-Does he suspect us?
-He totally does.
-We didn't take it.
-We'd let you know.
Put on a belt.
-Minoru Saji.
-Minoru. Mi-noru.
Master Sakata was in the hospital
the other day.
Really?
He got a little sick,
and was in for just a while.
One day he called for a nurse.
But when she came to help he said,
"The lion inside the AC unit
keeps looking at me."
What the hell?
We can order a meal, right?
That's right.
-What kind of food do they have?
-Here's the menu.
-Order whatever you want!
-Huh?
Kariyushi.
Kariyushi? Is that my name now?
-Sorry, I was just trying to help.
-No problem at all.
Okay.
Maybe she can change in there.
-Kurosawa can change over there.
-Oh, I see. This area is hidden.
-Okay, that makes sense.
-Yeah.
Oh, I didn't need to bring this.
There's no camera here?
I see.
I guess I should do something.
-Come on!
-Is Fujimoto okay?
I'm getting hungry.
That's dry ice.
Please.
What?
That's dry ice.
That's not regular ice. It's dry ice.
It's coming out of your nose.
What an entertainer.
-So much coming out of your nose.
-He's got it wrong.
-Aren't you guys hungry?
-I am hungry, actually.
-It's been almost three hours.
-Hey! It'll stick to your mouth.
Spit it out.
It'll stick to the inside of your mouth.
-It's dry ice.
-Does it melt?
No, it sticks to your mouth!
That was dangerous!
I like it cold.
-That was way too cold.
-Normal ice isn't enough.
There was so much white smoke coming out.
Nishizawa, don't you have
anything to say about this?
I put it on, but...
Well, I noticed you had it on.
Don't you have anything to say?
Well...
I'm sorry.
-Is this safe?
-Don't let it stick.
-You'll be fine.
-You can't let it stick.
-Just keep rolling it.
-Keep rolling it?
-Otherwise it'll stick.
-Really.
-It will peel off your skin.
-Seriously?
Put some water in quickly.
-I'll put the water in first.
-Ah, but... You're right.
Well...
-You have to close your mouth.
-Then it'll come out of your nose.
So little smoke.
So little.
There's so little smoke,
he's like a bedside humidifier.
-A small one.
-A weak one.
-Those weak ones.
-A small, lamp-shaped one.
It doesn't come out at all.
You left your mouth open.
That was difficult.
-Because your mouth was open.
-It's really difficult.
Take it away. That thing.
Let's put it aside.
Wow, it's frozen!
It solidified!
-I'd love to pour beer in there.
-You'd have big problems.
I'd take the ice out.
The glass will still be chilled.
I see.
What a loud voice.
I see!
Your voice is loud. So loud.
-Miyasako has a loud voice.
-You're eating cheese?
Yes, I'm hungry.
-He has a real singer's voice.
-Right.
I want to hear your voice
Especially when he sings that.
That's not quite right.
That wasn't it?
I want to hear your voice
-Right?
-Wrong.
Just a little wrong.
Really?
"I want to hear your voice..."
I want to hear your voice
Our key was wrong?
"Money" by Shogo Hamada.
MONEY / SHOGO HAMADA
These are oogiri answers
that once got laughs.
-What about the questions?
-The oogiri game?
-You only have the answers?
-They're answers.
-Only answers?
-Is that all?
Come up with a question.
The answers will fit anything.
They'll fit any question?
I'll give you the answers, one by one.
I wrote down a lot.
-They'll work for any question?
-I think so.
Everybody hates this school. Tell us why.
Because for them,
it's just another autumn.
It works, right?
I guess it sounds nice...
-It appeals to the senses.
-It does.
-It sure has your "Iio-style."
-Really.
Okay, let me ask one.
After Kodama, Hikari, and Nozomi,
what will be the name
of the next bullet train?
Madrid's sunshine did it to him.
How long.
What kind of pet don't you want?
Thank you gifts at a funeral.
-The pet gives out the gifts?
-Probably.
-The pet does?
-Probably a black cat.
-Thank you gifts?
-See?
That's scary.
Say something about this photo.
After an intense education in Sweden,
I became a cherry boy.
Cherry boy?
That one fits.
What a miracle!
I simply flipped to the next page!
Maybe it's Sakata that fits everything.
Try doing it in reverse.
He's resonating.
Say something about this photo.
Carbonated drinks aren't the ideal partner
for sponge cake.
He's a gourmet.
If Master Sakata really said that,
it would be super funny.
This is bad.
Let's look at the photo first.
Don't just look at the answer.
-Do it over there.
-Okay.
That way everyone can see both.
-Will you help me?
-Nobu, sit down.
Which answer shall we give next?
This one?
Are you ready?
-Here we go.
-Take a good look at the photo.
Say something about this photo.
While we're waiting,
let's make a heartwarming sauce.
That's what he said.
-Amazing.
-That really is good.
It does fit.
-This could be bad.
-We started something bad.
And it's in Fujimoto's favor.
-You're right.
-Let's do it.
-It works in his favor.
-He's on the performing side.
Fujimoto should take a good look, too.
He nearly laughed already.
Fujimoto, if you show it this way,
we may end up laughing too.
Let's hear him sing!
"Money" by Shogo Hamada.
But he's not Shogo Hamada.
Next.
Say something about this photo.
This is what people call "love."
How did this happen?
Madrid's sunshine did it to him.
In the Spain.
"In the Spain" wasn't there before.
-Get it?
-Do you?
He's not usually like this.
Madrid's sunshine did it to him.
After an intense education in Sweden,
I became a cherry boy.
Cherry boy.
He had a Swedish education.
-The same as Maiko Kawakami.
-Right.
-Free sex.
-Swedish Education.
-Thank you gifts at a funeral.
-It's his nickname.
Master Sakata's, right?
Thank you gifts at a funeral.
Fujimoto is sly.
-He is.
-You're right.
-Why do you keep adding extra bits?
-What exactly is your role?
-"It's his nickname"?
-I'm the support.
-The support?
-The support...
Shall I write something new?
-Just say it.
-I'll write it.
-Right now?
-Now?
-Let's do this.
-In real time.
-Ready?
-That's a little...
-It's raw.
-Yeah.
-It will be a normal oogiri.
-An oogiri show.
That's not good.
It's an oogiri show.
Yes, sure. Thanks.
-Say a word for this photo.
-I love you.
Wait a minute!
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
Come on! Please! That was too much!
You cracked up.
-Well, well, well, well.
-That was a laugh.
No, I said something. It was my voice.
Voice, voice, voice!
-Your voice?
-It was my voice, Mr. Matsumoto!
You can't get away with that.
Nobu was doing that the whole time.
It was all just a matter of timing.
-Let's take a look.
-Okay.
-Say a word for this photo.
-I love you.
You're laughing.
Nobu!
You're eliminated!
This is bad!
Real bad!
I didn't think he'd be the first to go.
The very first.
-The first.
-The first?
My million...
There's no chance at the 10 million?
-No more.
-Nope.
-You'll be a zombie.
-Try to make amends.
-You'll have to be a good zombie.
-That's right.
"Nobu Zombie."
Nobu Zombie?
Isn't he unfunny?
You're right!
That's what might make me laugh.
-Because of that?
-Yeah.
I'm worried I'll laugh at
the nervous-looking zombie.
-Let's go, Nobu.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
-Bye, Nobu.
-But that was unfair.
-What was?
-They focused on me.
-Yeah, you're right.
-They did target you.
-Bye, Nobu!
Bye!
I'll come back as a zombie.
He'll be fine as a zombie.
Nobu as a zombie doesn't seem so bad.
That was pathetic.
But my defense is too weak.
I did. It's about the vasectomy.
-Nobu.
-Yes.
The new ones are...
Of course the air is full of tension,
but it's also pumped full of funniness.
-Say a word for this photo.
-I love you.
Wait a minute!
If you could poke it with a needle,
it would explode in an instant.
I'm so upset.
Let's go.
It started.
There's sashimi, kimchi, meat
and other stuff.
-We have meat?
-We can either cook or order.
I think it would be nicer
if we ate what's here.
You'll cook?
-Wow!
-That's a super premium cut.
Please cook that.
-You're a good cook, right?
-I can cook.
Does anyone want apple juice?
Yes, please.
Get it yourself! You're a junior to me.
Sorry. What a rapid development.
-Why don't you drink some milk?
-You don't mind?
-Do we have milk?
-Show Daigo how you drink milk.
Daigo?
-Wait. Wait a minute.
-You started it.
He can drink the milk.
But we all watch.
Will your mustache be okay?
It's no problem.
Wait, Kurochan.
-It was your idea.
-It was my idea.
But I said to him,
"Why don't you drink for everyone?"
You didn't say "for everyone."
-Daigo was the one who asked.
-Show it to Daigo.
-Can I drink some?
-Yes, but if you go too fast...
The milk will stick to your mustache.
I don't mind.
-Cheers.
-Bottoms up.
Dunk it in. He dunked all of it in.
He dribbled the same way again.
It really doesn't stick.
-It comes out this side every time.
-That's funny.
-Drink some more.
-You don't mind?
Thank you.
-That will stick.
-It'll stick now.
That will...
You got it.
We don't need that face.
This will stick.
How much is he drinking?
He sounds like a sewer.
That'll stick.
Don't say he sounds like a sewer.
But he went "blub blub," like a sewer.
-What?
-Cheers.
That's enough.
Why?
-Hear that slop?
-Enough, right?
Want me to cook it?
-Yeah. Good idea.
-Really?
That was too much.
-Let's see how it goes.
-Sure.
Wow, is this cookable?
Shall we cut it?
It's amazing.
It's thick.
-Wow.
-It's barbecue time.
It's so thick.
Why don't we fry it as a schnitzel?
-The show would end before it's done.
-We'd end up becoming a cooking show.
That won't work?
-If we added eggs we could do it.
-Okay.
Are you okay?
He's furious.
-He got dirty, now he's furious.
-I got meat juice on me.
Stop being so fussy.
-There's meat juice on my jacket.
-Don't fret.
Is that an expensive jacket?
I was wondering if it was expensive.
You always seem to get worried about
things like that.
Do we have a wet towel?
Shall I make one?
Forget about it. You can get dirty today.
Let me do a Lightning Bolt.
No Lightning Bolts, please.
Lightning Bolt?
What's a Lightning Bolt?
Miyasako, let's not.
I was just trying to
cook the meat for everyone.
You may be wearing expensive clothes,
but that's...
-You know.
-Is this necessary?
Lightning Bolt?
-Lend me your back.
-What's a Lightning Bolt?
-Wait a minute.
-You can keep your clothes on.
Straighten up.
Keep your clothes on.
-Keep them on.
-There's Haranishi.
-It's Haranishi.
-Haranishi? There he is.
Wait a minute.
I'm your senior.
We've known each for so long.
-You can't talk like that.
-But I...
I won't allow it. Stand at this angle.
Really, don't...
-I'm scared.
-What's going on?
Ouch!
He's crying.
I've never seen him make that face.
-A grown adult.
-He's like Chaplin.
It hurt even over his clothes.
You and your big mouth.
-I was cooking the meat for you guys.
-You're right.
He deserved it.
He always gets so fussy.
You're still going?
Miyasako, seriously.
You always try to show off.
Sit down.
-Sit.
-What will you do?
Just sit down.
Why do you keep talking back?
That's not good.
That doesn't look good.
That was a really scary one.
That was... He flipped.
-He lost it.
-Scary.
Fujimoto!
He's doing it again.
How cute. Just like a cat.
-You shouldn't have glared at him.
-It's your fault.
Fujimoto...
-You're making it worse.
-Stop it.
You're both seniors, so...
-Watch out.
-That hurts.
That's a tough one.
Wow.
Like COWCOW.
Everyone endured it.
They did. They hung in there.
Kukky was very close to losing it.
Please.
-Keep it friendly, guys.
-Sure.
-I'll cook the meat.
-Thank you.
-They reconciled.
-Sorry.
Did you fool around like that
when you were in Tenso?
We've always fooled around.
Like we just did, for years now.
-That takes me back.
-But now, my bones are out of place.
Especially in my skull.
He has a sadistic side, right?
Toward comedians and mistresses.
Mistresses?
He doesn't have any mistresses, does he?
-Do you do that to women, too?
-I heard he was kind.
He is kind.
Very kind. But...
When he's in bed...
What?
Are you starting something again?
My son's a high school junior, you know?
-How dare you say that?
-Sorry.
-I lied.
-Why?
Is this the mouth that lied?
-It was just a joke.
-Did this mouth lie?
-It was a joke.
-It was this mouth, right?
Directly?
Really. My jaw will fall out.
You had to say it.
But it hurts.
It really hurts.
Looks like Hannya.
-Seriously?
-Seriously.
-Was it that bad?
-It was.
With a little more force...
-One more jerk?
-It would've fallen off.
-You mean dislocated?
-I mean ripped out.
Like in The Mask?
-The movie?
-The film The Mask.
But if your jaw bounced back,
what would be the first thing you say?
-I wonder.
-What would you say?
It stretches a meter, right?
If your jaw drops and comes back,
the skin here would be all saggy.
What would you say when it bounced back?
Is that another oogiri?
That was the topic.
Please don't make me do it.
What do you say after your jaw drops
to the floor and bounces back?
Ginkaku.
What...
What does that mean?
What do you say after your jaw drops
to the floor and bounces back?
I love you.
Quit making that noise.
I don't like going from
"I love you" to "sizzle."
I think it's the perfect sound.
That must have come close.
-Couldn't be helped.
-It was great.
Wow. It barely fits.
That's sizzling.
Is rare okay?
Looks good. I'll flip it.
-Do we have butter or something?
-Sounds good.
I don't remember seeing goodies like that.
There are condiments, I think.
Like spices.
How stimulating.
It was too stimulating.
-Are you okay?
-I'm sorry.
There were shells
in the omelet.
-Shells in the omelet?
-That was an omelet?
-There were eggshells.
-Eggshells in the omelet.
This...
-You got sick because of eggshells?
-Yes.
I see.
That's why you threw up.
I'm sorry.
I'm using so many of these.
Don't move.
I've used so many towels.
I feel sick.
It broke.
So spicy.
That was so spicy.
It's stuck in my teeth.
These are bladder control sheets.
-This one too?
-None work.
Nothing works.
It's off now.
Kukky is up to something, too.
It's working.
Ouch!
Hey, Iio.
Iio?
CARBONATED WATER
Is Iio laughing?
-Huh?
-Who was it?
-Who laughed?
-It wasn't me.
Huh?
Well, I saw Iio...
No!
He was laughing.
What?
-Really?
-Yeah.
-That's laughing, right?
-Yes.
He was laughing, right?
The thing is, it was so slimy,
I nearly vomited.
-You laughed at the sliminess?
-I laughed at the sliminess...
Did I really laugh?
What happened?
Really! It was so slimy...
Okay, I'll make that an orange card.
Why did I put that in my mouth?
So, well...
Iio will be eliminated with his next card.
I'm sorry.
Putting that in your mouth was gutsy.
While I was watching in the back,
what impressed me the most was
after you gave an answer to the oogiri,
the meat went "sizzle."
What do you say after your jaw drops
to the floor and bounces back?
I love you.
Quit making that noise.
I don't like going from
"I love you" to "sizzle."
I think it's the perfect sound.
That must have come close.
-It's amazing how you kept straight faces.
-But it sure was funny.
You endured it well.
It suddenly sounded like home.
-Suddenly it sounded homey.
-All in one "sizzle."
-We couldn't be further away.
-So homey.
Let's go.
Maybe that's why he went ahead.
He's doing that thing. I bet you.
-He must be.
-He is.
Kukky, wait. I don't want it.
This is bad.
Really bad.
Kukky, it's almost ready.
Who are you supposed to be?
Shinya Yamamoto.
Shinya Yamamoto?
-The director.
-The film director?
If I say I'm Shinya Yamamoto,
I'm Shinya Yamamoto, damn it.
He has to remove that thing to talk?
-It must be hard to speak.
-It must be.
Have Yamamoto's teeth always been so...
Do they protrude so much?
His teeth don't stick out.
He's not that pale.
He's not that bald, either.
Stop cooking that meat
so smart and cheerfully.
Excuse me.
My bad. Sorry.
What are you doing here?
It's great.
I'm out here on location.
Excuse me.
It's a great location,
so I came to check it out, naturally.
Shinya checks things out, you know?
It's the director.
He's just like the director.
Are you shooting a movie?
-Excuse me.
-Please stop putting that there.
It's someone's head.
I think it's best not to.
Okay?
Sorry.
Let me put this on you.
What are you doing?
Excuse me.
You were being polite?
It must be a lot different
without direct contact.
But...
Let's eat the meat.
Are you staying?
You'll stay like that?
Seriously?
-Iio?
-Yes.
Look properly.
The director has joined us.
But Fujimoto...
-You have to...
-No.
Can you share the dinner table with him?
Let's eat.
Miyasako...
-Please serve the meat. I can't stand it.
-Wow.
What's wrong?
Why are you having trouble
putting them in?
It was smooth before.
The moisture.
The moisture makes them expand.
-What was that?
-What did he say?
These dentures...
The moisture...
Moisture...
It makes them expand.
That's evil.
They're evil.
Take them out...
If you want to eat, take them out.
That's evil.
-That was gross!
-That was long!
That lasted so long.
You okay, Daigo? Sorry about that.
That really was insane.
I nearly lost it when
that banana came out.
Damn it!
That was close!
He didn't even get one bite.
I'm exhausted.
That was tiring for us, too.
I didn't eat a thing.
You didn't even get one bite!
Every one of you came close.
How could you endure that?
He was actually too close to see.
-That was nasty.
-He was too close.
It was the distance
between Sigourney Weaver and the Alien.
-The second one.
-Aliens.
That's how close they were there.
But I think he saved you all there.
It was thanks to Miyasako.
That tension was unbearable.
Let's take a look.
-That was impossible.
-I'm sure it was.
-What else could I do?
-You had no choice.
-That was impossible.
-It sure was.
Miyasako gets his first card.
-Yellow.
-He endured so much.
Zombie Time!
I forgot about that!
I can't take it anymore!
It's insane!