COCORICO Channel (COCORICO Channel)
(COCORICO Channel)
Hello, everyone. (Okuhida TV announcer, Kotaro Yamashita Cooking. specialist, Kaname Inoue)
(Okuhida TV announcer, Kotaro Yamashita Cooking. specialist, Kaname Inoue)
"What's the main dish today?" (Okuhida TV announcer, Kotaro Yamashita Cooking. specialist, Kaname Inoue)
Today's recipe is  (Okuhida TV announcer, Kotaro Yamashita Cooking. specialist, Kaname Inoue)
popular Chinese dish at home, (mapo dofu)
mapo dofu. (mapo dofu)
Well, mapo dofu
is very popular and easy to cook.
We can adjust
its hotness as we like.
And more over,
it's really suit for rice, I think.
Because it's been cold these days,
we're happy with such hot and warm dish.
Well, it's far from some dishes in a pot.
But  both it and mapo dofu
can make you warm.
Now, let's start cooking.
First, here's 400 grams of firm tofu. (First, here's 400 grams of firm tofu.)
(400 grams of firm tofu.)
This tofu, (400 grams of firm tofu.)
please cut in 1 inch each (400 grams of firm tofu.)
as equal as you can. (400 grams of firm tofu.)
Hey, can we use fine-grained tofu?
Well, it's easy to be broken its shape.
So I recommend firm one for mapo dofu.
Firm tofu is suits for mapo dofu.
So, how about tamago-dofu?
Well, it already
has flavor of egg.
So it doesn't also suit for mapo dofu.
I'm sorry,
but tamago-dofu doesn't suit for mapo dofu.
So, how about kouya-dofu?
Oh, it's
out of question. (It's out of question.)
I'm sorry. (It's out of question.)
Kouya-dofu is out of question. (Kouya-dofu is out of question.)
Now, prepare hot water
and putting salt to parboil tofu.
Please prepare 2/1 teaspoonful of salt. (Salt  2/1 teaspoon)
Okay. (Salt  2/1 teaspoon)
Hey, you know we write "tofu" as "spoiled bean" in kanji, right?
Don't you feel so good?
Well, I feel nothing.
And tofu is a kind of fermented food.
So,I don't feel bad.
It's okay.
Tofu is a kind of fermented food. (Tofu is a kind of fermented food.)
So please feel easy. (So please feel easy.)
Well, now
let's make sauce for tofu.
There're ingredients;
100 grams of minced meat, a slice of garlic, 2/1 teaspoonful of Tobanjan, (・minced meat 100g ・water 1 cup ・pepper little ・garlic 1 slice ・sake 1 tablespoon ・green onion 1/2(chopped) ・Tobanjan 1/2 teaspoon ・soy sauce 1 tablespoon ・Temmenjan 1 and 2/1 tablespoon ・salt 1/2 )
1 and 1/2 tablespoonful of Tenmenjan, 1 cup of water, sake, and soy sauce, (・minced meat 100g ・water 1 cup ・pepper little ・garlic 1 slice ・sake 1 tablespoon ・green onion 1/2(chopped) ・Tobanjan 1/2 teaspoon ・soy sauce 1 tablespoon ・Temmenjan 1 and 2/1 tablespoon ・salt 1/2 )
1/2 teaspoonful of salt, a little pepper, and 1/2 of chopped green onion. (・minced meat 100g ・water 1 cup ・pepper little ・garlic 1 slice ・sake 1 tablespoon ・green onion 1/2(chopped) ・Tobanjan 1/2 teaspoon ・soy sauce 1 tablespoon ・Temmenjan 1 and 2/1 tablespoon ・salt 1/2 )
Alright, let's start. (・minced meat 100g ・water 1 cup ・pepper little ・garlic 1 slice ・sake 1 tablespoon ・green onion 1/2(chopped) ・Tobanjan 1/2 teaspoon ・soy sauce 1 tablespoon ・Temmenjan 1 and 2/1 tablespoon ・salt 1/2 )
Hey, if we're not good at chopping green onion,
can we put in whole long one?
Well, it's too difficult
for us to eat,
so try chopping as possible as you can.
Try chopping green onion as possible as you can. (Try chopping green onion as possible as you can.)
Then, let's heat oil in Chinese wok.
There's 1 tablespoonful of oil here. (There's 1 tablespoonful of oil here.)
And (There's 1 tablespoonful of oil here.)
minced garlic. (Garlic (chopped))
After you catch its smell,
add minced meat there. (Minced meat 100g)
Hey, what should we do if we can't catch its smell?
Don't worry.
You'll be sure to catch the smell.
You can surely catch the smell.
Then, after heating meat,
add Tobanjan. And after catching its smell, add Tenmenjan.
Hey, what should we do if we can't catch its smell?
Don't worry. You'll be sure to catch the smell.
You can see it's heating, right?
You can surely catch the smell. (You can surely catch the smell.)
Alright.
And, as I told you before,
after heating chopped garlic,
minced meat will be cooked
and you can catch the smell. Then, add Tenmenjan.
After mix it, add water
and boil them up.
Hey, what should we do if it won't be boiled up?
Well, it's unbelievable.
It'll surely get boiled up.
I guarantee it.
I guarantee it, too. (I guarantee it, too.)
And okay.
Now, put tofu.
Because we cook mapo dofu, it's necessary.
Hey, do we need to add tofu?
Sure because it's mapo tofu.
You have to put it.
Please
put tofu.
Then add soy sauce, sake, salt and pepper.
Finally add starch with water for thickness.
The balance of water and stretch is 1:1.
Hey, do we only add thickness this time?
Yes?
Are there any netami (jealousy), sonemi (envious) and harami (diaphragm meat) needed? (Are there any netami (jealousy), sonemi (envious) and harami (diaphragm meat) needed?)
You know it'll be different dish if you add harami, right?
Alright. now
we've completed it. Look.
Well.
Let's dish up it.
and this is mapo dofu we've made 1 hour ago.
Well,
why do you show this now?
You don't have to
this now.
You don't need it because there's just completed one.
And dishing up,
it's time to try.
Let's try.
Alright.
Well.
Now...
It's good.
Yeah.
And its hotness is also good.
It's delicious.
I want rice, too.
Hey, what are you eating?
You know it is
mapo dofu.
Now let's review ingredients. (Mapo dofu ・firm tofu  400g sake 1 tablespoon ・water 1 cup ・minced meat 100g ・soy sauce 1 tablespoon ・starch with water little ・garlic 1 slice ・salt 1/2 teaspoon ・green onion 1/2 ・Tobanjan 1/2 teaspoon ・pepper little ・Temmenjan 1 and 2/1 tablespoon ・oil 1 tablespoon)
(Mapo dofu ・firm tofu  400g sake 1 tablespoon ・water 1 cup ・minced meat 100g ・soy sauce 1 tablespoon ・starch with water little ・garlic 1 slice ・salt 1/2 teaspoon ・green onion 1/2 ・Tobanjan 1/2 teaspoon ・pepper little ・Temmenjan 1 and 2/1 tablespoon ・oil 1 tablespoon)
We'll show you how to make Japanese popular Khao Man Kai tomorrow. (Khao Man Kai)
(Khao Man Kai)
(What's the main dish today? END)
Please subscribe! (Please subscribe!)
(Please subscribe!)