THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
This time I want to make sure we have
a clear, definite winner to the game.
I want to make it impossible
for passive players to win.
That's the plan this time.
You might call it an improvement.
We will be adding even tougher new rules.
I think these new rules will make
what's funny about the show more obvious.
That's how this season will unfold.
That hurts!
If they stop worrying about
structure and order,
things will get ugly,
and the game will fall into utter chaos.
That's what I hope to see.
My blow-up doll won't blow up.
You only brought titties
to thish sh-show...
PLAYERS DEFEATED SO FAR:
KAZUYA KOJIMA, JIMMY ONISHI,
MIYUKI OSHIMA, ATSUHIRO TSUDA.
It's sweet.
You put sugar in it, didn't you?
Oshima!
That's right.
Huh?
What's he doing?
"In Yoyogi..."
At 5:00 p.m.
-What is this?
-It's scary. Who is it supposed to be?
No idea.
It's scary.
What is it?
Is he a beer store owner?
-What is it.
-Why does it say "beer"?
We're going to restart.
-What's it based on?
-What's the concept?
Tell us what it is, Yoshimura.
I don't know its concept,
but it came up as the funniest mask
on the Internet.
Why does it say "beer"?
Is he a beer shop owner?
Yes. He likes beer.
A beer liker.
A beer liker?
If you say so.
-I'm cold.
-Maybe we should put on some clothes.
Yes, you should.
What are you wearing, Saito?
These?
Clothes.
-Your everyday clothes?
-Yes.
Your fashion sense sucks.
You wear that normally? Like, daily?
I do, actually.
Only baseball players wear clothes
like that.
I played Little League,
but they're just easy to move in.
That's an undershirt.
-It's lame.
-Fujimoto?
My stylist suggested it.
Scary. Scary. Scary.
That really is scary.
That was Saito's fault.
He ruined it.
Me?
I totally agree with him.
These two had me on the ropes,
but you turned off the pressure.
But his first character
totally missed the mark.
-You don't...
-You're overrating him.
You don't get it.
When I first came out,
I could tell they were
fighting to keep it in.
Then, the mask...
Of course, they didn't laugh.
They'd be out.
Those tits aren't funny at all.
But you came out like you thought
it was really funny.
I watched you.
Wait up!
Why didn't you have anything?
What the hell was that?
Himura laughed, right?
No way.
Why didn't you have any joke?
That wasn't right.
You can't do that.
I don't want to be out for that!
I looked for your gimmick,
but you had none!
What the hell was that?
What was it?
What were you doing?
Well, I wanted to do something.
You had something going.
That thing you had going.
Where you were all
dancing around together.
I wanted to jump in,
but you finished without me.
That's not the point.
-But...
-I wanted to join in!
-You came empty-handed!
-I lost the timing!
Himura...
It was me, wasn't it?
But, I think that should be
an orange card.
You're a lifesaver!
I think that's an orange card,
but let us check.
Those tits aren't funny at all.
But you came out like you thought
it was really funny.
I watched you.
Wait up!
Why didn't you have anything?
The next logical step is to give you
an orange card.
-Thank goodness.
-Last chance.
-Next time, I'm out. Okay, thank you.
-No more chances.
-What is humor?
-That's a good question.
-I don't know anymore.
-Exactly.
-Me, too.
-I lost it.
He just came out...
What happened there?
You looked like you'd been
sleeping upstairs.
You came down because you felt peckish.
The worst thing is,
he didn't even try to make us laugh.
-Here we go.
-You're right...
-That couldn't have been helped.
-That was close.
What's this for?
I don't know.
Maybe we could swing it around.
Okay, I'll swing it like this.
Try to dodge it.
-Like this?
-Yeah.
Is that a rubber ball?
Will it hurt if it hits us?
I don't know.
Did that hurt?
Not really.
Don't hit him in the ear.
-Is it a rubber ball?
-Yeah.
-Then it should be fine.
-They hurt, too.
Watch out for the ears.
Okay.
Shall we make a rule where we win
if we dodge it five times in a row?
Where did that come from?
-Let's do it.
-Okay.
What would you say about
going back to the vacuum?
Why not?
The vacuum?
I think Jimmy already took the vacuum
to its peak.
-I'm not so sure.
-Can it get funnier?
Himura tried doing something,
and now things have settled down again.
I think now would be a good time
to do the vacuum game again.
But what exactly is the point of
the vacuum game?
You want to suck someone's dick,
then put it in someone's mouth?
Is that the game?
-I'm not sure.
-Me, neither.
Why not suck with our mouths?
Suck what?
Dicks.
You're kidding.
That's too much.
Whispering doesn't make that okay.
If we do that, this becomes porn.
Dicks in mouths is porn.
Who'd laugh?
Oh, it would become one of those?
Sorry, I only had comedy on my mind.
-It would become one of those?
-Yes. Bad idea.
-Then how about this?
-What an idiot.
I came up with a game.
-I brought Akira's act today.
-Whose act?
Akira 100%.
His tray act.
He lent me one of the trays
he actually uses.
Wow.
So, I will do Akira's performance.
To win the game,
you have to slurp my balls.
-Come again?
-Akira flips it quickly, right?
-That's the game.
-We aim when you flip?
Whoever is able to slurp my balls
when they're exposed wins the game.
I see.
-Shall we?
-Go for it.
I think it's perfect.
What percent will Kotouge be?
Good question.
-What percent will you be?
-Percent? What do you mean?
Akira is 100%...
You're too close.
-What does he mean?
-Enough already.
What percent?
-Because Akira is 100%?
-That was the joke.
-What was that last bit?
-What can I do?
You don't want to do this?
We've had enough of that.
Let's do his thing.
Just wait for him, okay?
-Is he ready?
-I doubt it. Are you ready?
Come out when you're ready.
Akira is so fast when he flips that tray.
Where should we...
Why eat now?
I'm ready.
What are the rules again?
You attack, I defend.
I'll flip this tray around.
-In the meantime...
-I latch onto it, right?
-If you can, you win.
-Okay.
If you fail, my defense wins.
Will this work?
Ready?
Did I get him?
-I think you did.
-Yeah.
But that was...
What was that?
That time, I cheated.
I'm supposed to flip it.
But I was too chicken.
I pulled the tray straight back.
Even if you flip it, they'll crash.
-I come from this angle.
-That definitely won't work.
Should we just slurp my balls?
I got it. Let's try this...
Just "slurp" your balls?
That defeats the purpose.
Who slurps?
The tray is in the way, right?
Why slurp your balls?
The tray's in the way, right?
Just squirt my balls.
-"Squirt"?
-Slurp.
What do you mean?
The tray swivels forwards,
so they're always going to smash.
-We'll always hit the tray.
-Yeah.
Maybe you should slide the tray up.
That looks good.
-Wait.
-Let's try it.
Himura, come closer.
Will this work?
I don't like that!
That hurt.
Huh?
-What was that?
-What was what?
We told you to slide the tray up...
I got scared!
Having your balls slurped is scary!
Go like this.
-Then turn like this.
-That makes sense.
Without the tray.
You're getting rid of Akira.
-Let's slurp...
-I want to do Akira.
I want to do Akira!
If we lose the tray,
there will be no Akira in this.
The usual Akira won't work.
That's why we changed the rules.
If we lose Akira's tray too,
this will just be ball-slurping.
I want to do Akira!
Okay. Let's put Akira's tray here.
You can stand on it and spin around.
-How about that?
-How about what?
-Stand on it.
-Huh? Stand on it?
-Try it.
-Then spin.
-Now twist to the side.
-Twist.
See? You're Akira.
Have you ever seen Akira do this?
You're just like Akira.
Twist. Twist. Twist.
It works, right?
I dodge the vacuum like this?
You need to twist around farther.
Twist harder.
Twist your hips.
That's it!
I get it!
Great. We can't see them.
Good. Good.
Let's go with this. It's perfect.
You're Akira.
-Ready?
-I am.
I'm still okay.
Use those hips!
No!
Ouch!
He got impaled on the trunk.
It stabbed into him.
This part dug right into him.
I had the perfect angle.
He hit this part hard.
You have a wound on your back.
-Your back...
-Are you okay?
Kotouge?
Now I'm inhaling helium?
That's mine.
Is this really the time for helium?
-It's not working. You forced it.
-It's your normal voice.
I brought that.
I brought it.
-That's your normal voice.
-Same old voice.
Guys, please.
They keep on making chaos.
I brought one, too.
Saito's at it again.
But I brought one, too.
Look.
That's a bruise.
Am I injured?
Am I?
-You've done nothing but get injured.
-Wait a minute.
All he does is injure himself.
The poor guy.
Nothing but injuries.
-It's not that type of battle.
-He keeps hurting himself.
I nearly forgot why I'm here.
Himura...
-That was out, right?
-The decision's made?
He's out.
-He did it again.
-How injured can you get?
Let's look at what happened.
Saito's at it again.
I brought one, too.
Look.
Stop injuring yourself.
No more injuries.
Quit injuring yourself.
It was an accident.
I didn't do it on purpose.
It's a bit funny, but I'm worried too.
That's how severe it was.
You've injured your back and your head.
First you got dented, then you bled.
Himura, it's time to leave.
-Bye.
-See you again.
-Good work.
With Himura gone, this is a big chance.
This is getting hot!
That was a weird way to end.
The atmosphere in there was bizarre.
Really bizarre.
Everyone wants to do something, but...
Especially Saito and Yoshimura.
I know they want to do something.
But it's difficult, as you'd expect.
How can I explain it?
You can't do everything you want to.
-The prize money is within our grasps.
-It sure is!
Eleven million yen, right?
-That's right.
-Right?
We have to focus.
-We'll definitely have a winner today.
-Perfect!
But you're all hanging by a thread.
Understood. Sorry.
This will be tough.
Real tough.
Here we go.
It's like we're in a traffic jam.
I don't know whether to wait,
or just go for it.
Does that make everybody's voice higher?
Why don't we all try it?
You just press here.
You're doing it wrong.
You need to breathe out first.
This... Huh?
That was pathetic.
-Give it here.
-Let Fujimoto do it.
I had to pinch my nose?
That should work.
Hello.
See?
Was that me?
It might be me.
No way.
Who was it?
My voice is still...
That wasn't me.
-Me neither.
-Who was it?
Actually, I did smirk.
Maybe he's gotten stricter.
-Really?
It can't be true.
Would you call that out?
I don't know.
Who is it?
Well...
I'm a little suspicious of Kotouge.
But...
For a slight smirk?
But I did make one.
Let's take a look.
That should work.
Hello.
He's a grandfather.
He was looking at his grandchild.
That's the look he gave me.
What a kind, gentle face.
He gave me a big, sweet smile.
Wait! Really?
-He made no sound.
-Good point.
I kept it in!
What's this sense of unity?
It's like you're all on the same team.
-We don't want him expelled for that.
-I see.
-That's how you guys feel?
-He's a comrade in arms.
Indeed, that deserves
an orange card.
That was close!
You're on thin ice.
That was close.
I'm cold.
Because you're naked.
Even still.
Restart.
He got me.
-But it was funny.
-I bought two of these.
What?
-Don't you ever have enough?
-Can I try it?
I haven't done it yet.
There's no need.
It already worked once.
What's the first step?
Going by his face,
I don't think a high-pitched voice
will be very funny...
-It will suit him too much.
-I see.
-But give it a shot.
-Okay.
I exhale first, right?
Let all the air out, pinch your nose,
then suck.
Blow like you're trying to get
all the air out of your lungs.
Don't pinch your nose yet.
Hello.
That's a relief.
-It wasn't funny.
-I told you.
Isn't Yoshimura acting like me today?
You keep honing in on me, but...
He didn't need the teeth.
He's been bombing a lot today, too.
I wanted the straightforward version.
-Me, too.
-Right?
Why did you do that?
The simple version would've been fine.
It was hard to hear you
because of those teeth.
True.
-Exactly.
-That was the problem?
We wanted to hear your voice.
Will Kotouge be all right?
Can I have some tea?
Tea, please.
-That is funny.
-Yes, helium is funny.
It really is.
Comedy needs a gap.
I'll lose the teeth.
-Do it normally.
-Try that.
I think helium loves me.
That's right. Let me do that.
I'll do that... Huh?
It didn't really change.
This doesn't work.
Let me do that.
Do what?
I'm cold.
Huh? Where did I put it?
I'm hungry.
We can do nipple sumo.
Let's do that afterwards.
Do you know this?
-No. What is it?
-You don't?
-Gosso.
-It's Gosso!
-I've never heard of it.
-I was given this at work the other day.
-It's nose hair wax, right?
-It pulls out all your nose hair.
It pulls out everything.
Does it hurt?
It hurts a little, but it really works.
Want to try it?
I did it once.
It removed everything.
-How does this work?
-Don't you know?
-You melt them?
-In the microwave.
-Doesn't it get hot?
-You microwave them.
You heat them in the microwave?
That's right.
It's nothing to worry about.
That's twisted.
Heat for two minutes at 700 watts.
We have a microwave. Perfect.
Two minutes. 700 watts. Just as it is?
You add water first.
Water?
How much water?
Add water, heat for two minutes.
Who wants to try?
I don't have much nose hair.
Can I do it then?
Heat this at 700 watts.
For two minutes.
If it's 600 watts, make it four minutes.
700 watts...
It's 500 watts.
Will three minutes do?
500 watts? In that case...
-Maybe I'll have a beer.
-Go for it.
Yeah. I'm having a beer.
-500 watts needs five minutes.
-Five minutes? That's quite long.
-Is there no option for 700 watts?
-No.
-What about 600 watts?
There is 500 and 200 watts.
-Only 500 and 200?
-Can we raise this?
-I guess we can't.
-Just go with that.
Five minutes.
It will take five minutes.
Why did you take milk instead of beer?
I want a croissant first.
I'll eat a croissant,
then I'll drink a beer.
Anybody want milk?
-Nobody?
-No, thanks.
Has the microwave stopped?
It won't work.
It's scary.
It stops at 30 seconds.
-Is it broken?
-I wouldn't touch it.
Really?
-It won't work?
-It's scary.
It will work.
Huh?
Doesn't that say 200 watts?
It only has 200 watts.
-It said 500 before.
-Really?
Yeah.
Well, this won't work...
It's broken.
You laughed.
-Here it comes.
-Is it too weak?
Huh?
Who was it?
-Fujimoto?
-He did it. He's gone.
Really?
I did the same thing as Daisuke.
Eh?
I really screwed up.
Are 200 watts funny?
Doesn't that say 200 watts?
It only has 200 watts.
-It said 500 before.
-Really?
Yeah.
Well, this won't work...
It's broken.
Why did you laugh so normally?
-What's so funny?
-Please forgive me.
That isn't right.
Well, you have been doing a good job.
You've been on the attack.
I'll give you an orange card.
-Thank goodness.
-But you have no more chances.
-Kotouge, too.
-That's right. I can't slip up.
That was scary!
But Saito and Yoshimura
haven't scored any points.
ATTACK POINTS: FUJIMOTO = 3, KOTOUGE = 2,
YOSHIMURA = 0, SAITO = 0
I can't think of anything.
My mind's completely stopped.
You ran out of gas now?
-Things got too nice and cozy.
-You're right.
-I let something like 200 watts get me.
-Sorry.
Saito and Yoshimura have some work to do.
Yes. This is shameful. I'm sorry.
It's shameful. You're five watt comedians.
Hey!
Who are you calling a five watt comedian?
Restart.
I'm in trouble. I have no points at all.
Would you like a croissant?
Fujimoto.
Would you like a croissant, or not?
I'll take one. Are they...
-Are they sweet?
-Yeah.
Look at Fujimoto.
-Want this one?
-I'm good.
-Don't squeeze them.
-Sorry.
Fujimoto, it really does have 500 watts.
It looks good.
Bring me your nose hair!
He can't. It needs a few more minutes.
Should we just do it now?
-You have to melt it.
-It won't work.
Let's all calm down.
Yoshimura, stop being so crabby.
-Me?
-Calm down.
-I'm not.
-He's not being crabby, he's just...
That microwave is too weak.
How strong is it?
200 watts.
Are 200 watts that funny?
-That's weird.
-It wasn't funny.
One minute left. Shall we do it now?
You have to wait!
Why?
Peek inside. Has it melted?
I can't see.
It has to melt first.
I can't see inside.
-How many watts?
-200 watts.
Please stop saying 200 watts.
200 watts?
We have to say 200 watts sometimes.
Enough of that. It's ready.
Is it done?
Here it comes. Who wants to go?
Who wants to go? It's melted. Perfect.
That's hot.
Is this safe?
I think it's just going to burn.
It did a good job for 200 watts.
Normally, it would be rock-hard.
Maybe it was the strongest 200 watts
of the batch.
It's one of those 200 watts
that are close to 300 watts.
But it wasn't quite 300,
so they called it 200 watts.
Drop it, already.
Look at what you did.
It got all hard while you guys
were talking nonsense.
Is it ruined?
It's fine. Here.
It's still melted!
It's fine. Don't worry.
That's scary.
What is that?
Both sides?
That's hot.
But, look.
It's dripping.
-Is it working?
-You used too much.
Don't pull them out!
Is this really safe?
I don't know,
but it's getting more than your nose hair.
-It's on his skin.
-It's fine.
He's in trouble.
This is bad.
That is tough.
That is really tough.
Is that one minute?
I think that's long enough.
Go one side at a time.
"Once the wax solidifies,
pull them out at once."
Wait. Both of them?
Do it one at a time.
I think we should do both.
That is amazing.
-That will take its toll.
-This will hurt.
-Gag him. He'll bite his tongue.
-It's three minutes.
That hurts. My ears.
They won't come out. Have a feel.
-Look.
-That's rock-hard.
We waited too long.
Wait, I have an ear infection.
Let's pull out his ear infection.
Wait. I can only breathe through my mouth.
I won't pull. It's just...
Look at that.
We waited too long.
Look at him.
Look what happened.
I won't pull them out.
Don't worry.
His nose will come off.
See?
This is impossible.
-Don't worry.
-Does it hurt?
Yes.
His nose...
I may have screwed up.
I have an ear infection.
That doesn't change anything.
When my nose is blocked...
What happens? It's just an ear infection.
I can't breathe.
Well...
Somebody pull them. I'm too scared.
I can't do this myself.
I'll do it.
That hurts.
The right one will come out.
Do the right one first.
-They're solid.
-It will come out.
The right one. Pull it right out.
Here goes.
Ready...
This is scary.
Go for it.
Wow.
It's like a porcupine.
There's one really long hair.
My ear's always infected.
-When my nose is blocked...
-It's that bad?
Rip it right out.
This is bad.
Look at him.
It's stuck that strongly.
See? Take a good look.
This is not coming out.
But you have to rip it out.
-See?
-You can do it.
It will come out.
Here goes.
Ready...
That has to hurt.
Quit following me.
He moves just by doing this.
Just pull it out.
I feel bad for him.
Wait!
It's coming.
-It will come out. Pull it.
-Please...
Please tell me when you'll do it.
Should we...
But...
I'm scared.
-Should we...
-We should...
Let's just do it.
You can do it. Right?
-Help me pull my hand, Fujimoto.
-Okay.
Ready? Here goes.
Look.
Wow.
It's like a porcupine.
You keep bombing with that.
It failed the first time.
Wow. It removes so much hair.
-That is amazing.
-It pulls out a lot, right?
Is it okay to lose that hair?
It's a defense mechanism...
He still has a lot left.
My ears...
We should do it again.
-My ears are...
-Don't worry about your ears.
-You're fine.
-You still have a lot of nose hair.
Do I have an ear infection?
-You do.
-Your eyebrows...
Are they drawn on?
-No.
-Your eyebrows are drawn on.
Is that for work or play?
-Why draw on eyebrows?
-I drew them on over there just now.
But it wasn't funny, so I wiped them off.
Should we do it again, or not?
-I think that's enough.
-Yeah.
Let's move onto the next game. Nipples?
Let's do the nipple thing.
-Nipples, okay?
-How does it look?
-It looks really good.
-Really?
Nipple sumo.
This time, I'm attaching importance to
something called Attack Points.
I created a system where you can't win
if you don't attack.
ATTACK POINTS: FUJIMOTO = 3, KOTOUGE = 2,
YOSHIMURA = 0, SAITO = 0
If you get in a deadlock, you lose.
I thought we needed to incorporate
a system like that.
I think we will have a winner this time.
My only weapon is the fact
that I went to acting school.
ATTACK POINTS: ZERO
I was trained at the
Bungakuza Theater Company as an actor.
I believe that my acting skills
are my greatest weapon.
It's all about finding
the right time and place
to use my acting skills
and put them on display.
Okay!
I'm not sure how skilled
the other members are,
but I do believe that's where I'll excel.
I want to use that as my weapon
to make them laugh today.
Why am I here?
ATTACK POINTS: ZERO
Out of all the other comedians,
I want to be the champ.
I want be called "Number One."
Honor. Status. Wealth.
I want Mr. Matsumoto to acknowledge me.
I'm here for all of the above.
Amid all that tension,
in that peculiar environment,
what will I do?
What will they laugh at?
Just thinking about it terrifies me.
This is a nightmare.
Why did he come up with this concept?
-Why don't I have any points? Let's do it!
-Shall we?
Ouch!
Let's get on with this. We have no choice.
Ouch. Why haven't I won a single point?
This isn't me. Dammit.
What an unfunny comedian.
The next 30 minutes
will decide the winner.
You're too slow. That's stalling.
-We have no time.
-Let's get on with this.
Do we need microphones?
-No, we don't.
-Right?
We all have loud voices.
-Right.
-Let's go.
-Just speak up.
-Sounds good.
Okay!
-Okay!
-All right!
-What a day!
All right!
-Let's do this.
-Stretch out the rope.
Wait! Why attach me first?
We have to attach them at the same time.
Are you sure this won't
rip our nipples off?
It really might.
-The line's too short.
-This hurts.
I'll get injured again.
-That hurts!
-It hurts!
I can feel that.
Ouch!
That really hurts!
Quickly! Quickly! Quickly!
Hurry up and pull them!
Let go of the pins.
Ready...
Ow!
They didn't come off.
How strong are your nipples?
You stretched your nipples.
Look at the skin.
I stretched my nipples.
-They're white.
-They stretched.
-What should I do?
-I don't know. Mine don't stretch.
Do stretched nipples go back to normal?
-Are they inverted?
-Stretched.
We have to do it again.
-Wait. My nipples...
-Let's see how far they stretch.
Nipple stretching is embarrassing.
-Let's see what happens.
-Seriously?
Just show us your nipples
as they get stretched.
They're already stretched.
Let's see how far they can go.
I don't want stretched nipples.
Do you want stretched nipples?
I wouldn't like it.
Fine.
I really don't want stretched nipples.
I'm ready!
That hurts!
Stop!
It hurts!
Hurry up and pull it!
They're super-stretched.
Look at Fujimoto.
These won't go back.
These won't go back!
Seriously. Fujimoto.
These nipples aren't going back.
Seriously.
What are you going to do?
-Seriously.
-They'll go back.
They've obviously been stretched.
See?
I have obviously stretched nipples.
They won't go back.
Seriously. They're gone.
Stop it. Seriously. Gone.
Seriously.
-Oh, I really don't like these.
-Just push them back in.
-Come back. That's unfair.
-We've had enough nipple sumo.
No way! I'm going to lose!
What about our balls?
Should we stretch them next?
Let's do that.
Slow down.
Hey! Slow down!
Okay. Let's stretch them.
Saito, we're going to stretch our balls.
-What?
-We're stretching our balls!
-Our balls?
-It's ball-stretch time!
I'll stretch everything.
-Everything...
-It's not prohibited.
But this is crazy.
-That's wrong.
-I did everything.
-You have to stretch them.
-I think I'm too small.
Hey...
-This is too much.
-This is hell.
Don't forget our manners when we stretch.
Mine's too small. It will all go in.
Like I said...
And it's winter.
Let's not forget our manners.
I can't do this in winter.
I shrink.
Then...
We're the two weaklings.
We'll fight each other.
We'll find a winner.
We have to stretch them.
-Right?
-Let's stretch them.
-Okay.
-I'll do my balls. You do your nipples.
Why stretch my nipples again?
-Do wherever stretches.
-Where do I stretch?
Wait. Let me strip, too.
Oops.
Seeing Fujimoto naked is a rare treat.
What?
Yoshimura?
Yoshimura? Really?
I should be safe.
-Who was it?
-Who?
Was it both of you?
No way!
Who was it?
Mr. Matsumoto?
Yoshimura.
I think that was an orange.
-Maybe.
-He gets an orange?
Let's check the tape.
Joyman popped out.
So that's what happened!
-It was Joyman.
-Joyman...
How sly!
-You hid Joyman in your underwear?
-Yes.
Where do I stretch?
-Wait.
-It was the way he dropped it.
Okay. That was an orange.
That's a valuable point, too.
He got us!
Joyman was stuck to his butt for a moment.
It was damp.
And now... We're getting close!
You have 20 minutes left.
Ten million yen, here I come!
Twenty minutes?
It's 10 million yen. Imagine that.
Ten million yen in 20 minutes?
ATTACK POINTS: FUJIMOTO = 4, KOTOUGE = 2
YOSHIMURA = 0, SAITO = 0
-Ten million yen in 20 minutes.
-I'm in trouble!
That was a valuable point for Fujimoto.
-What now?
-What shall we do next?
What can I do?
-Let's play something.
-Why not? I'm up for it.
We should do something.
We can play look-this-way.
Okay. How about green-peas?
Green-peas.
The rock-paper-scissors variant?
-That's it.
-I remember that.
There are a lot of different rules, right?
But I know the basics of green-peas.
Okay.
Let's finish this off with a bang.
-Shall we begin?
-Let's go.
I'm so nervous.
-Will green-peas do?
-Are you in the lead?
-I don't know.
-I think he is.
Especially since he just scored.
No way. I might lose.
Let's do it. Green-peas. Ready...
Why play green-peas?
Ready, go. Green-peas!
Green...
Is he laughing?
-Green-peas?
-Hmm?
Fujimoto is in trouble.
How about a thumb war?
Shall we?
How about a soda chug challenge?
-Let's do that.
-What about green-peas?
Who would play green-peas?
Really?
Fujimoto, let's play green-peas.
Green-peas...
Fujimoto, don't run away.
I'm not.
We're doing the soda chug challenge.
Here's the soda. Now we're ready to go.
In how many seconds?
Let's all drink it together.
-The fastest guy wins?
-Okay.
-Let's do it.
-Fastest guy wins.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
These are cold.
Let's do it.
Is this okay?
-Is what okay?
-We only have 17 minutes left.
Let's go for it.
So, we're chugging?
We're not playing green-peas?
There are only 17 minutes left.
Ready... Go!
That was a really low move.
What did I do?
-Joyman.
-Yeah, well...
Fujimoto.
Seriously? Is that it?
-Seriously?
-For real?
No.
No!
No way!
No, no, no!
I don't want to lose now!
What a waste!
-No way!
-Such a waste.
-Fujimoto?
-No, no, no!
Stop! No!
Don't do it!
What was so funny?
This!
Wherever I looked, I saw Joyman.
He was even under the bottle.
What a waste!
-Revenge of the Joyman.
-I was sure you'd win.
-Seriously?
-Revenge of the Joyman?
Let's take a look.
But you laughed all the way through
that soda bit.
He had Joyman on the bottom.
That's pretty definite.
-I couldn't stop.
-He got stuck.
I kept laughing.
-At that point, I pretty much gave up.
-Yeah. You gave up.
What a waste.
You had nearly sealed the deal.
Did I nearly have it?
-You did.
-Really?
This is so frustrating.
I don't want to leave now.
All because of that? Damn you, Joyman!
Joyman...
He's everywhere!
What's with that? Seriously.
Let's go.
Okay...
-Good work.
-Nice fight.
-Leave it to us!
-Okay.
That's so frustrating!
That's going to sting for a while.
For quite a few days.
I think...
I was just about to win 10 million yen.
That thought must have crossed my mind.
I think that broke my concentration.
My concentration must have slipped,
ever so slightly.
Yeah.
Restart.
So, we should...
What should we do?
-I can't let it end like this.
-Yeah.
I have to do something.
Should we...
-Want to play a game?
-A game...
-We need to stay on the move.
-Let's keep moving!
I have an interesting way of jumping rope.
-Jump rope?
-Yes.
Kotouge.
Kotouge doesn't do well
in situations like this.
If I don't do something, I'll lose!
Old hag!
Huh?
Me?
Really?
Are you serious?
What happened?
It's probably me.
Yoshimura.
That means...
You laughed, right?
When he spat water on that old hag,
almost all of it ricocheted onto me.
All of it.
He spat at a completely different angle.
But I got all the water.
It was like...
It was like a miracle.
Don't call her an old hag.
Old hag!
That was it.
This can't be true.
-It just started to...
-What a waste.
I didn't expect Yoshimura
to drop out here.
Yoshimura...
Dammit.
How pathetic. I didn't do a thing!
That isn't true.
I am so disappointed.
You must be.
We all are.
-Ready to go, Yoshimura?
-I'm sorry.
Let's go home.
-There are only a few minutes left.
-For real?
Do your best.
That was pathetic.
I wasn't able to do anything.
I'm thinking, maybe I should quit comedy.
I am so disappointed.
Why was Joyman the only thing
that worked today?
He was my sole weapon.
I'm so disappointed.
That was a thorough loss.
There's no excuse.
I wasn't talented enough.
I deserve to lose a million yen.
NEXT EPISODE
SEASON 2 FINALE
Who would laugh at that?
-Bring it on!
-You bring it on!
A CHAMPION WILL FINALLY BE BORN
That's the kind of battle I wanted to see.
Right?