[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
We got them all together... That we sure did.
And we already had plenty of comedians in previous seasons.
So I wanted to have a clean break here.
Honestly, Ikemental and Joshimental really brought the whole package together.
From here on out, I am thinking of expanding the range of our guests.
I mean, the participants just have to be human.
As long as they're human they can participate.
Hey!
Are you listening to me?
In spring, I tried planting some spinach seeds given to me by an old gentleman in the neighborhood.
But some unknown weeds came sprouting out.
I tried making some Hitashi with it...
(EN: 1)
And it tasted like nothing I've ever had before.
I wonder... What was that?
With this, we have finally decided to host "Documental Unlimited".
Up until last season we only had comedians participate.
But this time around we have invited people from all walks of life.
There are no limits.
We have prepared the 10 million Yen, and we wait for your arrival.
I hope your courageous participation will lead to fruitful results.
Hitoshi Matsumoto.
-Hello, welcome!
-Thank you for having us!
Please take care of me today.
Thank you for having us.
So we've changed up the formula this time around.
We also stopped the whole "bring your own million Yen" spiel.
-What?
-Really?
Now, we will just give you the 10 million if you win.
That's so nice!
I'm so jealous!
We can avoid all that trouble with the bank, you know?
Totally.
I'm actually pretty excited, or should I say, nervous?
I'm full of expectations today.
It's been a while since I've felt this way.
Right, they might not play well off of each other.
-Oh, right.
-Totally.
Right, they might not play well off of each other.
-Oh, right.
-Totally.
Here they come.
Yes.
Oh, I see.
It's Yusuke.
-It's Kamiji!
-Right, Kamiji.
Thank you for having me!
I'm Yusuke Kamiji. (EN: 2)
I'm an actor, singer, celebrity...
I don't even know what I do anymore, but I'm trying my best.
Excuse me.
Good morning!
Here you go.
I've been watching!
Honestly, I secretly wanted to be picked.
In his case, he's very motivated.
He's an extremely motivated individual.
I'd like to say he'll come pretty well prepared.
Most of all, I want to wear the jacket.
I want it so bad.
I'm here with the full intention of winning.
But he's used to variety shows.
After all, he's been trained by Shinsuke. (EN: 3)
I think he'll do good.
I was a catcher at Yokohama High School's baseball club, and we were pretty good.
If you think about it, the catcher is like the team's director.
So I want to approach this by looking for openings.
There are a lot of cameras!
Here comes another one.
That's a lot of bags!
He's pretty hyped up!
Hello.
It's been a while.
It really has.
Excuse me.
It's really been a minute.
This guy looks strong.
-That's amazing!
-He's gotta be good!
I'm Show Ayanocozey from Kishidan. (EN: 4)
My occupation is: Pro Yankee.
I'm a bit nervous.
Excuse me.
I'm in my day to day clothes but I am Show Ayanocozey from Kishidan.
You really just appeared out of nowhere.
We're in the middle of the street, you know?
I always enjoy watching Documental.
I even watched Ikemental and Joshimental.
I would put my money on him.
He's that kind of musician with just the right amount of tension and relaxation in his spirit.
That's why I think he'll do well.
Preparation has been a big part of my life.
We always have to be prepared for festivals or really, any other event.
I'm always on the edge.
Will I succeed today, or will I pull the short straw?
It's a bit like my days in an indie band, before I even made my debut.
Because it's like a battle royale.
This might be the beginning of a new phase in life for me.
-I had no clue who would be here today.
-I couldn't imagine it either.
It's a weird sense of nervousness.
There're also tons of cameras around.
For real.
I never thought I'd actually be here.
Me neither.
He's also got quite the bag...
He's loaded.
Hello.
-It's Hiro.
-Awesome!
-That's Hiro.
-Hiro!
-Hello!
-Hello.
-That's Hiro.
-Hiro!
-Hello!
-Hello.
Nice to meet you.
-Hello!
-Hello.
Please take care of me.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Hiro, the vocalist of My First Story. (EN: 5)
I'm more nervous than when I played at the Budokan.
(EN: 6)
Good job today.
Good job.
Here you go.
So we're not getting any comedians this time around?
He's our youngest member.
I think he'll be very slippery and maybe even make it to the end.
But I'd bet his offensive power is not great.
I was born into this kind of family, so I might have to make use of that.
I'm gonna give it my best shot.
This is crazy!
Oh my...
I didn't think you'd show up here.
Me neither!
I can only act cool on stage.
So I'm gonna go all out today.
In any case, I will give it my best shot.
I thought there would at least be some comedians here.
Oh right.
I see, I see.
But none for now...
-Right.
-It's all musicians...
Yeah, all of us are musicians!
Who is it?
This is the best!
-This is awesome!
-He'll be way too strong!
Nice to meet you.
-That's a great hairstyle.
-Thank you!
I'm Naomasa Musaka. (EN: 7)
I am an actor by trade.
I will get that 10 million Yen.
This is the invitation.
Oh, from the Master himself, Hitoshi Matsumoto.
Oh my, oh my.
I've written some sketches for Mr. Matsumoto, and he's even directed some of my stuff.
He's been very good to me.
I just thought we needed someone like him.
That's why we invited him.
He's our oldest member.
Have you seen Documental?
I haven't.
But for 10 million Yen, I'd do anything.
It takes guts to appear on this show, you know?
I guess it's our first time meeting, right?
-Yes.
-Please take good care of me.
I'm a bit worried about his stamina.
Well, I've done plenty of 4+ hour plays.
To me a 4 hour play is not that long.
Honestly speaking, it'd be so boring if he won.
So we can still laugh, right?
Director Matsumoto, hasn't been in here yet has he?
-Yes, it's totally fine.
-It's still okay.
At least for now.
He won't come anytime soon.
But in variety shows they sometimes do it...
They sometimes come out.
It's pretty rare...
Hello.
Oh, if it isn't the Yokozuna.
(EN: 8)
Nice to meet you.
Oh, if it isn't the Yokozuna.
(EN: 8)
Nice to meet you.
Will he laugh?
-He won't!
-There's no way!
I am the 65th Yokozuna, Koji Takanohana.
I am here today because I received an invitation.
-This is the invitation.
-Thank you.
Documental...
It seems to be a deeply meaningful project.
When they told me he'd be participating I was like, "Are you serious?!".
Why?!
He must think it's some kind of normal documentary.
But this is something else!
It's a Documental.
As a kid I was often instructed not to show my emotions.
I was taught to act like this from a very young age.
So, I think I still have a bit of that old habit left in me.
He comes from a world where not even a fist pump is allowed.
So I'm very curious as to what Mr. Takanohana will show us.
I see...
I don't want to lose.
I will endure and take home the win.
-He's a superstar!
-Totally!
No, not at all.
I still remember how he won through those injuries.
I could never forget the face you made.
Really?
And that move as he uncovered his face...
Right.
It was such a great match.
Oh, again!
Nice to meet you!
It's his second time, isn't it?
-That's right.
-Right.
-He was in Ikemental.
-Right, Ikemental.
He seems to have enjoyed it quite a lot.
I never thought Katsunori would show up here.
Oh my...
No way, no way...
I'm Katsunori Takahashi. (EN: 10)
I'm an actor and singer.
I'm more nervous about this job than any other project I'm currently involved in.
Could it be?
I'm starting to get flashbacks.
It was very intense.
This guy is good.
I really wanted to bring him in again.
He really made his home at Ikemental.
It was super funny.
I only realized how fun it had been after the fact.
He actually handed me a very heart-warming hand-written letter after the last show.
He wrote of how fun it was to participate in Ikemental.
I do think this is a new kind of challenge.
I really wondered, why did he enjoy it that much?
This is amazing!
I don't wanna sit next to Yusuke.
Why?
Hold on, stay here!
Why?!
Director Shinjo, who was actually with the same agency as me, (EN: 11)
told me he was the only one suited for this job.
And that's when I got this invitation from Mr. Matsumoto.
So I thought it would be a good opportunity to improve my skill as an actor.
There's another empty seat here.
Oh, I'll go there.
Hold on!
It doesn't matter where you sit!
There's no deep meaning behind this.
But Mr. Musaka...
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
I'm so shocked to see you here.
Well, I'm currently doing some plays...
But I had to come since it was Director Matsumoto who called.
Oh, really?
Aren't you quite busy these days?
Really?
I'm also doing some plays at the moment.
Oh, it's been a while!
Hold on, this is crazy.
Hold on!
I think he'll be really good.
He's gonna be strong.
He'll be going all on the offensive.
I'm Shingo Katori. (EN: 12)
I just want to get this started.
What?
I would never refuse.
Shingo Katori will be on Documental.
We really got everyone this time around.
He's a big name.
I mean, he is an idol and he's also had some experience with comedy.
I think he really understands the premise.
Ma-chan invited me, right?
You know, I'm here today as a sort of audition.
To make Matsumoto like me.
I'm betting my whole career on this show.
I hope he goes, "That kid is good".
I'm gonna give everything I got.
Can I sit here?
What is going on?
I don't know!
I hate this!
How do we have this many big names?
What an amazing group.
This one's gonna be hard to predict.
-It's a really wild one.
-For real.
An actor?
I went to watch it yesterday.
-I was surprised.
-Once you watch it...
That's right...
-Oh, that startled me.
-Good morning!
Director!
What a stacked group!
Please take a seat!
I'm really starting to get worried now.
A shared house with all these members would be the worst!
Everyon, please take a seat.
Excuse us.
Oyakata, that is actually my seat...(EN: 13)
Oh, really?
It's fine, we'll just move.
Let's move around.
Please take a seat.
Sorry about that.
First and foremost, I am truly grateful that each and every one of you came today.
-Thank you!
-Thank you.
But I'm really worried about today.
I'm incredibly nervous.
We also have such a big gap in ages.
And everyone comes from a different industry.
So anyway, I don't know what's gonna happen today.
By the way, the prize is 10 million Yen.
-And Katsunori is the only one with experience, right?
-Yes.
That's right.
Right.
-He was on Ikemental.
-Oh, right! Ikemental...
I was here once before.
-He was on Ikemental.
-Oh, right! Ikemental...
I was here once before.
It was incredibly funny.
But unfortunately he laughed early on and dropped out prematurely.
So I hope you go far this time around.
-Please aim for a win today.
-I will try my best.
I'm a bit worried about Hiro.
-Me too...
-He's our youngest member!
That's right, I'm the youngest one here and it's also my first time meeting everyone.
It feels like I've been thrown in the middle of a hurricane.
Your father, Shinichi Mori, won't help you here, you know? (EN: 14)
Right, but I will give it my best.
Right, please do.
I will.
The only one I can't seem to read is Oyakata.
-Totally.
-Me neither.
I think he's gonna be good.
Everyone will laugh when they see those weird eyes of his.
I think so too.
Katori...
How are you feeling?
Katori seems to be quite fired up.
What are you gonna do?
I mean, I always have a smile when I talk.
Oh, right...
"Oh, really?!".
Oh, you'd be out with that.
That's not good.
I can give you an instant red card if it's really bad.
But we have the yellow card and the red card.
And we'll give you an orange one when it's a bit of a grey area.
But I've also brought this with me.
-This is the prize money.
-Awesome!
Awesome!
Before, each person would have to bring his or her own million Yen.
But we've done away with that rule.
Besides, there's no way I'd be able to ask a million Yen from you guys.
So whoever wins can just take this home.
That's awesome.
One of you guys will win.
Alright then, I will go back to judging.
-Please take care of us.
-Please do.
So, I will be taking my leave now.
-Please take care of us.
-Please do.
So, I will be taking my leave now.
The game will start once the buzzer goes off.
I'm so nervous!
Alright then, excuse me!
Thank you!
Take good care of us!
Oh god...
I'm starting to get nervous.
Oh no!
I'm so nervous!
This is not the cast I had pictured!
Everyone...
-Alright, these smiles will vanish once I press this button.
-Yes!
Let's go for another Documental...
It's very exciting.
...Start!
Here we go!
-Who's gonna attack first?
-Who is it?
The first attack is very important.
Right.
I was most nervous when walking through the door.
Oyakata is laughing?
I was super nervous, I could barely sleep yesterday.
-Is Oyakata laughing?
-Is he?
Did you get any sleep?
-Is Oyakata laughing?
-Is he?
I did.
Me too.
That's amazing.
I couldn't sleep...
Actually I was the first to come in.
Did you guys hear any voices before coming in?
Takashi is setting something up.
Everyone was laughing when I came in.
You three were laughing.
Right...
But I didn't hear anything else.
Me neither...
Oh, really?
-That part looks a bit like my home.
-Oh, really?
I was desperate.
Oyakata was definitely laughing right now!
Wasn't that too fast?
Did Oyakata slip?
No way!
Guys! You have to keep a lookout!
But I was watching!
No way!
That has to be the fastest laugh in Documental history.
The fastest!
Eh?!
Did someone laugh?!
Who was it?
This might be the fastest one yet.
It was Takanohana Oyakata.
That's surprising.
So, were you aware of your actions?
Well yes, I turned sociable for a minute there.
Hold on, hold on!
Let's check it out first!
It might have been my mistake so...
-That part looks a bit like my
home.
-Oh, really?
I was desperate.
You can't be doing that!
That was bad!
So fast! That was super fast!
You're out.
You were really smiling.
I mean, this is just a yellow card.
We'll get you even for something as small as that.
Right.
He was just venting.
Right, right.
Oyakata, you took the initiative and sacrificed yourself first.
Thank you.
Thank you, we learned a lot with that.