[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
Actually, this time...
Yeah?
The one that shouldn't have existed.
Right.
We've decided to call it Season 0.
Well, an experiment can also
be experimental-
An experiment can also
be experimental.
I agree.
World Premiere
The Phantom Pilot Episode
What's really sticking out to me...
Trendy Angel's Saito
As soon as things got started,
screamed, "Peh!"
There's no way something
like that would happen
and so,
this is,
They'll say "That's it"!
Right, yeah.
Normally, anyone would laugh
at someone saying "Peh!" on TV
But you know, that seemed like
the beginning to Documental.
That's how I felt.
Yeah.
Whoa, whoa, what is this? (Editor's Note: 1)
This is crazy, whoa.
Seriously, wow.
There's no one here?
This is really, kind of foreboding.
[In Season Zero, no one is allowed
to bring any props with them.]
Wait a second, what is this?
Huh?
Well, I might as well sit down.
Jiro? (EN: 2)
It's you, huh.
What?
I thought you'd be here.
Seriously?
You're here too?
I had a feeling you'd be here.
There's no way I could have known that.
Hey. (EN: 3)
Hello.
Wow
I get it now. This isn't a coincidence, is it.
Since Uchima is here too.
Are you nervous?
I'm not usually the funny one.
I've never been either.
I'm starting to realize that.
Something amazing just appeared. (EN: 4)
From the female contenders.
Where should I sit?
I have no idea.
This sucks.
An extremely clean envelope.
You brought that?
Yeah, I did.
They asked us to.
Because this is serious.
You brought something?
They're clothes. I changed my clothes.
Yeah.
You brought a change of clothes?
Basically, yeah.
If I got sweaty-
I don't think it's going to go that long.
I'm sure everyone will laugh
pretty quickly.
I wonder, I'm not too sure.
It's not me.
That wasn't really-
Something amazing just appeared. (EN: 5)
Wow.
Is this real?
Good morning.
Seriously...
What is he trying to say?
When he keeps saying "Seriously".
Your hair is a bit short isn't it?
Your hair is a bit-
Why'd you cut it?
Since I last saw you,
It's gotten way shorter than before.
Someone crazy could show up any second.
I want to see that.
It's happened again. (EN: 6)
another old man has appeared.
Good morning!
This is different.
Going by what I see,
I'm at a disadvantage.
Going by what you see?
His face looks pretty tough.
It does look tough.
Going by what you see.
Good morning. (EN: 7)
Good morning.
Another plain one has shown up.
Did you bring one million yen?
What?
Do you have the one million yen?
I barely got it together.
He's always... up to something.
Personally, I think Kiyoto is
the one to watch out for.
Wow. (EN: 8)
This is really..
Seriously.
Starting to take off.
Good morning.
Good morning
The worst guy (most dangerous) showed up.
The worst guy has shown up.
This isn't good.
I can't do this.
Did you bring it with you?
Do you have it?
One million yen.
Yeah, I have it.
It's dirty money, though.
Dirty money?
Yeah.
It's really dirty.
What is that?
You can't bring that here.
That's disgusting.
Morning! (EN: 9)
Huh?
Is this real?
Good morning!
Morning.
I'm Onigiri.
Right, right.
I'm getting nervous.
Are you nervous?
I am-
The one million.
Did you have one million yen?
You had it?
No, No.
I had to work for it.
I worked 18 hours straight.
I came straight from work.
I've got one million and five thousand
yen in cash right now.
After this, I'm only going to have 5000 Yen left
for the month.
You'll have to get a second job.
Wow. (EN: 10)
Seriously.
Good morning
This definitely isn't good.
Ah, I see.
And he's dressed so fashionably too.
This isn't good.
Why is he dressed so nicely?
Are you a comedian?
I don't think he is.
I think this is our first time meeting.
This is my first time.
It's nice to meet you.
As for being a performer,
Well, I used to play baseball
a long time ago.
But..
I can't.
Why are you laughing?
This isn't good.
Have you retired now?
I don't really get it but-
Good morning!
Good morning
Good morning.
Um..
One million yen.
Right.
Did everyone bring it?
One million Yen, everyone-
I brought it.
Yes.
Two hours before I left the house.
How did you get it together?
Um, Yoshimoto Finance
declined to help this morning.
Okay.
It's from my wife's younger sister and brother.
and my brother, who I don't even speak to.
Yeah.
Don't tell us anymore.
They gave it to me.
I got it. Thank you.
Yeah.
I'll start,
by going over the rules.
Okay.
Um..
What we want you to do today.
Yes.
It's very simple.
(1) Your time is unlimited
(2) Anyone who laughs will be asked to leave.
Okay.
(3) Those who have made it to the end
without laughing..
will be awarded 10 million yen.
You can do whatever you like,
there is nothing that is prohibited.
There are no time limits?
No time limits.
Forever?
Forever.
Until it's finished, right.
Until it's finished.
Not to be rude, but
If I look over there,
He has such a kind face,
so you can tell if he's laughing.
But me,
can a face like this laugh?
Well..
If you look at me...
I'll be the one who judges if
someone is laughing.
You'll be the judge?
Yes.
You’ll be able to look at our face
and tell who is laughing or not?
Well, yeah.
Well, obviously I can tell one of you
is an old man.
That's true.
As soon as he walked in,
he was holding his bag,
complaining like an old man.
Everyone please start gathering
the money together
and put it in the bag.
Pile it up, pile it.
That's crazy
Are you seeing this?
Wow!
Whoa!
It's so tall.
Wow!
He's putting it all in a bag.
He's like the banker,
putting it in the bag.
Thanks for providing the money.
We have to work hard.
Well, everyone.
Do your best!
Okay!
Thank you!
Scary, scary, scary!
This is getting scary.
Not good.
Calm down.
Documental
Start!
Peh peh peh!
Bando, did you come from the barber?
I just,
I just got a haircut.
Right, I went to the barber too.
Do you know whose haircut I asked for?
Who?
Kuwata Masumi. (EN: 11)
Now that you say something,
it does look like him.
It's the sides, I think.
You've got a stronger face, I think.
Really? But I'm talking about
hair right now.
Well, your entire face is like that so.
Well, they couldn't fix
my face at the barber.
This really isn't good.
Alright, alright, alright.
I can't, I can't.
If we drink, what happens?
Well, it's the timing isn't it?
This is going to be difficult.
I might get tired.
Where do they sell this?
Guam.
Yeah.
Guam? You went for work?
Yeah..
That sounds nice.
Everyone dresses like me there?
No, not really.
Anyway..
Really, what is happening here?
What is happening here?!
Please don't get so angry.
Yeah, we just got started.
What is happening?!
Isn't this weird?!
What in the world is
happening here?!
He's lost it. He's lost it.
This makes no sense!
They're really going to laugh!
Let me out!
Someone let us out of here!
What's wrong?
Let us out of here!
Calm down.
Someone is suspicious.
What happened?
What?
Hm?
That was really fast.
What?
You're allowed to laugh now.
Who was it?
Did someone?
That was so quick.
What happened?
Oshima, yellow card.
Really?
Wait, wait, seriously?
Let me out!
Let us out of here!
What's wrong?
There it is!
I was scared! It was scary!
You can't do that, you can't.
If the evidence was there.
You guys are way way too strict.
This is bad! I'm a bit hurt.
What were you doing?
Oh no, oh no..
Oh no, oh no!
Oh no!
What were you doing?
The cameras are amazing.
Really?
So is our Emperor.
You can see everyone reflected
in the window glass.
Oh wow, you can.
You can see everyone.
Everyone?
If I look behind, I'll laugh.
Scary.
I can't go back now.
To what I was saying.
How many windows are there?
Saito, you look terrible.
But he can come out as leader.
Why are you coming over here?
Why are you coming over here!?
Why do you keep following me?!
Huh?
You came over here and then you!
You guys are definitely working together!
That's enough!
As soon as we started, this business
has gotten scary!
I'm not holding anything, I'm just a woman!
There's nothing going on, calm down!
It's okay.
I'm scared!
Stop doing that.
There are beds here too! I'm so scared!
We're no where near the beds.
You guys are planning to
try something, aren't you?!
It's not like that.
You guys are definitely planning
to do something to me here.
As a woman, you're absolutely safe.
I'm scared of you the most!
Me?!
I'm way too old for that!
You still look like you've got some energy.
That's not true!
I'd need so much Viagra,
I'd have to go to the hospital!
Don't say that kind of thing in
front of a lady.
Sorry, sorry.
That's rude!
I'm just trying to comfort her.
Why would you say crazy things like
that to a woman?
That doesn't make sense.
What are you trying to say about Viagra?
I'm saying I take it, because I have no energy.
That's all I'm talking about.
Let's not talk about that
in front of women.
Okay, but you-
Let's stop acting so tough,
don't be so angry with me.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Right? Let's use our words.
We have so many performers here.
Does anyone have any one-liners
to make someone laugh?
One liners?
Saito, what's going on over there?
I can't tell if he's on the
offense or defense.
Bando, since entering Yoshimoto,
I'm sure you created some gags
or one-liners you could use?
Not, not at all.
I've just got some that I've
heard over the years.
Well, it's because I'm not a comedian.
Is the pay cheaper compared to us?
How much do you get paid?
Not that much. I never make
more than ten thousand Yen
Never more than that.
Less than ten thousand Yen?
If so, why not try something else?
Huh?
What?
You make more?
Or less?
Me?
Yeah.
I think it's more than that.
Wow..
What type of comedy are you
doing right now?
Right now, I'm doing that
thing with Umemiya.
Right.
Where we imitate each other's body.
Can I show you?
Yeah.
Everyone is going to explode into laughter.
My body.. my body looks like his.
I don't have everything with me, so..
Ah, you didn't bring it with you.
So, I can't do it properly.
Right, right.
I'm usually not holding it.
Here I go.
I get it.
So you stand like that.
And you move around like that?
Yes.
Must be pretty tough.
Well, the point is our bodies
look pretty similar.
Ah, right, your body.
Is it because the look the same?
Oshima, what are you-
Oshima, you can't do that.
She's right on the line.
When this happens, I would
usually say something.
If there's anything you like, take it-
If it's you it's fine.
Really?
They said we could do whatever we liked.
I wonder how they collected
all of this stuff together.
Let's get a garage together.
- Right.
Somewhere to put stuff
It'll be our base.
You can take it-
Have you ever run to
a base like this before?
That's one of those American radios.
It'd be nice if someone could
make use of it again.
An-chan! (EN: 12)
An-chan, can you fix that posture?
Not that again.
Can you fix it, An-chan?
This old man runs to the base like that.
He always stands like that, right An-chan?
Well, everyone already knows this.
You're this huge thing, like when
your playing sports,
and then you suddenly shrink
It's crazy, I know.
I think Bando is..
It really is.
-Do you want a massage?
-I'm good, thanks.
He's trying so hard to hide it.
So impactful.
Right here
Look!
What do you want?!
What in the world.
What is that?
I know right?
I've got no idea
Huh?
What?
Who laughed, who laughed?
Akiyama
Seriously?
Yellow card.
I had no idea.
You showed up quicker
than I thought you would.
So impactful.
Probably right there.
Look!
What do you want?
That's out.
Also..
Bando, you always
looked like you were about to laugh.
When I was talking, I definitely
thought I laughed.
Yeah, you looked like you were laughing.
If that happens again,
it'll be a yellow card.
What?!
Go complain to my parents about it.
Your parents? No, we won't
tell your parents.
Your parents?
Man, I'm sitting down.
It's getting late.
There's so many ways to lose
Yeah, definitely.
You don't even realize it.
Start.
Are they warming up?
Not yet, I just turned it on.
You're cooking them?
Yes,
I'm cooking.
Is it okay?
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Mayonnaise?
Sometimes, I do.
Like that?
Thanks.
It's delicious.
They're hot!
These taste really good.
This is a different way of eating them.
It's delicious!
Instead of cracking them and eating them.
Does it make a difference?
The burners are electric, so there's that.
What?
The stove is electric, so it doesn't
heat as well.
Thanks for the food.
They're good.
Can I have some?
Yeah, sure. Go ahead.
Can you crack them for me?
Whoa, whoa!
These are way too hot!
They're way too hot.
They're hot.
Who is it?
Now, I'm all tensed up.
This is terrifying.
I saw it.
Hachimitsu.
Huh?
What?
Seriously?
You're giving me that?
You're laughing?
Right.
Yellow.
Got it.
Can you crack them for me?
Whoa, whoa!
These were way too hot!
Too hot!
He was absolutely laughing.
He was laughing with his entire face!
He was laughing!
What was it?
What made you laugh?
Of course, the food was hot.
He asked me to give him some.
Scooped them in his hand and-
They really were hot!
They were hot?
It was too funny.
It's those small things.
Right..
It was pretty funny.
Next time will obviously be a red card.
- Okay!
Okay.
Thank you.
This is hard.
Let's.. Let's clean up a bit.
Bando, do you know everyone's names?
No idea.
What?
Really?
So, you don't know him?
It's fine if you get it wrong.
No, no.
We were on Kanjani together. (EN: 13)
I remember that.
Kanjani?
We were on a TV program that-
It was for TV, right?
But, we haven't spoken
in a really long time.
Despite that, you don't know his name?
Names are a bit, you know..
Bando, it's not good to forget
people's names.
I mean, we're doing jobs
like this together.
You don't remember anyone's name?
Not one?
Really?
It's okay if you get it wrong.
It's okay to guess.
It's okay if you're wrong.
To be honest,
I'm pretty sure..
I've known him for over 15 years already.
What?
Seriously?
Chibata too, I think.
We even played baseball together.
What?!
A professional team?
No, we weren't on the same team.
He was on the opposite team.
Now that I think about it,
when I've heard you speak to others,
You usually just refer to everyone
by the title "you".
Really?
First of all-
Ah, sorry.
I have an excuse.
No matter how hard I try,
I can only remember the player numbers.
When I need to remember,
I look at each person and
write it down their numbers.
Should we all go around
and tell him our names?
Self introduction?
Sure.
Okay.
Everyone.
Let's do it.
I know everyone's names.
Huh?
What?
Everyone's name-
What, you do?
Wait, you know everyone?
I know everyone's names.
What?!
Try and say everyone's name.
Yeah, say our names.
That's Akiyama, right?
Yes.
Ah, looks like he remembers.
Then...
Umm..
That's Happou, right?
Huh, no?
I'm not.
He's Happou.
That's my dad.
Or your son?
Do you know his name?
Oda Mudo, right? (EN: 14)
No, I'm not.
Oda Mudo is someone else.
We might have the same haircut.
Oda Mudo is working in Roppongi,
he's not here right now.
Oh, really?
Yeah. He's making a lot of money.
You know a lot about Oda Mudo.
I think he's acting in a drama, right now.
That must be nice
That's what I just said.
He's working in Roppongi.
but living in Wasaki.
Right..
There's a lot to know.
Bando, what did you do
when things were tough?
I usually made my own food.
So I didn't leave the house
for a long time.
They called me a shut-in.
A shut-in?
Yeah, so I was always at home.
Wow..
When I hear that story,
I always start to cry.
What? Well yeah, it was tough.
But it was a really long time.
To the point where I dreamed
of going outside.
Wow..
I dreamed of going outside.
He really did his best, you know.
He did?
He was working so hard
When no one even knew.
He really....
You really never left your home, right?
I never left.
Is it okay if we hear it from him?
Right, sorry.
I had heard about it.
Ah, you knew about it?
It was really hard.
You understand me, right?
I saw you.
You saw him?
They made a TV show about it.
Whoa, they made a show about it?
Amazing.
Bando, isn't that called house arrest?
That's crazy.
No, it wasn't anything like that.
Maybe I made a mistake.
Who was that?
I might have been thinking of Ryotaro.
That's crazy if you can't tell
the difference between Ryotaro and I.
Ryotaro?
Who is Ryotaro?
Um.
Who?
Ryotaro?
Who in the world is that?
Was it non-fiction?
Ryotaro Blues?
Ryotaro Blues!
Ryotaro Blues.
That was 100%
That was definitely a laugh.
She shouted when she laughed.
If that's what you thought, I'm sorry!
She was just happy-
I was just so happy!
Oshima.
Yellow card.
Okay, you got me.
Which means!
Right.
You're out!
Wow!
It was, well, a laugh
from the heart, right?
You can leave happy!
I admit this one, yeah.
Who in the world is that?
Ryotaro?
Was it non-fiction?
Ryotaro Blues?
Ryotaro Blues!
Ryotaro Blues.
Even before that, it was pretty close.
Things like stuffing your mouth
full of bread.
I saw everything.
She's really stuffing it.
She was stuffing her mouth full of bread.
Stopping up the corners of her mouth
so we can't see her laughing.
Oshima, that's what you were doing?!
Were going to miss you, Oshima.
You're out!
Thank you! Excuse me.
Good luck.
That's all for now.
Right.
It's all for one million Yen..
One million yen..
Now we're in trouble.
We're getting close to winning
one million Yen.
Start.
Let's start a game.
A new game?
Something like Saito's game.
Saito is-
What is that?
Can you show us?
I want to play.
First, create a nickname using
the two syllables from your name.
For example, I'm Saito, so "Saito".
Kubo, so "Kubo".
So if it were me, then "Banden".
No, "boiled". (Yude)
"Boiled"?
"Boiled", right, okay.
Well once you pick the two syllables,
for example, if we were to start with me-
We, start, with Sai,
Match it, to, the rhythm.
First, both hands on the table.
One.
Two.
Right.
This is loud.
Then left.
The rhythm is those four beats.
One, two, three, start.
Match it, to, the rhythm.
Bam, bam, pe, pe.
Like that.
Bam, bam, pe, pe?
Bam, bam-
You do one right after the other?
Yeah, you do.
So there's at least four.
Ah, I get it.
If we lose should we create a punishment?
Yeah, why not.
We might as well.
How about this?
How about slapping our ass with these?
How about it?
As a punishment for losing.
We can try it and see how it goes.
Okay.
One..Two..
The beat starts with Sai,
match it to the rhythm.
I choose Aki.
pe, pe.
I choose Sai.
I choose Kubo.
pe, pe.
I choose "Boiled".
Ah, I messed up!
You got me.
That would be an out.
Let's do the punishment.
It's me?
That thing looks hard!
Well, it's just your butt.
Of course, just my butt.
I'll do it like this.
Okay, okay.
Here I go.
Oh, are you okay?
My butt hurts!
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry.
Say sorry to him.
I'm sorry.
I'm okay. Don't feel bad,
it's a punishment.
I'm sorry. Punishments have
to be like that. I have no choice.
I'm sorry.
The sound scared me the most.
Did it startle you?
I'll do it next, we'll take turns.
Let's start with Uchima, then.
Here I go.
The beat starts with Uchi
Match it to the rhythm.
I choose Kubo!
Pe, pe.
I choose Boiled
Wait, I'm still in the game?
No, it's fine.
Your rhythm was kind of off.
Uchima you were going too fast.
Bam, bam, I choose Kubo
You have to say it like that.
So who is out, then?
I think it's Uchi.
Uchi?
Uchi, you're out.
He's out.
It's because of his rhythm, right?
He didn't follow-
His rhythm was off, so he's out.
If you don't do it properly, your out.
So he's out then.
I got it! I'm out then.
This really is a part of the rules, right?
Yeah!
I don't think I can remember this.
That hurt.
You should put something damp on it later.
They got him completely.
I saw it too.
I thought maybe they missed it.
I didn't see it!
Me?
No, I don't know, but.
Bando.
Yellow card.
Really?
He said "Really?"!
He was completely laughing
Was I?
It was a completely normal laugh,
from an old man.
I want to see if I was really laughing!
Was I laughing?
This is different.
You were just laughing normally!
Next time will be a red card.
Wow, they really got me.
You really were just laughing normally
That's his real face.
If you feel like showering, please do.
Ah, thank you.
They could see it.
That was really funny.
That was really..
Ha ha ha!
We're starting!
Bando, what time do you usually go to bed?
I usually sleep around 10.
Then I wake up around 6.
I go to sleep earlier.
Why do you go to bed so early?
I go to sleep around 8:30.
I'm usually in bed by now.
Really?
Wow, that's early.
You don't fall asleep again?
Well,
how do I explain it,
After the sun rises, I don't.
I always end up getting
tired in the afternoons.
But you look like you've
got so much energy.
No, that's definitely not true.
They says bad women are like piss stains.
You can't get rid of them, right?
Right..
Do you meet prostitutes?
No, I've never done that.
Speaking of prostitutes,
Women meet them too, I think.
They do.
They don't want anyone to know.
Right..
Do you know what I ask for?
I’ll get up and show you.
Let's pretend I'm thirsty.
You go like this.
Then it goes there.
That's it, you know?
That's what I like, anyway.
What type of entertainer is
Documental looking for?
As expected, well..
I'm looking for those who
will go on the attack and defense.
Right..
Of course, right?
If they don't attack,
then nothing will happen.
[Elapsed time 4 hours]
Okay.
Here I go.
Whoa..
That was amazing, just now.
Here I go.
Here I go!
Okay!
Whoa...
You can't keep doing that!
Here I go. Third time is the real one.
It's coming.
I'm gonna aim for this area.
Okay?
Okay!
Whoa.
I can't do this anymore!
This is against the rules.
I really didn't hit him.
He didn't hit me,
But this is worse than getting hit!
You come over here.
You want to switch?
That's fine.
That's fine with me.
Here we go
Wait, that's already how many?
Come on.
You weren't scared?
I wasn't.
Go ahead.
Come on. Come on!
Come on!
What is that?
There's no one here that isn't a performer.
[Eiji Bando's role in Season 0]
Well, Bando
Isn't really a comedian, is he?
He definitely acts like a performer.
Right!
There was that experience he told.
It was pretty funny.
Having him on the show and
messing around with him was really fun.
Absolutely.
You get a bit sentimental
thinking about it.
Ah, he took a shower.
Are you sure you wouldn't like
to take a shower?
No, I brought a change of clothes.
You brought pajamas?
No, just a change of clothes.
I didn't plan on sleeping here.
That's all.
Are they.. Well I saw this on Wikipedia..
Yes?
They have panties included inside.
Was it something else?
Panties?
Yeah, they have panties inside.
Basically, yeah, they have panties inside.
Women's panties.
They're supposed to have panties inside.
No way, absolutely not.
That's wrong, wrong, wrong.
Those are yours?
What is?
The ones with panties.
No, no these are-
I don't remember the store, but they're
regular men's underwear.
They look really fashionable.
Huh?
They're fashionable.
They are.
Really?
The giraffe print.
They're just-
If it was women's underwear,
there would be three giraffes.
Here?
Bando.
You laughed normally again.
I'm not saying anything.
They got me again!
You're out!
What a shame.
I even learned everyone's name-
It's a shame, you came so far.
Yeah!
Could you, maybe look the other way?
You can't?
What are you talking about?
I thought so.
What a waste.
I don't want to say that to you.
Bando is going home. Thank you!
Thank you! Man, I really messed up.
Great job!
Thank you!
Good luck to the rest.
We will! Thank you!
I really messed up..
8 are left.
Right.
Let's finish this.
Okay!
He left.
Bando is gone now.
We're starting.
Well, now..
Now that the oldest one, Bando, has left.
Will something in them
begin to change?
We don't know, but it could.
The atmosphere has definitely changed.
What's wrong?
Someone shut him up.
Who is that?
Wha- what's wrong?
What is it?
Peek a boo!
Ah, he's started again.
What are you doing?
I feel bad for him.
He's a crier, huh.
Hello?
Aki laughed, didn't he?
Um.
Akima, did you laugh just now?
Just now, um..
I was just trying to make someone laugh.
Do you want to speak with him?
Yeah, let me speak with him.
Yes, hello?
Um..
Usually, that well,
that would be against the rules.
Right.
That was pretty close.
Yeah, you're right.
When I was doing it, suddenly,
I noticed it suddenly.
I might look like I'm laughing.
But it really was
just a joke to make others laugh.
It was close, really close.
You were an inch from being axed.
I'm sorry, I understand.
I'll be more careful.
That was a long talk.
It was because I had laughed a little bit.
So no matter what.
I see.
I've got to be careful in that area.
It's hard to know if it's against
the rules or not.
I'm about to change, will you watch?
Sure.
The briefs that I'm wearing right now,
Yeah.
I'll show you how I take them off.
What?
You're going to change?
That's a good brand, Sophnet.
Surprise!
They came off pretty cleanly.
They're not torn.
What is this, an exhibition?
How did he do that?
It's an exhibition.
Is there something attached?
Can you lower your pants please?
There's nothing there.
He's right.
The king has appeared.
How did you do that?
It's not torn, it's cut.
You do that when you poop?
Yeah, I do.
When I poop, it pretty nice.
But I can't carry a grocery bag.
What in the world is he saying.
It suddenly got really interesting
and a lot started happening.
Done.
Huh?
You're annoying!
Get away!
If you want me to stop, just say so.
Go ahead.
I think the old lady
said something, sorry about that.
Life..
isn't fun when no one's spreading rumors.
Here's another thing that we've learned.
[What does Matsumoto think of
the first half of Season Zero?]
Eventually, that..
how should I say this?
Uchima, from the Slim Club
He'll do anything!
I had no idea, this type of guy
even exists.
Right?
He'll really do anything.
He'll tell jokes,
He'll do anything.
It helps me remember that
these guys do exist.
So, what should we do?
Well..
There's not really
any more challenges I can give them.
A lot of them didn't even take a bath.
I can't trap them here.
What should I do?
We're sorry.
[Time Elapsed 6 Hours]
He's sleeping.
I can't do that.
If it's not completely dark
I can't go to sleep.
He's sleeping better than I do.
You know what we should do?
Should we all show our asses?
Or, maybe we should make our asses speak?
Akiyama and the others can do the voices.
Like some type of ass doll.
Let's do that.
We can have two people show their ass.
So, how should we do it?
How about Romeo and Juliet
So paint them to look like
Romeo and Juliet?
Or, we could do a married couple.
Parents or something?
Let's do Romeo and Juliet.
We can make it dramatic.
For starters,
let's do the man first.
You're good at this.
Saito will be the girl.
Okay.
Try opening and closing your cheeks.
Try moving your ass.
That's perfect! That's perfect!
That's perfect! Perfect!
Perfect.
What happened?
It's a bit delicate there.
You can't even feel that.
No, I can. I feel it.
Well, I'm only human.
Seriously? I'm trying to do this.
Saito, have some self-control.
It itches so bad.
Wake him up when they start talking
to each other.
Instead of just showing them.
Jiro
How are you, Jiro?
You can do it! Keep going.
How have you been?
You went to Tokyo and went on
that comedy show, right?
Yeah.
Were you cooperating with everyone, Jiro?
I heard you didn't make a lot of progress,
and you were always talking about yourself.
Go back to sleep.
The story was different.
He was really calm about it.
It was a waste waking him up.
He probably saw us getting ready.
Should we do another game?
I'll start.
You can get on all fours.
Over the net?
Okay.
Can anyone give it out?
That's amazing.
Pull down your pants.
Okay.
Is that safe?
What are these rules?
Kneel in front of the net.
Mommy.
That was close. Akiyama almost laughed.
Watch out! Watch out!
Who was it?
Akiyama.
You're out.
This was so hard. I can't believe
I'm leaving this far in.
Not now.
[Time Elapsed 8 Hours Stalemate.]
Thank you for the food.
It's good.
It's delicious.
[8 hours in: Only eating.]
It's good.
I wasn't expecting this type of atmosphere.
Umm..
Probably, not one person
is going to laugh any more.
If you put your chopsticks like-
When I eat, I get really sleepy.
I'm not sure what to do.
I'm don't know.
We could stop it temporarily,
and take a break.
They'd be pretty tired, right?
[What to do during a stalemate]
You're right, they'd be tired.
Ah, there's places they can sleep.
Yes.
There are some beds.
Hello?
Um..
Let's take a short break.
Right, okay.
Um..
We'll start a timer for one hour.
One hour, okay.
That time,
starts right now?
Right now.
Understood.
Thank you.
He says we're taking a one hour break,
starting now.
Starting now?
One hour.
I jumped in there.
During the last part,
you went in there too.
I think I did enter.
You did enter.
Did I? I did do something like that,
didn't I?
You did.
Let's change topics.
This happened in Osaka.
I have a really heartwarming story.
Will you listen to my story?
Should we all tell one?
Will you?
I have a heartwarming story.
Okay.
So, I'll start then?
Sure.
Sakata Toshio (EN: 15)
Sakata was a-
Yes?
Hello?
I'm heading over there now.
Understood.
But the no laughing rule will continue.
I'll let them know.
Right now,
Um..
Matsumoto is on his way, but...
The no laughing rule continues.
That's not good.
Good work.
We've came this far.
Yes.
I thought I'd,
for the time being,
sit here with you guys.
Okay.
If I catch anyone laughing
I can card you right away.
I can laugh though, okay?
Okay.
You're going to try and make us laugh?
Well, if I think of anything,
Of course I'll try it.
Okay.
So what about that heartwarming story?
Right.
Koide was going tell us one?
So, what is it?
His name is Sakata Toshio.
When the season is just right.
There's a main street in Osaka
called Midosuji.
That fall,
Gingko nuts would ripen. (EN: 16)
and fall to the ground.
So Sakata would,
every fall,
go and collect them.
So he could eat them at home.
So, he went to collect them
that year as well.
and he would pick them up
and put them in his bag.
But it's hard to tell if a nut had
been sitting on the ground for awhile.
He would try and check the color
and things like that.
But the best way, was to smell it
and see if it smelled fresh.
One day he saw a nut that was a weird color
and might have gone bad.
He picked it up and when he smelled it
It was poop.
Which part was heartwarming?
What was heartwarming?
Yeah, what was so heartwarming?
Well his name is Sakata and-
I have one to tell.
He's popular in Osaka.
Many years ago,
Yeah.
I had been participating in M1 training.
Right.
I finished school around 20 years old.
I had never in my life read
a textbook before.
Then, someone gave me a textbook.
My parents gave it to me.
Two years later,
During summer vacation
So, it read
"Today
Jiro,
my little sister,
and little brother
all went to see Toy Story 2 together.
My little sister
spilled cup corn
Hm?
She spilled cup corn-
I wrote this down, okay?
She spilled the cup corn,
and it spilled all over the floor.
Since she spilled the cup corn.
So the teacher took a red pen, and wrote
"Pop"
"Pop" and corrected all of the mistakes
in each sentence.
My sister had dropped the cup corn, right?
It was written "Jiro would be angry",
I wrote "Jiro didn't get angry".
The teacher wrote back in red pen,
"Who is Jiro?"
That's a heartwarming story.
It was.
It made me all fuzzy inside.
So, heartwarming stories,
is all that we can tell now?
Well, it looks like that's what
we were going for.
Ah, let's do this!
This will make things interesting.
Tell me your shortest joke.
Okay.
It doesn't have to be that good.
So my mom,
When the pandemic had just begun,
she was riding the bullet train.
She went with a friend to
Yominojika in Sendai.
So-
The person sitting in front of my mom
asked if it was okay to fold the seats.
So, my mom answered,
"Please do."
When I was in 6th grade,
I was 170 cm tall
so they made fun of me a little.
I went to the Osaka Zoo for the first time.
Yeah, the Osaka Zoo.
An old man was stopped at the ticket gate.
He was stopped by an attendant
When they asked him for a ticket
He said, "I don't need a ticket!"
Right..
I was waiting for the train
at Osaka Station.
When the doors opened
An old man appeared.
Your dad?
I'm the only one laughing
Laughter is a mystery.
Yeah.
I don't think there's anything
we can do to make you laugh.
If someone sat on this table
and took a crap.
No one would laugh.
With who we've got left,
they definitely won't laugh.
That's exactly what I'm saying.
If one of the staff members
took a crap, we might laugh.
When you tell someone not to laugh,
the opposite happens.
When it's a TV show about not laughing,
you expect everyone to always be laughing.
This group definitely isn't going to laugh.
I see.
We're that type-
I get what you're saying
-of person.
The muscle that I use to laugh
doesn't even work anymore.
Exactly.
It's been half a day.
Hachimitsu is the calmest person here.
If someone like Hatchimitsu
is telling me that,
I don't think he's wrong.
This is really..
This may affect your jobs tomorrow.
The fact that we can never laugh again?
[Time Elapsed 14 hours 25 Minutes]
[Finish]
We saw a lot of things today.
[End of experimental Season 0]
Some went on the attack.
Some did things we didn't expect.
Some are fit for this, some aren't.
There are different types of people.
We didn't really get a chance to
See that type of thinking during Season 0.
Yeah..
Well, if it can't be helped,
then it can't be helped.
Well, it was an experiment.
We wanted to give it a try, so we could
decide the rules for the future.
We went for 14 and a half hours.
Nothing happened in then end, though.
In the end, that's true.
The hardest part was probably
the unrestricted time limit.
It's true there weren't any rules,
but no matter what form it takes,
a documentary is a documentary.
We decided that from the beginning.
But those members definitely went
and created their own rules
Right?
Whether there were rules or not.
I wonder what that is.
Are you working hard in Tokyo?
Jiro!
Why won't they let us out of here!
[Everything started here]
Did you see it?
He's Victor
Suck! Suck! Suck!
What are you doing?
You need to pay extra for that.
Let it go.
It's almost time to release Season 4.
Looks like it, huh.
Season 4.
I'm looking forward to it.
What feelings are you carrying
into this documentary?
Well you see,
Every time a different group is invited.
As for me,
I want to try build a zombie rule,
but I wonder if there is something else
I could do from here.
I'm going to have to think about it.
But I think there's plenty.
In order to spice things up a bit.
Right?