THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
-Stop that.
-Are you actually doing that?
What are you doing?
No!
Ouch!
The end result was truly wonderful.
Can this third season...
HITOSHI MATSUMOTO
...really surpass that?
Hm. I'm a little worried about that.
SEASON 2 KOTOUGE VS SAITO
-Bring it on!
-You bring it on!
Take that!
In the end, even those who studied comedy
in different places,
when forced into a corner,
learned to aim for the eyes
or below the belt.
A BATTLE OF INSTINCTS
It's no longer a matter of technique.
I saw that.
AN INCOMPLETE EXPERIMENT
Throughout Seasons One, Two and Three
this program has gradually evolved.
For this season, I am really excited
about the new changes in the rules.
Within these six hours
there will be periods of stalemate.
Until now,
those individuals who received red cards
were eliminated on the spot.
What if we were to leave them in?
They can no longer win.
A SECOND CHANCE FOR THE LOSERS
They will stay on as zombies.
REVENGE AS ZOMBIES
They will only be there
to make the others laugh.
Until now, we had been sending them home
without them having used
all of their weapons.
As a zombie,
you can make use of all you've prepared.
It is going to be very difficult
to win like this.
CONSTANT EXPLOSIONS
A COMEDY LABORATORY
There is this prevailing feeling
that our sense of comedy
is better than that of those
who don't watch  Documental.
A SECRET AMAZON PARTY
In some ways, this feels underground.
It feels like we are the only ones
who know about this.
It's like we're undercover documentarians.
GROWING MORE HIDDEN DOCUMENTARIANS
I absolutely cannot show this program
to my daughter.
I'm gradually becoming
more and more convinced of this.
At least, that's how I feel.
I heard on the radio the other day
that you need more than just fluids
to prevent heat stroke.
I heard that salt was also important.
This surprised me. Did you know that?
That being said,
I would like to offer you an invitation.
Could you prepare one million yen
and gather at a designated location?
I shall reinitiate Documental.
I have prepared a reward
of 10 million yen for the winner.
Of course, participation is voluntary.
For those of you who wish to participate,
I shall inform you
of the time and location.
I await your reply.
I wish you a splendid summer.
Sincerely, Hitoshi Matsumoto.
THE PARTICIPATING COMEDIANS ENTER
Wow.
I'm the first to arrive.
He has no idea
who the other nine people are.
Okay.
-Right.
-Over there.
It must be odd to be the first one.
Hello. I am Kendo Kobayashi.
It came!
What should I do?
Documental.
Kobayashi is really well-rounded,
you know?
He knows how to give quick,
funny answers when prompted.
He can also tell funny stories
and do one-man sketches.
AN EMPEROR WITHOUT A CROWN
Mr. Matsumoto invited me.
He did try to kill me once. He did.
He is also good at dirty jokes.
A MERCILESS PERVERT
I am considering circumcising myself.
I would have to fit him in my bag,
so I looked for a very flexible surgeon.
However, I had to give up in the end.
He is very stable.
He also has plenty of moves up his sleeve.
I see him as being very strong.
Under normal circumstances, I believe that
it would be best not to show
this sort of competition to an audience.
It's that sort of battle.
This is like a free-for-all
wrestling match.
I want to give it a shot.
If I do what I always do,
I think this will work out quite nicely.
What?
That's surprising.
It is surprising.
I didn't expect him either.
-I see someone really funny sitting here.
-Terumoto Goto?
I am Terumoto Goto
of the Football Hour comedy group.
All I can say is that I will do my best.
I will do all that I can.
Excuse me.
Huh?
Isn't this a program
for comedians who act silly?
Or at least,
for those capable of acting silly?
Right?
Goto has the ability
to observe everything
in a very objective way.
I see him as being an observant comedian.
If you receive this invitation,
you have no reason to decline, right?
There are plenty of reasons to decline
because of the dough.
This isn't about the money.
How will he control the events?
I think that he will be able
to draw a lot from the other performers.
COMEDY SNIPER
I haven't had this feeling
in a very long time.
It's not something I can experience
on other shows.
I'm feeling nervous.
He can work fine on his own as well.
I think it will be interesting to see
a side of him that we don't see on TV.
When I work on variety TV shows,
I go there for the purpose of laughing.
This is the exact opposite
of what I usually do.
I usually think about the next bit
while laughing at the previous one.
I cannot do that here.
That's painful.
Everything could end in a moment.
I want to be able to attack
at every opportunity.
Those are all the props.
Really? That's it?
That, plus whatever we bring here.
Really?
Hello.
He's here.
Oh, well...
Seriously?
-Damn!
- Of course they're not pleased.
Damn it!
Of course they're not pleased
with the situation.
-Did I surprise you?
-What?
I am Ryuji Akiyama
from comedy group Robert.
I have decided that I will definitely
be taking home that 11 million yen.
Excuse me.
Hello.
This program always had a place
right here.
I want to participate.
He will be a tough opponent.
His comedy is highly effective
against both newcomers
and fully-seasoned comedians.
He can get laughs both
through direct and indirect means.
I'm a little afraid of Akiyama.
THE MAN OF A THOUSAND CHARACTERS
He can also act.
It is almost unfair.
You told me about that Detox For Men.
What are you talking about now?
I just can't get a reservation.
This is not the place to bring up
aromatherapy salons in Shinbashi.
Why are you bringing that up here
of all places?
I felt that I needed to do this.
I can't run away from this.
Akiyama?
You're already making me laugh.
When the time comes to go naked,
how can I get laughs with my groin?
I bought some really expensive drinks
to enhance my vitality.
I do think that there is a higher level
in naked comedy.
-That door really seems important.
-Right.
We need to be careful around that.
I guess you can use it at your own timing.
I see.
That makes sense.
Right.
Right. It would be odd
if Kinoshita didn't turn up.
Here's the first player from Shochiku.
Hello. I am Takayuki Kinoshita
from the TKO comedy group.
I am a member
of the Shochiku comedy agency.
Invitation?
Really?
"Welcome to  Documental."
This is an honor.
They worked so hard.
Can't I bring Moriwaki?
This time,
there are a lot
of rather plump competitors.
This may be surprising, but
I think Kinoshita has a decent chance
of winning.
He does laugh fairly easily.
But if he avoids
having certain buttons pushed,
I think that he can survive for a while.
There is a certain madness in his comedy.
TRUE BALD ACTOR
I waited for this.
For those who live as comedians,
this is a festival of sorts.
That being the case, I cannot refuse.
This is the program I both want to
and don't want to appear on the most.
This program reveals
the true capabilities, skills
and techniques
of the people participating.
Among my comedian friends,
this program comes up a lot.
What could you do if it were you?
We would hold
our own personal Documentals.
Kinoshita's face is really powerful.
You're all well-known for your silly gags.
You're right. That's...
No, no. That may be, but...
-Here he comes.
-Hello.
-There are a lot of huge guys.
-Seriously.
How many props are in that bag?
Isn't this amazing?
Look at Kasuga's bag.
What is with that guy?
I am Kasuga of the comedy group Audrey.
Right now,
I'm really looking forward to this.
MUTSUMI MANOR
Hello.
What? It came.
It finally came.
This is wonderful.
Yeah.
Did you pick out that vest just for today?
That's right. This is a little brighter.
-This is a formal event.
-The material is different.
Kasuga has the ability
to skillfully cut through the noise,
find the best timing,
and get the laughs all for himself.
He gets very intense
regarding money.
I think he will play very conservatively.
A BIZARRE THRIFTY MONSTER
This is really important to me.
I put it in a safe.
I want it to be secure.
This safe
also fits 11 million yen.
On variety shows,
I do smile and laugh a lot.
But I have never laughed
outside of my character as Kasuga.
Kasuga was really interested to see
what would happen
if Kasuga appeared on this program.
Kasuga really wants to watch Kasuga
on that show.
I don't get that.
I have never used an outfit to get laughs.
That's true.
I thought about it.
If you don't get laughs,
you just go home depressed.
But I thought about that a lot.
Would pro comedians laugh at this?
Right.
Some things won't work.
Wow.
Always troublesome
I was worried about you.
This is bad.
His comedy is my biggest weakness.
What is that?
-Take that hoodie off.
-This is a normal hoodie.
That is not normal.
This is my hoodie.
What is he wearing?
Hello, I'm Kukky
of the Yaseibakudan comedy group.
I am not cheap.
-Hello.
Good work.
This is the second time.
For me.
This is my second time.
While he will leave an impression,
he won't be winning.
WALKING THE TIGHTROPE
OF THE BROADCAST LAWS
Quite a chubby group.
-We're all big.
-Another big one.
If I had to compare him,
he is similar to Jimmy in style.
But he will laugh at nothing.
It makes you wonder what was so funny.
He could be out fairly quickly.
The last time,
everything felt condensed.
Even mentally.
It was like garlic egg yolk.
It was that condensed.
THE ULTIMATE WEAPON
You're all top comedians, I see.
This should be fun.
Who is top?
Mr. Matsumoto may have turned gay
if he wants so many big guys together.
I have begun to think that
comedy and fear
are two sides of the same coin.
I am thinking about trying to attack
that fear portion of it.
Mr. Matsumoto ended up choosing
a lot of muscular men.
All muscular men. He really did turn gay.
He's really tough.
I'm not tough. I laughed right away.
When I saw the first season,
he made me laugh a lot.
Another big one.
-Hello.
-RG.
I'm RG of the Razor Ramon comedy group.
I'm really excited about this.
A  Documental observation?
I will use the melody
of this Italian lullaby.
A Documental observation
That is what I will tell you
Santa Lucia
In Documental, there are
A lot of comedians with shaved heads
THE ATTACK
OF THE OBSERVATIONAL HUMOR SINGER
I think that RG
has a lot of jokes
that he can't say on TV.
If he throws them out here,
I think he has the potential
to be very destructive.
He also has a strong heart.
He might have the strongest heart
of the group.
THE IRON HEART OF JAPAN
I am who I am because I attack repeatedly.
That's how I was raised.
I will do what I can
to hold out as long as I can.
I'm thinking of this
as a pro wrestling ring.
I will make them laugh
and I will take on their moves.
If I can do both of those things,
I think that I will become the champion.
-Only three left.
-Wow. Three more.
Yeah.
Everyone here has the ability
to do something
that will immediately make us laugh.
He brought tissues.
Another big one.
You didn't bring anything?
-What?
-He brought tissues.
-That's actually impressive.
-Who do you think you are?
I need to clean my glasses.
What the hell?
I am Mikio Date
of the Sandwichman comedy group.
I will do my best.
What is it? Are you paparazzi?
So this is how you invite people?
I think Tomizawa would be better at this.
I'm going into this with no plan.
I'm not bringing any weapons.
I think something real
would probably be the funniest.
I expect that
Goto and Date will lead the others.
That's what I think.
BLOND CHATTY PIG
I expect that Date and Goto
will compete for the same position.
That dynamic will greatly affect
the direction of Season Three.
Honestly, this is a show I want to watch.
Not one that I want to appear in.
Just one to watch.
But if my seniors work hard
to crack jokes,
I might feel like I need to laugh.
It would be rude if I didn't laugh, right?
I'll just act natural.
I want to remain until the end.
Everyone is huge.
I know, right?
He put me here
to break up the massive men.
They seem to be getting along.
Everyone seems to be having a lot of fun.
What, why so...
Here he is.
-This is bad.
-This is really bad.
I am a member
of Yoshimoto Creative Agency.
I have been a professional comedian
for 15 years.
I am Yoshimasa Iwahashi
of the Plus Minus comedy group.
It's too soon for me.
Absolutely. No question.
A little of this.
The question is which way it will go
when he begins to go mad.
COMPULSIVE BEHAVIOR
-Are you the straight man?
-Right. I play the straight man.
You are not a straight man.
No, I am the straight man.
People who look like you
aren't straight men.
In my  manzai duo I play the straight man.
When Iwahashi is fired up,
he can be really funny.
But when he's not, he's not funny at all.
I wonder which Iwahashi will show up?
Will it be plus or minus?
Last month I made 320,000 yen.
I have two children.
My wife raises the children.
Our rent is a ridiculous
180,000 yen a month.
I am willing to die today.
I hope this will help me
step up to the next level.
I hope this shows my strengths.
This is almost like minor league players
batting against major league pitchers.
I want to shatter expectations.
Nine have gathered.
-Another big one.
-That's right.
Everyone is wide.
I think that the last one
will surprise them.
I think that some of them will be
meeting him for the first time.
Seriously?
I am Keiichi Yamamoto
of the Gokuraku Tombo comedy group.
Thank you for inviting me here.
I've seen this before.
I'm actually honored.
Honestly.
I almost never appear on broadcast TV.
I really appreciate this opportunity.
This is really going to be a surprise.
Right?
I really hope that
he releases everything
that has been building up
for more than ten years.
His balls must be packed.
RESURRECTION OF THE GOLD PIG
I have the feeling that
he's betting a lot on this competition.
I do think that he could shine here.
I'm not rusty.
I can't afford to complain
about being rusty.
I will treat this like a presentation.
I will do my best.
This is a presentation
for broadcast networks.
So these are the members.
This is very different
from what I expected.
That's right.
It is completely different.
Why did you come with so few props?
Date and Goto didn't bring much.
This is just to clean my glasses.
What is that?
There are tissues here.
-There are tissues, right?
-You can clean them with your shirt.
No. That would make them dirty.
Hey.
Good morning.
Hello.
Hello. Why didn't the last person
close the door?
Now here is a muscular man.
Good morning.
Amazing.
Hello.
Is that a bowling bag?
Are you going bowling?
Amazing.
That is thick.
Well, everyone,
take a seat.
Isn't this an amazing group?
Mr. Matsumoto, there are some suspicions.
What?
You've gathered
a brawny group of men here.
-Right.
-You chose us.
There are suspicions
that you have gone gay.
I am thinking
about going in that direction.
-That is scary.
-Wait a minute.
I'm thinking of making the switch
around the time of the Tokyo Olympics.
That's coming up soon.
It was just by chance
that you're all large men.
-Is it really by chance?
-There's no way.
I don't know.
I doubt that.
You can all do tug-of-war.
This is like a tug-of-war competition.
Yamamoto has agreed to join us.
Yamamoto.
Some of you may be meeting him
for the first time.
-That's true.
-This is my first time.
While you were taking time off,
all of these younger comedians broke out.
Right.
But I know that Yamamoto will show
that he isn't what you expect.
I have high expectations.
That isn't true at all.
Right.
Really?
I don't know if I'll be able to prove
that I'm not the man you expect.
That isn't the case at all.
I hope to see you work hard
from the start.
Your eyes are already red.
That looks painful.
I didn't expect to be among these members.
Do I even need to explain the rules now?
We generally know them.
I don't think I need to explain them.
You all brought a million yen.
Iwahashi, were you able to come up
with your million?
It was really difficult,
I borrowed it from the CEO in Osaka.
-The CEO in Osaka?
-That's right.
Yes. That was really tough.
-That must have been tough.
-It really was.
But if you win,
you get ten times that amount.
That is true.
Can everyone hand over their million yen?
Amazing.
But there are plenty of you for whom
losing a million yen
wouldn't hurt that much.
That isn't the case.
This is really painful.
In the last season,
Kotouge wasn't that excited
about winning the 10 million yen.
Seriously?
That isn't true.
It's 10 million yen.
He usually just passed
that amount to Anri.
They're still connected.
It's all connected.
I paid 30,000 yen before.
This is tough.
Well, well.
-What is that?
-One million yen.
What is that?
Why do you have a safe?
You didn't have to go that far.
I thought that was suspicious.
This is a good one.
You don't need to be so subtle
with your jokes.
I wasn't trying to do that.
Just say it normally.
Fine. I got it.
This is to help with the atmosphere.
-Right.
-It's not a bad idea.
Right. Please allow me this.
Quit joking around.
Wait a minute.
That has nothing to do with this.
This is really important.
How many props do you have?
A thousand.
I made them myself.
No way.
You just want us to tease you.
What are you talking about?
I'm being serious.
Please pass the cash this way.
You must have had trouble too, Yamamoto.
-It was tough.
-It must've been tough where you are now.
Yes. It was really tough.
Please pass it this way.
Here you go.
This is heavy.
This is amazing.
Amazing. 10 million.
Most people have fresh bills this time.
But this is a bit ugly.
This will be the prize.
Wow!
Look at that!
Amazing.
I see.
You all donated a million yen
to the prize.
So if you win,
you would only gain nine million yen.
Right.
So I will put up the last million.
WHOEVER DOESN'T LAUGH
GETS 10 MILLION YEN
PLUS MATSUMOTO'S MILLION YEN
Thank you.
That's terrific.
This doesn't bother me at all.
You don't have to say that.
I'm sure that it's true.
That makes sense.
-I'm sure that's true.
-But please be a little more delicate.
-That's right! I almost forgot.
-What?
This time...
I created a special rule
for this competition.
You know about the cards, right?
There is yellow and orange.
If you get a red card, you are out.
Until now, the people who were out
had to leave.
This time I am establishing
a special zombie rule.
Zombie rule?
Even if you are out,
you may remain as a zombie.
Zombie rule.
When there are some people left,
you can reappear as a zombie,
and make the others laugh.
In other words,
if no one survives the six hours
a no contest will be declared.
Your million yen will be returned to you.
It ends there.
You can get your million yen back.
Right.
That's big.
The zombies can work as a team.
-The zombies can have a meeting.
-That's right.
In that way, I think
it will be very difficult to win this.
If you're a zombie,
you're allowed to laugh.
Really?
That's right.
The zombies can laugh.
They're already dead.
They are dead, after all.
I will answer any questions
you might have.
It seems you are all ready.
The six hours will start after this.
Six hours.
You seem to be getting along very well.
You sort of know how this works.
-Well, we've seen this before.
-Right. Right.
This is for 10 million yen.
Right.
Amazing.
That is a lot of money.
And we have an amazing group here.
-What is that?
-Amazing group?
Amazing?
Nothing.
I think you will link up together well.
You all want to win.
Right.
That much is certainly true.
That's right.
If you aren't funny here,
I will really come down on you.
Please don't do that.
I'll tell people
that you aren't funny at all.
Just from today?
That could be worse than
losing a million yen.
I'll tell my parents too.
-That doesn't bother me.
-That's fine.
I am fine with your mother thinking
that I'm not funny.
-Really?
-Yeah, I'm totally fine with that.
My mother doesn't really think
that you're that funny to begin with.
Why is that?
Does she hate me?
-Why doesn't she like you?
-I know, right?
Once I leave, it begins.
Are we starting?
That was quick.
There's food over there.
There are all sorts of things.
You can use these props too.
There are a lot.
All sorts of props.
The six hours are absolute.
Depending on you,
this could end in 30 minutes.
We could all lose instantly.
This is amazing.
Good luck.
Shut up.
Have fun.
The pressure is too much.
-Why are you trying to vomit?
-I couldn't breathe.
This starts once he hits the button.
That's right.
It makes a sound.
-This is scary.
-It is.
I'm going to put away my bag.
Season Three.
Let's get started.
Start.
It started.
All right.
This refrigerator is packed.
-It really is.
-There's plenty of stuff in it.
Amazing.
Water? Oh, water.
There's tons of stuff in here.
There's no water.
There is seltzer.
-There is beer too.
-There was water.
Look to the side.
Is it out of water?
There's just seltzer.
I don't want seltzer.
I don't drink seltzer either.
I can drink seltzer.
You drank out of that.
That doesn't matter.
Then, I'll drink this one.
Okay.
Could you?
This is really starting.
Are we going to waste electricity?
Scary.
What now?
-Right.
-I am sorry for yelling.
It started while I was in the locker room.
-Was that a fight?
-No.
It just sounded like one.
Fight?
No.
We are allowed to get drinks, right?
-He left the door open.
-I didn't open it.
Who opened it?
Was it Kinoshita?
Are you starting to fight already?
Right.
-Fight?
-We aren't fighting. I just scolded him.
They got dirty in my waiting room.
-Are we fighting from the start?
-Fight?
I just scolded him.
Okay.
Where can we smoke?
You can smoke at the table.
-Right there?
-No problem.
Are there any ashtrays?
Yes.
That's quick.
You're already going for the ashtrays.
No, I was just wondering
whether there were any ashtrays.
Over there.
Ja!
Ja! Ja!
Jumping jack!
That is really loud.
Indeed.
Is Kukky all right?
He might try to hide
by smoking.
Look at Kinoshita.
Can you do this?
Yes.
That's unbelievable!
-You are really good.
-That's amazing.
You're like a pro.
Wow!
No. What are you doing?
-Why could you do it before?
-Are you good or bad at it?
Your lips are going to turn white
if you blow that hard. Quit that.
-It only went well in the beginning!
-What's with that?
Everything.
What does he mean?
-What do you mean by "everything"?
-It's the same as my life.
Where are the ashtrays?
Ashtrays, you said?
-The ashtrays...
-Yamamoto?
Yamamoto looks suspicious.
-What are you drinking?
-What is that?
-Yamamoto is in a bit of a pickle.
-I found the ashtrays.
Here he comes.
What are you doing?
Be careful.
That's really dangerous.
You're not supposed to drink
too many of those.
What is that?
An Exorcism Cola?
Erection.
-Are you seeing this?
-Yamamoto?
Hey!
He is constantly smiling.
Where are the ashtrays?
Are there really none?
Kukky.
He is suspicious.
Who is that?
Who is the one chewing on something?
Is that good with ice?
Yes.
I see.
Right.
Good.
It's looking good.
You're good.
Take a look at Yamamoto!
A jam session.
A Yakuza boss
Mic percussion.
You have a lot of spots
around your nipples.
I have pretty nipples, right?
You really do.
-The areolas are pink.
-Yes.
-Check them out.
-Look at this.
-It's true.
-I have pretty nipples, right?
Yeah.
Please take a look.
I'm looking.
They're uneven.
This one has fewer bumps.
I haven't noticed that.
Hot.
Hot?
-Hot?
-Don't you mean "Ouch"?
-This one is different.
-I know.
-Right.
-Did you fix it?
-Didn't that hurt?
-They're fixed.
-That fixed them.
-Right.
-They're even now.
-It's true.
-Huh?
-Thank you so much for your help.
That's amazing.
-Are they fixed?
-What did you say?
You are a nipple doctor.
You are a true nipple doctor.
A nipple doctor.
-A nipple doctor. For real.
-He really looks suspicious.
-Good work.
-Thank you.
Good work.
Where are those ashtrays?
There are no ashtrays.
Thank you.
Look at Yamamoto.
I had no idea
You had such beautiful nipples
I am going to get Yamamoto.
Who?
Did someone laugh at that?
-Who is it?
-Did someone laugh at that?
Maybe.
That was quick.
Who?
Around ten minutes have passed
since we started.
Right.
Throughout all of those ten minutes or so,
Yamamoto has been laughing slightly.
Really?
That's terrible.
Constantly.
-He was constantly laughing.
-Were you?
-You were just smiling, right?
-It was like you were at a family reunion.
-Like you normally would.
-You were laughing as if it were normal.
You were smirking the whole time.
As soon as it began,
I felt that this room
had a really happy vibe about it.
You're just happy to be working
for the first time in a while.
That's true.
There's no sense of tension in you.
You did seem really nice.
You seemed like a nice man.
You were laughing like a proud father.
I had no idea
You had such beautiful nipples
Add some tension to your face.
-That was the problem?
-Really.
It really is the first time in a while.
I am meeting some people
for the first time in ten years.
So, I couldn't help doing that
when our eyes met.
-It was a form of a greeting.
-Exactly.
I understand that.
But I do have to give you this.
-That is quick.
-So soon!
-That was really quick.
-Wow.
-I understand.
-In ten minutes.
-That's so soon!
-You were constantly smiling.
That is true.
I agree. I was smiling.
-I was enjoying myself.
-He was having too much fun.
Please try to maintain
a neutral expression.
-A neutral expression, you say?
-Yes.
-Right.
-Not look like you're laughing.
That was quick.
-Yamamoto.
-It really was.
You were using your eyes.
I didn't do anything.
It is true
that you were constantly smiling.
-You told me this was a mint.
-What's the problem?
It's sharp. Touch this.
Of course it is!
Toos!
Kasu kasu.
-Damn!
-That's definitely the  kasu kasu.
-That's true.
-You're right.
Is that a  kasu kasu dance, Kasuga?
Kasu kasu?
It is.