I think the Tsukkomi is usually the funniest.
I'm Sakurai from Mr. Children.
I guess because I'm normally working
under that kind of system or something.
That's why I think it's difficult.
I don't like to talk shit on twitter.
I don't particularly mind it,
but I really worry it might be a bother to the show,
or a bother to Matsumoto-san,
or even to my fellow co-performers.
That's why this time,
I'd like people to say it was fun,
even if it wasn't all on me.
I don't know about the other nine guys.
—You're angry, aren't you?
—I'm not angry, I'm not angry.
You're really angry.
But I'm going to win this in three hours!
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Good for you guys. You're going home soon!
Tenryuu?
That's not Tenryuu.
—He laughed!
—He laughed?
I'm sorry for using other people's passports.
You're out!
Here we go!
That's not all.
I made more for today.
Is it okay?
—Just one?
—Just one.
Fine.
—Just one?
—Just one.
Fine.
The short one, okay?
—Please do the short one.
—The short one, right?
I'm leaving it all to you.
Okay, I'm playing it, okay?
Here we go.
This is pretty bad.
"I'm gonna kill you."
It was a little funny.
Come on, Goto!
One more, one more!
Should I play it again?
I'm gonna play it again.
Fine, fine, fine.
Let's do the short one again.
The short one, okay?
Wait a second.
Are you really watching?
Not watching is cheating!
I'm watching, really.
Yeah, not watching is cheating.
I wanna laugh!
I have another short one.
—Alright?
—Sure.
Your attention, please.
Is this it for Goto?
"I'm gonna kill you."
Did you hold it in?
Did you, Goto?
You look straight out of "Family History", Goto! (Editor's Note: TV Show)
Michio?
It's Michio now?
What was that? What happened?
—What's my problem?!
—Gross!
I thought I managed to hold it!
I'm getting a cramp!
Why you, Michio?
I was in trouble all along.
I was thinking it was gonna be Goto.
Goto, you really looked
straight out of "Family History."
While you were crying.
I thought I managed to hold it in.
Was that it?
So I lowered my guard.
Tamuken-san got you.
That was too bad!
I thought I had lost my mind, man!
That was tough, huh?
I'm holding it in here!
Though I don't know if crying
is actually valid or not.
I think Tamuken was out too, though!
Tamuken-san!
That was insane, though!
Really, what's up with that?
It was really creepy!
It was creepy, right?!
Michio really laughed his ass off back then,
and since he got a direct orange...
You're out.
Too bad...
—The videos are really good, huh?
—That sucks.
Aren't the young guys having a tough time?
Thank you for everything.
My normal face looks like this.
I'm always smiling a little.
So I had to hold it down and down.
So if I let go, I just burst out at once.
He put this make-up on for one show
And then the next show also needs him to be in this make-up, right?
That sucks...
Oh man...
Here we go.
You have to watch, okay?
I'm making sure you watch for sure.
I'm gonna play it one more time.
Something was getting closer to the camera, right?
That was Sunplaza Nakano getting huge.
(EN: Japanese musician)
That was Sunplaza Nakano there?
Well, I was playing him, yeah.
It's no good if you think about it,
but it's also no good if you don't.
Yeah, that's right.
Didn't you just smile?
Right now...?
I didn't.
No way!
I was about to, normally.
He definitely just smiled normally!
Again?!
You did this before, right?
That was a normal smile just then!
A normal smile for sure!
It was a reflex.
—A reflex, huh?
—A reflex!
I know...
—What was that?
—Another reflex.
He was smiling like normal.
I didn't see.
I was just smiling at them.
Explain that...
Whose point is that going to be?
Something was getting closer to the camera, right?
That was Sunplaza Nakano getting huge.
That was Sunplaza Nakano there?
It's no good if you think about it,
but it's also no good if you don't.
That's a regular smile, right?
He's totally smiling!
I really just felt like it.
Then that's a yellow.
Okay, nothing I can do about it.
That was just a very "golden week" smile. (EN: A week in Japan with a lot of holidays)
Very superficial.
Okay, let's tighten up a bit.
So we were watching right?
What were we doing?
—I'm gonna do it.
—Ah, Jiro-chan.
—The video, right?
—Yeah, the video.
Here we go.
Alright.
—So can I watch?
—Let's do it.
Jiro-chan, right?
Guess I'll sit at the back.
So you get more distance from the screen, right?
That's too close.
I think I like it here.
Why don't you get closer?
Goto, you should sit closer.
Goto, here, here!
No, I think here's fine.
—Just do it.
—Are we watching or what?
This is too close.
I fought with Onita last year, you know? (EN: Atsushi Onita - Actor/Politician/Wrestler)
With the exploding death bat.
It was pretty rough.
Are we going to see that?
There it is!
That's the exploding death bat.
—An exploding bat?
—Yeah, an exploding bat.
You wrap barbed wire around the bat,
run electricity through it and it explodes.
You did that, huh?!
So he did that to you?
This is from the ropes.
That's all barbed wire.
That must've been pretty hot.
Just for a second.
It was more like a pinch.
—It hurt?
—Must've...
And this is what it is.
—A new year's card?
—That's a new year's card.
It wasn't for new year's, though...
It's pretty flashy, though.
For 2018...
That's pretty funny, huh?
I really don't want Zakoshi to do me in,
so why don't we move on?
You see, my son is a real idiot,
and it kind of pisses me off.
Take a look.
—That's cute!
—He's so cute!
He got there faster than I expected.
He's all over the place.
I was so pissed off at my wife after that...
They sure can hold their own, huh?
I would've lost it there.
Huh?
—Knock knock!
—There it is!
Hello...
—The hell?!
—What?!
Hello...
What?
I called her.
She's not a zombie?
She's cute.
She's Colette-san, the fortune teller.
So she's here to help you out?
I'm Colette.
Nice to meet you.
Your help is a fortune teller?
That's right.
Colette-san is amazing.
Was that two years ago?
—No, it was...
—No, I mean...
about God's voice.
—That's right.
—You heard it, right?
How do you know that?
—Am I wrong?
—No
you're completely right.
And your powers have grown stronger?
That's right.
Two years ago?
That's pretty recent.
She's been doing this for a long time,
but two years ago she heard God's voice, right?
I did.
I became able to hear God's voice.
From the heavens, right?
And you became enlightened?
Why don't you explain
the situation when it happened?
Were you sleeping?
No, it wasn't like that.
When I was little,
I met a shrine maiden that said she could hear God's voice.
So after meeting her,
we kind of got involved.
At first I didn't believe in God at all.
When you were a kid?
That's right.
I believed in our ancestors.
And I thought that since the ancestors would give us their blessings,
they and God were one and the same.
—You're taking too long.
—Too long?
I'm really sorry.
So that's how I met that maiden.
—And since she was able...
Right, she was able to speak to God,
so I also became able to speak to him.
So now you're able to talk to him?
—That's right.
—Isn't that rude? You brought her here.
—Sorry, that was too long.
—I'm really sorry.
So now we have to play along with her?
No, her predictions are extremely accurate.
—She's that good?
—Yeah.
Why don't we have one of you give it a try?
Goto?
Okay, okay, I'll give it a try.
Then please take a look at Goto-san.
Okay.
Nice to meet you.
You're friends?
—No, it's the first time we've ever met.
—We just met.
So you really looked for someone amazing?
Okay, let's see how it goes.
She really is accurate.
This is scary!
Is there anything you want her to look into?
What do you mean?
When you say "look into" do you mean
guessing something that's happened?
Or is it looking into the future
like about my job?
I think it's better to talk
about the future.
So can you look into his past for now?
—His past?
—Because he doesn't buy it yet.
I normally look at a person's habits
using their birth date.
Can we start with that?
Sure, sure!
When were you born?
I was born on June 18th 1974.
1974's... what was that again?
June 18th.
Since that's June—
This is his birth date?
That's right, the 18th.
You can tell things from his birth date?
I can tell his personality more or less with his birth date.
That works for everyone?
Yes, for everyone.
Does a one second difference change something?
Well, sometimes it does, sometimes it doesn't.
That's why some twins are so similar.
What happens with people who change date lines?
Well, when talking about fate,
even though they might share the same personality,
—their birth date may change.
—That's too long.
You asked her about it.
Okay, shall we get started?
If we were to discuss your comedy,
I'd say naturally you are a very collected person.
So whenever you're doing comedy, and lose sight of your goal,
and you can't think of anything funny to say,
you just stand strong for a little,
until you can come up with something.
That's more of less the general groundwork of your comedy.
Yes.
I think you're a very work-oriented person,
so you seem to be more focused on work than romance.
-That's right.
—Is that true?
—When we talk about—
Wait a second.
You're really all about work?
—Work is—
—That means
Romance doesn't even get a memo?
—That's right.
—One hundred percent?
Hundred percent?
It mostly seems like it, yes.
Well, that's what she found so.
It's just as she says.
That's what I'm seeing.
See? She's completely right.
Since he's such a collected person.
He's not buying it at all.
That's not true!
You don't believe her at all!
Even though I called Colette-san here for you.
—You're so rude!
—You're one to talk.
—He's too rude!
—Hey, you...
Not at all.
You're one to talk, you're always interrupting her.
And you're the one doubting her the most, too.
I want to show him that it's totally correct.
Sure, sure.
What's the problem?
What do you mean? There's no problem.
It's just that you look the most doubtful about her.
No, I'm just checking if she's right.
You don't have to go that far to do that.
But you heard God's voice two years ago, right?
—That's right.
—See?
Well, yes...
Is she your friend?
No, I just met her.
You sure like to talk, huh?
Why did you call her?
Then why not have her look at me?
Sure.
If they're going to accuse me of that much.
Sure, here we go.
1974.
1974, right.
October...
25.
You seem to be very passive in romance.
Whenever someone falls in love with you,
you just accept it and play along even if you don't like them back.
No, sorry, it was the 26th.
The 26th, right?
In that case, I think the 26th
is still about the same in romance.
You seem to be the type to judge good and bad
based on your personality.
But since you can't tell what's true or not,
you get angry too easily.
I think that's probably how you were at a younger age.
No, not at all.
—It's way off.
—Is it?
Because I'm not like that normally.
I don't know.
—You're not dating anyone either.
—I really don't know.
To be honest, when I came here today,
I didn't even know your name.
You called out to me first.
I just called you Kato
because everyone else was doing it.
But even after knowing there was a Kato here,
I really didn't know it was you, to be honest.
What's with you?
For real.
For real, what's with you?
Well, this is a perfect example of that.
—What?
—You're a complete failure.
What are you talking about?
What's your reasoning here?
Come on, tell us.
I thought we could keep going a little longer.
What are you talking about?
Colette-san.
Why bring Colette-san into this?
Keep going, then...
Let's see Hayashi Hiroko-san's young face or something. (EN: JP Actress)
Don't mind them.
So mean.
How many times are you gonna cry?
He's crying about something again.
So mean.
—You're mean.
—Yeah.
Yeah?
Poor thing.
Who?
Me.
—Well...
—I suddenly turned like this,
even though I was properly thinking about this.
You were thinking?
I was.
You've been playing the same trick all this time.
That's true.
There's no punchline.
You write any jokes normally?
I do.
Jokes? For Xabungle? (EN: Kato's Comedy Duo)
Give your partner a break.
So mean...
Who's mean?
I am.
Can you take her away?
—That's alright, isn't it?
—Is that alright?
Thank you very much.
—We're really sorry.
—No, I'm sorry.
This guy is too mean.
I wasn't expecting that.
Thank you very much.
I thought something was going to happen
back then...
Shouldn't we change the batteries already?
Ah, four hours.
—I didn't notice.
—The batteries.
I'm tired.
Of course.
—Of course you're tired.
—I'm tired.
He laughed?
He definitely laughed.
—It was just a moment.
—Just a moment?
He lowered his guard and after the "of course you're tired"
he grinned
No one smiled.
There we go.
You lowered your guard.
For real?
You got careless.
Just for a second.
It was just a second.
Hopeless!
I held it together for so long!
I was eating an onigiri,
and didn't see anything. Miyazako?
Miyazako-san laughed normally.
But well,
he's still a virgin.
He's the only one?
No, Koyabu too.
I'm getting worried, though.
Shouldn't we change the batteries already?
Ah, four hours.
—I didn't notice.
—The batteries.
I'm tired.
Of course.
Of course you're tired.
You got this far!
I did something unforgivable!
Unforgivable.
Yellow!
It can't be helped.
Here we go!
Alright!
Two more hours.
This is too long...
Koyabu-san,
—What do you want?
—Your son
was too cute earlier.
He's an idiot.
That's what you said, yeah.
His mom isn't raising him properly.
No, it was way too cute.
That's right, that's how children are.
Just look at my own kid.
How old is he?
He was 7 when he did this.
Well the numbers were already written there.
Just looking at this
-I also felt like crying.
-That's just how it is
This is him trying his best.
He's great, huh?
He's really trying his best.
With the "ki" character.
That's difficult, isn't it?
And he's getting great marks, too.
Yeah, great marks.
He's even trying his best to write his own name.
Just like this.
With the "ra" character.
—That's difficult, too.
—He's trying his best!
With the "e"!
It's too hard!
—Well, I guess.
—He's crying again.
And here's "ku".
Is there any need to practice "ku" this much?!
Of course there is!
No, no, no!
"E" is hard for sure!
Let me see.
"E" is difficult, right?
"E".
He wrote it a lot.
Who was that?
"Ku".
Is there any need to write "ku" this many times?!
Who is he now?
He's meant to be High Waist?
Just who is that?
I'm Sakurai from Mr. Children.
I'm Sakurai.
What's with those clothes?
They're pants.
Huh?
This may just work.
It might work.
There it is!
That was close!
He's too strong!
Zakoshi-san is taking everyone out one by one!
So this is your pattern now?
That was bad!
Damn it!
I feel that Goto too...
It was close, for sure.
Let's take a look.
This may just work.
He was going all "fwah, fwah!"
When did you come up with that bullshit?
Okay, Koyabu.
Yellow!
Finally!
His first one.
That's everyone, right?
Now, yeah.
There are about two hours left.
Yeah, damn it.
Zakoshi-san is on a roll.
And he still has his V.
That's right, the V.
Yeah...
Here we go.
What were we doing?
The practice sheets, right.
That thing about "ku", right?
I don't see "ku" here.
What's that?
Who's that?
Nakajo-san! (EN: Kiyoshi Nakajo - Actor)
Good morning.
Huh? Good morning!
That surprised me.
That's a big name for sure.
What?
This is my help, Nakajo-san.
Who did you call?
He's finally here.
Why was he wearing a garbage can?
You know him?
He's always taken good care of me.
Nakajo-san.
They have to smile?
If everyone smiles, I win.
Smile.
No, we're not gonna do that!
But since Nakajo-san is saying it,
we have to go along with him now.
At least eat something...
Go and eat something.
What are you talking about?
Is that a bill?
It's hot.
That's the same gag as Azumax. (EN: Takahiro Azuma, nickname "Azumax" - Comedian)
Really?
It's the same thing Azumax was doing.
For real?
And then would come that ninja gag,
with the chainmail.
—The chanel, right?
—I think you mean chain?
—Chanel.
Chanel?!
Not channel.
Huh?
So you're not going to laugh?
No way.
I'd laugh if something funny happened,
but "chanel" and "channel" is just...
Yeah, we're not gonna laugh.
Yeah, if nothing happens,
we're just not gonna laugh.
Even if you ask us to do it, if nothing happens,
well no one's going to laugh.
—Why not do a staring contest?
—Where?
Right here.
No, do something.
And he's a big deal, too.
But I didn't feel like laughing in the slightest.
What about a funny face or something?
What were they trying to do?
Everyone, please make Nakajo-san laugh.
Now we're making him laugh?
Can you do it?
He's not gonna make us laugh?
No, you make him laugh now.
It's a staring contest!
He who laughs loses!
A-pu-pu.
He didn't even flinch.
He had this existencial stare.
He didn't even budge.
I thought it was kinda funny, though.
It's a staring contest.
He who laughs loses.
A-pu-pu.
What?
I'm sorry.
He's making me laugh?
Can he even stand this?
Make sure one of them makes me laugh.
I'm sorry.
That was scary.
He just whispers,
it's too scary!
What do we do?
Why don't we do something together?
Why don't we call the guitar samurai?
Let's give him a call.
Nakajo-san?
A book...
Do you remember
—the guitar samurai?
—I do, I do.
You know what he says?
"Didn't you say!"
I've never done that.
"Kitchen slice..."
You do it.
You should try something funny too.
But Nakajo-san.
I want you to do it.
—Can you do it?
—Can you give it a shot?
"I'm Imori Miyuki."
"Ikue Imori's Deli Deli Kitchen."
"Raw fish is definitely the best."
"It's delicious."
"Didn't you say"
What's with that?
"But you really are."
"Almost past the expiration date."
"Too bad"
"Imori Miyuki's"
"Almost-almost kitchen."
"Cut it up."
Who's he reading that to?
Read it.
Is that funny?
I can't do that, so read it at least once.
"I am Yakumaru Hirohi."
"Formerly known as Shibugakitai from Yakkun."
"Now I run a show for housewives every morning."
"Didn't you say."
That's funny!
Yours was funnier.
At first you were speaking normally.
Normally?
But not to make someone laugh.
"I am Nonomura Makoto."
"I try to discover this world's mysteries."
"I get all the answers."
"Today's is..."
"Borschwort."
"Didn't you say."
He's laughing a lot.
Huh? What?
It's not funny?
Well... we're not quite there yet.
—Why not do it again?
—No, that's well...
It's just not happening.
I think we should have him watch one of Zakoshi's videos.
Wanna watch them?
Can you watch one of my videos?
Then let's do it with the big screen.
Which means that we have to watch too, right?
Of course.
That's amazing.
—Ready?
—Sure, let's do it.
We just met at Kyoto station.
That's right.
Back then....
That's a subliminal effect.
I don't get it.
At all.
Well, it's not like there's anything to understand.
That's the point.
It's more of an experience.
So it didn't work, huh?
It's not happening.
It's not gonna make Nakajo-san laugh.
Yeah, exactly!
It's far too deranged for him.
I can laugh, right?
So I shouldn't be here, right?
No, not at all!
That's not the point!
Though you could go home if you wanted.
—Well, I guess so.
—Hey, you're rude.
I guess so.
We should have him leave already.
That's funny.
You can't do that.
We had him come all the way from Kyoto, too.
Aren't you leaving yet?
Watch out....
Really, watch out...
—So anyways.
—Sorry about this.
Really.
Sorry it turned out like this.
We're sorry, too.
No, no.
Apologizing is...
Well, you see...
Are you apologizing?
No, no.
The fact that the mood turned so awkward since you arrived
is kind of your own fault, Nakajo-san, so...
—You could've just told me.
—Please apologize.
Okay! I'm sowwy!
1 hour 40 minutes!
Anything there?
I kinda wanna play something.
You scared me! What is it?
—What?
—What was that sound?
—A dog?
—No, it's this key.
What's that? That's scary!
That hurts.
We had that?
What's that?
Who brought that?
I'm sure it's just a prop.
(Audio from "Quiz Derby")
It's this.
"Too bad!"
Was that a coincidence?
It's a coincidence
A coincidence for sure.
Which one did you press?
That's too dangerous.
It was close.
This one?
"Too bad!"
—Is that the real deal?
—It is.
Was that on purpose?
Who recorded that?
"The results are...!!" (EN: Hamada Masatoshi's voice)
Who was it?!
—Who?
—Who was it?
I held it.
—I held it, hey!
—Who was it?
I held it, of course.
—Me?
—I held it too!
It wasn't me!
Me?
No way, I held it!
I agree with everyone.
Tamuken was smiling.
I wasn't smiling, not at all.
I held it.
—No doubt about it?
—No doubt!
Let's take a look.
I definitely held it.
I can't tell for sure if it was a false alarm.
This one?
"Too bad!"
—Is that the real deal?
—It is.
Was that on purpose?
Who recorded this?
"The results are...!!"
He's smiling for sure.
He's smiling.
You were definitely smiling.
If you did that all of a sudden, you'd be smiling!
More than I expected.
Tamuken had an orange card already so...
No way!
You're out!
The lion dance ends here.
You weren't able to do it
I'm just taking it like this, so what?
Sure you are.
So you're not laughing even though you're allowed?
It's not like we were holding it, though.
I was tired.
Today was too rough.
With Zakoshi's beeping.
I really wanted to laugh.
For real.
And Kato's damned fortune telling was rough, too.
So you heard God's voice two years ago, right?
That's right.
I was waiting for something to come all the time.
Just like when you're in a haunted house.
"When is it coming, when is it coming?"
All the time.
That damned guy.
What's with him?
One and a half hour.
Can we do anything?
The six of us.
Why not press the sounds until we're used to them?
That's too dangerous.
Which one?
The "Results are..." one.
No, let's drop that one.
I remember which one it was, though.
"The results are...!!"
I just think of the whole picture.
I think I'm used to it.
Something's here.
Hey, mine was better!
If you punch me, I'll punch you back.
Many many times!
How many times?
Two billion times.
That's how many times to one?
Two billion.
What about four times?
Four billion times.
So it's not proportional, right?
—It's not proportional at all.
—That's right.
Four billion times.
I'll punch you back!
I'm sure you could.
Funakoshi Eiichiro's... wife? (EN: JP Actor)
Funakoshi Eiichiro's wife.
Is that working?
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Doing Hanzawa again? (EN: Naoki Hanazawa - Character in a TV Show with the same name)
That was too hard.
And he kept going!
Come on!
It's always like this.
That was too long!
Well, you laughed.
Of course I would!
I was wondering what he was going to say.
I was waiting for Hanzawa or Mom!
You just have a yellow so far, right Gotou?
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
He's locked on now.
Of course you laughed!
That was completely impossible.
—Orange!
—Yeah, I'm sorry.
Next time...
...you're getting the red!
Zakoshi has too many points
Too many?
We have to do something about Zakoshi-san!
What does Zakoshi laugh at?
I laughed at Jiro earlier.
So far,
what has made him look like he was about to laugh?
When you were going all "gah!"
I was doing that?
With the boobs...
At the beginning, right?
Since they were boobs—
Those boobs, right?
I bit on those boobs,
and you went all "gah!"
It was nothing, but I was about to laugh.
With that?
My boobs!
They're gone!!
Here we go!
Okay, can I turn this on?
It's a little hot.
Don't you think it's hot?
Can I do a Yasumura impersonation? (EN: JP Comedian)
Do "Tonikaku Akarui"
—Can I?
—Sure.
Music! Come on!
Stay calm!
—I'm wearing them!
—It's coming out!
Yeah, my dick is.
No, even if you wear clothes, there's no point if it's sticking out.
My dick is, yeah.
But rest assured.
-I'm wearing clothes.
-It's sticking out.
Yeah, but my dick is coming out.
My dick is coming out,
but rest assured,
It's sticking out.
I'm wearing clothes.
Rest assured!
I'm wearing clothes!
My dick is sticking out, thought.
Can you stop it with your dick?
My dick.
Zakoshi is strong, for real.
And he's going to put it back, for sure.
I think the zombies should go soon.
Who can do it?
Let's go.
Zombie time!
I forgot about this!
I had forgotten about this.
A zombie, huh?
Hey!
—It's been a long time!
—Long time no see!
Good to see things are getting heated around here.
It's the zombie.
Wai— Wait!
—What?
—I can't believe this.
What?
There he is!
—What's this?
—That's Iron Man!
—It's Iron Man.
—Iron Man?
Iron Man's here.
He came to the studio.
Take a look, Zakoshi.
Iron Man came flying in with his hands.
He came flying?
Flying?
He crashed in.
Is he fighting an enemy?
Right, he's fighting.
Amazing. Let's go, Iron Man!
Alright, let's go Iron Man!
Those are too many locks!
I had never seen such a wrestling Iron Man.
Give it your all.
Above you, Iron Man! Above you!
Do it above you!
This is rough...
That was okay.
He's really filthy now.
What a bother.
Almost one hour left.
Really!
Just a little more!
An incredible monster appeared!
Other than Iron Man?
Yeah, look!
What's that?
That's a scary monster.
Looks like something out of Resident Evil
Yeah.
That's scary.
—I'm freaking out!
—Did you cut that off?
Ah, so I think he's the type
that doesn't really speak.
Can you hear that?
He's really weak to that music.
But he put it himself...
He's really weak to it.
He's falling asleep.
Maybe it's healing him, though.
And I thought he was terrifying.
It's over.
—He noticed.
—Watch out!
Watch out, watch out!
That's scary!
Watch out!
That's scary, yeah.
Now's the time for Iron Man to fight.
Watch out!
What's going on?
Zai-Zen-Naomi!
Zai-Zen!
Zaizen?
Nao—
That's the head of Zaizen Naomi? (EN: JP Actress)
Zaizen Naomi.
Why?
You shouldn't hold on to it that much.
Zaizen Naomi!
What happened to Zaizen Naomi-san?
A friend...
You can't do that.
Don't hold your friend's head.
A token of friendship.
Your friend's done for.
—It's over.
—A token of friendship.
That's not a token
Zaizen Naomi.
Token of friendship.
Zaizen... a token of friendship.
Nobu-san, can I take one last shot?
Sure, go ahead!
A shot?
Shwut up alweady!
What the hell are you doing?
Who's that supposed to be?
Master Sakata. (EN: Toshio Sakata)
Hey, Zakoshi!
Sakata's calling out to you.
—He has something to tell you.
—What is it?
Don't copy my act!
—I'm not copying...
—We're not friends!
Kato-san.
Hey, Kato!
I love you!
I wanted to be like you!
He's really getting into it.
Really?
I wanted to be you.
But I couldn't.
And I don't have time to chase after you.
So I'm trusting myself to you! Shit!
The timing is all over the place, though.
That's Hachimitsu Jiro-san.
I don't know who that is!
I've never seen him!
Does he have an NGK show?
Sure, he's on it all the time.
I see him and Sinktank-san all the time.
I don't remember that.
Don't you like Sinktank-san?
I love Sinktank!
What a stupid question!
That's a stupid comment, really.
Since you love him so much.
—Now do Goto-san.
—Goto
I'm glad you're so unfunny!
Just seeing if Goto retires someday
is my only happiness month after month!
Hoping he's quitting month after month!
I'm not quitting, though.
So you've held on for a long time.
You're really hanging on!
What about his hosting skills?
When Goto hosts, it almost feels
like a damned dog doing it!
And not a cat?
Whichever is fine!
I just don't like how you do it!
For example?
For example, you were very unfunny
when you stepped into my yard.
What's the most unfunny example?
When you squealed at the height difference.
My relatives were frozen in their seats
not laughing at all.
The only ones who laughed back then were your manager
and maybe the younger guys.
If you can only make those close to you laugh,
then just quit already!
I feel bad for Iwao!
The M-1 in 2003 was your lowest level!
And you managed to be on TV with M-1!
He just won't shut up.
And now,
you expect people to play along to all eternity!
Did Sakata really speak that much?
Stop it!
I'll make sure to study more, then.
And you can't take it back anymore!
I'd laugh if you made at least some monkey jokes!
Why can't you do that?!
Did you quit the theaters?!
No, I'm still performing in theaters.
Then do the monkey!
Or for example~
Does he normally stretch that?
Of course I do.
You too, Koyabu!
How can they stand you?
Your daughter, or your wife?
I guess you're feeding them since you're in luck right now,
but don't get used to that money!
I guess they're just glad lucky guy is getting paid every month!
What about his chairmanship?
He's the most useless!
Are you trying to take down the NGK?!
You're banned from the NGK now!
Your NGK is now:
nothing!
With no time!
Just pure improvisation!
You know what I mean?
No time? Just improvisation?
You don't have anything!
You're just tall and appear on TV!
So you're stretching that part now?
Why don't we go?
Why are all of you youngsters
so damned unfunny?
Let's go.
Nothing since your Zakoba days!
Um...
What about this person right here?
Who's that boy?
Aren't you always fooling around with Sinktank-san?
I don't remember any Sinktank-san!
That was funny, really funny.
What was that?
Alright, let's do something.
Just to break the ice.
I don't want this anymore!
Do it!
Alright let's go!
What are we making today?
"What are we making today?"
"What are we making?"
What is that?
The answer was "anal"!
What does he mean by "making"?
This guy's an idiot.
That's good, that's good.
You held it in?
We did.
We held it in, huh?
Zakoshi is going all out.
I wish he could take it slow.
That was unexpected!
Hey, chairman!
Hello.
I'm a zombie.
A zombie?
A helper?
He's a helper.
A helper.
I'm here to make you laugh.
I'm counting on you.
I don't have any points, so I'm counting on you.
Chairman, please touch my nipples.
Touch my nipples.
Please touch my nipples.
—I have to touch them?
—Yes.
Touch them three more times, please.
Just tou-touch me
a-again.
Me?
Goto?
—Miyazako-san?
—I haven't smiled at all.
—Was it Miyazako-san?
—Who was it?
No way, I haven't smiled!
My hand just reacted instinctively,
but I'd say Goto's and Miyazako's reactions
were a bit too big.
Alright.
No, no way. That's too—
It wasn't that much.
Let's take a look.
There's a good chance you're in the clear.
Touch them three more times, please.
Just tou-touch me
a-again.
No, that's just...
Is he safe?
His face was just...
I could feel his face going off track.
And I just reacted instinctively.
To be honest, it was really close.
Alright, then.
You're safe.
That was close!
So does that mean I'm out yet?
Do I still have a chance?
You're still fine.
That was bad!
Pretty scary.
Here we go!
Alright!
46 minutes to go!
46?
Ah, there he is.
What's with that paper?
You see, I compiled everything in my life so far,
and wrote it down in a timeline?
A timeline?
So what's happened every year?
That's right, yes.
We don't have much time, so let's go with the events.
Alright.
"When I was just 0 years old,"
"My father Tomoyuki, and my mother Yuuko gave birth to their eldest son."
"My name borrowed one character from my father: Tomoyuki."
"The name comes from finding your own path by yourself."
"And so I was named Naoyuki."
"My mother wanted to name me Gou."
—That was 0 years old?
—Yes.
Two years old.
"According to my mother, I would catch a fever quite often."
—You might not remember, though.
—Exactly.
Four years old.
"My father told my mother not to feed me too much."
"The two got upset and started fighting."
"My father told my mother not to just put yellow clothes on me."
He's awful at turning the pages.
Maybe he's just too dry.
Maybe it's the texture.
"Six years old."
"Looking at my kindergarten pictures,
I can tell this is when I started to put on weight."
"Trying to remember,"
"I realize I was always exhausted as a child."
"My mom took me to a gym to lose some weight,"
"but the only people there were other housewives."
Why did you say it twice?
Maybe he thought it'd be funny?
I just let it slide.
So what's next?
"Eight years old.
We went to Himeji Central Park for a field trip."
"When I tried to get on the bus that was parked
in a corner of the park,"
"I stepped on a big dog's shit."
"Since we were about to go, my mom panicked,
and grabbed a stone."
"She started rubbing the shit off the shoe."
"And even tried washing it with the park's water,
but the shit was still there."
"My mother hit me, angry at me."
"I just got on the bus with my filthy shoe."
"I get really carsick normally,"
"and as expected, I had to withstand getting dizzy."
"However, I hurried off the bus once we reached our destination,"
"and puked in front of everyone.
So mom got mad and hit me again."
Okay, why don't we leave it at that?
Why don't you bring the other thing?
I'll be back soon.
What a great idea!
Can I take a look?
Sure.
How old is he?
A year older than me.
He looks pretty battered.
Well, he's 47 this year.
Just like Tomochika.
—So what now?
—Did he leave?
No, I think he just went to grab something.
Maybe he just got nervous?
I wonder if he'll take long.
Here we go!
There he is!
Who is that?
I'm Kusama Yayoi! (EN: JP Artist)
He's loud.
But he does look the part.
—Are you leaving?
Huh?
I wanted to talk to Kusama-san.
That was quick, Kusama-san.
Is that it?
He's changing everything.
I'm sorry, I think that's it.
That's it?
That's it.
What's he doing now?
—Wanna see?
—No, I'm fine.
Just saying.
Imabeppu!
Yes?
—Take off your shirt.
—Yes.
What do you mean by what he's doing?
Well, I don't know, I haven't done any of that myself.
I was just thinking about seeing his "anal" again.
Goto.
You dug your own grave, huh?
Wanna see, Goto?
I was just wondering how an Imabeppu version would be.
—Can you say "the answer was anal"?
—Sure.
What are you doing?
The answer is "anal"!
That's not it.
You see, Zakoshi
did that on the VTR.
—Didded you watch the video?
—I did, yes.
"Didded"?
Did you just say "didded"?
"Didded"? Why?
That doesn't matter.
You can just do it now.
That's alright.
What are you doing?
The answer is "anal"!
That's dark...
—He's too fat so I didn't see.
—You can't see a thing.
You're too fat
and we can't see!!
But if I put my contacts on,
the world changes.
The answer was...
"anal"!
It's too dark and I can't see!!
But if I put on my contacts,
the world changes!
The answer was "anal".
It's too fat and I can't see!!
But if I put on my contacts,
the world changes.
The answer was "anal"!
I can't see! It's too dark!!
But you're about to break too.
If you laugh, you're out, Gotou!
We made you laugh.
Why did I have to open my mouth?!
You dug your own grave.
Well, now it can't be helped.
I didn't even have to see it!
—I'm sorry.
—You're too fat.
You all managed to hold it in.
I guess Gotou couldn't do it, though.
I couldn't.
We don't even need the replay.
The answer was "anal"!
I can't see! It's too dark!!
But you're about to break too.
This one's too bad.
Yeah, it's impossible.
He was basically bursting out laughing!
He really was, huh?
Which means?
You're out!
Well I guess that's that.
This can't go on like this.
Everyone,
Zakoshi has become far too powerful!
That's right, his points are too high.
20 million yen!
He's too strong!
With a single show...
Well, I'm tired.
And I managed to hang on for so long.
It was always Zakoshi-san.
Mom! Mom!
But if I put on my contacts,
the world changes.
Every time he gets close,
I just get stage fright.
You idiot!
"Next time."
"The season 7 finale."
I did think Katou had been pretty strong so far!
He was amazing.