THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
It's a bit surprising,
but I've been getting a lot of remarks
from people who don't work in comedy
about Documental.
HITOSHI MATSUMOTO
They say it truly is funny.
-That's what amazes me.
-Sitting down and Sharon Stone-ing.
After all, I wouldn't call this
a very refined show.
I was really surprised when Rola said,
"I want in."
ROLA - "I WANT IN"
I thought,
"What? What's going on in your head?"
She said, "I can do it."
ROLA - "I CAN DO IT"
We've made small changes each season.
SEASON 2: "POINT SYSTEM"
IF THERE'S A DRAW AFTER 6 HOURS,
WHOEVER GOT THE MOST LAUGHS WINS
SEASON 3: "ZOMBIE TIME"
ELIMINATED PLAYERS RETURN AS ZOMBIES
Making slight adjustments
has worked out well.
I've added something
a little different this time, too.
SEASON 5: "A NEW EXPERIMENT"
They're allowed to bring somebody
completely unrelated into the room.
SEASON 5: "HELPER SYSTEM"
EACH PLAYER CAN BRING INTO
THE ROOM ONE "HELPER" AS A WEAPON
They could even bring in a stray dog.
-So, the comedians know this?
-They've been told.
I don't know if they'll all use a Helper.
Some may say, "I'm fine without one."
USE OF THE HELPER SYSTEM IS LEFT
TO EACH CONTESTANT'S DISCRETION
I won't reveal yet
how many have brought a Helper.
THE ENDING I WANT TO SEE
I think
it's high time for an "instant kill."
INSTANT KILL
"Instant" is an exaggeration, but...
ALL PREVIOUS SEASONS TOOK
SIX HOURS TO DETERMINE A WINNER
Nobody's won in an hour yet.
But it's like boxing.
First-round knockouts can happen.
I WANT TO SEE A FIRST-ROUND K.O.
ON THE LAWLESS BATTLEGROUND
Usually I play cheerful characters
All the members are finally here
IMPROMPTU TEAMWORK RUNS WILD
TEN ENEMIES
They're all enemies, but at the same time,
it's about team play, too.
WORKING TOGETHER TO ELIMINATE OTHERS
If they interrupted each other's bits,
the show wouldn't work.
In that sense, I think comedians
truly are a bunch of gentlemen.
A BUNCH OF GENTLEMEN
Even though these gentlemen
whip out their penises.
But they do it in a gentlemanly way.
IN A GENTLEMANLY WAY
As gentlemen.
AS NOBLES
They do it as nobles.
THOUGHTS GOING INTO SEASON 5
It's an interesting thing.
I host oogiri-themed TV shows.
I do talk-based shows,
like Suberanai Hanashi.
I judge sketch comedy competitions, too.
I know how each comedian
has their strong suit.
Now it's becoming clearer in my head
which kind of comedian
is best suited for Documental.
I did it!
-Good for you!
-That was amazing.
-Cookie won.
-What? What? Really? What?
I think we'll have to gather the winners
and host a grand championship one day.
LOOKING FORWARD
TO A GRAND CHAMPIONSHIP
Yesterday I watered the potted plants
in my yard.
This morning I was surprised
to see sheets of ice on them.
But I was told the plants would be fine.
The hardiness of plants is amazing.
I send you this invitation
with my best intentions.
I sincerely hope you will join me
with one million yen on your person.
I am hosting Documental.
I have prepared 10 million yen
as the champion's prize.
Whether to participate or not,
decision is yours.
If you are willing to participate,
I will contact you again
regarding the time and venue.
I look forward to your reply.
As spring approaches,
I hope it will bring you happiness.
Sincerely, Hitoshi Matsumoto.
THE COMEDIANS ARRIVE AT THE BATTLEFIELD
He brought a large bag.
Am I the first?
I'm the first player?
For Akiyama, it's like he's back
on old stomping grounds.
This room hasn't changed at all.
It's still the same.
I'm Ryuji Akiyama,
from the comedy group Robert.
Nice to meet you.
I think it's time I won.
Excuse me.
What's this?
I know this envelope.
Please take it.
It's the same every time.
THE THIRD INVITATION
Even the way you entered the room.
Akiyama is very versatile.
He can pretty much do everything.
MR. ALL-ROUNDER
And he's very well-suited to Documental.
He's more than ready to win.
ONE OF THE FAVORITES
What comes to mind is
that bit with Kenkoba.
SEASON 3 - WITH KENDO KOBAYASHI
DURING ZOMBIE TIME
"THE CHINESE MASSAGE LADY
AND HER CUSTOMER"
It was amazing.
It wasn't something I'd had in store.
I was simply imitating
a massage lady I knew.
There has never been an occasion
when my private activities
worked more to the advantage
of my comedy performance than that time.
Don't say he's not here.
THE HUMAN BULLET
POSSESSED CREATOR
But some people are still able
to keep straight faces,
so I need to kick it up a notch.
BECOMING "POSSESSED"
BEYOND ALL EXPECTATIONS
I'm not a first-timer anymore.
I can't just reprise the patterns
my seniors created.
SEEKING NEW REALMS OF COMEDY
I can't hitch rides
on others' jokes either.
ORIGINALITY
I want to bring unique weapons
to the battle.
Ah, this feeling.
All I really want is to hear one phrase
from comedians who saw the show:
"Hey, that really made me laugh."
PROVING HE'S A "ONE-AND-ONLY CREATOR"
Everything is the same.
Completely. Even the interior.
Here's another one.
We have a first-timer.
Really?
Akiyama!
I'm Takahashi from Savanna.
I brought one million yen.
I sure want to turn it into 10 million.
Hello.
What?
You want me?
You think you can get away with anything
if you say it's on Mr. Matsumoto's orders?
Takahashi is more of a brainy type.
MR. BRAINY
I think rather than doing physical comedy,
he'll work the room slyly.
SLY STYLE
I think he'll pace himself
and keep a safe distance from the action.
THE SUPER BROWN-NOSING COMEDIAN
I always look like I'm smiling.
People have always said that.
NATURALLY SMILEY
When I was in high school,
I was harassed by a gang of teens
three times.
Each time they came up and said,
"What's so funny?"
"WHAT'S SO FUNNY?"
Will this be considered laughing?
-It will.
-It will?
You are laughing.
This is no good? How about this?
-It'll be an out.
-An out?
NATURALLY SMILEY
If I'm not a tough judge on Takahashi,
I'll have another "Fujimoto issue."
THE FUJIMOTO ISSUE
People accuse me of going
too easy on Fujimoto.
I've never gone easy on him.
Takahashi.
You were invited?
I think that in any kind of competition,
the guys who win are able to picture
themselves doing so beforehand.
I can't picture a thing,
so I came here today thinking
I probably won't win 10 million.
AIMING FOR A SELFLESS VICTORY
-I can't picture it.
-What?
I have no idea how you will act.
I can't predict
how you will attack at all.
Morning.
Here comes a big fish.
A big fish.
-A very big fish.
-Why do you say that?
I didn't--
These are three totally different players.
Good morning.
It's stark when they're together.
Hello, I'm Eikoh Kano
from Maseki Geinosha.
Wait, could this be...
I'm in trouble.
I think he's good.
He may not admit it himself,
but he's goofy.
THE NATURAL GOOFBALL
-It's your first time, right?
-It is.
What does Documental mean to you?
It's a sumo ring.
It's a place where comedians clash.
Each brings their own weapon...
Well, they don't use weapons in sumo...
I'd say it's a battlefield.
I'm changing my answer.
It's a battlefield.
THE NARCISSISTIC
PRANK VICTIM
He tends to go on the offensive
in situations like this.
SURPRISINGLY AGGRESSIVE
But he's not funny at all.
But the fact that his jokes aren't funny
may actually become his weapon.
Whenever I get invited
to talk shows and stuff,
I often stammer, or say the wrong thing.
LIVING OFF UNINTENTIONAL HUMOR
Since people laugh when I mess up,
I never get to say my punchline.
To be honest, getting that kInd
of laughs is not what i want.
HE'S DISAPPOINTED
This time, I want to make the others laugh
with jokes and props that I prepared.
I have never won any titles.
Not the R-1 Grand Prix. Nothing.
HAS THE TITLE-LESS COMEDIAN'S TIME COME?
I did win once
on Tsurukou's radio show...
THAT TIME ON TSURUKOU'S RADIO SHOW...
Just once. There were three competitors.
RANKED NUMBER ONE, OUT OF THREE
Have we seen each other
since your comeback?
Let me see... No, we haven't.
Have you always had those lines
on your cheeks?
What? I lost that much weight?
Maybe it's been too long...
I guess he's been under
a lot of emotional distress.
This is scary.
Really?
Are you serious?
Well, I guess this would be
a little surprising to the others.
My name is Tomonori Jinnai.
I'm still thinking of going home.
I want to go home.
-Good evening.
-Long time no see.
It came...
-You know the story?
-Of course.
You need to prepare one million yen.
One million yen is not the problem.
I'd rather just hand over one million
and stay away from this.
This is going to be interesting.
He's the type of comedian
who is good at playing with people.
SHINES BY TEASING PEOPLE
So I expect him to do a good job.
MR. SOLO PLAYER
One thing I'm worried about
regarding Jinnai is
when it comes to oogiri games,
he's not funny at all.
I don't have one-punch gags.
I'm useless when it comes to making
people laugh instantly.
The other players won't just be good.
They'll be like top goalscoring forwards.
I AM NOT A FORWARD
How will I...
And then I get a police car siren.
EVEN RANDOM HAPPENSTANCE IS AGAINST HIM
When I had dinner with Jinnai
late last year,
we discussed what we'd do
if we were invited to Documental.
Yeah, we did.
-I said I'd definitely decline.
-You did, right?
I didn't bring anything
you might call a weapon,
so all I can hope for is
to win by counterattacking.
THE GAME PLAN IS "COUNTERATTACK"
Well... How many more are coming?
-Six more.
-Six.
So far we don't have many
who like to take off their clothes.
only brought a bag to hold the money.
There's a stick... A very long stick.
-This show is the peak!
-I know. I get it.
In Kano's case...
-Good morning.
-Really?
What a lineup!
-He brought so much.
-That's how much you should bring.
This brings out your true colors.
I see.
I'd be scared without props.
-Good morning.
He's the King of Conte champion.
I'm Kenji Yamauchi of Kamaitachi.
They say King of Conte 2017 was
the highest-level competition in history.
I come here fresh after winning that.
It came!
It came.
I'm in!
You are?
I think I have achieved enough
to get an invitation.
I DESERVE TO BE INVITED
I wouldn't want to compete against him.
Not Yamauchi.
He doesn't laugh much, and he keeps
a poker face when he attacks.
POKER-FACED KING OF CONTE
His face gives him an unfair advantage.
UNFAIR FACE
THE REGULAR WINNER OF CONTESTS
He may be one of the top contenders.
-What do you think?
-Go for it.
Will you lend me 500,000?
WILL YOU LEND ME 500,000?
Then give me 5,000,000 if you win.
Of course, no problem.
Keep in mind
that's only a verbal agreement.
Who'd lend you money after hearing that?
Now is a very important time in my career,
so I really will aim to win.
-It's your first time, right?
-It is.
I watch it... I used to.
It's a show I only used to watch.
I know this will make me sound greedy,
but I want to make the others
laugh their asses off,
and after I've gained
everyone's admiration,
then I want the 10 million.
MAKE AN IMPACT AND 10 MILLION YEN
-There's a million yen in there?
-Yes.
-In your "22" bag.
-In here, yes.
I had such a hard time raising it.
But you won all that prize money.
-Yeah.
-It's gone.
-You spent it already?
-Yes.
I gave some to my parents,
and I paid off all the debts I had.
I had no money left,
so I went to Yoshimoto Finance for a loan,
but they turned me down.
They didn't give you a loan?
-That sounds like a giant.
-That does.
Seriously?
-Jin's here!
-We had drinks the other day!
-"Is the red panda..."
-"Still standing?"
Unbelievable.
Hi. I'm the comedy world's fantasista,
Kenji Tamura.
Cha!
TAMURA'S GRILL RESTAURANT
This is for you.
I got one.
I've always thought
this show would suit him.
I've been trying to get him on
for a while.
Among today's contestants,
he's the toughest when it comes
to having nobody laugh at you.
That's his strength.
STRONG NERVES
SIDE BUSINESS KING OF KANSAI
And he has the virtual currency issue.
The human race created
the industrial revolution.
We switched from horses to cars.
Our productivity and transport capacity
increased drastically.
The human race evolved at great speed.
TAMURA TALK:
THE WONDERS OF VIRTUAL CURRENCY
Now it's happening in the currency market.
It's an industrial revolution.
He's a miser, more than anything.
His fixation on the prize money
will be stronger than anyone else's.
MISER
Nowadays people see me as
a grill restaurant owner.
Or as an entrepreneur.
But I want to make them stop and think,
"No, no. Tamura Kenji is a comedian."
TAMURA THE COMEDIAN'S BIG BATTLE
When I was younger,
I didn't care about the audience.
Wherever they were.
All I tried to do was
make the other comedians laugh.
I had a chip on my shoulder.
I always told Jinnai to go and die.
If I can go back to who I was then,
then I may have a chance of winning.
You're part of the comeback group.
-The comeback group?
-Him and you.
-Is this your comeback?
-I wasn't suspended.
-Oh, that's right.
-He wasn't suspended.
-I was never suspended.
-You weren't? But you deserved to be.
-You and Campylobacter.
-That's what causes food poisoning.
My restaurant got "suspended" for that.
-So Tamura is here...
-Give me a break.
-Wearing sunglasses is unfair.
-You're right.
-Someone's here.
-They are?
-Unbelievable!
-I'm scared!
Tamura, you're here?
-You've been on before.
-No way.
Jinnai, you got a haircut!
That's what people do.
-This is too much.
-Now wait a minute!
Hi, I'm Kendo Kobayashi.
Fortunately enough,
the public affectionately call me
"Koba Ken."
HOTEL
4 HOURS - 4,500 YEN
Oh, no...
-What are you doing here?
-I'm looking for comedy material.
LOOKING FOR LAUGHS
IN THE RED LIGHT DISTRICT
Jinnai, Kobayashi, and Tamura
were actually classmates at NSC.
THREE MEMBERS OF NSC'S 11TH CLASS
Seeing the three of them in one room
may be quite a feast for comedy fans.
GOOD FRIENDS AND ARCH RIVALS
Kobayashi has been here before,
so he may be feeling a little defensive
towards the other two.
Like, "This is my turf."
DOCUMENTAL IS MY TURF
THE EROTIC TENOR
WITH NO DOUBTS
I realized that I can't win
by playing the way I did last time.
I had unfinished business
and it was starting to nag me.
UNFINISHED BUSINESS
"THE CHINESE MASSAGE LADY
AND HER CUSTOMER"
I beat myself up
for not ejaculating that time.
WHY COULDN'T I EJACULATE?
I really regret it.
Last time, I didn't want to win that much.
Being funny was more important.
LAUGHTER OVER VICTORY
This time, I wanNA win more than be funny.
VICTORY OVER LAUGHTER
And I want to ejaculate more than
I want to win.
EJACULATION OVER VICTORY
If Jinnai puts on a silly costume
and does something silly on this table,
I might cry.
If he does, laugh.
Why not laugh?
-He made it to where he is now...
-Laugh, please.
...without doing that kind of stuff.
That's who he is.
-You're right.
-I agree.
That trait of Jinnai's
may actually work in his favor.
Now,
here comes another one.
-Those sunglasses aren't fair.
-I know, I know.
Don't be so jumpy.
Is he gathering all the classmates?
-He used to be with Yoshimoto.
-They're getting all of the 11th class!
Zakoshi!
Jinnai's here!
-It's like Nichome Theater.
-Three of you!
Hi. I'm Hollywood Zakoshisyoh.
-How are you doing?
-Sorry?
An invitation to Documental?
It finally came?
IT FINALLY CAME
I have to say he gets me a lot.
COCKROACHMAN
He has his own universe,
so he may actually surprise us.
TOP CONTENDER?
If he were my daughter's boyfriend,
it would be a real nightmare.
A NIGHTMARE IF HE WAS
MY DAUGHTER'S BOYFRIEND
A REPERTOIRE OF 200 MILLION IMPERSONATIONS
THE KING OF ARABIKI
-You're worried, aren't you?
-I am.
This is not good.
Hey, Eikoh is here!
Your voice is so loud.
-This is my big chance!
-He's happy to be here.
FOUR MEMBERS OF NSC'S 11TH CLASS
No restrictions on what you can say or do.
Who could beat me?
THE BEST WITHOUT RESTRICTIONS
Some people mount attacks,
while others don't.
What the hell is with those guys who
do nothing apart from trying not to laugh?
ATTACKS ARE WHAT MAKES DOCUMENTAL
I'll personify that spirit for you.
I am the true Documental.
I'M THE REAL DOCUMENTAL
Hollywood Zakoshisyoh, unveiled.
You don't even see 10% of me on TV.
THEY CAN'T SHOW ME ON TV
I'll show them what crazy is.
I want to show real insanity.
INSANE
My chances of winning just went up
thanks to you.
What do you mean?
I'm not going to laugh.
I'll never laugh.
I'm sure everyone will be surprised
to see this next person.
He didn't bring anything.
He's empty-handed.
-Are you serious?
-It's Junior.
It's a class reunion.
-You're right.
-It was nice and cozy in here.
It was brave of you
to accept this, Junior.
Hi, I'm Chihara Junior.
I'm excited to finally be invited.
Excuse me.
-Hello.
-Yes?
This invitation... There's no comedian
who doesn't know this.
IT FINALLY CAME
I wonder what he'll do.
I have no idea how he will play.
HOW WILL JUNIOR FIGHT?
To be honest, I thought this show
had nothing to do with me.
AN UNEXPECTED INVITATION
THE THEORY-LOVING ONOMATOPOEIC
MAESTRO OF CHATTER
-I can't believe you're here.
-Wait a minute. I don't stand a chance.
He's at the next level in his career.
ONE LEVEL ABOVE THE OTHERS
So I'm curious to see what he'll do.
HOW WILL HE FIGHT?
Rather than wondering if he'll win,
I'd like to see him reveal
a Junior we've never seen before.
JUNIOR AS NEVER SEEN BEFORE
I didn't bring anything with me.
I CAME WITH NO WEAPONS
I decided not to think about it.
There's no use thinking about it.
FIGHTING AS I AM
I don't have any tricks that I do
backstage just for comedians.
I truly dislike parties
where many people are present.
I have virtually no experience
working in groups.
Technically speaking,
I only graduated from grade school.
I'd like to know myself
what will become of me.
BECAUSE I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT WILL BECOME OF ME
Hello.
-It's Kano.
-Thank you.
When the last one enters...
I had no idea.
I'm sure the atmosphere
will change dramatically again.
Here they come.
Is it a woman?
It wasn't supposed to be a woman.
Maybe he became a woman.
No more from Osaka, please.
It couldn't be worse.
-This is the worst.
-Again?
It couldn't be worse.
You again?
My name is Jimmy Onishi.
This time...
I'm hoping to win.
What's this?
Oh, no!
The time is ripe.
AFTER A TWO-SEASON ABSENCE
I kicked him out for a while.
I had to impose
an economic sanction on him.
ECONOMIC SANCTION
I didn't think it was a good idea
to let him keep coming back.
I was afraid he may succeed
in creating a nuclear weapon.
HE MAY CREATE A NUCLEAR WEAPON
NATURAL-BORN NUCLEAR FUSION
In my mind, Cookie and Jimmy
come with a "Do Not Mix" warning.
WHEN COOKIE'S IN,
JIMMY STAYS OUT
They're like Nodong and Taepodong.
NODONG AND TAEPODONG
They're the two lethal weapons
of this show.
It'd be dangerous
to bring them in too often.
After the second appearance,
other comedians told me I was funny...
quite a lot.
A SOLID RESPONSE
HE EVEN MAKES HIMSELF LAUGH
I'm Hideko from Uguisudani.
What did you say?
I'm Hideko, from Uguisudani.
The infamous Tokyo town?
You stopped sounding Osakan.
So far I've lost two million yen.
Yoshimoto Finance won't
lend to me anymore.
NOT EVEN YOSHIMOTO
WILL GIVE HIM A LOAN
If I lose again,
I'm a genna... gotta...
It means I'll be working for free
for the next six months.
How pathetic is that? For this one try.
DOCUMENTAL'S SADDEST STORY
-I won't laugh.
-What should I do?
-Two, four, five... Ten?
-Everyone's here.
-All ten of us.
-What should I do?
Tamura and Zakoshi boost my chances.
Shut up. You keep saying--
-This feels weird.
-Yeah.
What is this?
Maybe it's because
we always get together like this.
It's like we're in a dressing room.
I didn't expect Junior to come.
Good morning.
Why this lineup?
What is this?
Jimmy, why did you...
Is that your "neutral" position?
Is that where you start?
This is where I start.
-Where do you go from there?
-Exactly.
He's definitely wasted one.
-He's already started.
-You've already shown a hand.
You don't mind?
It's okay. I start here.
We've already seen it.
-It's okay.
-We're growing used to you.
This... This has nothing to do
with my jokes.
Nothing?
-This is your blank canvas.
-It is.
It's your base character?
Now, everyone.
You don't need to hear
the rules anymore, right?
Everyone brings one million yen.
The last one standing will win 10 million.
-Yes.
-Good so far?
If you laugh,
there are yellow, orange, and red cards.
A red card means you're eliminated.
We've been changing the rules a bit
each season.
1 - IF ALL PLAYERS LAUGH AT ZOMBIES
THERE IS A NO-CONTEST
2- ZOMBIES MAY ATTACK LAST PLAYER
UNTIL 6 HOURS ARE UP
As you already know,
this time you can bring a Helper.
The Helpers will appear from here.
And you can use them once as your weapon.
However, it will be a problem
if the Helper sticks around for hours.
So they can only stay here
for a few minutes.
And since everyone has brought
one million yen, I have too.
Thank you.
I'll rip it open...
Like some kind of fast-food chicken.
Keeps your hand clean.
-Your hand stays clean.
-It won't get dirty.
It's clean money.
I see.
Now, please pass the money to the front.
Here it is.
You each bring different sentiments...
This one million yen
is filled with a lot of emotions.
Some have brought a loose pile
but I'm going to trust you.
Is this 10 million?
-Maybe cash does beat virtual currency.
-This is very real money.
This is different from getting money
from an ATM.
This is 10 million.
This goes here.
-10 million.
-Exactly.
And this makes it 11 million yen.
Of course,
the amount you paid is subtracted,
so the winner wins 10 million as a prize.
However, since there are circumstances
that concern the grown-ups,
we must switch that pile with this one,
or we'll be in trouble.
This is it?
Like money laundering?
Money laundering...
There's something, apparently.
There are some complicated rules.
Yamauchi, are you okay?
I'm fine.
You don't seem fine.
Do you see something
that makes you concerned?
It's just, you got quiet.
I left Osaka at about 8:00 and stayed
in the dressing room for a long time.
I'm feeling a bit tired.
You came from Osaka?
Yes, from Osaka.
Mr. Matsumoto.
My natural, normal face looks like...
Like you're smiling, right?
Well, to a certain degree...
How can I put it?
It's a bit tricky.
-He's smiling now, right?
-This is considered smiling?
Try to look a little more formidable
than usual.
Formidable?
He does tend to smirk when he talks.
He's making an excuse for later.
Just try to look a little stern.
Is this face okay?
That's smiling.
Okay!
I'm going to base my judgment on
whether it's your normal face or not.
-But I--
-I always get criticism.
Fujimoto's not here today,
but they say I go easy on him.
But you know, we're all playing as a team.
After all, this is a TV show.
Leave the judgment to me. I'll handle it.
-I see.
-You okay, Jimmy?
My hands got stuck on the bullet train.
-My hands.
-Why?
-They got stuck on the bullet train.
-Stuck where?
In the door.
-The door of a bullet train?
-The bullet train door.
-In between the doors?
-Yeah.
They did. Look. So...
-That's why they're red?
-Yes.
Why say that now?
So you rode the train like that?
I rode like this.
They were outside, right?
Your fingers were outside?
From around Hamamatsu.
-Why did the door open there?
-It doesn't stop there.
Why did they open at Hamamatsu?
Why did you tell that funny story now?
Why did you get close to the doors
at Hamamatsu?
I wanted to buy an eel bento box.
He gave a normal reason.
-A kiosk was right outside the doors--
-He's still going.
He just keeps talking.
-Then the door slammed?
-It slammed shut.
I would have laughed
if he'd said it during the game.
-Why did he say that now?
-No way. I'm in trouble.
-Until Tokyo Station?
-Tokyo...
No, it opened at Shin-Yokohama.
I was so relieved.
But my hands ended up like this.
-Why waste that bit?
-That was close!
The game starts
when the lights in the room change.
Have a great time.
-You're free until then.
-We can still laugh?
No way.
Do your best.
-How long do we have?
-No way.
What do we do with our bags?
We can put them away.
No way.
-I'll put my bag away.
-Me too.
Can we go now?
We can put our bags away?
Season 5!
Starts now.
-It's already been 20-30 minutes, right?
-It has.
-Since we came in.
-Right.
I was first.
It's started, right?
-It has.
-This is how it starts?
-Are you going to do something?
-No, no.
I'm just thirsty.
-What?
-I'm thirsty.
He's drinking it.
He emptied it.
-What did he drink?
-Mouthwash.
-Are you okay?
-Without diluting it?
-That's medical gargle.
-Medical gargle.
-You have to spit it out.
-It smells terrible!
-That stinks.
-That's not good, Jimmy.
I was just thirsty.
That's why you drank it?
Your throat will burn.
The smell is overwhelming.
-It stinks!
-Yeah, really.
Hang on.
There was something else in there, right?
No, this smells like
the real one. Seriously.
Are you stupid?
But it doesn't say you can't drink it.
So it's okay to drink?
But it could be bad.
Well, maybe you can drink it...
But it can't be good.
Of course not!
You usually dilute it.
I don't feel good.
-You don't?
-Of course you don't.
-What's it like?
-Says do not use except for gargling.
I'm hot!
Your throat is burning!
My chest is burning.
That's not good.
Is it burning badly?
My chest is burning.
You should dilute it.
-You should drink some water.
-I'll drink water. I don't feel good.
-What are you doing?
-Not good.
How about swallowing an egg?
An egg sounds good.
Dilute it with this.
An egg...
-Because it creates a film?
-Yeah. So...
Sit down, look up and open your mouth.
It could be bad.
Are you ready?
Like this.
Let's dilute it.
How do you feel?
I think it's diluted a little.
-He's shaking.
-Why are you shaking?
From carbonic acid.
Junior and Takahashi came close.
One more?
Swallowing too much could be dangerous.
How can you just swallow it?
-I'm atopic.
-What?
Kano is too. Right?
-Are you allergic to eggs?
-No.
I'm atopic.
Kano is allergic to a lot of things.
What?
Allergies. What do you have again?
What are you allergic to?
Soy beans, pollen,
dogs, cats, house dust,
and my own sweat.
-Sweat...
-Your own sweat?
That's tough.
I'm allergic to sweat.
-You get itchy when you sweat.
-I get a bad heat rash.
-So, you want one of these?
-No, thank you.
-Why don't you have one?
-Yeah, why not?
Me?
Can you eat raw eggs?
I'm not allergic to eggs.
What is this? What are you doing?
Treatment!
Is this a treatment?
But he's not sick.
-What?
-See that?
-I was fine.
Me?
Tamura, what about your sunglasses?
Yeah. That's cheating!
You said you'd take them off.
Are you smiling?
I'm not.
Look at Zakoshi.
Look at him.
Come on.
I can stand it.
Better take them off.
-It's hard to tell.
-You're right.
Then I'll go change.
This is uncomfortable.
Okay.
Right?
This isn't funny anymore, right?
What do you mean, "anymore"?
-It's not funny anymore.
-Anymore?
I'll go change.
We may laugh if you do a real "Cha"
in that outfit.
-With full force.
-A serious one.
Cha.
-Nope.
-You're right. It won't work anymore.
-It was quieter than expected.
-Yeah.
-Was that it?
-Real one is quiet.
Everyone thinks the real one is loud.
It's full of melancholy.
-How's showbiz version?
-The live show version.
Your "Entertainment Cha."
Cha.
Like that.
-How about by a lazy river?
-By a lazy river?
There's a lot of background noise.
Cha!
That was a scream.
Junior...
-At the Rising Sun Rock Festival.
-Junior.
I hate oogiri games.
It's not oogiri.
It sounds like oogiri when you say it.
No, thank you.
Junior...
He's losing it.
That wasn't oogiri.
-But it sounds a lot like oogiri.
-The way he set it up, right?
But you change your "Cha" according
to the place and occasion, right?
I do. But when you start digging deeper,
it starts to become an oogiri game.
-Don't say that.
-You make me shrink up.
If you accuse me of that,
I can't say a thing.
Say something, Eikoh.
You shouldn't run away
from any challenges in this place.
If someone challenges you,
you have to give 100%.
Eikoh will do his joke, too.
By a lazy river.
A lazy river?
Everyone, listen up!
Ramen, tsukemen
and sexy men like me! Okay!
He was just loud.
That sweeping hand movement was great.
Because the people float by?
His voice carries well.
The version you do when your dog dies.
See, it's oogiri.
When my dog dies?
Thank you.
Ramen, tsukemen and sexy men like me.
Okay!
It's not okay. The dog's dead.
But "Okay!" is part of the joke.
You did good.
Very good.
I'll give them a warning about that later.
That really could be bad.
It was a mistake.
Yes, it was.
I shouldn't have done it. I know now.
I put my body on the line.
You may get sick.
Is this really okay?
Try to swallow just a little.
No, it clearly says
"Do not use except for gargling."
But I'm sure my stomach got disinfected.
I guess so.
Zakoshi, I heard you had twins?
I have twins.
What are their names?
Hanma and Kanma.
-Bullshit.
-It's true.
Which kanji are used for "Hanma"?
The kanji for "half" and then "demon."
You could never use that.
And "Kanma"?
"Complete" and "demon."
Hanma and Kanma.
Calling your kid "demon" was a problem
a while back.
It's a girl.
They're twin girls?
A boy and a girl.
Which is which?
Hanma is.
A boy-girl.
You mean Kanma is a "boy-girl."
And Kanma is a girl-boy.
What if you have another?
They'll be Anbaran and Denderen.
-Anbaran and Denderen?
-Anbaran and Denderen.
If you have another set of twins?
Junior's out, right?
-Anbaran and...
-Anbaran and Kanbaran.
Anbaran and Kanbaran.
What about Denderen?
Denderen too... They're triplets.
If I have triplets, they'll be
Anbaran, Kanbaran, and Denderen.
If it's quadruplets, I'll add Dondoron.
Their names are Mai and Ami.
No, no, no.
-Mai and Ami?
-No, no.
-Those are normal, cute names.
And they're both girls?
-Are they really twins?
-No, no, no.
They're Headhunter A and Headhunter B.
That’s what those twin pro wrestlers
from W*ING were called.
How knowledgeable of you.
No, they're not. It's Miki? Mai? And?
-Miki and Tetsuya.
-Mai and Ami.
He's "Hollywood," so they're "Miami."
That's super normal.
-That's why?
-No, no.
He's wrong. They're Miki and Tetsuya.
Miki and Tetsuya.
-That's "Tetsuya Miki."
-Tetsuya Miki.
Tetsuya Miki.
-The "Doo-waa" guy?
-Right.
"It's me!"
The "It's Me Polka."
It's me!
"An over-exaggerated..." Shall I do it?
-"An over-exaggerated Tetsuya."
-Go for it.
That would've gotten me.
How about Junichiro Koizumi?
"An over-exaggerated Junichiro Koizumi."
Hello.
I'm Junichiro Koizumi.
Junior...
You set it up!
-You came close so many times.
-Me?
That was close!
He set it up himself.
Was it me?
You smiled a few times, Junior.
That was close!
Well, this is...
First of all, this applies to everyone.
You're drinking too much water.
The moment someone says something,
you bring a bottle to your mouth.
You hide by pouting your lips.
That's not good.
It's okay if you really are thirsty.
But let's not hold a bottle
to your mouth all the time.
And for now, there's one person to punish.
Junior.
-You scared me!
-This is scary.
I thought it might be me!
Hello.
I'm Junichiro Koizumi.
Junior...
Basically, you were smiling at everything!
Junior is bombing!
And each time, he tried to hide it
with the water bottle!
No, no.
Zakoshi is dangerous!
-Zakoshi is dangerous.
-He's my weak spot.
That was too much.
I admire everyone for holding back.
His power was amazing.
Takahashi, you're close too.
Takahashi and Junior
are always on the brink.
Zakoshi's my weak spot. Okay!
I wanted to put you all on your toes.
That's why I gave Junior...
I see.
...a yellow card.
Now, let's continue.
We're okay now?
That was fast!
It was.
You set it up yourself.
You kept setting up
your favorite kind of jokes.
I thought if I created the mood,
it would start to catch on.
Ouch!
Give me a break.
I'm half Japanese.
-That made me jump!
-Be careful, Golgo!
What's he doing?