Well, yes, I did simulations
In conclusion, I want to win in quantity, it may be boring and lame, but I want to win in terms of quantity
I'm Marin with the best pussy in Kitakyushu
The atmosphere there is really unique
You have no idea what's interesting anymore
Or what's not interesting as well
It's gonna come out as a bird
You're saying the wrong joke all the time
In regard to setting the mood, I bet Matsumoto-san is thinking "Fujimon, this dude is doing a fantastic job!"
He didn't say that to me though
He didn't, but I bet so, I bet he's thinking about it
Ahh, it's soda water?
Oh, so it's soda water
Yellow card, Jimmy   -Yes
"Sometimes it's sunny, Takajin"
"Be a little rough, Blue jeans"
Why are you looking this way, dude
Orange card!   -Eh?!
Eh? Orange all of sudden?   -Yes, orange
It hurts! My nose hurts!
You bastard...Fujimori...
I shouldn't have listened to you
You're out!   -Number one
The number one...
I really wanted to watch soda water (in his nose)
You want to watch it too, right?
(Yeah, really wanted to watch soda water)
(But that wasn't possible, due to the timing)
Let's start
Does anybody need a towel?
A towel?
I don't need a towel
Is there anything for me to wipe then?
Something to wipe?...
Eh?
Just wipe the oven then
The oven
The oven?   -Yes
Wipe the oven? Got it
Like this?
That's the stove
It started already?   -Yes
Which one is the oven?
The oven?
The oven? Is there an oven in here?
What happened to you?
(The way she's talking...)
People are going to see your nipples
You're looking at my nipples, right?
No, I'm not though...
He definitely looked at my nipples, right?
He said "people are going to see your nipples"...
There's a tape sticking to your barefoot too
(Tomochika and Yuriyan started an improvised performance as a Geisha, which involves traditional Japanese dance and uses gesture to tell a story)
(This is amazing)
"The phone rings"
"I'm not going to say 'Hello' though"
"Clean up the room, clean up the room"
"I have to clean up the room"
"My job is to clean up the room"
We can clearly see it
"People can clearly see it"
It's completely exposed
"Please hide it for me, please"
Jinnai, please hide it for her
Please hide it for her, Jinnai   -Please face the reality
Please hide it for her, she's a girl too, so please
He's at a loss
We can see it, clearly
Jinnai, fix it for her   -It looks like a mic
Jinnai, please fix it for her   -Your nipple is synchronized with the mic
But it's gonna be a problem if I touch it
Please use this to show her that it's exposed
The whole tip is exposed
Well done for holding on
(Incredible)
(That's tough)
(It's interesting, it's really interesting)
(What's going on?)
(Fujimon is very close, very very close)
"Should I go this way?"
"Nope, I'll go this way and turn around"
That was so close
Come on, stop it! I hate this!
I don't want this anymore! Please!
Come on, no more, please!
That was so interesting, what was that?
That's really interesting
That was so interesting
That was interesting
That's tough
We watched it in the studio, and still, it was so interesting
Her role as the master is really pissing me off
It seems like it's going to end for once, but then...
They were targeting Jinnai
It's dirty to target one person
Let's take a look
Actually, Fujimon is already...
He's already laughing   -Yeah, he's kind of laughing
That shouldn't be allowed, but...
"Should I go this way?"
"Nope, I'll go this way and turn around"
Come on, I saw a huge, huge butt coming to me
I see
Her collaboration with the master is really pissing me off
Jinnai already got a yellow card
I actually can't decide this
No, no please, brother, it's orange
Umm...   -Please, give me one more chance
Well, it wasn't took clearly...
Please, please...   -Umm...
Okay, orange then...   -Thank god
And Fujimon, seriously...
That crying face is unforgivable too   -Not even a crying face?
No, not that face
That's already like 80 or 90 percent laughing
So that's not acceptable
Okay, so crying faces are not allowed too
Yes, please keep that in mind
I don't want that anymore
So both of them scored points for that
Hooray!
Go get changed, dude!
Go get changed, and don't look this way!
Stop it, honestly, please stop it
That was so close
If Jinnai didn't laugh for another 10 seconds, I bet I'll be the one laughing
That's enough, honestly, that's enough
Let's start
Damn it
I'll take Fujimon for the next one
I told you to go get changed
Why are they coming in turns?
Excuse me, I heard that we can try dance lessons here?
It's not here
(She's being really aggressive here)
It's over there
(She's being really aggressive)
I heard that we can try dance lessons here?
It's probably next door
I think you got it wrong
Kamei Shizuka-san? (former Japanese politician)
*Haruna is always being teased about looking like male celebrities, and it has become a routine gag for her to reply with "No, I'm freaking not!"
No, I'm Iwaki Nobuko (another Japanese politician)
I think I heard some noise like "Ching Tong Chang" just now
It's next door
I'm passionate and energetic, I'm Iwaki Nobuko (the title of Iwaki's book)
You're not wearing pink today, huh?
*Iwaki Nobuko is known for her pink suits
Yes, I changed it, because I lost the election
And you changed it to green?   -Yes
I heard "Ching Tong Chang" just now...
It's from the room next door
Not from here
(Very interesting)
"I have no idea why am I here"
"But I want to say thanks to my parents"
"I'm glad that I was born in this world"
"Say this to your parents"
"Say thank you to your parents"
"The girls army is coming to you!"
"You know what I'm talking about, right? Hey, Jinnai?"
(What's going on?)
(This is hilarious)
(Huh?)
(Should this be counted?)
(Fujimon...)
"Where are you going?"
"I will not give up on you"
I hate this! Come on!
Come on!!!
I feel pity for Jinnai
That's dirty!
Why did that dude come out again along with "Papa-ra-pa"?
This is cruel   -Very cruel
They're completely targeting you
This is too dirty
Well, maybe that's their strategy to take you guys down one by one
Let's take a look
"I will not give up on you"
(The tune changed here)
Come on, that dude is just...they even changed the tune
Yeah, they changed the tune
No one expected that
Oh, come on...
Are you out?
Yes, I am...
Jinnai, you're out!
Ahh, really?
What was that "Papa-ra-pa"? Come on...
Let's go
The girls are strong
The girls are really strong   -Yes, they are
I'm so frustrated
You didn't make it this time, again
Yeah, I didn't make it
Well, I think I've entered the "zone"
I laughed at Yuriyan's dance for once
And while I'm still thinking "I mustn't laugh at that this time", here comes another dancer Haruna
"I have no idea why am I here"
"But I want to say thanks to my parents"
I just have to say, I've entered the "zone"
With Tomochika changing the tune and Yuriyan appearing just in time
I feel like it's a perfect stage prepared for me
And I just laughed naturally
Come on, please go get changed...
(So Tomochika is scoring a lot of points for this)
(Tomochika is really strong, right?)
It's almost like we've prepared it beforehand   -Exactly
Okay, let's start
I would have laughed if Jinnai wasn't here
Please go get changed, come on...
He's right
Please...
Shoji-san is making something
What are you making?
Well, I'm not actually making it
(Here it comes)
(Shoji-san's favorite gag)
(Shoji-san really likes this)
It's impossible to be a Talento forever, right?
So that's how you make it
What are you making?
Eh?
The head of a frog
So it's not a food?
It's not a food?
Yes, it is a food
What do you mean by the head of a frog then?
That's a joke
That's just a joke
Yes, that's just a joke
It's impossible to stay in the Owarai world forever, right?
Seriously, what are you making?
It's an experiment!
In case I lost my job and become unemployed
Never think that you can be a Talento forever, that's gonna hit you hard
How many times are you saying that?
Never think that you can always...
Let me say it 4 more times!...
Never think that they'll always be here, your parents and money
Well, of course
Anyway...
Can you go get changed?
Go get changed
But that's her style
I have pride in this
She has pride in that...
What are you going to do with this?
Where are you going?   -Please wait a second
It's really cool to do that, like she's putting on some hair gel
Like Aladdin
Amazing, that's a beautiful Fuji forehead (widow’s peak)
Yeah, it is
Fuji forehead A, Fuji forehead B, Fuji forehead C, Fuji forehead D
Yeah, exactly
Fuji forehead A
Umm...may I...umm...
Yes?
Umm...I stink, so...
I smell like sesame oil
How come?
Well, I smell like sesame oil
Did you use sesame oil?
Yeah, sesame oil
Of course you'll smell like sesame oil, if you're bringing sesame oil with you
Yeah, you're right
I like the smell of sesame oil
Oh, you like it?   -Yes
That's it?
That's it
With just that?
With just that
Yes
Is he the villain?
He's the villain
If you have the power, please stand up and save Japan
Please!
Here I go!
Checkmate!
Why don't you fight back?
Brigham Young once said...
"I have to save Japan"
"Although this has never been proven in history"
"However, well-known people usually think like this"
"Never walk backwards"
"Live with no regrets"
"And the most important thing that I always keep in my mind is..."
"To have a dream"
"You have a chance too"
"If the children are going to save the world in the future"
"Then you shall save the world now"
"You are trying to escape"
"You are just trying to escape from here"
"You are trying to escape from the family"
How could this be allowed? This is too dirty!
Are you okay?
That's ridiculous
They came to take me down together
But Jimmy-san, that's not acceptable
Don't try to hide your face
I really didn't want to laugh, they're pissing me off
It's unacceptable to hide your face in the refrigerator anyway
You're just hiding your face
These gals are really pissing me off
Yeah, Tomochika is so mean
She's so mean   -Very mean
She's scoring so many points
She's so mean, seriously
Without getting her hands dirty
Pulling strings behind the scene, what a terrifying women!
"You are trying to escape"
(Actually, Jimmy is already laughing here)
(This is not acceptable)
"You are trying to escape"
"You are just trying to escape from here"
"You are trying to escape from the family"
You collapsed on the floor!
I tried so hard to hold back this time and I came this far
Why me? Why are they targeting me?
Well, you only got a yellow card and you tried to hold back, so I'll give you an orange card
Orange   -Orange
That was awful
I don't want these girls to be here
They're working together as a team
Please stop collaborating, come on
Not sure if that should be prohibited though
Well then, Fujimon, you can collaborate with Jimmy too
Even if we two collaborate, probably nothing good will come out of it
Well, that's hard to tell
What happened?
Please hide it
It's gonna pinch your breasts
Yeah, my breasts...
Do you play guitar?
Yes
You laughed just now, right?
Nope...
I didn't laugh...
Oh, is it?
Oh, is it
Nope, I didn't laugh
(They're nasty!)
(Fujimon have no choice but to join them)
Perfect timing
Hey! Come on!
No...no...
I'm just knocking it like this...that's it...
Excuse me
Who are you?
You mean me?
Infinite testicles syndrome
He bursted into laughter?
"Ta-hahaha"?
I didn't expect that!
What happened?   -No idea at all
His testicles got me
You weren't even looking at him
You only heard it
"Ta-ha-ha"
He was laughing so loud that I didn't understand what's going on at first
He was laughing so loud that I thought he's not laughing
"Ta-ha-ha"
It's almost like he's actually not laughing
As if that's actually legit
Who are you?
You mean me?
(He tried to escape and went that way, because he knows he's going to laugh)
Infinite testicles syndrome
He bursted into laughter
So, Jimmy
You're out
That's the loudest laugh in Documental history
"Ta-hahaha"
Infinite testicles syndrome
Infinite testicles syndrome got me
That's a syndrome though   -Yeah, a syndrome...
I didn't expect Tomochika and the girls army to work so well together
The arrogant and outrageous Kasae at the roadside
That's so long
I'm Marin with the best pussy in Kitakyushu
And I'm actually really weak at dirty jokes
I won't laugh at testicles, but that infinite syndrome was just...
Infinite testicles syndrome
How much did you pay so far?
4 million now, and seriously...
Please forgive me if I'm on the news tomorrow
Let's start
You're so beautiful
No, please don't say that
That's not good
You're beautiful
Please don't seduce me
I do not belong to anyone
How many days a week do you work here?
About 5 days a week
You're beautiful
Please leave me alone
My husband will be jealous
How long have you two been married?
It's a second marriage for both of us, so...
Well, 4 years now
It's embarrassing to talk about my age, but...
My kids can take care of themselves now
And they said to me "Mom, feel free to start a second life"
And that's when I met him
Meisa?
He's your son?
Yes, he's my son
Your mom is really beautiful
Very beautiful, very sexy
Is it here?
What do you mean?
Bee complaints
Bee?
Oh, so you're a bee exterminator?
Yes, because someone contacted me
But although your face is being protected...
-Your arms are completely exposed
-That's too dangerous, what if it stings you?
I'm always being stung
Is it fine?
It's dangerous if you got stung two times in a row, right?
But I have im...imm...immunity to it
Mei-eki?   -Immunity (men-eki)
*Immunity (men-eki) and Nagoya station (mei-eki) sounds similar
You mean the Nagoya station?
That's Mei-eki
He was like "ha-hum"
Very naturally
No, no, no
You said "ha-hum"
Did I?
Of course you did
That's just the sound of my breath
But you never breathed like that before
Yes, exactly, that's it
So you did laugh, right?
I heard him saying "Hum-hum-hum"
Yes, he did   -He was like "Hum-hum-hum"
No, that's really just the sound of my breath
No, no, no   -Let's take a look
But I have im...imm...immunity to it
Mei-eki?   -Immunity (men-eki)
*Immunity (men-eki) and Nagoya station (mei-eki) sounds similar
You mean the Nagoya station?
That's Mei-eki
Huh?   -What was that?
What was that?
This is so difficult to judge
What was that?   -Yeah, what was that sound?
To be honest, I was just thinking "Um-hum, that was quite interesting"
So you're laughing?
No, I'm not laughing
I'll be a bit harsh for this one
Yeah, he did actually laugh
Yellow
My first card
It's difficult to judge Tomochika too
She laughed during her performance as another character
How should that be judged?
Haruna, you laughed as well, right?
Even when you're performing, if you go too far, I'll count it as laughing too
In regard to this, I actually laughed during my performance too
So honest   -Very honest
You're so honest
I ordered food delivery just now
So tiny
That's too tiny
This should be enough for 3 people
No way, that's not for 3 people
Octopus, shrimp, sea urchin
Oh, no it's not
Octopus, shrimp...
Nope, it's shrimp, sea urchin, Shikoku*
*The shape of the Octopus sushi looks similar to the Shikoku island
The island of Shikoku, the island of liveliness
Ise-shi has a lot of visitors because of the seaport in Tsu-shi. Tsu-shi is prosperous because of the Grand Shrine in Ise-shi.
*This is a folk song popular during the Edo period, which praises the Nagoya Castle
And we Owari Nagoya has the Nagoya Castle
Eat nothing and drink nothing when you arrive Numazu*
*The original phrase is to hold back and "Eat nothing and drink nothing before you arrive Numazu"
Tsume has no Tsume, yet Uri has Tsume
*This is a phrase used to memorize the difference between two similar Kanji, Tsume (爪) and Uri (瓜)
That's how you write it in Kanji
When the mountain smiles, the rivers will disappear
Is it true or is it just superstition?
Is it superstition? (Mei Shin ka)
Shin Ka Mei
The Meishin Expressway is now congested with traffic for 50km
Ahh...so slow...
Who are you?
Excuse me
Will I see you again?
Who knows?
When will you come next time?
I'll come whenever I want to come
That is my choice
Why are you always so capricious?
I'm capricious?
Well, that's because...
A capricious journey
That start of a love story
And when I open my eyes
It's you!
When will you be here next time?
Please don't escape from love
(Uh-oh?)
You won't be able to escape!
(He got caught)
Jenny, who gets lonely easily
Come on! Come on!
Jenny got it! Jenny got it!
First Fuji, second hawk, third eggplant
*This is a phrase used to describe that it is considered to be good luck to dream of Mount Fuji, a hawk, and an eggplant in the first dream one has in the new year
Inside that helmet...
There's a quail egg in it
Really?
Oh no!
(Someone laughed?)
(Who laughed?)
Oh my god!
(Tomochika laughed)
She saved me!
That was like hell
That's so rare
Self-destruction?
That's not like you
What was so funny?
Actually, whenever these two people sing and dance, I'm trying so hard to hold back my laughter
Really? You were holding back?   -Yes
I paid full attention to Fujimon only
Yeah, you should, that was like hell   -Yes, it was hell
What the hell did you gals do to me?
And the other guys are not coming out at all
Yeah, those two guys   -They are so mean
It was like a cheap musical
Let's take a look, that really surprised me
(What is she even trying to do?)
(She completely laughed)
This might be a bit harsh to Tomochika, but...
I'll give her an orange card straight away
But Tomochika scored many points
I see
How many times did you gals perform those musicals? Come on!
Seriously, those musical theaters...
Because these two girls are always starting it
The guys are not coming out at all   -Yeah, they're not coming out!
That's no good, I'll give you a penalty if you stay inside for too long
Yes, please tell them about this
Why are you coming right to me?
What was that "dog-dog-dog"?
What's going on?
Let's start
Maeda really likes sunglasses, huh?
Hello everybody
Don't mind me
You catch my eye though
We're curious about you
No, please don't mind me
Well, of course we'll be curious
Please don't mind me
So curious...
No, excuse me
I'm just a single father passing by here
Are you milking?
Yes, I have to extract milk
It's not gonna come out, not for man   -It's coming out though
No way, it won't
Quite a lot came out though
Yeah, it's coming out
So it's father's milk, not mother's milk
Yes
Father's milk (Fu-nyuu)
Fu-nyuu   -Ha-nyuu?
Funyu Yuzuru   -Yes, Funyu Yuzuru
*Hanyu Yuzuru is a famous Japanese figure skater
No, it's Hanyu
(That's preposterous)
I'm back
I'm Funyu Yuzuru
It's Hanyu   -The ring is...
You saw it, right?
No, we didn't
It's exposed
What's exposed?
Your nipples are exposed
"Your nipples are exposed"
"My nipples are nearly exposed"
"My nipples are completely exposed"
"Boobs, boobs, boobs..."
"Here a boob, there a boob"
"When I'm sleeping, when I'm awake, it's all about boobs"
"So glad to be born as boobs"
You didn't get it right
(Fujimon?)
Dodosuko?*
*"Dodosuko-suko-suko...I love you" is a gag by Tanoshingo
Dodosuko-suko-suko, Dodosuko-suko-suko...
I love you
I want to eat picked eggplant
Dodosuko-suko-suko, Dodosuko-suko-suko...
My molars are gone and disappeared
And then I found it on the floor
Aren't you laughing?
You're laughing, right?
Eww, his nose hairs are sticking out
You're not Dave!
Who are you?
This uncle is so strange!
What are you doing here?
Don't talk to me like that
Yes, you're right
I'm Henna Ojisan*
*"Henna Ojisan", which literally means strange uncle, is a famous character created by Shimura Ken
I'm Henna Ojisan, so I'm Henna Ojisan
He's Henna Ojisan, so he's Henna Ojisan
She's Henna Obasan, so she's Henna Obasan (strange auntie)
She's Henna Obasan, so she's Henna Obasan
Can clearly see her nipples
This guy touched the side of my breasts
This uncle is so strange!
Get out of here!
Yes, you're right
I'm Henna Ojisan
I'm Henna Ojisan, so I'm Henna Ojisan
(That's barren)
(It's interesting though)
Where are you going?
She's double eyelid now
She's single eyelid before
So cute   -She's looking sharp
Thank you
Oh, Shoji-san too
Shoji-san too
She's imitating someone...
Mori Shinichi-san? (Enka singer and composer)
My Dear Paper Bag (Kami-hukuro)
*The original phrase is "My Dear Mother" (Ohukuro-san), a famous song by Mori Shinichi, which sounds similar to paper bag (Kami-hukuro)
It should be My Dear Mother (Ohukuro-san)
My Dear Twisted Bag (Neji-hukuro)
Twisted bag?   -It's My Dear Mother (Ohukuro-san)
My Dear Little Pouch (Ko-hukuro)
It should be My Dear Mother (Ohukuro-san)
My Dear Paper Bag (Kami-hukuro)
Someone said that already
Someone said that?
I didn't hear that
She clearly said it though
Okay, so are the zombies ready?
What should we do?
Ahh, I'm not really confident about it
Well, I did prepare a gag though
Let's go for the zombies?
Okay, let's go
Zombie time
Hello everybody   -Hello
Hello, he's Mr Jimmy   -I'm Jimmy
Mr Jimmy?   -Yes
You are Mr Jimmy right?   -Yes
Please listen to Mr Jimmy's erotic Shigin*
*Shigin is a performance of reciting a Japanese poem
If you met me and saw me at the station
If someone saw you?
I feel like I can get a girl today
Make her pregnant
Say "I bet there will be"
*The well known erotic Shigin comedian, Kimura Takuhiro, always ends his performance with "I bet there will be..."
I bet there will be...
Not here, dude!
You have to say "I bet there will be"
I bet there will...
Not here, dude!
Say "I bet there will be" at the end
Excuse me, please listen to Mr Jimmy's erotic Shigin
Going with girls...   -Going with girls?
To the love hotel   -To the love hotel?
I bet there will be condoms
Of course there will, dude!
Of course the hotel will have condoms, Jimmy!
Please do the erotic Shigin properly!   -Yes
That was terrible   -Yes
Here comes Jimmy's flag raising corner!
Please do it, Jimmy-chan   -Yes
Raise the red one
Lower the red one
Don't raise the red one, then raise the red one
Raise the red one
Lower the red one
Lower the red...   -It's all about the red one, dude!
So hot
No it's not hot
It's all about the red one, dude!
Here comes the "Guess what is Jimmy saying?" corner
So many varieties
So please guess what's Jimmy saying
Okay, I see, so what is he saying?
Pee-po, Pee-po, Pee
That's just the sound
Why? Why?
Exactly, exactly
So Jimmy, what's the correct answer?
Jingisukan
Completely different, dude!
So hot
No it's not hot
Why are you feeling hot? And the pronunciation of Jingisukan is completely different from Pee-po, Pee-po!
Here comes the "Guess what is Jimmy singing?" corner
Please do it, Jimmy-chan
Okay, so what is Jimmy singing?
Fight, fight
Hachiro, Hachiro
I am Hachiro
It should be a song though
That was interesting, huh? Jimmy-chan?
That was so funny
Yeah, that was funny
So Jimmy-chan, what's the correct answer?
Belly button, belly button, belly button
What the heck was that!
So hot   -No it's not hot
Why the heck are you feeling hot for this?
There's no such song as "Belly button, belly button", right?
So lastly, let's end with Jimmy's erotic Shigin   -Yes
So please do it, Jimmy-chan
Tomorrow, I will order a delivery health (call girl)
And I bet I will be paying 23,000 yen
So you're really going to call a girl, huh?!
So hot
No it's not hot
He said it for me
You really got him with that
Let's go?   -Let's go
Let's go   -Yes
Let's go   -Let's go
This is getting serious
46 more minutes