What is the most difficult part about Documental?
Well, umm...
They become out of the loop
Well...
Of course, this is nothing like being on stage, there's no audiences and no laughters
For comedians, having no laughter is like having no lighthouse
Kawashima-san that's no good
That's no good Ku-chan
Feeling like "where am I heading?"
And they may feel anxious from time to time
But the reverse is also true
While there's no laughter, they may think that this part is hilarious and try to elaborate further
Just to find out it was not interesting at all afterwards
It's me, it's me, Hamburger!
So I've prepared...
What the heck is Pengin Shokudo nara?
Pengin Shokudo
There's throwable Shumai too
Young actors be like "How are you doing buddy"
Between you two?
You mean Fujimon-san?
Who do you mean?
You mean me?
Who?
What happened?
Wait a second...
Why are you covering your mouth like that?
Ah, a lot came out
Is Kurosawa-san laughing?
Oh, come on, you're so drunk again
Oh, don't fall asleep here
Wow, orange...
The nipples beam cross section is in heart shape
Ah, straddle
Ah, ah, straddle, straddle
Well, maybe yellow...
Are these words...
Ka-ha!
Ka-ha?
Wait a second...
-You're just one step away, you'll be out next time
-Yes, I understand
Is he angry about this?
I have no idea
He didn't say anything to me
That's just because Daisuke-shisho didn't know he was being fooled
-But I bet you put a lot of effort
-Yeah, it's amazing
Yeah, it took me a lot of time
-Did you make this with computer?
-Yes
I need to crop the photo first, and then merge it again
-He was squeezed in this photo right?
-Yes
Close up view...
SHA-SHA-SHAAA
SHA-SHA
Why are you screaming like Gamera
SHA-SHA-SHA
The close up view was good
By the way, I've brought some new smartphone cases as well
Smartphone case?
Please help me pick one
Wait a second, Nishizawa's smartphone case?
This is scary
This is it
It's translucent, we can see it already...
-Huh, did you laugh?
-No, I didn't
No, he's not dead yet
-He's Yoshio-shisho
-Yes
Who is that?
-He's Obitani-san
-Ah, he's Pot (his nickname)
This is amazing
-So Yoshimoto is selling these?
-Yeah...
*The people on the smartphone cases are all employed by Yoshimoto
-Yoshimoto is even selling Obitani-san?
-Well...
That's amazing
-No one will buy Obitani-san
-But that regent haircut is freaking cool
It's Obitani-san
-From a different time
-Eh, is this Obitani-san?
He looks like BayStars' Miura Daisuke from this angle
-Ah, yeah you're right
-Especially his hairstyle
-But it's from a different time right?
-Yeah, his glasses are different
Shinpuruosan-shisho
-Those tiny teeth look good right?
-That's not the main point dude
Sakata-shisho
I can't make up my mind what to choose
Is he wearing a restaurant napkin?
Sakata-shisho...
That's impolite
The elevator at Kozamu-shisho's house is very slow
There's an elevator at his house?
It's a stand-alone house with elevator
-Have you been to his house?
-Yes, I did
-There's an elevator right?
-Yes
-And it's unbelievable right?
-Yes, it is
It's like this
-Is it that slow?
-Amazing
It must be Nishizawa
-Because of Miyazako-san...
-He laughed slightly like "ku-su"
He laughed at the speed of Miyazako-san elevating
It's Nishizawa right?
It's Nishizawa, but...
But I didn't see that clearly too
Let's confirm this together
-Have you been to his house?
-Yes, I did
-There's an elevator right?
-Yes, there is
-And it's unbelievable right?
-Yes, it is
It's like this
He laughed
This is the most natural type of laughing
Yes, I understand
You just laughed out naturally
You seem to forget about this for a moment
-But that elevator is seriously so slow
-It's really that slow?
Before he even reaches the 2nd floor,
his wife went back-and-forth for 4 times already
-4 times?
-I must have laughed if I heard 4 times
We're in danger if we heard that
No, no, no
It's safe for now
What a waste though
Ah, I missed this one, that was close
-Let's start
-Yes
This is getting serious
Let's start
I bet no one will buy these
Obitani-san should be salable
No way
Maybe like 300 yen?
No, that's too expensive
I have a present for everyone too
Eh, really?
What is it? Photos?
Itoda-san are these photos?
Photos?
-Can I open it?
-Sure
Let's open it together, one, two, three...
She's your mother...
Ah, mother-in-law?
It should be ex-mother-in-law
I want to watch this badly
Let's watch this together
Why though?
I hope everyone knows more about her
Know more about your mother-in-law?
(Come on...)
This is awful
-She's beautiful right?
-Yeah, beautiful
Look at this
That's pretty aggressive
-Ah, she's really showing everything
-Yes, everything
-She's beautiful
-Absolutely beautiful
-She was 60 years old when taking these photos
-Eh, 60 years old?
Really?
I can totally understand why she wants to make photo books
Yeah, she's really beautiful
Is this in demand?
This actually sold a lot
Yeah, that must be true
Nobu, this page is amazing, have a look
No, I'm good
This page
Check it out
No, I'm good, I can watch it on my own
-This page right?
-Yes
The next few pages are good too
Hey...
This is...
A mysterious page?
Mysterious page?
These pages are sticking together tightly
Eh?
Look at this
-Eww...
-Come on
-He must have masturbated
-Seriously?
He masturbated to his mother
If you want to pity me, then masturbate to me*
*The original line is "If you want to pity me, then give me money" from the famous drama "Ie Naki Ko" (Child Without a Home)
Ah, I screwed up
How could you masturbate to that?
Eh, did you say something just now?
Hey guys...
I got a tattoo
-Eh?
-What are you talking about?
Well, I'm a comedian and I thought it's a good time to get one
Are you fine with this?
I just wanted to get one badly
And I'm a comedian, it shouldn't matter
But there must be tasks that ask us to get naked
-That's not like you Fujimon
-You can't even use a public pool
Eh, where is the tattoo?
There's no tattoo
That's very well-done
-Why would you get a tattoo of your duo partner?
-What an amazing duo love
That's the face of him after doing gags right?
It's the face after the gag "Ore-yade" right?
No, it's after the gag "De-de-de-de"
-It will never come off
-Are you fine with that?
Excuse me, I want to tell you guys something too
I got a tattoo too
Seriously?
Nobu especially doesn't have that impression
Maybe it's good to have some contrast though
-The tattoo is fire
-Fire?
Ah, fire...
Yes, fire
Because I wanted to fire myself up
-I see
-I can totally understand that
Fire?
Yeah, that does fire one up
I got..
I got a tattoo on my armpits
That's amazing
So it's black fire right?
Black fire
Ah, that's amazing
I've actually...
You got a tattoo too?
Yes, please let me confess this, I got a tattoo too
-Eh?
-That's no good for you, Iio-san
I actually didn't want to show this to anyone
Eh? Are you fine with this?
Especially not on TV
Yeah, I understand that
-Anyway, please have a look
-Eh, really?
If you guys think it's inappropriate, I'll do a laser removal
And remove the tattoo
-That doesn't match your character
-Yes, I know
But I really want to move one step forward
Please have a look
Please tell me your true feelings
Is it okay for you?
If you guys say it looks good, then I'll just keep it
-Ready?
-Yes
Seriously?
Where is it?
Despite my age, these are on pink fire
-That's a tattoo?
-That's not a tattoo
So it's a pink tattoo?
-Ah, pink tattoo?
-Colored tattoo?
That's amazing
-They do look pink
-They're beautiful
Nipples show a person's character right?
Your nipples and your face are related right?
Well, I heard that the size of your nipple is the same as your eye pupil
No way dude
Your nipples are the same as Kazama Morio
Ah, yeah, the color is the same
-They look the same?
-Yes
The color is same
Excuse me...
I lost my wallet
-Wallet?
-Yes
Eh? Where did you lose it?
-Wallet?
-Yes
We didn't see it
Your hair is so freaking thick dude
-Yes?
-Your hair is so thick
-Are you a student?
-Yes
-Did anyone see my wallet
-Your forehead is so narrow
No, we didn't see it
But I'm sure I lost it somewhere here
I lost it here
What kind of wallet?
Eh, it's a Puma wallet
Puma?
Are you a high school student?
-It's a Puma with hook-and-loop fastener
-Ah I see, the one that sounds "bilibili"
How does it looks like?
It's a checked wallet
I've never seen a checked wallet from Puma
It's rare to see a checked wallet from Puma
-Your hair is so freaking thick dude
-Yes?
Ah, really? I just cut my hair yesterday
Yesterday?
Your hair is growing so fast
-Well...
-It looks like a honeycomb
-Are you on a school trip?
-I just asked them to make it thinner
-Nope
-You're local?
-Yes, I'm local
And his forehead is so narrow
We just can't find your wallet though
-How come...
-We didn't take it
We didn't dude
-Are you suspecting us?
Just leave
Yeah, I'm leaving already
You're scaring me, stop being moody
Just leave dude
I'm leaving
Didn't your mom say anything about your hair?
Huh?
Didn't your mom say anything about your hairstyle?
Yes, she did
She did right? She asked you to cut more right?
Go make your hair thinner first
Tell us your name and leave
I'm Saji Minoru
Saji?
Your last name is Saji?
How do you spell it?
You spell it with "Left" and "Myself"
*"左 (Sa)" which means "Left" and "自 (Ji)" which means "Myself"
-Ah, it should be temple, excuse me
-How could you get that wrong?
*"寺 (Ji)" which means "Temple"
You must be lying if you got that wrong
-"Left temple"?
-And it's pronounced as Saji
What's your first name?
-It's Minoru
-Minoru?
So the usual Minoru?
It's "Jitsu"
So just one word "Jitsu"
And then "Noru"
Hiragana?
-Noru is in Haragana?
-Yes
Have you ever heard Noru in Hiragana?
-And with Saji
-Never heard that before
Okay, I understand
His hair is so thick
And his forehead is so narrow
Are you suspecting us?
He's absolutely suspecting us
-We didn't take it
-I'll tell you if I find it
Sakata-shisho was admitted to the hospital recently
Eh?
He wasn't feeling well and went to the hospital
He then pressed the nurse call button, and the nurses came and ask him "What happened?"
And he said "A lion is staring at me from the cooler"
Eh, really? That's terrifying
-We can call food delivery right
-Oh, yeah
What can we call for food delivery though
-Just choose whatever is on there dude
-Eh?
You Kariyushi*
*Kariyushi is a pun from the previous episodes
Kariyushi? Was that my name?
-Sorry for being rude to you
-No problem at all
Kurosawa got changed over there right?
Ah, I see, you can hide inside here
-I see
-Yeah, you're right
There's no camera here
Let's do something
Fujimon
I'm feeling hungry
-That's dry ice
-Come on
That's dry ice dude
It's not ice, it's dry ice, and it's coming out from your nose
What an entertainer
-He's putting too much in his mouth
-Is he doing this wrong?
Aren't you guys hungry?
Yeah, I'm starving
It's 3 o'clock already
It's gonna stick to your mouth, spit it out now!
The dry ice is gonna stick to your mouth forever
Won't it melt though?
No, it won't melt, it'll just stick to his mouth, this is dangerous
It's too cold
Of course it's too cold dude
A lot of smoke came out
And Nishizwa what can I do with this?
-Well...
-I tried to wear it
Yes, I can see you wearing it
What can I do with this?
Well, I'm sorry
Are you fine?
I'm fine
It's gonna stick to your mouth
Just keep rolling it
-Keep rolling it?
-Yes, or else it will stick to your mouth
It's gonna tear off your skin
Eh, seriously?
Yeah, so you have to drink some water immediately
-I can drink some water first right?
-Well, yeah, you're right
-You need to close your mouth
-Then it'll come out from your nose
That's so weak
That's as weak as the humidifier beside the bed
The small and weak one right?
Yeah, the small one that looks like a lamp
It's not coming out at all
Because you kept your mouth open
This is so difficult
Because you opened your mouth
This is just so difficult
Let's put that aside
Okay
Wow, it's frozen
Ah, it's hardened
That must taste good with beer
No way dude
I mean like an ice beer
Ah, I see what you mean
You're so loud
AH, I SEE WHAT YOU MEAN
-Miyazako-san is always so loud right?
-Yeah, he is
-Remember how he sings?
-Yeah
Like when he sings "I want to hear your voice"
*"I want to hear your voice" is a line from the song "Subete ga Boku no Chikara ni Naru!" by Miyazako (Kuzu)
But you're singing it wrong though
It should be "I want to hear your voice" right?
That's wrong too
Just a bit wrong though
"I want to hear your voice"
You mean the melody is wrong
Money, Hamada Shogo
These are the most hilarious answers for my past Oogiri
What about the question for the Oogiri?
Only the answer for the Oogiri?
Only the answer?
Please ask me any question, I bet the answers will fit
Eh? It will fit any question?
I've prepared loads of answers, and I'll just show it one after another
-Eh? And it will fit whatever question?
-Yes, the answer will fit whatever
I don't want this kind of school!
What kind of school is it?
Because it's always autumn for us
Well, it does fit
Yeah, in some sense
-It's quite poetic
-Yeah, it is
Any more questions?
Let me think...
What is the name of the new Shinkansen
after Kodama, Hikari and Nozomi?
Madrid's sun will decide it
That's so long
What kind of pet is annoying?
A gift in return for a funeral offering
-So the pet is given in return?
-I bet so
-A pet is given in return?
-Like a black cat
That's scary
Comment on this photo (Sakata-shisho)
Work hard! Swedish education made him a Cherry boy!
*Sakata-shisho is famous for being a cherry boy (virgin) even at the age of 70
Cherry boy
This fits in
This is just miracle
He showed it in order
-Maybe anything fits Sakata-shisho?
-Oh I see, so reversely
Let's try
Comment on this photo
Never eat Castella cake with soft drink
He's a gourmet
-This must be hilarious if Sakata-shisho said it
-This is awful
-You should look at the photo
-Yeah, he's always facing here
Do it over there
Ah, I see
Sit here Nobu
I'll start from the next page
Let's start
Show us the photo first
Comment on this photo
Let's use this time to make a pleasant sauce
This is amazing
Yeah, it's hilarious
This is awful
We started something awful
Fujimon is in a favorable position
-Yeah, he's in a favorable position
-He's the one performing
Fujimon please watch the photo again and keep it in your mind
Please don't show it this way, we will be in danger too
Please sing us a song
Money/Hamada Shogo
He's not Hamada Shogo though
Another one
Comment on this photo
People call it love
Why is he like this?
Madrid's sun made him like this
In the Spain
In the Spain is not written on there
Do you get it?
He don't use to be like this, it's Madrid's sun that made him like this
Work hard! Swedish education made him a Cherry boy!
Cherry boy
It's Swedish education guys
*Kawakami Maiko is a Swedish-born Japanese actress
Just like Kawakami Maiko
Sweden education
-A gift in return for a funeral offering
-It's his nickname
A gift in return for a funeral offering
Fujimon is always...
Yeah, Fujimon keeps adding extra words
What is your role?
-Like saying it's his nickname...
-I'm his man of virtue
Man of virtue?
Should we write it now?
Yeah, just write it now
Write it now?
Let's write it now
So in real time?
Let's do this
So we can watch it in raw
It's a live
Oogiri live
It's Oogiri live
Comment on this photo
I like you
Wait a second...wait a second...
Wait a second...
Come on, wait a second, this is terrible
You laughed out loud
Oh dear, oh dear...
No, no, that's just my voice
That's my voice
That's just my voice, Matsumoto-san
There's no excuse for that one
Nobu is actually laughing slightly all the time
It's just sooner or later
Well, let's have a look first
-Comment on this photo
-I like you
Nobu!!!
Out!!!
This is just awful, come on
I never thought Nobu will be the first one out
He's the first one
I'm the first one...
So no more chance for the 10 million prize
No more chance
You'll be back as a zombie
Just try hard as a zombie
Yeah, I understand
Nobu zombie
Well, Nobu zombie won't even be interesting right?
Yes, exactly
But that's funny too
In another sense
It's hilarious to see a nervous zombie that is not funny at all
-Nobu let's go
-Yes
Bye Nobu
That was cunning, seriously
-They're pinpointing at me
-Well yeah, indeed
They were somehow targeting Nobu
Bye bye Nobu
I'll be back as a zombie
That zombie must be fine
Nobu zombie must be fine
This is truly embarrassing
But my defense is just too weak
This one was about vasectomy right...
Are these words...
Ka-ha!
Ka-ha?
While there is anxiety in the atmosphere
But on top of that, the atmosphere is absolutely hilarious
-Comment on this photo
-I like you
Wait a second...
It feels like I'm going to burst with the slightest poke by a needle
I'm frustrated
Let's start
It started
There's Sashimi, Kimuchi and meat here
Shall we fry it?
Fry it or call food delivery?
Let's try the foods here, this is a precious chance
So we're going to cook?
That meat is amazing
Please fry it
-Miyazako-san is good at cooking right?
-Yeah
Anyone want some apple juice?
Ah, I want some
Do it yourself dude! You're just a junior, you idiot
Ah, I'm sorry, I didn't expect this
Just drink some milk
Ah, may I?
-Is there milk?
-Let Daigo see how you drink milk
(Eh, Daigo?)
Wait a second...
You said it right?
Well, I just asked him to drink some milk in front of everyone
Will your beard be stained?
No, it won't
-Ah, wait a second Kurochan
-Yes?
Huh?
-You asked him to drink some milk right?
-Yes, I asked him to drink some milk, but in front of everyone
No, you didn't say in front of everyone
Daigo asked you to drink it, so show it to Daigo
May I drink it?
Your beard will be stained if you chug it
Stained with milk
No it won't be stained
I'll drink it now
Chug it
It must be stained
It's leaking in the same way
It's really not stained
It's leaking from that side every time
Drink it one more time
Ah, may I?
Ah, okay
It will definitely be stained this time
Yeah, it must be stained
Don't make that face
(Of course it will be stained)
(How much is he drinking?)
It's making the sound of a drain
Can you not talk about the sound of a drain now?
But it made the sound "Kobo-kobo" like a drain
What are you talking about?
-Don't drink it anymore
-Why?
-You're gonna be stuffed
-Yeah
Shall we fry it?
-Yes, please
-Really?
-I'll just fry it then
-Yes
Can this even be fried though?
Maybe cut it into pieces?
This is amazing
This is thick
Wow, barbecue
This is so thick
Maybe we can even deep fry it?
The show is gonna end by then
-Maybe we can just focus on cooking and make this a gourmet show
-No way
What happened?
He's angry because his cloth is stained
It's stained with meat juice
You're being overly concerned
-But my jacket is stained with meat juice
-Who cares
Is that an expensive jacket?
I just asked you is that an expensive jacket?
Because you seem to be so concerned about it
Is there any wet towel?
Let's make one
Hey no, I just thought you shouldn't care about your cloth today
Let me do a Thunder
Please don't do a Thunder
A Thunder?
What is a Thunder?
Miyazako-san, please stop that
I'm the one who is frying the steak for everyone
I know you're wearing expensive cloth,
but just don't be overly concerned...
-What's a Thunder?
-Show me your back
-No, wait, please...
-You can keep your clothes on
You can keep your clothes on, so just stay still
You can keep your clothes on
It's fine, just keep your clothes on
Just stand over here
-You should never talk to your seniors like this
-Yeah, I know, but...
Just stay still in this angle
-Miyazako-san, please don't, seriously...
-This is scary
OUCH!
He's crying
I never saw Fujimon look like that
And he's an adult
Even above his cloth
That's because you complained
I'm the senior and I'm cooking for you guys
Yes, you're right
But he's just overly concerned about it
You're still talking about it?
Well, but Miyazako-san always try to act cool right?
Sit here
Just sit here
-What are you going to do?
-Just sit here
Why are you always talking things like that?
It's inappropriate to say those things
That is so scary
That must hurt so badly
-That's scary
-Oh, no
Come on, Fujimon-san
He's gonna be punished again
He's cute, like a cat
Because you glared at him right?
That's your fault
Fujimon-san...
Please stop this
Both are you are seniors, please stop this...
-That's dangerous
-That must hurt so badly
Well done for holding on
Ku-chan was close though
Thank you
-I'll fry it for everyone
-Thank you
-They made up
Were you two used to performing like this as juniors?
Well, yeah...
We used to perform like this
I miss those days
But some of my bones are dislocated because of this
He's sometime sadistic right?
Towards comedians and towards women
Women as well?
He does those things to women as well?
I thought he's kind
Yes, he sure is kind
But I mean...
When he's on the bed
Eh?
So you're talking like that again?
My child is already in high school
Saying those things is inappropriate
Sorry, I'm just joking
Who's mouth said that?
No, please, I'm sorry
-I just thought it's interesting
-This mouth said that right?
Directly?
It's seriously gonna be dislocated
That's because you're saying those things
But it really hurts
It really hurts so badly
For real?
Yes, for real
It really hurts so badly?
If he push a bit harder, it will be dislocated
-Dislocated?
-Yes, it's gonna come out
Like in Mask?
The movie Mask
But what should you say at the first moment when it comes back
Yeah, I wonder what to say
When it stretches and come back, a lot of skin will stay here right?
So what should you say at the first moment when it comes back?
Are you asking me to do Oogiri dude
Because we're talking about this
Please leave me alone
When your jaw dislocates and reaches the ground, what would you say at the first moment when it comes back?
The Silver Pavilion
What does that mean?
When your jaw dislocates and reaches the ground, what would you say at the first moment when it comes back?
I like you
-It's dangerous to hear that sizzling sound after "I like you"
-That was a perfect combination
(That was a really good one though)
That's amazing
Would it be fine to have it rare?
This should be fine, I'll flip it
-That's amazing
-Looking good
-Is there any butter
-Oh, yeah
Have a look
-But I think I saw some spices inside
-Really?
Like some seasonings
This is thrilling
This is so thrilling
There was some eggshells inside
Eggshells?
There's eggshells?
Oh, I see
-So you're puking because of eggshells?
-Yes
I'm using too much
I used so much towels
I feel gross
It was so spicy...
These are incontinence pads
(Is Kurochan going to do this?)
Are you ok?
OUCH
Huh, Iio?
Iio laughed right?
Eh, who is it?
-Who laughed?
-No, I didn't
Well, it's Iio
-Eh?
-He laughed
-Really?
He definitely laughed right?
He laughed right?
I just went "Hu-wa" because of the sliminess
-So you laughed at the sliminess right?
-Well yes, I laughed at the sliminess
-The sliminess was just absolutely awful
-Well, I have to give you an orange card
Ah, I shouldn't have put it in my mouth
-So Iio will be out next time too
-Ah, come on
Ah, I'm sorry
I can't believe you put that in your mouth
What I found the most difficult to hold back was during the Oogiri
The sizzling sound went "Jyuwa"
When your jaw dislocates and reaches the ground, what would you say at the first moment when it comes back?
I like you
-It's awful to hear that sizzling sound after "I like you"
-That was a perfect combination
(That was a really good one though)
It's amazing for you all to hold back on that one
That was hilarious though
-Well done for holding on
-It made a fierce sound right?
Yeah, all of a sudden
-And went like "Jyuwa"
-That was amazing
Let's start
Ah, so that's why you laughed just now
I bet he is doing that...
-Yeah, he's doing that...
-Sure he his
Wait a second, Ku-chan, please...
This is awful
This is absolutely awful
Ku-chan, the steak is almost ready
Who are you?
Yamamoto Shinya
-Yamamoto Shinya?
-The director
The director?
I told you I'm Yamamoto Shinya, so I am Yamamoto Shinya
He can't talk with that denture?
-It's difficult to talk wearing that
-It's difficult to talk?
Do Yamamoto Shinya director have those protruding teeth?
He don't have protruding teeth
He's not that white
And he's not that bald
Hey you, don't fry it with a delightful face
Please excuse me
Excuse me
What brought you here?
Looking good...
I'm here for site inspection
Please excuse me
I'm looking for cool locations
And cool locations are looking for me
He's director for sure
Are you filming a movie now?
-Please excuse me...
-Can you stop putting it there?
Don't put it on other's head
Please stop it
You understand me?
I'm sorry
I'll put it this on
Please excuse me
He's being considerate
That's much better than putting it directly
No dude
Let's eat the steak
Eh? You're staying here?
You're gonna stay here like this?
Seriously?
Hey, Iio-san
-Yes?
-Look at him
Director is here, so face him
No please, Fujimon-san
No listen to me...
Fujimon-san, are you able to eat with him?
Let's eat together
Miyazako-san...
Please just take the steak here...I can't take this anymore...
What happened?
You're finding it difficult to wear the denture right?
Because of the moisture...
It's absorbing the moisture...
What did you say?
The denture...
The moisture...
The moisture swelled it up
He's so mean
You need to take off the denture to eat it
This is just...
That was so long
Are you okay Daigo?
Oh my god, that was just awful
Damn it
-That was close
-He didn't eat it at all
Ah, I'm so tired
I'm so tired too
He didn't eat it at all
Everyone was close though
How did you hold back on that?
-He was actually too close, so I can't see his face clearly
-No man, that was awful
That's the distance between Sigourney Weaver and alien
It's like in Alien 2
Yeah, the distance in Alien 2
Well, Miyazako-san saved you all
That anxious atmosphere has never been seen before
Let's have a look
-That was impossible to hold back
-Yeah, that's impossible
Come on
That's impossible
So the first card for Miyazako, yellow card