Comparing to those who have participated multiple times
Are those who are making their first appearance disadvantaged?
Well, I wonder about that too
This somehow depends on their length of career and even their employer
But personally, I think those who are making their first appearance as the most junior person can get along well
I see, it's you!
I know you, you lost the R-1 competition, right? -Wait...why?
Just say I'm the one who won the M-1 competition
Well, to be honest, of course I didn't choose every contestant, like "this guy, and this guy"
The staffs show me 10 carefully selected contestants, and I make the final decision
Come on... -No, no, no way
Why did you come, dude
Why can't I come, dude!
You idiot! -No I'm not, you're an idiot!
However, well, how should I put this...
The audiences really hate Fujimon, so...
I think there:s no chance for him to join again
And I'll ignore him even if I meet him somewhere else
What happened to you?
It's full of blemishes
I don't like seniors with blemishes... -So cold!
Yeah, my body gets cold easily
Because I had stomach cancer
Huh?
He let out a "ku" sound -Yeah, I heard that
It's normal to say "ku"
He bursted out laughing -Hooray!
No! No way! I don't want this!
Anyway, yellow, yellow...
won't do Ciao anymore
No one will laugh at it
Even I won't laugh at it, of course no one else will!
Eh? Just now?
I have to give you this -Ahh, I screwed up
That was too easy
So it started -Started
Just look at Kato's face...
I can't hold back my laughters already
Yeah, don't try to look at him in the eyes
(Kato's face...well, yeah, that's true)
(Kato himself is hilarious too) Jelly, there's a jelly here
Nice, there's a jelly -Eat it then
Nah, who likes jelly?
No one will want to eat jelly now though
Well, if I have to choose between like and dislike, then yes, I like it
I'm really good at feeding others jelly
No, I"m good, no thank you
No thank you, don't let me do this
Seriously
But Nobu you said you like it, so... -Exactly
We don't eat jelly at all, right? -Yeah, I rarely eat it
But Nobu you like it, right?
Stop it! I don't need jelly now
But you said you like it, so...
Wh-wh-what are you going to do?
Bite it with your mouth
And purse your lips
Are you ready?
It got in my eye
"Got in my eye" killed him
So fast (What was that?)
(What was that just now?)
It's me, right? It's my point, right?
"It got in my eye"
It's him, he laughed
No, I didn't laugh
All I said is "it got in my eye" -No! It's you!
All I said is "it got in my eye"
It's Nobu-san
I didn't laugh at all
What is this low quality comedy?
Such a lame joke
Did that make you laugh?
You guys are professional!
Because he said "it got in my eye" at a perfect timing
It should be my turn to get angry and say something -Exactly
It was chaotic so let's watch it again
Seiya's point?
Bite it with your mouth
And purse your lips
Are you ready?
It got in my eye
"Got in my eye" killed him
No one cares!
No one freaking cares!
No need to say it -Of course I need to! It got in my eye!
So this is Nobu -Hooray!
Really? This is awful
Well, for the points...
Although not intended, maybe the point belongs to Seiya? -Thank you very much
Very lucky -It indeed got in his eye
Yes, it got in my eye
When Nobu was about to say something...
"It got in my eye"
That's an unexpected accident
Everything is becoming funny to you now
Keep yourself nervous
Let's start
Started
Definitely won't laugh
You guys are so sticky already
Koyabu-san gave me this. What the heck is this?
I don't think it's a handkerchief
It's that thing used to cover dead body
What is it?
It's the bandage used in field hospitals
Why did you bring this with you?
Let's calm down guys
That's true
It's still half past five
Yeah
That's not half past five
I meant 5 hours 30 minutes, but I said half past five
That's not half past five -Never mind, Tamuken-san
He said it's half past five?
It's indeed half past five now
It's half past five? -It's indeed half past five now
It's really half past five now! -They're the same
They are the same -By chance?
Is he kind of laughing? -Yeah, he's laughing!
We all agreed to calm down! That's teamwork! Stop being destructive!
Okay, okay, wbat about doing an exaggerated Sakai Masaaki?
No thank you, I'm good
Take a look
Firstly, this is the normal Sakai Masaaki
That's two stars!
However... -It's already exaggerated
For the exaggerated Sakai Masaaki
Do you need to practice that?
Of course I need to practice
Why didn't you say three stars?
Why two stars?
You're right -Yeah
Three stars are more understandable...
He scared me..
What?
Huh?
Eh? I found a pair of boobs here!
Eh? Can I touch those boobs?
Whose boobs are. those?
Better not touch them -Yeah, cut it out
But those boobs don't belong to anyone
That's why, that's exactly why you shouldn't touch them
Who will scold me for touching them?
If you don't know whose boobs are those, then you definitely shouldn't touch them
-No, no, but those don't belong to anyone
It probably belongs to the person who owns that cap
No, but no one is here
It should be fine to touch it. Just a little
We tried to stop you though -Exactly
Anyway, I'll touch it, just a little
Whoa! It's super soft!
It's super soft!
I can't hold back!
You know? It's super soft!
Look!
It's super soft!
Why is it so soft?
Because these are boobs
That's how God made it
Do you want to touch it too?
No, I'm good -No thank you
Seiya, go touch it
That's good for you -No, I'm good...
You need to experience more now
Look, they're so soft!
These are so soft! And she never complains
She won't get angry at all!
She won't get angry even if you touch them
It's all-you-can-touch
Seiya you're young -Yeah, go for it Seiya
Is it really fine?
Isn't it scary to touch boobs for free?
May I?
Excuse me
You're going too far, dude!
Those are my boobs!
You're going too far!
I'm the first one to touch them, so they are my boobs!
Stop it, stop it -Too dangerous
Why the heck did you lick them! You're definitely going too far!
Those boobs don't belong to anyone!
But I touched them first so they're mine!
You're gonna hurt his ears
Surely, that's true!
That's how you hold people in the army
Hey! Did I say anything wrong?!
That's how you hold people in French army
I'm talking to you! -Yes, sir!
He became a French soldier
Even his shirt looks like France
Don't lick them, dude
Ahh, he's aiming someone
Why the heck did you lick them!
Hey!
That's ridiculous
Don't even think about licking them
He's still in the army
Don't lick them
(How did they hold back on that? That's impossible for me)
(It's getting chaotic) Don't lick them
Seriously
Why did you lick them?
No...
You licked them just now, dude! -No, no, I didn't
You definitely licked them just now! -No, I didn't
How dare you look into my eyes and lie like this?
Hey, wait...
My boobs are being...
They're popped!
I actually bought this bucket recently
Eh? Finished?
How much do you think this costs?
Can you first explain to us, what was that farce just now?
What was your plan? What should we laugh at?
Don't bother with those boobs anymore
I bought this bucket
How much do you think this costs?
Eh? Done with those boobs already?
Well, it does look expensive though
How much do you think this costs?
This is not an ordinary bucket
The shape is quite unique -Yes
Probably about 300 yen -Yeah, that makes sense
Eh? Are buckets that cheap now?
even has a spout
A spout! -Why do you think it's expensive to have a spout?
He keeps emphasizing that spout
Because although you can make those normal ones with machine
But for this, you have to pull here
This uses a different machine with a different mould
Machines can only make round-shaped buckets
So the craftsman needs to pull here at the end
Just add the spout to the mould, and it will be shaped like this
No one will pull it at the end
Of course the craftsman will pull it at the end, just like this...
Then each bucket will be different
So how much did it cost?
Yeah, exactly
300 yen
He got it right then
And then, this is not an ordinary bucket
Not "and then", dude
What was your plan if we got it right? What's the right answer?
What's the right answer? 300 yen the right answer
No, after we said 300 yen, what should happen and how will you make people laugh?
No, it's not about making people laugh, 300 yen is the correct answer
Are you in a bad mood today?
No, but you're pissing me off
Let's stop this, so scary
It's 300 yen, so what?
This is not an ordinary basket...bucket
Basket? -Did he say basket?
This is neither a basket nor a bucket
It's a bucket
Why are you full of sweat?
It's not a basket
I know, it's a bucket
Please look at him, look at his special basket
This is not an ordinary basket
Basket?
Nobu, it's a basket
Shut up, shut up...
Shut up!
You can't just close your eyes -Look at his special basket
Are you looking at him then, Goto-san?
Yes, I am
What are you looking afr?
Basket -Basket
Basket?
I'm looking at his special basket
A special...?
Basket -Basket
Look at the basket -Galm down, ealm down...
(Calm down, calm down, he's very close)
Basket
(It spread to him)
(It spread to Miyasako)
He endured it?
Basket, basket
Enough with basket, so annoying
Basket won't get me anymore
This was not funny at all
I was so close with that basket
I was so close, and that basket almost got me, but then I saw this
This was not funny at all
Anyway, what's about that bucket?
It's 300 yen, and then what?
Everyone, please look carefully at this basket
What the heck?
This is not an ordinary basket -It's a bucket
Even if you say basket, you're just pissing us off, no one will laugh so please stop
So harsh, he's being so harsh!
Believe it or not...
This is’a weird face basket
Change it back to bucket!
Whoever put this on will have a weird face
Sounds good
Who wants to give it a try?
You do it first -Yeah, demonstrate it to us
The weird face basket
Yes -It's not a basket, it's a bucket
My face will change instantly
You're ready?
It changed, right? Isn't it amazing?
Seiya? -You used up your frustrated faces
It's already out of stock
Can I give it a try too?
Yeah, sure -Do it, Michio
Don't do it Michio
Don't do it Michio!
Nobu, go watch it in the front row
Hello, I'm Michio
Don't do it Michio
Take off your hat first
You hat -Michio, better take off your hat first
Eh? What happened? -What happened to your head?
This is actually, a maze
A maze? -Yes
Start from here
Please try it out
Whoa, it really is a maze!
Amazing! -What the heck is that?!
So you asked them to shave it like that?
If you can reach the goal, I'll give you a prize
Eh? This looks quite easy though
Yes, go that way
Almost there, this way
Yes, almost there! -This way, goal!
Well done, congratulations
Congratulations
I'll give you the prize, Goto-san
You'll give me a prize? -Yes
What is this?
Adamo-chan?
Why did you take the photo of Adamo-chan in transit?
Not during a show?
Is he your senior?
He's his senior?
Photo of him in transit?
Why in transit? -It's definitely better to take a photo of him in shows
He put on this makeup for one show
And the next show also needs him to be in this makeup, right?
(Who's point is that?)
It surprised me!
He legitly laughed
That's a self-destruction, he should receive a red card for this, right?
That was a loud laughter!
He should receive two cards
It's probably not just a yellow card, huh?
No, no, no...
That's definitely not just a yellow card
He completely laughed -Bursted into laughters
"Ta-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha"
It's still the first half, so please...
It's indeed quite funny to know Adamo-chan is in the same makeup in transit for the next show
What's that photo, seriously?
He even has his own seat belt
Let's watch it again and decide the color of the card
Photo of him in transit?
Why in transit? -It's definitely better to take a photo of him in shows
He put on this makeup for one show
And the next show also needs him to be in this makeup, right?
He laughed out loud!
He bursted into laughters!
He completely cracked up
You legitly laughed
I'll give you an orange card for this
Yeah, that's fair
I have to give you an orange card to be fair
That was disturbing even as a sound effect
This photo is awful
It's probably even funnier to him, because they are in the same company
Goto's verbal attack is fearful
Let's start
Can I put on the basket as well?
Eh? -You mean the one just now?
But my head is really big
You don't know whether it will fit or not? -Yes
I'll ask "Are you ready?", so please reply "Yes, we're ready" -Okay, got it
He's diligent
Yeah, surprisingly, he takes it seriously
Are you ready?
Please come in -Yes, we're ready
Where's the basket?
Eh? The basket became this shape?
It's broken? -It broke into pieces?
That's very artistic
It's finely carved
That's so cool -Yeah, so cool
You can't talk anymore?
So he can't talk with that on..
There's more? -The basket is gone
You guys probably didn't saw this...
He came out like fury from the curtain
He went in like fury too
Yeah, you're right
Is that still the same basket?
It became even smaller
You mean you reshaped it just now?
No way, it's impossible to add those colors
The basket is already broken
Only the front part covering the face is left
The back part is already gone
Come on, it costed me 300 yen
300 yen is nothing
300 yen is really cheap
It looks completely different
So freaking scary!
Darth Maul -That's Darth Maul
That dude is life-threatening
Maybe this is his face mask series?
Who would even buy that? -You're right
Who would be happy to buy that?
Oh, you mean that face mask as a product?
Yes, who are the buyers?
It became wider
Huh? It’s bigger, isn't it?
It's different from the previous one
Yeah, it became bigger, right?
And the’color changed too
Why is he smoking like a gay?
Does he always smoke like a gay?
It changed dramatically
He's that guy who protects the forest
That's not the tag, that's the hook
So that thing is being banged in some kind of shop?
It's probably piled up and hanged for sale
He's so tender
He's Tenzan (wrestler)
Why did he came out in this order?
Tenzan always open his mouth, huh?
You guys know about Tenzan?
Oh, he's talking
When Tenzan left the Tokyo Dome, he kept saying something like this, right?
I asked him about this in person
I asked him "what were you saying?
And he said he was just moving his mouth
Moving his mouth? -Eh?
That's what he told me
"I'm gonna beat you up," not something like that?
He didn't say a word
This is a disaster -What happened?
This is a true disaster
You're angry at so many things
No, this is the worst
What happened? -Just say it, dude
Well, you guys probably don't know him, but Kitamura-san is very angry now
Kitamura-san? -Yes
Who's Kitamura-san?
Yeah, you don't know him, right?
I don't -He's a real pain in the neck
Whoa, maybe Kitamura-san is going to call me
Whoa, that's absolutely terrible
Do you need to be so upset because of someone else?
Because he's furious with me -You're right
Because you don't know the fearfulness of Kitamura-san
We don't know - I've never met him before
Is he going to call you?
Yeah, maybe he'll call me. Come on, we're still recording now
He never cares about otheYs
Well, he probably don't know you're recording now
Oh gee
Will he break in the studio?
Nah, he probably won't go that far
Well, then that's fine
But he's really angry now. He's really annoying.
Come on, give me a break, Kitamura-san!
When is he going to call you?
No, no...maybe he won't call me
How dare you ask us to gather around then?
Huh?
If he's not going to call you
We all gathered around and waiting for you
What the heck is wrong with you?
Can you make it clear, dude? -Honestly, what's going on now?
So you don't know about Kitamura-san, right?
Do you know him?
Eh? What are you talking about?
You don't know about Kitamura-san, right?
Why are you frustrated? -No, no, no...
Why are you already frustrated?
I don't understand your plan
You guys don't even know him
Of course we don't know, you're the one who said it, and that's why we all gathered around
You guys don't even know about Kitamura-san, you guys have no idea
(This dude is quite interesting)
You guys know nothing about Kitamura-san, so stop being sarcastic
Oh, you mean Masa-san? -That actor?
Kitamura Masahide, right?
Eh? Masa-san?
Not Masa-san!
If it's Masa-san, then I'll just say it's Masa-san, right?
Why would I take the trouble to say Kitamura-san?
Stop making fun of Kitamura-san!
What's wrong with you guys?
You guys are idiots, honestly!
Absolutely no idea.what's going on
I definitely don't want to laugh at this and receive a card
(Yeah, it’s not concise, I can’t give out cards neatly too)
(Someone's coming)
(That's awful, something awful is coming)
(Something awful is coming...)
(Something awful is coming)
(That was awful)
(That was awful, and it's cunning if you don't look at him)
(That was unexpected)
Something is making a "ji-ji-ji" sound
Something is hapj5eningtover there
Something wth a motor?
Is that a mouse?
What's that?
Whoa, that's a cat
(He laughed?)
(No, he didn't laugh)
How come?
*Around the time of the show, while Tamuken was eating at a ramen shop, one of hte staff took a photo with him and posted it on the official Twitter, saying that "Tamuken is a boring person without mic and camera." The shop was criticized by many comedy fans.
Ramen...
Ramen? -He said Ramen
So that cat is probably raised by one of the staffs in that Ramen shop
Eh? So this cat is on that Ramen shop's side?
Well, yeah, this cat is probably living in that Ramen shop
He was furious with me only, he was so friendly to everyone else
(There's a traffic jam)
You're shaving a lot of hair
You're shaving your hair? -Yes
You have to look in the mirror and shave it carefully
Whoa! -No, stop it, that's too dangerous
I'll do it for you, so stop it. I'll do it for you
I'll do it for you (Yeah, that's scary)
You're gonna hurt yourself -Too dangerous!
Don't move it up and down, that's insane!
What the heck are you doing?
Too dangerous...
I told you not to move it up and down!
Stop it, that's too dangerous
No way, no!
No, no, no way! That's insane!
That's ridiculous! -So scary
Ridiculous -I told you to stop it
Too dangerous
Cut it out -Is my head shaved?
Of course it is shaved, Michio
And he's uninjured
You don't need that maze anymore?
Yeah, I'm done with that maze, or else I'll be scolded
Who will scold you?
My parents
Please stop it, seriously -Then can you...?
Please do it for him
Do it tenderly
Is it fine?
Can I really shave it?
You don't have other jobs? -It's okay
Do you need to look the same on shows? -No worries
I'll just be scolded by my parents
You're not starred in any drama shows?
Your maze is gone, is that fine? Do you need that maze on other shows?
Of course he won't need that maze on other shows
What happened to Tamura-san and that cat?
Thank you very much -Looking good now
I've only shaved the front part of your head
Excuse me, thank you very much
What the heck is this gauze in field hospitals?
Your metaphors are all about battlefield
Because I've just watch Private Ryan
(That was fast)
(That response was fast)
Hey, dude! -Yes?
Your jokes are always bothering others, that jelly as well
Well, yeah, that's tru e
Others need to tidy things up for you
I'm sorry
Your seniors are tidying things up for you
What kind of education did you receive?
Well, nothing special...
I'm sorry, please forgive me
What's wrong with your parents?
My mom is dead
This has nothing to do with his parents
So you're from a single-father family?
Well, yeah, part way through
Part way through? -Yes
I'm from a single-father family
Work hard and do you best, dude -Yes
You got me? Don't lose to anyone
No, no, this is terrible -Stop it, cut it out
Dude...you finally did this to me, huh?
That's seriously inappropriate
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth. I'll pay him back double
No, no more, cut it out
I'm gonna pull his hair out
Miyasako-san said that already
I said it already, sorry
He already said "there's no hair to pull"
"I can't grab it"
Ah Kato-san, behind you
Watch out
Good morning
He got that on so quick
-Good morning
-He can prepare something like that so quickly
Good morning
So quick
He's a school principal with an iron wig
That’s not the principal
It’s "Tokudane!" (Editor's note: Morning News Show)
-“Tokudane!”
-Oh that one
-Good morning
-It’s Ogura-san
Don't say that
He will get angry
Good morning
He can’t take it off?
-He can’t take it off
-He did his best
-I wonder if Kitamura-san will call
-Is he still attempting that?
You, really, really need to stop it
He’s very angry
Did the call come?
Why don’t you know? Look at your phone
Did something arrive through LINE? (EN: "LINE" is a Messaging App)
Is something wrong with the plan?
-Can you see it on my phone?
-He's on LINE
He does have LINE, then
Koyabu-san is already laughing
-That's how it is... Soon…
-Koyabu-san is already laughing
Say it to Koyabu-san
What is this!
Do you know anything about Kitamura-san?
What are you saying?
Do you know...
About Kitamura-san?
You don’t know, right?
I already told you many times
that I don't know
From that annoying Kitamura-san
I may get a call from that annoying Kitamura-san
He's crying
Wait… I’ll wipe my tears
This is bad, this is really bad
-This guy is dangerous
-Koyabu-san is laughing all the time
-Wait a second
-Yes
"Kitamura-san", what's up with that?
Seriously, you’re right
What is he saying?
He attempted the joke twice, and couldn't land it twice
He was really worried about something
Hey, I recently got into a hobby
A hobby, or rather a "special skill"
I, myself...
I thought that I couldn't be hypnotized
If you think I can't hypnotize you, I can
By the way, like...
I’m starting to get a little interested myself
You're very susceptible, aren't you?
I’m very susceptible
I'm not sure if you know this, but...
Hypnosis?
If I get hypnotized
I can do things that I normally couldn't
It’s easy to do
Ah Tamura-san
You can do hypnosis?
Who? Who wants to go first?
What… what is this?
This is an example, but-
When there are noodles in ponzu, I can't slurp it
I just spit it out
That's how it is
But if I’m hypnotized...
I can quickly eat it
Amazing!
Then... Goto
Alright
First you eat it normally
Slurping it all at once
It's so acidic
Is there only ponzu in here?
Yeah, only ponzu
No, wait a second, wait a second
There are quite a lot of noodles
- Add a lot more
-How much is this??
Come on already
What?
He said "Fun fun" now
He completely just went "fun fun"
I didn't say "foo foo"
I said "ha ha"
You said…
You said it yourself...
You're enjoying this
Because that's what I thought he said
Did he laugh just now?
I’m not laughing
It’s exactly what I expected
-Stop looking in a different direction…
-You’re laughing, see...
-This is disgusting
-That much?
No, this is harsh
This is bad
Now let's try it with hypnosis
Seriously?
Wait, I want some time beforehand
That's a special skill, right?
Close your eyes, Goto
Relax relax
Feels good Feels good
It feels good
Yes, Goto
Now it feels good
You're in Documental
but forget it for now
What? It feels good
Are you good? Then I’ll count down 5 seconds
This ponzu, which was sour until now, is going to be nothing
So I...
After I count “5 4 3 2 1”
Raise your head
And open your eyes
5 4 3 2 1 ...
-Aren’t you laughing?
Yes, open your eyes
Goto, hey...
Did you just laugh?
Huh?
Do you want to eat it?
-Eat it!
Why did you laugh?
-Go for it
-It would be amazing if you could eat it
He laughed so hard
Two people
-What’s this?
-Two people just completely lost
I was about to laugh... I was about to laugh
No, I didn't laugh!
So much was going on
No, I didn't laugh!!
Tamuken was completely laughing
No, I laughed after the alarm
It wasn’t ringing yet
Goto was about to laugh when he was hypnotized
No, you're wrong, you're wrong
He said "raise your head"
My head was already raised, though
I don’t get it
If he made a mistake, it shouldn't affect you
So I...
After I count “５ ４ ３ ２ １”
Raise your head
And open your eyes
He’s laughing!
This was really interesting
He’s already laughing…
This…this…
I wonder what to do about this
I was holding in the laugh!
Well this is, Tamuken…
It would be amazing if you could eat it
-You just laughed a lot
-See!
Two people
That's Tamuken, right?
That said, it’s my point, right?
Well, that’s right Tamuken…
He already had yellow, right?
Alright, let’s continue
Was that really hypnosis?
You can’t do it. It's impossible
If we can’t do it
eventually we’ll vomit and spit it out
Don't say that!
Everyone knows
Start!
Let's get on with it
So many cigarettes
With this body shape... I'm a little fat
Wait Nobu
This guy is funny
I can't take this, I'm laughing way too much
Thank you for waiting
Um, are you guys a group?
-What?
-Are you Kitamura-san?
No I’m not
Eh, Kitamura-san?
-Group?
-Group members
Well then
Please sit down
In that case, we're a group
This guy is interesting
Minako-chan can go right away
Mai-chan?
Yukari-chan
They... can go right away
-She's a little chubby
-It’s a chubby service, right
-No no no
-Is this your speciality?
Eh no
Waist 57 58…
No no no no
That's wrong
Waist 57
This waist is around 100 (EN: He might've meant the hips)
-Is that so?
-Everyone is so fat
Around 30 minutes...
If you have time...
-Aiko-chan
-I don't want to wait
Wow wow wow
-This is Ichigo-chan
-Who will be waiting for this?
-I won’t wait
-It's the same, right?
Do you specialize in chubby women?
No no
Do you like slender women?
Ah, yes
When it comes to Miruku-chan
She’s still chubby
Akari-chan
-Still chubby…
-The same?
It's the same person
She’s just changing wigs
Akari-chan
Miruku-chan
No, if it were 3 separate women, the 3 sizes (B, W, H) would change
And now, the most talented
-Amazing
-The best one
Yuu-chan
Why are you doing this?
What do you mean?
7000 yen for 40 minutes
-Expensive
-Eh cheap
-Is it cheap?
-It’s cheap, it’s cheap
The market's amazing
What are you on about?
Do you usually have it done secretly? (EN: Not 100% sure about this line)
Watanabe?
She’s a female entertainer called TOY
She's an entertainer?
-Ah, so is everyone an entertainer?
-Ah, everyone?
Do you make female entertainers
do these kinds of things?
Ah, is that so
-She’s a married woman
That's not good
If you'd like,
Our store manager has published a book
If you want, I can give this as a service
What?
This person's the store manager?
Yes
Do you know him?
No, sorry
I'm sure the manager will be pleased
-I don’t need this...
Are you sitting down?
Yes? Together
-You’re from the store, right?
-Soon...
He almost laughed
He’s holding back his laugh
I'm not holding back my laugh
He's holding back
It’s frustrating, isn’t it?
That's how it is
Do you want to sit together?!
That’s how it'll be very soon…
I'll tell you that soon
What am I supposed to do...
Do you like Goto-san?
What should I do?
-Goto-san
-Are you crying?
It's really messed up!
What is this?!
But you...
What I want to know is
what you're doing right now
Too. Bad!
Koyabu-san too...
Just reading the book like that
Please read it out loud,
any sentence is fine
I’m Kazuki Enari
A student of Hana-College
I want to enjoy campus life
Which social circle should I join?
Didn't you say?
But you, you're not allowed to join
I’m sorry it's because you don't belong
The world is full of old ladies
You see!
Goto-san… Goto-san too
Go ahead and laugh at me!
You don't have to read it
It's fine
What should I read?
Anything is fine
I stayed at my boyfriend’s house yesterday
I went to work today
Oh no!
There's a kiss mark on the back of my neck
When did he do that?
Didn't you say?
He's doing it properly
-Really by the book
-Very skilled
But you!
This is because of the ticks that were on the futon at my boyfriend's house! (EN: Not 100% sure)
Too bad!
This is messed up...
The person who I fell in love with disinfected the place (EN: Not 100% sure)
This is dangerous
Can I read it?
Why you crying?
Can you tell us?
For real
That's how you do it, Goto-san, and so soon...
This face is unfair
It’s so sly
That’s how Goto-san did it!
You’re already laughing
Aren't you laughing this whole time?
What are you doing?
Do you have something against me?
You're spitting on me
When I look at my nail art
That's the rhythm
It’s the latest pattern
It’s so colorful
It stands out, right~
Let me see your fingertips more
Didn't you say?
That's so embarrassing...
But you!
The most noticeable thing is
the hangnail!
-He's laughing
-What a shame!
I heard the sound of your runny nose
-Really, Seiya?
It can’t be helped
It’s really bad, but...
This was Kato's point
Ehh, but Kato, wait...
-Isn’t he cheating?
-Kato, that's right
This needs to be judged
When I was first reading
this guy was already laughing
No, I was crying because I was sad
Whenever you think you're about to laugh
You make that face
No, no, it's because I’m sad
I have to be careful about this
But this is dangerous
This is dangerous
You can see the joke
The pages are also dangerous
I can’t see the end
Let's watch Seiya
Looking at my nail art
That's the rhythm
It’s the latest pattern
It’s so colorful
It stands out, right~
Let me see your fingertips more
Didn't you say?
That's so embarrassing
It was already out of control here
But you!
The most noticeable thing is
the hangnail!
-He's laughing
-What a shame!
At the time of “Didn't you say”
You were really getting into the rhythm
That's hilarious
-Um, is it the first time for Seiya?
-It’s my first time
-He was full-on laughing
-No, no, no, no, no
But at least I did it to myself
Pile it on
No, Matsumoto-san this is…
-Well, well, yellow
-That’s a relief
-I'll give you Yellow
-Thank you very much
And hey,
Kato you need to stop
I'm suspicious that you're running away with it
-Yeah, that's enough
-That's not fair
It's been unfair until now
Please wait a moment
Does that mean that I'm not allowed to cry?
No, no, it’s fine to cry but...
The “Frustrated” face
I'm genuinely sad (when I make that face)
When you’re about to laugh
Don't do that anymore
But when I'm about to laugh
And I suddenly feel sad
What am I supposed to do then?
What the hell does that mean?!
That doesn't happen
He’s laughing so hard
If anyone laughs with that face
-That's the worst
-It’s the worst
What is this handicap
Handicap? Handicap
Start!
Kato-san
Your teeth are amazing, too
Is it for sale?
-What’s this?
-Would you like to wear it?
No
Obviously you can't wear it
How much was it?
How much do you think?
What a trivial question...
300 yen
How much do you think? Koyabu-san
Goto did say it...
300 yen
-You're giving the same answer?
-Yeah
Aren't you adventurous?
No, it's around 300 yen
-You're okay with giving the same answer?
-Yes
Eh, you're not adventurous?
No, it’s not an adventure
I just think so
Eh, it’s odd
It really smells
-Huh?
-It smells, really
Please smell it
Would you like to wear it?
There's no way to wear it
It stinks
It stinks!
smell, smell, smell, smell
Smell it
Uwa it stinks!
-Disgusting!
-It smells!
I don’t want to
It stinks
I don't want to do this anymore...
I don't want to wear it
I'll just smell it
It stinks
Why is everyone smelling it?
-That’s enough enough
-Really
-Are you guys done?
-That's enough
So how much was it?
The price was 350 yen
Or 450 yen, I think
I don't care which
Don't chop off 50 yen
For something like that
Eh, who put this together again?
What is this, round 2?
Oh, right
I saw that someone put the boobs in again when I was there
What? Whose boobs are these?
-His turn has been going on for a long time
-Eh, that's enough...
-It’s been a really long time
-They're soft!
-His turn is so long
-I've had enough of this
It’s soft!
I wonder why is it so soft?
Koyabu-san, you had better check it out
Koyabu-san it’s soft
I’m so happy
Boobs like these
This guy who was supposed to be the salesperson before
If he’s the salesperson
I’m pretty sure he’ll touch them
I don’t know, but...
Ugh, Kitamura-san is coming
-I laughed
-Really?
-What, why?
-I didn’t notice at all
Don't switch gags in the middle
From boobs to Kitamura-san
There are 2 suspects
Was it Nobu?
No, no, no…
Koyabu and Nobu…
No, Matsumoto-san
-I think Nobu is suspicious
-I’m not suspicious at all
I’m not so sure either
Can I take a look?
Koyabu-san it’s soft
I’m so happy
This guy who was supposed to be the salesperson before
If he’s the salesperson
I’m pretty sure he’ll touch them
I don’t know, but...
Ugh, Kitamura-san is coming
Ah, Nobu-san
-It’s Nobu?
-I’m safe
It’s definitely Nobu
I already have one
Nobu
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
For Koyabu, let's say he was safe
Really??
Thank you very much
Wow, amazing
With that Kitamura-san crap
-What's the point?
-Oh man, this is dangerous
That's dangerous
Everyone is following Kato's pace
-You're right
It’s dangerous it’s dangerous…
You're so persistent, Kato
-Kato's persistent
Very persistent!
Persistent, persistent
Oh my God
This is really bad
-Tamura-san
-I have an orange card
-I have an orange card too
-Who else has an orange card?
-Ahh, three people
-Orange card?
-Orange card. There are 3 of us.
-I'm out of here
Wow, so fast
Seiya has a yellow card?
-I also have a yellow card
-Oh, yellow?
-I have 0 cards
-Zero, zero, zero
The people who have 0 cards are dangerous
Koyabu-san was laughing too
No, that was close
Nobu was first
I’m sorry, that’s right
Nobu, don't you feel that way?
It’s dangerous
Start!
Okay, well...
Are you hungry?
I’m hungry
I heard there's something on the way
-Yes, it is
-Something's coming
May I?
Hmm…It's still early in the game
100% Akira exaggerated
Easy type
-Yes, yes, yes
-Easy type
Hiya hiya
Did it get chilly? (EN: might be "Did it get lame?")
Did it get chilly?
Hiya Hiya Hiya Hiya
This one that doesn’t have a mosaic
Hiya Hiya
Did it get chilly?
-It's so insanely erected
-Hiya Hiya
-Bin bin
-His balls are so huge
Bin bin
Hiya Hiya
Did it get chilly?
It’s hitting his navel/belly button
It’s a penis
What are you talking about?
-Penis
-That's how people from the country say it
The lid hitting the floor is loud
-Yeah, it’s surprising, isn't it?
-The lid hitting the floor is loud
Did it get chilly?
Hiya Hiya
The sound scares me
Dangerous
Do you want to eat something?
-Delivery
-What’s the deal with delivery?
What?
Goto Kazutoyo Jiro
Miyasako Zakoshi are untouched
Surprisingly, Goto is doing well
-What’s the matter?
-What’s wrong?
The menu?
What’s wrong?
It came?
Goto-san, what happened
Goto-san, did it come?
-Nobu, check it out
-Nobu
-No, no…
I’m hungry
No, I’m fine
I’m serious
I’m serious. I’m serious. I'm serious
Seriously!
Wait a moment
-Wait a second!
-What the hell is that?!
What's with that face?
Wait a second
You shouldn't make that face
There are so many kinds of paella
Look here
You can't be serious
Opening this...
Paella has so many types
I'd like to try some paella
Tamura
Want to see it together?
Why?! Why?
You can see it alone!
Why?!
-Please
-Why?
I saw it
There were quite a lot of options
Because you’re in the restaurant industry
I want you to see it with your own eyes
In that case, Michio has to come too
-Alright, Michio too
-Alright
Let's see it as the Orange-Army
Come on
We can take it
-Let's see what it is
-Yes
Ready go!
Ahh, the menu
This topping
Something's there
The delivery came?
-The meal?
-Yes
Did anyone ask for this?
If my memory is right...
Today’s special is!
This
-Great, but
-Oh…
We've got a new delivery!
If my memory is right...
Today’s special is!
This... on a penis
-Yeah, okay, okay…
-It didn’t have any hair before
-Nobu Nobu Nobu Nobu Nobu
-I heard “Kuk”
-Nobu
It didn’t have hair before
In between all of this
In the last little while, the hair grew back
A-Damo-chan
What would you like
No, really
I’m a little hungry
Maybe a croissant or something
Ahh, bread
But something like that
I can make an omelet
Eh, I don't like anything from Michio-san
Your omelet,
I really don't want to eat it
That’s right
Here comes a new one
That’s enough
Today’s special is!
Just a penis here
He totally just laughed
Give me a break, this is crazy
He laughed completely
Oh my God, how can you laugh so beautifully?
But, already...
It was bound to happen, wasn't it?
You've seen it so many times
Isn’t it funny?
It’s funny
When he was saying "choo choo"
he was already holding his laugh
Here comes a new one
That’s enough
Today’s special is!
Just a penis here
-There is no Adamo
-He shattered
This is completely Zakoshi's point
-So quick
-Eh Nobu...
OUT!
Eh, he's out?!
This is funny, right?
That is dangerous
What the hell were you thinking
when you made that
Come on, Nobu
I didn't put out anything
Yeah
First, again
-You didn't get to do anything
-I didn't get to do anything
-We still have zombies
-Zombies, yeah
-I’ll be back
-Yes, as a zombie
-Let’s go Nobu
-Yes
-Try your best
-Good luck
Shit
I did it again...
I was first again...
That's it
I don’t understand
Kato-san
Koyabu-san it’s soft
I’m so happy
Boobs like these
Normally, if you're talking about boobs...
That's where the joke stays
Suddenly the topic changed to Kitamura-san
Ugh, Kitamura-san is coming
He's funny
There's a possibility that he might win