THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
FINAL EPISODE
Hi. I'm Hollywood Zakoshisyoh.
I'm aware I'm what you'd call
an offensive player.
But!
Eiichiro Funakoshi betrayed me!
He uses Viagra!
He has a penis sticker!
Hi, I'm Chihara Junior.
For a comedian,
when there's no laughter for so long,
it gets really, seriously depressing.
I'm about to come.
You have to convince yourself.
"I'm okay. I'm funny."
"Somebody's laughing somewhere."
There's nothing you can do but
believe in yourself and just keep going.
And I laugh so easily.
POST-FILMING INTERVIEW
-It's done.
-It was exhausting even just to watch.
-It was.
I think this season had
quite a few highlights.
Everyone tried so hard.
We really couldn't have asked for more.
OFFENSE HIGHLIGHTS:
CHIHARA JUNIOR
I have to touch my eye?
OFFENSE HIGHLIGHTS:
HOLLYWOOD ZAKOSHISYOH
Hey! Wait a minute!
OFFENSE HIGHLIGHTS:
JUNIOR & ZAKOSHISYOH
ATTACK POINTS SO FAR
HOLLYWOOD ZAKOSHISYOH: 5
CHIHARA JUNIOR: 3
Just you and me, doing something together.
This is a first, isn't it?
Right.
I couldn't be happier.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Okay, I see.
I'll be right back.
This is an over-exaggerated Akira 100%!
Did you get sweaty palms?
Sweaty palms.
This sure is funny.
That's a funny sight.
Keep it up.
Imagine watching it so close up.
Did you get sweaty palms?
Sweaty palms.
Good, good.
He endured it.
You don't know much about games,
do you, Junior?
-No, I don't.
-You don't play.
-You mean video games?
-Yes.
That rules out video game impressions.
-You made a list?
-I did.
-You have so many.
-I do.
How about Toshi-chan?
Want to see my Toshi-chan?
-Out of all these, you'll do him?
-Yes, Toshi-chan.
Here I go. Junior, look.
I'm Toshi-chan!
Toshi-chan!
What are you gonna do, Toshi-chan?
Hey, Toshi-chan...
I'll do an Ikko impersonation. Ikko.
-You don't say her catch phrase?
-I don't.
-You don't say it?
You don't say it?
Is there a version where you do say it?
No.
Time for the zombies.
Here come the zombies.
There's someone
I'd really like you to meet.
Who?
Someone I'd like to--
-Okay.
-Really?
-You don't mind?
-Well, okay.
But we are a little busy.
Please sit.
There's someone I'd like you to meet.
-Okay.
-Will you sit down?
-Sit here?
-Yes.
We're a little busy.
-Yeah, we are busy.
-I'm sorry about that.
But I think you'll be happy to meet them.
-We'll be happy?
-So it's someone we know?
I think you know them.
Please come in.
-Do you know who it is?
-No.
Yes, you do.
No, I don't.
I'm sure you do.
He looks very angry.
He scares me.
You must know him.
-I don't!
-I have no clue.
It's Teru from Joto High School!
Give me everything you've got!
Give me your underwear!
-I'm Teru!
-It's really--
If you have a problem,
come see me at Joto High!
Got it?
It's really that Teru.
He's wearing gangster pants!
Give me those jeans!
The mic's stuck.
His shoes...
He's laughing.
Because it got stuck?
No, I was just thinking...
How clumsy can you get?
-It's all Takahashi's fault.
-That was a little difficult to judge.
Junior is definitely out.
However, there's still time on the clock.
And since it was a zombie
that made Junior laugh,
Zakoshi has to endure zombie attacks alone
until the time is up.
-What?
-I see.
If he laughs, there'll be no winner.
Damn.
-But that's only 30 minutes more?
-Right. 30 minutes.
Anyway, Junior is eliminated.
What made you laugh?
It was such a clumsy effort.
The mic's stuck.
His shoes...
The cord was pulled tight.
Let's go, Junior.
-Thank you.
-You almost lost it in the first half.
-Yeah. I was in real trouble.
I thought I'd be kicked out
in 20 or 30 minutes.
"A gum-like substance came out."
Hello.
I'm Junichiro Koizumi.
Junior...
Zakoshi is just too strong.
Na, ka, ta. Nakata
He's too strong?
He's strong.
I did it.
I'm the only one left.
Come on, zombies!
Come on!
Bring it on!
Okay, let's go.
A half hour of Zombie Time?
That'll be super hard.
All I can do is, "Not laugh."
Come in.
Lie down over there. The open space.
Sorry about the mess.
-You been here before?
-Yes, about six months ago.
-You're a regular.
-But the location changed.
New location. We have a new owner.
We have a new owner.
Lie down here.
Here, mister.
Were you having sushi?
We were having a Chinese New Year party.
Lie down there.
Did you lose weight?
You think so? Thank you.
Are you busy with work?
Do I lie down on my stomach?
Yes, on your stomach.
Here?
-You lost a lot of weight.
-Really?
-You must be tired.
-Yes.
-Where do you feel most tired?
-Well...
Around my lower back.
Here?
The area around my hip.
Is it raining outside?
-You don't know what the weather's like?
-I don't. I'm always inside.
Okay. Let's do the oil massage.
You'll feel so good, mister.
It's a special deal.
All of our girls are so good. Lily, Lulu.
All of them are so cute.
Lily is from Dalian.
-Dalian.
-Lulu is...
Lulu is from Shanghai.
They're so cute.
Are you his friend, mister?
We're friends.
It feels tight here.
Thank you very much, mister.
That's all.
But...
Give me the VIP Treatment, please.
Get on your back.
Is it cold outside?
Actually, it's warm outside today.
We don't have many girls now.
It's February.
Everyone goes home for Chinese New Year.
All right.
Here we go.
Mister.
-You have muscles. You must work out.
-Thank you.
-You work out.
Do you have a girlfriend?
-I don't.
-No?
He has a wife though.
-You're married?
-Yes.
-No fooling around, then.
-I can't.
-You can't come to my parlor.
He comes a lot.
-Don't get ticklish.
-Sorry.
Here we go, mister.
Your lymph nodes.
Lymphatic massage for lymph nodes.
Lymphatic massages
are the ones that feel the best.
Lymphatic massages feel the best.
You don't have any hair here.
It's a long story.
You must fool around!
One thing led to another and I lost it.
You have no hair. You must fool around.
Okay.
There you go.
Okay. Thank you.
The VIP Treatment has a higher level.
"Best VIP Treatment."
-I'll have that, please.
-Okay.
Thank you, mister.
Best VIP Treatment.
This one feels the best.
-It makes you feel the best.
-What idiots.
The lymphatic massage treatment.
Mister is having the lymphatic massage.
-Total idiots.
-Lymphatic massage...
Stop moaning. Stay still!
Sorry.
Stop moving. You make me jump.
The lymphatic massage treatment.
Mister.
Intense lymphatic massage.
-How embarrassing.
-Zakoshi...
Have you been to our parlor in Tamachi?
I've never been there.
-We have a new owner.
-Is that so?
I've been to the one in Shimbashi.
First-time customers
can make an appointment on the phone.
First-timers must call.
But the second time,
I can give private massages.
VIP Treatment.
Tickle, tickle.
The lymphatic massage treatment.
Thank you, mister. Well done.
Don't touch there!
You need "VIP Touch Treatment"
to touch me.
"VIP Touch" to touch.
-You want to touch?
-Yes.
Only touch here.
This special treatment feels good, mister.
The best one is "VIP Propeller Treatment."
Propeller treatment.
VIP Propeller Treatment.
Now let's rotate the other way.
I like it that way.
-This way?
-Yes.
The feel-good massage.
The best feel-good massage.
Wait, wait.
It feels the best.
This is no time to laugh.
-That's all.
-Can he have a turn now?
I see. That's the strategy.
Really?
That may be a good idea. I see.
This will be tough.
This will certainly be tough.
Him too?
It's his first time.
This could be the climax.
It's your first time? Let's take this off.
Just lay down, mister.
Like this.
Where do you feel tight?
-My neck.
-Your neck? Okay.
Mister, you want VIP Treatment?
-Yes, thanks.
-Okay.
Okay, on your stomach.
You mean on my back.
Yes, on your back.
Okay, the feel-good massage.
You have a big belly!
You must eat a lot.
Look at you.
What have you been eating?
It stinks.
No, it doesn't.
VIP Treatment.
The VIP Treatment starts now.
Lymphatic massage.
Lift up your legs.
That's right.
The lymphatic massage.
The lymphatic massage treatment.
Mister, this is the lymphatic massage.
Lymphatic massage treatment, mister.
There, mister.
Why move like that?
You look like a cockroach!
Is the shower working?
No?
The shower...
Is he laughing?
Is that him laughing?
Okay.
This is the last step.
Where are you touching? Hurry up.
When I touch here, we're done.
And that's it.
That's the end, mister.
Do the rest yourself. That's the end.
-Thank you. Now take a shower.
-Thanks.
-Did that feel good?
-It did.
Our parlor is more fun when you come
with your friends.
-Take a shower, okay?
-Yes.
Aren't you done with the shower yet?
What if they massaged Jimmy?
I kind of want to see that.
Go, mister.
Are you done? He feels better.
-How was it?
-It felt good.
Are you meeting with friends?
Yes, we have to go.
I'd like a massage too.
Me too, please.
Do you have an appointment?
I made one just a while ago.
-Do you mind if I watch?
-Is that okay?
Excuse me.
Wait a minute.
Singa-pole.
-Can I have a massage?
-Sure.
Interesting thing you've got there.
You.
Should I take my clothes off,
or just go like this?
It's fine just like that, mister.
You're such good friends,
staying for so long.
Right.
Ready, mister?
Straight to VIP Treatment?
-VIP Treatment?
-VIP, please.
VIP Treatment. This is in the way.
Should I take it off?
What should I do with Singa-pole?
What will you do?
I'll leave it to you, ma'am.
What should I do?
The Singa-pole is funny. Leave it on.
I should leave it on? My Singa-pole.
Okay.
The lymphatic massage first.
It's not funny.
There is nothing dirty going on here.
Okay.
Macau!
Macau?
Mac... Macau.
Macau! Macau!
Is that Macau?
Ma... Macau! Macau!
Ma'am!
Ma'am! Wait! Please!
You'll make me come! Ma'am!
Stop! Ma'am! Seriously, stop!
You're seriously making me come!
Seriously! Ma'am...
Stop! Seriously!
I can't come here!
Ma'am, I'll come!
Shut up! You talk too much.
I'm sorry. Hey, ma'am! Don't--
-Singa-pole!
Zakoshi is amazing.
I'm coming!
I'll come, Ma'am!
Ma'am...
-I can't hold it.
-If you want to come, do it yourself.
Okay, thank you. Take a shower.
Thank you.
-I'll go home now.
-Unbelievable.
That was unbelievable.
No shower?
-You don't want a shower?
-Well, a shower...
That was close.
Sorry. Can I come in?
Well...
I have a friend.
He performs kabuki,
but someone stole his costume.
What? That's terrible.
And we're looking for it.
Can we look here?
-Sure.
-It's okay?
It's okay! Come in!
KENJI TAMURA'S HELPER
BIYORI MORIYA
You need it, right?
-What does it look like?
-It's for my name-taking ceremony.
-Your big ceremony is today?
-Yes.
-But your costume's gone?
This is not good.
My son's making his debut today too.
-That's a big deal.
-He lost his underwear too?
Is this it?
No, it's not.
This is bad.
I didn't take it.
-Really?
-Yeah.
They're filming a documentary
about me for Jounetsu Tairiku.
So what? I didn't take it.
Look all you like.
We're not accusing you of stealing it.
Is that a wart?
Excuse me.
He has a huge wart.
-Excuse me.
-It's a huge wart.
-I found these shoes.
-But they're not for my stage.
We found them!
But I'm still missing everything else.
-Thanks.
-Are they yours?
I'll wear these for now.
-For some reason...
-Can he tap dance?
For some reason, these shoes...
They fit me really well.
He has many hobbies.
I wish I'd taken tap dancing lessons.
He didn't take lessons?
The shoes fit perfectly, but...
-I wish I'd taken lessons.
-But it looked like he did.
-He's a kabuki performer.
-Really?
-When would he tap dance?
-Well...
Do they tap dance
while striking kabuki poses?
-You have a point.
-Try it.
Hey...
I wish I'd taken tap dancing lessons.
What do you think?
He should take lessons.
He has a wart.
Take a look.
What the hell?
-Where?
-A wart.
-Here.
-Where?
-Here!
-It's a wart!
Where?
Here. Right here. It's a wart.
-Take a look.
-I did.
Thanks.
He doesn't laugh.
-Have that wart taken care of.
-Seriously.
Ten minutes to go.
There's not much time left.
It's like I said.
-Him again?
-You should just stay retired.
I want to fight.
Your punches aren't as powerful as before.
I think you should quit.
I want one more chance.
-Check his...
-Should I sit?
I'll sit.
Check his body punches.
I took a few earlier, but they're not
the same as they were in his prime.
I'm sure they're less powerful, but...
Let's go.
-He's done.
-He's weaker, right?
He's far from being in his prime.
Why do this butt naked?
He's not even close.
-He's weaker?
-Much weaker than before.
If you aren't powerful enough
to knock him down...
He's much weaker indeed.
-Me too? Don't do it.
-One, two, three.
-You're too weak to even knock him down.
-Well, that won't make him laugh.
I pooped my pants.
Of course, that won't make him laugh.
Is he a pro?
Yes.
His punches hurt.
-He has world titles in three divisions.
-But that really hurt.
Don't you know him?
-Who is he?
-He doesn't know?
He doesn't know Hozumi Hasegawa?
Really?
-Hello.
-I'm Hasegawa.
Nice to meet you.
-I don't watch boxing much.
-Let's talk backstage.
What's this?
I'm Miko.
Timotei, Timotei
He almost lost it there.
So, there's hardly any time left.
Is some kind of accident
the only thing that might get him?
-Bring it on.
-Yeah.
Come on, zombies!
No one's coming?
What's he doing?
-What's all the racket?
-That's scary.
-I hear a lot of noise.
-Scary.
You're too noisy.
There are limits to things, you know.
You know?
There are limits.
What's all this noise?
Well, yeah,
I think I should get him for that.
Well, I'll just give you an orange card
for that.
-He got you a little.
-Yes.
At this stage in the game...
This is...
That's creepy.
-So creepy.
-That is scary.
You're too noisy.
There are limits to things, you know.
There are limits.
Okay.
-You get an orange.
-Okay.
Five minutes to go.
Okay. Akiyama, let's go.
This is not good.
What's he doing?
What the hell?
I'm Miko.
I came from city hall.
I work at city hall,
in the game department.
Okay.
My social media handle is
JJ.
JJ?
I'm Miko.
You're Miko.
Please call me again.
Okay.
-I'm Miko.
-Okay.
-Well...
-Thank you.
-There's no time.
-It was a pleasure.
They're running out of time.
But if they're ready to attack, go for it.
We're down to the last three minutes.
That was close!
-Akiyama, can you go?
-Or Jimmy.
One minute.
They want to make him laugh somehow.
They're trying, but...
Hey.
Why don't you try laughing?
-What?
-Why don't you laugh?
I did.
-Laugh more.
-I already did.
-You usually laugh so easily.
-I laughed.
Laugh.
I did.
What was that?
Is he smiling a little?
My kneecaps!
You'll break my kneecaps!
Laugh.
My knees will break.
Eat the sushi.
It's all dried up.
-I did.
-One more.
-One more?
-Yeah.
Keep eating.
We'll be back!
This is the final stretch.
Miko. I'm Miko.
You really are too noisy.
I'm Miko.
Right?
Show more consideration
for the people around you.
This really is creepy.
-Are you listening?
-No, no. I'm Miko.
Miko.
You really need to start using your head.
So, it's almost over. Almost.
-Here we go.
-Please.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six, five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
It's over!
Is it over?
It is.
It's all over!
-I held out!
-You did!
I did!
-Zakoshi is the champion!
-Thank you!
-He's strong.
He really did it!
Thank you!
When he came at the end,
I didn't know if I could take it anymore.
Well, that was truly amazing.
Well done!
Thank you!
I did it! Thank you!
-Thank you!
-He was the strongest.
He was.
-It was indisputable.
-Really?
-Indisputable.
-Thanks.
You were too strong.
Look! This is 10 million yen.
Amazing. It's twice the amount
of the R-1 prize money.
When did you come closest to laughing?
Well, I did laugh.
Zombie Akiyama was funny.
There are limits to things, you know.
Who wouldn't laugh at that?
The other thing was
the toy Eikoh Kano brought.
What the hell are you doin'?
It's a tag match!
That came really close.
That was...
Right? It repeats everything.
So, I'm the fourth champion?
That's right.
The first season had no winner.
-Right?
-Yes.
Oh, yeah!
All right!
This is 10 million yen!
But please,
don't break into my house or anything.
Like Topreed. Don't do it.
What can I say? Well, it was indisputable.
Did you get sweaty palms?
As the show nears the end,
you want the survivors to laugh
even more and more.
It's a funny thing.
-He was good at both offense and defense.
-Right.
-He just wouldn't laugh.
-He wouldn't laugh.
Well...
We had the former world boxing champion
Hozumi Hasegawa,
but he had no idea who he was.
That lack of knowledge...
That was quite unexpected.
He must have been thinking,
"Who is this guy?"
But even so,
he was always on the offensive.
I think he's a true champion,
without doubt.