Translated by kentranslations
Timed/Edited by blakeo_x
I'm sure this thing will escalate.
Are we gonna be alright?
What's really the point of staying still?
Tarantulas...
Those are a no-go for me.
Thinking about it, that was an
abuse of power by Hitoshi Matsumoto.
If I go to the finals...
I don't think it'll be
about winning or losing.
Rather, it's gonna be about
being as still as possible.
And I've evolved throughout
all the different battles.
I can feel Matsumoto's
philosophy in play here.
I'm using my five senses to
the fullest, but that's what's hard.
I have to use them to the fullest, but at
the same time I'm forced to shut them out.
I didn't realize how funny
"non-reactions" could be.
I was so happy when I
won the consolation match.
And I could be
representing the celebrities.
So I wanted to show them
how amazing we celebrities are.
I think I'm stronger when it
comes to pain endurance.
I'm here!
Who are you again?
I'm Kuro-chan!
You know me, don't you?
- Aren't you Bobby?
- I'm not Bobby!
I won the consolation match.
What did you guys do?
I won't tell you. That might
give you an advantage.
I'm gonna fight to the death.
- That scared me!
- Alright, everyone!
We're finally here.
Yes.
Everything will be decided here.
Who will win the 1 million yen?
- He looks so happy.
- For real.
Don't you hate him for that?
You're right, he's the ultimate sadist.
Kuro-chan climbed all the way back here.
And the other two are undeniably strong.
We're just freezing in place.
But you know, everyone
else failed at that.
That's right.
I can't even imagine how
this match will turn out.
But this is the final stage.
- Let's go!
- Yes! I'll do my best!
I won't lose!
I definitely won't lose.
- I mean, that's good and all...
- But you know...
We lived through the turbulent Showa era.
So we learned to bear it all.
It's a bit different from today.
I won't be fazed by anything either.
Anyways, this room is super small.
- You're right.
- It's so small.
Even so, you have to endure it.
Alright, it's about time to start.
Everyone looks really tough.
But, Kuro-chan is not as
weak as you might think.
He's pretty strong.
But will he overcome these two?
I'm kinda hoping Kuro-chan
ends up being a dark horse.
It all depends on how he does here.
Right, let's go.
The pressure is starting to rise.
And here it comes.
I would hate this.
I would really hate this.
I really loathe this.
With this challenge,
the faces and reactions
will be a bit hard to see.
Isn't this great?
Diamond Yukai isn't even
blinking despite the situation.
This thing will keep growing.
That's good, that's great.
Everyone, make sure to pay
attention. Don't miss the moment it pops.
There should be some sudden reactions.
Will they still be able to breathe?
Yukai still has some room left.
Kuro-chan must be suffering right now.
Hang on, Morohoshi might be in trouble.
He doesn't look ok anymore.
Morohoshi has lost all ability to move.
Morohoshi has...
Yukai didn't move at all!
That hairstyle!
None of them laughed?!
They aren't even smiling.
- That was an amazing match.
- Hold on...
What was that?!
That was impressive.
Whoa! My eyes hurt.
His eyes hurt?
This...
Yukai...
I mean, there was no place to run!
- Hold on!
- That was so good!
That was good?
- What was good about it?
- It was an impressive match.
- That was good?
- Do you want to see the replay of this one?
- Yes, I wanna see.
- Let's look at the replay then.
Diamond Yukai wasn't
even closing his eyes.
Amazing.
- That was amazing.
- Really?
How were your eyes open that whole time?
Your face was all smushed.
Yet you kept your eyes open.
The battle of the open eyes! Amazing!
I thought I was gonna die.
It was suffocating.
That first one was really
something I didn't expect.
That was so scary.
I couldn't see anymore.
You know, I'm not that good at this.
I don't have any
experience with these things.
I mean, things exploding and all that.
It's never happened to me.
Let's go to the next one!
- Is there more?
- More?!
Hold on, that one was pretty intense.
Right?
It was scary too.
Yes, so why didn't you close your eyes?
I mean, we're supposed
to freeze. Like this.
Even there?
- Here we go!
- Hold on...
The mighty Diamond Yukai...
However, it may be that Yukai was
just well fit for the balloon challenge.
He might be weak in our next challenge.
How will they deal with this?
Alright.
Of course, they're
fighting with all they've got...
But they won't hurt the guys around them.
They won't point the bamboo
swords towards our guys.
However...
Getting hit in these close
quarters is inevitable.
-- is inevitable.
Yukai is amazing. Look at him.
And Kuro-chan as well.
Morohoshi fell down.
Alright, this is awesome.
This is amazing!
Okay.
Let's get them back for now.
Let's get them back.
Bow.
What?!
That hurt!
- What the heck was that?!
- Did you fall?
They pushed and kicked me!
They were crashing into me too.
- That's so dangerous!
- It is.
- What was that?
- They bumped you, right?
- What the heck was that?
- What?
Wonderful!
- Wonderful?
- Yes, wonderful.
Why did you fall? I missed it.
One of the guys tripped on my foot.
Let's take a look at the replay.
He got caught! See?!
I wonder about that...
But the fact that you didn't move
afterwards is a plus in my eyes.
Thank you.
I didn't fall on my own.
The Kendo guy got stuck on my foot.
- Is that so?
- He got stuck and pulled on me, so I fell.
I didn't move.
That was pretty suspicious.
I didn't say anything at the time...
But really, I think he fell on his own.
Right, let's continue.
Yukai has completely
gone into his own world.
"I'm going to another planet now."
Or something like that.
Something unexpected might happen here.
Yukai is amazing.
Kuro-chan is also great.
They're flying, they're flying.
Whoa, they're really flying.
They're going pretty high.
They must be hot.
They've gotta be really hot.
They must hate this.
Don't you think Kuro-chan's
expression has changed?
It seems like Kuro-chan doesn't like this.
Morohoshi just got hit in the leg.
He flinched a bit, right?
It must be hot.
That one hit him right
between the rips in his jeans.
I totally saw him moving his leg.
Oh, it hit his arm! It's hot!
Hot!
That must hurt!
I would totally hate this.
After all, popcorn only flies
when it's really hot, right?
We could also go right back
to kendo without releasing.
Should I do it? Okay.
Yukai is awesome.
Alright, what's gonna happen?
That hit him!
Okay, let's get them back.
Have them come back. Okay.
That hurt!
- It was so hot!
- What hit me?!
That was amazing! It was super hot!
Morohoshi just got hit in the leg.
He flinched a bit, right?
It's so hot and itchy.
Why are you clapping?
What are the claps for?
- It's over!
- What?! We're done?!
It's over!
- It's over!
- Good job, everyone!
Kuro-chan, did it hurt when
the popcorn landed on your arm?
It was super hot!
Alright, how is everyone
feeling about their odds?
I have no clue...
Well, I think I was able to
focus towards the later half.
Ah, I see.
That hit him!
What about you, Yukai?
I think I did my best.
Alright!
Now, let me announce the winner.
Please!
The winner is...
Diamond Yukai!
He's amazing.
Wonderful!
He's really good, it's so unfair!
He really was amazing.
I was worried I wouldn't
be able to pick a winner.
But there was a clear winner.
Is that so?
He didn't move an inch.
He didn't even move with the balloon.
Right, the balloon.
The whole time, I was
just trying not to think.
I'm glad I did my best.
Matsumoto, thank you.
We will give Yukai the 1
million yen! Congratulations!
Congratulations!
Yukai is amazing!
Thank you!
Would you compete again if
we ever did a second season?
I don't know about that...
This show...
It's pretty intense!
I mean, of course I'm happy.
But I had to walk through fire and flames.
I think my mind took a bigger hit.
I've never seen that
many snakes in one place.
It's so extreme.
I hope it was entertaining.
And I think it'll spread worldwide.
The prize is 1 million yen.
Alright!
Congratulations.
I'm a father of three...
So I was thinking of them the whole time.
I think that's what got
me over the finish line.
- Thanks for your hard work.
- Thank you.
That was amazing.
Really amazing.
I mean, everyone has a weakness.
But in the end, with Morohoshi and Yukai
I honestly couldn't find theirs.
Yukai sure is a strange guy.
Diamond Yukai is hilarious.
He's that funny without moving.
And he probably thinks he's so boring.
But that's also part
of what makes it funny.
You know, the tarantula...
Kuro-chan didn't move at all.
That huge tarantula was crawling
around his ear and he didn't move at all.
I think that was quite amazing.
And even he couldn't win
against the mighty Diamond Yukai.
That's quite something.
That guy is quite something.
He seems like a good guy.
But...
I wonder if his personal life is okay.
Translated by kentranslations
Timed/Edited by blakeo_x