The first Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!! Chiki Chiki!
Bet Your Life on One Mouthful - 100,000 Yen Prize Contest:
Kiki - Chili Oil!
This is the 34th episode.
Pretty impressive, right?
We've ALWAYS used that same backdrop.
That's true...
The person who drew it might not be even alive anymore!
So this time, Yamazaki's filled with confidence.
"It's chili oil, shouldn't this go well?" he says...
Isn't this really hard?
It is hard!
No, look at these...
They're completely, you know...
Well, the appearance is different.
So say it here! Blabbering mindlessly before the title call...
He pissed off people before the cameras started rolling.
Actually...
My confidence is crumbling!
So, how shall we begin?
What should we do?
Hamada, couldn't you start?
Should I go? Okay, so let us start!
Kiki - Chili Oil.
First, the one holding the best
success-rate, a six time winner, Hamada.
First item comes from restaurants of Nagoya,
Kaburaya Group's "Daruma Chili Oil".
The sample comes like this...
This time it's just the oil.
What!? Are you kidding? So that's why...
No, no, no, no, no...
Earlier, there were various chips in it,
like garlic chips or something...
But now, they have been removed.
In one spoonful, there's just oil.
There's only that.
You must savour it.
You're nose is already in it, you idiot...
It's totally on your nose!
Sorry, sorry...
This isn't "Nose Oil"...
I can't see like this, so...
This isn't "Nose Oil", you know...
I guess so...
Even from the midst of darkness, he retorts.
Ah, he ate it!
Here we go...
Uwa, what's up with this?
This is just plain oil!
Who the hell could remember this!?
This is what you have to guess.
Where should I start with all these?
It was just oil!
It's hard, isn't it?
Well, for now... I'll start with Momoya.
Speaking of them...
Well, Momoya, you know, really...
They've been on the dinner tables for decades...
We have been in their care, right?
It starts here...
How is it?
Ah - this isn't it!
He can tell it...
I feel like it wasn't this spicy.
Also, the saltiness... and there wasn't
much of a smell so this must not be it.
The oil I ate...
Momoya's...
"Seems strong, but isn't; Mildly Strong Chili Oil"
WAS NOT IT!
So you can tell the difference?
Yes.
It's just that when Hamada said "This isn't it!",
could you stop going like
"Huh!? He can tell it!?"
That was unforgivable.
Eh - did I really...
You TOTALLY said it.
"He can tell it..." you said.
Really... I was also surprised...
"What's up with that reaction?" I thought.
This is the 34th episode!
After this, he continues to seperate the tastes
and easily clears two in a row!
...Okinawa Chili Oil" WAS IT!
Oops... WASN'T IT!
No, that was out, wasn't it?
What's up with you!?
He was fooling around with the "was not it" from the start!
And then he fumbled with his words, what a pathetic conclusion.
He had so many still left...
I'll go from this end.
Ochanokosaisai's "Maiko-han Hii Hii Chili Oil".
Maiko is an apprentice geisha.
Would maiko serve that?
So I guess you aren't a maiko?
Strrrong!
"Strrrong!"
The oil I ate, Ochanokosaisai's "Maiko-han Hii Hii Chili Oil" WAS NOT IT!
That's four cleared.
Could I have some water?
Was it that strong?
Strong, strong.
Well there must be few strong ones among those.
Must be, right?
Woah, this one is also Ochanokosaisai!
The same one?
Yeah, the manufacturer.
STRRRONG!
I shouldn't have eaten these!
Was it really that strong?
You'd want to eat it with rice...
SHARRRAP!
"Sharrap!" he says...
"Sharrap!"
"SHARRAP!"
...is what he said.
When you'd want to make the horse accelerate...
...a command or something.
A horse would run so fast!
This one isn't that hot, but at the end it lacks
that kind of an "escaping" feeling...
We have no idea what you're talking about.
I guess so.
THIS ISN'T IT!!
The final "escape" isn't there!
He's really emotionally unstable.
The oil I ate, Ochanokosaisai "Kyou Chili Oil" WAS NOT IT!
That one, too...
A sign of the male menopause...
Emotional unstability!
Chikuzen Tanaka Aburaya.
Oh? It didn't smell like this...
This is close.
REALLY close...
I wish it would have that "escaping" feeling, though...
H- He's just making faces!
Stop fooling around!
He's trying out all sorts of things, isn't he?
Ah, just what should I do? What should I do?
Is this it?
I can't drink any more oil than this!
You don't have to drink, just licking should be fine.
No, when you'll do this you'll understand.
All those strong ones will get to your throat.
They're so strong.
Which one is it?
You wanna to stop or keep going?
It's all right, sorry for taking so long.
I'll go with this!
I'm pretty sure this is it.
This... lack of taste.
The oil I ate...
Chikuzen Tanaka Aburaya....
"Ah! Hot Chili Oil!",
WAS THIS!
Come!
Please... I beg...
Seriously?
A foreigner...
This is scary! Scary!
A machine!
Where should I stand? Here?
Setting up the chili oil...
Should I roll the apron?
You damned TOAD!
Toad?
Looks painful...
A toad?
A toad!
"Daruma Chili Oil"?
So, you see...
"Daruma Chili Oil"
You didn't come by it.
Isn't this the worst pattern?
It is the worst.
This isn't it.
That's one evil looking face!
The second challenger is Tanaka.
His goal is Chikuzen Tanaka Aburaya's "Ah! Hot Chili Oil".
Why did we have to something this difficult?
Right, but if we added the chips...
Woah, this is much more oil-like than I expected!
Do you usually eat chili oil?
Usually, I put it in gyouza, but...
What?
"But..." what?
So, who hit you just now?
Hamada.
Well, that's correct.
When hit, he gives an instant answer.
Hamada insisted that this was really strong...
This "Hii Hii Chili Oil".
I'd like to try this one.
The smell is different.
I think I can tell even without eating.
His face looks odd...
The smell is different!
His "drama" face.
His "acting" face.
Like he's reading his lines.
Strong! The flavor is different.
The oil I ate... "Maiko-han Hii Hii Chili Oil" WAS NOT IT!
Seemed pretty strong...
Yes! It was ridiculously strong.
Momoya's "Seems strong, but isn't; Mildly Strong Chili Oil" WAS NOT IT!
Trusting on the sample's flavor, he tells them apart splendidly!
Four successive clears!
I'm trying to pinpoint them, but...
...still not hitting it?
Ochanokosaisai's another one, here I go.
"Kyou Chili Oil".
Not bad.
The smell...
It's close.
I can't tell his feelings anymore...
It's a one man play.
Aoyama Amphitheather.
But I still can't get what he's trying to express.
His tickets aren't selling at all, it seems.
Because it's so hard to tell!
Seriously, what's up with you?
That's not it.
EXACTLY...
...the same amount of spiciness.
No doubt.
The oil I ate...
"Kyouto"...
"Kyou Chili Oil" WAS THIS!
You had no doubts, huh?
I thought that was it!
Is that so?
So I thought that Tanaka was amazing! But that wasnt it, right?
Wrong, wrong, wrong.
I thought he really hit it!
Are you kidding?
Scary...
Your hair...
...is greasier than chili oil!
That was dangerous!
Try eating that one, the correct answer.
I thought Tanaka totally had it...
So it was the third one!
No, it's different....
But you had absolutely no noubts, right?
I had not, when I picked this.
Impossible!
Hopeless!
Without chips, it's impossible!
Put the chips in! Chips!
That's not possible. Not happening!
Next one is Housei, who hasn't guessed right in nine years.
The target is Asahi "Gudakusan Okinawa Chili Oil".
Among us, I think I'm the one eating the most.
Ah, you mean chili oil?
It seems like you've been really hooked on that stuff.
Oh? What's that?
Isn't that Ijirii Okada?
A comedian, best known for being the MC of Gilgamesh Night
Fast!
You're ripping him off, aren't you?
I really like it and eat it all the time, but...
I... really think it's this one.
So you already have this in your fridge?
You already ate it?
Yes.
Can I go for it?
Are you serious?
I'm sorry.
This is it!
Is it really alright?  Like the footage and stuff...
But it's fine, right? If I'll say it's "wrong" on purpose...
It's alright? Well then, this time..
I'll bring this.
Thank you very much!
The oil I ate...
Momoya's "Seems strong, but isn't; Mildly Strong Chili Oil".
WAS THIS!
Techno boy. Techno child.
Not cool.
This time, no paycheck.
If you say that was you doing your work, I can't stand it!
Wait a minute, really?
Your guess and jokes totally bombed!
It hurts!
It hurts! It really hit the target!
If it hits the right place, it truly hurts, right?
Trying to extend your screentime?
Quit it, we don't need that.
We just go without much footage of you.
You extended your screentime just now.
Your Chouno habits took over again.
You're doing the same thing with Chouno.
Kiki Chili Oil
Endou's target is Momoya's "Seems strong, but isn't; Mildly Strong Chili Oil"
He took quite a load.
How is it?
Is it strong?
Woah, it's really mild.
Not strong, at all.
Isn't eating with your index finger dirty?
Right?
They say that Endou's index finger is even dirtier than your average.
I'll try this one with garlic,
Gyokaikei's "Reclaimed Land Chili Oil".
Different. Ah, this...
..traditional Japanese taste really kicks in so it's completely different.
The oil I ate "Reclaimed Land Chili Oil" WAS NOT IT.
After this, Endou easily clears one after another.
Well then, excuse me for a moment.
So, after that it's...
"Seems strong, but really isn't; Mildly Strong Chili Oil".
Here I go!
I wonder if this is too audacious.
Maybe it's too audacious, but I have a feeling that Momoya should be also appearing soon.
But having a prejudice like that isn't good.
After all, it's a battle of tongues.
This isn't about human relationships.
He's really desperate to get his footage used!
No, but this is different. Here I go!
The oil I ate, Momoya's "Seems strong, but isn't; Mildly Strong Chili Oil" WAS NOT IT!
Now THIS is the worst!
I thought you could do it!
I'm sorry!
This is scary, as always...
Your head and sense of taste are both dulled!
That's enough, Endou.
Stand up!
Wait a minute!
Give me the chips in it! I'm last and I'll make it with the chips!
You'll have the same conditions as everyone else!
Endou did it too -
PUT THE CHIPS IN!!!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH PUTTING THE CHIPS IN?
CHIP! CHIP!
PUT THE CHIPS IN IT!!
Shut your mouth already!
Extra challenging Kiki Chili Oil.
The item is same as Hamada's, Kaburaya's ""Daruma Chili Oil".
I'm gonna go with two-finger, alright?
This two-finger style's... this...
That thing you're doing is the same as Endou!
This has more flavor than I expected!
The garlic really stands out.
Next I'll try the chips...
Strange... No chips?
There aren't any chips!
CHIP! CHIP!
I'll start from this end!
So I can't change after taking this?
That's against rules.
Just wait a moment.
I can tell it!
Completely different!
I get it!
I understand, however~!!
Nobody does that anymore!
Yassan imitations...
Yokoyama Yasushi, comedian. Partner of Nishikawa Kiyoshi.
The oil I ate, Momoya's "Seems strong but isn't; Mildly Strong Chili Oil" WAS NOT IT!
I could totally tell this one!
I am different from you guys so far!
I can really recognize the differences by taste!
Matsumoto is full of confidence! True to his words, he clears four more with a breeze!
I totally get this!
Here I go!
Close!
So here it comes...
Who picked this?
Who picked this one?
Say it in rapid-talk! Who decided this one?
We did it together...
There's four of you, just who picked it? In rapid-speech.
Just who put most of their fe-feelingses in it?
Feelingses?
You're talking so fast you're not making any sense.
No, I'll trust my insticts here.
It was much closer than the previous one,
but this one's not gonna fool me.
The oil I ate...
Wakatake Chikui... Jikuchi's...
...Tsukiji no [Reclaimed Land] Chili Oil - Gyokaikei Garlic! "
WAS NOT IT! Best regards!
All right! I did it!
I overcame this one!
Which should I do next?
I guess I'll go in the order afterall.
I'll keep going with the two-finger style.
With two-finger...
It's here!
THIS IS IT! YOU GUYS!!
I'll believe in myself! This is definitely it!
Could I try this one just a little?
That's out of bounds!
Just this one!
That's against the rules.
I really wanted to try this one, too.
Also, nobody has tried this one!
There's a possibility you're messing with me,
but in that case it's hopeless.
I'll just lash out and go home.
I'm 90% sure I'm right with Daruma.
But still -
If it's within these three ones, I couldn't care less. Not my problem.
You can't do anything with those you didn't taste, after all.
ALRIGHT!!
Right now, my eyes totally met with that camera assistant.
That's fine, he's just doing his job.
SHALL I GO~!?
I'll get through here, since were always going around the other side.
How's that?
I'll go now.
This is it. This is definitely it! Look, here I go again!
Alright!
The oil I ate...
Kaburaya's "Hot Chili Oil...
...DARUMA CHILI OIL", WAS THIS!
Well done!
You really did it!
I guess all the studying paid off after all!
Studies?
My student days...
Wonderful! Congratulations!
It's really great you could do it with your sense of taste!
It's been a while!
Tomorrow, the phone at the office won't stop ringing!
"Who's that old guy?"
"Who's that old guy..."
"Couldn't he join Waratte Iitomo! already?"