Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
So... What is this
Well...
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki... once again...
How do I say it...
He want's to do a new challenge
There's a lot of people here
Yeah your right
He want's to do a new challenge huh.....
Are you sure?
I guess so....
Oh Look!
Yamazaki Housei
He made a grand entrance huh
Your right...
Hello everybody!
Hello!
I'm the chairman Yamazaki Housei
The reason I gathered you all this time
In July 2007
I'll be entering my 20th anniversary as a performer
Ah I get it
Now for something such as big as this
If you squish it down...
It could fit 2 years
I thought "What haven't I done"
For my anniversary I thought about what I haven't done
And so I gathered you all here
Something he hasn't done huh...
For now because you guy's dont understand
I will pass out the scripts
He's pretty prepared for this
He's completely ignoring us huh
Please hand these out
Yamano Ishimatsu's 100 Cut's!!
This is pretty packed!
What kind of picture is this?
Uwa Look Matsumoto!
So this is an acual thing?
When you think of a 20th anniversary,
This really is
a big
trns...
turning point
Huh!?
When you say the word "Human"
You think of a mature adult
And So I want to do both together
TL: Turning of age (20) and his 20th anniversary
"When you say the word Human"
Your also
a human...
This time!
I will unprecedentedly
Slay 100 people!
Honestly...
I think it's an amazing feat
Use your nerves
Use as much things as you can
He said it
Everyone!
He said nothing but "Nerves"
Please dont go about this half-assed
Because your betting your life...
Wait you!
What are you holding right now?
A sword
So you know it's a sword!
It's not a toy
The sword
your holding right now
Is not a toy! Understand!?
Think of it as a real sword!
Sorry...
I'm getting a little tired but
It will become a big sword!
He's using Kansai-ben now
He was using a lot of Osaka-ben
Sorry I'm here!
They're late
What's your excuse?
Well.. Uh...
We were at a Manga Cafe and we didn`t realize the time....
A Manga Cafe?
So what your telling me
You knew it was Yamazaki Housei's 20th anniversary
And you still went to a Manga Cafe?
"You knew it"...
Go home!
GO HOME!
WE'RE RISKING OUR LIVES HERE!
We're really sorry!
Will you take this seriously now?
He forgave them huh
That was quick
All of you especially
Because this is a 20th anniversary
START TAKING ALL THIS SERIOUSLY!
Please excuse us!
YOUR ALL GOING TO RISK YOUR LIVES RIGHT!?
YES!
LET'S DO IT!
THANK YOU!
THANK  YOU!
Ah Hes coming!
Well....
You made us wait for a while
I guess so
So is it alright if we just watch?
No, Well...
Your in the flyer
Why?
What?
What is this?
Why you ask?
Your all entered in this
Where did you get this picture?
Look at the schedule as well!
So your charging 800 yen for this huh
Well naturally...
Huh? The times are 1pm 3pm 5pm and 7pm!
Your performing 4 times?
That's some amazing stamina!
Well then I guess I'll enter the 100 people
But you've explained what happens when we get cut
Well what do you want us to do if you get cut?
Well I dont think I'm gonna get cut but
If I get cut
please put the count back
What do you mean?
Supposing I cut 50 people
If I was cut it would go to 51, 52 ,53
So it'd be like that
So it would increase the count?
Yes
Are you really gonna cut 100 people?
I'm going to cut 100 people!
Alright Let's go!
Amazing...
GET READY!
OK!
Today, as well
he looks
as small as ever
Brought to you by: DCSubs
www.gaki-no-tsukai.com
www.reddit.com/r/GakiNoTsukai
Celebrating his 20th year into the Performer world!
Yamano Ishimatsu's 100 Cut Challenge!!
Yamano Ishimatsu
TL: Yamazaki is impersonating Morino Ishimatsu
Wagering on the scales of Duty and Sympathy
A mans world has a heavy sense of duty!
There's a difference in long and short but
It's unrelated to an empty life
A wild kid of the sea route!
NOW COME!
AT YAMANO ISHIMATSU!
Remaining
He's amazing!
Amazing!
So cool!
COME!
COME AT US!
He's saying "Wait"....
But 100 people...
Yamazaki...
You haven't cut 100 people yet...
Are you coming?
How many people are left?
Are you gonna come?
How many are left?
Adding it up...
There's 122 left
123....
Your wrong
Somethings wrong
There's something wrong? What is it?
Please yell before you come at me
Ah sorry about that!
So we yell then...
Remaining
5 minutes later
10 minutes later
Shut up!
Come on let's continue!
You still haven't cut 100 people yet
That's right
What's he at now?
2944 people remaining
Yamazaki...
What should we do?
Please let's
go back to the original number
What did he say?
He want's to go back to the original number
Well I thought you were doing good and all
Can I have a talk...
Huh?
Matsumoto!
He want's to have a talk
Today isn't the day for that
Your right
Let's remove all the extra points hes accumulated
For now let's just do 100
I see... That's good!
So we're resetting it
Good luck!
Are you fine?
It's 100 people!
What is this?
Yamano Ishimatsu!
What is it?
Is 50 people fine?
Can I just cut 50 people?
"Can I just cut 50 people?"
What do you think Matsumoto?
Can you do 50?
Didn't you say you could cut 100 people?
I guess we'll do 50
50 is fine?
Are you sure?
Yea
Thanks
What happens to Yamano Ishimatsu after this?
Celebrating his 20th year into the Performer world!
Yamano Ishimatsu's 100 Cut Challenge!!
Wagering on the scales of Duty and Sympathy
A mans world has a heavy sense of duty!
Theres a difference between long and short
COME AT ME!
Remaining
ISHIMATSU!
WAIT ISHIMATSU!
Ishimatsu got away...
He ran away pretty fast huh?
He sure did!
He went quick!
After this Yamazaki's Wailing!
So what happened Matsumoto?
Well...
Sorry everyone but...
Right now....
We have no other choice but to find him
Isnt this for his 20th anniversary
Man this is tiring
It is isn't it!?
Yea it is...
In the end he ran away...
Even in the beginning seconds
He was a lot like Ishimatsu
Suddenly
He already turned into an old man
Meanwhile Yamazaki...
Is hiding in the shadow of the building...
Tanaka you go!
Just to talk right?
They send the loving Tanaka to persuade him...
It's fine!
It's just me!
Yamazaki!
I came just to talk!
Its fine Yamazaki!
Yamazaki its fine!
Yamazaki runs away ignoring Tanaka
Wait Yamazaki!
Its fine it's only me!
I really don't want to see you in the state your in but
Where Yamazaki?
Is he coming?
He's crying
Matsumoto!
He's crying somewhere what do we do?
Hes crying?
Crying you say...
He kept running and running
Towards Omekaido Highway
What the hell!
He kept running and running and finally
Where is he now?
Right now he's just over there
Omekaido Huh?
Can you come Matsumoto?
Yamachan!
Don't cry like that!
What's wrong!?
Everyone's waiting!
I'm just gonna say it bluntly
I dont understand what your crying about
Anyhow
my back
hurts
It hurts huh?
Well anyways I apologize for myself
Sorry about that
Anyhow
my back
hurts
Be more careful!
Definitely be more careful with your back!
I
only touched it a bit and
It felt like it was on fire!
Alright I understand but you gotta go back
As it is you have to apologize to everyone back there
For now can you just give me some time?
Well, just work a little more
Anyways Yamachan, when we go to cut you
We will yell before we do it
Absolutely!
I really
can't trust you
Well before we didn't know we had to do that!
No, Theres really no way with you
"You"?
Who are you calling "You"
HOUSEI!
Finally Yamazaki...!?
For now go talk to them!
What are you doing?
Its really cold out here!
For now let's go inside and greet them
And then we'll get prepared
For the sake of the 100 cut challenge Matsumoto thinks of an idea!
What if we stick cardboard on your back?
I'm fine with that
Oh really?
Ah that's good!
If we use this it'll be fine
Where else do you want it?
There and here
Don't say it
so nonchalantly
Anyways you look amazing!
Considering
you look like Nobunaga
You should have put on armor or something in the beginning
Sorry about that everyone!
Sorry!
Thank you!
There's no excuse for this
Celebrating his 20th year into the Performer world!
Yamano Ishimatsu's 100 Cut Challenge!!
Wagering on the scales of Duty and Sympathy
A mans world has a heavy sense of duty!
There's a small difference between long and short
It's unrelated to an empty life!
YAMANO ISHIMATSU!
COME AT ME
Remaining
ISHIMATSU!
5 minutes later
Remaining
HE'S GETTING AWAY!
What is this?
Ishimatsu!
Ishimatsu
He's on his knees
Save me~
He look's so fragile!
SAVE ME~
♪ Without looking back~ ♪
Song: 誓い (Vow)
Artist: Ayaka Hirahara
ちかい
♪ We start walking as is ♪
♪Towards a new stage!♪
♪Until we finally reach it~♪
♪And Until that time~ ♪
♪ I wont give up! ♪
Congratulations Yamachan on your 20th anniversary!!
Brought to you by: DCSubs
www.gaki-no-tsukai.com
www.reddit.com/r/GakiNoTsukai