Translation, Encoding and subtitles by ForegroundNoises (Shion) (twitter: /paintthemblack)
Self proclaimed American citizen, profession: Dancer
Immigration office headquarters
Are you really an American?
Yes!
If by chance you're really american
I bet you have no problem saying
in thirty seconds at least 10 words
Beginning with the letter A of the alphabet
Am I right?
Yes!
And... Start!
America
Apple
A... A...
An@l
Why picking up that from the many?
Was that the third(word)?
Not fair!
Even this clip is not fair!
Not fair on so many levels!
You said you're a dancer so... Are
musical instruments your strong point too?
A recorder was prepared for you, try playing something
It stinks...
Jimmy's sense of smell is sharp to abnormalities
Are you bullshitting us?
No..
The tough part came, didn't it?
Why is it tough from now?
He began the "it stinks" part...
I wonder if he will stop...
It's all about Jimmy's sense of smell, isn't it? It sure works strange.
It stinks...
That's kinda Hamada's weak point,
The authors must know it too, right?
Stop saying "It stinks"!
Ok, Just three times!
Think of something else, let's help each other
It stinks...
Please stop... Really... Let's skip that!
What the hell, man?
You can still get better
Enough... let's see what's next
No, from here Hamada-san
I got it, I got it.
It stinks
I've been tempted, damn! I've been tempted!
This must have hurt
Proceed, please
Please...
I'm really sorry
I'm proceeding for sure now
I tried to endure that mess, but
You're not the American citizen
you claim to be, aren't you?
Get the hell away from this country!
The immigration officer's job is not over yet!
That was hard
I guess you're all worn out, aren't you?
Furthermore, this clip will continue...
Global economy of confusion
The road to revival
Katayama Satsuki
TN: A Japanese politician and bureaucrat. She was a member
of Japan's House of Representatives for about four years
Good evening
I'm Katayama Satsuki, member
of the House of Councilors
No sub
Today, the topic is "The real path to the World Economy"
And we'll soon start a conversation about it
Therefore, let's call here a special guest
From the international school of analists this person!
Please, come in!
International's School Analist
Oonishi Hideaki
He's Mr. Oonishi Hideaki
Good evening, it's a pleasure
This week, we welcomed the
international analist Oonishi Hideaki
That's so wrong.
So, now that you're there, first of all, about TPP
TN: Trans-Pacific Partnership.
Yes?
The previous chairman of the democratic party
council said that the TPP idea was like a ghost.
But regarding that "TPP is like a
ghost"... What do you think Mr. Oonishi?
An offensive...
Pressure...
is...
Uhm...
Panicked
and
Ended up turning into a ghost.
What does TPP stands for?
Daddy
Is in a pinch
While picking