Librarian's Note: Unsubbed
DOWNTOWN
Matsumoto Hitoshi       Hamada Masatoshi
Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
More clips? Subscribe to Shion (ガキの使い用)! | shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Any words?
Right
Yeah I thought about it and there is actually one
Yamazaki Housei
For real?
Yeah, in the end it was
"Cutlet Curry" (katsu karee)
KATSU KAREE
(cutlet curry)
Limit Series 4th Episode:
This summer curry was like a trend,
you know that uhhh... stamina
Yeah yeah, I got your point
you know, that thing
We can't afford not to do this, right?
Exactly
The first challenge was Ice Coffee
They accepted the challenge to order it by changing the order's name to "Ouyan Fifi"
I'm ordering an Ouyan Fifi
...Excuse me?
Ah, an Ouyan Fifi, please
An Ouyan Iced Coffee
An ice..?
Is an ice coffee okay?
Yeah
Following this, they faced the challenge to order Chilled Chinese Noodles by saying "Suzuki Kyouka"
Uhm...
A Suzuki Kyouka
"Sui"...?
Suzuki Kyouka
Steamed buns (sui gyouza), right?
Then, Steamed buns (sui gyouza)
You just ordered steamed buns!
And as the third round, they tried to order a pack of Mild Seven by saying "Micheal Tomioka" instead
Do you sell cigarettes in here?
Yes, which do you want?
A pack of Micheal Tomioka
Are there some Micheal Tomiokas?
There aren't
Episode 4
Getting closer to the limits of "Katsu Karee"
This time round they'll test out the limits of "katsu karee" (Cutlet Curry)
Translation, Subtitles & Encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
www.foregroundnoises.wordpress.com
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Cocorico
Endo Shouzo Tanaka Naoki
The challenge has come yet again!
Yeah it did
Let's take a look
I really have a bad feeling about this
Well, let's take a look at them, shall we?
"Well done!" (otsukare)
Yeah, this could work, it sound close to the actual word
Here's the second one
"I'll kick your butt!" (ketsu kere)
Shouldn't it be "ketsu keré"?
＊Hamada is pointing out that Matsumoto said "ketsu kere" stretching the last "e" (a short vowel) to make it sound like the "e" in "katsu karee" (a long vowel)
"I'll kick your buuutt!" (ketsu keree)
You know, a way of saying it as if shouting it
It's just a different way of saying it
Like "I'll kick yourr butt!!" with a short vowel won't just work
Got it
"I'll kick your buuutt!"
With that being said, the next one is uh...
"Katsushin"
＊It may refer to a samurai portrayed in many books / novels
It's a bit different, right?
I think this one is a bit though
Definitely a though one
Next one is...
Kangaroo (kangaruu)
I'm guessing this was kind of forced in
Well, that's because from this point it gets hard
Makes sense
Then we have "Kahimi Karie"
＊A famous japanese singer
It's not even close!
Kahimi Karie...
The next one is
"Fried pig thing with indian spices"
This one is a bit different
But I think the meaning will be conveyed enough
Ohh, yeah, that could do
And then our last one
Otsuka Nene
＊A japanese actress & photographer
So that's all
Ok
Dismissed!
Ok, we're going
How far
Is a katsu karee (cutlet curry) a katsu karee?
Let's go find out!
Katsu Karee's Limits
~study results~
OTSUKARE
"Well done!"
Uhm... I'll have
An OTSUKARE ("Well done!")
A katsu karee cutlet curry)?
Yes, please
Apparently "otsukare" ("Well done!")
works fine!
Right!
OTSUKARE = OK
KETSU KERE
"I'll kick your butt"
Uhm...
I'll have a ketsu kere ("I'll kick your butt")
Come again?
He straight up said "ketsu keré" (long vowel)
Sir!? Did you say "katsu karee" (cutlet curry)?
I'll have a ketsu kere ("I'll kick your butt")
Okay, one katsu karee (cutlet curry)!!
KETSU KERE = OK
Awesome!
It works fine!
KAKU-GARI
"Crew cut"
Excuse me
Can I have a large serving of kaku-gari (crew cut)
Sure                              Ok
"gari" and "karii"
sounds alike
Then a large serving, please
It's going so well!
It was no
problem at all!
This kaku-gari (crew cut) is delicious!
Is it?
Thanks a lot
KAKU-GARI = OK
KATSU-SHIN
I'll going with a...
Katsu-Shin
Uh?
a Katsu-Shin!
"Katsu-shin"
is just...
Uhh?
I'll have a ketsu kere ("I'll kick your butt")
A ketsu-keree ("I'll kick your butt") please
A katsu-karee (cutlet curry)!
KATSU-SHIN = FAIL
KETSU KEREE = OK
He just fixed
it anew!
KANE KASE
"Lend me some money"
Uhm...
kane kase ("lend me some money")
...Sorry?!
Okay so uhm...
kane kure ("give me some money")
Uh!?
You mean katsu kare...?
Kane kure ("give me some money")
Is katsu karee okay?
KANE KASE = FAIL
KANE KURE = OK
He changed to
"kane kure" which sounds closer
Ah! Now I get it!
HAIGO-REI
"A ghost behind you"
I'll have a...
Haigo-rei (a ghost behind you)
A wakadori curry?
＊A variety of curry with chicken cutlet
He heard "wakadori"
A haigo-rei (a ghost behind you)
One of it, please
A wakadori, was it?
HAIGO-REI = FAIL
KANGAROO
Then I'll have a kangaroo!
What?
Well, it's not on our menu
For real?!
Just choose what you want by pointing at it with your finger
Then I'll have a small serving
So, is a small serving of beef curry okay to you?
No, no, you got it wrong
A kangaroo
Which one is it?
They must have
thought he's a
complete idiot
This one!
Yamazaki points it on the menu
Cutlet Curry (katsu karee), Okay!
KANGAROO = FAIL
KAHIMI KARIE
One serving of Kahimi Karie...
Uh...
Wait a moment, please
Sure
KAHIMI KARIE = FAIL
Second Challenge!!
I'll have a  Kahimi Karie...
Please, choose from the menu
Okay
Once you're done just let me know!
This one's a no, uh
Looks like it
Got it
KAHIMI KARIE = DOUBLE FAIL
BUTA-AGE INDO KARA-MESHI
"Fried pig thing with indian spices"
I'll have...
A fried pig thing with indian spices
Mhh!?
He said it
so clearly!
Fried pig thing with indian spices
The employee laughs as he's confused
Fried pig thing with indian spices!
Fried indian pig...
Fried pig thing with indian spices = FAIL
OTSUKA NENE
I'll have a Otsuka Nene
What?
Otsuka Nene
Uh? Which one is it?
Otsuka Nene.
There's no such curry in here, sir...
His voice is
getting softer
I'm really sorry, can you please point that out on our menu?
See, it comes to this
if it's not clear enough
Yeah...
He straight up
refused to point it
out on the menu!
Oh, he's leaving
What the hell!
I just wanted
to get out!
It was so long
I started feeling nervous!
Now the poor
employee will
think he made
a customer mad!
OTSUKA NENE = FAIL
Though this one was close enough (kane kase), its sorrounding didn't make it, like this "katsu-shin"
Yeah, "Katsu-shin" was nowhere close to it
Well, is that
The "katsu" part is ok, but "karee" and "shin" are absolutely different, aren't them?
Yeah, you're right
You can't possibly deceive someone with it!
I was positive that "Otsuka Nene" would make it, though
But there were only three words that worked perfectly
Yeah
3 of them
Yup
Okay so, moving on
Uhh... starting from now
Hamada-san
Yeah
Let's go
Good luck!
Please!
What are we using?
Let's aim even higher
It's this one, uh...
"Totsuka yotto sukuuru" (Totsuka Yacht School)
＊As the name suggests, it's a famous japanese Yacht School
No way, that's impossible!
Yeah, he's right!
No way it's gonna work!
That's a little too harsh!
This one can do the trick
I really think this one is going to work
The "TotsuKA" section is like a rougher version of "Katsu"
No way, no way
You know, "totsu-KA" - "Katsu KA"
See?
I really doubt it though...
And so, Downtown are now moving towards a curry shop
Will they be able to order a Cutlet Curry (katsu karee) by saying "Totsuka Yotto Sukuuru" (Totsuka Yacht School)?
I'll have a beef curry
Is everyone ordering a beef curry?
Uhm...
Ok, I'm going for the beef curry too
Excuse me, I'll have a...
Totsuka Yottsu ka~re~ (totsuka yacht cu~rry~)
＊Matsumoto nervously changes "yatsu sukuuru" to "yatsu karee". Also, from this point onwards he starts stuttering his order / speaking in a weird accent
A Totsuka Yo---
A Tots-
A Totsuka yotto sukareeru (Totsuka Yacht Schurry)
What is he sayin'?
Excuse me, can I order?
Sure
I'd like
A Totsuka yottsu karee (Totsuka Yotts Curry)
An employee stares oddly at Matsumoto
Oh, is it forbidden to smoke in here?
Is it forbidden to smoke in here?
No, it's okay
Then I'll have a Totsuka yotto sukaree (Totsuka Yacht Schoorr)
A Totsuka yottsu karee (Totsuka Yotts Curry)
＊Matsumoto is speaking in a foreign accent for some reasons
No one is playing along with Matsumoto
A Totsuka yottsu karee (Totsuka Yotts Curry)
He has completely switched to "curry"
Totsuka Tsuyotto Sukaruu Karee (???)
Enough!
TOTSUKA YOTTO SUKUURU = FAIL
He just left
What the hell!
Enough!
But why?
I didn't like this outcome!
How was it?
Was it good?
Come on, man!
That was fast!
It didn't work at all!
The mood wasn't okay!
What happened?
What was it?
No one dared to play along with me!
At least you were able to say it?
Of course I did, countless times!
They just ignored my messages
But I think that it MAY actually could have done it
Because you know I made lots of words that worked fine
As if they did!
All I did was being left here waiting!
That's 'cause it wasn't working!
The mood was off!
That's exactly why
What the hell, man
We'll uhhh
Just say that it was a failure!
No, don't just say "failure"
There's no reason to say it was a failure
But you didn't succeed!
Just don't say "failure"
Don't say it anymore
Woah, ok, I won't say it
We'll have this fixing our outcome
Yeah
CHAGE & ASKA
＊A popular J-pop duo
This one starts already weird with that "CHA"
I think this one may get the shop manager pissed off
This one
Is up to you!
What the hell!
I've always being the main supporter of all of this
Why me?
Now I'm just sick of it!
So they move to yet another restaurant
And this time Matsumoto, Cocorico and Yamazaki will support Hamada
Will Hamada be able to order a Cutlet Curry (katsu karee) by saying "CHAGE & ASKA?"
Let's see...
I'll have a CHAGE & ASKA
＊Hamada isn't pronouncing it right on purpose in order to (try to) make it sound closer to "katsu karee"
What!?
Uhmm... uh..
Wait a moment, please
Come on, just order something
Ok, ok
Uhmm, ok, Lady!
A CHAGE & ASKAre
＊Hamada adds "re" to make "ASKA" sound closer to "KARE"
What is he saying!?
Wha-
Excuse me!
What is it?
CHAGE & ASKAre
Rice Curry!? No, it's not it, right?
Right, no
Is it dry curry?
CHAGE & ASKAre!
I can't understand what you're saying!
Can you pronounce it more clearly?
Oh, I'm sorry
What's that!
CHAGE & ASSKASSKAREE!
That's what I don't understand!
Say it clearly!
Is it rice curry?
You know, this guy wants that...
CHAGE & ASSKATSU-KAREE
Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
More clips? Subscribe to Shion (ガキの使い用)! | foregroundnoises.wordpress.com
Ah, a katsu-karee! (cutlet curry)
You just said it so clearly! - Ouch
CHAGE & ASKA = FAIL
The hell are you doing, idiot
I can't even rely on you, what do I have to do?!
You damn business saboteur!!