If there's an animal nearby
I can't eat at all!
Around a month ago
(you can find this episode on shionnotsukai.wordpress.com)
Yamada Yoshi's House sleepover!!
Yoshi
Mayo
Nikori
Sakuharu
In order to learn more about comedians as a producer
Heipo stayed in CowCow Yoshi's house
And then, even though he said he didn't like animals...
Heipo used to hate animals...
Affection for the dogs
What's wrong? Aren't you sleepy?
Heipo grew fond of Yoshi's dogs
Heipo used to dislike kids...
Not only, our single-man Heipo didn't even like children...
Doting on Yoshi's kids
But then he fell in love with his kids
Heipo became more like a human, but what now!?
But what's in store now for our completely changed Heipo?
First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai!
World Famous Heipo's Camp Trip with CowCow Yoshi's family!
Oh yeah!
Oh boy, this is our second time
Yamazaki Hosei
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Heipo
It is
- Incredible
He already had a sleepover some time ago
- Let me say this
That episode had a huge response!!
And yet the viewing rate sucked...
Well---
Lots of people were surprised
a Gaki episode could be so touching
- I see
That's what I said, it improved Heipo's image to me!
But the viewing rate sucked...
Come on, enough with that!
Come on, it's fine
- Really...
It was really amazing...
Well, that's what, like, only two people told me...
It figures
- Come on!
That's enough, isn't it?
And I don't even remember who it was
That doesn't help
By the way, it meant so much to him
That after that, he gave the kids a present
After the On-air?
- Yes, unrelated to it
Like, a toy or something?
Yes, for the record
He bought a Nintendo 3DS for Nikori and a bicycle for Saku
Present for Nikori
Nintendo 3DS
That's right
Present for Sakuharu
Bicycle
That's true
You paid for those?
- Of course
That's a lot, man
- Really
I was scared when he said "toy" at first, you know...
No way!
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION        shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
FOLLOW: FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI ~ TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
WANT TO SUPPORT? YOU CAN:
- DONATE ON KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
- BECOME A PATRON ON PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
,.,AND GET EARLY ACCESS TO RAWS, SOFTSUBS & UPDATES!
Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Heipo + kids + street at night = ??
Camping with Yoshi's family!!
This is World Famous Heipo's
VTR of him enjoying a camp trip
with the children, just that.
Somewhere in Tokyo
It's a day in August
Heipo heads to a public park to meet Yoshi's family,
which he first met around a month ago
Headed to a park to meet Yoshi's family
Even the way
he walks has
changed
- You're right
staff) make sure to leave some good memories
Of course, it's Summer, that's for sure
And I love them, you know!
Is it here?
Mr. Heipo!!
Aah~ It's been a while! How are you?
Oh my, you got so big, didn't you?
Hi there
Nikori
6 years old
How's the bicycle, Saku?
Sakuharu
4 years old
Thanks for the 3DS, Heipo
Did you use it? Yes?
Incredible
The bicycle he got for him
That's a good bicycle
He's doing great
He looks good
- Did you buy the helmet too?
No, I didn't buy that
Why didn't you? Geez
The game he got for her
You gave me this, right?
- Yeah, I really don't know much about it
I mean, there are so many DSs around!
They told me why am I buying it if I don't even know what it is!
What's going on, Saku-chan?
So cute, like always!
Ufufufu~
That's...
What a weird way to say it
- He's cute, that's a fact!
World Famous Heipo + CowCow Yoshi's family
Camp Trip!!
World Famous Heipo and Yoshi's family
are ready for camping!
- World famous my ass
Like this?
- We should get Heipo's first
Going to the camp with Yoshi's car
Like this?
- Behind that
Are you excited?
Wife
Mayo (29 years old)
Not at all!
- You can tell his wife wanted to be only with the family
Their pet Chihuahua is going with them
Are you all ready?
We're off!
- Oh boy!
Alright, let's go
One, two and departu~re! let's go~!
- Alright kids, I'm ready
I wanna go!
Departure
Me too
And so, the trip for making good
memories for the kids has begun
They must be so excited for it
I can't wait!
That's right, I agree
What? That sticker has a scent?
Lemme see
Oh, you're right
Niko-chan loves to collect stickers
Bye bye!
And also something else...
But she also likes...
♪ Heavy Rotation - AKB48
Who's your favorite idol, Niko?
Yuko Oshima
- Oh, I see
Is she your friend?
Oh yes, I happen to know her
Eh? Really?
Most likely a lie...
Really?!
- Yeah, I know her
No way that's true
- No it's true, I know her
Niko-chan is obsessed with Yuko Oshima
You know a lot about her, don't you?
Niko-chan really likes Yuko Oshima
It's been 2 and a half hours of driving so far
Arrived at Yasuragi-no-Sato camp, Ibaraki prefecture
They arrived at Yasuragi-no-Sato camp, in Ibaraki prefecture
serenity village
Pretty long ride, huh
They chose it so the city-raised kids can enjoy the nature
Camp site shrouded in nature
So, that's why you all drove for 2 and a half hours
The cottage where they'll stay for the night
But first, they head to the cottage where they'll stay
Let's go～
Such a nice place
- Really
But really... such a waste
to bring Heipo with them
- It should have been family-only
Alright, let's get in
Can't disagree on that
- He's such a burden
This is so good
Don't call me like that!
- But that's what you are
I want him to leave our planet Earth
Come on...
Heipo, come see the bathtub!
You want me to?
- Just go!
Follow him
- Don't question them
This one?
I bet the kids are so excited
- Totally
Watch your steps
Don't
- Pretty big, huh?
The kids are loving it
The kids are really enjoying the
nature surrounding this place
Why with your hands raised?
Alright, what do we do?
Let's go to the river!
Wanna go to the river?
- Let's go
Playing by the river
Can't we do anything about the skipping?
We should de-excite them a bit
Very excited
filmed by Yoshi
They're so lively
Look at them run
They're really excited!
Playing by the river to their heart's content
It's time to enjoy the nature to the fullest
But something happens to Heipo...
Something strange occurs to Heipo
- What now?!
Wait-- I dislocated my shoulder...
Can we go?
- Wait
I can't move my shoulder, what the?
Can we just go?
You know when I had to put on my seatbelt?
I put it like this
Dislocated shoulder!?
It's been hurting since that!
- Is it out of place?
I think it's fine, but...
It's probably ok
staff) you're moving it without problems!
But it's true! It hurts
He lied because he doesn't want to swim
Heipo refuses to swim so much he chose to lie
There's a reason for why he doesn't want to undress...
He says there's a reason for why
he doesn't want to get undressed
Sorry, director
Watch out for your feet, you should wear some slippers
Hot hot hot hot hot hot!!
I have a pimple on my chest...
Can I keep my T-shirt on?
Are you embarrassed?
- Kinda
staff) undress, if you can...
Got it
He's embarrassed about the pimple on his chest
Heipo still wants to be popular among the female audience
- What the heck!
Looks like he wanted to hide the pimple
Very aware of the female audience
Why the freeze frame? Come on!
It's pretty big, isn't it?
The kids are playing innocently by the river
A slide?
- Yes
Oh shi- it's so cold! Aah! Move aside, move!
Here I come
What the heck
Huh? My glasses, my glasses!
You have them on, you dumbfuck
Oh, I had them on me, geez...
What's going on?
You're wearing your glasses!
Of course you are
Attack!
Aaah! What are you doing?!
Oh, come on! You got me
I even drank some of it!
Watch out
Fully enjoying playing by the river
Heipo is enjoying the river with the kids
This place is great
Let's slide down together, Heipo!
She really likes you
- Yes
Hold firmly, Saku-chan
Can we do this together?
Is it gonna hold?
- I hope so
They're going--- what was that?!
It's so cold!
Oh shi--- I lost my glasses for real!
- Just take them off...
Look out for his glasses!
Over there, Saku-chan
Oh, here they are! Arigato! Thank you!
Sorry for that
Oof, save me
Were you tired?
- Definitely
Are you ok?
What's wrong?
- What was that for?
Ah-- ah- sorry, my feet hurt
He's listening to your complaints
The one who needs the most care is this 56-yo man
To grant the kids the best memories...
Over here!
After playing by the river, it's time
for bug-hunting in the forest
Bug hunting
Ah! I got a big one!
Eh?? What??
Nice one, girl
Look, a butterfly! Try to catch it
That's not rare at all
Seen anything?
Aren't you afraid of cicada shells?
Like this
Aren't you afraid of it?
- It's empty inside
See? The real cicadas are up above
He wants to let the kids touch the bugs
Here it is
- Way too high
Yes, but that's how they do it
Oopsie daisy
Ah, I can't reach it at all! What the--?!
It flew away
It's gone...
Aaaaah! Agh--
It's a branch...
- You're making them worried
Traps for rhinoceros beetles
This is pretty awesome, isn't it?
Let's go get them back tomorrow morning
Dinner time
For dinner, he'll be making yaki-soba with the kids
Making some yaki-soba
- This is actually nice
Heipo, do you like yaki-soba?
- With the bbq and all
- I love it, it's so good
It looks so good, but there's a lot of it
It looks tasty
- Really
Do we need this shot?
Let's dig in!!
Maybe he smelled suspense in the air?
- It must have been that
The yaki-soba is great
- It's good, yes
So? Do you like your yaki-soba?
After dinner, they got back to their cottage
Back to the cottage after dinner
What's that thing?
I bet you all were tired
Touching the dog with ease
Ah, that one...
- He's fine with it by now
Really
I think the dog wants to drink some water
Can I use this?
- Sure
Yes, that one should do it
- He's not afraid of it anymore
Look, his ears got all pointy-- he's going!
See? He really wanted to drink water
That means I was right
That's impressive
Yeah, I kind of felt that
- Is it really that impressive?
He understands how the dog feels
He barely did anything
- What's wrong?
Oh boy, you're so cute!
- The hell are you doing?!
It's not a problem!
Fireflies sightseeing
After resting a while in the cottage...
So many events...
- The children want to see the fireflies by all means
Heipo can barely stand up
Heading towards a spot near the river
They leave Mayo behind and go to
the river to see the fireflies
Let's go, Saku-chan. You ok, Niko-chan?
Are they gonna be fine?
Be careful!
I hope so
- I mean, that's scary
Wait for us, mama!
You should have sent your sister instead
Aren't you scared, Saku-chan?
Yoshi) Are you scared? You're good?
- You're ok?
Saku) I'm not scared
Saku-chan is amazing, isn't he?
A fearless 4-year-old boy
Aahhh... Aaaaaaaaah!!
I stepped on something
I feel safe with papa around
Aaah! Something's there!
Eeeeeeeeeeeh!!
Oh shit
A 6-year-old girl toying with Heipo's emotions
You scared me! Pranks are no good!
Man, these kids are brave
Yoshi) Hear that? It's the sound of the river
I can clearly hear it, man, it's so scary in here
Arrived by the river
Watch your steps, ok?
It's a glove!
Look
This is some scary stuff
Aaaaaah! No way no way no way!!
- Eh? What's going on--?
There was something... I don't know
But I felt something
Here he goes
That's a classic
Was there something there, Saku-chan?
Nothing
- That's a face I've seen countless times
Aaah!! Aaaaah!! Scaryyy~!!
There's something! Something! Something!
I saw it, it's here!
What the--?
- How can you be so calm?
Saku-chan is so brave
- He's a strong boy
This is scary, for real
You ok? Are you scared?
The kids must be so confused
I'm holding Niko-chan's hand so tight right now
They're gonna hate him    - Stay close, Niko-chan
Niko-chan annoyed by Heipo
Be quiet...
Wanna walk some more?
Where are the fireflies?
- Ahead
♪ Let's walk, let's walk, I am...--
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH
Heipo) It's a tree, sorry
Come on...
Niko) Heipo is making me jump off all the time
- Yes...
Niko) Go back home!
Go home--?!
She's right
Heipo) I don't wanna go alone
A ghost could pop out...
- No ghost will pop out
You're so strong, Niko-chan, let's just go
Niko) There's a cobweb in there
Niko) There's a cobweb in there!!
She snapped
Niko-chan is furious
- What's wrong?
You suck, man
Heipo is the only one shouting and ranting
Heipo is making a fuss over everything
Niko-chan got angry, and the
fireflies sightseeing is suspended
Fireflight sightseeing: canceled
Heipo was very scared
I was, wasn't I?
A lot
Papa was so strong, right Niko-chan?
I'm glad there was another adult with me
Ignoring Heipo as much as she can
Sorry about that, by the way
It's time to sleep
The parents are concerned about their angry daughter
Niko-chan, wanna sleep here with Heipo?
Sleeping with Heipo so they
can be friends again
Are you ok by now?
The parents and Saku-chan
will sleep in the other room
Wife, husband and Saku-chan will sleep in the other room
Heipo and Niko-chan
Ahh--- the futon feels so nice
- It really does, huh?
Let's go to sleep, ok?
No! Picture book!
Want me to read it?
Yes, because tomorrow we can't
Right, I'm reading it
Oh, a recovery chance
- It's crucial
His figure reflected in the snow light...
Quarrel-solver picture book
Here
- Yes
The white-bearded old man put his hat back on...
Is this a famous book?
I don't think it's famous
So it's not, huh
But you are famous, aren't you?
In a way yes, I guess so
Looks like Niko-chan has forgiven
Heipo's attitude from before
Niko-chan has forgiven him
I can't sleep if it's bright...
You can't if there's a light? I see...
I prefer it when it's brighter, though
Who cares?
Whoa, you'll sleep soon
What does that mean?
Sleep well, ok? Alright, so cute
Goodnight!
- "You'll sleep"...
Do you think Saku-chan is sleeping already?
I bet he is, he felt so sleepy before
The parents and Saku-chan
That snoring... is it Yoshi?
Holy cow
- That's impressive
coming up
Big trouble before parting!!
You can't make that face
The next morning
Going to get the rhinoceros beetle
The four of them woke up early to go check
the trap for the rhinoceros beetle they set
Let's go
Let's go, Saku-chan
Come on
Is it here?
Oh, here it is! It's here!
Really?
It's a big one
This is incredible!
Go get it, it's here
Oh man, here we go
Here, I took it Saku-chan
Check it out!
Noo～
What's wrong? You ok?
What's going on?
What--
- What's happening?
What the heck!!
What's going on?
- They're fighting
Siblings quarrel
What happened?
- What should I do...?
Where do you want to put it in?
You want it in your box?
You want it inside your box? I see, that's it...
He wanted it for him
- Ahh, I see...
As soon as I put it in, close the lid
- What about Niko now?
Like that, nice
Alright, Niko-chan, wanna take that stag beetle?
Nice, huh?
I don't wanna
Are you afraid of touching it?
It's a big one
- It is
It's a stag beetle
- A big one
Don't you want it, Niko-chan...?
- Put it in, Niko
This looks fine
There's a lot going on here
I can't open this up!! I'm getting mad
Heipo, can you open it for her?
Niko-chan's mood is awful
And now, Niko-chan's mood is awful
But it's almost time for their camping trip to end
How was the camp, Niko-chan?
I'll get you the change of clothes
Ignoring her dad's question
Oh no...
She's not in her best mood
The atmosphere is really tense
But Heipo has a surprise for the kids...
A surprise from Heipo
Well done
- Good one
AKB48 theater
That's actually nice
Heipo heard that both Niko and Saku are a fan of Oshima Yuko, so he reached her out
Oshima Yuko
And he managed to get her sign
for Niko-chan and Saku-chan
stick with me some more!
Nice
- That's really nice
With this, Niko-chan should rejoice
- Well done
Niko-chan's smile will return
Speaking of something else...
Who's your favorite girl from AKB?
Acchan (Atsuko Maeda)
Yuko Oshima, right?
No, it's Acchan (Atsuko Maeda)!
Huh?
"Acchan", unexpectedly
What?!
What a turn of events
But you said you liked Yuko Oshima...
I like Acchan more than her!!
Niko, don't say it like that
So stubborn...
She's being sassy
I got a sign from Yuko Oshima, you know...
Oh! Amazing!
Sometimes I meet her when I'm working...
That's a lie
It says "for Niko-chan and Saku-chan"
It's real
Incredible!
It's really incredible!
She wrote this for you
She made it for you, will you take it?
coming up
an unexpected conclusion!!
Niko-chan...
I got a sign from Yuko Oshima, you know...
Amazing!
Incredible
That's incredible!
She wrote this for you
That's so nice
of him
She made it for you, will you take it?
- Thanks so much
No problem
Alright, stand up
Come with me
She got angry
- Yeah...
You can't make that face now
That's not the face you should make
- She likes Yuko Oshima, right?
Yes, she's really happy about it, but...
- Yes, I kind of get it
Tell me what's the problem
We'll have to say goodbye to Heipo
in a few minutes, you know?
I don't...
Behave! What do you want to do?
I don't wanna...
Everyone's waiting, can you behave properly?
They can't wait for you to calm down at your pace
If that's so, just stay there
Heipo...?
Sorry for that...
It's fine, don't worry
Don't make that face!
The mood before parting away is the worst
The camping trip should have been full of beautiful memories, but now the mood is the worst...
What will you do, Heipo?
Excuse me...
There's still something I want to give her
Nice, go
We're counting on you!
- That's the best thing he's ever done
The first?!
- In your entire life
Niko-chan?
Look
I got this picture book too
Together with this
She said "give it to Niko-chan"
Thank you so much...
Sure, and sorry
Hey...
I also have this secret sticker, only for you
Don't tell Saku-chan or he'll steal it, ok?
Let's go back, ok?
Makes sense...
- Very nice Heipo, you did great here
- It's fine, here's Niko-chan
Here we are
Take care of it, ok?
- Ok?
Say thanks to Mr. Heipo
Thank you...
Sure, it's fine
Say you're sorry and give him a hug
A hug? For me?
It's fine, come here
I'm sorry...
Shit man, this turned out to be so nice
- Cheer up, ok? It's fine
Unexpectedly wholesome
- It's so good
♪ Our very own Summer
Time to say goodbye
Say bye to Heipo
Here goes
You're so cute!
Let me give you a kiss
♪ Lies behind that hill
Thank you so much
Thanks for everything
Heading back to Tokyo for work
♪ We can't even hear the sound of the wind
Bye bye! See you again
Work? You?
Bye!
Bye bye!
- They're so adorable
♪ For we're so fixed on staring at it
They're coming along
Enough of this
♪ Our hearts on top of each other
It was their first ever camping trip...
♪ Dreaming of that Summer we shared
♪ Our hands firmly joined together
And Heipo's wish is only one
♪ And a little miracle is born
Even though it was just a single day:
♪ Our miracle is born
♪ Our midsummer miracle
To hope this becomes
an unforgettable memory to them
That was really something
- I know, right?
Oh man, oh man...
Such a nice episode
- Really
Yeah, but don't forget
How scared shitless Heipo was when the mom got angry!
- Pure terror!
She wasn't angry with you, you know!
- I know...
But she was so scary!!
- I don't blame him
But overall yeah, it was nice, wasn't it?
After seeing it all, I'm even glad you went with them
- Yeah, I agree
Did you grow even more attached to them?
- Oh yes, no doubt
Niko-chan is... you know, good and--- eh? what?
Eh? What's going on?
Which one of your personalities is that?
- What the?
Who are you?
It's getting crowded
- How many people are in there?
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION        shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
FOLLOW: FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI ~ TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
WANT TO SUPPORT? YOU CAN:
- DONATE ON KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
- BECOME A PATRON ON PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
,.,AND GET EARLY ACCESS TO RAWS, SOFTSUBS & UPDATES!