1st Time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arrahende...
So loud!
He is.
He's just so loud.
Definitely in good form.
It's so loud, I have no idea what he's saying.
You know they say, 'The louder the person, the more insecure.'
1st Time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arrahende
"I'm the One Who Understands you Best!"
"Anyways, I Think You'll Like this Item!!"
A special series on Gaki, where the members buy gifts for guests based on their interests!!
What did you guys think about it this time? You find it hard?
It was super tough this time.
It was right?
Yama-chan, you've gotta try harder.
Hōsei
Tanaka
Endō
Matsumoto
Hamada
You've had the worst item 8 times already.
Really?!
But isn't this the segment where we expose Tanaka's lack of style?
So, who is today's guest!?
So, let's welcome out today's guest!
Nakamura Tamao
Good Evening.
So today you've come dressed casually just for us.
'There's no way she's gonna show up in full body tights, right?'
Actress Nakamura Tamao
She has a strong image of wearing traditional Japanese clothing.
The Gaki members will be presenting her with a top and an accessory they think she will like!!
We usually have this image of you in a kimono...
This is probably the first time we've met like this?
What a shock!
You've met Downtown on so many occasions.
You've just completely s@#t on all of that!
You mean in casual stuff, right?
I can't think of a time where you haven't been in a kimono.
This is how I usually dress.
If that's the case, this might be a little difficult.
Is that so?
We just had a nice chat in the green room.
Thank you very much.
Have you ever met him much?
With me.
No... not really...
For work.
We've only met briefly on occasion.
I've met you quite a few times though.
Since I see you on TV, I'm not sure whether we've met or not.
Tamao-san, sorry...
Several times...
We've met.
Sorry
Do you even know my name?
I don't know
I'm sorry
I can't hear you!
You know these two of course, right?
Yes
More or less.
More or less?!
There's no way you'd know us then.
Hamada-san and Matsumoto-san.
Wrong way round!!
Before the show, the five members went shopping.
Musashi-Koyama Shopping Street "Palm"
Hōsei, looking for something different, heads to Musashi-Koyama Shopping Street "Palm".
This is perfect.
This place's image is perfect.
But...
I'm not looking for this kind of pattern.
Something white or black.
But, these are the kind of image I'm thinking of.
Something nice and bright
for around the neck.
Shibuya
Hamada is heading to a store which sells various styles of fashion.
I can't really imagine her wearing anything too bright.
Hmm... Nah...
Hamada is struggling to find something he likes.
Hmm... I see...
A ___________ kind of look.
This might be good
Do you think she'd wear this to pachinko?
Pachinko is a pinball like arcade and gambling machine which uses steel balls as both the currency and playing piece.
What will Hamada choose?
Ginza
Endō is in Ginza, does he have the same image in mind as Hamada?
A bag... I think this is the right sort of idea.
These look kinda like pachinko balls.
I really like this, the sleek white with the bright gems.
I seem to really like things with balls.
Harajuku
Hoping to find an accessory,
the always struggling Tanaka heads to Harajuku.
When I was thinking of an accessory to suit Tamao-san
I came up with something straight away.
Tanaka seems to be full of confidence.
This is good, this'll be great.
These are cute.
They're pink and nice and feminine.
Do many people buy these?
The light pink colour is a favourite among girls and women
of all ages.
All ages?
and nationalities?
Yes
Thank you so much.
Thanks to you, I have no more hesitations.
Ginza
Matsumoto, in search of an accessory, heads to Ginza.
This time definitely feels like it's gonna be the hardest.
She's a well known actress.
I can't just get anything, right?
This is by far the toughest one yet.
How about
a Swiss army knife?
I can't just think of it like I'm buying something for my mother.
Matsumoto just can't find what he's looking for.
Then... suddenly...
Maybe...
What do you think?
Innovative, right?
Staff
It may be unexpected.
With that, the 5 members finish up their shopping trip.
This time, we've gone and bought a top and an accessory we think you'll like.
I love shopping!
No, I just explained that we went...
Hamada-san!
No, Tamao-san isn't shopping
You're not going, we went for you.
I still like shopping!
Subbed by Inepped
This is a free fansub
Please support the official release
Gaki members are presenting items they think will suit our guest.
As usual, our guest, Nakamura Tamao, will take home her favourite item. The member with the worst item will have to pay for their item.
First up, a top that will suit Nakamura Tamao.
First up is Endō, but what sort of top has he chosen?
Go Shōzo!
Nice to meet you, I'm Cocorico's Endō.
This is gonna be a disappointment.
I was thinking of Tamao-san and picked this out.
Open it up please Tamao-san.
Eh... her face just...
Price conversions are approximate for time of airing.
(£38/$55)
Oh no!
No no no!
Endō!
Endō, come on man!
Totally wrong!!
Yep, this is totally off!!
I think it's a little similar to what you have on, light.
I was thinking about what you could wear anytime and I think a cardigan is a good choice.
Because I know you like pachinko...
I also picked thinking about that.
The balls?
The image of the balls...
Are they supposed to represent pachinko balls?
This is just in poor taste.
I just seems like it's in poor taste.
Don't you think it suits her?
This is wrong.
I think it really suits her...
When you think of her first reaction, she didn't seem that into it.
Her reaction was...
Yes yes yes
That's true... You didn't seem to be too enthused.
You won't know, you won't know.
I...
She's an actress, so of course she's got a perfect poker face.
That's what I want you to think.
Next up to present his top to Nakamura Tamao is Hamada.
Like Endō was saying, I wanted something
something comfortable and easy to wear when playing pachinko.
Everyone seems to be focusing on pachinko.
Focusing too much on that.
Eh, Hamada-san?!
What is it?
A lightweight bomber jacket.
It's an MA-1.
I'm not so sure...
£31/$44
What do you think, it's good for pachinko, right?
The size is perfect but...
It's good, right?
I'm not sure...
Do you normally wear jeans to pachinko?
I do.
So quiet.
So you do wear jeans normally!
Hamada-san
At first I was also looking at an MA-1.
Really?!
Then I thought, nah, this isn't it!
Stop messing with me!!
Not convinced of Hamada's choice, what did Tanaka go with?
C'mon then Tanaka!
Please be kind.
Thank you
Here
The Japan Self-Defense Forces (JSDF) are the unified military forces of Japan.
Self-defence forces.
Apologise!
£28/$40
That Japanese style image...
No! No!
As soon as she opened the bag, she said "Self-defence forces"
That's definitely a bad sign!!
It's called camouflage.
Camouflage?
She's quick to take it off!
It's light!
She's already done with it.
She's young
I think Tamao-san has a youthful image.
It's whether Tamao-san likes it or not.
That's why I think, although different, this is something that Tamao-san will like.
Fourth to present his top to Nakamura Tamao, is Matsumoto.
Matsumoto-san, you're up.
You often wear jeans right?
No matter what, people usually picture you in traditional Japanese clothes.
But what Tamao-san actually likes...
Is Rock.
£49/$70
Isn't this perfect?!
Definitely not.
This is perfect!!
Could you imagine her walking around in this!?
You totally could!
I can't see her wearing this!
The yellow...
The yellow colour makes it.
The yellow does, huh?
You could see her showing up in this, "Good morning!"
It wouldn't look out of place at all.
Well you may think that Matsumoto-san, but Tamao-san might not.
As soon as I saw this I thought 'This is it!'
You wear jeans, right?
YES
She's just responding 'YES'
Why are you suddenly only saying 'YES'?
This is heavy isn't it Tamao-san?
The other's are much lighter.
Those one's all look lame, you don't need that bland colouring.
This is a clear cut yellow.
You'll definitely like this.
YES
She said 'YES!!'
Last up, the member with the most losses to date, is Hōsei.
So far, nobody has paid attention to the season.
I'm looking forward to seeing the accessories.
You don't think these take it into account?
No, who wears a jumper in spring?!
Sparkly
We finally see you smile Tamao-san.
It's sparkly!
I really like sparkly things.
£70/$100
What is this? A sheep?
A unicorn
A unicorn?
An animal?
Yes
An imaginary animal... It's like a horse.
A happiness horse!!
An imaginary animal...
Handed over by an imaginary comedian.
Where is this from?
Tamao-san, do you really like sparkly things like that?
I really like sparkly things.
Having shiny stuff all down the arms?
Yeah, sparkly stuff is cute, right?
Just now
Tamao-san asked me in a whisper "Where did you get this?"
Let's get this hung up please.
Among these five, which will come out on top!?
Have you finished deciding?
I'm struggling with 1st and 2nd.
Hōsei
Matsumoto
Hamada
Tanaka
Endō
There's other things to think about...
I have to take into consideration...
Things like my age...
I'm now 76.
So for that reason...
...That time...
...I'm trying to say...
Well whatever!
She's still speaking!!
Things like sleeves
My arms can become itchy if theres a pattern.
I know what you mean!
Like when there's stitching on the inside or something.
Also, I like the colour green!!
That's enough preamble!!
YES
So, Tamao-san, which of these is your favourite?!
I'm sorry to say, it's yours!
Sorry to say?
Despite your meanness.
It's light!
But you weren't totally sure about Hamada-san's?
I really didn't want it to be Hamada-san.
To be honest, I really liked this one too.
But
It's too heavy, at my age.
Between you two...
I'm not just flattering you but
I liked both of yours.
You should like mine too!!
Which one is in third place?
We've got first, second, which is third?
In third is...
Sparkly.
Eh, really?
Sparkly!
Eh, but I thought you liked green?
I do like green, yes.
So, which of these will end up in last place!?
So, we're down to our last two.
Which is the worst?
Because it's cold, this one.
Cocorico is just truly the worst!!
I don't want to...
I don't want to join the Self-defence forces! It's scary!
Once again in last, Tanaka has to pay out 4,602 yen!! (£28/$40)
Next up, an accessory to suit Tamao.
First up is Hōsei who surprised us with his top choice.
You picked well earlier.
Yeah Hōsei-san.
I went around loads of places and
this was a must have item in loads of shops.
Really?
Yeah
It's a more decorative item.
For the older age group?
That's right.
I think Tamao-san will love this.
See, look at that smile!
What's that?!
£32/$46
Oda Mudo, (1952-2020) was an eccentric Japanese monk and talent.
It's Oda Mudo.
It's pretty.
Ah, but she said it was pretty...
Earlier you were saying how much
you hated wearing heavy things!
This is definitely heavy!!
How about trying it on?
This is actually quite light.
There's no way it's light.
This is definitely heavier than my jacket.
It's great.
You're tired, right?
This is the best.
This is just boring, it's not even funny.
玉 (Tama) can mean 'ball' or 'gem'
I focused on the Tama of Tamao-san.
It's full of meaning.
After wearing it
it's not actually that heavy.
I don't like seeing Tamao-san so placid.
Next up is Endō, what has he chosen?
Who's up?
It's my turn.
This one was tough, I looked around loads.
£66/$95
It's a hat, but...
I spent my time selecting the right one.
It looks great, it really suits you.
I don't really have any hats.
Is there a reason you don't?
They're itchy.
Then a hat's a definite no go!
Everything's either itchy or heavy!
Next up, the winner of the first round, Hamada.
This is always a solid pick for an accessory.
What is it?
Sunglasses?
Thinking about it, you could easily go wrong...
They're pretty fashionable.
It's all about the wearer.
They're massive!!
Huge!!
The size is way off!!
You look like a dodgy fortune teller.
Last in the previous round, what sort of accessory will Tanaka present?
You're up 'Zero sense'!
Stop giving me stupid nicknames.
How pretty.
See!
How is my sense now!
£66/$95
I've never worn anything like this.
Why is that?
They look like they'll be heavy.
They aren't, try lifting them.
You'll see when you wear them, they're super heavy.
Geta are traditional Japanese footwear resembling flip-flops usually made of wood.
It'll be like wearing iron geta.
They look cool.
The sakura blossom pattern is great.
Don't I look a little odd wearing them?
Very odd.
It pains me to say it!
Tamao-san, you should say how much you hate them!
That's alright.
I've already made up my mind.
'I Think You'll Like this Item!'
Last up to present his item is Matsumoto.
I don't think Tanaka was a million miles off.
To the one before?
But he was laughing at mine...
When thinking of one item for someone...
Think of hobbies.
What is that!?
£99/$142
This guy has no dignity at all.
It's a swimsuit.
It reminds me of my husband.
It reminded you of your husband?
Isn't that wonderful!!
Katsu Shintarō (1931–1997) was a Japanese actor, singer, and filmmaker.
That reminds you of Katsu Shintarō-san?
How does that...
This is the greatest thing I've ever done!!
I MADE HER THINK OF HER HUSBAND!!
When we went to Hawaii, he bought me a swimsuit like this.
But in the end, I didn't wear it.
That's ok, you can now fulfill that dream.
In the pool or whatever.
I see.
The sneakers and that are just...
A swimsuit is a proper item.
You can remember your husband as you're frolicking in the water.
So, which of these will be her favourite!?
Amongst these, which is your favourite!?
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Hamada
Endō
Hōsei
YEA...
She sure likes teasing us with this.
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Hamada
Endō
Hōsei
I'm looking forward to wearing these.
I get to keep these, right?
Of course.
Why did you choose these?
Why?
Because I like them.
Pretty simple reasoning.
Here, Tamao-san mistakingly says uchi instead of ie. They're very similar in meaning, kind of like うち(uchi) “home” and いえ(ie) “house”, but in this context sounds a little strange.
Back home I...
You mean back at my house.
So, Tamao-san, please pick out second place.
Let's go for simplicity, ok?
Matsumoto
Hamada
Endō
Hōsei
I want to take this too.
It's a little heavy... I don't have anything like this.
So Tamao-san, in third place is?
Matsumoto
Hamada
Endō
I kind of want this just to destroy it, but at least it's nostalgic.
So, which of these items will come in last!?
Which of these items does Nakamura Tamao dislike the most!?
Which one comes in last place?
Hamada
Endō
In last place...
Because it's itchy.
No matter where I go, I will never find a use for a hat.
This was a complete waste of money.
Endō has to pay a large penalty of 10,800 yen (£66/$95)!!
Just a moment...
Hamada-san, how much did you pay for those sunglasses?
500 yen (£3/$4)
No way!
It's a good job you didn't lose then.
It must have been tiring searching for these things.
Well, you get to take home your favourite items of the day.
What were they?
Your shoes and...
Shoes and...
Hamada-san's
Oh, the jumper, right.
You forgot all about that didn't you?
When she picked it you were so happy as well!
He'll forget the whole episode soon enough.
What did we do 30 minutes ago?