[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
The First Gaki No Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
The First Gaki No Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
Shimokitazawa Edition!
Alright!
Isn't he being really quiet?
You think so?
Maybe you're about to die?
It's because you're always telling me I'm loud!
You gonna die, or what?
Right, he always says that.
But Hamada is always saying how much he hates this program.
Do you hate it?
Please, just don't go home!
Actually Tanaka, what kind of bugs does this tree house?
Well this tree probably...
You ain't got to force a follow up!
I think this is a Ginko tree...
So there must be a reasonable amount of bugs living here.
This is our sixth time!
Our sixth time?!
We met Mr. Gajiro Sato last time.
Right, Mr. Gajiro.
This is our sixth time shooting this program!
I found it!
Hello!
Amazing!
They guys have successfully managed to meet countless celebrities!
What are you doing here?!
He's got a ton of tissues!
It's so raw!
Super raw!
And this time around, they'll be searching this area!
Shimokitazawa in Setagaya Ward!
A town of culture, full of theater and fashion!
Shimokitazawa is full of celebrities!
But the guys cannot go home until they find one. A harsh challenge awaits them!
Everyone, what do you think of Shimokitazawa?
Do you come here often?
I haven't been here in a while.
I used to live here.
Right, you lived so close.
Tanaka and I did.
Yes, I also lived around here for over 10 years.
So what's the deal? Are there a lot of celebs walking around?
I have met Jun Itoda from Speed Wago walking around.
(He participated in Documental S4)
I've also heard of celebrities holding concerts around here.
Something's up.
A musician?
There are a ton of band members around here.
-Band members?
-Yeah, band members!
And a lot of theater people.
There’s a ton of them!
Let's stroll around until we find a celebrity!
Shimokitazawa Edition!
These are the rules:
The shoot won't end until we meet a celebrity.
However, all members must know the celebrity's name.
And naturally, we also need filming consent from their respective agencies.
Now, will the guys find any celebrities in Komazawa?!
The time is 4:10 P.M.
Under the shining sun, the show starts!
The weather is super nice today...
It really is.
This is just the season in which all the celebs start coming out.
The guys are headed to the southern gate shopping district first!
It's really been a while since I've been back here.
It really has.
Right, we used to come here all the time, didn't we?
Yeah, we did come a lot back then.
Tanaka is ready to go!
Oh my god!
Have they found their celebrities already?!
Let's stroll around until we find a celebrity!
Shimokitazawa Edition!
It's really been a while since I've been back here.
It really has.
Right, we used to come here all the time, didn't we?
Yeah, we did come a lot back then.
A few minutes after starting, Tanaka spots someone!
Ah! Over there!
Who?
We're done!
It's over, right?
Sorry for disturbing you in your private time.
No worries.
You're married right?
-We sat next to you at Moto Sano's concert.
-Right, we did!
Matsumoto has no clue!
He completely forgot.
I mean, I specifically went there to see Motoharu Sano!
I didn't see who was sitting next to me!
Excuse us for a minute.
Just a moment please.
I have no clue.
Who are they?
Chocolat.
Huh?
Chocolat, they're musicians.
Chocolat?
What? THAT Chocolat?
What's with you?
Chocolat and Akito!
Formed in 2005, this duo is composed of husband and wife, Chocolat and Akito.
Regarded for their musicality and individuality, this duo has been highly regarded in the Japanese music world!
Are you sure they are famous?
Yes, I'm very very sure.
What about you?
Of course I know them.
Stop lying!
Come on man...
Stop joking around!
(TL Note: In the episode aired on May 15, 2016, the guys were trying to make Hamada say the phrase: "Stop joking around" on the day of his birthday, but he never said the words.)
You said it!
He said it!
(TL Note: In the episode aired on May 15, 2016, the guys were trying to make Hamada say the phrase: "Stop joking around" on the day of his birthday, but he never said the words.)
But it's too late now...
Why did you say it now?
(TL Note: In the episode aired on May 15, 2016, the guys were trying to make Hamada say the phrase: "Stop joking around" on the day of his birthday, but he never said the words.)
We wanted you to say it back then!
You're just casually blurting it out now?
Never mind, forget about it!
Sorry about that.
So sorry... By the way, what are you doing around here?
We were just strolling around.
-Is that so? Sorry to disturb you.
-No, don't worry.
Do you guys live around here?
-Ah no...
-Not at all.
We were just coming back from a gig.
Oh, you had a gig?
Oh no, we just came to see one of our friend's performances.
Oh, is that so?
You're on your private time, right?
-You're not working, right?
-That's right.
But we did meet at Motoharu Sano's concert.
No one but Tanaka could name them.
The task is not cleared!
Thank you.
-That was so fast!
-Thank you for everything!
Tanaka was the only one who knew!
Of course!
Are they famous?
Yes, they are super famous.
Really?
Yes, really.
I've heard their names.
I have heard of them.
You stop joking-
There you go again...
You said it again.
He was like: "Chocolat?!".
If you say "Stop joking around" again, I'm leaving.
I'm making that an extra rule!
He just said it again!
He was like: "Stop joking..." and stopped in the middle.
You sure are chatty today!
I just can't believe it!
For real!
A wonderful start!
Now, the guys head to the theater area, where plenty of people are waiting around!
This is where the theaters are, right?
-That's right.
-Yes.
There's a surprising amount of theaters around here.
And they're all super famous, like the Honda Theater.
Yeah, the Honda Theater.
And there's just apartments on top of the Honda Theater, huh?
Yes.
That's amazing!
I never knew that!
But this is gonna be hard... I don't know the names of any musicians or theater actors...
I'm never gonna know who they are.
We just have to do another lap and we'll run into Chocolat again.
And we'll be done.
But wouldn't that be super inconvenient?
Oh my, look at this.
Oh, it's Okada Ijiri.
So, today...
(It's customary to send a bouquet of flowers when a new play is opening)
Hide Nakayama!
Oh but it doesn't necessarily mean they're here.
They must be working here.
Oh, right.
We might be able to catch some of them if we wait around.
But we'd have to wait around.
So this is also a theater?
Yes.
Tanaka, keep an eye out.
I am.
I just feel like this is your day.
For real.
I'm so mad, we could have ended the shoot so quickly...
It really would have been the shortest episode.
We wouldn't even have had enough footage.
I'm expecting big things today.
Me too.
Is Shimokitazawa big?
Well, yes. It has all kinds of areas.
Really?
But it sure has changed!
It has!
For real.
It's completely different!
All the stores from the past have disappeared.
Yes...
Has it been about 10 years since you were last here?
Ah! The train station is gone!
The station is gone...
Everything went underground.
Oh, right!
There used to be an intersection here, but now everything's underground.
I met up with so many people in this station!
Here?
Yeah!
Shocked by the town's transformation, the guys keep looking!
She could be famous.
She must be a celebrity.
Should I ask?
A celeb?
They've found a candidate!
Hosei and Tanaka spring into action!
Are you a celebrity?
It's either a very fashionable girl, or a model whose name I don't know.
But he's taking a while...
How was it?
No luck.
So it was just a fashionable girl.
Indeed.
But you took so long to ask though...
-She was pretty cute.
-Right?
She has the aura of a celeb.
Is this the station?
Yes, but all of this used to be on a second story.
Before, you'd climb some stairs to get here.
Is that so?
Once again, the guys head towards the shopping district's south entrance, and begin their search northbound.
Did you spot anyone?
The girl with the coffee could be.
She looks like she could be someone.
Or maybe it's just another fashionable girl.
She looks very scared.
Of course she'd be scared.
Tanaka is scary.
She was just another fashionable girl.
No luck.
This is such a fashionable town!
She's not a celebrity, right?
So... Wait... Which way was Ohsho?
(Japanese restaurant chain)
It's over here.
So... Wait... Which way was Ohsho?
(Japanese restaurant chain)
It's over here.
I wanna eat some gyoza.
Again?
Yeah...
You were saying the same thing last time.
"I wanna eat gyoza"
I mean, I never get to go to Ohsho unless we're filming.
You were saying the same thing last time.
"I wanna eat gyoza"
I mean, I never get to go to Ohsho unless we're filming.
Right...
We never go.
Let's eat some gyoza, come on.
Gyoza!
I also wanna stop by the pharmacy!
Search inside the stores, you bastards!
We're looking...
You're just walking around doing nothing!
What show do you think you're on?!
You guys have to look at both sides of the street!
There's no need to be on edge on this show.
Just pay attention, that's all.
They could be inside these stores.
You're right, Hamada has been looking in the stores this whole time.
This brings me back!
This one's really famous, right?
It brings me ba-
Hello!
I used to come here all the time!
You brought us here, remember?
Right, right, right.
Hosei brought us here one time.
It's really good.
It looks delicious.
Yes, it's very good.
I remember when you brought us out here.
-Are you guys looking?
-It's fine, we'll be fine.
We're looking, we are.
I'm looking really hard.
We have to be quick or all the celebs will realize we're here.
Right.
They'll run away.
Those guys always run away...
We have to be quicker than them.
If we found some celebs from overseas I don't think I'd know...
Right, me either...
It's been 20 minutes since the guys started searching.
And now they are near Matsumoto's dear gyoza.
Alright, let's have a strategy meeting while we gulp down some gyoza!
We told you, no gyoza!
Why?
No one wants to eat gyoza!
Come on, let's go.
No way.
-This is so embarrassing!
-It's super empty!
Right.
It'd be really nice...
It's super empty now, we can get some gyoza, come on.
What does that have to do with anything?
Let's keep searching!
We can eat some of that Japanese food afterwards if we only get one portion of gyoza now.
This is not a food show, man.
We're looking for celebrities here.
But look, it's so empty inside...
We can eat some gyoza and have a look through the window. It'll be alright.
No, no, no...
You guys don't want some gyoza?
Not really...
No way!
Do you guys want some?
Now that you ask me... I don't really wanna eat....
For real?
Are you guys stupid?
Now that you ask me... I don't really wanna eat....
For real?
Are you guys stupid?
I don't wanna eat right now either...
I really hate all the Gaki members!
Do you wanna eat gyoza that badly?
There's gotta be someone around here!
Yes, I'm sure of it too.
But celebrities don't come to crowded places like this.
-Right...
-We have to move away.
They would never come around here.
-Right...
-We have to move away.
They would never come around here.
And there's a ton of very fashionable girls here...
Totally.
-Like... You really can't tell.
-Yeah, you can't tell.
Totally.
-Like... You really can't tell.
-Yeah, you can't tell.
Everyone is just dressed too nice.
Yes.
Sir, have you seen any celebrities today?
Not today, no.
Oh really?
So, who do you usually see?
Have you had any celebrity customers?
We get a lot of musicians.
Oh, musicians!
Artists.
Artists...
Artists, huh?
You're already drinking beer?!
At this hour?
Let him be!
Please, just take it easy.
Well, it's actually not that early.
You think so?
It's a bit early.
-Tanaka keep your eyes peeled!
-Yes!
You're the tallest of us all!
That's right, Tanaka you bastard!
You're the giant of the group.
I'm not that tall.
Height is the most advantageous in this show.
It doesn't make that much of a difference, you know?
What's with you?
You're as tall as an observatory.
Look from your heights.
Stretch!
There's tons of really famous thrift shops ahead.
Oh, really?
Let's go there.
There's tons of really famous thrift shops ahead.
Alright, let's go.
Let's go there.
Go and have a look inside.
I'll go check the top floor.
Alright.
Is there a store on the second floor?
Kokoriko go into the stores to look for potential celebrities!
Will they find them?
There were a lot of autographs hanging on the walls.
And it looks like Kan Nabeya was in yesterday.
He was here yesterday.
I would have wanted to meet him.
They also told me they get a lot of theater actors.
Kan Nabeya thrifts, huh?
There was also an autograph from the comedian, Yoshio Kojima.
This area is famous.
Oh, really?
I guess celebs really do come around here.
I can smell them closing in on us.
But I feel like there's a lot more up-and-coming comedians around...
Up-and-coming, not the really famous ones.
Right, I think so too.
And once again, Tanaka spots someone!
Tanaka has found a certain famous female celebrity, but she is not allowed to appear on our program.
Not Clear!
That was amazing.
That was pretty wild.
As expected.
This is what we expected of Shimokitazawa.
That was amazing.
Right?
Unfortunately we could not show her on camera but the boys have a refreshed sense of hope!
There are very few people around here.
Oh, something's going on.
Some celebrities could be getting their hair cut.
Have you seen any celebrities today?
-We haven't seen any today.
-Really?
Who do you usually see?
It's not good.
We get Mr. Emoto a lot.
Mr. Emoto?
Akira Emoto?
Which means his son could also be around.
Actors, huh?
I see.
There really are a lot of celebrities in Shimokitazawa.
Well yeah, we've already bumped into several people.
Doesn't this bring you back, Tanaka?
Yes, especially this area.
Hamada, do you remember this?
What? What?
The back of this building.
What back?
Someone was living here, don't you remember?
Ah! I remember!
It was Nitta, right?
-That's right!
-We came here with Gaki!
We sure did.
Right?
We came and dumped everything, including his mattress.
Next, the guys walk along Chazawa road towards The Suzunari.
-There's tons of stuff around here as well!
-Right, all the plays at the Suzunari!
The Suzunari side street has such a vibe.
Look, it's so vintage.
Should we really keep going forward?
There's nothing ahead, is there?
Look, it's so vintage.
Should we really keep going forward?
There's nothing ahead, is there?
-This area used to be a bit sketchy back then.
-Totally.
This area wasn't too popular.
And the railway crossing is now gone.
-You're right, it's all gone.
Yeah, this area used to be so great.
Whoa, I remember that bar!
The manager of that store gave me a kiss on the forehead when I was working part-time.
What the heck is that?
Was it a woman?
No, a male manager.
-Cause I was cute.
-Oh, really?
You really used to be cute back then.
Thank you.
-But now you're quite repulsive.
-Repulsive?
But you used to be really cute back then.
Thank you.
Totally.
It's been 45 minutes since the start of their search!
The guys have decided to take a break.
I'll have an iced coffee.
Iced coffee?
Let's get 5 iced coffees.
Why?
I don't wanna drink ice coffee though...
Everyone has their preferences.
Just drink the damn ice coffee!
You guys are such a pain!
Everyone has different tastes, right?
Just drink the damn ice coffee!
You guys are such a pain!
Everyone has different tastes, right?
I'll take a cafe latte.
Cafe latte?
Warm, please.
Warm.
Me too, I'll have a warm cafe latte as well.
Where did you learn about a drink like that?
The guys get their drinks 5 minutes later.
Three iced coffees.
My drink is the easiest one to make, right?
Yes, it's the easiest one. Thank you.
That's right.
You guys ordered all the most complicated drinks...
Latte? Where did you learn that word?
You're from the most rural part of Amagaski, you doofus!
"I'll take a latte", he says...
Well, we're still looking around, right?
Spotting someone while we sit here would feel so good.
Right, and it would be great if it was someone from Yoshimoto.
I'd love to meet Musashi right now.
Wazzup!
Oh, he replied!
-Is he a boxer?
-You box?
Yes, I'm a boxer.
Whoa! Amazing!
Kazuo Umezu's gotta be around here.
In Shimokitazawa?
He would stand out like a sore thumb.
Right...
Where is everyone?
What about Jun Kaname?
That'd be great.
Jun Kaname would be perfect.
Who would you like to meet, Endo?
I'd like to find Naotaro Moriyama.
He seems like the type to hang around here.
Naotaro Moriyama.
Were you fishing for laughs with that?
I just thought it would be great.
I figured he'd definitely hang around here, and I was also fishing for any laughs I could get.
Ok.
Was that good?
Thanks.
What about you Yamazaki?
Saburo Tokito.
You're just joking around now.
He really went hard.
But pros don't fall for those jokes.
But who are we gonna meet, really.
-For real now.
-For real?
I mean, there's all kinds of people around here.
Well, sure...
Oh, there they go again.
-Oh you're right, it's Chocolat.
-It's Chocolat again!
We could have cleared the mission since everyone knows their name already.
-Right?
-It would have counted.
Let's go on three...
-Chocolat.
I feel like we could also meet some porn stars.
No way.
I wouldn't know any of them.
I'd have no clue.
Do you know any porn stars?
I have absolutely no clue of who's doing what in the porn world.
I mean, me either..
Liar! You're the one that brought it up!
I was just saying... It was just an example.
Who? Who? Who?
I don't know anyone past Toyomaru.
That's like 30 years ago!
-Toyomaru was popular 30 years ago!
-Toyomaru?
That's the only one I know.
Was she the one that lied?
Or is that someone else?
Wasn't that Kuroki...
It's Hitomi!
Kuroki was the one with the "armpits stank"... I meant the "armpit hair".
They'll get mad at you.
And what's with the "armpit stank"?
-I was trying to say armpit hair.
-Right, hair!
This is getting out of control.
I was saying hair... Hair.
It was Kaori.
You mispronounced her name and then insulted her!
You got everything wrong!
What about that spot, Tanaka?
The search resumes! And the guys head towards the train station.
Over there.
Was it there?
I used to get drunk here.
Right, there used to be a bar.
Matsumoto always brought us here.
Tanaka, Yamazaki and I always hung out together, right?
That's right.
Huh?
This place is kinda nice, no?
Yes!
Isn't that Chad?
No way.
That's a woman.
A woman?
-It's a blonde girl.
-Running into Chad would have been great.
Sure, sure...
Is there a celebrity inside the store?
There isn't...
There's no one.
They said Ryuhei Ueshima comes here often.
Mr. Ryu?
That would have been great.
Mr. Ryu!
Celebrities are amazing, right?
They're everywhere.
They sure are.
They go around town.
This place looks good.
Let's eat some gyoza!
You're really craving some gyoza today!
I'm not really craving it...
But you just have to eat gyoza, you know?
You guys piss me off.
It's been 1 hour since the start of the search.
Oh no...
This might be bad.
The guys are not finding anyone.
A bad mood starts creeping in...
What are we gonna do?
There are less and less celebrity look-alikes.
Yeah...
What about her? She looks like a model.
You were just about to go crazy, weren't you?
They were just very excited and loud.
I was looking at you, and you were about to burst out in laughter.
They were super loud.
Have they finally found their celebrity?!
When the guys were about to give up...
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy! Oh my god!
Amazing!
What are you doing here?
What's up with this?
That's so embarrassing!
Right?
I mean, that's so embarrassing!
This is a bit too much!
There's something weird going on here!
I am just heading to a concert.
Where? Where?
Over there, that building.
-There?
-Yes.
That's such a typical Shimokitazawa venue!
We really met one of our guys!
This is amazing!
So, are we done?
-Of course!
-He's a celebrity!
Let's say his name first.
One... Two... Yoshi from Cowcow!
Thank you.
I mean, I had this idea of finding someone stylish walking around the streets of Shimokitazawa...
But then you came in rattling this thing around!
What the heck is this thing?
What is it, really?
Really, what is it?
An unfinished poster?
You're going to a concert, right?
Yes, it's for the 50th anniversary of this meat restaurant.
Oh, is that so?
Then we're done, right?
Right, we're done.
What's with everyone's lukewarm mood?
I mean, we see him all the time.
How anticlimactic...
What the heck...
You look almost pissed off at me.
You're about to explode!
I mean...
It's like opening your fridge and seeing eggs...
Like, "It's just eggs...".
"Eggs, huh..."
Right, right.
Totally.
That was crazy.
Thank you!