* Itao is watching! *
Downtown's Gaki No Tsukai's first. . .
"Knock away winter's coldness! Blazing Badminton Match!"
Well, let's get started!
Today, all of us are going to shake off the winter--
Okay, let's go!
First, we have Hamada-Endou team!
And next we have Matsumoto-Tanaka team!
- Haha. A dropkick!
- Okay, everyone! To the court!
- That sounded defeated at the end!
* Match start! *
- That was in!
- Which one was it? In or out?
We've got money on the line!
- Just a minute. Look over there.
- Who's that? - Is that. . . ?
That's Itao-san, isn't it?
- Ah! It is!
* A figure similar to Ittsuji Itao from 130R is looking down from the veranda *
- Is he worrying you? - Well, it is a little hard to do with him staring.
- He is staring pretty hard.
- Maybe someone should go up there?
- Fujiwara! (Downtown's manager)
- Itao's up there.
He's up there watching us.
- That is Itao.
Manager Fujiwara goes up to ask Itao to return to his room, because it's worrying the crew.
- Excuse me. Um...
Knowing that Itao is watching. . .
It's making it a little difficult for us.
- Why?
- Well, performing in front of someone they know...
makes them feel weird, knowing that it's you watching.
- Well just tell them "Don't worry about it".
Then you can just go ahead with it.
- We'd like to get done soon though.
- Ah. That's fine. I was about to step out.
- Oh, is that so?
Then hurry up and go.
- Are we okay now? - Okay. Let's go.
* The match resumes *
- That was out! Out!
- Look at it! It's way out!
- You can't swipe at it. Can't swipe at it!
- Again.
Eh, Fujiwara. Didn't he say he was leaving?
- Well, I did go up there and talk to him. Sorry.
- But didn't he say he was going somewhere?
- Yes. He was going out, so would be able to play.
- He hasn't even changed clothes.
I think the way you said it was too polite.
Maybe if you made it clear that this is a problem.
This time, numerous people go to talk to Itao.
- You guys could have kept going, couldn't you?
- Well they say it's hard to work with you staring.
- Why is that?
You don't have to say stuff like that.
Right?
- They are saying that it's difficult to work.
Oh, really?
- It's making them tense.
- Well, maybe it is.
- I understand. I get it. - Thank you very much.
* Finally, Itao returns to his room *
* The match resumes *
- I saw that! I saw it!
That was out! Out!
- This is Set Point!
- It's Set Point!
- Um... Wait a minute.
Sorry.
- Him again?!
Once again, Itao is watching the shoot on location.
- Does someone have my cell phone?
Yeah, Matsumoto. Call him.
- Hello.
- Itao? - Yes.
- Hey. It's Matsumoto. - Ah. Good morning.
- You probably already know this, but we're shooting on location today.
- It looks like you are, doesn't it?
- Well, sometimes you seem to be getting in the shot by accident.
- Ah! Is that so?
But, on the other hand. . .
I kind of thought of that.
But you're the one that came here on your own.
- That is true, but...
what are you doing?
- Well today is a day off for me. I was going to go out for a little while.
- At what time?
- I'll just step out, then.
- Really? Well, whenever you're ready.
- But what's is with all of this?
Normally, you'd be fine.
* Suddenly Itao gets mad * - You decide to shoot on location here.
- Well, do you mind if I put you on with Suga-san?
- Sure.
- He seems like he wants to talk to you.
- Hello.
* Because Itao is getting angry, they pass the phone over to producer Suga *
Hi, this is producer Suga from Nihon TV.
- Ah, hello. - Good mo~rning!
We wouldn't have a problem if it was just the general public.
But now they're all thinking, "Isn't that Itao?"
And the viewers are going to be look up there too.
- I get all that, but you came here and this is MY house.
What's with all of this?
Was it something I did?
- No it's not like that at all.
- But you are talking like I did do something wrong.
Even though I'm a fan of Nihon TV. That's unfortunate.
- Well, we thank you watching and supporting us, but...
- That makes you feel bad, doesn't it?
Getting told something like that over the phone.
- I am personally asking you.
It is rude for me to ask something like this of you.
But for obvious reasons, we're here covering an event, and would appreciate your cooperation.
*Producer Suga brings up the idea of giving some money in return *
- Well, if there's nothing else...
I mean, if I'm not going to get anything else from Nihon TV.
Something heartfelt.
- Once again, we're trying to shoot here, so we're asking for cooperation.
- Well, that has some substance to it.
- Thank you. Without a doubt, when we finish, you can feel free to do as you please.
- Well, there's no reason for me to make demands, then.
* Finally, Itao returns to his room again *
- I never thought he'd get angry like he did.
But let's do this before he comes back.
- When we left off, it was Set Point.
* The match resumes *
* This time Itao is calling Matsumoto on his cellular phone *
- Hello?
- Hello. It's Itao.
Do you mind putting Suga on again?
- Hello. - Hello.
You know what happened before?
All that stuff that started to take form...
Are you going to be paying Yoshimoto? (Itao's and Downtown's Talent Agency)
Then are they going to be spreading it on to me?
- This is more of a personal matter, isn't it?
So it should be fine if I just pay you directly, correct?
- Well, if you put it like that... that's completely fine with me.
But when you do, make the check out to "130R's Itao".
As an "Appearance on a TV program" fee.
- HUH?!
- Did something just come up?
- A fee?!
- Of course so.
If I were an amateur, you probably wouldn't have a problem.
- Wait a second.
* This time, Itao is requesting an appearance fee *
This is a shot on location, so it's not like we asked him to be here.
- Tell him an "I'm sorry, but..." type of thing.
His wife is probably behind this, calculating the plan.
It's like he's doing all this for his wife.
- Hello. As for the fee...
It will be paid to Yoshimoto, assuming you do this.
- So all of that is okay? - Yes, yes.
- If that's true, do you mind if I just come and get it myself?
- HUH?!
- I'm was just about to go out.
- You mean if you come and get it? - Along those lines, yeah.
I'm not really saying anything.
I'm just saying, in case if you to say so...
I'm the one that brought up the whole fee thing.
So I don't know whether I can come collect it or not.
But if it came down to it, it would be fine if I just came down there, wouldn't it?
I am already going out and all.
* Suga reluctantly bargains with the persistant Itao *
- He said he's coming down personally to get the money.
- He hasn't changed clothes at all!
- Didn't he say he was going somewhere?
- He said because he was going somewhere, he'd just come get it.
- You were going somewhere? - Yes, I was about to go.
This flew into my house, by the way.
- This one just flew in?
- Maybe my wife appeared on camera too...
- Well, we don't know if that happened.
- But we know that I was in the camera.
- We will cut that out, in postproduction.
- But since I was on film...
- Will that might be, but those shots were no good.
- But I think you got my wife on camera.
So, you're all the staff?
* For some reason, Itao suddenly takes a photograph *
- Well, this is what we talked about...
* Suga hands the promised money over to Itao *
- Haha. He was covering it up.
- Sorry for all the trouble.
Sorry for bothering you.
- So what do we do about the wife, if we got Itao's wife on film too?
-If that happened, instead of an appearance fee...
she'd probably take us to court.
- Probably, that's why he took that evidence photo.
- Just in case it came to that?
- So, who won and who lost?
* Everyone loses their will to continue the shoot *
- In the end, both teams lose.
- Everyone loses.
* Everyone loses! *
- Well, it can't be helped.
* This story is fiction. *