Translation by Sara & SJKaarosu
Subtitle by SJKaarosu
Someday in April, at Nippon Television
At the Gaki no Tsukai Shooting
Regular members and 5 guests are invited
Nobody knows what they're going to do...
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende! Chiki Chiki!
Audition quiz! Who cares about the quiz winner? Good Boy Contest!
So, this audition will replace all Gaki members!
Wait, hold up
So it's like this
Downtown has the concept of kindness, we want to be sweet all the time.
We want to be ser-sur-surrounded by good boys.
Ser-surrounded?
Boys like wafers.
I can totally understand
I don't care who wins.
I just want to know who is a good boy.
It's a quiz battle to become a regular member!
But it has nothing to do with the quiz!
It's all about if you're a good boy or not!
The judgment is done by Matsumoto, using these buttons.
Each time he thinks they're a good boy, they get 10 points.
The five who have the highest points, become the new regular members.
However somehow, some of them don't start from zero...
Is it fine if I ask something?
Yes
Umm, why am I starting at -10 points?
Because you're divorced.
And Inomoto also has -40 points.
Why am I also on -40 points?
Because you kind of have the eyes of a thieving cat.
Then why do I have 30 points?
It's because you have such high potential in being a good boy.
But Matsumoto-san, I feel bad for having 30 points...
Could you divide my points equally between everyone?
Tanaka, Good Boy!!
Right now he's doing really well at being nice.
Well then Matsumoto-san, I need to be the best partner for Inomoto
So, I'll also take the burden of having -40 points.
Fujiwara, Bad Boy!!
It doesn't work like that.
Do you think I'm stupid?
Some of today's guest haven't spoken yet, can we start?
I believe it's because they're trying to be good.
Oh really?
They can't cut into our conversations.
We couldn't cut into the conversation because it was funny enough, it was very funny.
What do you mean by "enough", Hosshan?
Yagi!
I know we're not supposed to take the quiz seriously, but I want to enjoy it too.
Yagi, Good Boy!!
This is good.
Should be like that.
Yagi-kun, your face is somehow stiffening.
You sure are very nervous.
Ok then, the first game is "What's your nickname?!"
People will show up in here, so give them the best nickname.
Alright!
It is just so easy guys.
It's just so easy.
Starting with the first person, come out please!
Obviously this man has some weird stuff on his head.
Give the best nickname for him, without hurting his feelings.
This is a quiz buzzer round, go!
The left hand user.
Uuh, the most advanced.
The ace relief pitcher.
Hossan, Very Good Boy!!
That was good.
Not bad.
Uuh, Mr. Delivering-Lost-Property
It's not bad, if only he could say it more clearly.
Go ahead.
Discovery Channel
Buffalo A, Very Good Boy!!
Was that good?
Now let's ask him what his real nickname is.
It's "Forehead".
I see
Old Man, Very Good Boy!!
Next up is a man whose head is weird and keeps looking upwards.
This man is a little unique.
That's right, a little unique.
Go ahead.
Mr. Intentionally
Not bad
The witness of history.
Go ahead.
The doll of May.
Okay, let's go.
Who should we go from?
A pinch hitter.
Fujiwara, Quite A Good Boy!!
I see.
Academy Award for Best Short Film.
Buffalo A, Very Good Boy!!
Is that alright?
Excuse me, please now tell us your real nickname.
It's "General"
"General"?
Can you tell us the reason?
People at my workplace call me so.
General is younger than me!
Daishiro Tamai (47)
Maybe the nickname is for his huge presence which people around his age usually don't have.
I see, I was really surprised. But thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
OK, now for the last person, please come out!
Ah, I see, so it's this woman, alright, go ahead.
Next up is a woman with big breasts, what is her nickname?
They are big though, aren't they?
They are.
Go ahead.
A woman who wuldvesin is a PV by Keisuke Kuwata, ah would be seen.
Buffalo A, Bad Boy!!
What.. what are you saying?
Go ahead
A miracle.. of big melons.
Wait hold up, you guys need to at least be able to speak clearly.
Go ahead
The nurse room
Daikichi, Very Good Boy!!
I see
Go ahead.
Woman from 10pm
Endo, Not A Good Boy!!
Not a good boy.
So please tell us your real nickname.
It's "Fujiko-chan"
* A sexy female character from anime Lupin III)
Aah~ her nice body~
Thank you very much.
The alarm is ringing, what is it?
It's "Macchan's Direct Negotiation" corner.
I'm going to give you the quiz directly, so please answer it quickly.
Alright then, thank you very much.
Is it understood?
Yep
If a puppy was drowning in the river, what would you guys do?
This is a quiz buzzer round guys. Go ahead.
I don't even want to think about something so tragic.
Kawashima, Good Boy!!
I see.
Not bad
Yes, let's go.
Of course I would go save it's life right away, but also scold the owner very badly.
Fujiwara, Not A Good Boy!!
Too long, it's too long.
Too long, it can't be too long.
It's hard to imagine due to the width and depth of the river,
But I would scream at the top of my lungs!
Daikichi, Incredibly Good Boy!!
I really love his courage.
Go ahead.
I would save his life, dry it's fur and then keep it for the rest of it's life.
Yagi, Very Good Boy!!
He would keep the puppy for the rest of it's life. That's wonderful isn't it?
Now for a different question.
Please sing us a Good Boy Song~
The theme is to sing a Good Boy Song.
I see.
Yes, go ahead.
Yes, Yamazaki-san
Mother, thank you
And Father, for working so hard for us, thank you.
Yamasaki, Very Good Boy!!
A very good boy. Wonderful. Really good.
Was that really an improvisation?
Makes your heart flutter, doesn't it?
Let's get on with it.
Go ahead.
Yagi-kun go ahead.
Go home~ When you come home from outside
You should wushyohinds (Wash your hands)
What the?
Yagi, Incredibly Bad Boy!!
What the hell?
What the hell is he saying? We don't understand him.
The beginning was also hard to listen to.
Not being able to say what you want, is also part of being a good boy?
All of them have gained some points, now we are heading towards the next game.
What is inside the box?!
This game also has nothing to do with whether or not you're correct.
It's all about whether or not you're a good boy!
First up, Yamasaki takes on the challenge.
The others members have a chance to show their goodness during Yamasaki's try.
Please take care.
You guys don't need to cheer me on so much, it's not good for your throats.
OK, let's move on, the first challenge is this one!
Please stop, please stop.
This is a bit...
Please take care.
Please be careful.
Really please be careful, you could get injured.
Hamada-san should also be careful, his hand might hurt you.
What do you mean? What do you mean? Hamada?
Ah, it's just that I thought Hosei-san's hand would be dangerous for Hamada-san.
I see.
Endo, Good Boy!!
I really love your care for Hamada.
I'll be very careful with my hands, so that you don't get hit.
We've talked enough about hands, let's move on, enough of Hamada's care.
I'll do it slowly
Let's go slowly.
Wow, I really appreciate the staff. Thank you, this box is really soft.
What do you mean?
The place where he puts his hand in
That was really nice of you to notice.
This really is super soft!
Who made this? Thank you very much.
Move on, move on.
Why doesn't he give me any points?
It's alright, it's alright, let's move on.
Woah, he doesn't show any hesitation!
Is it alright (to answer)?
It's alright
You know it?
I really appreciate all the staff, thank you very much, the answer is 6 scrubbing brushes.
Yamasaki, Bad Boy!!
You didn't speak clearly, again.
You can't do that, right?
I did want to give you points
Sorry.
Ah, sorry for this.
Right now did you guys see how Hamada-san showed me the way back to my place?
Then what kind of feeling did you get from Hamada?
I'm just... Thank you!
Yes, there is such a thing.
Well done. Good job.
Next up, Hosshan takes the challenge.
Is it.. ok for me to go?
Yes. It's fine. Go ahead.
The tape, be aware of the tape.
In case there isn't any left.
Oh camera crew. You guys don't need to film me if the tape is running out.
Hosshan, Quite A Good Boy!!
That's really good, he's a good boy.
Here is what's inside of the next box!
Hold up. This is a bit...
This is..
Please really take care. Take care. Be careful!
Go slowly. Do it slowly. Be careful. Take care.
The lid of the box.. it's not the same as before.
That's right.
Once the inside has been changed, the lid has also got to be changed.
Should go from this side? This side?
Hosshan, Not A Good Boy!!
Is that scary?
Good boys don't do this when they're scared.
I was trying to get in, but it was already there, so...
Either way, I'm sorry.
Do it nicely.
I'm fine.
It's a living thing. Be careful. Do it nicely. Do your best.
It's coming out.
Right now you can't look at your hands.
It came out! Just now.
Look from this side.
Don't look at it. Look away.
Ow ow ow ow ow it hurts.
Did it hurt?
It doesn't hurt.
Did it bite you?
It bit me.
Are you serious?
Yes, like a person would do.
How was it? Did you figure it out?
I know it's a living thing.
I see.
Then the answer is one of the living things.
That's fine.
Excuse me! The answer he gave just now, could you take it as correct?
What do you mean?
Because..
..what he's trying to say is korret, right?
Is correct, right?
What's wrong with this guy? He's weird today.
Next up, Kawashima from Kirin
Be careful.
Ok let's go, this is what's inside the box!
So, Kawashima, what's inside the box
Wait, this is...
Excuse me...
Woah. Is this ok?
He's doing this just to be good. He's doing this just for goodness.
Kawashima, Good Boy!!
Right now, he still hasn't made contact.
Yep
Smile. Do it nicely. Nicely. It's living.
Use the back of your hand. The back is good.
That's great.
Smile! Keep smiling! Smile!
I kind of feel like you're not a good boy.
That's right.
You should smile!
Your gaze is a bit..
It has wrinkles on it.
That's good. Good!
Maybe you should try picking them up from the bottom once.
That's good. Yeah, like that!
Just hurry up and let them bite your fingers.
Hamada, Not A Good Boy!!
These snakes are usually very dangerous, but today they are harmless.
How will Kawashima handle this hopeless situation by being a good boy?
Umm, can I look inside and let them bite me myself?
Kawashima, Good Boy!!
It's coming out. No way. Don't. It's coming out.
So this, this was inside the box?
That's right.
Then Kawashima-kun, you're going to do it by yourself?
By myself.
Err.. he's using the slide door now.
He's grabbing the snake like it's nothing.
That's good. It's ok. That's good.
Kawashima, Good Boy!!
Woah, awesome! Cool!
Wow...
Woah, that was amazing. No way.
Now, should we ask him, what is the correct answer?
I don't know what the right answer is.
Kawashima, Good Boy!!
Kawashima, Incredibly Good Boy!!
That was amazing.
That was awesome. Amazing. Good job.
It's my first time seeing someone taking such care of what's inside the box.
Putting a plaster on.
Let me do it for you. No it's fine.
Give it, give it.
I want to wear it just once.
Buffalo A, Quite A Good Boy!!
Buffalo A, Very Good Boy!!
Buffalo A, Incredibly Good Boy!!
What if they have poison?
They don't have poison so it's fine.
Kawashima, Quite A Good Boy!!
Excuse me, isn't that camera heavy? I'll take it for you.
Endo, Very Good Boy!!
Endo, Incredibly Good Boy!!
ENOUGH!!!
Go back to your places quickly.
Are you ok?
The next game is Intro Quiz!
The rules are simple.
As soon as you figure out a song name, go get the ping pong ball, go to the mic and sing.
Those who aren't playing should give good boy comments to gain points in between.
OK, let's go, Intro Quiz!
* This song was Hamada's hit song when he was young called WOW WAR TONIGHT
Ah this is. Oh it's this. It's really this.
What's wrong? Who's going to sing?
Do you know it?
I kn- Yes.
He's got it.
Oh no.
What's wrong? Huh? What's happening?
What's wrong?
Wrong Answer
I'm sorry, I knew the song but I'm not great enough to sing this song.
Inomoto, Incredibly Bad Boy!!
Bad?
In that situation, you should have sung the song.
I see.
Second Round
Let's start the next song, Intro Quiz!
Ah, it's this.
Is it ok? OK.
Are you ok?
Sorry...
I'm sorry for the next person who touches this.
* He's singing a very famous song from a High School Drama
What's wrong, Hosshan?
Please do your best.
Please do your best!
What's going on Hosshan?
I'm sorry!
Wrong Answer
What's happened Hosshan? You were nearly there.
This song REALLY reminded me of the drama.
The scenery from the drama made me cry.
Hosshan, Incredibly Good Boy!!
I'm sorry.
Hosshan, Very Good Boy!!
I'm sorry for this.
Good job. You did well.
What's wrong Yamazaki?
His tears made me cry.
So ugly!
Yamasaki, Very Good Boy!!
Third Round
Let's go, Intro Quiz!
I know this song.
Ah he's got it.
Endo, Incredibly Bad Boy!!
What's going on?
Everyone please be understanding, I thought out of everyone I would be best to mimic the song.
Really, you guys can't do it?
No. I can't do it. Of course Endo's the best.
Really?
That's right, I can't ask "What time is it?" in such a rude way like he does.
I could only ask if it's "If you don't mind, could you tell me what time it is now, sir?"
Daikichi, Very Good Boy!!
Hosshan, you can't do the imitation?
No. I can't. I was the one who told Endo to try mimicking in the first place.
Oh no you don't have to say that.
Hosshan, Quite A Good Boy!!
Endo, Very Good Boy!!
Hosshan, Incredibly Good Boy!!
Endo, Incredibly Good Boy!!
Yamazaki, what's wrong?
Their friendship makes me cry.
Yamasaki, Incredibly Good Boy!!
What is wrong with him?
Wow, what a nice shoot we're having today.
The quiz battle to become a regular member is in confusion.
And in this moment...
What's happening?
Macchan's Direct Negotiation!
Great. Thank you. Cool.
What can you say to Kobayashi Sachiko-san?
* She had trouble with her manager
Yes, Tanaka.
I'm always with you.
Tanaka, Very Good Boy!!
That was good.
It was good.
Yep.
Yes, go ahead.
Some of your troubles was caused by me.
Hosshan, Incredibly Good Boy!!
Of course!
You've got a really great sense of responsibility! Such a huge defense zone!
It's really great!
Eh? Something happened to you?
Daikichi, Good Boy!!
This kind of sympathy really helps.
Is this ok? No more answers.
People who've had a long career, like Yamazaki, should come up with something.
Kobayashi Sachiko-san, I'm watching you.
What you've done, is incredible.
I'm supporting you..
Sachiko-san...
I love your outfits.
Understand?
Oka~y.
Thank you very much.
So, Matsumoto-san, who are the good boys who will become the regular members?
Is it ok to wait a bit?
What's wrong, Yamazaki-san?
For doing such a great audition like this one, for us all, I thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I should be thanking you.
Oka~y.
The winner please.
The top 5 who were the best at being good boys, is...
Everyone is a good boy!
You all did it!
Thank you very much.
All of you were good boys!
Amazing.
Foe ebrii sekom (for every second), you were all good boys!
No worries.
It's fine.
Didn't he say "foe ebrii sekom"?
I'm just overwhelmingly impressed!
Oka~y