It's year 2011
With an unusual determination in his heart
There was a man who started the new year with an unshakable determination
Good evening everyone
It's Yamasaki Hosei
Today, as a matter of fact
I'm going to show you that I have
an exquisite sense of tsukkomi humour
Actually
When I debuted as a duo, I did tsukkomi
To be fair, I'm not now as good in tsukkomi, as I was before
(Director Komurasaki - nickname Kom)
Komu
Yes
(Director Komurasaki - nickname Kom)
When I'll be doing it
Yes
I'll be counting on your help
Right now
The main Gaki cast
are already inside
I told them to do
any kind of boke set up
I don't know what kind it will be
But someone
out of these four, I donreeli know who will do it
This year was positioned as the first year of the Tsukkomi
A man with 24 years of experience in the arts.
Using his own extraordinary sense of style
From the phrases that he unfolds
To his timing of them
He will demonstrate high quality tsukkomi
Let's go?
Let's go inside
The other four were waiting for him
For the first time we are going to witness
exceptional quality boke and tsukkomi!
Greetings everyone!
Good day
Right away, Hamada
Performs a boke with his pigtails
When and what kind of tsukkomi phrase will Yamasaki unfold?
It's quite warm in here
It's warm, isn't it?
Yes, but outside it's quite cold
Indeed, on the outside
Wellm how shall I put it
When I came suddenly inside, it felt really warm
You're right
It's like a body sensation
What did you order?
Hot coffee
Hot coffee? And Endo?
Ice tea
And what about Hamada san?
What is this?
Ice oolong
I see
Well, I'll order something as well
Excuse me?
Please, this is our drink menu list
Something hot
Can I please have oolong tea?
Thank you very much
It's so elaborate...
From the cold
Your back can get stiff
Don't they?
Sorry for your waiting, here's your hot tea
Please
I wondered if they'd give me a pot...
WHY DO YOU HAVE PIGTAILS!?
"High quality tsukkomi explosion"
How did I do?
Honestly, a lot of tsukkomi ideas come to mind
Right?
I thought, is it always like this!?
The thing is, my level of boke and tsukkomi do not match at all
And it's so painful
I don't understand it at all...
The atmosphere
I don't get the atmosphere... It's so tough!!
Hamada san says, he has a funny face
He's proud of it...
I think, I'm back in form now!!
But somehow
I'm back in shape
I'm still rambling about boke!!
I think, I understand the atmosphere a bit more now
Is he still talking?
His commentary is still in progress
Confidence in where he went wrong
For a comedian who was not well liked, isn't easy to leave the dressing room!!
It's like he's gossiping in the back
I wonder if he'll say anything, when he returns
Why does he use this red carpet for?
It's very important for him
It seems like it
This time
Mysterious schoolboy appears
What quality of tsukkomi will Yamasaki demonstrate?
...no, but I didn't go that far in the past...
Is that so?
A long time ago...
Excuse me!
Yes?
Hot oolong please
Yes, please wait for a moment
You really like hot oolong?
It was quite cold, I'm already chilled to the core
One needs to warm up a bit...
I wish I could go somewhere warm
Wouldn't it be nice...
It's a bit tough on location, this time of year
It's quite freezing... Thank you for your order
Here is your hot oolong tea
Please
Thank you
Enjoy it
This one will warm me up
It's so warm
Where did you buy it?
This thing?
I bought it in Shibuya
Because it's (chest) quite open
I wonder if you feel cold?
That was probably an old man's idea
Young kids are surprisingly open these days
I definitely wouldn't be able to... You'd be quite cold?
If I'll open it completely...
WHAT IS THIS SCHOOLBOY DOING HERE!?
That's the first time I made a joke and Hamada san became surprised
I didn't think I'd be that good, but this time I did great
I did the timing right
And then the choice of words!!
There were various tsukkomi ideas circulating in my head
That was such a bland tsukkomi
He just asked what is this student doing here
It's not just normal, but the choice is strange
Are they still saying they're going to do it?
Do they?
Well, if that's the case
I'll keep up with them
If he'll order that tea again we can guess
That it's part of his tsukkomi
That's right...
Somehow...
Alright, alright
Endo provokes with a challenging boke (Kiyoshiro Imawano)
However, will Yamazaki
complement this boke
with his sharp tsukkomi!?
Oh, my back...
Do you know if a typhoon
will or won't come?
At this time?
That's unusual, this time of year
I thought there's going to be one
I don't think there are any at this time of year
Can I have something cold?
Excuse me?
Yes
Can I have something properly cold!!
I'll go, have a pee real quickly
If you excuse me
I understand
He's causing so much trouble
Can't he just stick with oolong?
That's right
What's up with him?
Yamasaki rests in the toilet
To complement Endo's boke
we'll give some freedom to Yamasaki
So, they did it like that
I'm talking about memories from when I was in secondary school
That's rough
Again, they went with such rough boke
It brings back memories of my secondary school days
I've been through a lot, you know, I've been in clubs and stuff
It's a great distraction to remember all those things
Well, I'll manage somehow
'cause I've managed to do it so far
It's not even tsukkomi any more
He's more like skidding in place
Of course typhoon would never come here now!!
And his back is absolutely fine!!
Each time he does it like that. In a lame way
He's panicking right now
His options are getting narrower and narrower
When he looked through the scope of his options this size
His panic spread fast
That's as much as he could see
Alright, let's do it!
What was he doing?
Thank you for waiting
What's that?
Oolong tea?
I might be too sweet, though
Speaking frankly...
But you know
That's your usual cold oolong tea
What's that thing that oolong tea has?
There's an ingredient like that, that kind of thing
I can't help much with such descriptions "like that" or "ahh that one"
You're right
That's true
My body...
How many times did he mention it?
"5 minutes later"
What kind of place do you go to and
how long does it usually take everyone to get a haircut?
A haircut?
I just do this myself in the bathroom once a week
That sounds great
But that's
Well, well
I wonder if it's really that great
I thought you were going to ask everyone?
Why don't we have a meal?
Why don't we order some?
Let's try different meals
I'll order some
Excuse us
There's so much alcohol in the menu
Can I make an order?
Go ahead
Then, can I have
Chow mein...
What's that?
Chow mein style
fried soba
1200, wait 1250
Why are you from "Bad Rouge Magic"?
Enso's effort was worthless
That was so bad
That was so badly done
That was so terrible. What did want to say?
Chu?
He said Chu
I have no trust anymore in you, Kom
Why can't I have a "Rouge Magic" memory of me in junior high school?
Because I remember when I was in junior high school, that used to be a funny gag
Well, you've said it clear
I did not!
Just as I was about to do it, I just sucked in my breath...
I'm sorry
Give me more time
I will definitely do it
I understand
You know...
The sun is setting fast
I thought it was getting late
Around the end of the year, it's even earlier. Around 5:30
So fast
Here's your order
Why don't we have some food?
Here's your spaghetti
That looks delicious
Here's your Indian sweet and sour pork
Boke with Indian sweet and sour pork
Will Yamasaki be able to perform a precise boke?
Looks delicious
Looks great
With what emotions shall I eat it?
Why is it stuffed with feathers?
What kind of dish is it?
I don't understand
That was a disaster
I was looking so much forward
For him to say something
That's true
"What kind of dish is it?" He asked it, right?
Because of his earlier mistakes. Kom waited for too long
That's right
That's quite troublesome
This time I'm a bit...
I disbelief grew even more in Kom, but
I think, somehow now, I am in shape!!
Finally, I'm saved...
Finally, I'm saved? What does he mean?
When I'm doing it
During that moment, all my boke gags
mix up
I had to deal with lychee
which had a lot of feathers
Lychee?
Is there a lychee?
It doesn't have any!
Well, that's
quite simple, he's just presbyopic
He saw meatballs as lychee!
He did it indeed
That's right
What was that?
I had no luck with that thing!!
The rest got ready with new boke prop
That should be easy to understand
Lobster tails from Matsumoto's nostrils
Can he do it as soon, as he gets here?
All the time, once he sees us, he already grins
Is that so?
And then he does it like that
He's been pretending to be unwell for too long!
"I'm not feeling well" "My body hurts"
For this boke when and
what kind of tsukkomi will Yamasaki perform?
I feel a lot better
What's that?
You see...
I don't know if I twisted it around here
Over here
Perhaps, you've sprained your neck?
YOU CAN'T DRINK IT!!
BEACUSE YOU'RE CROSSED OUT!!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO THINK!!
WHAT'S GOING ON???
It's finally over
He's hopeless!
What the hell did he do?
I wondered what's wrong with him, and now it's clear that he's simply bad at it!
They laugh, they laugh!
They laugh so much!!
I think I get it now
I wonder, if that's my hot instict?
You're right
Although, the timing
had no role here...
I think
it came before my mouth
Before? I see
I'll go with that!!
But January...
or February...
February came too fast...
Tanaka goes full force with double boke
Will Yamasaki face this boke
with a 100% tsukkomi?
That was fast...
It's so dry right now
I usually heat up the water to 30 degrees
To 30 degrees?
Me as well, after a rough day
I'd open the bathroom door and leave the shower on for a bit
For around 5 to 10 minutes
So, you dry up like that?
ARE YOU SURPRISED!?
FOR SOME TIME
YOU'RE EYES ARE POPPING OUT!!
AND YOUR TONGUE IS STICKING OUT
WHAT'S THE MEANING OF IT?
YOU SCARED THE SHIT OUT OF ME!!
That's just horrible
He's hopeless
That was shit
That's shit
Just leave the industry already
Hey!
Tanaka, you completely destroyed him!
I've put a lot of effort into this!
How was I?
I liked it a lot!
Because I pulled the gag, that Tanaka would look funny
When I did it
Tanaka can barely stand up after that!
You're probably Japan's first man with eyes and tongue popping out of his head!
Isn't it right?
You've challenged others now
Because you did it for the first time, I want it to be established
He did so shit!!
That was so shit...
That went really bad
Even NSC (Yoshimoto New Star Creation) newcomers will say that he's shit!
This time the mysterious schoolboy is at an extraordinary setting
How will Yamasaki
handle this boke?
It's already February
I have a Birthday
You have a Birthday, right?
I'm done with my medication
I'm done with it
And you know...
I'm very happy
When this Birthday will come...
I WON'T BE HAPPY ANYMORE!!
DID SOMEONE DIE?
IT MAKES ME FEEL SAD
WHY, WHY DID YOU BRING IT HERE?
TELL ME!!
OH, FINE
That was a forced finish
What do you think, TV viewers?
If you have anything to write with you
I'd like you to write a few words
Please write Yamasaki = shit performer
If you can get it written
We're sorry that you had to go along with some weird stuff
Don't ever be like that guy!