There is an inn where a group of liars have gathered
You!
You cheated and took a day off!
I didn't cheat!
Hosei took a day off because he had influenza
Why'd you do that?
I didn't cheat!
You did!
You could've shown up still!
I definitely couldn't have, sorry
The 4 had to endure the cold in summer clothes
No, listen-
It was hellishly cold!
It was so cold!
I had it tough too!
I got a brand new hemorrhoid the next day!
That cold made a lot of hemorrhoids appear
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Hamada Masatoshi
Tsukitei Hosei
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
It was that cold
That could happen
Indeed
Because of that shoot?
I wanted to take part!
You've got it wrong!
"Were you alright?"
Nobody asked me that!
For one thing-
"Are you alright? You got influenz!a" - None of you said anything!
Then fine,
Did you get the vaccine afterwards?
Yes did you?
Like I said~ I couldn't get it
So irritating
What the hell?
Why didn't you?
What's with that condescending "Like I said~"
Like we've made him explain this already
On DownTown DX he wanted us to make fun of his bald spot and get laughs,
But then he went "please cut it out :("
Yeah
He had a blatantly pissed off expression
Eh? But it's funny!
Right?
Everyone's laughing
Right
He's balding, and they're laughing!
But then he goes "enough already :("
I'm not even balding
No no no
You're balding!
Look look look
I can see it
Hosei-san
It's been like this for years, I don't really,
I see, so if we say that,
I don't see it
It's like we're lying?
It's bad for you?
It's bad for me
Hmm
Well that's unfortuante
So that's why
Don't every say it again please
It's not that big a deal
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
An inn full of liars!
See how they maintain the lie!
Totally improvise
Everything!
Liar's Inn
Totally Improvise Everythin! Liar's Inn
Whoever's card get's selected picks someone to tell a massive,  plausible, or small lie
Whoever gets picked has to run with the theme and keep up the lie!
Alright, the cards have been shuffled
Yes
So someone will come up
It's scary
This is scary right?
It is
It is, for the person who gets picked too
Go ahead Hamada
Eh?
Here I go
Yes
Hamada will pick someone to tell a massive  lie
Hamada-san picks a massive lie right?
A massive lie right away?
A massive one first?
Hamada can pick anyone right?
That's right
Hmm
You...
I've head you,
You're being targeted by the FBI?
Eh?
That's an American agency too
Eh? You're joking
You're joking
No hold on, this is, I am,
I'm really pissed off at the FBI now
Eh?
They said "Don't tell anyone!" so I kept quite about it,
I wanted to make a joke about, so I did actually want to mention it
I thought saying it out loud would be safer
But the FBI told me "I won't say anything, so you shouldn't either"
So I didn't tell anyone, but if Hamada knows then they told someone right?
That's true
That's why right now
I'm really pissed of at him
Him?
There are specific people?
There are
But why?
I don't get the point
Out of the blue they asked me "Is it alright?"
They asked "Is it alright if we target you?"
Directly to you?
Did you do something bad?
It was last week, for real
Last week?
Last week
Umm,
Over there
In the Shinbashi area
Why there?
The FBI, in Shinbashi?
In the Shinbashi area, they asked "Is it alright if we target you?"
Was the FBI guy Japanese?
Yeah?
I wonder what nationality he was
He was a East-Asian
There's a lot of people like that
But you must've done something then, right?
It was like, they needed to decide on who to target
It was really weird! I thought he was lying or something
I have no clue what you're saying
What are you saying?
I can't follow this at all
Are you not lying?
What did you do?
No no, I really didn't,
In Shinbashi, I parked my car,
I had to buy something
I had to pay 300 yen
Oh yeah
I was gonna pop in and out in less than a minute
So I thought "Well it's fine if I don't pay"
But right then, someone stopped me "hold on there"
"Who the hell is this guy" I thought
He said "You're that guy right?"
"You're a celebrity aren't you?"
Oh yeah I know the type
He probably knew you
Well that's-
But why did he ask him that?
Right?
And then he asked "is it okay if we target you?"
But why?
I thought maybe they found something shady
And they found out
It might've been that
No no, I'm pretty pissed off
I'm really pissed off
Is that it?
Like they didn't say someone is gonna follow you
Ah no, not that
Yeah maybe even now
Yeah perhaps
Someone watching him continuously
You might be under surveilance, by the FBI
Ohh
There might be
No listen WHAT did you do?
Right?
No no listen-
The FBI!
Then make up a reason for me! I just heard about this too!
What did I do?!
Wha-
It doesn't matter what I did
Right
He asked me "Can we target you?"
That's where it all started, I see people hiding
It's the same guy?
Like hiding behind poles
Those are FBI agents?
I don't know if they are!
In fact,
I didn't know they were FBI until now
I thought they were random old men
Now that Hamada mentioned I think "Oh, they were FBI"
Now I made the connection - And that's why I'm so pissed off
I wish he would say what he did!
That's right, what did he do?
I don't know! Listen to me!
Why did they ask to target you?
Maybe it was cause I didn't pay the 300 yen
Cause you didn't pay 300 yen?
I don't know
Guys like that are totally random
He did it randomly?
He wouldn't do it randomly
He said "I'm a really random guy"
Lie TIME over
That was brilliant
Is this for real?!
It was a massive lie right away
Why the hell did  you pick me
A big lie right away
A big lie
It's gonna be like this I guess
That was a lot
It was a big lie after all, right away
Indeed
Yes
So Matsumoto-san, choose the next one
Right, of course
Yes
Endo?
I wonder...
Endo picks a big lie
Another big lie...
Hosei-san, is that story true?
Demi Moore
You and Demi Moore had dinner at "Gyoza no Ohsho"?
No way? When when?
At Ohsho?
Is that-
Is that at the Osaka Ohsho or the Kyoto Ohsho?
I don't know, I don't know
You should know that!
Yeah
Have you two done this before a lot?
Oh you've gone to both?
Oh yeah, yeah
Oh you've been to a lot?
Ah, so this wasn't for TV?
It wasn't for TV?
It wasn't for TV
You did this privately?
It was in private
Right, cause then we would also know, not just Endo
Yeah cause it was private, so you don't know
I was told "Don't tell anyone about this"
Demi Moore's father told me not to
But why do you know her?
How do you know her?
That's-
You really knew her before?
I want a, a detailed explanation
Right
I guess I should explain it clearly
Since I'm saying this anyways
Yes please tell us
Right
My  relative's grandfather is an American
Your,
I didn't know that before
Your relative?
Yeah he's an American
That's-
What's his name?
Umm
Demi Rouge, that's his name
Demi Rouge?
Demi-
So his name is also Demi?
Demi Rouge?
I didn't think the name Demi would come up this quick
So that's how, you know Demi Moore?
Right?
She's his relative
Right, right she's my relative
So that's how?
Right
Which Ohsho was it? There's a lot of branches
Well,
It was in Shinbashi
I know that store in Shinbashi
A lot Shinbashi today
Yeah there is one
Well won't people find out now?
Yeah that's not good
Yeah
It's the place near the small theatre
Won't people find out now?
Nobody found us out though
Nobody knew it was Demi Mo-ore
Cause she was wearing a baseball cap
A Hanshin baseball cap
It was the two of you?
Yeah
What did you get?
Well we went together, we got Kata Yakisoba
So actually, you didn't get Gyoza?
Yeah, cause like Gyoza,
She said it makes her breath smell
She really didn't like it, Mooah didn't like it
You call her "Mooah?"
Mooah
So then why did you go to Ohsho?
Right, why?
Why did you hide it?
Even from us?
Yeah
I don't get that
Well,
Cause it's an impressive story
Yeah it's nothing indecent
Well honestly,
If I told everyone I was related to Demi Moore,
People like Hamada-san will come around asking for an autograph
Surely Hamada-san wouldn't do that?
Yeah
It's to avoid something like that
It's a burden
Surely it's not a burden
So it's a true story then?
Oh yeah of course of course
Yeah
Are you for real?
Why didn't you go to a nicer Chinese restaurant than that?
Yeah
It seems unlikely
A Japanese restaurant maybe
Husband, you know her husband?
Her husband?
It was Bruce Willis before
Well she might be divorced now
It was Bruce Willis, before
That's right, they were married
Yeah
Bruce Willis wa-her-hu-band
Lie TIME Over
He has no punchline
No punchline at all
A judgement call had to be made
Yeah
Cause the Bruce Willis thing is a really old story
Man it's all massive lies!
Yeah
It's scary
They're all massive lies
I'm really nervous right now
Endo picks someone to tell a small lie
I have to say it?
Hamada-san,
What?
I've heard recently,
You've been going to Saitama to drink a lot these days
How do you know?
Well,
Yeah
I've just heard "Hamada-san likes to drink in Saitama a lot"
Ah, yeah, well yeah I have been doing that
Do you know where?
I know the location, it's in Omiya
I see
Omiya Omiya, yeah
It's in Omiya?
Yeah
Omiya is pretty urban
It is
Well yeah I guess there's no point in hiding it,
It's with Suga-chan
Chief Producer Suga Kenji
With Suga-san?
You've been drinking with Suga-san?
Yes yes
He lives in Saitama?
Suga-san invites me a lot
Suga
Ah, you go cause he invites you?
"Let's get something to eat, let's drink"
But you have to go there?
Yeah!
We could go somewhere in the city, but he says "Come please!"
Like a snack bar?
Like an Izakaya or such
What's it called?
What's it-
Gonbei
Gonbei?
Never heard of it before
So lame!
So cheap
A chain store?
Sounds cheap
Maybe it's a chain, maybe not I think
What do you guys talk about?
Do you guys go into detail?
"What if I appear at the end of No Laughing?"
He asked that
Ah, stuff like that?
That's not a good conversation for an Izakaya
That's true
We're tired of that
Anyways, that's what he said
Listen to this old man
You drive there?
I take the train sometimes too
Eh?
Ehhh?
Really?
This is surprising!
Well maybe it's to avoid drunk driving
Ah
Yeah perhaps
Yeah yeah exactly
So I go on the train
Why not a Taxi?
Which line?
Hmm?
Which line goes to Omiya?
Yeah which train?
Where do you get on?
I-
The line?
I don't really know but, I'm just sort of on the train
Amazing, he does it all by sense
Amazing indeed
Lie TIME Over
He doesn't even know the line
Well there's a lot of interchanges
Maybe the Saikyo Line?
Alright
Matsumoto picks someone to tell a small lie
Tanaka?
Is it true that out of all the comedians, you're dick is the biggest?
For real?
Out of all the comedians?...
First time hearing this
Did Kato-san from Gokuraku Tombo tell you that?
Oh, yeah, it was!
Well, comparing to other comedians,
I don't really like showing that part of me
Oh yeah, you're not
However,
I've shown my dick to just Kato-san before
And he was really surprised, like "Wow that's big"
And I had no idea personally
But Kato-san,
He's seen almost every comedian's penis
So he can tell
How big is it?
Right now? Well in all honestly it's not that big flaccid,
But it's impressive when hard,
My boner is very impressive
It's embarassing-
So Kato-san saw your boner?
Yeah exactly
What are you saying about Kato-san?
Why were you hard?
So Kato-san, he's seen every comedian's ...
every comedian's erection?
That's the conclusion
Kato-san is the weird one
Yeah that was just, morning wood I guess
In the morning he just pulled the blanket while I had morning wood, as a joke,
So as a joke, he went like that,
And then after seeing my erection,
He was taken aback
"Is it really that big?" is what I said
I wonder how it ranks amongst the other comedians
I think it's within the Top 10
Did he tell you if you're smaller than anyone?
Ah,
He did he did,
XXX-san
Well it's a rumor but,
I've heard his is pretty impressive
Was it erect?
It was an erection I believe
He saw his erection?
I didn't really have that image of you
Coincidentally we have the same birthday
Really?
April 26th
Oh really?
So maybe that birthdate and our dicks are related
I don't know any others,
But like, this kind of story is shocking right?
Yeah I get it
It's difficult to bring up
What about your wife?
Has she said anything?
Well, yeah my wife has seen my erection of course,
What did she say?
My wife, well,
My wife said "Your cock is impressive!"
I've been told
Lie TIME Over
What the hell
What the hell man
What kind of story did that turn into?
It's embarasing!
I don't really tell this story
It's actually, difficult to brag about that
Hamada will pick someone to tell a small  lie
Hamada-san...
Again huh?
I want to take this chance to confirm this story,
It's kind of weird,
Endo?
I've heard before eating dinner, you always eat a booger first
Sorry
This is...
Really?
You shouldn't do that!
I know that
It's something children do
That's true
Even kids don't do that!
Actually, have you guys never done that?
Well maybe messing around as a kid I have
Yeah yeah
But as an adult...
Never
Yeah never
I don't understand why you'd eat that with dinner
Well, of course it has that salt taste
It's salty?
It's salty
It's tasty?
Honestly, it is tasty
What?
Oh wow
There's no way that is tasty!
Well, like-
You're disgusting man
Why?
What's tasty about boogers?
Well one time, Hamada-san invited me out to dinner
Yes, yes
I thought I would get caught, did you notice then?
I didn't, I didn't
You didn't right?
How do you hide it?
Well for example,
Right
So I do this for snacks, as well as meals,
Like this, when I'm doing this,
Should I do it like I always do?
Yeah like always
Yeah show us
Ah, you wouldn't notice that, yeah
Yeah
Oh like that huh?
You have to pay really close attention
You wouldn't notice that
Indeed, you wouldn't
So you do this multiple times throughout the day?
I do it for sure before eating
So in fact, you save your boogers for before meals?
Yeah I do that
Even when I'm not that hungry,
I have dinner BECAUSE I want to eat my boogers
Ah, it's backwards then,
The boogers are more important
What?
Just eat your boogers then
But, that's the one thing I won't do
That I won't do
You don't like that?
You don't like boogers on their own?
I don't like the that
Cause that's gross?
Do you ever feel grossed out?
Never- Well maybe once
When I had a fever, and I had to eat something
And my wife, or girlfriend at the time would make me food,
And while I was laying down in bed,
She would feed me, since I couldn't do it
And when she would feed me,
When she would feed you,
The person feeding me doesn't know I eat boogers,
So then, I like,
There were a few times I fed myself, and I did this,
And when I did this,
I cut the inside, with my nail
And then I was grossed out a bit, I thought it would taste like blood,
I did think "Damn, I should really stop this"
But other than that incident, I do it nearly daily
Even today,
Today this morning,
Lie TIME Over
You should stop doing that
The flashback was too long
Yeah the flashback...
The flasback was a bit too long
Alright then,
Hamada will pick someone to tell a plausible  lie
A plausible lie huh?
I've heard the guy in XXXXXX is you...
Eh?!
After this,
Matsumoto is secretly that person?!
Wow, that's...
Hamada will pick someone to tell a plausible  lie
I think you guys,
I think you guys will be really surprised at this story, like "Wow really?!"
I just wanna confirm,
You...
I've heard the guy in the Funassyi costume is you...
TN: Funassyi is a mascot for Funabashi, Chiba. The mascot is known for it's energetic movements
Wow, that's...
No no way
I can't really believe that...
Well this is...
Well it was,
I'm not always the guy in the costume,
Ah I see
Yeah, uhhhh
There was just one time I was asked to do it
And I said "Alright"
It was someone who helped me out in the past
Who?
The actual guy in the costume
The real guy inside?
Yeah yeah yeah
Why did he ask to switch?
He was feeling really sick
Well, I guess Funassyi is pretty busy
Yeah
Well it would make sense they'd get tired...
Yeah once in a while
But asking you...
You'd get found out
Isn't it really tiring to imitate those movements?
Yeah, he said "Matsumoto, sorry about this"
I just need your time. It's unrelated, but for Fuji TV,
At Odaiba they had some event
They had me running around on a Tatami mat the whole time
Sounds tough
There's a lot of jumping too
Mmmhmm, yeah yeah
How would you do it? Show us
I wanna see that
That's not it
Funassyi!
Ah!
You would say that?
Doesn't she jump a bit more than that?
There's also the greeting
What are you doing?
She jumps too right?
Like this, and then
The "Nashi!" line is something I adlibbed
And they said "That's a great idea!"
Ah, you came up with that?
Yeah
It wasn't there before?
I wanted to say like "This sucks!", so I said "NASHI!"
"Yeah Matsumoto we can use that"
Eh? Did it sound like the normal voice for Funassyi?
Yeah yeah
How many times have you taken over for them?
Yeah
Ummm,
I did it 2 or 3 times,
And you probably don't know this,
There's other celebrities inside the costume
There's like a secret league for the people that have done it
Incidentally,
There's a bear character too right?
Is the guy in the bear costume someone we know?
Yeah, yeah it's Shibata Kyohei
TN: Famous actor
There's a lot of unexpected people doing that
Shibata Kyohei?...
Why not just bring out Shibata-san then?
Yeah that would be better
Yeah forget the costume then
Sounds tough!
It does
I said that too
"Shibata-san, do you really need the costume?"
He said "You flatter me!"
And then we laughed
And then you laughed?
Well, if you say so
Oh wow really?
It was amazing when I found out
Eh so it's like that for other mascots?
Yeah
One of them is TKO Kinoshita
Well anyways, I thought it would be fun
How did it go again? Show us once more
Yeah once more
Funassyi~! - Like that
Do you need to make that face too?
Well after all, it is fun to do so
To get into it like that
I might as well right?
Next week
Improv Liar Inn - Finale
"I've been smacked by a Gorilla"
And then the gorilla crouched down and-
A sad farewell to the ones who raised him
And last time I saw them, they totally ignored me
The truth behind the "Best Father"
All we ever talk about is XXXXX
No way!
That's not on!
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband