First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende...
..."Who is the most convincing?" Self-health presentation!
I'm sure you know this already, but...
...out of the five of us, I'm the smartest.
Today we'll see how much of it I can show it off to you.
How am I supposed to feel?
We all drifted off, somewhere far.
That means that none of us are convinced...
...of him being that smart.
Well, whatever.
We'll now be given the subjects to study.
We have a library at our disposal.
We'll compile materials and give a presentation.
First the health-related subjects are decided with a lottery.
High Blood Pressure
This is going to be complex!
I don't have the faintest idea about high blood pressure!
T/N: Background music is "Winter Winner" by Orange Range
Furthermore, Hamada got aging prevention...
...Yamasaki got hip pain...
...Endo got summer fatigue...
...and Tanaka got bad breath.
What kind of presentations will they give?
To study about their subjects...
...they went to a library to gather materials.
We can't be too loud here.
It reminds me of the Silent Library series.
That brings back bad memories.
Anyway, let's go.
The search for materials to study begins right away.
I can't go without checking this one.
I'm at a dead end already.
I am completely lost.
I don't know how to approach it.
Don't know at all.
Will Endo be able to find the materials he needs?
Meanwhile, his partner Tanaka...
Bad breath bye-bye! Bad breath bye-bye!
Bad breath bye-bye.
Found them!
There's a lot of them!
Alright!
Hamada has also finally found something.
I've had enough.
Can I take these with me?
Why??
After gathering the materials...
...they proceed to making the presentations.
The Gaki members are unusually serious about their presentations.
"...this survey was done on 288 people by Kanebo..."
T/N: Kanebo is a major cosmetic brand in Japan.
"...raise your feet to a 90 degree angle and do this..."
I've never drawn a picture like this.
Never ever.
What am I going to do?
Will Hamada's picture be completed?
Will he be able to give the presentation?
Everyone, are you feeling a bit tired?
We had about two hours.
Frankly, I ran out of time.
I'm usually better than this.
I study more before doing things.
Well let's just do the presentations already.
Tanaka is the top batter.  He has the subject of "bad breath".
This spring, two subordinates come to you.
But you can only hire one.
They both have equal looks, ability...
...judgment, and character.
However, one of them has bad breath.
The other does not have bad breath.
In that case, which one do you choose?
Yes, Hamada-san?
If at all possible, the one without bad breath.
Exactly!
Bad breath can cause problems...
...in school...at work...
...or at home.
What is this bumbling, are you ok?
I'd now like to talk to you about bad breath.
Your introduction was so long!
Two meters.
What do you think this distance is?
How far bad breath reaches.
Precisely.
Did you really have to cover that?
I'd like to do an experiment now.
A bad breath check you can easily do at home too!
I'll give each of you a cup.
You prepared all this?
Breathe into the cup, and put your hand over the top.
Then, take a deep breath.
Now, sniff the cup.
How about it?
Can you detect your own bad breath?
It kind of stunk when I took the deep breath.
I'd like you to look at this flipcard.
Kanebo did this study in 1994 to men and women aged 18 to 25.
That survey is damn old.
More than 10 years ago!
Teacher! I don't care!
Let's just look at it, ok?
Who cares, it's 12 years old!
Ideas might have changed already.
Smells people like!  Third is...
...freshly baked bread.
I don't think that's right.
I don't think too many people say that.
Number two.
Flowers.
And number one is soap's natural scent.
Because Kanebo did the survey.
It's the Pink Lady era!
T/N: Pink Lady was a female pop music duo popular in the late 70s and early 80s.
And now...bad smells.
It's not that old.
Third most hated is...
...body odor.
That goes without saying.
Number two is...
...kitchen waste.
And of course number one...
...is bad breath.
I could see that coming.
Bad breath ranks higher than kitchen waste.
Have a look at this other flipcard too.
The drug company Nihon Kayaku, in 1990...
That's even older!
You lose interest right away!
Of course, number one is... bad breath.
That's the subject, after all.
And bad breath is number one for women, too.
Wow, about eight out of ten.
That's right.  Eight out of ten people, both men and women, hate it.
But it's from 15 years ago.
That's true.
The question is, "who is a partner I would not want to marry?"
What's the point in covering them?!
"Somebody whose mouth stinks."
This is the theme, we know it.
How many visits to the doctor...
...does it take to get rid of bad breath?
Can it be healed?
Yes. Depending on the treatment, you can cure it!
Is that so?
How many times do you think, Endo?
Five times?
Endo!
I got it right.
That's pretty embarrassing.
He looked really annoyed just then!
That's the end of my presentation on bad breath.
That was great!
Next up is Yamasaki who is full of confidence.
His subject is "hip pain."
My subject is "hip pain."
When you think of hip pain, what image do you conjure?
I don't understand what the hell you're saying.
When you hear "hip pain," what does it make you think about?
Old age.
Old age, yeah.
Well, old age ... and stuff like that.
What the hell was the point of that?!
You should show us something!
I'm so envious of gags like that.
Three things.
We can divide hip pain into three things.
Let's look at this first.
First of all...
(Blank) on the hip exceeds its strength.
Matsumoto, what is placed on the hip?
Umm... Stress?
Yes.
We got another one right.
Yes, you did.
Number two...
...the (blank) itself is abnormal.
How about it, Tanaka?
Well...
...the hip?
No way.
Yes.
It fit in there so perfectly.
It was the only reasonable answer.
You should at least try to hide the length of the word.
Let's take a look...
...at who is at highest risk of having hip problems.
Everyday life ranking.
This was quite interesting to me as well.
What do you mean, "everyday life?"
Yeah, what does that mean?
When you live your life.
Is it about when you might get hip problems?
Yes, that's it.
Where excessive stress is placed on the hip.
Yes.
Number three.
Night shifts.
Oh, so it's like that.
That's when it's easy to get pain in the hip.
Especially men.
Let's have number two.  What do you think it is?
Washing the dishes, or something like that?
Washing the dishes...
...is actually number one.
Household chores.
Housewives are right up there at number one.
Well now I don't care about number two any more.
We don't care.
Here it is.
"Playing."
(* - This is Yamasaki's own ranking and has no basis in reality.)
What the hell do you mean, "playing"?
Yama-chan's "You Gotta Remember This!"
You have to memorize...
...what's best in foodstuffs.
What do you mean?
Vitamin B and calcium are good for hips.
What do you think is best, among foods?
Eggs?
Eggs are close.
What about cheese?
Endo is correct!
That ripped off really cleanly.
Why did you hide the entire card?!
Today, on this special occasion, I've brought cheese.
We've all seen cheese before.
I don't need to look at it.
Please, take it.
I don't want to.
We know what cheese is.
We don't want it.
That's the end of my hip pain presentation.
Thank you.
Next up is Endo, who had trouble in the library.
His subject is "summer fatigue."
Out of the five of us, he's the problem child.
Hello.  I'd like to tell you about summer fatigue.
When you hear "summer fab-... summer fatigue"...
...summer fatigue...
Let's look at the issue on a planetary scale.
That's a big scale.
What's El Niño?
You have some sort of an idea, right?
Well, I've heard of it.
El Niño is a phenomenon in South America...
...where on Ecuador and Peru's coast...
...every 4-5 years, sea temperatures rise.
You have the explanation here.
So you just copied that text.
I'd like you to understand this first.
He just keeps turning the pages.
I can't memorize anything!
Just look at this first.
Do you know what this is?
Summer fatigue?
The El Niño phenomenon.
What's the point in covering that?!
It changes the atmospheric currents...
...and causes what around the world?
What comes before low temperatures?
Tanaka-san?  Before low temperatures?
Well, not before.
This is a hint.
High temperatures?
It causes high and low temperatures, rains and drought...
...which causes...?
Calamities?
Abnormal weather conditions.
El Niño causes abnormal weather conditions right now.
Abnormal weather conditions mean that...
...winters are getting colder all the time.
Summers are getting hotter and hotter.
When it gets hot, what fatigue is it?
That took forever!
Summer fatigue!
You get summer fatigue.
Let's talk about summer fatigue now.
Finally.
Here's a health check-up list.
I'll go from number one to number ten for everyone now.
I'll read these, and if one fits you...
...please remember it.
Your eyes tire easily.
Your shoulders and back are stiff. Yours, right, Hamada?
You tire easily.
You have nausea.
Your face twitches.
You lack appetite.
Your hands tremble.
Your feet and hands feel cold.
You can't think straight.
It's "palpitations".
Palpitations.
You experience palpitations.
It's obvious he just copied the text.
He didn't read it at all!
I had about two fit me.
Two for me, too.
Two.
I have three.
Zero to one means...
...good health.
We're all in the second group.
Let's look at four to six then.
Needs attention.
Seven or more is very worrisome.
Worrying about summer fatigue, right?
Two to three is the average person.
Well it's over now.
What the hell, man?!
We don't need to know more.
When you get summer fatigue...
...you lose your appetite and stop eating.
The molecules that store energy...
...do you know what they are?
Gly...
Glycogen!
It forms glycogen and stores it.
It has a deciphering effect.
It's "detoxification"!
Endo!
We're not talking about encryption!
I'm so envious of mistakes like that!
At last, Matsumoto's presentation.
His theme is "high blood pressure".
I'm not going to be joking even half the time from now on.
First, a simple problem.
What is the connection between these?
I've got it.
Well, "high", of course.
I could tell you about any one of these...
...but today let's look at high blood pressure.
Sooo... Tokyo University's circulatory organ clinic's...
...diagnosis chief Yasunobu Hirata...
...has done research about it.
What do you think these are?
This is the number of people affected...
...by high blood pressure in Japan.
35 million people.
Only approximately, though.
There's no point in covering that!
Well, that's how it goes.
What's that about the FBI?
FBI, what the hell?
Who decides the basis for the diagnosis of high blood pressure?
Number one is FBI.
Number two, PTA.
Number three is the WHO.
Which one is it?
Correct.
We know it can't be the PTA or FBI.
I know, right?
Isn't this the end, then?
We don't need this any more.
If you put the same amount of water through...
...a stiff, narrow hose - compared to...
...an elastic, thick hose, the narrow hose...
...spews water with a higher force.
This is the principle.
The more narrow it is, the higher the pressure gets.
This is what it looks like.
I've explained it in simple terms with a rubber hose.
It can also be shown with jeans.  Same thing.
So you really have to be careful.
This is what it's about.
That's a lot of text.
Internal secretions regulate the blood pressure...
...through autonomic nerves.
This is how they're related to each other.
If you just look at this, you'll pretty much understand everything.
Various things result in high blood pressure.
Get this through your thick heads.
Could you explain it a bit further?
If we think about it in terms of Yoshimoto comedians...
T/N: Yoshimoto is the agency that Downtown, Hosei, and Cocorico work for.
I'll name it the difference between rich and poor people.
Well, they resemble each other.
Think about that.
You can't show it too long.
It disappeared so quickly.
That's about it.
I don't have anything else to tell you.
What is... this solemn feeling?
Hamada finishes up with aging prevention.
Good evening.
My subject is "aging prevention".
We're all steadily aging.
I'm sure we all relate here.
We are all getting older.
First up - what is aging?
He's aged so much he can't insert the flipcard properly.
This is aging. Read it out loud.
Along with aging, internal organs' functions gradually deteriorate.
Eventually you become unable to cope with your surroundings.
It's a process that leads to death, and it advances all the time...
...being irreversible.
That's difficult.
Isn't it?
So, everyone...
When does aging really start?
Let's guess.
One by one.  Tell me.
When does aging start?
Teacher, excuse me?
What?
It's hard for me to think like this.
When you're 40!
40, ok.
It's aging, so I'll say 50.
50? OK.
I think 20.
I also think it's pretty early...
...so I'll take the middle ground and say 30.
One of you got it right.  It starts at the age of 20.
Yes, from the age of 20, aging has begun.
What is the phenomenon of aging?  Let's take a look.
Aging is...
That's creepy!
It's like that guy from Dengeki Network.
T/N: Dengeki Network was a group of four men who were known for performing dangerous stunts.  They were popular in the 1990s.
Dengeki Network
Nanbu Torata
Mr. Nanbu!
Dementia, cataracts, diabetes...
...bones and muscles deteriorate, balding and gray hair...
...wrinkles, high blood pressure like we had earlier...
...and the decline of reproductive functions.
This is what aging is all about.
His pace is quite fast.
Indeed.
After middle age, what are the abilities that get better...
...and the ones that get worse?
There are abilities that actually improve?
Yes, there are.
Memory improves with age, right?
These are the abilities that improve.
Imagination, analysis, judgement and thinking.
I see.
They're all intellect-based.
When you get older, these actually go up.
Things like learning ability.
There are the abilities that deteriorate.
Memorization, long-term memory and concentration.
They deteriorate.
However, even if you become unable to...
...do tricky calculations in your head...
...you can still live a good life...
...as long as you have good judgment.
It doesn't matter if some abilities deteriorate.
That's what the proverb "the older, the wiser" means.
Why did you write that in brown?
For the sake of the atmosphere.
Out of all the colors you chose that.
Bones and muscles deteriorate.  Let's concentrate on this.
How old are you in terms of elasticity?
If you're in your 20s, you should be able to do this.
Creepy!
Both your hands can touch the floor...
...and your face can reach your knees.
The arms and legs are way out of proportion!
In your 40s the tips of your fingers reach the floor.
Lastly, in your 50s...
...your fingers are further than 20 cm from the ground.
I'm probably in the 50s.
The man in the illustration is moving further from the foreground.
If you think about your elasticity, how old would you be?
I don't have any confidence!
Me too, I can't do it.
So everyone is in this group?
Your fingers can't reach the floor?
Oh, mine somehow reaches the floor.
Are you serious?
I can't do it.
We're all in our 50s!
It's no good.
So, aging is...
We don't need that!
It's scary!
Let's go back to this.
We talked about this, right?
This is like the main menu of a video game.