The 1st Gaki no Tsukai Arahende chikichiki
Dance until you spread on social media~!!
Well...
is everyone aware of the temperature outside?
It's a nice day today.
- Yes, it's easily over 95°F. The heat is really intense!
Regarding today's plan...
let's go around drinking delicious iced-coffee around town.
That's drastically different from what was said.
"Dance until you spread on social media."
- Oh is that so?
I didn't get a chance to communicate with the staff.
Get that part right.
Things spread on social media so fast. So-and-so did this. So-and-so did that.
And we won't be playing against each other, but...
right now, one-by-one, we'll dance somewhere in public.
And you can't stop until you get on social media.
Rule 1: With no visible film crew, dance by yourself in the park.
Rule 2: Until someone tweets about it, you can't stop.
But today is a heat wave above 104°F!
Ueno Park as the stage, the curtains open up to a harsh environment.
These are the dances.
There's lots.
Tako Dance...they have to mention the dance too.
"Endo is doing the Para Para."
So it has to have those two words.
It's about 2:30, right now.
The temperature is going up and up.
Let's finish this quck.
What should we do about the order?
One-by-one, right?
Let the young guys go first.
We're not that young though.
We're 47.
This is Japan now.
With that, the young, Tanaka attempts.
His dance is?
When you think Tanaka, you think "Loach Scoop".
So Loach Scoop? I understand.
Better not pretend to faint.
If you're gonna fall, fall forward. Backwards is fainting.
(Ueno Park in front of the water fountain)
- Where is he at?
Ahh! He's walking. Left. Left.
No one's following with cameras so...
it looks like Tanaka's private time.
Tanaka does a solid job.
Chopsticks.
Do that and carry that.
Let's go!!
The chopsticks...
might make it harder to recognize that it's Tanaka.
Maybe he shouldn't have used them.
This is bad. They think he's weird so nobody wants to get closer.
They're watching and laughing from afar.
I mean, if that was there, would you go?
Some sightseers...
are doing something.
Just passing through.
A lot of tourists!
- This is bad!
Your movements are too slow.
You don't look like your scooping loaches.
Cleaner.
Do it for real!
Yea, yea, yea...
You'll pass out in 10 minutes.
You're not showing up at all.
Not showing up at all?
Please, hurry up.
How many loaches did you catch?
Right now, I caught 3.
Caught 3, did ya?
That's a lot!
It's been 10 minutes.
- It has been 10 minutes.
This is a disaster.
Nothing's showing up.
Is that so?
What do you wanna do?
- It's cus no one's watching.
There isn't even a tweet regarding Tanaka, is there?
Oh he's doing something.
Is he waving?
They just came to look.
But maybe he...
inputted to them that Tanaka is loach scooping so.
But they just nodded and left.
I wonder what they're thinking.
This is tough.
Wanna bring him back?
- Bring him back.
Tanaka, wanna come back one time?
This is impossible.
I'll come back.
[Challenge Time 15:16]
How is it?
No, nothing.
Nothing.
- Not even "Cocorico Tanaka".
He's back.
Nice job.
How was it?
Um...
It doesn't matter how long.
You're sweating.
We were all saying...
another hour and it'll be good.
No way!
No way. I'll pass out before then.
Let's try someone else.
Please, please. Someone else go.
Shall we go Emperor!
Who? Who's goin?
- Emperor!
Ahh! Dahama-san, right?
If it doesn't work here for Dahama-san, then it's impossible.
That's right! If it's impossible for Downtown then it's impossible.
Next challenger is Hamada
His selected dance is?
I can do the Twist.
Ehhh?
This feels super exhausting.
The familiar the dance, the better.
They'll know what the Twist is.
Please, Hamada-san!
Already...
while on standby, a guy recognized him...
and took out his cellphone.
That guy, right?
He's taking pictures!
It started!
He does the Twist fast.
Was the Twist that fast?
Even the Twist experts don't go that fast.
They're coming!
Wow, you're right! Incredible!
Agh! Did he pull his back?
What's wrong?
- He probably pulled his back.
Tired.
You're getting a lot of attention, Hamada! Nice, nice, nice...
You're doing good. Keep twisting.
Lookin good!
Hard breathing.
Is he dying?
Nothing's coming up.
- It's too hot!
Staff, go check on him.
IT'S HOT!
It is hot. Let's hang in there!
[Hama-chan, started something shitty yesterday so I wanna kill him.]
Maybe it's a different Hama-chan.
Maybe Hamada got into road rage with somebody and now he wants to kill him.
It's a different Hamada-san.
- You think?
And just then!
We got something!
[Found Hama-chan at Ueno Park.]
Yes, yes, yes...
- We just need the "Twist"!
Do the Twist!
He's not moving so good.
It's not a big deal.
Shall we bring him back?
- Yeah. He almost had it.
Come back, one time.
[Challenge Time 10:43]
But...
But there was a tweet.
Whoa! So much sweat!
Not bad.
So much sweat!
Did you cover yourself in water?
Why would I?
It's dizzying.
We can't do this! We can't do this!
Is this what it's like!?
You look varnished!
Varnish.
He's so shiny.
You're a woodworker's finished product!
You had a close one.
- Oh really?
[Found Hama-chan at Ueno Park. On location??]
No "Twist" though!
What's this, "shitty"?
[Hama-chan, started something shitty yesterday so I wanna kill him.]
Did you start something yesterday?
- Why would I do something like that.
How do you know it's me?
Well, Hama-chan could be anybody.
Maybe they're talking about Nishida Toshiyuki.
The Twist was no good, huh?
Isn't it time for that?
Let's get one with Shozo. With that flashy...
The Samba, right?
All out Samba!
- Samba?
It's flashy.
Next, Endo attempts with the Samba!
Will he get tweeted!?
(Ueno Park in front of the Tokyo Metropolitan Art Museum 93.9°F)
He's a man who knows the Samba.
I think Endo will do it.
There he goes.
Nice, nice. It's the Samba.
Can he keep this up?
Is this the rhythm of the Samba?
It's working.
What happened?
What's wrong?
How bout her?
Is that her cellphone? Did she take a picture?
Endo, what's wrong?
It's hot!
It's not that hot!
It's super hot.
You're fine.
There's no sense of the Samba.
Really?
It feels like Samba here.
Smile more.
Like you're having fun time.
I'll show more fun.
Nice! Nice!
What's this rhythm?
I've never heard of this rhythm.
Endo reaches the limit of his all-out Samba.
And then!
[Cocorico's Endo is at Ueno Park with feathers and dancing the Samba.]
YES~!
Thank you very much!
Man, I'm tired.
I wonder who it was.
- I have no idea.
Probably a college girl.
Amazing, Endo.
Except...
...what is that?
That's not Samba, is it?
Wasn't that in a commercial?
It's the Ippon Manzoku.
Maybe that came out.
So who's next?
- Ain't that you?
Shall we?
Of course it is.
That's fine. I'll do it. But there aren't any more dances.
Do Wotagei.
- Wotagei?
I've never done that.
I've never done it.
No "dying" out there.
None of that.
He just falls back.
No "dying" and running away?
If you please!
Wotagei.
(Ueno Park National Science Museum 93.6°F)
Here he comes.
There's people in front.
He's already getting attention.
They gave him something.
Pen lights.
Oh fast.
- What's he doing?
What's he doin?
- That ain't Wotagei.
What's he doin!?
This ain't Wotagei.
He's not doing it at all.
People notice him, right?
Everyone's looking at the weirdo.
Makes sense.
They're scared.
Maybe the uncomfortable people will tweet something.
You're sluggish.
What is that? What are you doin?
Wotagei.
I don't know Wotagei.
Is it faster?
- Faster.
Faster?
- Yeah.
The speed's gone up.
- Nice, nice. It's cleaner.
No tweets?
But people are watching.
The people around you are watching.
This is tough. This is tough.
This is tough.
Maybe they're foreigners.
- Maybe.
That whole family's staring.
Right in front of the stage.
- Those are good seats.
You don't get to see Matsumoto like this.
- That's true.
Everyone's playing with their smartphones.
Are they filming him?
Is he playing the music?
Yea, try it with the music.
Here we go.
They're looking.
The family is taking pictures.
What kind of movement is this?
People are gathering.
Until now, this is the most people.
Now, if they'll just tweet it.
He's shutting down.
They're taking pictures.
Matchan, do your best~!
"Do your best", the kids are saying, Matsumoto-san.
It got faster.
Matchan, do your best~!
What's goin on here?
If this many people are watching and taking pictures, you should get a tweet soon.
Do your best, Matchan~!
Wanna come back, one time?
Comin back.
[Challenge Time 11:05]
This should get some.
They might come later.
Look, he's tapping away.
He is tapping away.
They're not posting cus you were still there.
And the kids were cheering you on.
I've never wasted so much energy in my life.
There's a high possibility. A lot of people were typing.
No way. I should get something.
Anything?
Something came.
[I got a picture of Matchan falling over.]
Except there's no "Wotagei".
- That's true.
What the hell is Wotagei?
I don't know it.
- That's not our fault! That's what it is.
There were so many people! There were so many smartphones...
Something?
[Matsumoto Hitoshi-san was doing Wotagei at Ueno.]
That's complete! That's complete!
Wow, wow, wow...
There's even a picture!
- That's perfect!
Complete! Complete!
That's perfect.
- You even have a picture!
You did better than Endo.
It feels good when you get it.
- It does feel good when you get it!
Next, Housei attempts.
He picks the Tako Dance.
Here?
We're changing spots.
If you can, go deep.
Like an alley or something.
Not an alley.
Someplace with a lot of people.
You can wander around the alleys.
Like an octopus.
Find a narrow alleyway and just...
Moving to a popular evening, sightseeing spot, to Odaiba we go.
Can Housei get tweeted doing the Tako Dance?
(Decks Tokyo Beach Center Deck 90.5°F)
- There he is!
Quietly enters the scene.
No movement as of now.
Counting on you.
They see him.
Nothing at all!
Like Bruce Willis in Sixth Sense.
No one can see him.
It's not like he's dead.
But people are watching.
People are gathering!
Show them the octopus.
You gotta do the kissy sounds.
Oh, from her bag...
She's taking something out.
She took out her cellphone!
Makeup touch-up.
- Sorry, it was a compact.
Nevermind.
Stopped?
Did the octopus stop?
Can I do the Samba? They'll come if I do the Samba.
Can he do the Samba?
Ah, nice.
He's bringing a different rhythm.
He's out of breath...
Anyway, people are watching.
With all of your energy show us one more strong Samba!
Nice!
Gimme more!
Here it comes!
He's outta breath.
We're checking right now.
I have a feeling, it's coming.
They're gonna think a bird died.
Animal Control is gonna come.
Something big died.
Housei reaching his limit, ends his challenge.
He's back.
We're checking right now.
People were watching.
How was it?
- Um...no movement yet.
[Yamazaki Housei-san was at Odaiba. He was moving very strangely.]
"Moving strangely" is no good.
But there was mention of me. Yamazaki Housei is awesome!
- No, no, no...
So strict.
Afterwards, Tanaka who has yet to clear, does the Para Para.
He's flag signaling.
Look! The kids.
The kids are copying him.
This scene is fascinating.
- This is interesting.
Look! Look! Look!
What's going on?
What's goin on?
It turned into a kid's show.
Then Hamada attempts with the Awa Dance.
If they tweet now, that would be the best.
You're becoming more like Oka Hachiro.
However...
[Downtown's Hamachan was at Odaiba.]
No tweet of the dance name.
With that, here are the results.
Matsumoto and Endo only clear.
It's unfortunate but, the only one not to get their name tweeted was Tanaka.
Tanaka, batsu game.
Inverted crucifixion.
Inverted crucifixion?
I've never even heard of that.
Kimu has always been dealing with the record boss, Oozaki.