Translation by typesoshee
Proofreading by Oolong
Typesetting by Hinnerk (Team Gaki)
Corrections by DuckToaster
dtr-subs.tumblr.com
August 20, 2000
Backstage of Gaki no Tsukai
Hello.
Can you tell I'm slightly smiling?
Yes, I can see your teeth.
Hahaha
... the white of your teeth.
Ok.
So, I don't need to tell you, then.  You know this, right?
Remember, we did this?
This whole thing?
He came to me.
He came crying to me.
Again?
The dream that Matsumoto envisioned was...!?
After the high jump from last month,
Matsumoto has now set his sights on
The Vault
The vault.
An extremely high-level skill where you flip
twice with your legs tucked in!!
And within vaulting,Part 2
said to be the most difficult skill,
is where you tuck your legs in while in the airPart 2
An extremely high-level skill where you flip
twice with your legs tucked in!!
Forward handspring with double front salto tucked
and flip twice:
The forward handspring with double front salto tucked.
If you do two flips well enough, you supposedly get a perfect 10.
I see.
Oh.
But there's no way he'll be satisfied with that.
3 flips is what he wants.
No way.
No.
There's no way.
You think so, too, right, Hamada?
What's the point for you to say "no way," "no way" before we've even tried?
We'll give it what we got, but
if Matsumoto himself
is all like this, like he was before
he won't be able to do any flips.
He literally puts nothing into his muscles.
Seriously.
I mean.
Don't worry.  He himself brought this all up so he'll do it.
Really?
Hmm.
Don't worry.  Let's just give him 3 flips, all right?
He was crying.
Why would he cry?
He cries so easily
for some reason.
Lately, he cries really easily.
Yeah.
When you get to a certain age, you cry.
He's not that old.
To dream, again.
Four kurokos* rise to the occasion.
*Kuroko is a traditional Japanese theatre stagehand.  Kurokos wear all black to imply to the theatre audience that they are supposed to be invisible and not part of the onstage action.
Unprecedented
Triple Salto
Matsumoto Hitoshi Goes
For a Perfect 10 on the Vault!!
Unprecedented
Matsumoto Hitoshi goes for a perfect 10 on the vault!
But my question is, why the vault after the high jump?
Yeah, why is that?
He's here.
Hello.
We're ready.
Uh huh.
So, why? Right?
Umm, what? Why the vault?
You might be wondering.
Umm.
I've been
in show business
for 18 years
as a horse face bit, this whole way.
To be a horse face and not be able to do the vault
Then it's hard for my juniors to call me a horse face.
It's hard to say that and I also don't know he's talking about.
Huh?Part 2
Huh?  You get what he's saying.
I don't get it, I'm sorry.
Is he a horse face?
He's a horse face.
So,
this is why I want to try 3 flips.
Because it's unprecedented.
Yup.
Because no one has done it before.
Did you just say, "Because no one has done it before?"
Right, because no one has done it before.
Well, in any case.
Yeah.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, definitely, we're ready.
Good luck.
With dignity.
Ok, we're ready?
Ok.
No problem.
Let's do it.
Do it properly.
Put some spirit into it.
Let's get this right in one try.
Wait, wait.
Huh?
Then I'll go here.
I'll be behind.
Hey, you get there, quickly.
Let's, go.
Ok.
Get his feet, his feet, on the ground.
Endo!
Got it.
Ok.
Ok, ok.
Come on.
No, no, no.
Forward, forward.
To the front, the front.
Come on.
Higher, higher.
Don't hit his neck.
Not hitting his neck.
Ok, good.
Good.
Just like that.
Tuck his legs in.
Ready and
Go.
That was good.
Wait.
I got smacked.
Yes, you did.
Are you ok?
Why is he angry?
I don't get it.
He flipped, didn't he?
Yes, he flipped.
He was turning.
Was it because it was just 1?
Oh yeah, it was 1.
Yes, he was saying 3.
Geez.
Are you ok?
He hit you.
The four go back to talk to Matsumoto
Matsumoto had returned backstage and was playing fukuwarai*
*Fukuwarai is a Japanese game in which a person is blindfolded and then places pieces of facial features on to a board with a blank face, creating a humorous-looking face in the end.
Matsumoto.
What?
Well, yeah
you did say 3 flips, and that was
1 flip.
If you can't do it, just say you can't do it.
What was with you all, acting as if you could do it and looking all confident?
What was "vault" about that, huh?
What was "vault" about that? Think about that.
Every one of you.
Every one of you, think 80% of that.
All right?
If you can't do it, then you can't do it!
I want to jump!
You know?
You have to do it right.
Tell these guys.
Let's do it right.
Matsumoto's Second Attempt!
Matsumoto's second attempt.
No, no, no.
It's the other way.
We have to turn him around.
Get his feet to hit the ground.
Hit the ground.
Ok, got it.
Got it.
Ok.
Up, up, up.
Yamazaki, that's you.
Here we go.
Ok.
Looks good.
Got it, got it.
Ok, raise it.
Higher, Endo.
Yeah.
A little more.
He's looking.  He's looking this way.
Hurry up, he's looking.
He's really staring.
It didn't work.
The next...
Let's go to the next one.
Oh, oh, there.
It's that.
Don't worry, the next one will be fine.
From here, please.
We were kind of thinking that one might not work, right?
His legs!
Got his legs.
Ready and
Ok.
Should we make it touch the ground?
Hold him up.
Ready and
There.
Ok.
Ready and
Get that side.
It's good.
Yes, it's good.
Flip him.
3 flips, ok?
1...
2...
Go.
Ready and
There.
He's going back.
His face was completely red.
The four go back to talk to Matsumoto again
Matsumoto was peeling a daikon radish
We were talking and
thinking we mixed up the vertical and the horizontal
of the flips.
This is not the sort of thing that 3 juniors
and a duo partner does to someone.
I got hurt.
It hurt like hell!
It hurts if you're thrown in that kind of position.
But seriously,
we mixed up the vertical and the horizontal
so we got it now, right?
Yes.
You "mixed up the vertical and the horizontal?"  What kind of mix up is that?
Who the hell mixes up
the vertical and the horizontal?
It's pitiful.
Excuse us.
Matsumoto's 3rd Attempt!
Matsumoto's 3rd attempt.
Hurry up.
Lay him down.
Ok, send it in.
This way.
Fast forwarding
Raise it.
Yes, please.
Turn it this way.
Above, here.
Good.
Yes, yes.
Good, good.
Ok.
Back, a bit.
Back just a bit.
Raise it.
A bit more.
Back a bit more.
Back.
Ok, stop, stop.
Stop.
All right.
Ok.
Ok, here we go.
Good.
Ready to go.
Looks good.
Lower it a little bit.
Ok, good, lower it.
Ok, get it out of the way.
Back, back.
Whoa, whoa.
Good.
3 flips.
Here we go.
Turn him.  Go, go.
No, no, I can't.
Almost got it, almost got it.
Tanaka, come on.
Gee, he was heavy.
He's really staring at me.  I don't know why.
Hamada, don't...
After he was laid down and put on
the forklift
He was staring at me the whole time.
The four go back to talk to Matsumoto again
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait.
Please, wait.
We're right now
It's dirty.
It stinks.
What is that?
Matsumoto was changing his underwear,
which had poop on it
No, seriously, wait.
If you could just put a bit more effort into it
then we could
I am putting in effort.
You're not putting any effort into it.  You just let your body go totally loose.
I agree completely with what Yamazaki said.
Yeah.
Hold on
Don't trash my reputation saying things like that.
Think about me.
I'm thinking, "What the hell are they going to do to me this time?"
Just equipment after equipment.
The time in the air is way too long.
Matsumoto's 4th Attempt!
Matsumoto's 4th attempt.
I don't want to end this in a gloomy way.
That's true.
Let's go.
Ok, ok.
Get him up.
You're not putting anything into it.
Wait, Endo.
Hurry, hurry.
Good, good.
Firmly.
Hurry, hurry.
Help.
Ok.
Looks good.
Lift him up.
Ready and
Get him to hit the ground here.
Hit the ground.
Get it to the ground.
Get his feet.
There.
Get his feet on the ground.
Got it.
Ok.
Ok, the feet hit the ground.
Flip him.
Turn him now.
1st Somersault
Once, ok, ok.
Ok.
Watch out!
Twice.
2nd Somersault
Ok, twice.
Ok, here we go.
Here he comes.
There, yeah.
Whoa.
Ok, three times.
3rd Somersault
There.
Ok.
It's a ten!
We got it!
Forward Handspring with Double Front Salto Tucked
Matsumoto Hitoshi's
is a Success!?
Yes!
Hooray!
Translation by typesoshee
Proofreading by Oolong
Typesetting by Hinnerk (Team Gaki)
Corrections by DuckToaster
dtr-subs.tumblr.com
Hooray!