Gaki no tsukai presents...
I am the one who understands everyone the best!
At any rate, you like this item, right?! Championship'
Wonder what it is exactly?
How long have we known each other?
10 years can't do it
20 years?
24 years already!
Oh 24 years since Gaki aired for the first time.
Yes and some of us even knew each other before that. By now we should know what each other likes and dislikes.
Also hobbies and things we carry and so on.
At any rate, you like this item?! Is what we are going to shop for.
"Wow you know him well" is the reaction we want.
Here are the things we are going to find.
A jacket that Matsumoto will like
I wear a jacket every day, so you must know.
Like, you must have seen it!
A cardigan that Tanaka likes.
That the easiest one!
The easiest? Really?
If I have time i will knit it for him
They each head out to find goods that the other members will like, but will they succeed?
Wow, this place...
So amazing, totally Endo.
This would look good on Tanaka.
The others are good too though.
Endo could wear this..
So much something he'd wear
isn't this fine?
So fast!! (at deciding)
This will do, right?
So many t-shirts I think Hamada would like.
Hamada... which do you think he'll like?
I wonder what he likes..
Yamazaki's interests are totally opposite of mine
But I like people that are completely opposite of me.
Now this is a good one
Because he is this weird guy
I'm not joking I really think he'll like this one.
That went fast
The one I'm most unsure about is Hamada's T-shirt
Translation by Outlaws
Timing by yamasakigifs.tumblr.com
At any rate, you like this item, right?! Championship'
They each pick items the other members will like, who knows their fellow members the best?
The person receiving the items will rank them according to their taste
whoever takes 1st place won't have to pay anything. The person on last place will pay for the cloth that they found.
I ain't going to lose
First up is the always cap wearing Endo
Starting is his partner Tanaka
I'm the one spending most time with him..
So confident!
Go ahead
Look!
Right?!
You surely like that.
So much you.
fits with your hobbies.
I'll try it on.
Yes! try it.
Good feeling around that one
The thing is, the front doesn't matter
that much, but the side..
If side isn't good..
looking at it now...
Oh yeah, i see.
Next up is the cap that Hamada chose for Endo
What?
Is it good?
Looks good
Think he's got it.
Good one!
Hamada.. I feel like I'm gonna cry
Very good one!
Not bad at all
3rd is Yamazaki with his choice of cap for Endo
Here's the one I chose for you
Oh, but why this camouflage-pattern on it?
I don't feel a hat that big is for Endo
I might like this cap when playing golf
Yes exactly
thank you
Endo..
You made a good comment..
"When playing golf" That's the thought i had in mind. Yours are a little off
He may like yours, but he'll love mine.
Take a look!
You serious?
no no no..
No really, so much him. look!
Endo, tell them
Totally honest, it's pretty good
You see? I knew it!
I see right through him.
You might think it's a joke or that I'm just being positiv because he's my sempai
But i'm honest about it
i tend to go to the extremes
when playing golf, so I like this cap
I like it!
It's getting close to Endo. It has a secret intention.
Like it says "Endo, reach out your hand and pick me!".
But to be honest, i wouldn't wear any of them
Really?
Don't want any of them.
Would throw them away instantly
What about the golf cap?
That's the worst one!
Really?
But that doesn't matter, I only though about Endo
Yes, it's about me now
But which cap does Endo like the best?!
This one
Yes!
You must be kidding..
I probably wouldn't wear it
most public places
But at the golf course,
I think I'll wear this a lot
I can't wait meeting people with "golf" written on my cap
Would be a good loser.
Now it's time to find out who's going to pay for the cap. The worst cap is...
Sorry Hôsei
To be honest
I wouldn't buy this.
Liar!!
Hôsei has to pay 3,675 yen
Why wouldn't you buy it?!
Did i lose to the golf cap?
You're serious, right Endo?
I would never wear this.
true story
How many point would you give Yamasaki's?
Out of 100?
Around 15.
so low.
it must be a joke
It's no joke
All your bad points are showing today!
Next up is the search for Hamada's favorite t-shirt
1st is the loser from last round Hôsei
High quality right here
Touching it and you just know it's for Hamada
Right, here it is.
You know nothing about Hamada
No way
No way he likes the "Hawaii" written there
The color is no good too. This is surely going to be the worst one.
You are making fun of Hamada
The color is no good
2nd to show what they've found is Endo
Take a look at the old feel of it. Certain you'll like it.
that's true, think he's found a good one.
Much better than Yamazaki's. Just look how he's laughing.
Pretty good.
And now it's time for Tanaka to present a T-shirt that Hamada will like
This one.
That color, huh?
I see.
I bet you like that color.
I get it.
But the text is not very good
The text is too high up too..
The text?
Should be lower.
What are you talking about?!
That doesn't matter, it's fine.
Last to find a T-shirt for Hamada is his partner Matumoto
I think he'll sleep wearing it tonight
You think he'll like it?
I've known him since kindergarden after all,
so this is what i found...
This is...
Riddell.
Riddell? who..?
Some random guy wrote it.
He just wrote it?
Yeah, I get it.
Right?
I could wear this.
Yes, right? Riddell is written after all.
Riddell doesn't matter!
In fact the T-shirt is reversible
When you wear it you can for example do this
Take a look at that.
On the other side it's white
No sorry, no good.
He will absolutely put the pin-mic there!
But i could wear these, no doubt.
Yes, all of them!
I wear these types a lot, right?
Them all!
But this.. Yama-chan I really have no T-shirt with a place written on it
But it will fit you, I know it will fit you Hamada..
This feels cheaply made too,
I don't like that.
It will fit you Hamada
I'm sorry but this is the worst of them all
Hôsei has to pay 1000 yen
Really?!
What's going on?!
That was an easy one
Not my style
No way at all!
Must be kidding...
So Hamada which do you like the best?
I have made my choice..
Number 1 is...
This one
Yes!
Don't they all look alike?
Well, number 1 and
these two are all very fine.
But no way I'd wear this!
Next up is finding underpants
for the 2 times in a row loser Hôsei
Matsumoto goes first
Right?
Like it, right?
Hold on a moment.
He's smiling..
show them
Look!
Right?
What's funny?
He's all happy now
Seriously...
He totally loves it.
Truly loves it.
Got him with this one
You'd wear a thing like that!?
You'd wear it though
you're 40-something?
I'm 46.
He likes them this cute
Even if I liked the look I could never wear it.
So cute
It looks even better when on a mannequin.
Second to present is Endo
You get it, you totally get it!
You're kidding me!
Stop it already!
But the drawing is on the butt.
On the ass.
Endo,
Yea?
that's a problem...
the front is too plain.
This is the back?
That's right.
Nah, should have been opposite.
Does he really want it to be that cute?
Yamazaki won't like that.
I don't get it...
No way...
See, told you.
Really?
Has to be full frontal cuteness.
Eh, this isn't the front??
No, no it isn't.
What underpants have Tanaka found for Yamazaki?
I searched a lot for this one
I don't doubt you.
You'll like it, I'm sure-
Even yours?
Even you Tanaka?
You got it.
well of course, I've know him for so many years.
You're not far off..
Unbelievable!!
Cute!!
You nailed it, Tanaka!
Known him for so many years.
You understand!
A cute Mr. bear with pancakes.
I can't believe it!
You totally get him, Tanaka.
Hamada-san... give Hōsei
the pants he'll like.
I looked at it differently
When searching for the underpants
I thought of a more adult Yamazaki
The adult Yamazaki..
You don't know Yamazaki at all.
but it's been many years now
All the time, frankly,
you can't  stay in the world of cartoons.
What's this world of cartoons?
Eh... cartoon world?
Didn't know such thing existed
Ahh...
All yours are so cute
Hamada got it wrong!
What the... huh??
Hamada's doesn't fit at all!
Look at his face!
It.. it's giraffe...
no, no, no...
You absolutely don't know him.
G-giraffe...
I'll pick the loser now.
Sorry but the loser is...
this one!
Hamada has to pay 3,360 yen
It was obvious.
Yep!
This thing is frightening!
No doubt!
A thing like this...
Yeah, yeah.
Hold on!
What kind of pants
are you wearing today?
See, like that!
Cuute...
Cute!
This is hopeless...
I give up!
But they're like that see.
I see.
What do I do??
Huh?
With Endo's,
Yes?
it'd be perfect if that was the front.
Ah, that so?
It had to be the front.
Choice between cakes
and a bear-like thing..
This is agony!!
What the heck?!
What?!
I've made my choice
This!
Alright!!
Ah, really...
Well, he likes the cute stuff
That's right!
That one's overly cute.
As you'd think.
Indeed.
Too cute?
Yep.
Just a bit too cute.
As a dad that is no good
What about that?
Wandering around getting ready for a bath
The kids are gonna ask "What the heck is that"?
Same with yours!
Next is Matsumoto who's in good mood after being declared the winner in last round.
Um... Matsumoto,
I've never seen him in anything
other than something like this
Oh you are looking at it the opposit way
Exactly
Totally him
Right?
You have that image of him
I have to be honest
"i'm no fun" is what this says
No but...
I think,
Is this Frankensteins?
I want one..
I want one that is a little more positiv
This is Frankensteins jacket.
It's not his.
What jacket has Endo picked?
He's got his usual jackets
But I don't think any of them are black
When you look more carefully...
That's right
You don't think?
I actually like this camouflage-like look.
And how the camouflage is not that obvious.
Not bad at all
Ah, thanks.
Wait, let's see it on.
Seems good
Size is perfect
Yes it's perfect.
I could totally arrive anywhere
saying "good morning" with this one
Yes it's perfect.
Next is Tanaka with a jacket he thinks Matsumoto will like.
This is not bad either.
This is very nice Tanaka!
You see?
No way..
This is good, very nice.
You truly know me
Matsumoto would never wear totally black
Don't make me older than I am!
Matsumoto's partner Hamada will now reveals the jacket he's found.
I found a jacket he could wear doing winter
This'll be fun.
Oh, really?
The jacket?
Yeah, yeah.
Here we go.
Once again camouflage.
I thought so.
Pretty safe when choosing camouflage
Right, yeah.
I thought this was good
And it's covering him well
It's good, right?
What?
It's not bad.
Right?
Huh??
You can't go wrong with that pattern
Right?
Not bad at all
Look, look, see!
Hold on.
Hama-chan this is good!
I could totally wear this
So much you
But which of the 4 is his favorite?!
It's this one!!
Thank you!!
Ma-chan, thank you!!
This is the jacket I would look after in a shop.
You serious??
Yes, something like this
We'll..
So glad you 3 noticed
that i like camouflage
But this one is just making a joke of me
Hōsei has to pay 19,000 yen
Don't make fun of me!
Where did you buy this?
At Ueno?
A district in Tokyo know for it's cheap market.
Last up is the always cardigan wearing Tanaka
That's not it.
What the...
Why so black?
What's with that...
Tanaka is in trouble!!
I don't like seeing Tanaka in so much distress!
Hold on now...
Poor Tanaka!!
Please... just wait!
Tanaka's in deep trouble!!
No, no, no!
Tanaka doesn't wear such cloth.
Just look at him.
It should have a more loose fit.
Too stiff.
Yes, too stiff.
this will fit to any arrangement.
You don't know him at all.
This..
The first shot was this...?
Next is Tanaka's partner Endo with a cardigan.
This is the image I have of him.
Good!
You nailed it.
Nice!
So much Tanaka!
I see, I see.
It's good, real good!
Looking good!
It's perfect for Tanaka!
It fits him
No matter how you look at it,
I really like it.
How does it fit you?
It fits so well.
Looks like it's perfect.
It is.
What cardigan have Hamada found for Tanaka?
I believe this is just right.
Might be good!
It is!
He got it
Hamada-san!
Wow, that's...
Seems good
Wait a sec
It's great!!
Eh!? I see it...
This multiple pattern
The back is different too
Pattern is different.
A messed up cardigan
But Tanaka likes these messed up cardigans
Woah, so Tanaka.
So Tanaka.
No doubt,
That cardigan is especially him.
Exactly
Last up is Matsumoto with a cardigan for Tanaka
Yep!
Looks like he got it.
This one's good.
Look!
I get it!
He gets it!
I see.
Right??
Yes, yes...
You understand him.
Tanaka is always wearing these bright colors.
This is what I'd propose for Tanaka anytime.
Oh god, this is a tough one
A tough one.
Perfect cardigan.
It's great on him.
Yes, it's so Tanaka, the size is perfect too.
Nobody but Tanaka could wear that cardigan.
This cardigan cannot rest in peace
(if Tanaka doesn't wear it)
But which cardigan does Tanaka choose?!
Can i pick the worst?
This one.
Truly horrible.
Truly bad.
Hôsei has to pay 24,570 yen
Not this one, no way, nope.
As for the rest, I like them all!
But I can boil them down to 2.
I like them, but have to put one aside.
Go ahead.
And that's endo's.
Saw it coming.
I understand it too.
I like it...
I like it, but... I want it to be more relaxed.
Yes, of course
Ah, I see.
Can i just say this?
I asked the shopassistant if they didn't have something a little bigger
But this is all they had
You asked, huh?
I did
What the heck!?
What kind of conversation is that?!!
Which cardigan does Tanaka like the best?!
The cardigan I want is...
This one!
Yeah!!
Mhm, it's good.
It suits Tanaka.
But I want to buy this one
Ah, yea, yea.
I would by this.. immediately
I see.
This is the best, because...
The design
You like the design
This is the cardigan that is most me
So the loser is...
Yama-chan!
Gonna be expensive.
That's an expensive one Tanaka!
24,570 yen
Can we just do that?
Yea...
And he just takes it from the wallet.
How much in total?
48,245 yen! (around 480$)
I though he had a better eye for fashion.
It honestly hurts!
Hurts, huh?
Yes really!
Really.
Seriously, right?