Special thanks to GAKIDAVE for typesetting this episode!!
Gaki no Tsukai's famous series: Shichi-Henge
In this series we get to see how a true comedian behaves
In a harsh situation in which they can't fail!
And today's contestant is...
First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
Bananaman Himura's Shichi-Henge!!
Finally Bananaman
We all talked several times about wanting Bananaman to do Shichi-henge
But we were all thinking Shitara would do it
But in the end Himura was like "I'll do it"
Seriously?!
It feels like we left a half-opened door
Let's call him here
Please
I mean, Shitara is the mind behind Bananaman's skits, right?
Yeah that's true, it's me
So, why did you accept this?
Don't say it like that man, it really hurts
It's ok to get injured, but please avoid spurting blood at us, ok?
Yeah that's the plan
So, these are our past records
That's how it is
Where do you think you'll fit in?
Just asking, you know
I see there are few people from Tokyo in here
That's true
And I can see Arita is no. 10, so at least above him
Yes, yes...
I'd be happy to overcome him
So 10 or above
Yeah
You don't know what he'll be doing?
I saw him with our manager lots of times during our meetings
And they were... shockingly silent
We didn't have a clue about what to think
I had no idea what I should do for this
Or better, there were lots of things I thought I should do
But in the end, I didn't want to do those
Translation & editing by: Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Typesetting by: GakiDave
find more at: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
like my page: facebook.com/shionnotsukai
support my content on:
・ ko-fi:  ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
・ patreon:  patreon.com/shionnotsukai
So, what should we do today?
Yeah, what?
This one struck me, "Endo's self-brought plan"
"Re-propose to Chiaki"...
I didn't bring that
I never thought about a second marriage
I'm happy now
What do you mean? That's 'cause you're young
Yeah I guess right now we're both fine by ourselves
It's all calm and peaceful now, huh?
Shitara do you usually watch our show? What do you think?
I must say, every time Heipo shows up I can't help but laugh
Is that so?
Not me, I get so mad even when I have to take the elevator with him
But I thought that this "family" got along pretty good...
We can't get Heipo doing stuff right now 'cause he's busy
Also we don't have plans he could fit in right now
I wonder what can we do about it
What can we do?
That's also true...
Is there something...?
Hello?
Yeah, I'm about to tune it
Yes, it's ok
Put 'em in
Why was he so fixated on that song?
It became his body blow
That couldn't fail
It was pretty unfair
The song he chose
It was unfair, wasn't it?
That's the only one he can play
And I did know that, so I was like "no way I'll laugh at it"
But it seems like I laugh easier than I thought
I was like "oh crap, am I the only one laughing? That's embarrassing"
Are you still working on "Yamazaki's Opera"?
I'd love to do that, but how should we...?
If we're talking about Yamazaki...
You remember that 100-people cutting episode?
We're close to Gaki's 1000th episode by now
I see... Oh! I got it
How about 1000-people cutting...?
Let's do it!
But I couldn't even cut 100 of them!
My back was destroyed after that!
There's no way I could do the 1000-people cut
Come on it's fine, you're not that Yama-chan anymore
No way, I'm even older
Sorry for taking your time, it's a pleasure to meet you
It's fine, my pleasure
We'd like to begin the interview right now if possible
Sure, please
We're currently having a special report section about Downtown on our magazine
And we wanted to ask you few things to you mr. Himura, being so close to them
Oh I see, ok I'm in
First off, what's the relationship
Between you and Downtown?
Well, it's not much more than a work-related thing
I mean, you saw them on tv, right? They make everyone laugh
I can say they're the most influential comedians
I see, here's our next question
What do you think makes Downtown so funny?
I see... I think it's their Kansai-dialect
They both use it, and I think that's what makes them so funny
They both use it
Is there something else...?
Yeah, for example Matsumoto's boke (funny man) act is really hilarious
I do the same job as him and yet I always think like "how could he come up with that?"
It makes me think
But to say it more clearly I think...
It's the Kansai-dialect
I think the Kansai-dialect is hilarious
Anything else?
Well, even Hamada is incredible
The way he takes control of everything is unmatched
His tsukkomi act is always on point
And he's always speaking in Kansai-dialect, right?
I mean, his tsukkomi
And Kansai-dialect is hilarious
Is there anything else?
Yeah even their DVDs, I mean...
You can hear a lot of Kansai-dialect in those
Kansai-dialect is hella funny
I was thinking about it but...
Maybe if they didn't use Kansai-dialect...
They would probably suck
After all it's in Kansai-dialect... and it's so hilarious
I see, thank you so much for your help
Thanks to you
Excuse us
Come on
So irritating
That was straight up criticism towards us
It totally was
I laughed while also feeling a bit frightened
So, 1000-people cut?
Let's do that, it was so funny
Ok it was fun, but I couldn't do 100 people, how can I do 1000 of them?
That's cause you surrendered halfway
But a lot of people... would beat me up...
What's with this childish explanation?!
Is that hearsay?!
Forget about it and let's go cut 1000 people, come on
1000 people is too much...
The hell is he doin'?
Like this
He's staring so much
That was exhausting
- At least open that thing properly
Yeah, at least that
So stupid
That's not what he was aiming for!
He was supposed to open that, right?
Yeah, it's not even hard
But he kept on messing it up
I have no idea if he did it on purpose or not
He also forgot about rolling the lipstick out of its cointainer!
It wasn't even twisted
He just moved the cylinder around!
Don't you think Heipo knows this type of shops?
On whiteboard: "Popular guy Heipo teaches us popular stores for women!"
Where do you usually seduce a woman?
Skewer meat places or such
People from Osaka loves em
They also say you have to go there at least twice, so
It's popular between people of Osaka
So I thought like, maybe some girl from Osaka...
Would like to go there with me, don't you think...?
Who cares?
I wanted him to say "eh?" to be honest...
He usually says that
Step inside, please
I shall now proceed
To cleanse you from evil spirits
Do it, please
note: just some random mantra-like yelling action, no meaning whatsoever
Persimmon seed
I feel relieved
Thank you very much
He spat em out one by one so nicely
I wasn't expecting persimmon seeds
He put so many persimmon seeds in his mouth
Plus, without any soy sauce
I thought those were his teeth
Is he really popular in cabaret clubs?
note: on whiteboard - "Discussion 'till morning! Why is Yoshinobu popular in cabaret clubs?"
Yeah I said it lots of times before, it's true
Really?
Producer
Yoshinobu Nakamura
I'm not popular at all by the way
That goes without sayin'
Come on, don't say that
Eh?!
He said it
Don't say "eh?!"!!
You said it too quickly
He really is
Is that so?
He's popular between who? I mean, age range...?
He actually dated girls
From cabaret clubs for a pretty long time
He dated a girl from there
Didn't he had a wife...?
Is it really ok to say that...?
He had a wife right? A daughter too
I know that for sure, man
Well, the fact he's popular is true, though
Oh shit, you're right!
Of course man, you should have known that
I don't know, man
Hey bro, can ya lend me some money?
- Stand up, dude
But I don't have any
Of course you do
I don't
No way you don't, lemme see
I don't, really
I bet you do
I don't!
Some coins at least?
I don't...
Then jump
I can hear em, jump some more
More!
More!!
What the hell!
I don't have any
You do!
One more time
But I don't have any
More! More! More, you punk!
Come with us
Come on, man...
I didn't know he could tap-dance that well
He practiced a lot
Gimme a break
They're piling up good, ain't they?
He actually can tap-dance
I had no idea
I knew it so I noticed his shoes as soon as he got in
I thought "ok, he's gonna tap" and I thought I could bear it, but...
But I didn't know how he was going to start it!
So friggin' irritating...
They usually sing as they dance, too
This kind of... became some high-quality stuff!!
Making you laugh with tap-dancing... amazing
- That's impressive, yeah
Maybe I should learn tap-dancing too
There's also this thing with Tanaka here
It's been a while
Oh, here you are
You know
I have something to say
You're doing my impression right? It's not good lately
You're not like Himura at all
Like Himura?
Like Hiruma, yes
...
I mean, I'm doing so good but...
It's kind of irritating
Can you be a lil bit more Himura?
I'll do it, you follow me, ok?
I'm doin' it~ later~
Try it
I'm doin--
That's not it, completely different
Let's try it together
One, two...
I'm doin' it~ later~
That's completely different!
Completely wrong
Yes, I'm sorry
It's not good
You're not Himura at all, what's with that pronunciation?
Everybody: SAFE
He looked like him
Yeah, he does
So much
He said "Hiruma" the first time...
You're in this one, Tanaka: "Infidelity audition for serious comedian Tanaka"
Yes
What's that?
'Cause Tanaka is not the type to have affairs
Unlike Yoshinobu
He hasn't much lust
Are you actually [several dirty jokes]?
That's scary!
If I'd see that I'd be like
"Man, that's not like Yoshinobu!"
Of course it's not like that
Sorry for all of this, we're done for today
We're not gonna mention it again
You should blame Heipo for this
Heipo started it all
Yeah we just followed that
Today's hard, we can't decide anything...
I can see it
They're exposed
No way, no way
Watch out!
Wait
That's not how it works
I can totally see them
Are you breeding them?!
It hurt me!
They're rustling all over the place
How many of them do you have?!
Geez...
Watch out!
It's getting scary
What the hell, man...
What are you doing?
Et voilà!
"Et voilà" my ass!
Just go away
That's what took him so long
This friggin' guy
Should we take this dove too?
As soon as he entered I already saw one popping out
That's what made me laugh
Geez
That poor dove flappin' around in his pocket
Translation & editing by: Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
We're done
How much?
Huh?
It's 46
You mean 46'000￥?
- Yes
Typesetting by: GakiDave
And that means...?
Fifth place
That's really good!
I did it!
I made it
find more at: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
You're above Haranishi
Really?
Yeah, you're over him
- Impressive
Thanks a lot
The hell, man?
like my page: facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Thank you
It's pooping to its heart's content
Was the dove part fun---
support my content on: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai or patreon.com/shionnotsukai
It's making sounds
Is that their sound?
Is that how they sound like?
Yeah, it was them
It sounded like a laughter
I had no idea they did that
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FAN-TRANSLATION MADE BY A FAN FOR OTHER FANS. ALL COPYRIGHT ARE RESERVED TO THEIR RESPECTIVE OWNERS.
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SPECIAL THANKS TO GAKIDAVE FOR TYPESETTING THIS EPISODE!!