Matsumoto-san, I don't think these guys want the money
- No no no
- That's not true
That's what we feel like
You guys don't have that hunger from your youth
- No it's not like that
- Well if you put it like that
- Kinoshita can you do it?
- I think these guys have the wrong technique for winning the money
- I see
If you think about it,
you should be putting on a show
You earn money by putting on a show
That's right, this is supposed to be entertainment
I used to dance when I was a teenager
So I want to recreate that time
We used to dance in front of the NAVIO in Osaka
So I want to dance for you guys and recreate that time
Aiming for the prize, onegaishimasu!
(... that's why he's in blackface?!)
He's not in sync
He's just getting started
Got a bad feeling about this
In front of the NAVIO, the NAVIO
Aim for the prize money
- He's having fun
- The judges are ready
The whole time I was watching, all I could think is,
"Are you fucking kidding me?"
Not only can he not dance,
it's not even entertaining!
I will do some karate stone breaking
I think this might be it
In the past, I've broken 10 stones on this show (Special Skill Demonstration episode)
Today, I will do 15 stones
- Will this turn out okay?
- Fujiwara make sure it's alrught
- Go at your own pace Fujiwara
There might be fragments, so I will wear these goggles
Regardless of if it breaks or not, the judges will decide if it's a success
We wanna see someone win the 30,000 yen
- Barely broke them
- Write down his score
That's it?
He didn't even break 10
He broke 7 stones
All I can remember is his "Senya!"
That "Senya" is really embarassing, isn't it?
Most people would get 700 yen
Fujiwara, what happened?
It, genuinely hurts
This is something I've tried on other TV shows
I think I can win by tight-rope walking
That is certainly unique
I will cross this 7m rope (0.077 football fields)
You're not just messing around right?
No of course not
I think he can do this, since Tanaka is a serious boy
He takes this kind of thing seriously
- His clothes are lame though
- His clothes are lame
C'mon focus
Please, allow me to focus
Tanaka-kun, proceed at your own pace
- That's ok
- No problem you can do it
He's safe if he returns right?
Yeah he just can't fall down part way
Is it better to be slow, or fast?
Here he goes
- That's OK
- He's still safe
That's all you can do!
- Let him focus
- Focus, focus!
"Are you kidding me?" is all I can think right now
There's no way he can return now right?
What is this?
He really returned after that huh?
That "PAN!" was really loud
Why does his ass make a "PAN!"?
You're done man!
What are you doing?
- Get down!
- He can do it!
It doesn't matter if he can do it
No hang on, why is he doing it again?
He's done!
Why did you keep doing it over and over again?
You're just entertaining yourself while mom makes dinner!
Until she says "it's ready!"
This is not supposed to be a way to kill time
What was that, seriously?
If I get another chance, I'd like to try again
Why would you get another chance?
No more chances?
Cause, man,
The rice is cooked already!
- Mom's done cooking?
- The rice is cooked man
She's telling you to hurry up
Dad started drinking his beer already
What are you guys gonna do, seriously
- Can you still do this?
- Please let us continue
30,000 is too much I think,
can we lower the prize amount?
Tell us then
Tell us, how much you are aiming for
Like "I'm aiming for 40,000"
I can make this cardboard box very quickly
Someone else should do it first so you guys understand how good I am
Tsukajiro-san, please try this out
Try this out, fold the carboard box
- Fast as you can
- Into a box right?
He's fast!
He's an expert!
17 seconds
That's pretty quick
That is pretty fast,
but I can do it in half that time
How much is this worth?
15,000 yen
Wel'll start when you say OK
That seems like cheating
- Are you opening it?
- No, no I'm not
What are you doing? Stop that!
I'm just checking the fold
- 9 minutes, 20 seconds
- Thank you very much
It was pretty sloppy
If you set your own prize amount, and can't win it ...
Right?
This is tough
It wasn't even that funny
- You don't wanna hear that
- Yeah that sucks
There used to be a TV talent show that gave you a white guitar for performing right?
While I was watching that show, I did the same thing they did
And that guy won that white guitar
So I want to perform that talent that won him a guitar
A white guitar is expensive
So I am aiming for 12,000 yen
I will my put my ear, inside my ear
"Put my ear ... inside ... my ear"
It's in!
None of us can do it right?
So close!!!
That was close desu ne?
That was certainly not something anybody can do
But you came close though
Next, Tsukajiro tried jumping rope 20 times in a row
Then, Fujiwara from LISCENCE performed his nose-mouth udon act!
- It's a walkway
- Udon walkway
If you ask me,
this is a terrible day for all of us
Can you guys do it or not?
I still use a flip phone, even today
On this flip phone,
I can type out a text without looking at the phone
So if you guys give me a phrase I can just tap it out
- I can type that phrase, without mistakes
- How much is this worth?
1500 yen (~$15)
So cheap!
Well OK, it depends on the phrase
Write out "Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai Ya Arrahende"
He's looking towards me
How did I do?
3000?!
He gave you 3000!
I thought it was worth that much
How do I put it, it's kind of an illusion
An illusion is a great idea
- Everyone, please look at that monitor screen
- Again?
I am doing it live, but please view it on the monitor
I really want to win 4000 yen
In just a moment, you will see, in my mouth, an illusion
I present my "Mouth Water"
It is over in an instant, so please pay attention
With that said, here I go
"Mouth Water"?
But we've seen this before, you know
We've seen this before?
This TV show has been airing for a while
We've been doing this for 29 years
He's done this on a previous episode
What does this mean, I don't understand
I've seen this so many times
And during the drum roll,
you did it by accident
What do we do, should we leave it all up to Tanaka?
Please let me have my revenge
- Can you do it?!
- YES, YES!
We've had enough fooling around
I have no choice here but to succeed
I will give us a good ending!
30,000 yen, that is what I want
So you're not changing the prize money
At your own pace
- You're alright
- Focus!
The way he returned was not cool
Like he was about to advance
He's halfway there
This is tricky!
"This is tricky!"
Alright we're done!
Though the filming is over, some big news for Downtown?!
Hamada-san's Kyary Pyamyu Pyamyu - I mean Hamada Byamyu Byamyu
Kyary Pyamyu Pyamyu's producer,
wants to make song for Hamada-san
So just forget about this 30K yen thing
This is a big chance for you
Your fate has really changed!