[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
-This is...
-It's a postcard.
Of that show.
It's me as Hikaru Yuki.
Hikaru Yuki is quite beautiful.
This is it!
He was singing and dancing.
I am thinking of selling these.
Why?
And where would you sell these?
In Harajuku, of course.
Harajuku?
No way!
Harajuku is hot these days...
You should sell them at Nittere. (Broadcasting Station).
These won't sell in Harajuku!
-Excuse me...
-We're talking here.
You again?
Again?
Ehm... I have another letter from our guy, Matsumoto.
-Sorry, please read it.
-Why?
I've had enough.
-The same thing happens every time.
-That's right.
It's happening again.
It's the same pattern.
I hate reading these things.
Let's look at the map first.
Please read the letter first.
Okay, I'll read it.
Sure.
"You lot are asexual lowlife trash comedians that don't understand sexuality."
"It pains me to see you act like little high school boys whenever you are faced with the opposite sex."
Here it comes...
Every time...
"So let us see who the real sexual technician is."
"Who will be named 'Beast Don Juan', the 'Manic Sexual King'?"
"That is the purpose of this letter."
"Come to the specified location."
"Hitoshi Matsumoto".
Dixie Normous' Mansion!
And Kazuo Umezu's House!
The landmark...
Dixie Normous is labeled as the "Erection King".
He's the erection king of Japan!
It's a pretty big building.
So we have Umezu's house and Dixie Normous' Mansion...
But I don't know what this street is.
And he wrote 'Around here'.
-Around?
-So the building could not even exist.
That's right, it might be the wrong place.
He's not specific at all.
This guy sends us all these letters...
But in the end he's always next to last place.
-That's right.
-He’s always about to lose.
-Even last time... I couldn't watch him do that...
-Yes!
He's so rude!
-He is!
-Totally!
We always win so easily.
What should we do?
Is it close?
He's over there.
This map is useless!
Let's just go.
-Isn't it right there?
What the heck?!
The guys have been putting their male pride on the line in these past 5 challenges!
Matsumoto has called upon them once again for another serious match.
What is awaiting them in this next stage?
Over here.
Isn't this the G Studio?
It was just around the corner.
Yes, it's so close.
100,000,001.
100,000,002.
100,000,003.
100,000,004.
100,000,005.
100,000,006.
100,000,007.
100,000,008.
100,000,009.
100,000,010.
-100,000,011.
-Stop it already.
Are you a child?
So you came?
Of course we did.
You bastards...
You're always just !%!@$%# around.
Never mind that...
You always call us so late.
Alright!
You guys... are completely hopeless!!
No, you are hopeless.
But I know that you bastards haven't been sucking on any breasts lately...
What does that even mean?
Tell me, when was the last time you sucked on a nipple?
Hamada, go.
That's too raw!
-Yamazaki!
-Yes?
When was the last time you did it?
Sucking a nipple?!
You have to tell me the truth!
-What?!
Really, don't lie.
Well, for me it's been about a week.
Really?!
After Gaki's recording.
Whoa, so Wednesday?
So after last week's Gaki recording?
Yes.
Endo, how about you?
I haven't done it at all.
I've been single for a while so...
Just tell us about the last time!
-The last time?
-Yes.
Well, it was the other day... In Gotanda...
About 3 days ago...
-You sure talk!
-I sucked and she also sucked back.
Actually I think I saw him there.
I mean, I don't care.
You're single after all.
Alright then.
Draw the curtains!
-You've gone and made something crazy again...
-So many mannequins.
Nipple Speed Sucking Match!
The challenge consists of sucking all the raisins off the mannequin's nipples.
Contestants have to go back and forth and their time will be measured.
The loser will have to face a harsh punishment.
-Can I ask a question?
-Sure.
-Can we touch them?
-I mean, other than our mouths...?
-Of course, they are women, so please touch them.
Please touch them.
So? Who's going first?
This one looks like a long one.
-Right, right.
-But we still don't know.
-Alright then, let's go with... Endo!
-Me again?
I wanna watch people go first.
Everyone just wants to see how fit you are.
Yeah, we wanna see.
Go, Endo!
Sure.
As usual, our first contestant is Endo.
What will be his time?
Alright then, Endo!
Yes!
Go!
Let's go!
He seems nervous.
Oh, I see...
He's stumbling already.
He's doing pretty well.
But you have to go deep or you'll never get the raisins.
Oh right, right.
-He's so gentle.
-He is.
But it's also kinda dirty...
Gentle...
But you really can't be dropping any of the raisins.
-So you have to hold them inside your mouth.
-Oh, right.
Or you could also eat them as you go.
He hasn't been sucking any nipples lately.
-It looks a bit awkward for him.
-Right.
He's also always the one getting stuff done to him.
-Right?
-Oh, right!
-Right.
Yes, yes...
He would be the one with the raisins on his nipples.
He's being really gentle.
-He is.
Pretty good, no?
The end!!
How did he do?
How did you feel?
-Can I be honest?
-Sure.
I was like, "What the hell is this?".
"What the hell am I doing?"
As I was doing it, I thought...
"This is so stupid".
-But you kept your rhythm and did it at your own pace.
-Yes.
I don't know if that's good or bad.
-Alright, let's look at Endo's score.
-Yes!
This is it!
43 seconds!
That's fast!
We still don't know if that's good.
-We don't know.
-I mean that's fast!
-It's not slow...
-But he took his sweet time...
Right... He was pretty carefree.
I think he was going pretty slow.
But he didn't miss any.
Right, he got them all.
-And we could feel his love for every single nipple.
-Right, we felt the love.
Right.
Also, there's an old lady mannequin at the end.
-Right...
-So please give that one the most love.
Alright!
Are there any volunteers?
How about it?
-What should I do...?
-I wanna go.
Shall we try you out?
-Really?-You can go next, Yamasaki.
Really?
Alright.
Okay then, let's go.
Yamasaki.
Our next contestant is Yamasaki.
Will he beat Endo's time?
-Alright, are you ready?
-Yes!!
Yamasaki, let's go!
Can he beat 43 seconds?
He's pretty good at these things.
Oh, this might be bad.
-You have to go back and forth!
-Back and forth!
Isn't this pretty slow?
Back and forth!
-Look!
-He's pretty slow.
Was I faster than this?
I don't know...
He's not that slow.
I think it was about the same.
He's not fast enough.
Isn't he getting faster?
-But he's not touching them at all.
-Endo did it like this as well.
That's true.
He's not touching them at all.
I wonder how he'll do...
-Alright, be gentle.
-Gentle, gentle.
Gentle...
With love.
That's good.
The end!
-He was a bit faster.
-I wonder about that...
How did you feel, Yamasaki?
It didn't feel fast at all.
I think he'll be comparable to Endo.
You're right.
Yes.
How did you feel?
I was like, "What the hell am I doing?".
Right?
You start to question your actions...
Right, right.
The staff was asking me the same thing in the rehearsal.
What is his score?
Let's see!
So fast!!
-That's fast!
-So fast!
That's crazy! Crazy!
He's safe from the punishment.
That's amazing!
So fast!
That was fast.
Oh, I forgot to tell you, but today's punishment is pretty harsh.
-What?!
-No way!
-It's always harsh though...
-Right...
Okay, I'll go next.
Hamada, are you going?
Are you going?
-Do it gently.
-Be gentle.
Next up we have our local sadist, Hamada.
Will he show a gentler side?
Alright Hamada, let's go!
The start is looking rough already.
From the start...
From the get-go.
Right, right.
Remember to alternate.
-Oh, he's eating them.
-He's eating them!
He is!
He's the type to eat on the go.
He's eating!
-He's picking up his own rhythm.
-You're right.
Doesn't he look like Shimura?
(Ken Shimura)
Right, his movements!
He looks like Shimura.
-Just like Shimura!
-You're right!
He's moving like Shimura.
-He's doing the Shimura-style.
-Right, Shimura-style.
He's surprisingly fast.
Be gentle here.
-He's pretty fast.
-Yeah.
The end!
-That was fast.
-So fast.
Surprisingly fast.
-It was fast.
-Yeah.
-He stumbled at the beginning.
-Yes, he struggled a bit.
Was that fast?
-I think he was surprisingly fast.
-This one was fast.
-But he looked like Shimura.
-Right, the Shimura-style.
Like this, like Shimura.
He found his rhythm.
While sucking on some nipples.
Okay, what was his time?
37 seconds!
Same time.
Alright!
I see...
-Hamada is also exempt from the punishment.
-Right!
Maybe Endo is the slowest...?
No way!
Our fourth contestant wants to show off his youth.
It's Inomoto from License!
-He's surprisingly slow.
-Maybe...
-He didn't miss any of them.
-Right.
Yeah...
He showed off his agility.
And got a high score of 34 seconds.
Next up is his partner, Fujiwara.
He's very gentle.
That's right.
-He's doing pretty good.
-You have to keep up the pace.
-Missing one is the worst.
-Right.
He keeps up the pace and reaches the goal!
He gets today's high score of 32 seconds!
How was it, Fujiwara?
I could smell someone's spit while I was doing it.
-No way!
-That's gross!
I hate that!
I would get whiffs of some foul stench along the way.
I really hate that!
-Please don't!
-That's bad!
Guys! Please clean them properly!
This thing is getting hot.
Endo is in trouble.
We still don't know.
Okay then, let's just go with Tanaka next.
-Let's go with Tanaka.
-Alright!
-Maybe he'll do good today.
-I'll redeem myself.
-Are you ready, Tanaka?
-Yes!
You have to beat 43 seconds.
I can probably make it.
As long as I remain calm.
Now that I look at it again, Endo's time is extremely bad.
-Right.
-It's pretty bad.
-Yeah, it's so slow.
43 is so bad.
So bad...
I guess the first one always has a disadvantage.
That's right.
I've lost 4 out of 5 so...
I've had enough already.
I will win.
Tanaka has been constantly losing throughout this series.
He has to clear his name for the sake of his wife.
Alright, Tanaka!
Let's go!
-Oh no, oh no.
-Why is he so nervous?
Oh no, this is gonna be bad.
Alright.
Oh, he's pretty good.
He's quite fast.
So fast!
Oh, he's going for it.
But he's fine, it's fine.
That's pretty good.
Yes, he's fine.
He can do it.
He's being careful not to miss anything.
Right.
He's being very aware.
He's clinging onto them.
He's very greedy.
He doesn't wanna drop any.
Oh, the wig fell off!
Is that okay to do?
The wig fell off!
-I guess it can't be helped.
-He's really going for it.
He is!
He's panicking a bit.
Here comes the last one!
Almost there
He's got this!
Isn't this close?
Isn't it close?
He went back to the same nipple!
He went back and forth 2 times.
That was hard!
Pulling the wig off was a bit questionable from my perspective.
-In terms of prettiness I mean...
-Right, the beauty points.
-I wonder how you did...
-You were a bit too over-excited.
-But I think I did alright on time.
I wonder about that...
You never know, you never know.
Alright, let's see it.
Tanaka's time!
Here it is!
He made it!
Alright!!!
-For real?!
-Yes!!
Wife! I did it!!
I cleared my name!
-Matsumoto!!
-Sorry about that.
Endo was so slow!
43 is so slow.
It is.
-Everyone else was in the 30s.
-Right.
Yes!
So... Do I really need to go...?
-Of course!
-You have to!
But you know, I have some sore muscles...
I don't care!
And I'm also the organizer... So...
I don't feel the need...
-No, no, no, please do it.
-No way, no way.
-You have to establish your dominance then.
-Right!
Matsumoto, who has barely been able to avoid punishments, will try to aim for the top.
Alright, our last contestant is Matsumoto.
Let's go!!
I just go, right?
Ready?
Start!!
He's going ahead!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Why?!
-You had a false start!
False start!!
False start!
-You are so desperate!
-So desperate!
You made me look so uncool!
What did I do?!
You went before the last ring!
-Alright, let's go!
-He really wants to win.
Ready...
-Start!!
-Not yet, not yet.
That's crazy.
He's pretty fast.
So fast!
Oh! He missed!
-He missed!!
Oh my god!
Alright! Alright!!
I did it! I made it!
This is bad.
It's so bad.
-This is bad!
-So bad!
This is bad!
-This is bad!
-So bad!
He already missed two.
Isn't he disqualified?!
He might get the same time as Endo.
He might.
They might go to a sudden death rematch.
It could happen.
-Look, he's so slow.
-So slow!
-So slow! So slow!
-He's a slug!
So slow!
It's bad.
-Be gentle.
-Gentle!
This is bad.
-This is bad.
-This is bad!
I was set up!!
What do you mean?!
My raisins were so hard to suck!!
There were some really small ones as well!!
Everyone had the same ones!!
I have never seen such small nipples!
Show we open it up this way?
Outside in?
Yes!
Right?
He's definitely not within the 30s mark.
Now way!!
Yeah, no way.
-You were so slow.
-No way you got under 40.
He's definitely in the 40s.
Here I go.
Okay!
Good for you, Endo!
-See?!
-We told you!
-Time to beat is 43 seconds?
-Yes!
Anything below 4...
And Matsumoto gets punished.
Let's go!!
Here it is!
Same score...
Really?!
Sudden death...
Alright!
Whoa, it's sudden death.
Sudden death!
-Isn't this our first sudden death scenario?
-Yes.
Awesome!
But we won't have to do it again, right??
Right?
Endo will go first on the sudden death re-match.
Will he be able to pressure Matsumoto?
Sudden death!
Shozo Endo!
Let's go!
Can he win?
Maybe.
He's done it once already.
He's gentle.
That's good.
You won't lose time as long as you don't miss anything.
-What? There's one missing.
One nipple was missing!
He is going for it.
He's going steady.
He's recovering.
I think he's being very gentle.
Like he's never seen a nipple.
He looks at them.
He's that kind of guy.
I don't know about this!!
Endo is pretty slow after all.
-But he really hasn't done anything different.
He was the same last round.
-Right?
But he was speeding up in the middle there.
He hasn't gotten any faster.
That was pretty slow.
No, this is bad.
He was pretty slow.
His time hasn't gone down.
Let's see it after Matsumoto does it.
I'm sure he got into the 40 second slot.
Right.
Matsumoto is feeling confident after seeing Endo's performance.
Who will win?
Sudden death!
Hitoshi Matsumoto!
Let's start!
He wanted to go.
He's not being gentle at all.
Look at his desperation!
Why is he dropping them?
The nipples disappear into his mouth.
It's because he's got a dirty mouth.
But he's picking up the pace.
-Oh, that's true!
-Yeah, a bit.
He's picking it back up.
That's fast.
Fail! Fail!!
-He's coming back!
-Oh, so fast!
So fast.
He's pretty fast!
Be gentle.
-He's coming back!
-Oh, so fast!
So fast.
-Huh?
Why?!
He was very gentle there!
You went twice!
You went twice!!
What?!
You went twice over there.
You did!
For real?!
Yes, look at this.
Really?!
Yes!
It's true!!
-Alright guys, I'm gonna reveal them at the same time.
-Alright!
This is Endo's time.
So please pay close attention.
And this is Matsumoto's.
-Understood?
-Yes.
-Please!!
-This one is Endo's right?
-Who is the winner of the sudden death?!
-Enough already!!
-Who is the winner...?
Here it is!
Please!!
-This one is Endo's right?
-Who is the winner of the sudden death?!
-Enough already!!
-Who is the winner...?
Here it is!
Oh! 38 seconds!!
Endo won!!
No way!!
No way!
I did it!!
Let's go!!!
Yeah!!
-I'm telling you, it's wrong!!
-Alright!!
Okay, Matsumoto will receive the punishment!!
-Matsumoto's punishment is titled, "Screaming Out Loud Feat. Weather Camera!!".
What does that even mean?
It means that they'll film you from the top of a building.
Oh right!
Like an ant.
There won't be anyone nearby.
-I see...
-That's gonna be embarrassing...
Hello everyone.
I'm Hitoshi Matsumoto.
I actually have a bit of a cold.
So my doctor gave me some medicine...
My nose is also pretty blocked up.
But I guess that's all besides the matter...
Anyways... With all the medicine and all...
You know... I don't think I should be moving much but...
But I can't do anything about it...
So I'll just do this...
Talking about it won't change anything...
Here I go.
I'm here!
I'm here in Ginza!
That was the worst
I'm here in Shimbashi!