Why such a stern face all of a sudden?
Do you plan on scaling the final stretch of Mt Fuji from the 6th station?
You've got to be mistaken!
What do you mean?
Everyone has latent, secret hidden paranormal powers like clairvoyance and telepathy!
That maybe so....but I really don't know....
Surely you've heard of pyschokinesis?
Not really, what's it all about?
Then surely, you must have heard of pyrokinesis!
Nope, never heard of that either!
That's when you set things on fire with your thoughts!
Oh really!
It's a kind of a paranormal ability!
Just by thinking hard about it....
..for example that guy over there....just by willing it, you could set his head on fire! Pooof!
Wow! That's some power!
Yeah, isn't it? That's called pyrokinesis!
And then there's psychokinesis....and you've got all kinds of kinesises!
I'll have you know, I too have a little bit of paranormal ability!
oh? And what's that?
Thing is, my paranormal ability is kinda low-key and inconspicuous!
So, it's not exactly the kind of thing you can brag to people about!
And it's also really hard to get them to believe that I have this paranormal power!
Well, why don't you give everyone a demonstration before our eyes then? You should be able to move some things around by willing it, right?
Ok, let's see....take this wagon here for example....
Would you mind pushing this wagon for me?...like this
just give it a light push!
(matsumoto clenches his teeth)
see?
The fact is!...Don't move!
The fact is...your push would only have resulted in the wagon moving to this extent!
But that extra distance it covered was due to my paranormal abilities!
That was a display of my 'wago-kinesis'!!
What the hell is 'wago-kinesis'?
Well...it's a wagon, isn't it?
Are you even allowed to latch on a 'kinesis' to an object, and make a paranormal power out of a thing?
Well, that was my 'wago-kinesis'!
But do you see why it's so hard to prove to people I have this ability?
see?
Without my paranormal powers, it would only have gone that far!
Ah! Even that postcard falling down was due to my paranormal powers!....That was my 'card-kinesis!
See?!
Look at me, dammit!
That just doesn't seem right to me....that bit about the 'wago-kinesis'
I mean if it was just standing still, and you moved it....
Ah! That's my 'card-kinesis' once again!!
You're always late!!
You always start freaking out and doing your thing AFTER the event!!
You should do it BEFORE it falls down!
Wait, wait! What? What? Whaddya mean? How am I supposed to do it?
For example, if it was originally standing here, and you were there, and you started freaking out with your 'GRROWWWL!', and THEN it moved, that would be something!
THAT would get the audience all excited and worked up!
What's the big idea in pushing it first, and THEN claiming it moved because of your powers?
But isn't what I just did just now significant and note-worthy?
What is?
Isn't is significant? - Isn't it?! - Isn't it?!
Who are you mimicing?
Is it not significant that my paranormal powers are supplementing and adding to the original force you imparted on an object?
But the point is that's difficult to establish!
If you made it move on its own, then THAT would be different and easy to establish!
I can also do the reverse!!
What are you talking about? What's 'reverse'?
After you push it....
After you've pushed it....
Push it, will you?
Now, what we have here is....
Wait, wait! Hold on just a minute!
It's so creepy when you make those weird paranormal faces!!
What you saw just now....
What you just saw, ladies and gentlemen, was a demonstration of 'reverse wago-kinesis'!!
OK, what's that about then?
Well, it was actually supposed to go a bit farther than that!
Do you imply you stopped it?
Indeed, I did
Who cares, you jackass!
(mimics Hamada) - 'Who cares?'