Tonight at the arena, a huge audience became electrified by the
Unbeatable champion Moriman
And the man, who has never yet been victorious, the eternal challenger
Yamasaki Hosei's revenge match
This time, despite Yamasaki's persuasion, he failed several times
Pantyhose removal match
Beer smashing showdown
Gobou stick match
And also piping hot soup battle. All of the showdowns were a disastrous failure to him.
Champion Moriman was destroying him
Tonight, the scenes that no one saw before with the fighters will be shown
Yamazaki vs Moriman Storming Last Final Revenge Match the second part
I think Happosai ended at every home
After the end of the "pipng-hot Happosai showdown",
Matsumoto-san, I don't want to say this
But we can't do Happosai battle anymore
Fine, then let's go with "cheese fondue"?
I will do my best!
Be more careful
Next time I will
"Flaming hot cheese fondue" showdown
There's so much of it
So, it started!
Yamasaki-san
Moriman was all in bread crumbs
And in cheese
When he was throwing bread at Moriman, he was so sloppy
Volleyball showdown
VOLLEYBALL SHOWDOWN!!!!
"Volleyball showdown" fight
Let's start!
Volleyball match
Go, go, go!
Here it comes!
He should concentrate
The hell you're doing?
You were so close, Yamasaki san
What have you been doing? Volleyball ball is over there!
What happened?
I'M DONE!!!
What are you doing?
MORIMAN!!!
Alright, "honey battle"!
In the "honey showdown" one shall dip opponent's head
Alright, let's start!
Here it comes!
~Yamasaki! Do your Best!~
What was with that hand?
What does this hand mean?
He got covered in honey that much
I was very surprised
That was so fast
Will you be able to go on?
Yes, I can
Is it alright to rematch?
It sounds perfectly fine
Did you expect us to refuse?
When we look at your head, so much stuck to it
"Honey head-dipping match" Round 2
There is no way for him to escape
He can't see, can't see
Completely blinded
Oh, he went for a swept-back hairstyle
He looks like Bond now
Wait a moment
Listen,
How much stuff did stick to you?
Yamasaki san, are you alright?
I don't get it. I think he meant wants to stop it.
For some reason he now tried to hold onto her
What was the purpose of it?
This round someone will definitely win this match
Please give me a real match!
We've seen it before. You don't seem like you really want to do it
Understood. It's a promise
Let it be "K-1 showdown"
K-1 SHOWDOWN!
The match is in earnest now, - "K-1 showdown"
Let's commence!
Somehow Yamasaki managed to knock Moriman down. What is going to happen next?
He just fell here
However, just before he was full of excitement
Without expecting anything he was just knocked out
EVERYONE!!!!
HOW DID YOU LIKE IT???
MORIMAN!!!
TODAY WAS THE LAST MATCH!!!!
NEXT TIME!!!
NEXT MATCH!!!
His throat got tired from talking
And with that, Yamasaki ran away from the ring
Then Cocorico ran after him
Ladies and Gentlemen, I think he lost all of his strength
And that's why this time...
~Hamada-san are you alright?~
What happened to you? Did you answer wrong at the quiz show?
Did someone press a fail button?
Cocorico!
And then, 10 minutes after Yamasaki's escape, Endo returns
Will Yamasaki return back to the ring again?
Or is it the end?
Ladies and gentlemen, please listen
Yamasaki-san said in purpose of his advantage,he won't be returning
Endo, that's no good
However!
Although, he's not returning. Tanaka on Cocorico's behalf will perform before you at this New Year's Eve.
Tanaka, come in!!!