Original translation by (if you know please let me know)
Revised and colored by Yakarin.
Everyone's so excited!
QUIET!!!
Yeah, everyone's so excited!
You know, when I think about it, I seem like I'm always angry on TV.
Yeah, yeah.
I have the image of always being angry.
I'm really thinking of not getting angry anymore...
Ah, ahh!
Is that so?
Yeah, I'm thinking of that but, I bought the TV Taro the other day...
TV Taro?
You know, TV Taro.
Something like a TV guide?
Yes, it's a monthly subscription,  and it's called TV Taro.
Ok, ok.
I'll never forget, March 26th, I bought the TV Taro.
Ok, ok, the date doesn't really matter...
Well, it does.
So, what about the TV Taro?
Well, you only need to buy that once a month, right?
So, that's why I bought it on March 26th.
Then I went home, and I was reading it... I really didn't notice at first.
Ah, I see, I see...
Huh? I've seen this before...
I looked at the cover again...
It's the March issue.
So you bought the same one?
It's definitely the convenience store's fault, right?
Why?
Because the next issue of TV Taro is already out!
It comes out on the 23th!
They hadn't changed it!
And the cover of TV Taro. It's always some portrait of a Hollywood star going like this...
One doesn't really notice the changes every month.
When you see it on the shelves, you think it's the right one! You think: it has to be the April issue!
I bought the TV Taro just for 3 days!
Absurd, isn't it!?
However, that was your mistake, right...?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
Because you don't agree with me, I get more pissed off!
Well, it's your fault for not checking, right?
It's completely the store's fault!
Why is it looking like I'm wrong or something?
You could have just checked to see...
No, no, no, no...
Hamada-san...
It's the end of March and you see the TV Taro on the shelves...
You don't bother to check!
Well, if you thought the store was wrong, why didn't you just go back and return it?
Who goes back to the store at 5:00am in the morning?
Just go back the next day then!
The next day!
But...
If you thought they were wrong.
You go for me... I'm too tired for that...
In the old days, I would of, I would of went back and said: GAAAAAA!
I'm too old for that!
I don't have the energy anymore...
Look, I went to McDonald's the other day.
Because the meat was missing.
Huh?
Bread, bread, beef, bread.
Oh, it's supposed to be...
What kind of food are you eating anyway??
Well, don't you eat McDonald's?
What kind of burger?
The one that's double.
Double...
You're so young!!
You're eating that kind of stuff at this age?
No, no, my wife got it for the kids, and I heard.
"What is this??"
So I got up and looked...
It was bread, bread, meet, bread.
Bread, bread... ahh... I see, you're right.
I asked her and she said she just bought it so...
I thought: "that's interesting"... I said "Give it to me"
I wrapped it back, changed my pajama...
took the receipt and drove the car.
Ok...ok...
So, the people in the store were like: "Ah, it's Hamada"?
I just barged in with the burger, so no one tried to come close to me.
I guess they probably knew I was pissed off.
They probably saw fumes coming out of your head...
I thought I went in the store normally, but my face was probably like this...
So young!
They said "Yes?"
Ah, it had to be just some part-time employee, right?
So I said "Could you get the manager, please?"
No, no, no, no. I'm not wrong, right?
Probably in the back they were saying...
"Manager, there's a gorilla in the store".
Not a gorilla!
Not a gorilla, I was just standing like this.
And the manager comes and says "How can I help you?"
So I asked "Are you the manager?"
I swear you didn't speak that nicely!
"Are you the manager?", he says "Yes" so,
I said "I bought this earlier but..."
"...could you tell me if this is correct or incorrect?"
What kind of question is that??
Just in case, right?
He says "Huh?" opens it and notices...
"Ahhhhhhh!!..."
Yeah...
"We're sorry"
"Well, which is it, correct or incorrect?"
That's enough! Show mercy on him, he said "sorry"!
Well, I want to hear it.
"It's... incorrect"...
You made him say "It's incorrect"
I replied "That's right, right?"
I have the receipt here, I just bought it.
Oh really... and  then?
"Bye"... and I left.
No, wait, wait. You got a new one, right?
They insisted but I said "No thanks". And just went home.
I just wanted to tell them that.
That "You're wrong!"
Such an evil personality...
Why? They might make the same mistake with another person, right?
Refusing the new sandwich is... It's just nasty...
"Yeah!!"
Wait, wait, what do you mean by "Yeah!"??
You wanted them to owe you, so that you can demand stuff later, right?
What kind... What kind of stuff??
Something... like.... mmmm... small fries....
That's why...