This is a recap from part 1, skip to 2:16 for new content
You haven't watch part one yet? You can find it @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Special talent demonstration meeting - let's raise our views!
Last week, they all tried to raise the ratings by showing their yet-unseen special skills
"TANAKA - BLOWPIPE WHILE RIDING A BALL"
(watch part 1 for subs @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com)
"FUJIMOTO - BLAST WAVE PLASTIC BOTTLE KNOCK DOWN"
While Tanaka and Fujimoto had success...
"INOMOTO - FREE KICK WATER BOTTLE KNOCK DOWN"
"ENDO - 100% FULL SCORE SINGING AT KARAOKE"
"MIYASAKO - PERFECT NUNCHAKU"
The next 3 challengers fail their job
Will the remaining contestants be able to overcome this and raise the views?!
Simpler-than-usual subs & translation by Shion
Like my page:  fb.com/shionnotsukai
More j-comedy @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
▀
Subbing takes time & effort.
if you want to show your support,
please consider donating few dollars:
- on ko-fi @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
- or patreon @ patreon.com/shionnotsukai
(thanks to all donors <3)
WATCH PART 1 FIRST ON SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
THIS EPISODE IS ACTUALLY PART 2 OF A PREVIOUS EPISODE!
☠
Will the remaining contestants be able to overcome this and raise the views?!
Here's our next special skill
That's the turning point
"Creamy facial-cleanser foam"
The hell is this?
What's that?
- So sudden...
Maybe our world view is different
Who's this?
Here
Hosshan?
I can make a creamy foam with soap for face, without instruments
It'll be creamier than you're thinking, for real
So creamy it could be used for CMs
I could even flip it and it wouldn't fall
- I see
That's right
But you don't make foam with it
Do you use it without foam?
And that explains your skin
- First you make foam...
And then you use it
That was brutal
Hosshan is aggressive today
But why?
You'll get how amazing it is once you'll see it
Go to the challenge room
- Ok
What's amazing about it?
I didn't get this
We're counting on you!
We're expecting a lot
I don't know how much this can be related to view-raising
Maybe our female audience will like it...
It's time for Hosshan's creamy soap foam, which mainly targets ladies
What will it be about?
Is that all you need?
Yeah, this is enough for something great
No idea how this will end
Here's Hosshan view-raising attempt!
We don't need this, don't we
- Yeah, we don't
VIEW-RAISING: START
It's not worth our time
He used a lot of it
He wet his hands,
took some cream...
What's this?
What is...?
What is he doing?
Why do we have to watch this?
Is this going to actually raise our views...?
Maybe when he's done...
- If he succeeds maybe they'll raise
He's making a lot of foam
- Is it working?
What is this person doing everyday?
Our views won't raise
His face is so focused
I mean, you don't need to be an expert for this
Here goes
Look!
Of course it does it
Isn't it obvious?
That's like a praying mantis egg
Normally it would fall
It was a success, why are you gaving me that?
.
- "Gaving"?
I wanted something which would have made me go "woah"
That's right
And a standing ovation
- Yeah...
Isn't it impressive? With only these tools...
Not really...
- He's complaining a lot
This show has become "old dudes grunting around" by now
Old dudes complaint show
Our views won't raise like this
This week is bad
- Oh, he's back
He looks so pissed off
Look at his face!
- He's really angry
I did it properly, why does it have to be like this?
I mean, we should start discussing about this
You should know this
Your face is becoming just like a Wagen
Your face really looks like a Volkswagen right now
Absurdly enough, 5 between the 7 contestants failed their challenge
note: Hosei's footage has been cut away from the final edit of both episodes
Will they be able to fix this course of events?
Man, this isn't going well
- Let's go
It's an old story by now
Success is an old story
Here's our next special skill:
"Karate chop bre--
Bric-- brea--- br---"
You couldn't say a word of it!
I somehow felt like this wouldn't go well
I meant "brick break"
You haven't been speaking properly since a long time by now
You're losing your focus
Who's this?
That's me
Oh, Fujiwara?
- I figured it
And how many bricks..?
10 tiles
For real?
- Yeah
My partner couldn't make it, so I have to do this
Makes sense
- I see...
I'll change this atmasp--- atmosphere
- Huh?!
Those who haven't stuttered yet, please raise your hand
I haven't
- I haven't yet
You're such a liar! You stuttered like crazy
What's this?
It's like this because we keep on failing
Must be its bad influence
- Countin' on you, Fujiwara!
I'm changing this flow! Here I go!
Amazing!      - Go for it!
- Break em all!
In order to stop this horrible slope and raise the views...
Fujiwara faces his karate chop bricks break, with 10 tiles
If from now on every challenge goes well, our success rate will be over 50%
From now on failure won't be an option
Looks like he's ready, let's call him: Fujiwara!
Yes
That's a lot
- Impressive...
With a chop, right?
Let's go
- Go for it!
Here's Fujiwara view-raising attempt!
You can do it
Go for it
- Please do it
VIEW-RAISING: START
Please do it
Holy cow!
That's the good stuff
Wonderful
That's what I wanted to see
Great job!
- That was incredible
He made it look so easy
Really
He broke em so cleanly
Amazing
That was good
- So cool
It went well
Finally
- We're back at it
They'll definitely raise with this
We have to fix this
- Yes, we're done failing now
Let's keep this pace
Yes
Let's go then, here's our next special skill:
I beg you...
"Golf magazine scent guess"
- What the-?
Looks like we're back to crap...
Who's this?
It's me
What's this?
Well, you know...
I really like golf, so...
I read so many golf magazines that I can guess which one is it just by its scent
Isn't it weird that's the skill you developed instead of being good at golf?
I mean, it's about golf...
- Yeah but golf is hard
Then why are you reading those magazines?
- No, I mean...
Because I want to become good at it, I'm just an amateur
And yet you learned how they smell?
For real?
How many magazines?
Today I'll guess between 5...
5?
- Yeah
If he guesses it I'd be amazed
Yeah and only by smelling it
Hotohara, confident about his olfaction
Will try to guess the correct golf magazine
How much will he be able to raise the views?
He got a national certification for
"handling poisonous and deleterious substances"
And for that, you have to do a test
In which there are many elements like ammonia
And you have to guess a certain right element
between a large number of others, just by smelling it
That's incredible
- He got that
Looks like he's ready, Hoto-chan?
I'm ready
So, how are you gonna do it?
Let's see
- Yes
"GOLF DIGEST"
"PAR-GOLF"
As you can see there are 5 magazines
I'll now put on a blindfold
"GOLF TODAY"
"ALBA"
"GOLF STYLE"
And I'm going to guess it just by smelling it
Is someone going to pass them to you?
- Yes, Nakamura is in charge
Which is the one you like the most?
Woah, it's difficult...
Let's move on then
Here's Hoto-chan attempt to raise our views!
I want him to get them all
VIEW-RAISING: START
So, which will be the first one?
Ah, he's shuffling them
And now they're all mixed up
No way he'll get this
- I think so too
But maybe they actually smell different
I see
Alright
That much?
Like that?
- Is he for real?
I think...
Another page, please?
I think our views-per-minute are going down
I hope he'll get it right
- Yeah, that's it
I got this
Really? Can he make it?
May I?
Sure
It's "Par-golf"!
"GOLF DIGEST"
He got that wrong
WRONG ANSWER
The signboard fell down
It fell as soon as he answered
You got that wrong and as soon as that happened, the signboard behind us fell
Get back here Hotohara
Yes, here I come
I'm hating this
I'm coming back
Good reaction at least
Here I am
This place is becoming haunted
That was incredible
- It really was
"Par-golf" and it went "crack", then the buzzer
I think everyone already changed channel
And that's why this thing fell down
Here's our next special skill:
Please...
- Please be good
"Blindfolded folding chair sitting"
Huh? What's that about?
What's this?
Sounds dangerous...
- Who's this?
That's me
Yes
What's this?
What is...?
I'll wear a blindfold and have the staff place a folding chair somewhere
It will make a sound as it's placed
And that's where I'll sit
It could be good if he actually does it
Is there any proof you can actually do that?
Mh?
Something that proves it---
Is there really someone who could answer that question?
He didn't hear me
But you never actually tried doing this, isn't that right?
Well, yeah
I'll show you that I can
It'd be amazing if you can
But really, wouldn't it be the best one yet?
An incredible skill which will surely raise the views, if done well
Haranishi is ready to face the blindfolded folding-chair sitting
He's ready by now, let's call him: Haranishi?
Yes
Show us the studio before you start
- I see
- Pretty big
There are tons of obstacles!
- Looks dangerous
Are you sure?
To be sure I don't know where it'll be...
- Yes?
This person here...
"This person"?
- But that's Nakamura
He doesn't know him much
I'll rely on sounds so please let me focus
He's right
- Alright, we got it
We'll be quiet
Here's Haranishi's view-raising attempt
Maybe he measured it
With a ruler or such
VIEW-RAISING: START
I hope he can make it
So fast!
What the hell!
What the hell, dude!
What was that?
You idiot!
His direction was spot on though
Of course you'd get the direction right
Everyone could get that right, at least
It was my first time, I couldn't know I'd hit the side
I should have put protectors on
He went so fast
For a moment I thought you could do it
It didn't seem like he was ready to sit down
He kept on moving forward
I wanna see it again
We can't raise our views at all...
Now it's all up to you two guys
- He's right, we're counting on you
Let's go then, here's our next special skill:
I wonder which is it?
"Stout arm rope climbing"
Is it one of you guys?
That would be me
Yeah, it's not me
Long story short, I'll climb up a rope by only using my arms
Like this?
- Oh, amazing
It's 6 meters
Ehh?!
- What?!
I see
6 meters is pretty high, isn't it
You have to do this, man
Give it your best!
After all he's being working out a lot, recently
- That's right, he is
- Yeah
I actually tried it once
It's fine until you're halfway through it
- That's when things get hard
I can do like 3 or 4 meters but
But after that my arms start hurting and if I let go of one, I can't get any higher
You just have to do it in one shot
It's over once you stop
Now I get this atmosphere
As failed attempts pile up, Matsumoto will face the 6 meters rope climbing
Will he succeed and raise the views per minute?
Looks like he's ready, so let's call him: Matsumoto-san?
It's pretty high
Is it? Please show us the studio
I see
So high!
Only with your arms?
Yes
Impressive
This will raise our views if it goes well
It's pretty high
As failed attempts piles up, Matsumoto will face the 6 meters rope climbing
Only with your arms?
- Yes
Impressive
This will raise our views if it goes well
Here's Matsumoto view-raising attempt
Will he be fine?
Start!
VIEW-RAISING: START
Amazing!
Incredible!
- Woah!
Keep on going!
- Incredible!
Incredible!!
It was a piece of cake for him!
Amazing!
Wonderful
He made it look so easy!
We did it!
Really impressive
Why everyone is cheering so much but no one stood up?
- 'Cause he was so calm about it!
I see, I see
Matsumoto-san
It was a success
Huh? Who are you, Rola?
Why that Rola pose?
- Why?
There's no need to do that, you know
Thanks!
Great job
That was good
- So good!
You think I'm ready to go to "SASUKE"?
note: japanese version of tv show "Ninja Warrior"
- No way
That's too much
That thing is in the final stage
Adult! Cool!
- You know there are three stages? That's just part of the last one
And here we are
Only Hamada is left
Yeah
- I don't know what he's going to do
Let's see then, here's our next special skill
"No-damage slap"
What's that?
It'll only make sound
I'll slap you and it won't hurt you at all
Of course it will make sound
But you'll be like "Huh? Did I get slapped?"
The aim is unclear...
It feels like a huge raincloud suddenly came through
It's totally fine
But who's gonna get slapped...?
Anyone's good
Yeah but...
- No way, no way...
Don't worry, I'll be waiting
Huh? Waiting? You're going?
Yeah, in the challenge room, anyone's fine, so...
Alright then, come, Tanaka!
It won't hurt at all, it'll be fine!
By "it won't hurt" he means
That there won't be "sadness" or "anger" in it
- You have to try it to get it
Go find that out for us
- You have to do it
Are you kidding me?
There's the risk it may hurt
So it's a damage-slap?
I don't want that
But he said it's a no-damage slap
You'll be fine
I really don't know...
- I mean, he said that--
He's reacting as if he invited him to a public bath
I bet it'll hurt
Poor Tanaka
After the ball-riding success this was probably the best day of his life...
You're right, he really surprised us before
To be slapped after his best spotlight...
Hamada will show us his no-damage slap, which can't hurt
Will he keep the views high with this special skill?
Looks like he's ready, so let's call him
Hamada-san?
He's so scary
The way he's moving his neck...
I've been waiting here for so long, geez
He's pissed off...
- He looks angry, I think he'll hurt him
It looks like he's wearing a collar
Everyone would have been fine but I passed by him, so here's Tanaka
"Passed by"...?
He's so pale!
He's becoming a noble
You'll only hear a loud sound
But he won't be hurt
Alright, whenever you're ready
Ok, here's Hamada's attempt to raise our views!
VIEW-RAISING: START
You sure there's no damage?
He's becoming red
He left a mark
Tanaka?
Any damage?
No damage
You liar!!
We're not buying that, Tanaka
I swear it's true
Are you forcing him to say so?
No, I'm not
Come on, who's next?
- There's no need for that...
It won't hurt you a bit, right, Tanaka?
It didn't hurt at all
Choose the next one, Tanaka
What do you mean?
Does he have to say it?
You're doubting me, so I want you to believe it
Just ask Tanaka, he'll say it was just a sound
Was it really no-damage?
Yeah, it doesn't hurt
Your cheek became so red!
I can see three fingers there
Those are definitely fingers
Really?
But I swear, it wasn't painful at all
Are you doubting him?
We're not doubting him
- Not really...
Let's call it a day
What are we gonna do?
Who's coming here? Matsumoto? Miyasako? Which one of them?
- "Which one"?!
No way I'm going
You see...
- But it really is no-damage!
This year...
Is going to be the 30th anniversary of Downtown
I see, I see...
No way I'm getting a slap from my partner as a gift
AFTER THIS - HAMADA WILL SLAP MATSUMOTO!?
Who has been the worst one between us today?
Are we going with majority vote?
- We are
I hit that red bean, you know
I think there's more than one
How about we all choose one in order?
- Ok
Who should I choose?
There have been a lot...
So, who sucked the most between us?
The smell thingy
Well but, I only tried once and failed, so...
Miyasako's nunchaku
Yeah, that one...
I didn't like Miyasako's attitude too
I see
But I hit that red bean--
I think the nunchaku
3 points
Miyasako-san?
I hit that goddamn red bean
Foam
Oh, that one too
- I almost forgot that
Matsumoto-san?
Probably smell-guess
That one, huh...
I'm not surprised
Yamazaki?
- Foam
Poor guy
Endo?
- I'd say...
Smell
Tanaka?
I'm sorry, foam
Now they're all even
What an amazing fight
- They all scored three points
It's all up to License now
I'll vote...
Nunchaku
Now it's all up to you, Fujiwara
But I hit that red bean...
Nunchaku
Miyasako, who failed his perfect nunchaku,
Will be the one to face the no-damage slap!!
It's just sound
It'll be like "wham!", but there won't be any damage
But I hit that red bean...
There's no need to be worried
- Right
I hit that red bean
AZUKI - DIAMETER 7mm
The red bean
Can you hit it?
Well, I did
This feels so strange and hard to believe...
Miyasako has arrived
So you were chosen, huh?
Even though I hit that red bean
Again?
- He's still saying it
I'm ready anytime
But wait, Miyasako is focusing right now
Does he need to?
In a way he needs to focus
Red bean again?
But I hit that red bean
Here's Hamada's view-raising attempt: start!
He's laughing
I hit that...
It will be fine
VIEW-RAISING: START
It's just sound
The red bean...
Huh? What happened?
There wasn't much sound
That was an old lady beating a carpet
Miyasako-kun
Was it no-damage?
I hit that goddamn red bean...
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
WEBSITE
FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
LIKE IT
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
DONATIONS
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SPECIAL THANKS TO ALL MY KO-FI & PATREON DONORS:
♥ THANK YOU SO MUCH!! ♥
(it means a lot!)