Murakami Shoji's classroom series started without anyone wanting it
In addition to the low ratings every time
The guest star took over the lead role
What will await us today?
Matsumoto san, the hell's that?
You see, today
Well
I don't know if I like it or not
Shoji san's
We've had enough already...
Not again
We had enough of it...
I heard that there was a lot of discussions going on
Deciding it to be Dracula Class
Why are we doing Dracula in the middle of the day?
Well, today is a rare occasion of a good weather
That's right
With this guy's bad luck...
He was very particular about the location this time
Really?
If there's a field, a lawn, or a loophole...
That really doesn't matter
For us, there are fields and open spaces
It would be great if it got lost in there somewhere
You can't swallow with this thing
How Dracula even lives like that?
Today's weather is great
The sun shines so bright
If I play Dracula today, I'll just vanish
It's like
Dracula's leisure
What a beautiful sight
Wouldn't he normally die?
If he'd been a real Dracula
He would have absolutely died
He's so white
Like like a wall paint
Is that really Dracula?
You're face is so pale... Good morning!
The kite is quite high up
He's quite skillful
What are you doing?
That's a kite, right?
I...I didn't know where should we meet
The person who forgot the meeting place was Murakami Shoji
You look so bright
You look like you're terribly backlit
You're so off
Well today...
I told my manager that it's too sunny today
But I was made to
Even if it's sunny, you'll do it
That's what my manager told me
My boss
I'll have to do it
It's so tough...
That sounds scary...
We don't have time to discuss that
We're doing Dracula Class today
My teeth still don't fit in
I need to ask my doctor Fukada
To fix the last ones
I have only temporary teeth now
I can't bite my wife's shoulder properly
Bite her shoulder?
Yes, when I try to do it
We see
I can't bite it well
So you can't her shoulder well?
This time, I've added gameplay element
That's right
Hama chan, you say
"When big brother comes, our ratings plunge" and
"He's scary" and
"I came all the way there last week"
I hear that too often
First, Dracula's basics
Learning how to suck blood
How many cc did I suck in!?
Without further ado, let's start
Our first game!
Murakami san, please!
Yes!
First of all
He's that kind of guy...
What's that?
That's something very different...
That's part of our game
You see the red substance?
What do you think is that?
Isn't it a tomato juice?
You're spot on
This blood
You should calculate
how many cc there
by your own intuition
That's too difficult!
That's too tough!
I don't get it...
Understand?
Zero
Ma-chan
Please
96 cc
That's quite high...
Start!
Use your intuition!
Make it 96 cc
Isn't it too long?
How was it?
I think I did it
92 cc!
Amazing!
If this goes this way, you'll be an honors student
Thank you very much!
I've never seen anyone drink so close on the first try before
Let's continue
Yamasaki, try it
Do your best!
Do it good as well
Yama chan do your...
What?
Drink 1 liter of it
Do it, Yama chan
Wait a minute
Drink it, drink it
But that's different from before
Shouldn't we identify cc woth our intuition?
You again...
Your sister said the same thing
When she wanted to become Dracula...
You, like the guy who works part-time at the convenience store around the corner
You and your family...
You all can't measure
Drink as much, as I tell you
I understand
Drink it, drink it, Yama chan! 1liter
Do your best!
He goes for it!
Vacuum it all out of the glass
Don't stop
Go for it!
Yama chan, drink it all!
Do it well!
Go for it! You're amazing!
He made no progress...
Wait a moment, I can't drink that much...
Ah, thank you very much...
He's so gentle...
Yama chan, what was that?
But I've managed to drink this much
Listen
If you visit once
most prestigious restaurant in Ginza
You're that type who'd never go there again
What are you talking about?
Your teeth fell off
Are you alright?
I'll take them off for now
Really, when I wear them
When I wear them for too long, they wear out
I can't wear them
And nothing funny comes to mind
Then take it off
To suck the human blood
It is important to know certain approaches
In the village
when Dracula appears
Well, you know the rest
That's
pretty well-known
That's why
In the meantime, we have villagers inside their houses
Whom we need to lure out, or make them let us in
This time
We will practice this process
Ma-chan
Can you do a housewife? A housewife? Fine
We need to add one thing
Put this on
You're a housewife
Your two kids
went outside
And your husband
Is on a business trip
And Dracula comes here
Don't open the door! It's so late...
Yes?
Excuse me, Miss
Who's that?
You see...
I've just recently moved in
My name's Takamiya
Takamiya san?
Actually, I went fishing the other day
I fried lots of mackerel and decided to give it to my neighbors
Yes
I brought some with me
A mackerel?
We're fine, we don't really need it. I'm sorry, thank you very much
Wait!
Please wait a moment
In addition to mackerel
I've brought seasonal baby squid
With all these sea food
We really don't need any
No need to worry about us
Miss, wait a moment
Can I borrow some gas?
No, please wait, Miss
Wait a moment
Can you lend it to me?
What is it?
Well, you see
That thing started today...
Listen...
Excuse me, could you open the door?
That means, we're done here
Even the ship says that it's over
Yamasaki took the role of Dracula
How will it go?
Listen
Make me open the door
I need to make you let me in?
That's right
That's difficult
Any help is fine
I understand
This time, the housewife doesn't care about any celebrities
I just want to make her open
It's cold...
Excuse me!
I'm sorry!
Please, listen, I'm about to be attacked, please open the door!
I'm sorry, but I'm now
I'm also about to be attacked
He absolutely failed
No way!
Please!
No, please listen
Excuse me
Yes!
Yamasaki
If you'll keep doing it like that, you're going to scare the hell out of the people inside
That's why you should have
made the housewife go "What?" just if a celebrity came here
You want me to say that?
Just if you were a celebrity
Alright, this time she is a big fan of Kenichi Mikawa (1960's transgender enka singer)
I see
That's why
Make her open that door
I understand
My husband is quite late...
Good eveing
Who is that?
It's Mikawa
Mikawa who?
It's Mikawa Kenichi
What?
Miss?
Shogo Hamada san didn't come? (late 1970's rock singer)
Good evening
It's Hamada Shogo
Miss?
What was that?
I think he's nervous
He really tries he's best
Yama chan, that was unfortunate
Although, you tried hard
Watch and learn a bit more from other people
Endo, try next
Me?
Try doing it
You should already know so far all the good and bad points
But you would
Absolutely not open it
I have no ideas
Find a way
Will the housewife open?
Well
My husband is quite late
Darling?
Have you returned?
Are you back?
That's completely different!
Isn't he a Dracula?
He opened it straight away...
The next is
Quick push quiz corner!!
The quiz is the best way to get high ratings right now
That's right
With ratings in mind
Let's learn some Dracula trivia
Question 1
Dracula was modeled on a real-life European aristocrat
But what country did he come from?
Yama chan? Engalnd!
Tanaka kun? Romania!
Amazing!
I knew it!
Let's go
Dracula has shed a tear once
When did that happen?
Come on
Well, I think...
It was when...
When a cross was shown to him
When he was sprayed with holy water?
Time's up
He cried?
When his little sister was hit by a trailer
Is that really true?
He was shocked
When trailer hit?
Yes... Next question!
One time, Dracula laughed really hard
When did that happen?
When did it happen?
When he was pissed off of the bloodsucking
I see...
When he laughed a lot?
Yes?
When he couldn't suck out any blood at all
That's quite hilarious
I wonder if that's possible...
Here's the answer
When he asked for miso soup, but got ordinary soup
That's impossible
Is that for real?
That's absolutely true!
Of course he had funny incidents
He was like "The hell's that?"
Next one
Next up is
Mistake-finding quiz!!
Spot a mistake
I'll be doing it
Alright?
I will be going from behind this curtain
To the one over there
While I'm running
Find something off
We see
And after that, give me your answers
Tell me what was wrong
I'll prepare a few things right away, okay?
That's quite a distance...
Wait a moment
How many time will you run?
I can't tell you that
So, remember, please
That's a huge distance...
Aiming to further improve knowledge skills
They are challenged to find mistakes
We're ready. Here I come!
Start!
The hell's that?
Did you get it?
Can you run one more time?
Did you spot anything?
Fine
Yes, please!
Start!
He's like running for his life
I wonder, where's a mistake? I can't see anything...
I don't know
I can't really tell...
He's done
You're so fast today!
With your running
You were too fast, we couldn't spot anything
Did you spot any?
Did you?
I think your collar was out of place
That's probably it
My collar's the same
Collar is the same
Really?
You removed your suspenders?
That must be it!
Are you joking?
The hint is the sound
From the lower half of the body
What?
Can't you run one more time? We didn't catch anything at all
Lower half?
Here I go
Once more, please!
Run in this direction!
Dash, dash!
Go, go!
I know!
I know! Matsumoto san?
You're without socks?
I see!
You don't wear any, right?
We don't see any socks
That's true
What are you doing?
There's so much went out
You've got such a running nose!
It's geta (shoes)
Really?
Do you get it?
I'll go for the last one
Number two
Mistake-search question 2
The Count with a dashing appearance
Where's a mistake?
What's off?
I have no clue...
You wear shoes?
He really does
He definitely changed his footwear
Buu...
What do you mean?
I carry it
There's no such thing as a lack of luck
Or competency
You really have none of it
Really
You really have nothing of it
CAN'T YOU JUST SHUT UP???
SHUT UP!!!
Let's rest
Let's have a break
I knew we'd be hungry
Such meal?
That's peperoncino with garlic
What a great meat smell!
Sorry
Thanks for the meal
The hell you're eating garlic?
You can't eat garlic
No, but the Count...
What are you eating?
Peperoncino
Do you impose that I'm selficino?
You think so?
What do you think Yama chan
Our events are a bit too long?
That's right
When you've mentioned it
They could be shorter
I've already said this at the meeting too
We don't need such long ones now
There's five of them after all
I don't know what their reaction will be
You know...
And there's four of us here
A scriptwriter
And a director
There are things that I want to say, but can't
That's what I mean
And they also want to leave
How many other classroom ideas do you have?
Well, I bring a lot of stuff
For classes
I'm thinking about 30 more
That's impressive... Really?
Shoji san, do you have any new planned?
Ninja Class, part 2
You want us to do it again?
The Green Beret
We've done that already
No, but that's part 2 as well
Who's idea was with peperoncino?
Peperoncino...
I'm selficino...
As selfish
That's
Me...
He really used it
Just as I thought
The final step
In getting a sweet blood
Here
Come closer
That's great!
All of Dracula's hated things
You've trained really hard
These are Dracula's least favorite things
Makizappa (newspaper sword)
That's what he hates the most
Shouldn't be a cross? No, he really hates when his head's hit with it
Holy water
You see
The villagers are getting stronger
They're already coming after us as a group
One needs to go through many obstacles
to return back into one's coffin
Escape for the attack
That's the most vital training for survival!
Let me explain
Escape to the coffin from the attacking villagers
Smash through the wall of cans and go under the net
And finally get inside
Once you're inside, close the lid
With that
Meaning you're safe
Let's do it
Hama chan?
Try it
Hama chan
Hama chan, please
Shall I take that?
This look good
That will be painful
I don't really know how shall it be done...
Can't show me an example?
He's right
And then I'll do it
Okay
Watch carefully!
Yes
I'm sorry. Don't sweat it
Will you wear it?
Yes, I will
Hama chan, I've got several of these
I understand
Yes
If you'll need one. I understand
Then, we're all villagers
Wait a moment
I'll run up to you
Here I go!
Destroy him with garlic
Get ready!
Go!
NOW, NOW!!!
GET THAT, DRACULA!
GET THAT!
it hurts... GO AWAY!!
DRACULA GET LOST!!!
YOU BASTARD!
DON'T EVER COME BACK!!!
CLOSE IT!
YOU BASTARD!
Serves him right
Alright!
He's done for good
We've done it
Let's head home
Yes
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW HOLY WATER IS SPELLED!!!
COLD WATER, COLD WATER
IT'S NOT WRITTEN AS A COLD WATER, YOU IDIOTS!!!