Translated and subbed by: Venomghast/Highlander1536/Hashiru
16:11, START!!
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Well then, without further ado, let's get started.
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Yamazaki Hosei
Hamada Masatoshi
Cocorico: Endo Shozo
Who are you?
Let's find out more about Tanaka today.
What a sweet voice.
Quiz: 500 things about Tanaka. First question.
What are Tanaka's hobbies?
Hobbies?
What can it be?
Ah, that one.
That went fast.
Are you done everyone?
Yes.
Ah, that one.
I didn't know at all.
Let's see your answers.
Watching Movies
Videos of Animals
VC Figures
Watching Animals
It might be Hosei-san's answer.
But Hamada is completely wrong.
Let's announce the right answer.
I didn't know at all.
What are Tanaka's hobbies?
Hobbies?
Watching movies.
Yeah.
Amazing.
He likes animals...
Correct answer was: watching movies.
Ah, so it was watching movies...
Yes.
Only 499 left.
Question number two.
What is Tanaka's astrological sign?
Eh?!
I have no idea.
This one maybe.
Are you done everyone?
Let's see your answers.
Taurus
Pisces
Endo
Hamada
Matsumoto
Yamazaki
Let's announce the right answer.
What is your astrological sign?
Say it faster!
Taurus.
So he is a taurus.
Correct answer was: Taurus.
Hey, you were right.
Amazing.
I am probably the one knowing most about Tanaka.
He knows that the answer is Taurus so he should just say it faster.
Yeah, he should.
It's really hot in here.
Yeah.
Lets us just continue.
Tanaka can't hear anything we say in here.
Really?
Question number three.
What is Tanaka's blood type?
Ah, this is easy.
Are you done everyone?
Let's see your answers.
O-type
Let's announce the right answer.
Say it fast this time.
What is your blood type?
It's O-type.
What the hell?!
Say it faster.
Correct answer was: O-type.
My first correct answer.
What is Tanaka's favorite kind of nabe?
What does he mean?
What?
Kind of nabe?
Anything is fine as long it's a kind of nabe.
I didn't understand.
Are you done everyone?
That's wrong.
Ah, that's what he meant?!
The taste, right?
Let's see your answers.
Simple Water Cooked Style
A Pressure Cooker
(They were laughing at Matsumoto because he mistook it as
what kind of pot instead of what style of hot pot cooking did Tanaka like.)
Pressure cooking nabe?
Shabu Shabu
Korean Style Jigae Nabe
Let's announce the right answer.
What is your favorite kind of nabe?
Sukiyaki.
Everybody was wrong.
When was Tanaka's first love?
First love?
Let's see your answers.
15 years old
Fifth grade
Second grade
19 years old
Let's announce the right answer.
Third grade of elementary school.
Ah!
Correct answer was: Third grade of elementary school.
What was the name of Tanaka's first love?
How should we know that?
Let's see your answers.
Miki
Midori
Shigeno (last name)
Let's announce the right answer.
Ogawa Natsuko-san.
It's almost the same name as Hamada's wife.
There is only one hiragana difference.
Amazing.
What do you like about your partner?
Eh? Me? Does he mean me?
What can it be?
Let's see your answers.
Haircut
Sensitiveness to others
Honest
Gets on with others (friendly)
Haircut
Sensitiveness to others
Let's announce the right answer.
Good with other people.
It's obvious that you are right. It makes me feel sick.
He only looks straight ahead.
This makes me feel disgusted.
What is Tanaka's favorite story?
Eh, that one...
Let's see your answers.
Hanasaka Jiisan
The one with the axe
Kintaro
Let's announce the right answer.
Shitakirisuzume.
What is Tanaka's favorite animal?
(Narrator says in order to know Tanaka there were two important answers.
First one is his favorite animal is a Rhino. The second one is he liked 8th grade a lot.)
Rhino.
If Tanaka would be able to go back in time, when would he go back to?
Second year of middle school (8th grade).
That was fast.
Correct answer was: Second year of middle school.
Spot on.
Something must have happened during that time.
Weren't they in the same class?
How disgusting.
They must have gotten close then.
If Tanaka could go drinking with one of the following:
Matsumoto, Hamada, Yamazaki, Endo, who would it be?
Let's see your answers.
Yamazaki
Matsumoto
Yamazaki-san
Let's announce the right answer.
Matsumoto-san.
You were right.
I didn't feel good after I told Yamazaki about this.
Who do you think is the filthiest out of the four others?
Does he mean us four?
Yes.
Let's see your answers.
Endo-kun
Hamada
Me
Let's announce the right answer.
Who do you think is the filthiest out of the four others?
Yamazaki-san.
He answered directly.
That was fast.
Everybody was wrong.
That was the fastest answer he has given us during the whole quiz.
Who do you think is the most malicious out of the four?
This is absolutely me.
This is unexpectedly hard.
Let's see your answers.
Endo-kun
Yamazaki
Me
Hamada-san
Let's announce the right answer.
Who do you think is the most malicious out of the four?
Matsumoto-san.
Everybody was wrong.
It's impossible for me to be the most malicious.
Why?
That's what Tanaka thinks.
I am pure, pure, pure boy.
How many floors does Tanaka's house have?
Let's see your answers.
Let's announce the right answer.
Three.
(Around here they start copying Endo by making faces when the camera zooms
and the banter is usually "that looks forced!" or "you are trying too hard!".)
Who has Tanaka been talking a lot too recently over the phone?
Let's see your answers.
Wife
Ronbu Ryou
Manager
Wife
Let's announce the right answer.
Who have I been talking a lot to recently?
Manager.
Which item from Doraemon would Tanaka like to have?
Let's see your answers.
Moshi-Mo Box
Small Light
Dokodemo Door
Moshi-Mo Box
Let's announce the right answer.
Moshimo Box.
You are overdoing it.
How much money does Tanaka usually have in his wallet?
Let's see your answers.
30,000 yen
70,000 yen
35,000 yen
30,000 yen
Let's announce the right answer.
Around 70,000 yen.
Aren't you overdoing it?
They have been going on for over two hours
but are only done with 200 questions. It's time for a break.
These are the results after 200 questions.
(During the break Yamazaki is asking Matsumoto questions (that they already answered) and he doesn't know the answers. Yamazaki then asks a question and Endo answers it and Yamazaki says "wow you are really into Tanaka". Endo responds by saying "Yeah, I'm pretty into Tanaka". Then the narration says after this a mircile happens to Matsumoto.)
Matsumoto-san, here I go.
What was his favorite story?
Ah, I remember.
What?
You don't remember a thing about Tanaka!
What was his favorite story?
Shitakirisuzume.
Right.
Let's continue.
What does Tanaka's wife often scold him about?
She wants me to talk more with her.
(Can't see answers)
During Tanaka's middle school time, who was his favorite comedian?
Nishikawa Norio.
(Can't see answers)
Which song does Tanaka remember best from old times?
Erimakitokage.
That's three in a row.
(Can't see answers)
I won't miss once after it has become evening.
(Apparently Matsumoto is on a 20 for 20 streak after the break.)
I feel disgusted.
You'll remember more about Tanaka.
It doesn't make me like him more.
I'm turning into Tanaka.
No that's impossible.
What town does Tanaka want to live in?
Let's see your answers.
Paris
Monaco
Los Angeles
Ishigaki Island
He really likes this place if I remember right.
Let's announce the right answer.
Futago Tamagawa.
Then move there!
You can move there next week.
After this did they get 20 questions wrong in a row and they are getting more tired after every question.
The four of them are looking more and more lifeless.
What is Tanaka's favorite type of gum?
Let's see your answers.
Plum     Plum     Plum     Plum
Let's announce the right answer.
What is your favorite type of gum?
Plum.
What animal do you think Tanaka would like to ride?
Elephant
Horse
Camel
Rhino.
Where do you think Tanaka would like to travel with his family?
(At this point the narrator says another important keyword to understanding Tanaka a little more, they are the answer to the next questions. Those were "Ishigaki Island" and "wieners".)
Ishigaki Island.
What do you think Tanaka would definitely want in his lunch box?
Wieners.
What food do you think Tanaka would use salt with?
Salt?
Let's see your answers.
Tomato
Boiled Egg
Tempura
Tomato
Let's announce the right answer.
Boiled eggs.
What food do you think Tanaka would use ketchup with?
Let's see your answers.
Omelet
Fried Potato
Rice Omelet
Let's announce the right answer.
What food would you defiantly have ketchup with?
Wieners.
When Tanaka grows old where do you think he'll want to live?
Ishigaki Island
Futagotama
Ishigaki Island.
He really likes that place.
Which class do you think Tanaka would like to meet the most?
Eighth grade
Middle school
Eighth Grade
Second year of middle school (8th grade).
(Matsumoto points out a lot of answers are "eighth grade,
Ishigaki Island, weiners" and when it comes to animals it's "rhino".)
Among Tanaka's friends, who do you think has the funniest nickname?
What kind of last question is that?
Let's see your answers.
Pakkyun
Hedoro-chan (Sludge-chan)
Kintaman (Mr. Balls)
Higenikibi
(Pimple-stache/Pimple Mustache)
Let's announce the right answer.
Hekochopin.
Good work everyone.
I will now announce who had the most correct answers.
The winner is: Endo Shozo with 123 points.
There is a nice present waiting for the winner.
Thank you very much.
The price is...
Meet Tanaka!
Meet Tanaka?
After 7 hours and 14 minutes, they are done.
Oh, Endo you did it!
I knew that you would make it.
How many questions did you answer right on?
About 120.
I thought that you would do better than that.
Let us talk more.
No, I think it's enough.
Oh, I see.