The Yamasaki Hosei "Sneaky Thief" Trial will now begin
Jury and Prosecution, enter please
Prosecutor -  Hamada Masatoshi
Chief Jury
Next, defendant Yamasaki, enter
He's messing about ...
He's already started
He's not taking this seriously
subbed by /u/senor_wristband
If you'd like to support my subs, consider donating @ ko-fi.com/buresurettosan
Any support is appreciated :)
Prosecutor Hamada, present your evidence please
Yamasaki's thieving nature, we've got a video to explain it
Please, observe
Yamasaki Hosei "Sneaky Thief" Trial
Incidents of him ignoring rules
This incident occurred when filming "Umezu Kazuo's 500 Questions", aired the other day
This is so recent
"The winner is ... Endo Shozo!"
I did it!!
That day, Endo gave the most correct answers
And his prize ... a caricature drawn by that famous manga artist
Wow! I'm really jealous
We don't even get to meet Umezu-san
Yes, only the winner was allowed to meet him
Everyone else wasn't allowed to see him even after the filming ends
"Here you go, congratulations!"
Thank you very much!
Endo was delighted by this special present just for him
However when the filming wrapped up, this incident occurred,
Please pay attention to this shocking video
While Endo was getting an autograph, behind him ...
He was loitering about
I'm really really happy about this
Yamasaki ignores the rules
This is amazing right?
Woahhh, that's amazing
Man this makes me happy
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
That's amazing
Even as the staff wrap up, Yamasaki stays there
What the hell are you doing there?
He has nothing to do with this
What the hell?
He said that sweater might look good on him
He won't leave at all
Yamasaki waits for a lapse in the conversation
As soon as the conversation ends,
These shocking words come from Yamasaki's mouth;
Sensei, can I get your autograph?
Can I get your autograph?
Not only did he meet Umezu, he even asked for an autograph!
In this moment he stole the winners prize!
How low will this man go?
Your honour, is it OK if juror Endo presents his testimony?
Come forward
I'm not sure why the judge is so nervous however
I'm sure everyone here also wanted to meet him,
But we didn't meet him
We couldn't meet him, that was the rule
You weren't allowed to meet him at all
So Yamasaki-san, what was the meaning of that?
Well what it means ...
I'm honestly, a huge fan of him
Well in that case, we could've also asked him for an autograph
But you know,
The first manga I ever read was "Makoto-chan"
I have a different affection for him
But still, you had to follow the rules
Then you should have gotten more answers
That's true
What was that, waiting for the conversation to end,
Waiting there like some advertising agency employee
Hold on a second please,
An autograph at least, it's alright isn't it?
No it isn't!
That is the problem!
Then how come during Ikko and Tanaka's thing, you didn't even approach them?
Well I couljn't joo anything-
"Couljn't joo"?
Hold on, this is,
I just asked for an autograph, and Umezu-san excitedly gave me one.
And he drew a portrait by his own will
We've brought this thing in,
What is it?
This here, look
What's that?
He even got him to draw a portrait
But still, Umezu-san was glad to do it,
He said to me "Actually, I'm the one who's glad"
Did he really say that?
Umezu-san said he was gwad I went to meet him
"Yamasaki-kun"-
He said he was "gwad"?
Yes, instead he was-
Stop acting like these are your first words
How Yamasaki's steals his new styles
One day, after filming Gaki,
"Hmmm what should I do, I'm lost"
"Hmm? What happened Zaki-san?"
"I'm thinking of what clothes I should wear for my new style,"
'But there's nothing good!"
He wracked his brain for ideas,
But he couldn't find anything that easily
But then, nearby,
"Good Morning!"
Gaki no Tsukai's #1 "Fashionable Boy", Director Takahasi had arrived
Why the hell?
"Zaki-san, what were you talking about?"
AH! THAT'S IT!
Where did you buy this? I see, this style and that style,
What shoes are those?
Yamasaki really liked his style, and asked him about every little detail
But it was a totally different image to Yamasaki's usual look
"But Zaki-san, are you sure this kind of look will suit you?"
"It's fine! I'm just checking it out anyways"
And with that, the day ended
And then a week later...
"Good Morning~"
Yamasaki showed up in exactly the same style as Takahashi did last week
"Hello, I am the reborn Yamasaki"
He stole every bit of Takahashi's style, and bought the exact same clothes
It's been said Takahashi threw away those clothes...
Was it really exactly the same?
I have proof here
Really?
We can see how similiar they looked,
First, this is Director Takahashi
This here
He does dress like that normally
Yes, we've seen him like this often
Now pay attention here,
Next,
Just 1 week later
No way...
I'm kind of scared now
This here,
This is unacceptable!
You can't do that!
There's a limit to "inspiration"!
It's just the shoes!
Yes
He's wearing the same shoes he always wears
He actually wanted the shoes as well
It's exactly the same!
The other thing is, it's not just at Gaki's studio,
So he's wearing this to other shoots
And when he comes to this show, Takahashi is there too
Exactly, like they said in the video,
He hasn't worn those clothes since!
Not since!
Two people on set in the same outfit, that's embarassing isn't it?
And in fact one of them is a celebrity!
Takahashi has no choice but to change
That's really bad of him!
What were you thinking?
What did I do wrong here?
This is wrong of course!
It's creepy isn't it
Incidentally, how long after that did you buy these clothes?
Well the next day, I was in Shinjiku, coincidentally!
Was it really? Was it really coincidental?
No it really was for work, I had to go to Lumine
And also, the fragrance
He thought that Takahashi smelled nice,
He brought his nose up close and said "man, you smell nice"
"You're using some cologne aren't you?"
And the defendant bought the same cologne! He went as far as to copy his smell!
Unfortunately however, that nice smell was coming the fabric softener!
It was just the laundry smell
I see
Just from washing the clothes?
He just went "Wait, really?"
It wasn't the cologne
It was softener?
It was just the smell of the softener
I see
Like he said before, at least keep it to different studios. At the very least
Why would you wear it here, on purpose?
I,
I like Takahashi
Sorry?
I really respect him, as a person
So you wore those clothes here on purpose?
It wasn't on purpose, I wore those clothes on other days after seeing Takahashi
You know, it's just,
A celebrity, looking up to a staff member...
I've never heard of that
He looks up to a younger staff member
He's sure having fun, look at that face!
But you know, If I like someone,
What the hell have you been saying?
That's not what you're on trial for
Well that's just the reason,
Why did I wear these clothes? It's cause I like Takahashi
As a person right?
I like him as a person
But does Takahashi like Yamasaki?
I've never heard him say it, but I bet he does
I've talked to him a lot
What do you mean?
Like in meetings...
That goes for all of us then
Stealing Ideas from other people
Yamasaki has come up with many gags
But almost none of them have become popular
These are some of them
But that bumbling gag maker got a big chance last year
Next year is gonna be tough for Yamasaki, so we'll have him perform a new gag for us to close us off
Yamasaki was put on the spot;
"Uwahh what should I do? Oh no! I can't keep on like this-"
"Wait! There's that one!"
Yamasaki's brain remembered a famous gag. That gag is ...
"But that doesn't matter! Ah that doesn't matter!"
It was the gag Kojima Yoshio came up with last year
In that moment, Yamasaki crossed a line as a comedian
"Doesn't matter, cause it doesn't matter!"
He's copying Kojima Yoshio's gag
He's ripping it off a bit
Copied "But that doesn't matter"
Thank you God!
Yamasaki was able to get big laughs from that stolen performance
An act of sneaky thievery indeed!
Your honour, we have a witness regarding this matter, can we bring him in?
It makes sense he's in no mood to dance
Yes, that's not what this is about
You watched that video as well
Honestly, when that aired the other day,
Do you have something to say as a victim?
I do,
Honestly, I thought I could keep that gag going until April at least
I was gonna keep doing that, however,
Cause of that guys "Cause it doesn't matter"
So I've come up with a new gag to take its place
Well, we didn't know about that
Could you show us?
Yes, if you do have a new gag
Yeah, Yamasaki can't copy this one. Feel free to do it
IT'S YOUR FAULT!
Kojima, Kojima calm down
I wanted to do it starting fresh,
So what do you think after hearing all that?
Do you have any objections, defendant?
You copied him right?
Yes, you accept that right? You have no objections
Why are you poker facing this?
You're gonna start poker facing now?
Oh he's speaking
Can I say one thing?
Well even if it's one thing, explain yourself
I do not believe I copied him, in my opinion
However!
They sure are similar...
We're the ones who think it looks similiar!
If you thought they were similiar then why did you still do it?
Would you do that? If you had a similiar gag you would stop doing it?
Of course I would!
Lies! That is a lie!
How many gags do you think there are in the world?
That's not really the point...
There's always some similar part
So saying things like "stolen" or "copied"-
Are there any other gags that are similiar like that?
Of course!
They're all like that
Like?
All of them?
I would be glad to hear an example
You know that "Gajong!" one?
So that "Gajong!" gag, and my other gag...
You can't use yours as an example!
You can't say your own!
So then you are copying them
"My other gag" you say?
Up until now, Yamasaki has been able to weasle out of the allegations,
However, after this, some definitive proof will be revealed!
In regards to this gag, your honour we have another victim
For this gag?\
Can we introduce him?
Understood. Witness, enter.
Yamasaki finds himself in trouble when that bomb comedian is revealed
Regarding this gag, your honour we have another victim. Can we introduce him?
Understood. Witness, enter.
As I'm sure you all know, this is a young Yoshimoto comedian named Nagai Yuichiro
What kind of performances does Nagai Yuichiro do?
He appeared on "Enta no Kamisama" as "Axel Hopper"
He showcased his ungforgettable rhythym gag,
What claim does he have against Yamasaki?
Well as you saw, I have this "Axel Hopper" performance,
After that, they let me do my "Nights Nights" gag
This year, 2008, I was thinking of introducing some new material,
That person over there, used that material,
And even though he was doing the "Doesn't matter" gag,
It still resembles my material
Huh? That part is also similiar?
So he took the words from him,
The words of "Doesn't matter"
And from him he stole the movements and the tempo
Surely not,
I don't think Yamasaki is that rotten!
Even though you are a victim. I'm sorry, I don't think he's fallen that far
I think that might be going too far
Alright, alright then let's watch the video
Yamasaki's modification of "That doesn't matter"
"Doesn't matter, cause it doesn't matter!"
Yamasaki stole this gag from Kojima Yoshio, however,
There is one more act of theft in here
This occurred 2 months before the creation of that gag
On Yoshimoto's comedy show,
On that day Nagai Yuichiro was performing,
Pay close attention
"This queen's rhythym is no prblem,"
"Cause it's no problem!"
That's no good!
The rhythym is exactly the same! Yamasaki stole from both of these comedians
That really hurt!
God that really hurt!
When did you learn Yamasaki stole from you?
I run a blog,
And people leave comments on there. I saw one of them,
I went "Eh?"
"I'm watching Gaki no Tsukai right now, and Yamasaki totally stole your 'No Problem!' gag"
So you learned from that comment
From a viewer
Also, I went to this drinking party. I did pretty well in my live show that day
And at the seat beside me, the "Doesn't matter, it doesn't matter"
It became like a drinking chant,
I just thought, well there goes 2008
Well Nagai-kun,
I must apologise to you
He totally stole that from you
You believed in Yamasaki too
I didn't think he was that rotten
Defendant, what do you have to say?
Well, now that I've heard it,
What's with your stoic acting?
So full of himself
So full of himself, very annoying
Excuse me a second,
Did you know about his "Axel Hopper"? Did you not know about it?
Can I be honest here?
No shit
Yeah you idiot
I knew about it
He really just confessed that
So you saw it?
So you were ripping him off during that gag
But, just let me say this please,
Well honestly, I knew
And the "Doesn't matter gag", I thought it was great when I saw it
Well, he is complimenting your gag
So I took that gag I liked, the "Doesn't matter"
And using the rhythym I remembered, all I did was combine them!
That's what we're saying!
So you stole it then
Why are you saying I stole it? That's awful!
Honestly that story made me happy!
That "Doesn't matter" gag at the drinking party,
My gag, "that doesn't matter"-
He said "My gag"
That made me really happy!
That's never happened to me before!
Well that's dangerous then, that it become so popular,
It's fine isn't it?! I didn't do anything that bad!
This trial has established he's a thief
No, why is that?
I don't feel that way at all
I never intended to hog all the glory for myself with that gag,
I intended us to do it together!
What a liar
Well, why don't you tell him then
It's actually supposed to be a collab
This is the first time I've met him!
It's the first time we've met
Oh really?
Wait? It's your first time?
Wow, even that is awful
He stole from someone he never met
This year ... this year ...
No, not this year, it really is the first time
He lied again
This is a courtroom
Why did you like like that?
Cause you're all attacking me
What?
I didn't rip him off, I want to collab with him!
I just said I want to collab, I did!
Then do it, show us here
It's gonna be really great
Kojima you too, all 3 of you
Is it alright then?
That's all I'm saying
They're both your victims,
Why are the victims keeping their distance?
Let's see this then
This is amazing what you've pulled off
You should fear god
Do it, do it
Are you ready?
Here we go
Please do
Ready, steady ...
Sorry
We won't broadcast this
Don't mind
Next week, more tales of Yamasaki's thieving nature