Subtitles: Zurui
Goodbye
Its getting hot...
Oh, someone's moving out
Hey!
Mister!
Oh, hey
You live here?
What are you talking about?
What?
The name plate
You're wrong, what are you talking about?
Why are you hiding that?
You live in this house?
Well.. yea
I'm leaving
Leaving?!
Yea
Where are you leaving to?
Well.. where I'm going. I can't tell you
But...
I have a lot of debt
I can't pay it off
That can't be
Sorry
Don't tell me sorry
I'm going
Don't say that!
Don't tell anyone
I wont, but...
If you aren't around, what am I supposed to do?
About what?
I'll get bullied!
Yea, that's true
Please, don't go
Well... let's do this
What?
Let's take a photo
If you show that we are friends, no one will bully you
Really??
Don't worry
Are you really sure?
Really. I'm sure... here stand next to me
You really going? Will you be ok?
Sorry, I have to go
Will you be ok?
"Mirakuru...Faito de..."
"Sakigake Rock & Roll"
Ok, well be careful
See you!
Wait a minute!
W..w..wait a minute
It has to develope
There's nothing on there
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Mister! Wait!
Miracle Ace!
Come back again ok!
It's appearing, wait just a minute!
There's nothing there
MISTER!!
I'll loan you money!
The end