Subtitles: ZuRUi
Drivers License
Ma-kun!
Wait! Wait!
Give me a ride!
Huh
Are you an idiot?
Can't you give me a ride to the train station?
Just walk!
I'm just asking for a little favor!
It's just nearby!
You're so irritating!
I can't help it! You know my bicycle was stolen!
That's why I can't ride
Take me there...
near the train station
You don't have...
What?
you know.. that... seat...
Life... belt!
What is that?
Life belt!
Oh, here it is!
You know how I feel about riding in cars, it's dangerous!
Why are you complaining to me?
Where's your sea... oh here?
Here?
Do you have your's on?
I don't need it
Wear it for my sake!
Wear it, don't talk like that
It's scary if you don't wear it
Like you know... that...
That...
Boiled egg...
Raw egg... smashed!
What are you talking about?
If you don't wear it... YOU WILL BECOME
LIKE THAT RAW EGG!!
Seat!
Ok, already!
Let's go!
Where are we going?!
What?
Where?
The train station
Why don't you just walk!
That's ok, just do me this favor!
It's like we are both on...
the Chuo freeway!
What are you talking about?
Hurry, let's go
Hey! Watch your speed!!
I know! Irritating!
Shut up!
Watch your speed!!
I'm not speeding!
You have to use your signal when turning!
I know... don't touch!
Hurry, use it!
What are you doing!?
Hey! What was that?
You touched it!
Hurry up! Turn it on!
I KNOW!! SHUT UP!!
Make sure you use it!
Yea! Are you an idiot?!
I'm gonna kick you out!
Oh you...
What are you touching!!
What?
I can't see behind!
I can't see the behind!
STOP!
What??
What is it?!!
Itao-san!
Here, here!
Where are you going?
Oh, Mrs!
Oh you're driving! Wow!
Who's car is this?
Ma-kun borrowed it from his friend
Wow!
It's so scary to be in a car
C.. can we ride?
Sure!
Shut up!
Where are you going?
Home
Oh, you're going home?
We just came from s...school
Get in!
What are you doing?
Why do I have to give them a ride?
Are you an idiot?
He said it's fine!
Oh it's ok?
Is it really ok?
Really?
It's fun...
with more people, it's fun
How does this work Ma-kun?
HOW MA-KUN?!
What?
MOVE THE SEAT FORWARD!
Sorry you have to sit in the back
Ok, let's ride
Sorry to bother you
It's a little cramped
Sorry, it's a little cramped
It's good to ride
Ah, I'm getting a sunburn
Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry Mrs, please move down
Ok, where to first?
Tell him
Ok, me first
Tondabayashi
You know Nishimeihan?
Near Fujiidera
yea, near Fujiidera
Mrs, is it ok to smoke?
Sure, that's fine
What are you saying?
Oh, it's hot
Yes, let's go, it's hot
Oh, it's so hot!
Where's your ashtray?
Mrs, ashtray?
Ma-kun where's the ashtray?
Don't drop your ashes in someone else's car!
Here, use this
Hey, why did you take it out!?
Do you have air condition?
Ma-kun where's the air condition?
What?
Air con!
It's there!
This one?
No! That's not it!
It's this one
It was scary today
This one right?
Ah, it feels good!
I don't understand these mechanical things!
I know what this is
When I press this, it will become cooler
HEY! WHAT IS THIS?
We'll be crushed!