http://zurui.blogspot.com
Subtitles: Zurui
Shinsui Kazoku
(Flooded Family)
Be sure to tell them, ok?
I know
Are you sure?
I will!
Ok, let's go in
I'm home!
Welcome home!
Hello, good afternoon
I'm Yuko's mother
Thank you for always taking care of Yuko
Please come in
Come in
Your father is waiting
Oh, really?
Don't be shy
Here's your slippers
I'm sorry but can you close the door?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Because of the neighbors
There was so much traffic
Is that so?
- Yes
Dad's been waiting for a long time
Really?
Please come in
Don't be shy
Here's your slippers
Becareful, shall I take this?
Take this?
- Yes
Dad, Yuko has arrived!
Are you ok?
Here you go
Come in!
Come in, don't be shy
Give me your coat
Come in, come in
Dad, I'm home
Nice to meet you, I'm Hamada
Nice to meet you, I'm Yuko's father
Aren't you a little late Yuko?
There was too much traffic
Oh, really
Please have a seat
It's nothing special, but please have a seat
Here you go
It must've been tiring
No, really, have a seat
Please
- Please
Don't be shy
- Yes
Have a seat
No, no, really
Sit properly, don't be shy
Just relax
Make yourself at home
He's just nervous
He's nervous? Same as me, I'm nervous too
It's the first time you bought
your boyfriend over right?
Oh! That's right, it's nothing
special, but I brought a cake
It's nothing special
- Sorry to give you so much trouble
I'll make some tea, Yuko can help?
So you are Yuko's boyfriend?
Excuse me
- Ok
It's the first time she brought someone
Here you go
Here you go, dear
Is the dog ok?
- Yes
You work for a company, Hamada?
Yes
He works with Yuko
He's still young, but he's a supervisor
So you must be making a lot of money?
Don't talk about that, dear
It's ok
Oh yes, Yuko!
Shall we have a look at your childhood pictures?
No way dad, it's so embarrassing!
Good idea, right?
You're kidding!
Where's the album?
Where did you put it dear?
Um, it should be there
It's embarrassing, no way!
This is a masterpiece
Take a look
- Ok
This here...
Great, huh?
- Yes
Yuko, that's when you were young, huh?
No, wait.. it's embarrassing
No, lean forward
Realx, relax
Lay down
Ok
This is a masterpiece
This brings back memories
No way!
This is great right? I took this picture
This bring back memories
Oh, really
No don't show this one!
Oh here
When was this?
It's ok, this was her previous boyfriend
Dad!
It's ok, we wont say anything
This is..
good right?
Oh, by the way, is your stomach ok?
Oh, yeah, I thought you didn't look so well
No, I'm ok
- Oh, you must be angry
I'm fine, really
Um, lets eat that thing we always eat
*They are preparing to eat "Nagashi somen"
Ok
*Some noodles are floated down a bamboo ramp
and eaten before they reach the bottom
This is very famous in our house
Is he ok?
He's fine, don't worry
Ok, thank you
Well, we don't prepare much gourmet foods
but this is famous in our household so please try it
Ok, please have a seat
Please have a seat, don't be shy
Give him to me
He's all wet
Please add the condiments
I'm adding the condiments
I'm starting!
Here it comes, get it
Help yourself dear
Here it comes!
The noodles were sticking together
Catch it nicely
Here you go
It's ok, I can get it myself
Hamada-san, do you like tomatoes?
Are tomatoes ok?
- Yes
Ok here's a tomato
Mom give me more
Here, here, here you go
Here you go
Dear... you sure like this, huh?
This is delicious
The noodles came out great
Right?
I tried my best
Is this ok?
Mom, the sauce is a little thick
But it's delicious
Sorry about that
Here you go
Eat up, eat up
Pour this on top?
Like this, here
The noodles dropped around here
It's all stuck together
Hamada-san are you could?
A little
He's cold
Sorry about that
Let's warm you up
Tell me when to stop
When it's ok, let me now
A little more
I'm ok now
Are you ok?
-  Yes
Let us know if you need anything
Well, she finally showed us her boyfriend
Really
I wondered what type of person
he was, but he seems nice
A really nice person
We don't have to worry anymore
What about her?
- Yes
how is she?
Dad!
How far did you go?!
Dear!
Stop it, dad!
How far did you go, bastard?!
he's funny
He's always like this
Actually I have something to ask you today
Actually, sir..
Please let me get married to Yuko
Please
Hamada-kun
Yes
You're a very nice person
It's rare that I like someone
the first time I meet them
Yes
Actually, when you ask someone something...
you should bow deeply
or it doesn't seem sincere
Right?
You should learn
to understand about how to bow to other people
Wrong. Hamada-kun
That's not right
I really took care of my daughter
Right?
Because of that...
you should be able to bow a little deeper
Noodles...
Please let her get married to me
Dear!
Dad!
Hamada-kun
- Yes
It should be 4-5 minutes
No appreciation
Yes, that's true
It shows no appreciation
Do it
Yuko, you too
Don't let your future husband do it by himself
Please let her marry me
Please
Dear!
From our side
Please take care of her
This isn't good