Subtitles: eChie
This is good, huh?
- Yes, it is
How would you like?
Sir and Madam,
How's everything?
Well, everything is so delicious
Thank you
Especially this sauce is very delicious
It's the chef's specialty
Thank you
We would like o acknowledge the chef
Because everything is so good
The Chef?
- Yes
Hi
I'm Chef Matsumoto
We're really enjoying your food
Thank you so much
Especially this sauce is excellent,
may I ask what's the ingredients?
What is it?
What?
- What about?
The ingredient
The ingredients? You made it, right?
What! Don't say it loud!
- that's YOU!
What!?
He's asking you for the ingredients
Errr...wine
Pardon me?
um..
Wine?
Red or white??
Hurry, just say it!
Well..white wine
- White wine?
White wine..white wine
- Say it properly!
Why don't you tell them?!
- They asked you!
Is it white wine?
- Yes, sir
Is it white wine? It's unique, isn't it?
He's asking you
Isn't unique?
- Yes...yes
Also, the meat is so tender..
May I ask what kind of meat it is?
I don't know what it is
Didn't you buy it?
- You bought it!
You don't need to slug me!
What kind of meat?! Remember!
Foie gras...
Foie gras
Foie gras isn't meat!
Who the hell do you think you are!?
Aren't you the chef?!
I have no idea!
Which one in the fridge did you use?!
You tell them first!
I am a manager!
Anyway, we're taking too much time, we have to go back!
I'm laughing, so you better go..
Shut up and just go!
Delicious
Thank you for waiting, sir
It's lamb
Oh, is it?!
It is not!
You told me to say something!
That's fine, then
Is it lamb?
- Yes, sir
It is lamb
It is so rare
- Yes
We are satisfied
Shal we go then?
- Yes
Excuse me. How much is the bill?
How much should I charge?
What?
How much?!
I have no idea
Didn't you make it?
I don't know, so just tell them
They're waiting, just make up your mind
Maybe 1,000 yen and 1,000 yen..
So 2,000yen?
Yea..1,000 yen each
Excuse me,sir.
- Yes
Total comes to 2,000 yen.
Only 2,000?!
- Yes
Is that so? Then,
Here is 10,000 yen bill.
- OK
Out of 10,000 yen
- Yes, thanks
Just a moment
- OK
That's so cheap, huh?
Let me borrow some 1,000 yen bills
Do you have any?
Why do I have to?!
Too loud!
Why ask me?
- Never mind!
Give it to me!
Only 5 bills
Hurry up!
Excuse me..
Just a moment
So wrinkled
Dirty
Count it
I don't remember how much I gave you!
Calculate it later!
You gonna give me back, right?
I will
Excuse me, sir.
- Yes
Thank you for waiting, here is the change
Ok, thank you
Ah, excuse me
I only got 6,000 yen
I gave you a 10,000 yen bill, so
Yes
I am short of change
Is that so? Just a moment, please?
Why is that?
You fill the shortage
I don't have any more
Why is it always me!?
Don't be so loud! I will give it back to you later!
Just give me the money!
Give me everything, hurry!
Hurry up!
Don't put it on here, stupid
You, shut up! Don't talk so loud!
You dropped money, what are you going to do?
Is that..
Oh, this is nothing
Why did you use coins?!
I said bills!
Now I don't know how much I got
Wait..one, two, three..
I gave you like 6,000 yen
If you give me a 1,000 yen bill,
I'm short 5,000 yen!
I used some of mine, too!
You..you!
What about me
What?
- I'll take it back
Yeah, take it back
I am sorry, just a moment please?
How much did you give me?
I gave you like 6,000 yen
No, you gave me 4 bills not 6
Excuse me, we need to leave..
Just a moment, please
Where is my coins?!
Never mind about that!
We can't pay back with coins!
Give me that!
You gonna take my money away again?!
Don't say it loud!
All good if we pay back 8,000 yen
We need to pay back 8,000 yen
Here's your change
I'll take the 10,000 yen bill
Excuse me.
- Yes?
I'm short 2,000 yen
You're hiding money aren't you?
I'm not
..ah.. here it is!
You were keeping it
You don't have to push me, let's do it later
Ok
Here's 2,000 yen
Thank you very much
ah..but we had a bottle of wine
A bottle of wine?
Why didn't you remind me
I don't have money
- Me neither
So we just charge for the wine
How much..how much?
- How much?
How much is it?
Thank you for waiting, sir. The wine is
60,000 yen
60,000 yen?!
He's surprised!
I have no idea
We made him surprised, what do we do?
I have no idea..I don't know
You should check all of the prices!
How old is the 60,000 yen wine?
How much..how much is a can of juice?
It's 120 yen
It's 130 yen