Translation: Zurui
Life Guard
Everyone, tomorrow and the day after
tomorrow the beach will be open.
Yes.
Accidents will increase,
which means our job will increase.
Yes.
So if by any chance,
an accident happens, we must react instantly and help.
Let's get prepared for that.
Yes.
Let's use this doll for practice.
OK, Nishihata-kun.   Give the doll heart massage.
Yes.
Do your best.
- Yes.
Use more strength.
OK, You-kun...
mouth to mouth.
Try your best.
Try hard, You-kun.
This is an emergency.
You need to save his life.
With mouth to mouth.
That's it.
What are you doing?
Just making a funny face.
Give it your all!
What's this...
The beach will open the day after tomorrow.
Oh, he is dead.
Is he? That's enough.
Imada-kun! Let's see how it's done.
Yes?
OK!
You did mouth to mouth!
I did it.
Understood?
Yes!
You, try your best!
Huh?
That's enough!
Never mind. Just try it.
But, I'm just a musician...
I can't.
Show us again Imada-kun.
- Will do!
Excuse me.
This is how you do mouth to mouth.
This doll was eating a croquette earlier.
Was it?
- Yes.