"This show was broadcasted
on the 13th of June, 2021"
Welcome to The Quest.
Today, Ganbareruya will embark
on the Calendar Project,
and we'll have
the 16th Miyagawa Expedition.
Wasshoi!
Hello, hello, hello.
Hello!
"Yoshiko, Mahiru, Ganbareruya"
"Ganbareruya goes on a Calendar Tour
full of stunning sceneries"
We'll go there?
This place is so scary.
The Goto Islands!
I've caught it!
Yellowtail amberjacks
at the Goto Islands!
Members of The Quest go to various
places in the world every month
to take beautiful photos.
They aim to collect the photos
and complete the 2022 calendar.
This is
"The Quest" Calendar Project.
We'll go to Kochi Prefecture
and Ehime Prefecture this time
to take photos
of stunning sceneries.
We have come to Kochi Prefecture!
Now, it's time for Yoshiko Quiz.
Kochi Prefecture here is the place
where a famous actress is from.
Who is the actress?
Dad, please answer that!
- Dad.
- Ms Ryoko Hirosue.
Isn't it?
Who is it?
The correct answer
is Ms Ryoko Hirosue!
- Who's that?
- What is she doing?
Wait a minute.
My joke was so lame,
I feel awful now.
The first stunning scenery
they visit is...
The feature of early summer,
fireflies.
The Shimanto River basin and various
places in Kochi Prefecture
are well-known
for the fireflies there.
They will try to take a photo
of them surrounded by fireflies.
We have the assistance
of Mr Rei Ohara,
an animal photographer.
I used to be
a gossip magazine's photographer.
- Gossip magazine.
- Yes.
I washed my hands of that.
Now, I take photos of baby seals,
long-tailed bushtits,
and fireflies.
That's why I'm good
at taking photos in dark places.
I scoped out celebrities
and took photos in many dark places.
That's because one must not use
lighting to photograph fireflies.
Fireflies communicate by the light
emitted from each other.
So if there is
artificial light nearby,
it disturbs their light-making,
and leads to extinction
in the worst-case scenario.
The photoshoot will be done
in a special way.
The time period
when many fireflies come out
will be too dark for
the two of you to be seen.
I'll take a photo of you after
sunset when there's a little light,
keep the camera fixed there,
and take photos of the fireflies at
the same place and add them there.
It'll be done by multiple exposure.
I'm looking forward to it.
The stage of the photoshoot
is Sukumo City, Kochi Prefecture's
Kurokawa Hotaru no Sato.
Firefly is an endangered species,
but here, because of the effort
made by the residents,
the number increases every year.
Wonderful!
Oh, I found one!
Over there!
It's there!
- Yes, that's a male firefly.
- Look.
As you can see, during the day,
fireflies rest on the back of leaves
and the shadow of the grass
to preserve energy for the night.
What firefly is this?
Genji-botaru.
Why is it called that?
Genji-botaru and Heike-botaru
are aquatic fireflies,
Heike-botaru mainly fly low
above farms,
they aren't very fast.
Genji-botaru fly high
above the sky.
Hence, "Genji" connotes momentum,
and "Heike" connotes inertia.
I see.
They start emitting light
30 minutes after sunset in general.
But there is some time until sunset,
so we'll introduce activities in
the neighbouring Ehime Prefecture.
It is this one.
Will it be in time?
What's this?
- A natural water slide.
- You can slide?
It's a great waterfall chosen as one
of the 100 waterfalls in Japan,
Yukiwa Waterfall.
We aren't going to slide down there,
are we?
You'll get injured if you start
at the top,
so you'll start near
two-thirds of the height.
Is it really two-thirds usually?
It's always two-thirds.
You aren't too fired up, are you?
- You figured it out?
- Hey!
Mahiru goes first.
- Don't let go yet.
- It's okay, not yet.
- Don't let go yet!
- Okay, okay.
Are you okay? I'm scared!
- Three, two, one.
- So fast.
It's too long!
She slides 40 metres straight down.
Machan, are you okay?
It got bumpy halfway.
Yoshiko goes next.
Okay, let's go!
Three, two, one.
- I know how you feel.
- It has just started.
Oh, no.
Watch out.
It's dangerous.
She fell inside.
Yocchan.
It was scary.
Then, a problem occurred.
Yocchan, look at your GoPro.
Hey!
There's no way it filmed anything!
Yocchan, do it once more!
Why?
We must report about your GoPro
to the director.
There's no need.
- Ms Maekawa--
- Don't tell her!
It's fine,
only the editor needs to know.
- Ms Maekawa!
- Don't tell her!
There's no need to tell her!
I told you not to tell her!
They check Yoshiko's camera.
Let's go!
The standby at the beginning
is already not good enough.
Most of it wasn't filmed.
Not most of it!
The first part was filmed!
On the other hand, Mahiru's...
How was it?
Wow, it's stable.
Amazing.
Impressive.
That's journalism.
At the same time, the photoshoot
of fireflies has started.
Here it is.
First, a photo of the ladies
is taken before the sun sets.
Then, when the area starts
getting dark...
- It's emitting light.
- So pretty.
So pretty.
- Is it saying it's time to go?
- Yes.
There are two special chemicals
in a firefly's lower abdomen,
and the firefly makes the chemicals
react to make it glow.
In dark places, the fireflies
gradually fly to high places,
like they're flying
towards the stars.
The origin of the firefly's
Japanese term means "star drops."
They fly like the stars
are dripping down,
so they're called "hotaru."
We have filmed fireflies many times
in The Quest so far,
but it was very difficult to convey
how beautiful they are in the video.
That was you.
But with the use of the latest
high-sensitivity camera,
as you can see, people and fireflies
can be shown vividly.
Impressive.
We couldn't have filmed this scene
20 years ago.
It would've been difficult
even two or three years ago.
The lifespan of an adult firefly
is only about 10 days.
Until its life ends,
it emits light and flies around
to look for a mate.
- It doesn't leave you at all.
- Not at all.
You got yourself a huge female.
When the sun sets completely,
he opens the shutter
and takes photos of the fireflies.
This is the finished photo.
Amazing!
You look like fairies
in the world of fireflies.
I actually wanted you
to look more like monsters.
Darn you!
She said it.
It's never made anyone this happy.
I'm happy.
Next, they'll try the art that
gained a lot of attention lately.
Modern artist, Ms Chad,
will show us how to do it.
This is her performance.
Impressive.
She's strong.
She uses a giant brush and writes
the words that come to her mind.
This art performance is a fusion
of calligraphy and dance.
I see.
The performance is unearthly,
and Yoshiko empathises with it.
- She's crying.
- Yoshiko loves it.
Amazing.
"Now...
make your voice be heard."
is what I wrote.
Can they also
make their voices be heard?
Mahiru goes first.
The material doesn't tear, right?
The material is tough.
It's Kochi's Washi paper.
- She slapped herself.
- The slapped boy.
I think they're cut out
for performances like this.
They are.
Is that a teardrop?
The teacher nodded deeply just now.
- She wrote on her face first.
- Yes.
Oh, in the middle.
This suits them.
She matched the lyrics.
- "Me."
And now, the words
finally came to her mind.
What words came to Machan's mind?
She's snickering.
- What's that?
- Just write it.
What does this piece of work
look like in the end?
Amazing, Machan.
I knew you wrote the character
of "Me" in green.
I don't recognise any character
you wrote after that.
"Full tank."
"Empty."
"All love."
You created an extraordinary artist!
Everyone has been moved.
I didn't do it to move people.
Is that so?
Next, it's Yoshiko's turn.
The song is Koji Tamaki's "Den-En."
- "Den-En."
- Good.
She's cut out for it.
The weather is good.
Good.
She's just dancing.
She doesn't write at all.
She doesn't.
She's not writing yet.
No word has come to mind yet.
- Good.
- "You."
Good.
She doesn't write.
She's not writing yet.
The words haven't come to mind.
Because it's quiet.
She got it?
- With her foot.
- Good.
The words don't come
to Yoshiko's mind.
Not yet?
But now...
She got it.
She suddenly started, wow!
The way the words come to mind
is awesome.
There are many words.
She's writing a lot.
Wow, the words came to her mind.
She doesn't stop.
She turns it over.
She's gasping for air.
Is that all?
It feels so good!
Can I ask what you wrote?
"Do you think,
only you can't do it?"
"It's..."
Did she really write that?
"not because you can't do it,
it's only because your motivation
isn't strong enough."
Here.
"Who decided mountains are green?"
"Who decided the sky is blue?"
Wow, she got so many ideas?
"You work too hard,
Japanese people!"
Yocchan works too hard.
She improvised it just now.
Next, they'll go to see another
stunning scenery seen only at night.
A total lunar eclipse.
When the Earth, the moon and the sun
are in one straight line,
the moon goes completely
into the Earth's shadow,
and it looks reddish brown.
They went filming on the 26th May,
and it was the best chance
to see the first total lunar eclipse
in Japan in three years.
I know that.
It's the Super Flower Blood Moon.
You mean supermoon, right?
What?
You don't know?
First, a full moon in May
is called Flower Moon.
- Is that so?
- And today, the 26th May,
the full moon
will look very close,
and it's called supermoon.
Also, a total lunar eclipse
is called Blood Moon,
so this is
a Super Flower Blood Moon.
You asked us to come here
without knowing that?
This time, they'll use the Super
Flower Blood Moon as a background,
and jump on a bicycle.
They'll try to take a photo
like this.
E. T.?
- Beautiful.
- Yeah.
The stage of the photoshoot
is the Shikoku Karst across Kochi
Prefecture and Ehime Prefecture.
This will be your jump ramp.
What?
The moon will rise from the shadow
of the mountain there.
The camera is on the opposite side.
Can it see us now?
I think so.
To make the moon look big
in the photo,
it must be one kilometre away
from the object.
So we'll use a telephoto lens
at a place
where the moon
and the object overlap.
We must be able to jump
to begin with.
Kochi BMX Association's Mr Kubouchi
will teach them how to jump.
Use the momentum
to raise the front tyre.
Right, we have to
raise it ourselves.
Can Mahiru do it?
Amazing.
Impressive!
Amazing!
I can do it already.
So quick!
Next, it's Yoshiko's turn.
- You can do it.
- Be careful.
Good. Parallel...
This is scary.
I'm scared.
It's scary.
She changes gear and tries again.
Oh, I'm scared!
Oh, I'm scared. I'm so scared.
Without the skill to raise
the front tyre...
You can do it... not.
Oh, I'm scared!
I'm scared.
How do you do so many patterns?
I'm impressed, Yocchan.
- But a big problem occurs.
- What?
- Wow, it's big.
- It's big.
The rain hits from the side.
Unfortunately, it is raining
in Shikoku on this day.
Obviously, they can't even try
if the sky isn't clear.
Indeed.
At the same time,
the sky is clear in Ishigaki Island.
Amazing.
The total lunar eclipse has started.
The moon entered the Earth's shadow,
faint sunlight shines on it,
turning it into
a mysterious reddish brown.
Amazing.
It's gorgeous.
I wish I could jump
in front of this.
But we want
to at least take a photo like this
of the moon and Ganbareruya,
so they tried again the next day,
but...
Bad weather.
It's impossible today too.
What's this?
The fog is extremely thick.
Completely white.
There's no way something a kilometre
away can be seen by a camera.
In fact, we don't get many chances
to take a photo like this.
Why don't we make an appearance
from there naked?
What the heck?
It's okay if this area
is covered in fog.
Out of desperation,
Ganbareruya makes the fog art,
"Adam and Eve."
Wait, I can see a bit.
We don't need this.
It's very obvious.
Beautiful.
The photo is amazing.
This is amazing.
We can use it for the calendar!
Next, the stunning scenery
Shikoku is proud of.
You'll climb a mountain
and go towards the stunning scenery.
Their outfits
are for mountain climbing.
They've come to the highest peak
in West Japan,
Mount Ishizuchi.
Can we climb it?
Oh, you put bread inside!
- Why can't I?
- It's the bread given to us,
and she keeps it to herself.
Why can't I? I was hungry.
You definitely need to say it.
Their mountain guide
is Mr Matsumoto.
Mount Ishizuchi
is the deity worshipped
at the Ishizuchi Shrine.
It's also a place for training,
you'll reach a state
of selflessness.
Put the bread here before you go.
I'll bring the bread.
Basically, primary school children
to old people
can enjoy climbing Mount Ishizuchi.
But Yoshiko's weight
is 80 kilograms,
the path is too difficult.
- She gained weight again?
- Machan!
The woodland peonies are blossoming.
Yocchan.
Everyone is waiting, Yocchan.
Sorry.
I won't blame you if you're late
because you're tired,
but don't be late
because you keep talking.
She's strict.
When they're about to reach
the limit of their stamina,
a dangerous route that stops
beginners appears.
We'll now climb up here.
What?
We'll go there?
Give me a break.
The climbing chains
were made in the past
for monks who aims to reach
a state of selflessness.
The cliff is almost vertical,
they'll only use the chain
to climb up.
The chain is 65 metres long,
they can't turn back
once they start climbing.
Wow, I'm scared.
A problem occurred after
they climbed 10 metres.
Maybe Yocchan's condition is bad.
Yoshiko has almost used up
her energy before coming here,
she's reached her limit.
Yocchan!
Your limbs are too tired,
aren't they?
Don't force yourself!
That's what Machan says.
I'll do it.
Yoshiko squeezes out the last bit
of her strength
and climbs up the chain again.
Yocchan, you can do it!
Then, finally...
She worked hard.
All right!
I made it!
You did very well, Yocchan.
Let's hurry to a flat ground.
- This place is scary.
- It is.
Five hours after they started
climbing the mountain...
We're here.
Amazing!
They arrive at the peak
of Mount Ishizuchi,
which has an altitude
of 1,974 metres.
- It's fantastic.
- Impressive.
Japan is beautiful.
It's gorgeous.
But this isn't the stunning scenery
of their destination.
You see a shrine in front of you,
don't you?
- Yes.
That's the highest peak
in West Japan.
That's your destination.
What?
Their destination is the main peak
of Mount Ishizuchi, Tengu-dake.
It's dangerous, Mr Ishii.
My bottom tightens when I see you.
Mr Ishii, please come closer here.
- Please, I'm scared.
- I'm scared.
They'll go to the knife ridge
where both sides are cut off.
This place is so scary.
They can only rely on their bodies.
Former climber, cameraman Ishii,
walks swiftly there.
It's dangerous, Mr Ishii.
Mr Ishii, no...
Mr Ishii, please stay still.
The further they go,
the more dangerous the path gets.
Oh, no, I'm falling.
Stop.
- You can do it.
- Stand up straight.
- Yocchan, don't go too far there.
- What?
- Don't go too far, you'll fall.
- I'm okay.
I'm scared, Yocchan.
Stop, I'll be scared
if you say that.
Sorry.
Hurry up, come here, Yocchan.
Stop it, Machan is making this
twice as scary!
I can't look.
Don't look.
Mr Ishii. Mr Ishii, stop, really.
I'm scared, Mr Ishii.
They climbed for one hour,
and finally...
We made it.
- Is this the peak?
- The peak.
They arrive at Tengu-dake,
the highest peak in West Japan
and Mount Ishizuchi's main peak.
It's here.
Thank you.
We're finally here.
The view is stunning.
This scenery is gorgeous.
It's the first time I see
a view so stunning.
Right?
I can see the whole of Shikoku.
Indeed.
This is the scenery the Tengu saw.
They take a commemorative photo
at the peak.
Nice back.
Tengu-dake, 1,982 metres,
we climbed here successfully!
Mr Ishii!
- Stop it!
- Stop moving like that!
For June in the calendar...
we'll use this photo.
That's all for
Ganbareruya's Calendar Project.
They shone the most
in the calligraphy session.
I think I'd be good at the combined
calligraphy and dancing too.
Dad, you look like you do.
Chen and Kurosawa
will be good at it.
I am moved.
We'd think too much
and it wouldn't be funny.
- That's possible.
- Yeah.
Next, it is this part.
The 16th Miyagawa Expedition!
This time, it's the Fishing Series.
What? Fishing?
I'm not confident.
The other day, we changed from
catching tuna to yellowtail at once.
His target is...
What? "Catch a huge bigfin reef
squid longer than a man's height!"
Bigfin reef squid is usually
about 40 centimetres long,
but in spring, when they lay eggs,
at Nagasaki's Goto Islands,
monsters that are longer
than a person's height appear.
The mission this time is to make
squid rice with the giant squid.
I couldn't catch tuna,
so I want to try again.
I want to show our viewers a giant
bigfin reef squid longer than a man.
How about this, Mum?
After filming the tuna fishing
last time,
Assistant Producer Hirata, known
as Mum, got hooked on fishing.
I can't forget the feeling
of catching cod,
I thought my arms
weren't strong enough,
so I have personal training
once a week.
- What?
- Good.
Sorry, but the direction
you work hard is wrong.
A new member joins their team.
- Assistant Director Yui?
- Yes.
Wait, you're an assistant director?
- Your top is Dior?
- Yes.
What?
What? Your shoes are Vuitton?
Why?
My grandpa is the president
of a certain company.
We'll bleep it. Which company?
"Secret"
"A huge enterprise"
Seriously? The bleep just overlapped
with my "what?"
The celebrity works as an assistant
director for work experience.
Will your grandpa not get angry
when he sees this?
If he gets angry,
we'll be finished in an instant.
We'll go to the Goto Islands!
We'll do our best!
Will he be able to catch
a monster-level bigfin reef squid?
Miyagawa Expedition.
Catch a giant bigfin reef squid.
The stage is a World Heritage,
the Goto Islands,
where history coexists with nature.
Miyagawa Expedition.
It's obvious when you see it,
it's impressive!
The 16th tour!
In the Goto Islands!
I've had enough.
There are too many places to visit.
Mum.
That's "Tsuribaka Nisshi!"
"Hama-chan"
That's Hama-chan.
Captain realised
something wasn't right.
Yui?
- She isn't here.
- Indeed.
Hello?
Hello, Captain.
Hello.
We've come to the Goto Islands.
Have you?
Don't laugh.
Miruku is feeling lonely,
so I didn't go.
Who is Miruku?
- The dog I keep at home.
- A pet dog?
The pet dog is more important
than the expedition.
It can't be helped. Idiot!
Captain stands still for a while.
I'm sad.
This is okay in 2021?
So Assistant Director Sakamoto
joins at the last minute,
and these are the team members.
They also recruited reliable help.
Mr Usui is a coordinator
who specialises in fishing.
He has gone around the world
and caught many giant fish.
We'll fish.
Around the Goto Islands,
various kinds of fish swim around
along the Tsushima Current.
Big fish gather in this ocean
to look for food.
When Miyagawa tries his fishing rod
before catching squid...
Got it!
I caught it!
He caught one right away.
And Mum also...
The fish he caught is...
It's huge!
It's a yellowtail amberjack,
rarely seen caught on television.
They are yellowtail amberjacks
in the Goto Islands!
Sakamoto also...
Amazing!
Good! It's huge!
It's huge! Look at the sea bream!
It's a giant sea bream that's rarely
seen caught on television.
This is the Goto Islands.
They will hunt bigfin reef squid
in this sea of abundance.
I want to catch one
that is too big to put in a pot.
A huge one, about as big as Yogibo.
I want to use it to make squid rice.
Finally, it's the bigfin reef squid.
They'll use a lure for squid
called squid jig.
We sink it down to the bottom,
then we jerk it up.
Then we sink it like this.
It's when the squid will hold it.
- It's holding rather than biting.
- Hold.
Bigfin reef squid
at the bottom of the sea
preys like it holds the food.
At that moment, the rod is pulled up
and the needle is hooked.
But when the squid bites,
it is only felt weakly
through the rod.
It feels like breaking
a mechanical pencil lead.
We have to catch it like that,
that's how delicate it is.
Captain noticed something was wrong
with the boat on the side
where the cameraman was on.
Omori!
What are you doing?
My trousers are wet!
You're in your underwear again!
Wait, why?
How many pieces of underwear
do you have?
Three.
You brought three pieces
of underwear?
What would make him wet?
I know the sea is rough.
They fished for 20 minutes,
but caught nothing.
Mr Usui can't stand watching it
and holds Miyagawa's hands to do it.
It bit!
I caught it.
But he caught the wrong squid.
This is a swordtip squid,
our target is a bigfin reef squid.
Make sushi with this.
AD Sakamoto was trained
at a sushi restaurant last time,
and makes it into sushi there.
You broke its ink sac.
The sushi is going to be black.
Is this okay?
She broke the ink sac. Is it okay?
You removed the rice.
You pressed,
then removed the extra rice.
I haven't seen
sushi restaurants do that.
Here it goes.
But how does it taste?
Delicious!
- Squid dishes!
- Stop it!
You like that joke,
but we don't want it.
They also put out a boat at night,
but couldn't catch
any bigfin reef squid.
But attracted by the light
on the boat...
We caught a baby squid.
What? Really?
This is a baby bigfin reef squid.
Oh, it's there.
- Squids die in one year.
- Is that so?
No matter how big the squid is,
they grow that big in one year.
When breeding season comes,
bigfin reef squid come
to shallow water from offshore,
and lay eggs on seaweed or rocks.
The shape of the eggs
is like field peas.
There are babies in each
of the pod-like rooms.
They grow into about
1 centimetre long in one month,
and leave the capsule.
Amazing.
So cute.
Mum's maternity can't stop.
- Mum! I know how she feels, though.
- Hey.
But babies have to be returned
to the sea.
I will free it.
Take care.
"Rough"
Day two.
Strong wind at over 20 metres
per second blows in the morning.
Let's go back.
They can't fish at all and withdraw.
On this day, they go to the mountain
to get food ingredients.
This is mugwort, right?
Won't it be delicious
if we turn this into tempura?
Can we pick the root?
No, not the root, Mum.
Mum, are you hungry?
You heard tempura
and it made you hungry?
There's also a food ingredient
that's unique to the Goto Islands.
Is this camellia? What's this?
It's camellia.
People eat camellia
in the Goto Islands.
No way. What do they eat?
The leaves?
- They eat the flower.
- The flower.
The Goto Islands is one of Japan's
largest camellia-producing areas.
The seeds are used to make
its speciality, camellia oil.
The flower is made
into tempura for eating.
Found it.
It's amazing.
Anything to it cut with?
Yes, that's right.
Shuffle them like this.
Say stop. Okay, stop. Okay.
Say stop.
Stop! Okay.
Remember this.
Idiot!
Brilliant.
Not that!
I can't do anything with
playing cards.
Something to it cut with.
That's right.
Use this like this.
Yes.
He understands.
Where will you go?
Oh, Shimbashi? Okay.
Okay.
Cut to the right.
Idiot.
He continues to cut.
That's wrong.
What can I do with this?
We have to wait until it falls,
then it won't be
the best time to eat!
Something to it cut with.
- I tried hard.
- You did.
That's right. This.
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
It's coming!
I boiled it for too long. No!
And...
You're fired up.
The noodles look tastier
than the flower.
"Nagasaki Champon noodles"
It makes me want the noodles.
Oh, this one is nice.
They harvested
fresh camellia flowers,
and rented a local restaurant
in the afternoon,
and made lunch with
the food ingredients they got.
It's huge.
They used the fresh seafood
to make sashimi.
Sakamoto, look at how my hand moves.
Isn't it genius? It's nice.
"Yellowtail amberjack
caught yesterday"
A luxurious sashimi boat of squid,
sea bream, and yellowtail amberjack.
Wow, it's gorgeous!
- Mum is making Goto Udon.
- She works there.
The sauce is made with dried flying
fish stock and squid ink.
It is served with
camellia and squid tempura.
Let's dig in.
- Bon appetit.
The noodles will get soggy,
let's start with the Goto Udon.
It looks delicious.
Goto Udon is thin.
Absolutely delicious!
The stock is so rich. Who made this?
It's amazing, Mum.
Next, it's yellowtail amberjack
sashimi.
It has to be good.
- It's fleshy.
- Fleshy.
It's fatty,
but it's light,
and the taste doesn't linger.
Lastly, it's the local cuisine,
camellia tempura.
What does it taste like?
Crunchy.
It has no taste.
"No taste"
Ridiculous.
It's crunchy tempura.
It's tasty.
Captain, something worries me.
What is it?
It doesn't look like
Miyagawa Expedition anymore.
I see.
Well, but...
It can't be helped.
Day three.
The weather recovered,
it's a perfect day for fishing.
They want to catch a bigfin
reef squid today no matter what.
I don't know if it'll be longer
than a person's height,
but they're there.
We want to catch them
no matter what.
I've been thinking passionately
since this morning.
Nobody has seen a bigfin reef squid
longer than a person's height,
so I want to show you.
I've been thinking passionately
since this morning.
Fishing starts. And then...
Something's wrong already.
- He's messing with us.
- Again?
He's messing with us at work.
You're giving Ryudomaru trouble.
No one will give Ryudomaru
jobs anymore.
My trousers are wet.
Come on, that doesn't matter.
Why do your wet trousers bother you?
But they caught bigfin reef squid
because of this.
It is caught by...
Caught it. Joji's catching it!
- Enjoji.
- You can do it.
He doesn't have seasickness
this time.
Yeah.
Bigfin reef squid!
Its big fin looks like a round fan.
It proves that this
is a bigfin reef squid.
This is the most expensive
among squids,
one of this size costs 5,000 yen.
Good, Joji.
Also...
Enjoji caught another one.
He caught a second one in a row.
It's here! Isn't it huge?
He caught five squid consecutively.
Impressive!
- Really impressive.
I knew he was lucky.
He has been doing it for 15 years
since our festivals.
So far, in The Quest,
the highest rating we got
was filmed abroad,
"What happens if we let the
hairdresser decide the hairstyle?"
That got us the highest ratings.
It's shocking.
He has to be lucky.
He brightens up the atmosphere too.
It's unusual for you
to praise someone so much.
Well, I like that guy.
He also gets on my nerves,
but when I get annoyed,
I can tell him frankly.
I'm fortunate.
Where would you be
without Mr Enjoji, then?
I'd be here.
It isn't like that.
After that, Sakamoto caught
a swordtip squid.
Mum also caught a bigfin reef squid.
But Captain couldn't catch any.
Oh, no. I'm impatient.
But this happens when you fish.
How frustrating.
Even so, here is what
they caught this day.
None is longer
than a person's height,
but the filming is certainly
going well.
That night,
the team went to the city
to look for an open restaurant.
Wow, I'm curious about this place.
"Royal Pub...
Sharlock."
It looks like that at the back?
- Captain.
- Yes?
Holmes is there.
Sharlock and Holmes.
Anxious.
The Royal Pub in a strange city.
- Full of mystery.
- This place...
It's difficult to go inside.
Hey...
Joji. Go on.
"Sharlock."
It's surprisingly bright.
Okay? Really?
- May we come in and film?
- Go ahead.
Excuse me.
Oh, there's karaoke.
It's a nice pub.
Thank you.
Okay, let's have a seat, then.
Okay.
Welcome.
Welcome to our pub.
What? Wait a minute. Mum?
I'm Sayuri.
Sayuri?
She looks like Mum.
She looks just like Mum.
- Do I?
- Yes.
You even have moles
at the same places.
Someone dressed the kimono for you?
You brought it here?
Yes, it's mine.
Yours?
- How do I look?
- It suits you, but...
you got changed into that... Mum.
There's no need to show us
the back of your neck.
There's no need to turn 360 degrees.
On the final day,
they leave the port
when the sun rises.
Nice.
I swear, I'll catch a bigfin reef
squid longer than a person.
In the name of
the exploration party,
they can't let it end like this.
Sakamoto catches the first squid.
It's here--
What's this?
Wrong! What's this?
What's that? Its mouth is huge!
It's a fish called John Dory.
It swallows small fish whole
into its big mouth.
It isn't our target,
but it's good luck.
Nice, nice!
But after that, they couldn't catch
anything for seven hours.
You didn't catch anything
for three whole days.
It's tough,
I want to catch a squid too.
I have no idea what's wrong.
But even while not knowing
what's wrong,
they kept on catching squid.
I cheered at that time,
but inside, I thought,
"Get off the hook!
Don't catch squid before me!"
- Longer than a person?
- Not "longer than a person."
Which part are you talking about?
How old? Who?
It can be tiny, I just want
to catch one squid.
Let's go somewhere else.
Casting a rod, then going elsewhere.
They keep repeating the process.
It's the period of patience.
Cheer for me.
Everyone, cheer for me.
You can do it.
At that time...
- It's here!
- Caught it.
The first one Captain catches
in three days.
Okay, this one is huge.
Here it is,
it's longer than a person!
Everyone, it's longer
than a person's height!
See? It's huge!
Can he catch a bigfin reef squid?
It's huge, it's huge. Huge!
It's huge!
It's huge.
Yes!
I'm happy.
He caught the bigfin reef squid
he's been wanting to catch.
The expedition party caught a total
of 22 bigfin reef squid.
The biggest one...
Oh, amazing.
It weighs 2.26 kilograms.
Impressive.
It is 94 centimetres long
when its tentacles are straight.
The big squid is longer
than a 3-year-old person.
Captain, it's big, right?
This is a little monster, right?
You don't catch one
like this often, right?
No.
Right?
But you must have been wondering
if any bigfin reef squid really
is longer than a person's height.
It is here.
It weighs 5 kilograms
and is 1.5 metres long,
it's a real monster.
We actually wanted to catch one
like this.
This is the biggest
bigfin reef squid we caught.
They'll end this
with making squid rice.
When I look at it again,
it's a bit big.
Also, I put it in ice,
so it shrank a bit.
Also, when a squid's nerves are cut,
it turns into the colour
we're used to seeing in sushi.
Thank you.
The gut is boiled
and added to rice with vinegar.
Stuff the squid with the rice.
It's heavy.
It's about the weight
of a water pillow.
It is ready after being cooked
in a special sauce for one hour.
Have a look at the cross section.
The squid is thick.
How does it taste?
Delicious!
It's absolutely delicious!
- It's surprisingly tender.
- Tender.
The rice is delicious too.
The tastiness of the seasoning
is monster-level.
Oh? That was a good comment.
It was a little monster,
but the taste is monster-level.
And it gradually shrank.
It shrank when we cooled it,
and shrank a lot after cooking.
That's all for Miyagawa Expedition.