"The Quest".
Today's first segment is...
Daisuke Miyagawa's Way
to Japanese Festivals.
One day...
Gosh, you startled me!
Mr Miyagawa,
the season of festivals has come.
Did I imagine it?
Somehow you look smart now.
Your vibes are a bit different.
- Because I'm wearing black?
- Yeah, you look a bit fit.
Because I'm wearing black.
I eat the same amount of food.
- I binge eat.
- That means you eat a lot?
Eat? Yeah, I think I eat
just as much.
The stages this time
are Kagawa Prefecture
and Hyogo Prefecture.
What's your impression
of Kagawa Prefecture?
Udon noodles.
The prefecture of udon.
Udon?
Is it udon?
From what we've been
talking about...
Oh, udon?
I can eat udon.
I can eat 15 portions
if they're the wriggly ones
like Osaka's.
I'll go to Kagawa Prefecture
and Hyogo Prefecture!
What festival is waiting ahead?
"This show was broadcast
9th of May, 2021"
Welcome to "The Quest".
Tonight, it's Daisuke Miyagawa's Way
to Japanese Festivals,
and Lotti Nakaoka's QTube.
- Wasshoi!
- Hello!
Hello!
Nice to meet you!
First,
it's Way to Japanese Festivals.
Filming this time
was really tough as well.
He made it last for 30 minutes
only with a rock last time.
It was worth watching.
Many people said
they were impressed.
They went, "You can hold a rock up!"
"You can easily pick this up, then."
They went,
"You can pick this up, right?"
I see, you hold it like a pro.
What?
This is Taga Hoop World Tournament!
All right!
"Daisuke Miyagawa's Way
to Japanese Festivals"
"Lotti Nakaoka's QTube"
"films funny videos in Okinawa"
Daisuke Miyagawa's Way
to Japanese Festivals.
He came to Shodoshima Island,
Kagawa Prefecture.
Wasshoi!
The place I have come to
is Shodoshima Island,
Kagawa Prefecture!
- Look at this!
- Beautiful!
This is called Olive Beach.
There are olive trees here,
that's Shodoshima Island for you!
Hey! Festival Guy
of Shodoshima Island!
Bring it on!
Our guide is
the host of the tournament,
Mr Yasuo Yamamoto,
5th Generation owner
of Yamaroku Soy Sauce.
- You make soy sauce?
- Yes, we're a soy sauce brewery.
Is this a festival or a tournament?
- It's a tournament.
- Tournament!
Is it a dangerous tournament or not?
If you continue to break the record,
it might hurt a bit.
It'll hurt? Because of soy sauce?
Or hurt your back a bit.
- Hurt my back?
- Yes.
Red and swollen.
- It'll be red and swollen?
- Yes.
No! I don't want to be
red and swollen!
They go to the stage this time,
Yamaroku Soy Sauce.
Mr Miyagawa, have a look at that!
What?
What did Miyagawa see there?
It's a man spinning a huge hoop.
What? I see, it's that one!
The name of the tournament
is Taga Hoop World Tournament!
You say it with force.
Taga is the hoop that holds barrels
or tubs together.
People spin it and compete
for the number of spins
in the Taga Hoop World Tournament.
The first tournament was held
in 2015.
Participants come from
all over the world
and it's always lively,
but it's cancelled this year
due to the pandemic.
Participants pray for it
to be held next year.
- People liken the hoop coming off
- Yes.
- to losing tension and relaxing.
- That's right.
It's that hoop.
The hoop comes off and it's broken.
This is the wooden barrel
that matters most
in soy sauce making.
Impressive!
It's an amazing technique.
Why did you start it?
The wooden barrel is important
in soy sauce making,
but only one percent of soy sauce
is made in wooden barrels.
In 2009, only one company
still has crafters
who make wooden barrels,
so we ordered new barrels from them.
We were the first soy sauce brewery
that ordered new barrels after WWII.
It's because they can be used
for 100 years.
The next order would be placed
100 years later.
I see.
The wooden barrel soy sauce making
on Shodoshima Island
has 400 years of history.
But it's costly, so the amount
produced reduces every year.
At the same time, companies
that make big wooden barrels
are also forced
to close their business.
That wooden barrel company also said
they don't know when they'll close,
so I thought
we could make them ourselves.
Mr Yamamoto started a wooden barrel
crafter revival project in 2011.
He gathers soy sauce manufacturers
in Japan here annually
and teaches them
how to make wooden barrels.
When we were weaving the hoop,
I thought it'd be funny
to spin it like a hula hoop,
so I spun it.
I thought it was quite fun,
so I made it a world tournament.
That's how it started.
Yeah, hula hoop is something
common globally.
- Right?
- Yes.
Now, he's going to practise.
There's a square in another colour
in the middle,
you'll spin it inside.
- I lose if I go out?
- Yes.
What? Really? It's strict!
- You lose like this, too.
- No way!
It's too strict, Mr Yamamoto.
The referee will blow the whistle
and stop you.
This is a Taga Hoop
with a 1.8 metre diameter
for the prelims.
The one used for
the world tournament is even bigger,
and its diameter is two metres.
Miyagawa will try it
using the 1.8-metre Taga Hoop.
- There's a secret to it, right?
- There is.
- Wait...
- What?
- No practise.
This is the tournament's rule.
Seriously?
It's the real thing at once?
- Yes.
- Today?
But we have a special rule
starting from the last tournament.
Please tell me.
You pay 100 yen
to practise for one minute.
What?
- It's charged. Yes.
- I have to pay?
We don't have a fund
to run the tournament.
But if you think about things
like how it'll look on air,
I want to practise,
even if I have to pay.
100 yen per minute.
- 10,000 yen for 100 minutes?
- Yes.
Expensive!
Are you kidding me?
100 yen per minute?
- 100 yen per minute.
- Indeed.
What rule is that?
- Will you practise?
- Yes.
Of course.
Please put 100 yen in here.
- It starts counting at that moment.
- No way!
Start.
- Practise starts.
- Hurry up!
It's like this? And...
Can Miyagawa do it?
He's good...
You're very good at it.
Despite looking bad,
Miyagawa is spinning the hoop.
But...
He's out!
- What? One minute is over?
- It was close.
It's fine, one minute.
It's okay now, right?
This isn't a tournament.
He's good at it...
But it drags you quite a bit.
- Oh, I get it.
- 30 seconds left.
Actually, Miyagawa's potential
is quite good.
Most people can't spin it once
when they spin it
for the first time.
I get the gist of it now!
- I can get it done with 100 yen!
- You can.
I can do it! With 100 yen!
I can do it with 100 yen!
15 seconds left.
I can do it!
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one. Finish!
Till it falls...
Let me do it till it falls!
I can't practise!
If I only think about money,
Then the weather got worse.
They go to the brewery
where soy sauce is made.
I'm coming in.
It smells very nice
even when I'm wearing a mask.
It's unrefined soy sauce.
Look at this wooden barrel.
The history.
It's amazing.
The wooden barrels
at Yamaroku Soy Sauce
are about 150 years old.
The barrels have live bacteria
called the Brewery's Treasure,
and they vary
from brewery to brewery.
That's why each shop
makes its unique soy sauce.
It has no additives and is made
in the traditional way. I'll try it.
- Looks delicious.
- Wow, it's delicious!
The echo came too soon.
Ordinary soy sauce
leaves a salty taste,
but this one leaves an aroma
and sweetness.
Sweetness exploded in my mouth.
Mr Yamamoto,
are you going to cook later?
- I'll cook.
- No, it's "Dining Al Fresco".
I thought I could eat udon
with egg and soy sauce, but no!
It's Taga Hoop World Tournament!
We have raw egg on rice
and grilled rice cake, though.
I want some.
Today's featured dish
is raw egg on rice.
- Break the yolk.
- It has to be good!
- I'll try it.
- It's irresistible.
- I'm jealous.
Oh, delicious!
What's this?
It's nice and aromatic,
and sweetness comes afterwards.
The soy sauce is rich,
but the taste is light.
Mr Miyagawa, please practise.
It costs 100 yen per minute.
If it costs 100 yen per minute,
I'll do it in the tournament.
I'll use the 500 yen I saved
to buy this!
Indeed.
The rain stopped,
so practise starts again.
The world record.
Tell me how many times it was spun.
It was 400.9 times.
400?
The 10th place spun 52.8 times.
- 10th?
- Yes.
What? I might be able to beat it.
He has a look at the world ranking.
And then...
The sixth place...
There's a name you know, right?
It's Kaneko!
- Kaneko spun it 209 times?
- Yes.
When Oceans Kaneko appeared
in a breakfast show,
he made a record
of spinning 209.6 times.
I can't let him beat me.
Miyagawa's soul of festival
is fired up.
He put in 100 yen readily.
I did it with this power just now.
It's impressive enough.
It isn't stable.
It's not by momentum.
But...
Oh, I spun it too high.
Oh, my neck!
He came out. It's strict!
He pays more!
- It's difficult.
- You can do it!
What should I do?
That costs me about 20 yen!
The time of the decisive battle
has arrived.
- Can we ask for the champion?
- Champion.
Please do it.
Let's ask him here.
- This is the champion, Mr Inose.
- He comes out of the brewery.
So cool!
Is that the trophy?
Somehow he looks strong!
This is the Taga Hoop
World Champion,
Tomoya Inose.
This man spun the 13-kilogram
Taga Hoop 400 times.
He is at the top of his game
with his overwhelming power.
When was the first time
you participated?
It was in 2017.
- 2017.
- Yes.
Why did you participate?
I also wanted to spread the culture
of barrel making,
so I wanted to participate
in the Taga Hoop Tournament.
How confident are you?
I want to defeat you!
I will go all out.
Champion, would you be my opponent?
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
Let's begin!
Taga Hoop World Tournament
Special Version starts now!
Held at Yamaroku Soy Sauce,
Taga Hoop World Tournament
Special Version has started.
Let me tell you the rules.
They'll compete
for the number of times
they spin the huge Taga Hoop.
But if the hoop touches the ground
or if their foot goes out
of the designated mat, it's over.
Five judges will measure the record,
their average number
will be the official record.
If Miyagawa wins,
the Legend Apron
given to the three-time champion
will be given to him this time
as a special case.
If the champion wins,
we'll give him a happi coat
with Miyagawa's autograph.
- Champion will go first.
- Champion.
- How will the battle go?
- It's thicker than just now.
Look at Miyagawa's
facial expression.
The moment of anxiety.
Now, the fateful match...
starts! Champion is spinning it!
Oh, the whistle is blown!
The whistle is blown!
Why?
Champion made a regrettable mistake!
Did that actually happen?
- Come on, champion!
- We'll watch in slow motion.
At the first spin, when the champion
started spinning the hoop...
The hoop touched the ground here!
Oh, it touched the ground.
What's the record?
1.1 times.
Oh, my goodness! 1.1 times!
Sorry, let me ask.
Are you really the champion?
Aggressive.
Okay, here goes!
Now, it's our Festival Guy,
Miyagawa's turn!
He'll win if he spins it twice,
but he aims to break
the world record, 401 times!
He picks up the Taga Hoop.
You can do it.
How is it going to end?
- Do your best!
- Approach run...
Now...
Start!
Miyagawa is spinning
the Taga Hoop stably.
It has already passed
the champion's 1.1 times!
He first aims to exceed
the 10th place
in world ranking, 52.8 times!
- Nice!
- It's stable.
He's spinning it well,
now it only depends on how much
his body can stand the damage.
It's going to be over 50 times soon!
He probably will rank the Top 10
in the world!
Exceeded 50 times.
Miyagawa spun over 50 times!
It's certain he'll be one
of the world's Top 10!
How much further can he go?
It must be tough.
Miyagawa said,
"One must remove the restraint
that suppresses one's limit to win."
Well said!
Oh, what happened?
The Taga Hoop is tilted!
But Miyagawa spun it back
to the original position!
This is Festival Guy
Daisuke Miyagawa!
Go!
- It has reached 100 times!
- Amazing!
He aims to break the world record!
The champion...
He will reach Kaneko's record
209.6 times soon, too!
- You can do it!
- We hope he'll continue!
Watch out...
Oh, the rhythm of spinning
is disturbed!
Can he hold out?
- He did! He survived!
- Watch out!
But it isn't stable yet. Hold out!
Oh, the whistle is blown!
It's over for Miyagawa now.
- You did very well.
- That was beautiful.
He spun the Taga Hoop beautifully!
I could've done more!
What's his record?
It's 135.3 times.
135.3 times!
"Record, 135.3 times"
What about the ranking?
You're in the eighth place
in the world ranking.
- Yay!
- Amazing!
He is in the eighth place
in the world ranking!
But may I say something?
- Champion.
- Yes?
- Would you try once more?
- Please let me.
Please show us your technique
and exceed your 400 times.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
1,000 yen per spin!
But this man
will make an extraordinary record.
Wow, oh, my goodness!
The champion is approaching
the world record 400 times!
Will the champion be able
to build a new pyramid?
That's a champion!
Do your best!
It's coming! 398, 399, 400!
It's over 400 times,
he broke the record!
Amazing!
Oh, did he relax?
The balance is off!
Spin it up!
- You can do it!
- Okay!
He held out!
He's exceeded the limit
of his stamina!
This way... Okay! Spin it up!
Spin it up!
Spin it up! Spin it up!
Spin it up! Okay, it's back!
The champion is incredible!
Twelve minutes after it started...
Mr Inose makes his own
carrot juice every day...
The hoop touched the ground!
Wow, impressive!
The champion demonstrated
his overwhelming strength!
- Amazing.
- What's the record?
714.5.
He spun an unprecedented
714.5 times!
He made a brilliant record!
How do you feel, champion?
It's the world's new record.
- Thanks to you.
- No.
You showed us something incredible.
Thanks for giving me a chance.
You aren't the guy
who spun once at first.
What makes this tournament
attractive?
I want to let the next generation
know about the wooden barrels,
and the hoops used for them.
I hope they will be passed down
for generations.
- It was wonderful. Thank you!
- Thank you.
We pray that the Taga Hoop
World Tournament
will be held again someday.
The next place he goes to is...
Wasshoi!
The place I have come to
is Shinonsen Town, Hyogo Prefecture!
Hyogo's Festival Guys!
Bring it on!
Our guide is an officer
at Shinonsen Town's town office,
Ms Taniguchi.
How long is the history
of the festival?
As a festival, it started in 1998,
the main event, that is,
the championship,
is held the seventh time.
Championship?
They go to the stage of the battle,
Hamasaka Port.
Mr Daisuke,
have a look at that!
What?
What did Miyagawa see there?
It's men shovelling something
into their mouths.
They're firefly squids.
It's the Japan
Wankohotaru Championship.
What?
In the Japan
Wankohotaru Championship,
participants must eat firefly squids
like Wanko Soba in two minutes,
and they compete
for the number they've eaten.
At the Hamasaka Port,
the peak of the firefly squid season
is from January to May.
About 1,900 tonnes of firefly squids
are caught annually.
Have a look at this!
They were boiled,
and they taste the best!
- May I try it?
- Yes, go ahead.
There are 10 squids in one bowl,
the weight is about 30 grams.
- It's a lot.
- One person can't eat 10!
Oh, delicious!
It's like sausages from the sea.
They're fleshy.
The liver inside
is absolutely delicious!
I can eat 500!
There are eight squids here.
How does it feel?
I'll try it once.
What does Miyagawa think?
He swallowed.
- How was it?
- No harm.
I can do it.
I really can.
- Will you practise once more?
- No.
Why did I eat 20 to practise?
I want to save it
till the real thing.
Can I try it
with vinegared miso, too?
Like this, right? And...
- He won't change the flavour?
- Like this, right?
How is it with vinegared miso?
What about vinegared miso?
You'd better not eat too much.
- He swallowed!
- It's quick!
He ate them at once.
You get the gist of it.
- Delicious.
- Stop it.
But it depends on how fast
the champion eats,
their body shape,
and how strong their throat is.
Keep watching this!
I might be able to win!
The time for the decisive battle.
Let's ask him to come.
- Already?
- At once.
This is the champion, Sumiyoshi!
- This person?
- A woman?
Oh, I see.
Wow, he looks like an athlete.
This man ate 207 firefly squids
in two minutes,
he is the absolute champion,
Takayuki Sumiyoshi.
- Nice to meet you.
Have you always been a big eater?
No, not a big eater,
it's only the speed.
I think the power of the throat
is the key.
- Yes.
- The power to swallow.
Just once...
Would you swallow once to show us?
It looks strong!
Let's begin.
Japan Wankohotaru Championship
Special Version starts now.
Special Version has started.
There are 10 firefly squids
in one bowl,
they'll compete for the number
of squids they eat in two minutes.
The squids are seasoned with ponzu
or vinegared miso.
If Miyagawa wins,
he'll be given Hamasaka's
most expensive brand snow crab.
Soon, the battle will begin.
- I can't wait.
- Miyagawa's facial expression.
What does that mean?
It's been a while.
This is fun!
Oh, Miyagawa doesn't look right.
It's been a while.
He feels emotional
on the stage of speed eating.
Before he fills his stomach
with firefly squid,
his chest is full of emotion.
- Okay!
- Miyagawa is fired up!
The match will be two minutes.
- Now, the fateful match!
- Go!
Start!
Both of them bolt down the squids!
- It's fast...
- It's fast!
They eat the second bowl in no time!
- Oh, Miyagawa, be careful!
- It's too fast.
- That was close! He held out!
He stares at one point already!
On the other hand,
the champion isn't stopping!
He's already eating the fifth bowl!
Miyagawa will catch up now!
Can he swallow these 10 squids?
He can't swallow! It's dangerous!
He looks up!
He swallowed them!
But his fighting spirit
is still there!
But the champion doesn't slow down!
All right!
Miyagawa is catching up
at high speed!
Oh, the champion seems to be
eating slower now!
You can do it!
And Miyagawa-- Oh, be careful!
He barely took the critical hit!
He held out somehow.
You can do it!
Miyagawa said he wouldn't end it
with glitter and sparkles.
Oh, what happened?
Squids are coming out? Be careful!
The squids...
He swallowed them back!
He held out!
Thirty seconds left!
Will the champion win?
Or Miyagawa?
Oh, the squid's tentacles stick out!
Can he swallow it?
- Can he?
- The music is dangerous.
He swallowed it!
Okay, the last spurt!
Miyagawa bolts down the squids
all at once!
It's dangerous.
Five seconds left!
Miyagawa is eating till it ends.
- It's over!
- He did his best!
Miyagawa is stupefied.
I'm off my game.
My throat got weaker.
It's different
from when I practised.
Somehow I was nervous.
My stomach shrunk
and it surprised me.
I've been wanting to spit them out
starting from the second bowl.
What's the result?
108.
Miyagawa ate 108 squids.
The champion's record is...
176.
The champion ate 176 squids!
The champion won!
What's the reason of his defeat
this time?
What is it?
The tentacles got me.
It nearly triggered the gag reflex,
I thought, "Oh, no!"
I was fighting it.
But I just ate half of the squids
put inside at a time.
This...
Do this, look.
- He swallows...
- Swallows?
I can't do it.
That's all for
Way to Japanese Festivals.
That was fantastic!
It doesn't matter how many you ate.
- The number doesn't matter.
- It doesn't.
It was so funny!
A lot of firefly squids.
Over 30 bowls, it went like this.
It's dangerous. Is it okay?
The familiar face is back.
- 108.
- I ate 108.
- The number of worldly desires.
- Yes, but I swallowed them.
People will talk again.
"It's a lot of firefly squids."
"You ate a lot of that."
QTube.
Did Lotti Nakaoka come to Okinawa?
He finally came?
That's right!
- Chatan?
- You figured out.
Lotti Nakaoka has come
to Chatan, Okinawa!
First, it's a prank video
as warm-up.
Upside-down mug.
We tell Nakaoka
it's a video to upload
to the show's Twitter account.
Put the cup next to your face.
- Like the mug is big?
- Yes.
The content is steaming hot coffee.
It's covered with a coaster,
the content will spill
if he takes it up.
Nakaoka, upside-down mug.
Wow, it's full.
Let's put it next to my face first.
- Here I go.
- He's totally deceived.
Something unexpected happened.
- It's stuck there.
- Does my face look small?
Amazing!
Whoa, it startled me!
- What's going on?
- Amazing.
- It's hot!
- It's late.
It's unusual to be surprised
by something so simple.
I thought the bottom fell off.
I thought the bottom was gone.
Next, it's a silly video.
Can he eat a raw egg in a bucket
filled with water?
It's dangerous. This is dangerous.
- Nakaoka, Egg in Water Challenge.
- You shouldn't do this.
First, pour water
into a specially made bucket.
I'll pour.
Sorry, the timing is wrong. Sorry.
When you said "pour",
I wanted to breathe air in.
The one last breath.
Pour after I regulate my breathing
and raise my hand.
- He looks like this?
- He tries again.
- He does it after a deep breath.
- I like that face.
It's funny already.
So cute! He looks like a baby!
- It's here, Sochan!
- You can do it!
Only the string went there.
Be careful!
I feel sick!
I took a deep breath, right?
I have to drink water
after I breathe in,
I can't do it.
That was a blind spot.
In that case,
do it after he breathes out.
- I see.
- Yeah.
Will he make it?
- Wow.
- He's calm.
- Good, he's calm.
- Oh, it's the wrong place.
The side...
- The side...
- I feel sorry for him.
The side...
The egg came, but he sucked the most
unwanted part of the white.
- That was genius!
- Thank you. Glad to hear that.
I saw someone who looked twice
in water the first time.
The egg yolk here,
you looked at the yolk here once.
Next, it's a video of an experiment
using sounds.
We have the help
of Mr Tenjiro's pupil, Mr Ebitani.
We connected an amplifier
to a speaker,
and put an iron plate
on the speaker.
Sprinkle table salt
on the iron plate,
and when we play a sound
on the speaker...
Amazing.
What...
What's this shape?
It is called a Chladni figure,
salt grains are repelled at places
with strong vibrations of sound.
They gather where vibrations
are weak and they form a pattern.
Interesting.
Patterns vary
according to frequency.
We'll do an experiment to see if
it can be done with Nakaoka's voice.
Not all sounds can make it
form a pattern.
Oh, really?
Patterns only form when the sound
is at a certain pitch.
Which singer can do it?
Someone like Mr Mera.
Mr Mera?
He tries with Mr Mera's voice.
Why did you choose "ke"?
It's blurred,
but a pattern is formed.
We recruited help to assist Nakaoka
stabilise his voice.
This is opera singer Mr Hibiki Kina.
It feels great!
Amazing!
I know how amazing it is even more
when I hear it live.
As a matter of fact,
Nakaoka has been saying he wants
to make opera singing a hobby.
He spent two whole hours
singing "Symphony No 9".
- Your voice is louder.
- Yes.
Now, the main topic.
Can Nakaoka's voice
make the salt form a pattern?
Do your best.
Nakaoka will sing "Symphony No 9"
as he wishes,
and tries by extending
the last note.
"Can Nakaoka's voice
make the salt form a pattern?"
What's this?
- What?
- Oops.
- No reaction.
- Oh, no.
Oh, something appeared.
- Nice!
- Oh, it's pretty!
It formed a shape
I haven't seen before.
It formed a beautiful pattern.
It formed a pattern!
I've been doing QTube
for seven years,
I've enjoyed this time the most.
Next, it's the world's
amazing technique video.
Climb on top of a huge balance ball
and do a forward roll.
It's so scary!
This time, he'll do it
on Okinawa's red clay soil.
It gets sticky
when it contains moisture,
so it's an outstanding cushion.
I might make it at once.
It might not be the muddy scene
you want to see.
Nakaoka, forward roll
on balance ball.
Will he make it in one go
as he claimed?
- Be careful of your neck.
- Wait.
It's impressive.
Stabilise...
The balance ball
isn't stable at all.
Stabilise!
- Stabilise!
- Be careful.
That's all.
It's not funny at all.
Nakaoka can't even balance
on the ball.
"The 5th time"
I can't do anything!
And the 21st time.
Thunder suddenly cracked.
Considering his safety,
this is the last chance.
- Is this Nakaoka?
- Ready, go.
What?
- It's so sad.
- Please let me off the hook.
Lightning is dangerous.
- It is.
- Let's go.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Tidy up the place, guys.
Leave me alone.
The thunder won't realise I'm here,
it'll think I'm mud.
It's the regular video selfie
produced and directed by Nakaoka.
I love this segment.
"Most comfortable and laughable,
Sofas"
Good.
Hello, we are Sofas.
Nice to meet you.
My partner, Sofa, looks like
he's been turned upside-down.
I went to play golf the other day,
someone asked if I was Sofa,
and I said yes.
I hit the golf ball,
it flew to the other side.
The caddy said, "So far!"
What the heck?
Thank you.
Zipline Nakaoka.
Wow, I'm scared, but it's fun!
Many staff members drew pictures
of Zipline Nakaoka for me.
Look.
This one, this one...
They are all Nakaoka.
I'm going to fire the person
who drew this.
Lastly, it's Captaincy Nakaoka.
This time, we'll work
with a girls' handball team.
Really?
We came to Okinawa Naha Nishi
Prefectural High School.
The handball powerhouse was
in the third place in the Nationals.
Who is your captain?
Captain, you have
a new captain today.
All right!
Hey!
I'm your new captain!
Who did you think would come?
- Yamapi.
- Yamapi?
What a shame, it's Nakapi.
What a shame.
They'll try to play "Symphony No 9"
by handball's jump shot,
like in this video.
"Nakaoka and girls' handball team
collaboration video"
This time,
they'll play it using bells
on a pole specially made
by our show.
Amazing!
The first half will be filmed
in several small segments.
The second half will be uncut,
they'll aim to hit 32 notes
consecutively.
It's a very difficult challenge.
First, they'll film the first half
in segments.
Okay, let's do it!
They try to hit eight notes
correctly in a row.
They don't ring.
It's difficult.
In this challenge,
hitting once isn't very difficult.
But it doesn't continue if they want
to hit the bells consecutively.
- It's difficult.
- Yes, it is.
This is bad!
The challenge itself
is difficult enough,
and various problems occurred.
- First, the strength of the poles.
- I see.
The power of the students
breaks the iron poles
from the roots.
- Fixing them wasted a lot of time.
- This is bad.
They realised
there was a critical problem
at the end of filming the first half
for five hours.
What?
I'm sorry.
It's the last part,
"do, do, re, mi, re, do, do."
The "do" has to be a low "do",
but we put the high "do" there.
They found out
they put a wrong bell there.
I'm sorry.
To make things worse...
I think something is wrong.
Not only "do", "mi" is wrong, too.
They put the correct bells back
and did a final check.
- Isn't that wrong?
- It's wrong.
All-- Hey, how many bells
did you get wrong?
Nakaoka called the crew outside.
Of course!
Of course, I would!
Oh, no...
You let high school students see
how careless
The Quest's QTube Team is.
"Maybe the sounds of the bells
are wrong."
"What? Let's check."
"Oh, it's wrong."
"Let's check one more."
"Oh, this is wrong. This is wrong."
Three out of six.
Fifty per cent.
That's half.
It's dreadful.
You got the wrong bells,
three of them.
The poles break.
The girls' spirit can't be lifted
by Nakaoka.
Maybe this is the biggest reason.
The challenge carries on
to the next day.
The bells are stronger.
Today, they aim to hit 32 notes
correctly in the second half.
- Yes!
- Let's go!
Nakaoka does the first shot.
They'll see how many they'll hit
out of 32.
Oh, nice!
Amazing. They've all improved.
It's quick!
They can hit at that speed?
The students practised
after filming yesterday.
The accuracy went up a lot.
- Impressive!
- It's impressive.
"Mistake, 1"
The last note is hit
by Nakaoka again.
Do your best!
"Mistake, 6"
It's difficult! I was so nervous!
We made several mistakes, right?
That already makes me nervous.
Someone made a wrong sound.
- My order was wrong.
- It was the order. I see.
I see.
They can't make even one mistake
in this challenge.
Their biggest enemy is pressure.
You were nervous just now!
You were nervous!
- Let's go.
- After trying for four hours,
a big chance came.
Good.
Nakaoka makes a regrettable mistake.
So close!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! Oh, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
I was so nervous...
Please do it once more.
A girl is just as nervous
as Nakaoka.
It's Goalkeeper Kaede,
who plays the 31st note.
After all, she usually doesn't make
any shot.
I'm sorry.
- That was bad.
- Yeah.
You were stiff.
In the chance that comes next...
- Go, go.
- What colour?
"Do".
They changed the order
right before they do it.
You ran away from pressure
last minute.
Let's not do that.
Don't be beaten by pressure.
The goalkeeper must work well
under pressure.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Last one!
In the 320th time they try,
the time finally comes.
Please listen to Beethoven's
"Symphony No 9,
4th movement, Ode to Joy".
I'm happy.
You can do it.
I'm counting on you!
Let's give it our all...
No! I hit it! I hit it a bit!
I hit it a bit!
Look, it's trembling!
Yes!
Okay! Yes!
You can do it.
Yay!
You're so noisy.
Don't shout, "Yay!"
Yay!
Let's go!
Now, they'll do the 32 notes
in uncut filming.
All right.
You can do it.
- The last seven notes.
- You can do it.
All right!
They did it successfully!
Yay!
We made it! I'm so happy!
I'm so happy!
You saved my life!
"You saved my life."
I thought I couldn't go back
to Tokyo!
Do your best to be
the national champion!
Yes!
Naha Nishi Prefectural High School
Girls' Handball Team,
thank you very much.