"The Quest"
Welcome to The Quest.
Today's show is Lotti Nakaoka's
Calendar Project
and Hot Spring Club's
Calendar Project.
It's two Calendar Projects!
Wasshoi!
"Morisanchu"
Hello...
Hello!
Hello, everyone!
"Soichi Nakaoka (Lotti)"
First, it's Nakaoka's
Calendar Project.
This time, it's a hot topic in
the Tokyo Olympic Games, surfing.
- What?
- Yes.
- You guys surf a bit too...
- Me and Asako.
- Mr Degawa also...
- I've tried wake surfing.
When you guys tried,
it looked like you failed...
No...
Hey...
Mr Uchimura,
how long did you stay there?
- What?
- "What"?
It felt like I stayed on the board
for 30 seconds.
It was shorter.
The water depth was 30cm?
No, it was 10cm.
It's 10 centimetres...
It was about 50cm!
It's 10 centimetres!
I didn't have time!
You practised?
Since July, when I went to film
at the previous location.
- That's petty.
- It's petty!
It isn't petty!
- That's petty!
- I only got two hours!
This is so petty!
This is totally petty.
It's not petty.
Please don't call
the effort I made petty.
Petty!
You must've filmed
something amazing, then.
I went too far, sorry.
Let's have a look, then!
Please don't do this!
"Lotti Nakaoka's Calendar, August"
This is impressive!
"He'll try surfing techniques"
"Oshima, Oniyakko, Okazu, Ganbare
on a cosplay tour in Mie, Gifu"
Members of The Quest
go to various places every month
to take beautiful photos.
We'll make a collection and aim
to complete the 2022 calendar.
The Quest Calendar Project.
Nakaoka goes surfing.
- He started practising in July.
- Petty. You started in July!
When he was filming QTube
in Hyogo...
Someone will help me!
For three hours every morning
before filming,
he trained intensively
at a wave pool in Kobe.
Surfing practise 1,000 times.
1,000?
People say practise 1,000 times,
but they don't actually do 1,000.
He had already practised 235 times
in four days.
This time, he practises repeatedly
at a wave pool,
and will learn techniques
of the highest difficulty.
You've outdone Chen!
We'll take a photo like this.
The star of surfing, tube riding.
Aren't you aiming too high?
Tube riding.
It's a bold technique done
in the tunnel of a breaking wave.
This is cool!
The stage is the newest wave pool,
Shizunami Surf Stadium.
Petty!
The pool is 160 metres long
in total.
For levels from beginners
to professionals,
it can create as many as 80 kinds
of waves.
There's also a surf shop
and a cafe.
Nakaoka will be practising here
and aim to take the best photo.
- Mr Uchimura can do it.
- The coach wants you.
Okay.
Music, start.
What?
"Hero"?
His coach is Amuro, whom everyone
talked about in the Olympic Games.
This is our special coach this time!
Wow! Impressive!
Impressive!
- Oh?
- What?
- It's Surfer, Amuro!
"Our cameraman messed up"
It's out of focus.
This is our cameraman Omori,
who has been one for 10 years.
- It's Omori!
- I have to film...
Miss Amuro clearly,
but it is out of focus.
"Out of focus in his 10th year"
Only film the part
when I leave the pool?
If possible, please surf again.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
Once more,
this time, the special coach is...
Wow, impressive!
It's the surfer, Amuro!
She'll go to America
three days later for a world tour,
but she agreed readily to be
his coach if it's just one day.
So cool!
I want to take this photo.
I think it'll be rather difficult.
- Obviously.
- Yes.
Waves rarely form "tubes" in the sea
in the first place,
and it's said that it takes 10 years
to learn this technique.
But we're at a wave pool this time.
It can create a wave that forms
a tube anytime freely,
so it depends on
how much effort Nakaoka makes.
First, he'll practise
with simple waves.
No!
But there's a small problem.
My feet can't touch the bottom.
-You have to paddle.
- This is bad.
The water is six metres deep
where the wave is,
and his feet can't reach the bottom.
Also...
Paddle!
It was the one just now.
It's much higher than Kobe's waves!
It uses air pressure sent from
the pool's bottom to create waves,
so big waves come suddenly.
It's scary.
Paddle! Paddle!
The result of his practise
beforehand doesn't help at all.
I see.
But it's impressive.
He runs out of strength at once.
I'm exhausted!
It was only four times.
He can't even return
to his starting place.
It comes again!
Like seaweed floating between waves.
Stop the waves!
As a result...
I have surfboard sickness.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm totally okay.
Please go surfing if you like.
- Okay.
- She's here for you!
Let's ride the waves with Amuro
and learn how to surf, then.
A surfer rides the wave sideways
and does tricks when surfing.
At competitions like the Olympics,
surfers are scored
on a scale of one to 10
according to the trick combination
and difficulty.
Everyone, this is Nakaoka!
I think you often see surfers
riding white waves,
but they're broken waves
that beginners ride on.
Skilled surfers ride on the face
of a wave, which is at an angle.
Manoeuvres are possible
only after you can ride on these.
This is very difficult!
Impressive!
He starts practising again
30 minutes later.
It was Amuro's kindness
that became his support.
Almost!
She never denies his effort
and helps him improve by praises.
This is fun.
Nakaoka has gotten back
into the swing of it.
Oh, you did it... Wow!
You made it!
That one was perfect.
- It was perfect?
- Yes, perfect.
I think it was a pass among today's.
What's the most important point?
It's paddling.
It's the most important in surfing.
It's paddle.
How is the paddling of a pro
different?
It's a paddling race between
Nakaoka and Amuro.
Nakaoka starts midway as a handicap.
I have to win like this.
No, I think I will win.
Start!
They start together.
Her entry is beautiful.
That's a bronze medallist for you,
the thrust of one row is strong.
Wow!
On the other hand,
Nakaoka doesn't go forward at all.
And then...
Wow, this is impressive!
Hey! Darn it!
Nakaoka is defeated miserably.
It's totally different!
She isn't short of breath at all.
Also, we'll inspect a pro surfer's
sense of balance.
They'll try surfing with hammock,
which Nakaoka had done before.
Can they stand
on a rocking surfboard?
Do your best.
Okay...
Be still...
Be still... I'll stand.
No!
What? Was it so difficult?
It's harder than taking
a tube surfing photo.
I think I won't fall.
- I think it's okay.
- I see, that's your goal?
Medallist Amuro tries it now.
You can do it.
Okay.
Okay...
Her body is...
The medallist fails instantly.
Oh no... You're funnier than me!
Oh no!
It's so hard!
I want to try again.
You want to try again?
That's the vitality that endeavours
on a global scale.
Oh no...
I change gear when I enter the sea,
and I'm determined to win a medal.
It's the fourth time she challenges
herself to this stupid trick.
Good... You can do it. Good...
You're standing...
Oh! You're standing! Impressive!
She finally does it successfully.
Wow!
The set makes it much more difficult
than last time.
The ropes are very long, we placed
the hammock low for safety.
I see...
What are you thinking, usually?
Day six of practise.
From now on, a legend in the surfing
circle will be his coach.
Champion of the year
of three Japan National Tours,
the legend had been a coach
of Japanese surfers
in the Tokyo Olympic Games.
This is Mr Masatoshi Ohno.
I heard you're too much of a legend
to be the coach of a beginner.
No, but I'll be very strict.
Whoa!
His goal today
is to ride a wave sideways.
He keeps practising.
Don't look down too often,
look at the direction you're going
when you stand on the board.
He corrects his line of sight,
and then...
- Amazing...
- Good job...
Good...
Good!
It felt so good
to ride the wave smoothly.
That's right.
Now Nakaoka's motivation
goes higher.
I'm getting close to success...
- Mr Nakaoka.
- You startled me!
You startled me.
- Practise?
- No, I'm here to teach you.
- Really?
- Yes.
Amuro is here again!
She keeps thinking about
Nakaoka's progress,
so she hurried here in private.
The legend pushes Nakaoka,
and the medallist checks it.
- Wow! Wow!
- This is amazing.
You should stand first,
then go sideways.
I see.
No, when he takes off at first,
- he needs to go at an angle.
- Oh...
But that's...
Our Japanese surfers are arguing.
Don't have a fight because of me!
Then, after he practised 406 times,
Nakaoka finally goes sideways.
Wow!
Amazing!
Ouch!
That one just now was good.
But it hurts!
Will he try a tubed wave next?
- Let's try it once.
- Let's do it once.
He finally tries to ride
a tubed wave.
It's the most difficult wave
at this facility.
A tubed wave is totally different
from the other waves.
The waves he's ridden so far
break along an angle,
so they're easy to ride.
A tubed wave rises gradually
when it breaks.
I see.
- Please watch this.
- Okay.
What is the wave like?
They planned to watch one, but...
You can't just look now, go.
- Go? Go?
- Yes.
The coach says go, so you'll go.
It started suddenly,
and he's engulfed by the wave.
I was washed together
with the board!
I was spun together with this.
This is really impressive!
It's so funny!
- You're still scared, right?
- He's scared.
His body is scared.
I'll be honest with you.
My brain is scared too.
As Amuro is here, we'll show her
how cool Nakaoka is.
A man who uses a drill to drink.
"A man who uses a drill to drink"
What's this?
He sucks it up?
Actually, it uses the spin
of the fastener.
Will Nakaoka be able
to drink up one litre of milk?
- Miss Tsuzuki is here.
- Oh.
Amuro is a huge fan of QTube.
Can Nakaoka show her
how cool he is?
Three.
Two.
One.
Oh, it's locked.
Gosh, this is...
Is it this way? Which way?
This is a gamble.
He unlocks it and tries again.
"Nakaoka drinks milk with a drill"
It's the other way.
He reverses the spin
and tries again.
"The 3rd time"
Wait, it's slow.
Isn't it slow?
It isn't at the highest speed?
It's awfully inadequate!
Correct all the faults.
- Three, two, one.
- Can Nakaoka do it?
"We are very sorry"
Almost!
It was going well, but the last sip
went into my windpipe.
- You'll try?
- Yes.
I'm scared, though.
No, don't try it!
We can't let you do it!
Amuro, please use your guts
for surfing.
Day seven of practise.
The pool is closed on this day,
so Nakaoka is trained indoors.
Take-off is the key.
Nakaoka's weakness
is that he is slow to stand up.
If you compare
the two kinds of waves,
on the left, when he stands up,
although he is still above the wave,
a tubed wave is fast,
so he has already gone down.
It's here. Go!
He practises this
200 times in a row
to let his body memorise it
thoroughly.
He looks determined the 200th time.
The wave doesn't come.
Day eight.
He wants results for his practise,
but he's struggling again today.
"615th wave"
"654th wave"
Darn it!
Maybe it's impossible to ride
a wave of this level.
It's not bad, though.
But a light shines on Nakaoka.
Wow! He did it!
He did it!
He managed to ride it on his knees.
It's Nakaoka's style,
but I went pretty far!
Kneeling is an original style,
but he creates new patterns
one after next.
Upright kneeling-style.
Also,
a style like offering prayers
to something.
It looks cool!
Wow!
Savanna Yagi's style.
Brazilians, do you hear me?
He trains himself hard
till the night.
Wow...
Kneeling has become stable.
If he enters a tubed wave kneeling,
it'll be the first time in history
and it's interesting.
There's potential.
The number of waves
Nakaoka has ridden is 833.
A part of me thinks
I should save some energy,
but when I start,
I just keep surfing.
I just paddle and ride a wave.
When I thought I must consider
tomorrow,
another wave comes.
The last day has come.
It's sunny and the pool looks blue,
the condition is amazing.
Good, the weather is good.
Nakaoka shows how well he surfs,
right at the start.
The last day has come.
Nakaoka shows how well he surfs,
right at the start.
Wow! Amazing!
- Impressive!
- Good.
He does a long ride to shallow water
right at the start.
That one just now was good.
- Wow!
- He was in the wave.
He does one more after that.
"835th wave"
Wow!
He's good!
It's a super-long ride,
longer than the one just now.
Wow, he didn't flip over!
That was amazing!
This photo is so cool!
It's really good!
They took a very good photo,
but he isn't in a tube.
We plan to go deeper in the tube.
Cameraman Kumano
is fussy about it.
It took a long time after this.
His standard is whether the wave
is above Nakaoka's head or not.
No tube.
I know, but...
He wants to go inside the tube,
even for a second.
Nakaoka rides 1,000 waves
by sheer determination.
You can do it!
Argh!
It has been five hours
since he started.
It's approaching the time limit,
so this is the last wave.
He's in. He's in it, right?
Was he inside?
He was in it for a second, right?
I did it, didn't I?
It was right before he fell.
This.
Now that he mentions it, he seemed
to be in the wave for a second.
What is Kumano's judgement?
Well, you didn't look good.
He doesn't look good.
He's in the wave, though.
Whether it's beautiful or cool,
it's just a matter of looks.
It's okay if I'm cool as a person.
Someone who cares about safety
is more cool.
Among the photos taken this time,
which one is chosen
to show in the calendar?
Let's ask Amuro, who is in America,
to have a look.
This one.
Oh, it's cool!
I'd like to show you
the manly look on my face.
Can you see this?
This is how I look.
Oh? A pro of the line of sight.
Your line of sight is a pro's.
So this photo will be included
in the calendar.
Amuro, do your best
in the world tour!
Impressive!
Let's say he's in the wave
like that.
The photo itself is cool too.
She came to visit you in private.
She came on day one,
went back after that,
then she spent about two hours
to come to see me
because she was worried.
Maybe she has a crush on Nakaoka?
Impossible.
At once! Why not?
Let us fool around for a bit!
Okay, next, it's this.
Hot Spring Club's Calendar Project.
Yay!
What tour is this?
This time, it's a cosplay tour.
Eh?
What? What? What?
A cosplay tour.
What is it?
You don't have to do cosplay.
We did it.
3.5 hours away from Tokyo,
Hot Spring Club goes on a tour.
The Quest Calendar Project
in Mie and Gifu.
First, they came to Mie Prefecture's
Iga Ueno Castle.
We've come to...
Mie!
The tour starts
with these four people.
They'll try wearing various
cosplay-like outfits
and take a photo of a good moment
for the calendar.
Mr Nagata is interested in it,
isn't he?
He only wants to see our cosplay.
He's smirking...
when watching, and rewinds,
watches again and rewinds.
Ew!
- "Ew!"
- It's me who wants to throw up.
You're blushing so hard!
Your glasses are cloudy.
Their cosplay tour starts now.
They've come to the Akame 48 Falls.
It's said that the Iga Ninja
used to train themselves here.
First, they'll try to take
a ninja-like photo.
Okarina, you wanted to be a ninja?
Yes, I dreamt to become a ninja,
I look up to people
who walk silently.
Do you get it? Like he's there
before you realise.
Mr Yotaro and Mr Masuda will teach
them how to do the ninja training.
Okarina said it.
You walk soundlessly.
Is that possible?
It's stealthy steps, right?
You lift your foot up,
then put it down.
Lift it up, put it down.
Then you can walk soundlessly.
Really? You made a bit of sound.
- No...
- She's awful!
- Because it's gravelled.
Lift up your foot,
put it down.
- It's okay, right?
- It is.
- Like this.
- Mr Masuda, you're competitive.
Now, the training starts.
She's fast.
At the Ninja Training Village,
you can experience Iga School's
Akame Ninja Art.
First, it's climbing.
Ninja can cross a high wall
without difficulty.
It's high.
It must hurt!
Ow...
Be careful!
Wow...
Be careful... She fell.
Then, in the Ninja House,
there are various gimmicks hidden
for escaping from the enemy.
What's that?
She went up there, didn't she?
Blue Ninja!
This is the Mizugumo technique,
which lets the ninja cross a river
without getting wet.
Go.
Blue Ninja!
Impressive.
Blue, well done.
Next, they'll defeat an enemy
in the dark when they can't see,
with a technique called Zasaguri.
They'll probe with a sword sheath
to locate the enemy.
He's searching.
The moment he finds it...
he kills it with one strike.
Impressive!
We prepared this for you.
What's this?
- This is...
- Oh no.
Wow!
- I get excited holding this.
- Yeah.
Okarina, will you have a match
with Mahiru again?
We'll see that again?
Last time, in the swordplay match...
Don't grab!
You shouldn't grab!
I'm going to grab you
the whole time when you do it!
Try that! I'll hit you even so!
They fought fiercely
and ignored the game.
She keeps getting hit!
What will happen this time
in the Zasaguri competition?
They're blindfolded and start after
they turn in a circle three times.
Wow, how can they go forward
so quickly?
She took it! She took it!
She took it!
What fight is this?
Be careful.
- It's fierce!
- Stop it.
She's strangling Mahiru!
Stop! Stop!
Wait... what are you doing?
It's the wrong sport.
They fought silently.
- You couldn't make any sound?
- Why didn't you make any sound?
It's like the fight
I'd seen on the street.
"Female Ninja Fighting
on the street"
- No way!
- This isn't a calendar!
Don't say "October," idiot!
Next, they'll learn about
Seki Blades in Gifu.
- Excuse me.
- I'm curious about many things.
The Yoshida father and son here
are swordsmiths.
We're swordsmiths of Seki.
I've heard about Seki Blades.
Seki City, Gifu Prefecture is known
as the City of Blades.
The traditional
sword forging technique
has been passed down
since the Kamakura period,
it is still inherited nowadays.
They'll see a real Japanese sword.
You pull it out like this.
- Wow!
- Impressive!
It's the first time
I see a real one!
It was owned by a warrior
400 to 450 years ago.
She tries to hold it.
It's a bit scary.
Is it okay to look like this?
Wow!
It's so cool!
They're both blades,
but a Japanese sword is forged in
a way different from a common knife.
Impressive.
They now try to forge a sword.
Cosplay?
Usually, only qualified people
can wear the costume,
but it's special today.
I feel sombre.
Yes...
Seki's sword making is passed down
as a religious ritual,
they even start the fire to use
from iron.
Wow!
- Impressive!
- You started a fire in a second?
Wow!
Impressive.
In that one second?
This time, they'll learn how
to forge a Japanese sword,
and make a knife.
The raw material is good quality
steel made from iron sand
called Tamahagane.
It is heated and rolled thinly,
then it's put on a lever and forged.
Air is sent from bellows
and it's heated.
The piece of steel becomes red
at once.
Impressive!
Now, it's the forging process.
Okay.
First, it is hit to make a cut.
It is folded...
Wow.
To make a double layer.
It's double-layered?
This process is called
"fold forging."
Wow!
The process of hitting it strongly
and folding is repeated,
impurities are hammered out
and it makes the carbon uniform.
Impressive!
The sparks...
The extra components are hit out
as sparks,
and the steel becomes strong.
I see.
Hit it right after it's taken out,
steel cools very quickly.
They first practise
by hitting a wooden stick.
Oops.
Well... The first time
was the most...
Oh, I missed the first one. Sorry.
Is it hot if sparks fly to my face?
- It is.
- Oh, I see.
Now, they do it for real.
- Do your best.
Okay!
Oops. Hang on.
- "Hang on..."
- Hey...
I'm sorry.
I got scared.
They change gears and start again.
- Okay!
- Alright!
Put it down.
- They fly.
- It's a lot of sparks.
Wow.
Okay!
What... which one?
Hit it or not?
I have no idea!
Wait a minute!
- What did that "okay" mean?
- I don't know.
That "okay" meant it's done.
It was really bent.
They'll use the power of a machine
to shape the forged steel
into the shape of a knife.
Impressive.
Next, apply a special clay called
Yakibatsuchi on the blade.
Wow, it's a knife already!
This is an important step
to blow life into the blade.
Apply a thin layer on the part
that should be hard,
and a thick layer
on the other parts.
The blade with clay applied
is heated to 800 degrees,
then it's put into water
to cool rapidly.
The process is called quenching.
It's amazing.
The steel's hardness is changed
by doing so.
The part with a thin layer of clay
cools quicker, so it becomes hard,
and the part with a thick clay layer
cools down slowly,
making it flexible.
The difference is what gives
the Japanese sword its pattern,
Hamon.
It's a beauty that comes from
the expert's technique
that pursues
sharpness and toughness.
And this is the finished knife.
The pattern is there.
- The Hamon is there clearly.
- Wow!
- Nice.
- It's very sharp.
It's sharp.
She does it in this costume...
Delicious.
We blew life into this,
shouldn't we name it?
Should we call it Nukumasa?
The kanji "On" of "hot spring"
and Mr Masaya's "Masa."
So, "Nukumasa."
- Amazing!
- Thank you.
It's elegant.
"Named by Okarina: Nukumasa"
One of the choices for the calendar
is the photo shown,
which captured a beautiful moment.
It's cool!
Next, it's a new sport
that originated in Mie Prefecture.
- A table-tennis table.
- Yeah.
- Hello...
- Hello.
Its designer Mr Murai
is expecting them.
Designer?
- Is this table-tennis?
- It is, right?
Usually, the ball goes above the net
in table-tennis,
but this goes beneath it.
- What?
- What's that?
- This is the ball.
- It makes a sound.
It makes a sound.
It doesn't bounce.
This is Lifelong Sport,
SS Ping Pong.
It is based on the parasport
Sound Table Tennis,
so even people who are
sight-impaired can enjoy
this universal sport.
You get a point if the ball touches
the opponent's end frame,
but you lose a point if it goes out.
Even without special skills,
the rally continues to some extent.
This is bad, I can do this forever.
This is fun!
- You'll have a match.
- A match?
The winning team will get
Matsuzaka Beef.
What?
You can have Sukiyaki Hot Pot.
Wow...
Will you do it?
- Of course!
- Let's do it.
It's seniors against young people,
Team Showa versus Team Heisei.
- I'll start.
- Okay.
Team Showa is at a disadvantage
when it comes to stamina.
A chance.
"Team Showa vs Team Heisei: 0-0"
Yes!
"Showa vs Heisei: 0-1"
Heisei's point.
It's "Kite" again.
- I said don't use "Kite!"
- I was thinking about the beef.
It's "Kite" again!
They try to keep up for the beef.
"Showa vs Heisei: 0-2"
Yes!
"Showa vs Heisei: 1-2"
Matsuzaka Beef!
But Team Heisei is younger,
their movement is sharper.
They got the match point
and led by a huge margin.
- It's the match point.
- So quick.
It'll be a sweeping victory.
Even so, Team Showa
doesn't give up till the end.
"Team Showa vs Team Heisei: 2-10"
Good.
Do your best!
Good, it's interesting.
It's a long rally.
This rally is long enough.
Yes!
"Showa vs Heisei: 3-10"
Just score the point.
A good match.
This is good.
Yes!
Game set.
Team Heisei gets a Sukiyaki Hot Pot.
But they don't know
how to do a food review.
They relied on Ms Murakami
the other day.
The look on Okarina's face
is super evil.
They've come to Wadakin, a famous
restaurant established in 1878.
They'll have Sukiyaki course meal,
Matsu, which costs 18,200 yen.
A waitress called Yakite
serves the beef in its best state.
Sugar, tamari soy sauce,
and a little kombu stock are used
to bring out the flavour
of the beef itself.
This is the ultimate Sukiyaki.
Looks delicious!
This is awesome!
They try it now.
Please review.
Just one bite...
What a waste!
Does she know how much it costs?
She eats like it's in a dream.
Delicious! It can't be more tender!
This is thick,
but it melts the moment
I put it in my mouth.
The fibres are fine,
the juice flows, flows,
flows along the fibres
and my mouth is full
of the juice of meat.
"A unique food review"
No... this is wrong!
Don't use it here!
Next, they'll stand-up paddleboard
and cruise along a river.
This is Miya River
in Mie Prefecture.
The clear river is known to be
Ise Jingu's river for purification.
There is a stunning view
at its upper stream.
It's so clear!
It's very clear!
- What's this?
- It's so transparent!
- It's transparent!
- Wow!
In fact, in the national
water quality surveys,
Miya River had been
in the first place 11 times.
It feels like I'm floating in space!
It is so transparent,
that it gives you the illusion
that you're at a high place.
As you're here, why don't you have
a boxing match again?
Why?
We are so serene now.
Let's do SUP boxing.
Will it be settled this time?
Mahiru versus Okarina.
Okarina,
now we can only have a conversation
with our fists.
Be careful...
It hasn't started!
Stop it! That's nasty.
Hey!
Stop it!
Okarina hates it.
Don't be ridiculous, jerk!
The match starts!
They fall.
So early.
My leg is still on it!
Wow!
Fall! You'll also fall!
You jerk!
Stop it.
The match is over.
Next, they've come to a mountain
in Gifu Prefecture.
Oh?
Hello.
Yui P and Oniyakko join them here.
Actually, this place is Sekigahara.
Wow...
The Battle of Sekigahara.
Who would come to power
after Hideyoshi died?
The Eastern Army led by
Tokugawa Ieyasu
and the Western Army
led by Ishida Mitsunari
fought a decisive battle.
The place they're currently at is
Ishida Mitsunari's headquarters,
Mount Sasao.
This is the place where a total
of 160,000 soldiers in both forces
occupied and fought.
They faced the opposite mountain
and fought below.
- What?
- On two mountains?
It's romantic.
You had no idea, right?
- You don't know, do you?
- You don't know that.
So I want you to fight
the Battle of Sekigahara.
What do you mean?
That's why you called them here?
I thought that was why
we were asked to come.
Isn't it too few?
Ask more people to come!
This is Sekigahara
Mount Sasao Exchange Centre.
The Armour Experience that
lets you transform into a warrior
is a popular attraction.
This time, they'll borrow
the costumes here
and take a photo
of the best moment in a swordfight.
Their teachers are...
We are Old Battlefield Hospitality
Warrior Team, Sekigahara Unit.
Let's go!
It's the members of Sekigahara Unit,
who advertise Sekigahara.
First, they learn the basics,
how to draw a sword from its sheath.
Then, put the sword back in
the sheath without looking.
Put it back.
It looks easy at a glance,
but putting it back is difficult.
You're cutting yourself.
The trick is to trace the back
of the sword with a finger.
- Wow!
- It goes in if you trace it.
Next, it's the way to wield a sword.
Wield the sword like
writing the kanji of "rice,"
and slay while taking a step.
This is the basics.
I see.
She's fired up.
- It's strong.
- Good.
Why do you stab?
Then, the main topic, a swordfight.
There was no sound at all
just now, right?
Actually, the swords
don't hit each other.
Stop right in front.
This is made of wood.
In fact, many swords used in
swordfights are made of wood.
They break if they really
hit each other,
so they need the acting skill
to stop right before that.
It's difficult.
From now on, they practise
sword fighting on their own.
We aim to take a photo
for the calendar
during the real battle scene.
Original period drama,
"Oshima Taiheiki."
In the civil war period,
the Oshima Army joined
the decisive battle,
but in front of the enemy's
overwhelming fighting power,
their situation is desperate.
General,
our army is almost wiped out.
10,000 soldiers in the enemy's force
are right there.
What?
Is that true?
What should we do?
Hey, be quiet!
But General Oshima, at this rate,
the enemy is going to come here!
General Oshima,
please at least escape alone!
Be quiet!
I shall not escape!
My friends and comrades
are in this camp.
Oshima!
Who is there?
General Oshima, it's already over.
Everyone, thank you
for following me for so long.
Thank you...
- Who wrote the script?
- Let's go!
The battle starts!
Oshima!
It seems your game is up.
- Darn you, P.
- She looks strong.
Your body is like
a Boy's Festival doll.
Isn't it funny?
Sakon, give me that.
Do you know what this is?
She took out a prank bomb
that the Oshima Army didn't know.
We aim to take a more realistic
photo by using this.
Should I throw it?
Should I throw this?
Stop it!
What?
What are you doing?
This is how I fight!
It's so heavy
that I couldn't run far.
It's scary!
My heart... It's scary!
Everyone, attack!
The battle finally starts.
They'll perform the swordfight
they practised
and take a photo for the calendar.
The General is there!
I can't tell who is who.
- What is that?
- It's awful.
Yoshiko's movement is good.
The warrior waited for her.
- What is it?
- Not like that.
This isn't what I expected.
It's different.
Oh, this isn't right.
Good.
She's defeated.
I must not fall!
It's wrong.
Because...
This...
costume is...
expensive!
So she can't fall?
Everyone, we'll escape!
Fall back!
Let's end this with an explosion!
Impressive!
Wow!
This is great.
Isn't this stupid?
This is impressive!
Okarina runs away
like a common foot soldier.
The look on each of their faces
is quite good.
We took a realistic photo.
So this photo is chosen
for October's calendar.
That's all for the Cosplay Tour.
Somehow it wasn't what I expected.
What?
And the script after
you started acting.
It was awful.
They must not do this behind
any epic drama.
The last part when they ran,
and "boom!"
Don't put "October" there, idiot!
What is so "October" about this?
That's not October!
What was that "October"?
People will think highly of it
sometime later,
it's criticised now, though.
Van Gogh couldn't sell his work
when he was alive.
It was after a very long time.
You mean after we die?
After a very long time,
people will go, "This October!'"