When I look up at the sky,
it makes me want to cry.
Oh no, oh no.
"The Quest"
"This programme was broadcast
6th December, 2020"
The Quest has started.
Tonight, we have rare animal hunter
Imoto, a Japan Tour, and...
Gone Forever.
"Ayako Imoto, Daisuke Miyagawa,
Asako, Ito, Tetsuro Degawa, Miyazon"
"Kazuko Kurosawa, Miyuki Oshima
Tomoko Murakami"
"Imoto Japan Tour in Okayama,
She'll try that sport again!"
- This is super hard.
- Right?
This is nerve-racking.
Am I doing bypass surgery?
I never fail.
It's not about fishing here.
I got one already.
So I put this on?
Have you seen a doll like this
in a museum?
Aiming to conquer
all 47 prefectures of Japan!
Rare Hunter Imoto,
Japan Tour.
She's going to Okayama this time,
known for its many
Momotaro legends.
Hello! It's Imoto!
I'm here in Okayama.
Where am I?
Now, it's the usual "Find Imoto"!
Is she all the way at the top?
No, all the way on the left.
- I'm here! I'm here!
- Where is she?
- I'm right here!
- That was impossible.
- You couldn't find that.
- The correct answer is...
- I was being part of...
- That's hard.
the Mizushima Industrial Complex.
You can't see that!
A vital part of Okayama's industry,
Mizushima Industrial Complex.
Its overall area is equivalent
to 520 Tokyo Domes,
and it contains over 220 businesses.
It's Japan's leading heavy chemical
industrial complex.
This is a prominent steel mill
in Japan, JFE Steel.
Wow!
That's beautiful!
- It's like fireworks.
- Amazing!
This is the refining process.
Molten iron is poured
into the furnace,
and all impurities are removed...
- by chemical oxidation.
- It's red.
This is impressive.
It's like a show.
- I'm no longer impressed by it.
- What?
Molten iron is cut into different
shapes while it's still hot.
There's a roll called a "work roll"
inside this chunk.
When the plates go through it,
it's gradually pressed down.
This steel mill operates 24 hours.
It produces eight million tonnes
of steel annually.
We have someone from Tottori
in our company as well.
What school are you from?
Yonago Higashi High.
That's a super smart school.
- You're from Yonago Nishi High.
- Yes, I'm from Yonago Nishi High.
What is Yonago Nishi High like?
Yonago Nishi High is known...
- for their beautiful girls.
- Thank you very much.
It's true.
It's true. That's local knowledge.
Yonago Nishi High is known to have
cute girls.
I won a beauty contest
at that school.
- Really?
- Let's start the Okayama Tour!
The reason she's in Okayama
is to attempt this challenge.
It's highlining.
Highlining in Okayama?
I've never heard of it.
Slacklining is done by balancing
on a thin belt.
Highlining is slacklining done
at great heights.
Imoto challenged it
in the United States a year ago,
but she was so terrified that
she couldn't complete it.
- This is scary! It's terrifying.
- It is terrifying.
- This is scary.
- I practised for a day..
and then I was taken 100 metres
above ground level.
That was a traumatic experience.
- Okayama has a highlining expert.
- There he is.
He's on it already.
Toru Osugi,
the first Japanese slackliner
to become a world champion.
In highlining,
he achieved a crossing
of 101 metres last year.
In Okayama?
Yes, at a place called Ojigatake.
Imoto will practise for four days
while continuing her Japan Tour.
She will challenge highlining,
overlooking the Seto Inland Sea.
Do you think I can do it?
If you think you can do it,
then you'll be able to do it.
If you practise thinking
that work is making you do it,
then it will be impossible.
Honestly, until you said that,
I came here thinking,
"This is my job,
so I have to do it."
So then, what am I doing
slacklining for?
To show everybody you can do it...
- when you attempt it.
- That's it.
I think it might be impossible.
She'll think about the reasons
for doing it later...
She'll report on Japan's best
in Okayama!
This is the place.
Amazing!
- Those are uniforms.
- There are a lot here.
That's cute.
Okayama is the largest producer
of school uniforms in Japan.
About 70% of school uniforms
in Japan are made here in Okayama.
So now, let's update
Imoto's uniform!
I've always worn the sailor-style
uniform, so I admire blazer types...
What should it be now?
- Like what Nogizaka is wearing?
- No way.
Hope is rising.
For this 34-year-old.
She'll select one from the uniforms
that are offered to her.
This is cool too.
This part is sailor style, but
this bit is more like a blazer.
This one combines sailor style
and blazer together.
It's currently a popular design
called a sailor jacket.
These are gender-neutral uniforms.
What are gender-neutral uniforms?
Female students can wear trousers,
and choose between
a tie or a ribbon.
I admire this one too.
A one-piece dress style.
This reminds me
of an all-girls group.
This is interesting too.
That part comes off.
This chequered part can come off.
- The uniform Imoto selected is...
- Which one?
Hi, I'm Ayako Imoto, also known as
Imorin with Nogizaka48.
- Imorin?
- Imorin.
It's 46.
So what do you think, Miyagawa?
Do I look good in this?
- I'm so glad!
- He's silent.
That much?
How about you, Degawa?
- What? Mai Shiraishi? No!
- Well...
That's too much of a compliment.
How about you, Uchimura?
- No one's saying anything.
- I'm about to cry.
Why is she about to cry?
Now that she's updated her uniform,
let's get her new shoes.
This is Mr Watanabe from
the sales planning department.
The world's highest peak.
You won't slip...
Your tongue was actually slipping
just now.
Nisshin Rubber spent
10 years developing...
these anti-slip shoes, Hyper V.
Their secret is in the soles.
What? This won't slip?
Yes, that's right.
It's not like the treads
are that deep.
The V-shape and the slanted sole.
This will repel water
and it won't slip.
Even on a stainless steel slope
covered with oil...
That's a bit...
You're right.
- It doesn't slip.
- It's not slipping at all.
Hyper V is amazing!
Wow!
It's like an NTV shop.
Now, let's do a slippery experiment.
If you are in Hyper-Vs,
can you win a slippery tug of war
against three people by yourself?
The Nisshin Rubber team is wearing
ordinary shoes.
Ready, go!
- Imoto!
- Amazing.
The Nisshin Rubber team is being
pulled as soon as it begins.
On the other hand, the Hyper-Vs...
display an impressive grip.
And then...
Yes!
- Hyper V is awesome!
- It's amazing.
Yes!
- Hyper V!
- Amazing.
However, suspicions were raised.
There's a possibility...
that this is what they want.
They want to show how impressive
Hyper V is to everyone in Japan,
so it's better for them
if Hyper V wins this match.
I'm starting to feel...
that I might be participating
in something outrageous.
Then let's have another match.
It's Nishimoto with Nisshin Rubber
in Hyper Vs versus The Quest team.
We won't slack off at all.
We're dead serious.
- The firm's future is on the line.
- Yes.
This will be broadcast,
even if you lose.
We will do this in earnest.
Start!
Come on!
The Quest team
is unable to stand firm.
Seconds after they start,
Imoto falls.
We want to show you a serious match.
Come on!
It looks fishier than before.
- Pull! Don't lose!
- You want their advert?
This is the fate of the show's team
dealing with a slippery surface.
Meanwhile, she continues
to practise her highlining skills.
She had an unexpected guest
this day.
- Who is the guest?
- By the way, who is that?
He's the Governor.
Did you supply him
with the school uniform?
- Of course not.
- Okayama's Governor?
What? Wait. They're coming this way.
We are so grateful that you came
to Okayama...
- we would like to cheer you on.
- Amazing.
If you have some time,
please join me.
Usually, you wouldn't take up
the offer...
but the Governor of Okayama
is serious about hospitality.
If you could see
how much it shakes...
It's quite-- Oh!
It shakes this much?
It's a lot more--
Right? Thank you, Governor.
Right?
Is someone shaking this?
The Governor knows
how to do his job.
- Okay.
- He's amazing.
It's fine. Go ahead.
Be careful.
Be careful. Governor!
- Governor!
- Wow!
- Amazing.
- Governor, be careful!
Aren't you shaking it?
That was all you, Governor.
- You're good.
- Thank you very much.
- In just a few days?
- I've been practising hard.
- Thank you very much.
- The governor completed his job...
and left.
Now, back to Japan Tour!
Next up, rare animals in Okayama!
This is it.
There it is!
A Japanese giant salamander!
The Japanese giant salamander
is a special natural monument,
that hasn't changed its form much
in 30 million years.
Yubara Hot Spring in Maniwa,
Okayama...
is Japan's famous habitat
of the Japanese giant salamander,
chosen by the government.
It blends in with the rocks,
you really can't tell it's there.
- It really does.
- It's hard to spot them.
What do they eat?
They mainly eat fish.
- They eat fish?
- Yes.
They chew them to eat them?
- They go "Gulp!"
- Oh, I see.
They gulp them down in 0.05 seconds.
In 0.05 seconds?
That was fast.
Today, we'll observe
an ecological survey of them.
The Japanese giant salamanders
they catch are weighed and measured.
Their health is examined,
and an IC chip is implanted.
It's done using a syringe.
It's policy to implant it
in their left shoulder.
- It's going in.
- This is how we do it.
- That looks painful.
- That must hurt.
It hurts a little. It's fine.
Okay, it's all done!
It's all done! Good job.
Okayama has another
well-known rare animal.
There it is...
It was just sitting there. What?
What is this?
It looks just like a capybara.
This is a nutria. It belongs to
the South American rat family,
just like the capybara.
It's a mammal regularly seen
in the rivers of Okayama.
Its teeth are orange.
Are all nutrias like that?
They are all like that.
After World War II, the government
brought in and encouraged...
raising nutria as a measure
to fight food shortages,
but once they weren't needed,
they were released into the wild,
and they multiplied explosively
in the western part of Japan.
It is now seen as a noxious beast
that tears up rice paddies.
Its eradication is recommended.
I like it a lot.
Thank you very much.
We don't get that too often.
"Heh heh heh"
Professor Kobayashi has been
studying nutria for 10 years.
He first began his research
in order to eradicate them,
but he was captivated by them.
He is now searching for a way
to co-exist with nutria.
What? You're going home?
"Ha ha ha"
There are no more carrots!
The two of them have
this healing effect.
Really?
I think of capybaras soaking
in hot springs...
How is the nutria connected
to hot springs?
Do they like them?
Shall I add some hot water?
Do nutria like hot baths?
Hey, nutria.
They prepared warm water,
at human body temperature.
Don't push me.
Don't you dare push me.
Oh, it's hot!
He went in. It's hot!
It's hot.
Let's cool it down a bit.
This movement...
is exactly like Degawa's.
His reaction.
So we've seen the Japanese giant
salamander and the nutria.
Next up is the strongest hornet,
the Japanese giant hornet.
Yasutake Atsuta,
an expert in capturing hornets.
Isn't this the most dangerous one?
It's the most dangerous
and biggest one around.
That's why it's fun.
No, no, no.
So once you capture them...
- you just enjoy them?
- Yes.
I capture them mainly for shipment.
I have three kids,
they all love hornet larvae.
- Your kids eat them?
- They love it.
There it is.
You found them?
It's here!
- Those are huge.
- It's huge.
- It's huge!
It's super huge. The Japanese
giant hornet is super huge.
This is some bait Atsuta set up...
- to lure the Japanese giant hornet.
- That looks scary.
I set a hive
of Japanese yellow hornet here.
Japanese giant hornets
eat other hornets?
Yes, they do. Hornets other than
the Japanese giant hornets...
are just food to them.
That's something else.
Then I put a cute ribbon on them.
This ribbon is tied to the hornet,
to chase it back to its hive.
Do you want to get close?
Atsuta is something else.
Can you put it on its body?
He's touching it.
- Really? That's something else.
- What?
Directly?
No, it'll sting you.
Here's Atsuta's expertise.
- He's coming this way.
- He's touching it.
This is no joke. Wait! Wait!
This is dangerous right now, right?
No, this is their feeding ground.
Stinging hardly ever happen
on a feeding ground.
Japanese giant hornets mainly get
aggressive around their hive.
The key is to tie
the ribbon around it...
while it's focused on its catch.
Like so.
It didn't like it, so it took it off
with its leg.
It noticed the string.
It noticed.
Will she do it this time?
She did it.
Slowly tie it.
Remember what you learnt.
Hold the base.
- Amazing.
- You're shaking a lot.
This is amazing.
Just a bit more...
Okay!
- Amazing.
- I did it!
I did it!
You're sweating like mad.
I was so nervous.
It's scary.
That was nerve-racking.
It felt like I did bypass surgery.
I never fail.
That was close.
I'm glad I didn't fail.
Then it will fly off.
The Japanese giant hornet
flies fast.
Its territory spans
a few kilometres.
We'd lose them if we randomly
chased them.
- There it is!
- It's flying.
The hornet flying from its nest
to the feeding ground...
is observed carefully,
to locate its hive.
After three hours of searching...
Amazing.
There's a hive for sure.
There are a lot coming and going.
All right, let's go.
They are in full protective gear
to go get them.
- This is scary.
- Scary!
See all this soil?
It was dug up by the hornets.
Japanese giant hornets
make their nests underground.
First, a basket is placed
at the entrance to the hive,
to capture the hornets
that come out to attack.
- There are a lot in there.
- Amazing.
See?
There's one with a ribbon.
There it is!
- It tore it off.
- You can see that it's torn?
Then it digs and digs.
- This is really something.
- Wait a second.
I think we have something.
- There it is.
- See?
From here...
- That's something else.
- See?
- We did it.
A bunch of them are flying out.
Atsuta is particular about
the taste of hornet larvae,
so he doesn't use smoke
to weaken the hornets.
- I see.
- That's how they come out?
Oh no!
- Oh no! Oh no!
- That's why...
all the healthy Japanese
giant hornets attack at once.
I'm scared!
All right! I found it.
He manages to find
the Japanese giant hornets' larvae.
Amazing.
Atsuta ships out
the ones in cocoons.
These are all queens.
- What? The ones in this section?
- They're all queen hornets.
They have that many queen hornets?
- You get a lot of them in autumn.
- The queen hornet.
So these are the larvae.
Over here, its eyes are developed.
It has a face.
Then the colour of its eyes
gets darker,
and becomes black.
And finally, this is its form
right before it hatches.
- You can see the whole process.
- Interesting.
Japanese giant hornets' larvae
are gigantic too.
- This is the larvae. Hornet larvae.
- You eat that?
Now, let's enjoy them!
You can only eat queen hornet larvae
during this season.
You can enjoy them because
you've come at this time.
Oh, so it's rare
even for hornet larvae.
A rare taste in exchange for danger.
It's very milky and delicious.
There's no odd taste to it.
Everyone around us says
it's disgusting.
Well, since it looks like a bug...
- It's tasty when you eat it.
- Eat it.
It's good.
- Here.
- They're cute.
Oh, was it hot?
It was a bit hot.
Is it hot?
Do you want to spit it out?
What's in your mouth?
It's so hot it made me cry.
- I'm sorry.
- He's so cute.
Now, another go at highlining.
The last segment
is another go at highlining.
She's been practising regularly
since the first day.
It's not 100%,
but she is able to walk across...
- the planned distance.
- Impressive.
- I'm impressed.
- I just might be a genius.
However, something she was able
to do a moment ago,
becomes a challenge again,
the next second.
Also, her traumatic experience
in the States haunts Imoto.
I want to cry.
Oh no.
This is no joke.
I can't handle this.
I sometimes get scared
with a challenge too,
but I trick myself
and take on the challenge.
Right. The first few times were...
- Highlining is fun in its own way.
- You're right.
- You look forward to tomorrow.
- I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
It's done at Ojigatake, overlooking
the beautiful Seto Inland Sea.
This is the line.
This is it!
- Wow
- Wow, that's scary.
This is high.
It's completely different
from yesterday.
This environment is different.
It's a completely different thing.
The Seto Inland Sea far below her...
adds even more fear
than the actual height.
Even experienced slackliners...
aren't able to perform as usual
without a strong mental disposition.
Imoto will walk this section.
If you fall close to the rock,
you might smash into the rock.
- I see.
- You'll start from a safe spot...
and end at a safe spot.
I see.
So the actual distance you'll walk
is quite short.
- It's short.
- Yes.
Taking Imoto's traumatic experience
into consideration,
her lifeline will be attached above.
I've been thinking for the past
five days, why am I doing this.
My conclusion is,
I don't know!
I don't know why I'm doing this.
But isn't life like that, though?
- Now, let's go for it!
- Amazing.
Come on!
I'm scared!
She'll hold the lifeline
until she reaches the start point.
I'm scared.
Wait.
You're at the orange tape
position now.
- Okay!
- It's super shaky.
- This requires guts.
- She's standing. That's impressive.
She starts once she takes her hands
off the lifeline.
She's looking up.
She walks while staring ahead.
It's so scary. Come on.
- Come on!
- However, here...
Let's hold it once. Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
Mental weakness leads
to an unbalanced body.
- One time.
- It's fine.
That's the challenge of highlining.
When I look up at the sky,
it makes me want to cry.
Am I weak now?
Mentally, she's at her limit.
Oh no.
- She's eating a banana.
- Yet she'll still eat a banana.
- That shows Imoto's strength.
- You need something.
It's been three hours
since she began her challenge.
Three hours is tough.
Okay, let's do this.
Her 32nd challenge.
I can do this.
You can do it.
You'll have to do it.
She takes firm steps
to the starting point.
- Okay. from there.
- Amazing.
This is where she starts.
Below her is the beautiful
Seto Inland Sea.
- She's not that slow.
- It's so wobbly.
- That's it.
- Amazing.
That's it.
Two more metres remain.
- That looks good.
- From here...
it's all about control and focus.
- That's right.
- Impressive.
Losing focus...
immediately shows up as instability.
- Just a little more.
- A tiny bit more.
And finally...
- Yes!
- Amazing.
I did it!
- I did it!
- Amazing.
I did it, right?
- Instructor!
- Yes!
I did it!
- That was great!
- Thank you very much.
I'm so happy!
Governor of Okayama!
I managed to cross it successfully.
Okayama is the best.
Thank you very much.
Governor!
That's it for the Okayama
Japan Tour!
Next up is this!
- Gone forever!
- Yeah!
Miyazon of Anzen Manzai
will take on the challenge.
This is what he'll challenge!
"Go capture a Bluespotted
Mud Hopper"
Go capture a Bluespotted Mud Hopper.
- Bluespotted Mud Hopper?
- That's hard.
- You don't mean Mutsugoro?
- No.
There's a fish called a Bluespotted
Mud Hopper in Saga.
It's called Mutsukake fishing.
It's a traditional fishing method
that requires advanced skills...
that have been handed down
at the Ariake Sea in Saga.
The news footage I saw
had everyone in the mud.
So this is my second time...
- with Director Kitami.
- Right. Chap.
Wasn't it that...
- Dolphin fishing.
- Dolphin fishing!
He likes it muddy.
Do you like it?
I think we can both grow from it.
An entertainer and a director
can both grow from it?
He's a wonderful chum.
He can't leave
until the goal is met.
Gone Forever.
The first day.
He arrives in Kashima, Saga.
The Ariake Sea has the largest
tidal difference in Japan.
The difference can be
as much as six metres.
Hello.
This is Tadayoshi Okamoto, an expert
in Mutsukake fishing.
Have you been Mutsukake fishing
for a long time?
I've been doing it
for almost 50 years.
I see.
And when he looks down,
what he sees...
The expert's fly is open.
So the way to fish for them is...
Miyazon's kindness is to let
the expert realise it on his own.
How is it done? Is it like...
going, "zip"?
What is the fishing rod like?
- The rod is--
- It's not like this?
I see.
Expert, your fly might be undone.
Oh, good.
Okay.
And then, the awkwardness.
So is it okay for me to see
how it's done?
- Yes, yes.
At the Ariake Sea, the tide ebbs
and flows twice a day,
and a tidal flat of three kilometres
is created.
Then the Bluespotted Mud Hoppers
appear,
looking to eat the algae
on the mud surface.
Can I take a look
at your technique?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
A mud sleigh is used to move around
the tidal flat.
Once he sees the target...
- It's tiring.
- It is tiring.
Amazing.
He's good.
He caught one already.
- That's an expert!
- No way!
He dropped the hook just in front
of the Bluespotted Mud Hopper,
and he pulled the rod back
to hook the fish.
This fast technique...
is Ariake Sea's traditional fishing,
Mutsukake fishing.
It's cute.
Strange how it has a blue tint
on its body.
Its body length
is about 15 centimetres.
It's characterised by its blue
spots and unique dorsal fin.
Experts can catch up to three
of them in under a minute.
Miyazon's goal is to catch one
a minute,
and if he catches 10 in 10 minutes,
his mission is accomplished.
That sounds hard.
Now, let's start practising!
It's super sharp.
These five sharp hooks...
are what's used to hook
the Bluespotted Mud Hopper.
Like this.
First, he'll use a golf ball.
I see.
He will learn control
by using a golf ball...
that weighs the same
as the fishing hook.
He's super good.
That's quite far.
Are Bluespotted Mud Hoppers
that far?
If you get too close,
they run away.
Bluespotted Mud Hoppers are timid.
If they get scared,
they dive back into the mud.
Therefore, a certain distance
must be maintained,
and that's the hard part.
Miyazon's first attempt.
You need to put more power into it.
This is impossible. Just a moment.
Oh, this is... It's impossible.
I can already see this is going
to be impossible to do.
However, after a few throws,
he is able to control the direction.
But, he is unable to reach
the bottles.
It goes just in front of the bottle.
I can't reach it.
So I haven't been able to control
this part yet.
You can step forward a bit.
So it was fine for me
to step forward.
That's why I couldn't reach it.
Once he steps forward...
Amazing!
Miyazon now has a sense
of distance.
He successfully knocks over
all five in no time.
Okay!
It's hard to believe you're holding
that rod for the first time.
So it was all about the distance.
Let's head out to the tidal flats
with this momentum.
Is it important to handle
the mud sleigh efficiently?
Yes.
The ironclad rule is to move around
quietly trying not to make a sound.
It's hard not to make any sound.
Oh, I see. Oh, I see.
It's hard to go straight
on this thing.
I see.
He can't help
but make splashing sounds.
It's not about fishing here.
And now, he's stuck in the mud
and is unable to move.
I was told there'd be plenty here.
You're the ones chasing them away.
I see.
As a result, they achieved nothing,
and then it was over.
They're sensitive.
Tonight, he'll stay at this house.
- That's nice.
- Amazing.
Hello.
Welcome home.
I like it that I was greeted
with a "Welcome home."
Let me say it.
I'm home!
This inn is a renovated
100-year-old Japanese-style house.
Oh! It's like this?
Their speciality is the Goemon bath.
Goemon baths were used from
the Edo period to the early Showa.
It's basically a huge iron pot.
There's so much steam that we can't
show it in a variety show.
Is it okay to take out so much
hot water?
You'll boil to death.
I'll boil to death...
You have to stand on the wooden
board, or you'll burn yourself.
That's right.
I see.
I see, it's too hot.
- He couldn't handle it.
- It's 53 degrees Centigrade.
The much-anticipated dinner is...
seafood from the Ariake Sea.
Is this Bluespotted
Mud Hopper sashimi?
Its appearance is grotesque
but in a good way.
Bluespotted Mud Hopper
goes off quickly,
and it should only be eaten
on the day it's caught.
It can only be enjoyed locally.
Amazing.
How is it?
- Wow.
- Is it good?
It's firm. It's good.
It was in the mud,
so I thought it was going to have
an odour to it,
but it has no odour. It's firm,
and super delicious.
Broiling it with in a sweet sauce
is a standard dish as well.
It's good, right?
It's slightly bitter.
It's quite... Can you eat it all?
Not all of it, so we usually skin it
like I did with the sashimi.
- I see.
- Yes...
There's something in here
that I can't quite swallow.
The second day.
Practising hooking it, using a hook.
We'll use aubergines as Bluespotted
Mud Hoppers to practise hooking.
I see. This is more like
pickled aubergine, though.
You throw it and drop it
on the other side.
- Amazing!
- In one attempt.
What's amazing is how he uses
the fishing rod.
He uses centrifugal force
and its pliability...
to hook the target, like a sniper.
His control is pretty good.
I can't hook it from there.
When he pulls the rod,
the hook faces upwards.
He won't hook a Bluespotted
Mud Hopper this way.
You have to drop the tip of the rod
down a little bit.
So I should pretend
like I'm pulling it this way.
As usual, Miyazon learns fast.
He's successful!
He's utilising the pliability
of the rod as well.
- Okay.
- What is this?
- I've got it now.
- Amazing.
However, it's not that easy to get.
The expert is right.
He has a lot more to learn!
Once again, he goes out
to the tidal flats to practise.
You should be quiet.
- No "I caught one!" "Yeah!"
- No.
This is TV,
but I won't react at all.
We'll add loud comments later.
So now, we'll deliver this
with Miyazon's voiceover.
All right! I'm going to catch you,
Bluespotted Mud Hopper.
With stealthy steps,
and making no sound...
I found one! You're mine!
Go!
That's far.
Ah! It got away.
I'll get it this time!
I can't quite get it.
If you make loud splashing noises,
we'll escape!
He does Bluespotted Mud
Hopper voices too?
Right, Bluespotted Mud Hoppers run
immediately from splashing sounds.
Who's this?
Didn't that sound like Tachiki?
How was that?
- Go!
- It sounded like him.
- I thought it was Tachiki.
- Run!
Failure.
Can I do "Failure" again?
I'm sorry.
That was Miyazon?
Failure.
- This is it.
- That's impressive.
Failure.
- That was good.
- The problem is...
the height of where to drop
the hook.
What's required is to throw it low,
and quietly.
That skill has to be hammered in
to the body.
I can't let them realise I'm there.
Tap-tap.
That's the theory, right?
So let's place a bottle...
between your legs, Kitami...
He'll aim for the bottle
between Kitami's legs.
Is it going to work?
He's braving it out.
The third day.
The low tide only happens
early morning and late at night,
so he took a day off from
practising Mutsukake fishing.
And he went on a tour of Saga.
He visited
Yoshinogari Historical Park,
known for its remains
from the Yayoi era.
The curator, Tokuhisa,
tells him about it.
I would like you to take a look
at life during the Yayoi era.
This poncho-like outfit
was common in the Yayoi era.
His hairstyle is called "Mizura,"
a common hairstyle for men.
How do you know that men
had their hair like that?
We dug up some hair.
Isn't it possible that that person
was the only one with that style?
So far, they've dug up two
at Yoshinogari.
So there were at least
two people.
So you're describing the Yayoi era
with just two examples.
Yes...
Miyazon goes from his ducktail do
to the Mizura hairstyle.
He's perfect as a person
from the Yayoi era.
Have you seen a doll like this
in a museum?
That huge building over there...
- It's huge.
- We call it a ceremonial hall.
This was a place
where kings discussed politics,
and the shamaness prayed
to their ancestors.
The famous Queen Himiko had to do
these ceremonies as well.
Queen Himiko, is this the sound?
The Yayoi era is known
for its rice cultivation.
The rice here is black.
They ate ancient grains
such as black rice back then.
They cook the rice, Yayoi style.
Are you an employee here?
I work part time.
- You work part time?
- Yes, I work part time.
What time do you finish today?
If nothing happens,
I'm done around five o'clock.
You clock out at five o'clock
to go home?
Yes, I do.
I'm actually working hard
at my other job,
so I don't really want to work late.
I'm sorry. We'll get this done
by five o'clock today.
If I say that, I'll get scolded
by my superiors later.
Superiors? Oh, the people who live
over there?
Right, the people
in the blue outfits.
They stand there pressuring me
not to say anything stupid.
Honestly, the Yayoi feel
is all gone now.
The fourth day.
Miyazon hasn't caught a single
Bluespotted Mud Hopper.
He goes to the tidal flats.
That's it.
Go!
Pull it!
It's there!
Ah!
It wasn't hooked.
It came off.
This one!
I'll get it this time.
Come on!
Oh no! I was caught!
"He finally caught one"
- He finally caught one.
- Amazing.
That's a big one.
So he finally caught one,
but he couldn't catch another one
after that.
So that was Miyazon's voice?
- Yes.
- I can't catch any.
- Why can't he catch them?
- It must be hard.
It's because each fish is facing
a different direction.
Bluespotted Mud Hoppers don't
line up neatly like aubergines.
Some Bluespotted Mud Hoppers
will be like this.
- Right.
- That's right.
If he can't catch them
in this random positioning,
he'll be useless on the tidal flats.
You don't just go in from the right,
you go in from the left too.
That's hard.
They become more alert as the number
of failures increases.
I see.
When they sense the hook,
they tense up.
Then they won't be hooked.
With Mutsukake,
the only thing that moves
is your rod.
I see.
So you can't let them
sense your presence.
You have to create that.
So when Bluespotted Mud Hoppers...
are saying "Morning!" to each other,
then when they go, "By the way..."
you smoothly hook them?
That's right. When they're 10cm away
from each other,
and when one of them is caught,
the other one searches
for the other one with a blank look.
I went to Saga the other day,
and I saw the photographs.
It's really great... Oh?
Like that?
The fifth day.
Saga tour number two.
Do we go on this?
- Yes.
- I see lots of rods in there.
It's for nori farming...
When you say "Nori",
you mean for rice balls?
Right, like for 7-Eleven.
I just had some...
Learn why the Ariake Sea is known
for nori.
Is this it?
Yes, this is the location.
Rods are placed about 100 metres
away from land.
So the nori will be floating
this way?
No, we set the net...
- and we put seeds on it.
- Seeds?
The Ariake Sea's nori is grown in
a unique way called the pole system.
Poles are placed in the sea,
the nets are set,
and then the seeds are strewn.
They utilise the biggest difference
in tides in all of Japan...
to apply direct sunlight to the nori
when it's low tide,
making it rich in nutrients
and flavour.
We harvest them at the end
of November.
At the end of November?
So today, we won't be eating...
any freshly harvested nori?
You can enjoy last year's nori.
I see...
I already had some
at 7-Eleven earlier.
Meanwhile, his Mutsukake
fishing skill has improved rapidly.
Like so?
Even the difficult
vertically positioned ones are...
I'll bring it in at an angle.
He handles the rod smoothly.
He's amazing.
He can catch them
from any direction.
- From the left? There.
- Amazing.
Amazing.
If the rod and the fishing line
can reach it, then I can do it.
The sixth day.
Today...
let me attempt the actual challenge.
He'll have a go at challenging
10 catches in 10 minutes.
All right, here I go!
Miyazon is an expert
at catching aubergines...
- Time's up!
- What?
- You caught two.
- He couldn't do it.
One more time.
He selects a target and catches it.
He then takes it off the hook.
He has to do this at a pace
of one fish per minute,
but his average catch
is still too low.
Time's up.
How many did I catch?
You caught five.
But then Miyazon realises
something at this point.
I finally realised why
I couldn't catch them.
Is it the mud sleigh?
I also wondered if the way
I released the line was wrong,
but the reason was simple.
It was the difference between
standing or sitting.
I actually didn't practise it
sitting down.
That was the issue.
You know how we don't notice
the simplest things?
When I wanted to listen to something
with headphones, it had no sound.
Was it broken? What's wrong?
It turned out to be the volume.
And you know what else?
With cup noodles...
- you pour water in...
- Right.
It's time, and you try to use your
chopsticks and it's hard as a rock.
You poured in cold water.
That doesn't happen.
He's right. Standing or sitting
makes a huge difference.
This is his view
when he's standing.
However, when he sits down,
it's harder to judge the distance.
Also, it's harder to manipulate
the fishing rod.
That's true.
The height is different.
He repeatedly trains with pickled
aubergines while sitting down.
Oh, don't pull it.
Placement of the hook.
Direction to pull the rod.
He's good.
He learnt to pull the rod
to the left,
in the most difficult situation when
the fish is positioned lengthways.
Yay!
- And after a week of training...
- One week.
You're either the best or
the second best I've seen so far.
I'm not the best? You can't tell?
Let's say you're the second best.
Then could you say I'm the best?
If I can catch 10 in 10 minutes,
will you say I'm the best?
Sure.
Will he be able to become
the expert's best apprentice?
His time starts when Miyazon
throws his hook.
He successfully catches
the first one with the first throw.
"One fish"
One minute later...
He caught his second one.
Amazing.
"Two fish"
And another minute later...
He's catching one fish per minute.
His third catch.
He's kept up the one-fish-per-minute
pace until now.
"Three fish"
He caught his fourth one
at five minutes.
- Come on.
- He slows down from here.
It dodged it.
They dodge it.
"Four fish"
That was close.
- It's tough.
- It must be difficult.
He caught his fifth one,
but he only has three minutes left.
However, he picks up his pace
once again.
"Five fish"
His sixth catch.
That's one quiet battle.
Yes.
He's silent.
There's a lot out there.
He's taking his time.
His seventh catch.
- Amazing
- Looking good.
Amazing.
"Seven fish"
What?
- His eighth catch.
- Incredible.
- I think he's going to do it.
- He can do it.
He caught three in a minute.
He has less than a minute left.
"Eight fish"
His ninth catch.
That's amazing.
Amazing!
"Nine fish"
He slows down unhooking the fish.
Come on!
He has 30 seconds left.
It will be his last attempt.
The Bluespotted Mud Hopper
is positioned lengthways.
This is the most difficult position.
Will he succeed?
"Nine fish"
He got it.
He succeeded, with 20 seconds left.
Amazing.
Time is up!
Yes!
Miyazon successfully mastered
Mutsukake fishing.
Expert, what did you think?
Expert?
He went to see some other people
trying out Mutsukake fishing.
Congratulations!
I did it!
Will you recognise my skill?
Yes, I do recognise it.
Isn't he taking it a bit lightly?
That's it for Gone Forever's
Mutsukake fishing episode.
Yay!