The Quest.
Today's first challenge is...
A man's challenge series.
What is it this time?
This time,
it's "marshmallow catch," again.
What?
- Again?
- Once again.
Degawa once managed to catch
a marshmallow at 170km/h,
which is the fastest speed
in the world.
In addition, he successfully
caught it from 52m away,
the longest distance in the world.
Currently, he holds two unofficial
"marshmallow catch" records.
However, when he attempted
to catch it from a 100m drop
for his third title,
he failed miserably.
He was unable to become
the triple record holder.
This time, he'll retry it
from that height again.
Quite frankly, it's difficult.
At the end, I had like 10 other
people help me out,
and even then,
we weren't able to catch it.
However, a powerful corporation
stepped up to assist this challenge.
It's Kashiyama Vacuum Solutions
in Saku, Nagano.
Yes, it's the company that
manufactures the vacuum pump
that pitched at a speed
of 271km/h at Imoto last year.
This pump is used to shoot
the marshmallow 100m up in the air.
And this time,
a new Degawa girl
will be participating.
What? You mean other than
those three?
- Yes.
- What's going on?
We need a breath of fresh air.
Do those three know about this?
No.
- They don't know?
- No.
- No, no, no. That's a problem.
- That's not good.
There's going to be trouble
for sure.
I mean those three cause
enough problems on their own.
Will he succeed this time?
And who is this new Degawa girl?
Degawa! Ready!
"The Quest"
"This programme was broadcast
24 January, 2021"
The Quest has started.
Tonight, it's the man's challenge
by our advisor,
and Asako Ito's Mystery Tour.
"Ayako Imoto, Daisuke Miyagawa,
Asako Ito, Kazuko Kurosawa"
"Tomoko Murakami, Miyuki Oshima
Tetsuro Degawa"
This is your fourth time doing
a marshmallow catch.
I already have two world records,
but I want the third one too.
In addition,
we have a new Degawa girl.
- I'm surprised.
- Is it going to be okay?
Those three don't know anything
about it, right?
The fact that the three of them
don't know about it is terrifying.
It is terrifying.
And Kawakita recently
got married, too.
- Exactly.
- That's something to celebrate.
Since she got married,
"Miss Retired" pops up
everywhere online.
That's not good.
- They want a new Degawa girl.
- I don't believe this.
- You traitor! Traitor!
- No, no.
Isn't it very intriguing?
What is this trick?
I shall retire today.
"Aichi's intriguing mysteries
are thoroughly investigated"
An hour and a half away from Tokyo
on Hokuriku Shinkansen.
A man's challenge by the advisor.
A 100m-drop marshmallow catch
in Saku, Nagano.
We are here
in Saku!
They start off with Degawa
and the usual three girls.
This is wonderful.
This is amazing.
- It's beautiful.
- It's cute.
Now, he will share the news
with the three of them.
This time,
a new Degawa girl is here.
- There you go again.
- Really?
You're horrible.
There you go again.
- You really are a traitor.
- Wait.
- You traitor! Traitor!
- No, no!
The news aroused fierce opposition.
Let's split this up today.
- Right!
- No!
I was summoned
to Nippon TV the other day,
and they said they wanted
a breath of fresh air.
A breath of fresh air?
Are you kidding me?
What shocked me the most is that
they auditioned before the pandemic.
What?
That's so long ago!
That's so long ago.
That's cheating! I feel cheated on!
You're such cheaters!
We just want a breath of fresh air.
We are fresh.
The way you said it made them sound
like a rotten tangerine.
- Like a rotten tangerine.
- Don't call us rotten tangerine.
I haven't met
the new Degawa girl yet.
- I see.
- Right.
I'm looking forward to it.
It'd be hard for her to appear
after all this disputing.
- I'm really sorry.
- We can do it together.
- I'll call her now.
- Yes.
Please come in.
How do you do, I'm Yumena Yanai.
She's Yumena Yanai, 20 years old.
She's a young actress who also has
the title of a Miss Seventeen.
- Yumena? Oh my, you're cute.
- Nice to meet you.
You're so excited.
You're too fast.
- You're too excited too soon.
- I've never seen you like this.
I'm not excited.
- You are too.
- He was fast.
Your smile is too much.
It's just that she came out with all
this lighting and she's very fresh.
It's a bit dull over here.
- That's horrible.
- We are not!
I'll be doing this
as a fresh tangerine.
- Thank you.
- She said it herself.
She said it.
Now, a last minute event,
New Degawa girl's interview.
We shall start the interview.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Yumena Yanai, I'm 20 years old.
I'm from Fukushima
and I live there too.
I commute from home
to go to work.
You commute from Fukushima
for every job?
Yes, I use Shinkansen.
Then your travel fees might be
more than your guaranteed fee?
Well, half of my travel fees
is covered by the agency.
What else do you do
besides "Seventeen"?
I work as an actress too.
What did you appear in?
"Mr. Hiiragi's Homeroom."
- Oh?
- What?
We haven't had a chance
to talk to each other.
Did you have a role
with lots of lines?
My seat was behind Mei Nagano,
and I had quite a lot of lines.
Wait one second.
If she had lots of lines,
then that means she had more
lines than Akane?
Please stop.
- It will be too real.
- You weren't supposed to ask that.
We have this
"actress inferiority complex."
It's an inferiority complex?
We have
this actress inferiority complex.
Is it okay for you to be a Degawa
girl if you're busy with work?
I've always wanted to do this.
It was my dream.
I've never been abroad.
I've never been on a plane either.
I'd like to go abroad
for the first time with The Quest.
Oh, it's not a trip!
Yume!
Our job is not to make trips
to make memories.
Make trips to make memories?
Do you have any special skills?
I was in a gymnastics club
for three years in middle school,
so I'm very flexible.
I can jump over a vaulting horse.
I can also do a cartwheel
on a balance beam.
Wow.
I can do a bridge too.
I'll do it right now.
That's amazing.
Amazing!
- She's flexible.
- There.
Can you really jump
the vaulting horse?
Then I'll do it.
- I can do it too.
- There she goes!
She can do it too.
There she goes again!
Go! Go!
Those two won't do it themselves.
Amazing!
I'm so happy!
Maria is so Maria
for jumping it here.
She won't support the newbie at all.
Yanai performs a cartwheel
on the balance beam.
Oh! That's a clean one.
There!
- Wonderful! That's pretty!
- Amazing.
- Amazing!
By the way, you mentioned how it
was your dream to be a Degawa girl,
do you admire a particular
Degawa girl?
Of course it's you, Kawakita.
She passed!
That's not right!
She pressured her with her eyes!
- She passed! I like her!
- She glared her down.
Now, the main event,
the marshmallow catch.
The event is held at a baseball
field at Saku Sogo Athletics Park.
Kashiyama Vacuum Solution employees
will assist us.
Kashiyama Vacuum Solutions
has the second largest share
of vacuum pumps in the world.
That machine is used to shoot
marshmallows in the air.
Air is pumped through
the cylinder in a vacuum state,
to shoot a marshmallow
100m up in the air.
We struggled the most with the wind.
We practised to increase accuracy.
However, there's a minor problem.
This is hard.
Why isn't it soft?
When marshmallows are in a vacuum,
they expand, as shown.
When air is shot through it,
then it then shrinks.
Then wouldn't it hurt
when it comes down?
Which hurts more?
An elastic band hitting you?
It hurts more than when you're hit
with an elastic band.
That's right. It hurts quite a bit
when it hits your face.
With that in mind,
a marshmallow catch from 100 m.
What's with this tarp?
We expect the marshmallow
to land in this area.
- Isn't it kind of wide?
- It seems a bit too wide?
Is that my imagination?
Marshmallows are affected
by the wind,
so it all depends on their luck
where it lands.
- Degawa, get it the first time!
- Okay
- Have fun!
- Good luck!
I'll be the true marshmallow king!
Come on!
Three, two, one.
- You can do it!
- You got it!
It's this way!
Ah! That's not it!
That's not a marshmallow.
That was close.
We forgot to mention to Degawa, but
a marshmallow is shot in a cylinder.
The cylinder is heavier,
so it doesn't fly as high.
Go!
That's not it!
On the other hand, a marshmallow
went as high as 100m,
but it dropped to the grass area
in the outfield.
That's not a marshmallow.
Take a look at this!
This is super hard.
Man, if this thing hit my face...
I'm glad I'm slow.
Now, a second try while
watching out for the cylinder.
- Where?
- That's hard.
Where is it? Where?
- Where did it go?
- There it is!
I couldn't tell at all!
You can't see it.
- There's no way to see that.
- How do you tell?
It's not "Oh no! Oh no!" but
I mean it's really is "oh no"!
Bring it!
Hotta will try it too.
- You can do it!
- Oh no!
It's so high and so fast
that the camera can't see it.
- There!
- No way!
The marshmallow barely landed
on the blue tarp.
Akane, did you see it?
Not even a millimetre...
- Right?
- Right.
It's like a shooting star.
The first day ends here,
due to time constraints.
It's already past 10:00.
And that's it
for the three Degawa girls.
Good work.
Good work!
- Excuse me.
- Good bye.
- Good luck to you!
- Good luck to you.
- We're cheering for you!
Wait. Wait. Wait.
Shouldn't you be more frustrated?
You know...
I just want to go home.
this is impossible. Honestly.
Okay, I got it. I'm about
to be discouraged here,
but what will you do, Yume?
I will accompany you!
- She's so cute!
- So cute!
That was just so cute!
Good work!
See you!
The admirable trio was brought in
to liven up for the newbie girl,
and they are now sent home.
Second day of challenge.
This challenge will take place over
four days at different ballparks.
Please watch our documentary
of adults running around
to catch a marshmallow,
for four days.
Take a look at how windy it is.
Today's condition is no joke.
They start their challenge
in wind at 3m/s.
Degawa, here it comes!
- Okay!
- Go for it!
Three,
two,
one!
The first shot of the day is...
- I can't see it! Right side!
- On the right side!
Right. Right. Right.
No! That's the drone.
What is this? Darn it!
Oh, it's not a drone.
What is that?
- That's a bird.
- A bird?
Just like last night, he can't spot
the marshmallow at all.
Yume, I don't think you serve any
purpose standing there.
How about you position her here?
Yanai will navigate the location
of the marshmallow.
However...
I don't see it. I don't see it.
I don't see it at all.
It's to the front.
- To the front!
Oh, to the right! Right!
Wait one second.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're no good at all.
You're just like me!
He attempts several times
to catch it,
but Degawa is unable to see
the marshmallow.
It's coming.
- Wow!
- To the left!
For the past few hours,
I've been standing here,
going left and right
for something I can't see.
As you're told...
Right, as I am told. It's just
that I don't see it at all.
I'll be more motivated
if I have a goal,
but without a goal or anything,
I just stand here doing this for
several hours in this darn cold,
this whole time.
And to make things worse,
it got very windy.
Since they can't do anything,
they eat the local speciality flan
for an afternoon snack.
- It's delicious.
- Is it delicious?
Yes, now use Fukushima dialect.
Degawa directs, a gourmet report
in Fukushima dialect.
What's this? It's delicious.
This is no joke.
This is delicious. What is this?
From what I heard last night,
I guess you and your family
had it hard.
You said you could only eat squid
even when you went out for barbecue.
- Just squid.
I couldn't eat any meat.
- What? Do your best.
- We couldn't eat meat.
And the challenge...
is done at night as well.
In the centre! Close to first base!
First base!
In the centre!
- It's easier to see at night.
- In the centre!
I saw it from around here.
But even if I see it,
I still won't get to it on time.
Then we'll just have to increase
the quantity.
The eight-marshmallow plan.
I see it.
I finally feel like
I'm participating now.
Okay.
Let's go with this plan.
This is the best idea.
We see the light now.
However, there was a flaw
to this plan as well.
Third base! Third base!
Oh, but first base too!
He hesitates to pick one.
Yume, which one?
Third day of their challenge.
Starting today, two vacuum pumps
will be used simultaneously
to carry out
a 16-marshmallow plan.
Then a huge chance came their way!
There it is.
Up!
A marshmallow hit Degawa's chin.
That was close!
Hey! Come on!
That was so...
You could have caught that one
just now.
I could have caught it.
I could have done it.
But you know,
I feel alive now.
I mean yesterday, I was like,
"What am I doing?"
However, he's out of luck
after that.
One!
Go!
Catch it!
What are you doing?
I chased after it!
You should have caught that one!
Yumeppe.
Yumeppe...
- Yumeppe, you--
- Yumeppe.
Yumeppe is cool.
No, it's not cool.
- Don't you think "Yumeppe" is cute?
- Yumeppe?
Her nickname shall be "Yumeppe."
How about you try it once, Yumeppe.
Then... I'll give it a try.
All right. Are you okay
with Yumeppe?
It sounds like a fart.
It sounds like a silent fart.
Right.
So Yumeppe will try now.
Will she get it done?
No, no, no.
Wait one second.
I apologise.
Did you get it? That pressure?
They come up to you every time,
and they go "What? What?"
Did you feel that pressure?
I really felt that just now.
Second attempt by Yumeppe.
- Go on.
- Looking good!
Good!
This was so close.
I don't want to say this,
but she could've caught that one.
What are you glaring at me for?
I'm not glaring at you.
- What are you glaring at me for?
- I'm not glaring at you.
- You're glaring at me.
- No, I'm not glaring at you.
- Come on, get upset.
- No.
I've seen this routine on TV before.
Don't say "routine."
Don't call it a routine! It took
Ryuhei Ueshima and I several years
to create this.
Change! Change!
A good one is coming right now.
Then came
the biggest opportunity of the day!
It wasn't for Degawa, but...
it was for Yumeppe!
It's coming. Come on.
Ouch!
A marshmallow strikes
Yumeppe's cheek.
It was three centimetres away
from her mouth.
You saw it coming,
and then it hit your face?
I wasn't ready for it.
It wasn't like, "Come on!"
It was more like,
"Huh? Is it coming this way? Is it?"
Then bam!
They changed positions,
but she's pretty much participating,
so now both of them will attempt
to catch a marshmallow.
What was that?
That's so annoying!
The trajectory changes!
Marshmallows have bad character.
They are twisted.
They are.
They are no joke.
Their third day on location
was done.
Even that beautiful moon looks
like a marshmallow now.
That night,
they have a strategy meeting
at a restaurant
that serves their local speciality,
boar-pig hybrid.
Inoppe, it's not Inoppe.
- It's not Inoppe.
Inoppe? It's not Inoppe.
It's not Inoppe. Yumeppe, could you
do a gourmet report?
How does
the boar-pig hybrid skewer taste?
This is delicious.
It looks delicious.
I'm really shocked.
You know at the end,
I think it's all about this.
This is what will make it happen.
Let's get it done.
Let's get it done tomorrow for sure.
We discussed a lot
in this strategy meeting.
I'm going to tell you this
since this is your first time.
Most of this won't be used.
You saw that with
Imoto's episode, right?
- Yes.
- Weren't you like, "What?"
Actually, my son said,
"That was short."
Will they succeed tomorrow?
The fourth day on location
starts with a challenge
for the new Degawa girl.
You are now a Degawa girl,
so we need you to take on
The Quest style.
- Flying frisbee catch.
- So suddenly?
- Flying frisbee catch?
Oh!
- Am I going to do it?
- Yes.
I can finally participate.
I'm happy about it.
- I'm ready!
- Okay!
- Here's her first attempt!
- She's all enthusiastic.
- She's very eager to do it.
- Her eagerness
- is amazing.
- That's great.
Amazing.
- That was close!
Oh man!
Her reach was only three centimetres
away from the frisbee.
- That was close.
- That was so close.
- I'm ready!
Okay!
Her second attempt.
Will she succeed?
She's wonderful.
- Oh no!
- Incredible.
It's looking good so far.
- I caught it!
- She caught it.
She succeeds!
- I caught it!
- What's at the end?
She slipped and hit her head,
however, that didn't stop her
from catching the frisbee.
She's really strong. I'm impressed.
This is what you call
a fresh tangerine from Fukushima!
I did it!
This is super fun!
And at night, Yumeppe repeatedly
comes close to catching it.
Oh no.
It hit my clavicle.
Looking good!
- It doesn't seem too windy either.
- Ouch.
Her head!
And finally...
it hits her lips.
- Ouch!
- Did it hit you?
- This is so annoying!
- You got some on you.
- This is even more annoying.
- You got it on you.
It's their last day on location,
with no success.
They could catch it any second.
Ouch!
And Yumeppe is the only one
who's come close to catching it,
and Degawa is nowhere to be found
at this point.
It's sweet.
So you can taste it too, then.
I shouldn't say this,
but I think Yumeppe can catch it.
However, it's their last night
at the baseball field.
Let's do our best here!
Let's do it!
Everyone cheers for them.
We'll catch it for sure!
We only have limited time left,
we'll definitely do our best!
- Yes!
- I'll catch it!
- Great.
They want to succeed
for everyone there.
They frantically run after
a marshmallow the whole time.
It's in your way!
Boy... how many centimetres
am I off here?
They can't end until they succeed.
That's the job of a Degawa girl
that Yumeppe yeaned for.
Ouch!
- She has yellow on there.
- Look below her eyes.
It's yellow.
It's starting to make me laugh.
She's got tears in her eyes,
because it's very painful when
a marshmallow hits her face.
It must hurt.
It'll happen. It's going to happen.
She doesn't want to end her first
location as a failure.
Front!
That was close.
Your mouth?
That must hurt.
Wow!
Again.
It tastes like marshmallow.
She's tasting marshmallow
for the second time.
Darn it! I want to taste
a marshmallow too!
I am yet...
I'm yet to taste one.
He's become a corner man.
However, the time has finally come
for Degawa to prove himself.
That was wasted.
Darn it!
This is so...
Now, they have one hour left
of the challenge.
So now we asked Sakai, who's
been with us for the past five days,
as well as Kodaira and Hanai
who've been shooting marshmallows,
to join the challenge as well.
We've been working hard together
doing this,
so let's ask them!
- What?
- Yes!
"Advisor's fist bad joke of 2021"
- Yes.
- Wait one second.
I'm sorry. That wasn't appropriate
right now.
- I'm sorry.
- I thought you were going to say,
"We've been working hard together,
so two of us will finish it off!"
But instead, you were like,
"Let's ask them!"
Let's ask them.
Then the two young men show off
magnificent physical abilities.
- Did it hit you?
- Yes.
- That's great.
- It hit you?
It hit you?
What? Both of you?
That's so cool.
They come close several times
after that as well.
- My right eye.
- My right eye too.
What? Both of you?
Finally, they only have enough time
to try three more times.
Last three!
Yes!
- Three more attempts.
- Go for it!
- Two, one!
- A miracle.
Will they succeed?
Come!
They only have enough time
to try three more times.
Three more attempts!
Yes!
- Three more attempts.
- Three,
- Go for it!
- Two,
- one!
- A miracle.
Will they succeed?
- Come!
- Someone!
Someone!
Ah!
It hits Hanai's lips.
That was so close.
It went in a little. I tasted it.
Only the few can taste the taste.
Now, two more attempts left.
We are ready!
I did my best for three years
with Japanese baseball,
although I never played a game.
Please, god of baseball.
Three,
two, one.
Will they succeed?
Go!
That was close!
He's like a little dinosaur.
Right here.
Oh man!
Did you taste it?
No, I didn't.
I can't even taste it,
since it hit me here.
This is the last one.
Let one of us catch it for sure!
Yes!
- That voice.
- This is the last attempt.
Will their wish be fulfilled?
Go!
That was close!
The last one hit Yumeppe
near her mouth.
They failed.
- Ouch...
- That hurts.
Wow, you got some on there.
I tasted the most marshmallow
with this one.
Wow.
Yumeppe.
I'm so disappointed.
Innocent tears that won't be shed
by any of the current Quest members.
-That is so true. Do you get it?
- This is the breath of fresh air
we were looking for!
- This is it.
- When he saw her tears,
this man sympathised and cried, too.
Yumeppe, you worked really hard.
You came so close,
with so many attempts.
This is really disappointing.
Really disappointing.
We are truly sorry towards Kajiyama,
but...
So what should we do, Yumeppe?
Should we try marshmallow catch
for the third time?
Please let us do it!
Everyone, thank you for helping us
for so many days, and I'm sorry too.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
We weren't successful
in marshmallow catch again.
We'll do it again!
Yeah!
Advisor, Yumeppe and Kajiyama
Vacuum Solution employees,
thank you for your hard work!
- That was great.
- Amazing.
So once again, here's Yumena Yanai,
the new Degawa girl.
"Yumena Yanai"
- Yumeppe!
What did you think after
watching this?
I remembered how I was disappointed,
and it made me tear up again.
Everyone, this is it.
We all forgot about this, right?
- We have.
- My heart aches.
We've never seen such beautiful
tears in this programme, right?
We've only seen tears shed
from greed.
Greed.
When I saw her last tears,
it made me think about it.
Thank you!
This innocence
- is what The Quest was missing.
- Right.
- She came from Fukushima.
- Amazing.
She tried so hard,
and she sounds great too.
Her strong voice
when she goes, "Ready!"
I only have good impressions
of Yumeppe.
She went and did that slider
on her own,
and she didn't even hesitate
to do it.
She didn't even say, "Again?"
If I hit my head like that, I would
be like, "Did you simulate that?"
- You're right.
- I would totally say it.
The other members are much
older than her, right?
And she could be
our daughter's age...
She's very pure.
I could watch her forever.
I mean I could watch her forever.
- I still want to see it.
- I want to see more.
I want to see more of her.
I just realised none of us
are in our 20s anymore.
- She's 20 years old.
- You're right.
I'm grateful. Thank you.
Let's try our best from now on too.
Next, an hour and a half away
from Tokyo on Shinkansen.
It's Asako Ito's Mystery Tour
in Aichi.
She came to Toyokawa Inari,
one of the three notable
Inari temples of Japan.
Isn't it intriguing?
- She's all winkled up.
- What's intriguing is
that my height
is shrinking every year,
but my feet are getting bigger
for some reason.
I'm experiencing
this terrifying phenomenon.
A mysterious phenomenon where
her body is giving in to gravity.
My feet
used to be 24.5cm, but now
25.5 cm is too tight for me too.
So now the stylist is starting
to give me nasty looks.
She was like, "We don't have any
ladies' shoes in that size."
People come to pray for business
prosperity at Toyokawa Inari.
There was a rumour that spread
by word of mouth.
A rock?
This thing here?
What is the big deal about this?
This rock holds coins of the people
who came to visit this temple,
and the rumour has it that
if you take it home, you'll be rich.
If that's the case,
I'll thoroughly look for it.
They probably place it in here,
so it's hard to grab.
Asako believed it
and is searching for it, but...
These are precious money offerings
from the devotees.
She's enthusiastically searching,
but please do not take
money offerings home with you.
That's right.
The rumour is a complete hoax.
You won't be blessed,
but will be punished.
Ah! I found one!
I found a coin!
So is it a blessing since
we take home this coin
that's hard to take out from here?
You won't be blessed with anything,
even if you take it.
Don't be so greedy
with your own desires.
- That's what it is.
- Don't be so self-centred,
but reflect on yourself and be
grateful. That's very important.
I think so too.
Let's start
the Mystery Tour in Aichi!
First up is Nagoya's speciality.
A mysterious dance where
ladies have to endure pain.
- Look, there's a pretty girl.
- She's cute.
I'm Suzume. I'm a Maiko from Nagoya.
The dance is
a traditional dance of Meigiren,
a group that represents
Maiko in Nagoya.
Before we start working as Maiko,
there is a dance
we must learn first.
What is this traditional dance
that comes with pain?
- What could it be?
- Shachihoko.
Shachihoko? Wait!
This is Nagoya's Maiko speciality,
- dance of the golden Shachihoko.
- Because it's Nagoya.
It's Nagoya!
- That's what it is!
- Yes.
Until they can do it properly.
Fast learners are able to do it
in a month.
I can't do that!
Let's try it!
Basics are simple. You are to place
your arms in front of the chest.
The head is lowered by setting
the arms as a pivotal point,
then the legs go up in the air
like a see-saw.
Ouch.
That hurt.
- I'm going to lift your legs.
- It's much harder than it looks.
This is how it is,
even with four people.
It hurts.
Younger Maiko seem to do it
with such ease...
But they are shaking too.
When you take a closer look...
It hurts so much that they shake.
What is this trick?
They are all desperate to get
Asako to do the Shachihoko move.
- It's impossible.
- Her body is positioned wrong.
It's impossible.
My face really hurts.
This lady who suddenly interrupted
is Maiko, who is a legendary dancer
of Meigiren.
Put strings on her.
- Put strings on her?
- The other trick.
This is known as
the Shachihoko ring.
It's a trick to keep the arms still
as a pivot by immobilizing the arms.
You know...
that looks like hell.
- Then...
- You can do it.
Her legs went up in the air.
You got it!
How can I get up now?
What she is,
is not Shachihoko, but...
You look like a sea lion.
She practised for three hours.
Here's Nagoya's traditional dance,
Shachihoko dance performance!
Excuse me.
Asako, 50 years old. Looks great
in these types of outfits.
- She looks good in it.
- Nice to meet you.
The dance of the Golden Shachihoko
performance starts.
I'm accompanied by the others.
Great.
That's Tomio Umezawa.
The wig and the kimono weigh
about six kilograms.
Additional weight makes it harder
to do the Shachihoko move.
She must put on the Shachihoko ring
without being noticed.
Now, she gets the ring ready.
Shachihoko.
All of a sudden,
she starts to sing very slowly.
She's trying to buy
some time for her.
- Amazarashi.
- Go for it!
Time for Shachihoko, will she go up?
- She does it successfully!
- Amazing.
Her expression was great just now.
Great.
That was amazing.
You always perform well.
So you'll make your debut now.
Yes, and I shall retire today.
Now, let us introduce you to two
incredible craftsmen of Aichi.
First, he's the best in Japan.
A thickness of 1/1000 millimetres.
Hello.
- Hello.
These are the craftsmen.
It's Mitsuya the boss and Hosoda.
What is your speciality?
We specialise in planing wood.
Hosoda displayed
amazing shaving techniques
to produce the thinnest slices,
to win a competition of woodworkers.
Its thickness
was 1/1,000 millimetre.
It's thinner than
1/10 of a tissue paper.
Please take a look
at his magnificent technique.
Amazing.
That is so thin.
The shaved wood is so thin
that you can see through it.
Planing process is necessary
to polish wood and for durability.
Its finish is considerably better
when it's thinner.
Its thinness is...
Wow! It's 0.007.
Incredible!
Look at the polished finish
of the wood.
- Magnificent!
- Incredible!
Look what you can do
with the shaved wood!
Hello everyone! I'm Minami Asakura,
50 years old!
- There!
- She's gotten old.
What time is it?
This hurts.
That's no joke.
Next is super eccentric!
The world's best master hairdresser.
This is Katagiri.
He's actually...
I'm the world champion
- in this industry.
- What?
Katagiri is a master hairdresser
who has won several competitions,
equivalent to the Olympic games
of this industry.
He's currently the official trainer
for team Japan,
as well as the judge
for the world championships.
What's eccentric is his technique.
This is the technique he did
at the world championship in 2016.
That's interesting.
It's flattening out.
He then bundles up the hair
that's been sprayed with a comb,
to create a design.
That's pretty!
It's almost done, but Katagiri seems
to be bothered about something.
This is no joke.
I think the competitor will question
my ability.
Really?
I hope my competitors' TV
stops working.
This is his finished work.
An eccentric ducktail.
It seems magnificent,
but he is not satisfied with it.
It was something to do
with the colours.
You're his wife.
What do you think of your
husband's work?
It shouldn't be made public.
That's harsh.
Katagiri is proud of this one.
Its colours and designs
are detailed,
and the silhouette
has a nice right angle to it.
- I guess it is different.
- So it's different.
Amazing.
Asako will try
an eccentric hairstyle.
You look like Ochimusha.
I'll leave it to you today.
First, her hair is made wavy
with a curling iron.
Then it's sprayed
to shape your hair.
Wow, this is amazing.
Wow, this is amazing!
Then it's coloured.
What does her hair look like now?
Let's see it now!
That's great.
Hello,
I'm Shachi Hokoko.
She reminded us of something...
She looks like Yokai Amabie.
You two created this together.
What do you think?
It's funny.
It's funny? What?
That night.
Tonight, we can actually see
the Northern Taurids.
Really?
She came to Okumikawa, known
as the holy land of the starry sky.
- Good evening.
These two are Goto and Hagino,
the starry sky guides.
It comes every year,
but you only see a few even
if you observe it for an hour.
So it all depends on your luck.
Don't you want to wish for something
if you see are shooting star?
You do say that.
What would be
your best three wishes?
- Right now?
- Yes.
Why do I have to tell you
before I see a shooting star?
Am I supposed to tell you?
Then grant my wishes then.
Asako's very fist wish is...
World peace.
- That's great.
- I've been wishing for that.
Don't chuckle. I'm serious here.
Do you have any other wishes?
If I have to come up with one...
Her second wish is...
I want my cholesterol level
to decrease.
That's random.
- That's so random.
- I said if I have to choose one.
And her third wish is...
I want my hair to stop thinning.
You hair is thinning?
My good friend Okubo's dog, Pakomi
eats my hair along my forehead.
So my forehead keeps getting
wider and wider.
Let's start stargazing!
The weather is clear.
It's a perfect day for stargazing.
- The weather was super nice.
- That's beautiful.
Please enjoy the starry sky
shot in time-lapse.
Taurus is this upside-down V here.
The shooting stars are seen
over an extensive area around there.
It's all about widening your vision.
That's the determining factor.
Come on, shooting star!
Come on!
That is when...
Please watch
the bottom of the screen.
There it is!
- Really?
- Where?
- It was quite big.
- No way!
Did you make a wish?
I didn't.
I just thought, "It appeared!"
It's coming!
The wave is coming!
It's coming.
Will she be able to make a wish
with the next one?
Ah! Thinning hair!
That was something else.
I saw the trail for a second.
- There's another one!
- Thinning hair!
The final one is a mysterious group,
where the elderlies
dance their hearts out.
What?
She came to Miyoshi,
located east of Nagoya.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
These are them.
What do they do?
So you dance your heart out?
Ready...
We do synchronised swimming.
They are a synchronised
swimming team of elderlies.
Their average age is 67 years old.
They met at a swimming class,
and they perform several times
a year at an event and competitions.
If you don't mind me asking,
how old are you?
I'll be 80 this month.
- What?
- She looks younger.
Amazing!
You don't look like it at all!
Anyway, let's start practising
synchronised swimming.
Thank you.
They will be coached by Ms Higaki.
Asako is 50 years old,
but she's
one of the younger ones here.
Can you swim about 10 metres?
What?
Yes.
Here? There?
From here to there.
- From the edge?
- No, from there.
If you can just swim...
- From over there?
- From there!
Their conversation is going nowhere.
Do you want to clip it?
I don't know.
I don't have a nasal bone.
- What?
- I don't have one either.
It's fine. it's fine.
We have even less!
A puzzling conversation.
Some of you may
have noticed already,
but their synchronised swimming
touches the bottom of the pool.
Asako, okay!
You're young.
Not at all.
She hasn't heard that in a while.
Ready, go!
Amazing!
How do you float in this condition?
With our own fat.
I need to eat more then.
She practised for three full hours.
How did it turn out?
Go team!
Synchronised swimming show.
"Average age 67 years old.
Miyoshi Tante Tante and Asako"
Solemn sisters enter.
They are all looking to the side.
They all are.
- It's Sister Act.
- Yes, it is.
Okay.
Their timing is a little off,
but that makes them
even more charming.
That's cute.
We can't tell Asako apart anymore.
Where is she?
Darn it.
Godaigo's Galaxy Express 999,
with a nostalgic touch.
"Ballet leg"
They all frantically
swim underwater.
That's incredible.
Now, they will all do a handstand
at the same time.
That's impressive.
Their average age is 67 years old.
That's lots of physical activity.
All of a sudden,
music from Demon Slayer plays.
Why?
Here comes the final move.
Grandma lift.
Amazing.
What's incredible is everyone's
physical strength.
We don't get that tired,
even when we do this.
We do this after we swim.
Consider their strong mentality,
just talking away at the camera.
So that concludes
Asako's Mystery Tour.
Yumena, what did you think?
Good work.
It really was incredible.