"The Quest".
The first part of this episode is...
Miyagawa Expedition,
the 14th edition.
This time, you'll explore Amami
Islands in Kagoshima Prefecture.
Amami Islands?
Like Amami Oshima?
Amami Islands are located between
the mainland of Kyushu and Okinawa.
They have a subtropical climate,
and are home to rare plants
and animals,
including endemic species.
It's an unexplored region
with its own ecosystem.
There are two things
that we want to find.
To find the legendary endangered
animal, the Amami rabbit.
I've heard of them.
But I've, of course, never seen
them, because they're legendary.
Another one is a mysterious cave
in the depth of the earth.
You love caves, don't you?
We went to a cave before, didn't we?
The golden cave in Thailand.
It was grey.
You told me we'd no longer
visit caves.
In the back of the cave, there are
stalactites on terraced fields.
Terraced fields? Are you sure?
I'm a bit worried.
This time, we'll visit two islands
of Amami Islands,
and capture Amami rabbit
and the mysterious cave on camera.
A new member wants to join
this expedition.
What?
Here I am.
It's Okasan.
It's Assistant Director Hirata,
also known as Okasan.
Who first started
calling you Okasan?
Mr Degawa was the first one
who called me by that name.
That's how it started.
What do you think of that?
I feel honoured.
You feel honoured?
What was your very first nickname?
Himiko.
That's a crazy first nickname.
Himiko? Were you a leader?
What kind of an adventure
will they have?
In addition to that,
we'll have Miyazon's helicopter trip
to see autumn leaves.
It's breathtaking.
"This program was broadcast
15th November, 2020"
The Quest has begun.
Tonight, we have Miyagawa's
14th expedition.
We'll also have "Go to the End
of the World and Stay There."
Yes!
First of all, Miyagawa, you went
to Amami Islands, Kagoshima.
That's right.
This time, with Okasan.
Her actual name is Hirata.
I wasn't sure if she liked
the nickname, so I asked her.
She said people also called her
Okasan at her previous job.
So I thought she didn't mind it,
and kept calling her Okasan.
Daisuke now calls her "Okkasan."
Behind his back, she told me she
didn't like to be called "Okkasan."
- She hates that.
- But Okasan is okay.
- Just not "Okkasan."
- Yeah, she doesn't like "Okkasan."
Why is that?
I see it.
It's over there.
"Miyagawa's expedition
in Amami Islands"
This place is incredible!
Wow, look at that.
It's pretty.
What a great view.
"Miyazon's autumn leaves tour"
It's incredible.
A great adventure is about to start.
Miyagawa Expedition
in Amami Islands,
Kagoshima Prefecture.
Miyagawa Expedition.
When you watch it,
you can tell it's the real deal.
It's our 14th expedition, and we're
visiting Amami Islands, Kagoshima!
First, they explore Amami Oshima,
the biggest island of Amami Islands.
Here are the four members
of the expedition.
Director Kitami,
also known as Chappu.
Assistant producer Yoshizawa,
and Assistant Director Iwashita.
Also...
Hirata.
Also known as Okasan.
People often call me so.
Yeah, I know that.
What are you wearing?
You intentionally
try to look like a mother.
But you're well prepared.
I like that about you!
You're trying to make people laugh.
That helps me a lot.
- It helps.
- Nice.
The first mission is
to capture the legendary and rare
Amami rabbit on camera.
Nature guide Masahiro Nishi
will assist in the expedition.
As an animal, Amami rabbit made
the first natural monument in Japan.
They're a special natural monument,
which is the highest rank.
The same species existed
in Mainland China before.
But when Amami Islands got separated
from Mainland China,
that species went extinct
in Mainland China.
Now, they only exist in Amami Oshima
and Tokunoshima.
I'm curious.
I see something written
on your left hand. What is it?
I had to tell the district leader
that we'd be filming here today.
I wrote down, "district leader."
I thought I'd forget it otherwise.
Like an elementary school kid.
That's all.
About two million years ago,
due to tectonic shifting,
the islands got separated
from Mainland China.
Ever since then, the islands
kept their own ecosystem.
It's a place filled with rare
animals, including Amami rabbits.
But most of the animals
are nocturnal.
So during the day...
If you find something that looks
like food, please let me know.
they'll look for food
in Amami's forest and sea.
Can we eat this?
Leader!
You scared me!
What is it?
Look at this.
Behind the leaves.
What are they?
What are they? They look creepy!
They're stink bugs.
"Stink bugs gathered in one place"
That looks creepy!
They basically don't move at all
when it's hot during summer.
- They gather in one place and rest.
- No way.
Since you have that camera...
I'll shoot them up close.
Could you also do the narration?
Since the last expedition,
the young director Kitami started
training himself
to do impromptu narration.
It's been one month now.
How much did he improve?
- Let's see.
- I have an idea.
Okay, go ahead.
A large amount of stink bugs gather
in a cool place during summer.
The way they stick
to the backs of the leaves
resembles ripe grapes.
You can tell yourself.
Here, Leader finds food.
Wow, what is this?
They're snake gourds.
Snake gourds.
It's a plant in the gourd family.
But they bear fruit four metres
above the ground.
It's not easy to reach them.
- I came up with a strategy.
- Okay.
Kitami and Leader,
please hold each other's shoulders.
I'll go on top of you guys,
and drop the gourds with a branch.
That's my strategy.
I'll go up.
That's how it should be.
How much do you weigh?
Sixty-seven kilograms.
Eighty kilograms.
Seventy-eight kilograms.
So it's you.
Let's get it started!
- Slowly.
- Here it goes.
Ouch, don't pull my hair.
- Don't pull my hair.
- I'm falling!
I'm falling!
Watch out!
Leader was hit strongly on his nose.
That hurt.
You went down this way.
This part dropped.
This strategy won't work.
Next, they decided to make a loop
with their rope,
and try to hook the fruit with it.
- I'm scared.
- It's fine.
Okasan will give it a try.
Below her is Iwashita.
Here we go.
"Iwashita's quiet battle begins now"
Iwashita's quiet battle begins now.
Step forward a bit, Iwashita.
Forward.
It's an important job.
You can do it!
Almost there. Once again.
Keep going, Iwashita.
Okay, nice. You go it.
- Wait, wait.
- Hold it, hold it.
Now, all they need to do
is to pull the rope.
Okay, here we go.
We've got it! We got two of them!
After going through trouble,
they've got two snake gourds!
However...
What is this?
It stinks.
They were too ripe to be eaten.
Next, they find Amami
short-horned grasshoppers,
which is in the same family
as rice grasshopper.
Can you capture it?
This is our only chance.
So quick.
The grasshoppers that they captured
will be boiled and seasoned
with Japanese silver leaf,
which is an Asteraceae plant
growing on the island.
We're at the sea!
Next, they'll try to find seafood.
Flip over large rocks like that.
If you dig ground underneath it,
you might be able to find
large mud crabs.
They're large crabs that are
more than 20 centimetres long.
Give me a shovel.
Shovel.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
"The Ant and the Grasshopper.
The sun is burning the fields
and forests.
It's hot..."
It was quick today.
The baby's asleep.
Are you asleep?
Good night. You idiot!
This is "Aesop's Fable."
I meant "shovel".
Why did you hand me "Aesop's Fable"?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I like thin ones rather than
thick ones. This one is thick.
Let's eat.
I love sukonbu. You idiot!
This is sukonbu.
I panicked a bit
when you handed this to me.
I told you to give me a shovel,
and you gave me this.
I panicked quite a bit.
I was really anxious. You idiot.
This isn't the right one.
I need a shovel.
Do you know what this is?
Does he know what it is?
That's right, this is it.
This is it.
This...
Yeah, I know what this is.
Woohoo...
What?
What is this?
- Sawadee kap.
- Sawadee kap!
Sawadee kap!
How would he know?
How would I know that?
Let's get back to mud crabs.
Oh, look!
That's not it.
That's not it!
I caught two animals.
Are they edible?
No, they aren't.
Unfortunately,
they couldn't find mud crabs.
But in the river...
I've got it.
He's good.
He found freshwater prawn, which is
a speciality of Amami Oshima.
I'm so happy.
With everyone joining forces,
they caught this many prawns.
They also found something perfect
for dessert.
- Bananas.
- They're bananas.
They are musa acuminata, which is
in the same family as bananas.
- With these...
- Will they grill them?
Try it, Yoshizawa.
Yoshizawa, who is the biggest fruit
lover in the team, will try it.
She's a fruit lover?
With the skin removed,
it looks just like a banana.
Banana.
She looks serious.
"Crunch, crunch"
It doesn't sound like
you're eating a banana.
It sounds crunchy.
I don't approve of this taste.
That's terrible.
- We can't eat it.
- You can try it on this end.
Sure.
I'll try it.
You spat it out.
Again!
Here are the foods from Amami
that they found.
Our guide Nishi
caught a lot of grasshoppers.
They simmer and season them
with Japanese silver leaves.
Freshwater prawns
are steamed simply.
That looks great.
I'm getting hungry.
Okasan makes salted riceballs
for everyone.
Very nice.
This will give them energy
for the night safari.
I'll try this. What is this?
Mecopoda elongata.
That's good.
Really? This kind is good?
How does it taste?
It's good!
"Good!"
It tastes like river shrimp.
Here's freshwater prawn.
- It's very good.
- It sure is.
Okasan's salted riceballs
are also incredible.
- It's great!
- Right?
It has the perfect amount of salt,
Okasan.
There's an extra-large one.
It's huge.
"Extra-large grasshopper"
This is an adult female
Asian long-headed locust.
That's good!
Go for it.
It tastes good.
Right?
But its jagged legs
stick in his throat.
"Woof"
It's 7:00 pm.
It's time for nocturnal animals
to start moving.
Please look at this.
There. Amazing.
He looks dignified.
What is it?
It's an Amami tip-nosed frog.
They are endemic to the Amami,
and a natural monument.
At night, it's easy to find bugs
on the street which they feed on.
So we'll walk on forest paths
like this.
Amami rabbits also come down
forest paths at night to eat grass.
However, they're a very
sensitive animal,
and they hide in a bush if they
sense the presence of humans.
How likely will we able to see them?
When you explore this island,
there's about 30 per cent chance
that you'll be able
to see the rabbit.
Then...
I see something.
Look.
It's over there.
That's Amami woodcock.
They're an epidemic species
of Amami Islands.
For a moment,
I thought it was the rabbit.
- I thought so, too.
- Me too.
But right after that...
I heard something.
This is it?
It's the sound they make.
Amami rabbits make this kind of
squeaky sound.
On top of that...
Wow, that's a lot.
On the forest path,
there's a lot of rabbit faeces.
"Amami rabbit's faeces"
It's a sign that they're nearby.
Right then...
There's one.
- There's one.
- Can I cast light on it?
- Yeah.
A rabbit appears from the darkness.
This is our country's natural
monument, the Amami rabbit.
Awesome.
It's facing its bottom
to the camera, and eating grass.
Amami rabbit.
It's bigger than I expected.
They're about 50 centimetres long.
They're that big?
The rabbit has small ears,
and has short legs,
features which have not changed
since ancient times.
They're often called
a living fossil.
- That's quite rare.
- Wait a minute.
Here it goes.
- It's leaving.
- It's hopping.
It's gone.
We could only see it
for just one minute.
Did you get it?
Yes, we did.
They successfully captured
the endangered animal on camera.
Impressive.
The second day of the adventure.
On this day, in the beautiful sea
of Amami Oshima,
they'll train their body and mind.
Taishi Otono, a coach of a water
rescue team, will assist them.
What will they do today?
We'll sink down
while holding a rock.
Sink down
while holding a rock, and...
And run.
- Run on the sea bottom?
- Yes.
Really?
They'll train to get their body
and mind in shape.
It's a rock training from hell.
We'll sink down
while holding a rock.
Sink down
while holding a rock, and...
And run.
- Run on the sea bottom?
- Yes.
Really?
They'll train to get their body
and mind in shape.
It's a rock training from hell.
But before that,
they'll warm up on the beach.
He swims nicely.
This is called "washing machine."
It's a training to stay calm
when the sea suddenly gets rough.
Breathe in.
We'll go backward now.
A large amount of sea water
comes into the nose.
I'm totally fine.
Now that he's done the warmup,
he'll start the rock training.
First, Mr Otono will show them
how to do it.
A rock is placed three metres
deep into the sea.
The rock weighs about 30 kilograms.
"Weighs 30 kilograms"
- What?
- He's running!
It's crazier than I expected!
Wow.
Seriously?
He runs 20 metres total
without breathing.
He finishes running easily.
- It's so cool.
- I can never do this.
Impressive!
That was incredibly cool.
Let's try it.
Chappu?
The first one to go is Kitami, who
is quite chubby for a 32-year-old.
Good luck.
Diving itself is hard.
Oh, no.
He manages to reach the rock.
Then...
You can do it!
He panics after two steps.
How was it?
It was already close to my limit
when I reached the sea bottom.
But you took two steps.
I could see that
you were determined.
Next is Leader.
So fast.
He holds the rock firmly.
Now, how many steps can he take?
- Impressive.
Impressive!
Leader takes light steps
on the sea bottom,
and quickly reaches
the half-way point.
He's leaning forward to have
the centre of gravity in front,
and runs as if he's flying.
Impressive.
Nice.
It's his first try, and he finishes
running 20 metres!
I'm very happy!
Next is an underwater backflip.
A backflip?
Bring the rock above yourself
and do a backflip.
It's a difficult trick, but Leader
impresses everyone again.
With the rock's weight?
Exactly.
Impressive.
He succeeds at first try.
I did it!
I did a backflip!
Next is Iwashita, who ranked ninth
at a national swimming competition.
The way he swims is different.
He does a backflip
with a great form.
And the second time.
He continues!
Nice.
Impressive!
Incredible!
He did three backflips, which even
Mr Otono wasn't expecting.
I did one flip, he did three,
so, Chappu, you do five flips.
Can Kitami prove that he can do it?
Go!
- Go for it!
- The way he swims...
Good luck!
You can do it!
Great!
- Go!
- More.
He did succeed.
You did it.
It looked terrible, but...
you did it!
Their training continues.
Wow, look at that!
Incredible!
This waterfall is 30 metres high.
It's called Shinoho Waterfalls,
and the water falls to the beach.
Look at this.
This power.
Lie on your back!
This will train your mind.
Here we go.
It's a tough training
that can only be done
at a waterfall without a basin.
It looks tough!
This must be hard.
Leader!
This is crazy!
Seriously!
Water pressure is so strong.
By enduring the strong impact
on their entire body,
they train their body and mind.
Chappu? Are you serious?
Seriously?
He goes to rescue him right away.
Pull him out, Iwashita.
After the training,
the members of the expedition
are now united even more strongly.
Tomorrow, they'll visit
the underground cave,
which will be quite tough.
Here comes the last day.
From Amami Oshima,
they go to Okinoerabujima,
which is where the cave is.
It's an island with a circumference
of 50 kilometres,
and there are 300 large
and small caves on the island.
The island has attracted many people
in recent years,
as the holy ground of caving.
Our guides, Arikawa and Daido,
will show our team the way.
About the cave
we are going to today,
for people who want to go caving
on Okinoerabujima,
we offer the basic course.
Only people who finished the basic
course can go to this cave.
You all haven't done
the basic course,
and you will be doing
something very advanced.
You'll need to do this
with a strong determination.
Please wait.
What should we do?
I think we can do it.
Thank you.
Chappu?
- We can do it for sure.
- You should wait.
You'll drag us down, guaranteed.
A terrifying underground cave
where their screams echo!
It's a cave called Ginsuido,
which is beneath this jungle.
It's a tough road to get there,
but when they reach the place,
there will be beautiful
terraced stalactites.
The small hole you can see over
there is the entrance of Ginsuido.
- What?
It looks creepy.
The entrance is already difficult
to get past.
It's already very tight.
What is this?
It looks crazy.
They crawl on all fours
for 20 metres in a river.
I've never done this before.
Crawling itself is quite hard.
But on top of that, rocks on the
ground cut their palms and knees.
Chappu and Okasan,
are you two all right?
- Okasan is in there.
- Yes.
We're fine.
It's a tough route that has not
been maintained at all.
They move forward carefully.
- It's a coral fossil.
- Here it is.
This is it.
This island was underwater before,
and corals grew there.
Okinoerabujima is an island formed
by the uplift of a coral reef.
Therefore, the ground is fragile,
and numerous caves have been formed
by groundwater erosion.
This part looks crazy.
They pass an area
with a low ceiling again.
They crawl in water.
We should take a break.
Let's cool down.
Wait.
Chappu, Okasan,
you look like you're at the beach.
You look like a married couple
watching kids playing in water.
Here comes the hardest part
of the cave.
This tiny hole is the only way
to get past this area.
This continues?
Yes, it continues to the back.
It's the hardest part.
This is crazy.
I barely fit in this.
It's only 20 centimetres from
the ceiling to the water surface.
This place is insane!
They move forward slowly
while facing up.
Wow.
It's dangerous when people panic,
so they all try to keep calm.
All of the members successfully pass
the hardest part of the cave.
Now, they're halfway there.
From here on, the cave starts
to look completely different.
What is this?
It's a beautiful world
of stalactites.
They're spirals.
Spirals.
They're spiralling
stalactite icicles called spirals.
Water drips quicker than the others.
I see.
- The shapes change based on that.
- Interesting.
This looks pretty.
Calcium carbonate crystals
in stalactites sparkle.
It's rare to see particles this big.
They sparkle a lot.
You're right.
It's been three hours
since they entered the cave.
Once they go down
this vertical waterfall,
the goal will be near.
We're almost there!
- Okay.
- Impressive.
Next is Iwashita,
who has a fear of heights.
Look at your face.
Your face, Iwashita!
Relax! You look really tense.
And...
Wow, it's so white.
This is the best viewpoint.
It's a completely different colour.
I've never seen it before.
I've never seen this before.
Glossy stalactites
in a pure white colour,
and completely transparent water.
Incredible.
They will instal about
30 white lights in this area.
Here's the view.
I'll look now.
It's beautiful!
It's such a beautiful cave.
It's a series of terraced
stalactite pools,
which is 50 metres long
and 30 metres wide.
A mystical scenery that exists
underground of a tropical island.
These pools are so pretty!
- This is quite rare, isn't it?
- Yes.
They line up like a paillette,
and depending on the angle,
the water has a deep blue colour
or an emerald green colour.
On this day,
there was plenty of water,
and according to the guide,
it was the perfect condition.
That's great.
Chappu, Okasan, are you okay?
Yes.
Ginsuido was formed
over millions of years.
After a rough journey,
the expedition members
finally reached
the depths of the cave.
There, we saw water
illuminated by simple lights,
glowing in different colours.
It's a miraculous product!
Good job.
"Chappu has reached the next level"
Look forward to the next adventure
of the Miyagawa Expedition!
Was it not for our calendar?
This wasn't for our calendar.
- That was calendar material.
- Definitely!
It was the prettiest of all places
Daisuke had visited.
To be honest.
You should replace
the high diving with this.
"October"
Here's the next section!
Go to the End of the World
and Stay There!
Yes!
Miyazon, what did you do this time?
This time, I went to see
autumn leaves, which is perfect now.
Autumn leaves.
It wasn't just visiting a place
with great autumn leaves.
We actually rented a helicopter,
and went up north from Tokyo
to visit different places.
Really?
Was it a fun trip?
Fun trip? No.
It was a super fun trip!
I see.
The journey began in Tokyo Heliport
in Koto Ward, Tokyo.
Here I am at the heliport!
Autumn has finally arrived
Autumn leaves are the best part
Of autumn
Let's take a helicopter
To see autumn leaves
Helicopters are perfect for autumn
Autumn is perfect for helicopters
Helicopters are perfect
For helicopters
Helicopters
Helicopters.
On this trip,
he'll take this helicopter
and visit different places in Japan
to see autumn leaves.
It looks so cool!
I've always wanted to go
on a helicopter since I was a child.
I'm actually getting quite excited.
- You're doing well.
- Yes.
Let's go see the autumn leaves.
- That's great.
- Yes, I am surprised myself.
This time, we prepared a helicopter
dedicated to filming.
We'll shoot footage
that you would never see,
unless you're Superman.
Rest assured.
Did you already start using tables
with heaters?
Stay warm and enjoy the show.
Now, the helicopter
autumn leaves tour begins!
They travel 700 kilometres north
from Tokyo
to Lake Towada, Aomori Prefecture.
I'll see you later.
Now, the helicopter
autumn leaves tour begins!
The first thing he sees is...
Wow, that's Tokyo Tower!
You don't get a lot of opportunities
to look down on Tokyo Tower.
Also on the left side,
I see Sky Tree.
On GoPro, it might appear small,
but with my naked eyes,
I can see it very close.
That's Nippon TV.
I went there earlier today.
Incredible.
I'm passing above Nippon TV.
I see.
Nippon TV is thinner than I thought.
After flying for 30 minutes,
the helicopter enters
Tochigi Prefecture.
Whoa, look!
I see Irohazaka.
It's curving.
It's beautiful.
The first autumn leaves stop is
Irohazaka in Nikko City,
Tochigi Prefecture.
During this season,
the place is crowded with drivers.
It's really a winding road.
This road connects Nikko City
to Okunikko.
There are 48 curves total,
and each curve is named after
the Japanese syllabary.
I'd love to go see it.
Let's go to Irohazaka.
- Yes!
- Awesome.
I landed.
Thank you!
We'll use this kind of system
this time.
Iroha ni hoheto.
"It's Miyazon!"
The guide was the one
who called my name.
He said, "To your left is Miyazon."
He goes up to a viewing platform.
Could it be that we'll see
a great view with autumn leaves?
It's Kegon Waterfalls!
It's pretty!
Let's go closer to the waterfalls.
Wow!
- It's impressive.
- Anything can happen on this show.
I've never seen the waterfalls
from this angle.
Amazing.
Waterfalls!
And autumn leaves!
Kegon Waterfalls is considered one
of the three greatest waterfalls.
Water is falling
among autumn leaves.
Behind it,
Lake Chuzenji can be seen.
It looks impressive.
Especially from a helicopter.
The waterfall is very tall.
The helicopter starts heading
slightly east.
There's a massive thing.
What's that?
He sees a statue that sticks out
compared to buildings around it.
I already know what it is.
It's Buddha.
This is Ushiku Daibutsu
in Ushiku, Ibaraki Prefecture.
It's the tallest bronze statue
in the world,
which is 120 metres tall.
I saw the Statue of Liberty
in New York.
This is as impressive as that.
It's three times taller
than the Statue of Liberty.
Three times? I thought so.
This one seems more free.
Here!
Thank you!
Here I am.
Look at this. It's huge!
Miyazon actually loves
Buddha statues.
There are lotus flowers
at the bottom.
You often hear
about Hail Lotus Sutra.
Hail Lotus Sutra means,
"I believe in the training
of the lotus flowers."
To make flowers bloom out of mud.
That's what it's teaching us.
- We need to take off our shoes.
- Yes.
- Put them in a bag.
- Really?
These days, plastic bags
cost three to five yen.
- Is it free?
- It's included.
Are you sure? Thank you.
This is the Buddha's toe.
This is the actual size. It's huge.
It's a toe in the actual size.
Just the nail is already
over one metre long.
There's a souvenir store.
- Nice.
- There...
I think I'll buy this.
Miyazon wants to get a miniature
Ushiku Daibutsu.
It's 4,300 yen.
Mr Yamamoto, do you want one?
Director Shirai?
I think I'll get three of them.
One for each.
As a gift?
They check the stock right away.
We have nine of them.
You have nine of them?
Should I buy them in bulk?
I'll take the entire box.
Thank you.
- Really?
- I'll take them.
I've never seen anyone
buy Buddha statues in bulk.
Thank you very much.
I'll need a receipt
addressed to Miyazono.
The helicopter continues
heading east.
The Pacific Ocean comes into view.
What's that red thing
behind the ferris wheel?
What is that?
It looks like autumn leaves.
I've never seen anything so red.
What is that?
Hey, please don't push!
Wow, look at this!
It looks incredible
on the ground, too!
He is visiting Hitachi Seaside Park.
There are fluffy ball-like plants
everywhere he sees.
They are also autumn leaves that
can only be seen during this season.
These are kokia plants!
They're usually green
and look like round green algae.
But during this season,
they change colours
and have a vivid red colour.
Here, Miyazon has a quiz
about kokia.
Once withered,
this plant turns into something.
What do you think it is?
- What is it?
- Mr Uchimura,
answer me within one second.
One second has already passed,
but you're fine.
Really? It's okay?
I'm sorry. Wrong!
Here's the answer.
I'm sorry.
- Here it is.
- What's going on?
Do you know what it is?
A broom.
Here it is.
It turns into a broom!
They're also known as broom plant.
In olden times,
they used this plant to make brooms.
Belvedere fruit,
which is also known as field caviar,
is actually processed kokia seeds.
I'll call this land coral leaf.
That sounds good.
Miyazon wants to find
a great metaphor for kokia.
But "land coral leaf" is...
Someone has already said it.
Okay, let's come up
with something else.
This one is very unique.
Land...
round red algae.
How about that?
Land round green algae.
Round green algae...
- A lot has said that?
- Everyone.
Everyone calls it that.
Can I have one last thing?
Land soccer ball.
Land soccer ball
is just a soccer ball.
That's right.
Miyazon finds that someone else has
a great talent in using metaphors.
What kind of metaphor would you use?
For example, oysters are often
called "milk of the sea".
A festive theatre of brooms.
He did better than me.
The goal in Aomori
is 550 kilometres away.
But here, he receives
unfortunate news.
We'll take a car from here.
What?
Not a helicopter?
It's because of our budget.
I see.
I'm staying positive.
If I said, "What? Why?
Why can't I take a helicopter?"
Then I'd sound like
a Hollywood star.
So from here on,
they head north by car.
They head to Narukokyo, a famous
autumn leaves spot in Tohoku.
Now, take a look at their
spontaneous trip to Narukokyo.
First is a great gyoza shop
in Utsunomiya, Tochigi Prefecture.
They have various kinds of gyoza,
and they're incredibly tasty.
But that wasn't it.
The shop owner was a folk singer,
and he started singing.
That's the last one, so please eat
while listening to my song.
It's the very last
gyoza
It makes it hard to eat.
A lodge in Tochigi Prefecture
that takes forever to check in.
What?
Are we in Egypt?
Is this a pyramid?
This place is called
Pyramid Genki Onsen.
Welcome.
Thank you.
- Nice to meet you.
- I like stuff like this.
I'd like to stay
at this inn tonight.
Sure, no problem.
I hear "Fur Elise" playing.
Why did you build a pyramid?
It's because of the energy
of the universe.
- Okay.
- Well,
- it's a long time ago, but
- Okay.
we had this thing
called Pyramid Power.
We gathered the energy here,
and concentrated it to one point.
We then put it in our bath.
That's what we did.
Sorry, I couldn't hear anything
because of "Fur Elise".
Thank you.
I'll go in.
When he thought
he could finally check in...
That light there and this...
He starts to talk
about the facility.
I couldn't say no to him
because I knew he meant well.
It lasted for about 30 minutes.
He told me about different things.
If you lay down here,
you'll be asleep within 10 minutes.
How is it?
You'll get sleepy.
No matter what you're thinking,
it's okay,
because you'll get sleepy.
Can I check in now?
Sure.
Charred roasted pork
in Fukushima Prefecture.
It looks pretty!
Shirakawa Ramen
is a local speciality
of Shirakawa City, Fukushima.
- This looks great.
- It was great.
How nice.
It's incredible.
The noodles are great.
Their roasted pork is also good.
It's a bit charred...
How should I put it?
It has a good aroma.
No, it's just burnt.
Really?
Cameraman Yamamoto's routine.
Here's Yamamoto.
- Is he studying something?
- He's taking medicine.
What kind of medicine do you take?
For my blood pressure,
- cholesterol,
- I'm worried about him.
- blood pressure,
- You're kidding.
- uric acid level,
- Don't go on a trip then.
- allergy.
- It's hard to live.
Tsuruga Castle in Fukushima that
didn't have autumn leaves at all.
Is this it?
Illuminated autumn leaves.
This?
How did this happen?
He is the reason.
I'm Hoshi from the tourism division
of the city.
Mr Yuto Hoshi.
Leaves are just starting
to change colours.
You came here a bit too early.
We were talking about
painting the leaves.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because you wouldn't have come
if we told you.
Kaleidoscope Museum in Miyagi
that they visited unannounced.
Did you see that?
It says kaleidoscope. It's a museum.
I want to go
because I like sparkly things.
He calls them right away.
I bought that at a roadside station.
Thank you for calling,
this is Kaleidoscope Museum.
Hi there, my name is Miyazono.
I'm filming a show called
"The Quest".
- Okay.
- We're on a filming trip right now.
Okay.
We'd love to stop by at your museum.
When do you plan to visit?
Actually, we're already in front
of the museum entrance.
What?
The most popular part of the museum
is a kaleidoscope
into which you stick your head in,
perfect for Instagram.
It's pretty.
It feels like I'm inside
of a piece of jewel.
- This looks nice.
- It reminds me of my childhood.
My family was so poor
and we didn't have toys.
So we'd get cardboard boxes
from a vegetable shop nearby.
I'd stick my head
in a cardboard box like this.
It was a way for me
to be in my own world.
This reminds me of those times.
After three whole days,
Miyazon arrives
at Narukokyo, Miyagi Prefecture.
- Wow!
- Everything is so short.
What a great view.
Incredible!
Natukokyo, Miyagi Prefecture.
Sheer cliffs up to 100 metres deep
are covered in autumn leaves.
The white bridge over here
brings all the colours together.
- That's true.
- So pretty.
When you see it, you understand
that those pine trees
are working very well.
They have a deep green colour, which
looks great against other colours.
That's why we get these colours.
I see.
Narukokyo.
"Kyo" in Narukokyo
doesn't mean "bridge".
It doesn't? I'm sorry.
I saw that this place
is called Narukokyo.
But it doesn't mean "bridge."
I see.
Then what is that bridge?
Miyazon receives good news here.
To the next autumn leaves spot,
we'll take a helicopter.
Yes!
Here it is!
Let's go!
- Awesome.
- Here.
Now I'm back on the helicopter.
The helicopter continues
to head north.
Then, something comes into view.
It's a massive lake!
It's huge!
Here's the last autumn leaves spot.
Lake Towada, Aomori.
Because of the complex terrain,
there's a wide variety of trees,
where visitors enjoy
different types of autumn leaves.
Autumn leaves and a lake
look great together.
Let's go down then.
Around that spot.
Around there.
Here we go.
I came down.
Miyazon even travelled through time,
and now it's sunrise time.
The sun is rising slowly.
I can see it!
It's a few centimetres away.
Then the entire sun will appear.
Then...
The sun has risen!
It's beautiful!
Ta-da!
- Good morning!
- Good morning.
When the sun rises,
autumn leaves are illuminated
by the sun, and glow orange.
You don't get to have
a morning like this very often.
You see?
You usually wake up to an alarm
to go to work.
You then set the snooze
for another 15 minutes.
Snooze, snooze.
Many people have mornings like that,
but not today.
Despite taking a lot of detours,
Miyazon fully enjoyed autumn leaves
in different parts of Japan.
How did you like it?
Everyone has different opinions,
but I assume about
70 per cent of people
who watched the show
thought it looked wonderful.
Okay, now let's go back
to the studio!
Here I go!
I do this to go up to an airplane
or come down from it.
That's all for Miyazon's
autumn leaves tour.
There were so many things
other than autumn leaves.
That's true.
It was quite messy.
What I remember the most right now
is the amount of medicine.
- The cameraman's.
- Yes, Cameraman Yamamoto's.
But they only spent 30 seconds
to show each place.
We'd be angry
if that happened to us.
What I remember the most
is how delicious the ramen looked.
It looked great!