The Quest.
Today's first segment is...
Daisuke Miyagawa's
Way to Japanese Festivals.
A certain day.
Here it is.
You startled me.
I hit it.
Ow.
The season of festival
has come this month.
You'll be surprised.
Do you feel like you're older
or you've become weaker?
It's sad, but I do.
I turn 49 this September.
I'm 49.
Of course... of course
I've got many things.
I have various old wounds too.
When the rainy season comes,
the old wound I got from
the Cheese Rolling Festival...
It's my medal.
Where's that?
My neck.
You say that all the time.
Even 15 years after
the Cheese Rolling Festival.
It's true.
No matter which osteopathic clinic
I go to,
they say my neck is bad.
They ask if I've had an accident,
I'd say, "I haven't."
"Had it been subjected
to impact, then?"
"Oh, the Cheese Rolling Festival.
I guess that's it."
The stages this time are Hokkaido
and Hiroshima Prefecture.
Okay, let's go!
Hokkaido, Hiroshima, here I come!
What kind of festivals
await him this time?
"The Quest"
Welcome to The Quest.
Today, it's Daisuke Miyagawa's
Way to Japanese Festivals,
and Asako Ito's Mystery Tour.
Wasshoi!
"Morisanchu"
Hello...
Hello!
Hello, everyone.
"Daisuke Miyagawa's fishing trip"
"Scallop fishing &amp; bicycle race"
I'm impressed by the champion!
It's so difficult.
It's what chimpanzees ride.
Who's this person? Go away! No!
It's coming... No!
It hit my crotch!
Daisuke Miyagawa's
Way to Japanese Festivals.
He has come to Toyoura Town
in Hokkaido.
Wasshoi!
The place I have come to
is Toyoura Town in Hokkaido.
Have a look at this.
Unfortunately, it's cloudy,
but this is a nice place.
Festival Guy in Hokkaido,
bring it on!
Hello.
Our guide is...
Funkawan Toyoura Tourism
Association's Directorgeneral,
Mr Takamitsu Okamoto.
Is this festival dangerous?
It isn't dangerous, but...
It isn't, but?
You need observation skills.
Observation skills?
Quick response.
Quick response?
And irritation.
Irritation?
It depends on how much irritation
you can give.
How much irritation I can give?
I am the one who irritates?
I'm not on the receiving end?
I'll irritate?
How do you do it?
Like this.
A whip! It's a whip!
It's like this,
or like this.
What?
You kneeled. On the other knee?
What's this?
On one knee.
On one knee?
On both knees.
Both knees!
What's that?
It's like some technique.
It's done at the championship.
You'll irritate something when you
compete in this world championship.
Wait, I don't get it.
It's a world championship?
Yes, it is.
Has the champion been
winning consecutive years?
Someone had won
three years in a row.
Will that person come today?
Please give me some time.
They go to the venue this time,
Toyoura Town
Regional Exchange Centre.
Mr Miyagawa,
please have a look at that.
What did Miyagawa see there?
It's men pulling up scallops.
Wait a minute. It's scallop fishing?
This is Toyoura World
Scallop Fishing Championship.
What?
In the Toyoura
World Scallop Fishing Championship.
Participants will pull up scallops
in the tank within the limited time,
and see who gets the biggest number.
Toyoura Town here faces Funkawan,
the culture of scallop thrives,
and it has more than 50 years
of history.
The Scallop Fishing Championship
was cancelled in 2020 and 2021,
so everyone is looking forward
to it being held again.
It's like this.
Put the needle in the place
you find to irritate it.
Startle it, so that it closes.
That's right.
Here it goes...
It falls if it doesn't bite firmly.
Is that so?
Yes.
Like him... Oh, he's skilled.
When you take it off...
Quick response. That's it.
Yes, this.
Everyone, that looks a bit like...
the prowrestling group's colouring.
But it isn't, right?
We didn't copy it.
Yes, you did.
Isn't it New Japan Prowrestling?
No...
You copied it.
No. Not at all.
You didn't?
Is that so?
Yeah.
Wait, that's NJPW!
Now, he'll practise the real thing.
Please tell me the official rules.
Okay.
There are healthy scallops
in the water tank,
you'll catch as many as you can
in three minutes.
Three minutes.
Yes.
He'll use a fishing rod
specifically for scallops.
It's a stretched curtain rail.
Yes.
How do you know?
Yeah.
There's a red part on the rod,
you must not hold or touch
any part other than that.
When you're fishing,
do not touch the line.
People tend to do that,
but it's not allowed.
If you focus on the scallops
too much,
you might wrap the line
around the rod's tip.
Yes, you might.
It's easier to fish if it's shorter.
Yes.
If it wraps around the tip once,
it's not allowed.
I see.
There's something I'd like you
to pay attention to most.
It's against the rule
to say anything insulting
about Toyoura's scallop.
"What's this stupid scallop?"
I can't say that?
No, you can't.
We're using the scallops
fishermen cultured with love
for the competition,
so treat the scallops with love.
Makes sense.
If violation like this is found
by the judge,
it's a yellow scallop.
He just wanted to do this.
If you get one, you'll be suspended
for 15 seconds.
Wow, it costs a lot.
It does.
You have a red one too?
Leave at once?
Leave at once!
It's insult towards the judge.
I see. "That one counts, idiot!"
No, not allowed.
It's not allowed.
It's going to be lively.
Very.
It's funny before it starts.
He tries scallop fishing
based on these rules.
I put it here like this,
put it in like this.
Yes.
irritate it here.
Irri... oh.
It came out.
I see. When I irritate it,
it might come out.
Yes.
I'll go here like this...
Where I let it bite matters too.
Yes.
Instead of the chipped part,
put it at the edge...
Put it here, pull, and caught it.
Well done!
And the quick response.
Is this okay?
Yes, hold it and pull it out.
Hold, and the quick response.
That's what I do?
Yes.
He's so good at it!
Now Miyagawa demonstrates his talent
in scallop fishing.
Is this okay here?
Yes.
I see.
At this time, this is okay, right?
You're good at it.
This champion
for three years in a row,
how many scallops did he catch
in three minutes?
It's a world record.
The champion caught
15 in three minutes.
15 scallops?
In other words, the champion caught
one scallop every 12 seconds.
Oh? Maybe I can do it.
Really? One per 12 seconds.
Count 12 seconds for me.
Ready, start.
One, two, three, four, five, six...
A scallop that has opened
doesn't always bite.
10, 11, 12.
Wow, I'm impressed by the champion!
If the position of this is right,
it enters easily,
but it might become straight
when I put it in.
This one is the one
that bothers me most.
I want to go for this one
when I get impatient,
but it hasn't bitten even once.
It has only been doing...
There probably is a trick to it.
In the scallop fishing circle...
Scallop fishing circle?
Yes.
He hasn't become a champion yet,
but he is just as good
as the champion,
and he has come here
to teach you today.
He's called the scallop fishing
circle's Unfinished Great Talent.
The name makes me feel sorry
for him.
I wish you wouldn't tell him
if that's the case.
Our unfinished great talent,
Mr Fumihiro Kobayashi.
Yay!
That's right, he is...
Mr Kobayashi, who has the ability
but hasn't become the champion.
Would you teach me
how to target them,
or irritate them...
Oh, you kneel on one knee.
I can only kneel
on one knee physically.
You start from finding your scallop.
The compatibility of the direction
of the hook and the scallop.
I see!
It's already started.
I see.
Instead of matching the scallop,
it's the hook.
When you've put the hook in,
irritate the scallop.
We call it Beat Fishing.
Give it the beat, then pull it up.
Okay...
You call this irritation
"Beat Fishing?"
It's a wellknown technique
among the scallop fishing circle.
Beat Fishing.
You do Beat Fishing,
then Mach Detaching.
Mach Detaching?
You didn't pull it out like this
just now. What is it?
Beat Fishing...
Knock, knock, knock.
Pull, pull, pull.
Okay.
Mach Detaching.
It's like... Mum's laundry.
You pull them down in one go.
Beat Washing.
That's Beat Washing?
There isn't a name like that.
Hang on.
You can improvise.
Brilliant.
We don't wait till it turns to us,
we put it inside, let it bite.
Beat Fishing.
Let it bite.
And then...
Mach Detaching.
Amazing!
Have you done it before?
No, I haven't.
You successfully did something
I just taught you.
If I can keep doing this, I can win!
I'll fill up the bucket
in three minutes.
Miyagawa's performance
will be amazing, starting now.
Ready, go.
Put it in, then...
I'll give this up.
I'll match this
and insert it like this.
Do Beat Fishing.
Pull it up,
Mach Detaching.
What's this?
Put it in like this.
Then Beat Fishing.
When it bites, pull it up.
Mach Detaching.
I can do it!
Miyagawa has grasped the gist.
Like this. Beat Fishing.
And then pull it up,
Mach Detaching.
He learnt it with
a terribly fast speed.
Okay.
Mach Detaching.
He's so skilled!
I think I can fight like this.
Lastly, when I compete
against the champion,
please give me some advice.
When you catch scallops,
you can each use one water tank.
Yes.
Use as much of it as you can.
I see.
Mr Kobayashi, you want to defeat
the champion too, right?
I do.
I'll carry your wish,
and defeat the champion!
Thank you!
The time of battle has come.
Call the champion!
The World Scallop Fishing
Championship's
three times champion,
Ms Sasagawa!
So cool!
What?
What...
They got the wrong one?
What?
That's right,
this is the threetime champion
of the World Scallop Fishing
Championship,
the absolute champion in
the hall of fame, Harumi Sasagawa.
I assumed it was a gentleman.
I thought it was an old man.
People always say that.
When did you participate
for the first time?
It was in 2011.
2011.
You participated for the first time,
and became the champion?
Yes.
What?
Why are you so good
at fishing scallops?
I practised secretly,
I think nobody else practised
at that time.
How do you practise?
I restore the scallops I've eaten
to their original state...
But isn't it difficult?
It doesn't bite.
The shell opens to a certain extent,
doesn't it?
I make some easy ones,
and some that are closing
and difficult to catch,
and practised by inserting the hook.
Wow... that's impressive!
We're on different levels.
Let's do it.
Toyoura Scallop Fishing
World Championship,
special version,
starts now.
The Toyoura Scallop Fishing
World Championship has started.
If Miyagawa wins, he'll get
a year's worth of scallops.
If the champion wins,
she'll get a happi vest
with Miyagawa's autograph.
The match will kick off soon.
You'll have three minutes.
Ready, fight!
It starts now!
First, Miyagawa goes for
a small scallop.
Wow, he already pulled one up!
What about the champion?
She pulled one up.
But Miyagawa is catching
scallops too! He's in the lead!
He wants to put a gap between them,
Miyagawa doesn't go for
scallops that don't react.
A good tactic!
Oh! It came off!
Stay calm.
The venue is enveloped in silence.
The champion is catching up
to Miyagawa.
Do your best!
You can do it!
But she's caught one!
Miyagawa isn't beaten!
Miyagawa is currently in the lead.
How about this?
He pulled this up!
I'm impressed.
Will Miyagawa go for one more?
Can he?
Oh, it came off!
The condition is good.
One minute passed.
Don't get impatient.
The champion is catching up too.
The advanceandretreat continues.
It's a good match!
Miyagawa wants to catch one more!
You can do it!
Beat Fishing,
then Mach Detaching!
He made it!
It's amazing.
But the champion is catching up.
No wonder she's the champion.
Miyagawa puts the hook into
the scallop's opening carefully.
This is the difficult part.
It bit! It bit!
Ah! It dropped!
But who would've thought
this would happen?
Miyagawa is cornering the champion.
He caught another one!
Champion... Oh, it dropped!
Now, Miyagawa has a chance to win!
The champion caught one.
Miyagawa does Beat Fishing!
Beat Fishing, and...
Mach... Oh, he can't take it off!
It's stuck there!
There's less than one minute left.
At whom will the goddess
of victory smile?
The champion caught one again!
Miyagawa's hand is shaking!
His hand is shaking and can't put
the hook into the scallop well.
My hand is shaking.
It's shaking, as you can see.
Can he catch it?
He pulled it up!
30 seconds left.
It's the last spurt!
Now the champion pulls one up!
That's why she is called a legend.
And then...
Two in a row!
Miyagawa's hook doesn't go in!
10 seconds left.
He's panicking.
Instead of Miyagawa,
the champion catches up quickly.
The champion caught one again.
The match is over now.
I don't know...
It was a good match.
What's the result?
Did I lose?
No idea. No idea.
We'll announce the result.
Champion Sasagawa
caught 12 scallops.
Impressive.
The champion caught 12 scallops.
And Miyagawa...
Mr Miyagawa's record is...
eight scallops.
It's so frustrating!
The champion won!
Oh? Oh?
I feel so frustrated!
Champion, what does festival
mean to you?
It didn't occur to me I could be
the champion three times in a row,
so I thought the effort I made
wasn't wasted.
Indeed, it's important
to make effort and practise.
That shows in the real match.
Our town's fishermen spend
their lives nurturing the scallops,
that's why we can use them
to hold the championship.
Our whole region will use
the festival to tell the world
how good Toyoura Town is,
we'll continue to do our best.
That's right.
Thank you so much.
It was a wonderful festival.
The next place he goes to is...
Wasshoi!
The place I have come to
is Innoshima, Onomichi City,
Hiroshima Prefecture.
This place is wonderful!
Our guide
is Oyama Shrine's chief priest,
Mr Takashi Makihata.
Is this a dangerous festival?
It isn't dangerous,
but the ability to balance
is important.
I only have a bad feeling
about this.
They go to Oyama Shrine,
the stage of the battle.
Mr Miyagawa.
Yes.
Have a look at that.
What?
What did Miyagawa see there?
Mr Miyagawa.
Yes.
Have a look at that.
What?
What did Miyagawa see there?
A man riding a bicycle
slowly on a board.
This is
the Bicycle Shrine Festival's
Slow Log Bridge Race.
Participants cycle slowly on a board
without falling,
and they'll compete their time
against each other's.
Oyama Shrine here
is the oldest shrine in Innoshima,
it was built in 773.
It brings safety to traffic,
and cyclists who cycle around
the Seto Inland Sea visit here,
so it is called Bicycle Shrine.
The Bicycle Shrine Festival is held
annually to celebrate the deity.
It's here.
It's eight metres long.
Eight metres.
The log bridge is eight metres long,
which is good luck in Japan.
It is about 25 centimetres wide.
How slowly did the last time's
champion cycle?
It was 8.63 seconds.
8.63 seconds.
Yes.
So it's one metre per second?
It's quite difficult.
Is that so? After what you said,
I thought maybe I could do it.
Now, he will practise.
We prepared four kinds of bicycles
for him this time.
Can I try them one by one?
He'll start from the city bicycle.
Miyagawa tries the Slow Log Bridge
the first time.
Will he be able to do it?
Oh, it's difficult.
It fell down the board.
The shrine has a bit of a slope.
I'm climbing up slightly.
It's so hot.
The temperature is 35 degrees,
and he tries the other bicycles too.
This is difficult.
Wow, it's so difficult.
It's so difficult!
Wow...
It's what chimpanzees ride.
By the way, this bicycle...
is the Chief Priest's granddaughter
Aoi's bicycle.
But this bicycle will make
an incredible record.
It's amazing.
Isn't he doing well?
Wow.
Isn't this good?
9.50 seconds.
He made an unprecedented record
of 9.50 seconds.
It's surprisingly easy
to balance on this.
Even if I pedal,
the wheels are small,
so it doesn't go forward much.
I can do it by finetuning this.
But...
If I use this and win,
won't I look bad?
Which bicycle will Miyagawa use
in the race?
The time of battle has come.
I'm getting exhausted in this heat,
but in the final match,
I'll cycle slowly once.
Please ask the champion to come.
Champion of Slow Log Bridge Race,
Mr Ichimura!
Here he is! Wow!
He is tanned.
Nice to meet you.
This is the record keeper of
the longest time on the log bridge,
Champion, Osamu Ichimura.
Do you usually ride a bicycle?
I cycle every day.
Every day!
Do you participate every time?
Well...
I happened to participate
and happened to win.
Wow!
Today, safety comes first too.
Looking forward to it.
Okay, let's have a match.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's do it. Slow Log Bridge Race,
special version,
starts now.
Let's do it. Slow Log Bridge Race,
special version,
starts now.
I will explain the rule.
On the eightmetreslong board,
they'll compete to see
who cycles more slowly.
If Miyagawa wins,
he'll get a Setouchi cyclewear.
The champion will go first.
How will he cycle?
Do your best.
It'll start
when the taiko drum stops.
It's a moment of nervousness.
Now, start!
He got on the log bridge.
It's fast too!
He brakes and holds out.
Alright.
He reaches the goal now.
His record is 4.08 seconds.
Is he nervous?
Miyagawa, this is your chance!
Okay, let's go!
The champion's time
was only half of last time's.
But there's also a chance he'll fall
from the board and be disqualified.
Which bicycle will he choose?
Oh, it's Aoi's bicycle!
Aoi, I'll borrow this!
Besides his victory, he also wants
to achieve a great record.
After all, the champion's time
was four seconds.
The video will be boring
if he just wins.
Now, Miyagawa...
Now, it's the fateful start!
He's slow!
He gets on the board.
He's keeping his balance.
It's over if he falls.
Will he get a miraculous 10 seconds?
Can he?
Don't fall!
Miyagawa just crossed the goal!
How was it?
The result is...
7.62 seconds.
Yay!
7.62 seconds, Miyagawa wins!
But there was nothing
worth mentioning.
Thank you.
I admit defeat.
This time,
it's one win and one loss.
Thank you, everyone!
You know, Champion...
We were boring
when we were competing.
That's all for
Way to Japanese Festivals.
Thank you.
It looked like you met an uncle
you haven't seen for a while
and cycled with him.
No!
The champion was very nervous.
We were surprised too.
His speed...
We were watching,
and were wondering
how much time we should give him,
but he just went
and cycled on the board.
When the champion's time
was four seconds,
I thought you'd choose
another bicycle.
No, because I lost
the scallop match.
The scallop match too!
What?
Hold on, you have to complain
about the scallop too?
Well...
What?
The video was edited like you were
going to win till halfway.
You were catching them quickly,
and when they lined
the eight scallops up,
Mr Degawa and I went,
"I think he caught more?"
It... it wasn't me,
complain to the director
who did the editing.
But that's a television show.
If you show the actual video,
I was losing in the last minute
in the second half.
My opponent was making
sounds like "Boom! Boom!"
I heard the sound of scallops
going into the bucket many times.
I knew she caught more than me.
There's nothing to complain about.
But your hand shook.
You weren't irritating it,
your hand was shaking.
No...
No, I was doing the Beat Fishing.
You've been Beat Fishing
before you put the hook in.
He's been Beat Fishing
before putting the hook in.
You caught them quietly.
No sign of getting a yellow scallop.
Just quietly.
You went, "I can do it..."
and caught them.
I wanted to play games like that.
They have so many things to say.
I feel frustrated.
And you, Tetchan?
Well, the conclusion is,
even I can win
in the bicycle festival.
Three hours by bullet train
and car from Tokyo,
Asako Ito's Mystery Tour in Nara.
Hey.
You must be wondering!
Speaking of wondering,
the other day,
Miss Okubo said to me,
"Oh, Asako,
your "society's window" is open."
I looked, and it was open,
so I went, "Oh no!"
I glanced when I was zipping it,
and saw Miss Okubo's
"society's window" was also open.
You must be wondering!
Explanation of Asako's
dead language, "society window."
People from the Showa era describe
the state of an open zipper
as "the society's window is open."
She has come
to the World Heritage in Nara,
Todaiji Temple, as everyone knows.
It's so cool!
It's so overwhelming.
The statue is 14.98 metres tall,
it's Nara's Great Buddha.
It's really impressive.
In the Nara period 1,300 years ago,
an actual seven years
were spent to erect this.
So cute! So cute...
She talks to the monk, Mr Tsutsui.
It's said that at that time,
the number of people involved
in building this Todaiji Temple
was 2.6 million.
2.6 million?
Yes.
It's about half of the population
at that time.
Half of Japan's population
gathered at Nara?
Yes.
Maybe your ancestor
was also involved
in building the Buddha statue.
So we'll give you a quiz
on the Buddha.
Have a look at the Buddha statue.
At the centre of its forehead,
there's something like
a mole or a wart.
What is it?
Mr Degawa, please answer.
What?
Me?
Well... something like
Ultraman's Colour Timer?
We'll now announce
the correct answer.
It's white hair called Urna.
Its kanji character
is the difficult version.
When he was thinking hard about
how to achieve enlightenment,
his hair here hardened
and became that shape.
The hair on his head also hardened
by wisdom in the same way,
and it is called Rahotsu.
My curly hair gets more and more
curly every year,
and it's gradually getting frizzly.
It shows that you have wisdom.
There are many theories.
The Mystery Tour in Nara starts!
Go wild! Pupils from the whole
country rush to this training hall.
This is the training hall.
What? Souvenir shop?
Hello.
Welcome.
He has the scooper in his hand
when he welcomes me.
This is a goldfish scooping
training hall.
Yamatokoriyama City here is
a big production area of goldfish.
So goldfish scooping thrives,
a world championship
is held every summer.
Wow!
It currently has over 400 pupils.
Among them, there are strong people
who are ranked.
They are the Ito Sisters, who are
1stdan and 3rddan respectively.
Do you both like goldfish scooping?
Yes.
Let the rank holders
show us their true abilities.
How many can they scoop
in three minutes?
They're so calm!
What? They're so calm!
Why doesn't the scooper break?
Even in the goldfish scooping
world championship,
the Ito Sisters rank high.
They polish their skill
at the training hall every day.
Three, two, one, stop.
They scooped this many
in three minutes.
Let's count the number.
44.
Wow.
Oh, it's the same!
They can scoop one
every four, five seconds.
When Asako tries to scoop...
If it breaks in the centre,
it shows you're bad at it.
Aren't you harsh on someone
who does it the first time?
They teach us the basics
of goldfish scooping.
When you put the scooper in water,
do it at an angle,
which won't strain the paper.
Put it in at an angle,
go under a goldfish,
make it flat, then you can catch it.
When you lift it up,
do it at an angle.
That's all for the basics.
If you can do this, you can scoop
so many goldfish that it's funny.
Ms Ito, you want to scoop
the goldfish so much,
that they can feel the frenzy.
Don't say it's frenzy.
Asako will try to do the firstdan
certification examination.
She'll pass if she can scoop
10 in one minute.
It'll be boring if you just do it,
so if you can't pass,
you'll bungeejump.
That's awful!
Come on,
they're two different things.
It's awful, right?
You feel sorry for me, right?
Tell him you feel sorry for Asako.
Ready, go.
Miss Asako, do your best!
She's ranked as a comedian.
Let's do it, then!
Ready, go!
You can do it!
Do your best!
Asako has a good start
and scooped one.
Then the second one.
You can do it!
Three in a row.
She hides her frenzy
and scooped the fourth.
Wow...
She becomes firstdan
if she scoops 10.
If she can't, she'll bungeejump.
At that time...
Ah! No! No!
Please let me do it once more!
They feel sorry
for the middleaged lady.
She can't scoop anymore.
It's over.
I practised so much...
No! I don't want to do this!
I look forward to watching the show.
You must be wondering...
So...
I won't look down.
Really?
Asako is at...
30 metres above the ground,
the only Bridge Bungee in Kansai
built on the approach to a shrine.
It's called Goodluck Bungee.
You can do it!
They're nice. They're all so nice.
The whole audience
is cheering for her.
Can I do it?
You can!
Five, four, three, two, one.
She jumped.
The Goodluck Bungee is successful!
The whole audience praises her.
Sorry for taking up your time.
Thank you.
You measure your weight?
Why?
It's pointless!
The whole audience teases her.
I thought I lost weight after that.
We'll now introduce
the wonderful traditional culture
of the neighbouring
Wakayama Prefecture.
We've come to Kitayama Village.
On the water, it's a cedar raft
that looks like a train.
It's 30 metres long in total,
this is Kitayama Village's
traditional rafting.
Originally, it was a way
to transport timber,
and go down this river.
In the Edo period,
Kitayama Village was a major
production area of Japanese cedar.
Rafting is a traditional culture
that has existed for 600 years.
Rafter Asako will experience
the wonderful skill.
It suits her.
She encountered the rapids
right after it started.
Is this okay? What should I do?
The 30 metres long raft charges.
I'm scared...
Be careful. Hold it... It's coming!
It's coming! No!
It hit my crotch!
No!
It hit my crotch.
The raft weaves its way
through the rapids.
It's coming again...
Be careful.
No!
The drone is doing a good job.
It's amazing!
The men in front
are controlling the raft.
He skilfully handles the tiller
and controls the raft.
They go past a sharp turn
without bumping into it.
The raft behind follows,
just like a train.
It's a proficient skill
against mother nature.
There is a secret spot
at the valley in Wakayama.
The mysterious valley
where people yell.
Ooh!
Oh?
It's something that
I mustn't go near.
Next, it's a mysterious valley
where people yell.
Ooh!
Oh?
It's something
that I mustn't go near.
This is the person
who made the sound.
Hello.
Why did this gentleman yell?
It's the place you hear echoes
most beautifully in Japan.
Oh, indeed!
That's right.
"The place in Japan where
echoes come back most clearly."
This is Tsubakiyama Dam
in Hidakagawa Town,
it's the place in Japan
where echoes are the clearest.
Asako yells at once.
Yoohoo!
Wow!
It echoed three times!
I was on the opposite side!
I was there!
Wow!
Isn't this amazing?
Isn't it amazing?
Interesting!
It's different from
the echo I imagined.
The words are so clear.
Echo occurs when sound is reflected
by mountains or valleys.
The requirements for a clear echo
are that there should be no obstacle
in front of the target,
and the distance
should be 300 metres.
Also, if the target
is a parabola like this,
it collects sound effectively.
This is the "Yoohoo point"
that fulfils both requirements.
One day!
In the forest!
I met...
A bear!
It's sung beautifully in rounds.
But Asako is careless
and forgot to check something.
It's going to be a basic question.
Yes.
Who are you?
Me?
Sorry, I forgot to ask.
I just talked normally.
Well, it's a sad story.
There's an Echo Competition.
What's the standard?
Is it how beautifully it echoes?
Yes, that's the first thing.
And there's one more thing.
It's the comedy element.
You need a sense of humour.
Humour!
I'm the first runnerup.
Isn't it sad? I'm not the winner.
Mr Kobata, will you show us
your ability as the first runnerup?
Okay, I'll do it.
The head judge was over there.
The mayor?
His head was shiny.
Shiny. Okay.
Bright and shiny!
He got the second place
without making the mayor smile.
Then they started to shout what was
on their own mind at that place.
My waist is...
88.8!
It's an auspicious number.
It's what Wakayama Prefecture's
people think during the pandemic.
I want to visit Osaka!
A yell from his heart.
You want to go to Osaka?
Yes.
But I can't.
Then, it's Assistant Producer
Morikawa's turn.
I want to go back
to my parents' home!
I want to go home!
Nice.
It's desperate.
It is.
Then, our cameraman Yamamoto.
Blood pressure, go lower!
Is it a bit high?
It is.
It's about 150 over 100.
It's high!
Each of them is high.
Get my pension this year!
Get my pension!
Get what?
My pension.
Oh, Gramps, is that so?
Oh, wow!
Then, it's
Assistant Director Iwai's turn.
I want a boyfriend!
It doesn't echo for some reason.
So weak! Your voice is so weak!
You used a megaphone!
Next, it's technology in Nara.
Most advanced!
A research laboratory
that makes tools of the future.
We've come to Nara Institute
of Science and Technology.
This laboratory mainly uses VR
to study how to deceive
the human five senses.
Student, Mr Yoshimitsu
will tell us about it.
The goal of this
is to relieve stress,
it's a research on the sense
of touch to tickle yourself.
It's a serious research
that studies how to tickle yourself
to get rid of stress.
It's called...
Tickle Me.
The nuance is suddenly different.
When you wear the VR goggles,
a girl comes close to tickle you.
Combined with the sound
and the video,
the glove that expands and shrinks
can let you tickle yourself.
Many people want to be tickled
like this.
She is ready.
I don't feel anything yet, though.
Let's begin, then.
Okay.
But in Asako's case...
Oh!
"Tanma..." I'm scared!
What's wrong?
She's tickled like this by the girl
without using the gloves.
You're too close! No!
What's wrong with her? Go away!
No!
Stop saying "tickle!"
The gloves they did much research on
are crying.
Someone... oh?
It's over.
What?
Miss Asako.
The girl came straight to me.
Miss Asako, that's not the purpose.
She got too close
and I don't like it.
I don't want anyone in my area.
That girl went, "Tickle, tickle..."
What do you think about the result?
It's too unique.
What?
Here, we'll explain
Asako's dead language again.
"Tanma"... I'm scared!
People in the Showa era say "tanma"
when they mean "wait a minute,"
One theory says it was derived
from "time out" said with an accent.
Tanma... I'm scared!
Lastly, it's a robot that holds
a Guinness World Record.
Regular participant of the National
Technology College Robot Contest,
Nara National Institute
of Technology has the robot.
Nice to meet you.
They are the students.
This is the robot.
It's so cute!
The Guinness World Record
he holds is...
Hang on! It's more impressive
than I thought!
It's long rope jumping.
Its record
is 106 times in one minute.
It's a penguin robot
made for jumping.
Its name is Jumpen.
How does he jump?
It detects the skipping rope,
stretches his leg...
Oh, it stretches!
Yes.
After that, it's pulled in suddenly.
The sensor in the upper part
detects the rope.
Instead of jumping, the stretched
leg brings the body up,
then crosses the rope
by pulling the leg back suddenly.
The level of completion is brilliant
and was highly praised.
Instead of people matching a robot
that jumps singlemindedly,
he senses the rope and moves.
Now, they'll try
to create a new record.
I don't think there's a record
of a person jumping with a robot.
There isn't any yet?
No.
Probably the world's first,
a person and a robot will try
long rope jumping together.
Asako and Jumpen.
How many times can they jump?
Do your best!
Five, four, three, two, one.
Start.
Wow...
Look, in human history,
this is the first time a person
is skipping rope with a robot.
Amazing.
He's cute.
A bit to the front.
But actually,
before they come this far,
it had been a series
of twists and turns.
Start.
"Practising"
Wait, I'm sorry...
The timing Jumpen and Asako jump
are different,
so it's difficult to sync.
I see.
Oh, sorry.
What should I do? I'll be too late
if I jump twice in between.
If it's once, it hurts my knees
and it's painful.
To match Jumpen's pace,
Asako jumps slightly
in between each jump,
but it hurts her knees greatly.
Don't make it sound so serious.
My bone... my bone...
It hurts my bone.
I can't stand...
Not "Kite."
It isn't "Kite" here!
Thank you.
Jumpen will be full of energy again
after the battery is changed,
but Asako's knees won't be back.
Oh, there!
Thank you, Gramps.
We need you to do your best.
An old person caring for another.
They practised for two whole hours.
"Making the record"
30 seconds after it started,
Asako can't lift up her knees.
You can do it.
Now it depends on how long
Asako's battery will last.
Don't use "Kite" here!
Oh, sorry!
It's over here.
How many times?
What is the record?
It's 51 times.
51.
Thank you.
Oh, that's my age.
This is auspicious.
Thank you.
Don't use it like that!
I jumped the number of times
of my age.
Don't use that song!
That's all for Asako's Mystery Tour.