The Quest.
Today's first segment is...
Daisuke Miyagawa's
Way to Japanese Festivals.
A certain day.
Gosh, you startled me!
Come on,
I was going to watch the telly.
There's a photo
I'd like to show you.
What is it?
Oh, he lifted up the rock
the other day.
Mr Takeuchi.
Mr Takeuchi from the Rock Lifting
Competition Miyagawa joined,
and Mr Hayashi
from Gon Gon Festival.
The two gentlemen
are in the same photo.
- Gon Gon Festival was held in 2021.
- Okay.
What? He joined God Gon Festival?
The two gentlemen had a match,
and they sent us the happy news.
Lovely!
It makes me happy
that they're connected.
Thank you for making it lively
for us.
It's enough to make me cry.
The stages this time are Fukui
Prefecture and Kochi Prefecture.
I went to Fukui Prefecture
quite a lot.
It's a bit related to you...
Glasses!
Fukui Prefecture is famous
for its glasses.
What do we compete at,
using glasses?
What kind of festival
is waiting for him?
Welcome to The Quest.
Today, it's Daisuke Miyagawa's
Way to Japanese Festivals,
and The Quest Hot Spring Club.
Wasshoi!
"Morisanchu"
Hello...
Hello!
Hello, everyone!
What?
It's over. My shoulders are over.
It's over for my shoulders
if I do this.
They will after this practise.
Hiroshima!
Don't grab!
Hang in there, Machan!
Daisuke Miyagawa's
Way to Japanese Festivals.
He has come to Sabae City,
Fukui Prefecture.
Wasshoi!
The place I have come to
is Sabae City in Fukui Prefecture.
Look at the signboard there.
It's a glasses frame,
it says "Sabae."
If the festival is about glasses,
I definitely don't want to lose.
Hey!
Festival Guy in Sabae!
- Bring it on.
- You waited too long.
Our guide this time
is Director-general
of Fukui Optical Association,
Mr Yasutaka Shimamura.
Say it again. What association?
I'm Fukui Optical Association's
Shimamura.
Yes, glasses!
- It's a nice frame.
- Thank you.
Please tell me what you take
seriously about glasses.
It looks heavy, but it's
surprisingly light when you wear it.
The glasses are light
when you wear them.
My facial features are quite close
together in the centre.
I want them to look wider apart,
so I use a bigger frame.
Scattering glasses.
- The festival held in Sabae here.
- Yes?
Is it dangerous?
- It isn't dangerous.
- No, right?
Can I ask the name of the event?
It's called Megamori.
What? After all these...
It's food?
Megamori?
They go to the venue that will be
the stage of the battle.
Mr Miyagawa,
please have a look at that.
- What?
- What did Miyagawa see?
It's men who are wearing
many pairs of glasses.
Megamori means a lot of glasses?
Megamori is an event
that participants compete to see
who wears more pairs of glasses
on their face.
80 percent of the glasses frames
made in Japan
are produced in Sabae City.
It's one of the three major glasses
frames production area in the world.
Glasses Festival is held every year,
Megamori started in 2014
as an event of the festival.
But it was cancelled last year
because of the pandemic.
People in the city pray
it'll be held this year.
That's many pairs of glasses!
Amazing!
- It's exciting, right?
- Yes.
It makes people smile,
from children to adults.
It looks so stupid.
The rule is very simple.
Put as many pairs of glasses in
the basket as you can on your face
in the one-minute time limit.
Stop for five seconds when it ends,
and the number of glasses that stay
will be recorded.
If they all fall when you say stop
and three pairs stay,
that'll be the record.
Three will be the record.
The way they count the number
is also full of love for glasses.
The Glasses Festival is set up
as a festival to thank our glasses,
so we fold them one by one
and say thank you.
We say thank you,
and continue to count.
Fold, and "thank you."
Thank you.
- Can I ask, Mr Shimamura?
- Go ahead.
How many pairs did the champion wear
to win?
35 pairs.
What?
My enemy is strong.
Now, he'll do some practise.
Pile them tidily,
one above the other.
You have to pile them up precisely.
This festival is so fun!
First, he tries it in 30 seconds.
Ready, go.
Miyagawa is putting
the glasses on smoothly,
but...
It falls if he doesn't put them on
carefully enough.
Not the pair that fell.
- It's difficult.
- Yes.
They barely hang there.
Five seconds left.
What...
Two, one.
Stop. Like this.
That's 30 seconds?
He'll stop for five seconds
after it ends.
I'll take them all off.
Didn't I put them on my face
surprisingly tidily?
Thank you.
Do not forget to express gratitude
to the glasses.
- Thank you.
- It's nice.
13 pairs.
We'll double it, so it's 26 pairs.
I need 10 more pairs
to catch up with the champion.
But it was only 30 seconds,
so it's going to get difficult
to find places to put them on.
It won't double just because
I did it for 30 seconds.
That's right.
I... Well, I want to win.
For example, it's not right
to put them here,
but it's quicker to wear them
than taking the time.
I see.
This festival is so fun.
He tries it in one minute,
like the real competition.
Start.
The record of the champion
is 35 pairs,
what does that look like?
I'll put them on quickly.
I guess I shouldn't overdo it.
The glasses are piled up tidily.
It looks good.
The difficult part of this
is you gradually don't know
how you're piling up the glasses.
So when pairs of glasses overlap...
They fall, as you can see.
Also, he can't see ahead,
so he can't choose glasses
that are easy to wear.
I see.
There is still space on the head
to wear them,
but Miyagawa can't see.
I see.
- The last spurt.
- You can do it!
Wow, it looks like
they are his eyes.
- Four, three, two, one.
- The lowest part.
Stop.
I think I wore many pairs.
Wow, he did so well!
Oh, I think I made it, right?
Then...
Thank you.
What's his record?
Thank you. So...
24 pairs.
In fact, the real difficult part of
Megamori starts at the 25th pair.
Stop.
The same. 24 pairs.
He can't break his record.
25 pairs.
It's the barrier of 25 again!
This is the winning record so far.
The champion hit a big record
of 35 pairs in 2019.
Obviously it also depends on luck,
but there's a chance he can win
if he can wear 30 pairs.
There's a chance if I wear
as many as 28 pairs.
I'll do it like the real thing.
Miyagawa improves his concentration.
Okay!
He's fired up!
He aims to wear 28 pairs.
You can do it.
Ready, start!
Start!
You can do it.
He put the glasses on
and leaves no gap.
You can do it.
Now is the crucial part.
How many more pairs of glasses
can he put on top of his head?
Miyagawa is grasping the feeling.
He looks very focused.
They get trapped by his hair
many times.
The pace he's putting them on at
isn't bad, either.
30 seconds left.
The sunglasses that might fall
are also fixed in place.
Wow, that was impressive!
He won't go past 25
if he makes any mistake.
He isn't thinking.
The last spurt.
The glasses are coming apart,
but they manage to stay.
Wow, they're trapped!
Impressive!
10 seconds left.
Isn't this really impressive?
- Don't let them fall...
- Don't let them fall!
- Amazing!
- Impressive!
- Stop.
- It's over.
I think I made it.
20.
What is his record?
28!
Wow, maybe I can do it!
He achieved his goal, 28 pairs.
Somehow I really understand now.
I do better in a real match,
so I'm confident I can put on
over 30 pairs.
What's left
is the Champion's nerves.
I'd like the cooperation
of our crew.
Please put the camera
very close to his face.
And now is the time
for the final battle.
I must do it. I'll defeat him.
Call the champion here!
Champion twice in a row,
Mr Yamahara!
Megamori's absolute champion,
Hiromori Yamahara.
The way he carries himself
is like a glasses advert.
35 pairs in one minute.
This man made
an overwhelming world record.
He has a nice nose.
Mr Yamahara? Nice to meet you.
I just practised for a bit,
it's difficult.
It is difficult.
I watched a bit. You're good at it.
- Really?
- I'm in trouble.
I'm a bit nervous.
- May I challenge you?
- Yes.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's do it, then.
Megamori special version starts now.
The heated battle between men
in glasses is going to start.
The time limit is one minute.
The one who wears more pairs
of glasses on his face wins.
If Miyagawa wins, he'll be given
a pair of golden glasses.
If the champion wins, we'll give him
a happi with Miyagawa's autograph.
Mr Miyagawa, are you confident?
To be honest...
I think I can win.
Oh, Miyagawa is already giving
the champion pressure!
Of course...
I'm nervous,
that's the key.
What Miyagawa said
is affecting the champion.
His face shows how nervous he is!
Now, the time has come!
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Now, the fateful match...
- Start.
- starts!
They both start wearing glasses.
Oh, what's wrong?
The champion is already panicking!
He's very nervous.
But Miyagawa is calm.
He's piling them up beautifully.
This is Festival Guy
Daisuke Miyagawa for you!
He performs well in a real match!
Wow, wearing two together!
Is he loved by glasses?
Lucky Glasses.
At the same time,
the champion isn't any worse.
He's wearing the glasses nicely.
What's wrong?
Oh, the champion's glasses
fell apart!
Will they hang in there?
Oh, they fell!
It's Miyagawa's chance!
You can do it!
Miyagawa is calm.
He doesn't slow down
and continues to wear glasses.
Amazing, Miyagawa! You can do it!
15 seconds left.
15 seconds left!
He'll surely win
if he doesn't make them fall!
The champion's fell apart!
Five seconds.
Five seconds left!
Can Miyagawa hold out?
- One. Stop.
- It's over!
Keep them there for five seconds.
Impressive!
- Yes! I must've won!
- Impressive!
Okay, I can take them off, right?
Yes! I've surely won!
I must've won!
That was impressive.
Miyagawa clenches his fist
in triumph!
I was so nervous!
We were nervous, right?
- I was so nervous.
- It was bad.
I've never been so nervous
putting on glasses.
I was so nervous.
My hands are still shaking.
We'll announce the result!
The first one. One.
Thank you.
They express their gratitude
for glasses and count.
Eleven.
Thank you.
The champion's record is...
12.
Thank you.
12 pairs!
25.
- Thank you!
- Amazing!
- Miyagawa's victory is certain.
- Awesome!
Now we'll see how far
his record will go.
27.
- Thank you!
- That's a big number.
28.
Thank you!
It broke the record
of Miyagawa's practise.
- 30.
- Thank you!
What's his record?
- 31.
- Thank you!
Miyagawa wore 31 pairs!
"Daisuke Miyagawa's record: 31"
Yes!
Miyagawa won for the first time
in a long while!
I got one lucky one.
It just hung here.
When I put it on my head,
it just got trapped.
It's your gold glasses medal.
Yay!
Thank you!
We pray Megamori
will be held again someday.
The next place he goes to is...
Wasshoi!
The place I have come to
is Saoka, Yamada Town, Tosa,
Kami City, Kochi Prefecture!
Have a look at this!
It's a really quiet,
wonderful place!
Our guide
is Saoka Region Community
Promotion Council Chairman,
Mr Takumi Maeda.
Mr Maeda,
is this festival dangerous?
It isn't dangerous to common people,
it's simple, but difficult.
- It's simple, but difficult?
- That's right.
How long has the champion
been winning?
Two years.
Two years in a row.
Kagami Town has its self-defence
force, he's a member of it.
Oh, no...
- I see, you need physical strength?
- That's right!
They go to the venue at once.
- Mr Miyagawa.
- Yes?
Have a look at that.
What?
What did Miyagawa see?
It's a man throwing scallion.
It's the Yakko Scallion Throwing
World Championship.
Kami City, Kochi Prefecture's
speciality is Yakko Scallion,
people throw it and compete
on who throws it furthest,
in the world championship.
The championship started in 2014.
At Saoka Spring Harvest Festival
held every year,
they used Kami City's speciality,
Yakko Scallion
to try revitalising the region,
and started the championship.
But it was cancelled in 2021
because of the pandemic.
The city's people pray
it can be held next year.
- This?
- That's right.
You can hold it and throw it
in whatever way you want,
just don't make it a ball.
Each person can throw two sticks,
but the scallion is so thin,
can it go that far?
Many people move too much to throw.
People usually do this.
Among them, some do an under throw.
Hold this part and throw like this.
I see, I see.
The world champion
throws above his head.
The second place throws from below.
How far can the champion throw it?
- 17.83 metres.
- What?
What?
We were shocked too.
That's close to the record
of throwing a softball.
So it's between 15m and 20m there.
It was in the middle.
Are you kidding me?
The tailwind must've been
rather strong.
Now Miyagawa will practise.
To be honest,
I have frozen shoulder now.
It hurts.
You're in a bit of trouble.
The champion is in his 20s.
I see...
This pain... Just a bit...
- Can I try it?
- Sure, go ahead.
I'll do it really lightly.
It went six metres away.
This is bad.
This...
Did he really throw that far?
I'm really impressed
with the champion.
The second one.
Oh, it's further.
But that's it?
His record improved from just now,
but it landed at six metres.
- It's light, so it's impossible.
- Yes.
He tries using more force.
- See?
- That's right.
It's over for my shoulders!
No. It'll be over for my shoulders
if I do this.
I'll try the under throw.
- Try it.
- Use centrifugal force.
Use centrifugal force
and do an underhand throw!
It went up, but...
His record improved.
I can do this.
I think this is better for me.
I don't hold it tightly,
and throw it this way here.
Miyagawa found a way out.
He devises a certain way to throw.
How about spinning once?
He spins to use centrifugal force
to throw it.
Go!
It went far!
It went further than 10 metres
the first time.
Amazing!
The record improved dramatically.
Mr Murofushi's way is great!
You go like...
A hammer is the same
as Yakko Scallion.
I can stand by like this.
That's right.
After this...
Look!
I've found it!
That's the Miyagawa Throw.
It is named Miyagawa Throw.
I want to go as far as I can
like this. Right?
But if I turn like this,
I'm going to try not to fall,
so I'll hold myself back.
My attention will be on my leg
over here.
But...
How did I move my legs?
- Which one?
- The other.
Which one? Hang on...
Then I put my weight here...
- Impressive!
- Amazing.
"14 metres mark"
- That went 14 metres?
- Yes, 14 metres.
It's possible now. It's right there.
- The champion's is there.
- Yes, over there.
But the centrifugal force
is too strong,
my blood goes there at once,
and my palm stings.
Miyagawa Throw is a two-edged sword,
the extreme spin causes blood
to gather at his fingertips.
Two-edged sword?
What two-edged sword?
I'll let it rest a bit.
It strains the body tremendously,
so the real match's two times
is all he can do.
He ends his practise now.
Daisuke, you really hate practising.
No, I don't.
That puts a strong centrifugal force
on my hand.
You'll be surprised.
If I go all out,
- my whole arm stings.
- Is it that bad?
It's true!
The final battle starts.
Yakko Scallion Throwing
World Championship,
champion twice in a row,
Mr Ishizaki!
This is the champion twice in a row
in Yakko Scallion Throwing
World Championship, Koji Ishizaki.
He's active in the force.
The champion looks strong!
He is a self-defence officer and a
former high school baseball player.
When did you make this record?
- About three years ago.
- Three years ago?
Is there a trick to it?
You know the result
the moment you choose the scallion.
I threw 14.4 metres
when I was practising.
Isn't it impressive
as the first time?
Yes, I think you can compete
for championship.
- Right?
- But 14 metres can't win.
You said it, Champion.
You can't beat me!
I'm not going to lose, either.
Now, let's do it.
Yakko Scallion Throwing
World Championship, special version,
starts now.
I will explain the rules.
Each person can throw two scallions.
The person
who throws it further wins.
If Miyagawa wins, he'll be given
a box of Yakko Scallion.
The champion goes first.
It's important to choose scallion
with a heavy root,
and the green part
should be straight.
That's what he says.
Miyagawa watches him do it.
- Okay.
- The champion chose
his best scallion.
He walks up to the stage
of the match.
How is he going to throw
the scallion?
- "Southpaw."
- It's "Southpaw."
The first throw
that has everyone's attention!
Wow, impressive!
He threw it!
How far?
The record is...
13.1 metres.
It's 13.1 metres!
A good match.
The champion is cornered.
Okay...
I think he's nervous.
Miyagawa's facial expression!
Can the champion show his pride?
I'll throw now.
The second throw decides his fate!
It flew!
Yes!
Wow, it's a lot further
than 15 metres!
He did a perfect throw!
The way he threw it was impressive.
What is the record?
It's 16 metres...
and 82 centimetres.
The champion made
a brilliant record!
Thank you.
I'll go further than 18 metres!
- Good!
- You can do it!
I'll go further than 18 metres!
- Good!
- You can do it!
He can't let himself be beaten!
Festival Guy, Daisuke Miyagawa
is here!
Choose the scallion.
Miyagawa said he'd do his
Miyagawa Throw twice in the match.
Even if it ruins his body,
he'll twist until his body
reaches its limit!
Now, he walks up
to the stage of the match.
Show him your power!
- Miyagawa Throw.
- Okay!
He aims to throw past 16.82 metres!
Okay, I'll do it.
Miyagawa's first throw!
You can do it.
- It's lighter.
- It's slower.
How far?
No!
It didn't fly at all!
Oh, no...
What's the record?
13 metres.
- But there's 13 metres.
- 13 metres.
He used too much force
and the scallion didn't fly at all.
"Record: 13m"
I'm cornered.
I'll make it next time!
Laugh or cry,
he has only one more throw!
Miyagawa poses to throw.
I'll go all out. I have to.
- Be careful.
- "I have to go all out."
I'll throw.
The last throw!
How far?
It didn't go far!
What's the record?
11.86 metres.
Miyagawa is defeated.
"Record: 11m 86cm"
His eyes are teary.
- I'm totally defeated. Thank you.
- Thank you.
He was strong.
But it's one win and one loss
this time.
That's all for today. Thank you.
That's all
for Way to Japanese Festivals.
You're quiet.
What was it? Somehow...
- What's the matter?
- Somehow...
It was one win and one loss,
you looked like you accomplished
your job when it ended.
You won the first glasses match
and I was very happy for you,
but I wish it'd be something
that would make us feel anxious.
- Like, "Please do it..."
- Wait, Ms Muu...
- It's a bit...
- Ms Muu.
I feel sorry for the champion!
Ms Muu!
The look on the champion's face
wasn't right.
It was so pale!
- You took advantage of it.
- I didn't!
That's how festivals are!
That's what a one-round match is!
When you won the glasses match,
you went, "Yes!"
They filmed you for a long time
after you won,
but the Yakko Scallion one
was over at once.
- Very quickly.
- Of course!
- It was short.
- When I lose,
I finish it quickly.
Okay, the next segment is this.
- The Quest Hot Spring Club!
- Yay!
1.5 hours from Tokyo,
the Hot Spring Club goes on
a tour in Hiroshima to solve
the problem of lack of exercise.
They've come to Itsukushima Shrine
in Miyajima.
Here we are...
Hiroshima!
The five of them are
the members this time.
It's my first time here.
- Have you all been here?
- Yes.
Because there's Boat Race Miyajima.
"Because"?
The tour to solve the problem
of lack of exercise starts now.
They've come to the Seto Inland Sea.
Let's do that, then.
What's that?
A huge surfboard?
It's called Big SUP,
the stand-up paddle board
carries 10 people.
What? It carries 10 people?
You'll go cruising to the island.
Wow, we can go cruising?
- Yay!
- Sounds fun.
The ladies set off.
They'll cruise and admire the view
of Shimanami Kaido
and Tatara Bridge.
Paddling is a full-body exercise,
they can train their bodies
just by standing on the board.
At that time...
Okarina falls.
You idiot!
They'll do one more exercise
on this SUP board.
The three winners
will get a reward.
You can eat Mashi Mashi Oyster.
Mashi Mashi Oyster.
- I want oyster and Okonomiyaki.
- I want that.
I want that.
There are enough people,
so I'll also join.
What?
Is it okay to punch you?
Machan has done this before.
I'll beat him up.
A real SUP Boxing match.
First, it's Oniyakko versus Ms Muu.
It's been a while!
It's been a long time!
I'll sink you again today!
Right back at you, jerk!
Fight!
It's weak.
It's weak!
They're just playing.
Oniyakko is defeated.
I won!
I'll bring the locals here
next time.
Next, Okarina versus Yoshiko.
Let's fight, Bob SUP!
What?
- Bob SUP!
- What?
This SUP is your grave!
Don't get Bob Sapp involved
because this is SUP!
Bob SUP!
I'm not Bob Sapp!
Fight!
It's strong...
Bob SUP is defeated.
Mahiru will fight against Director
Nagata, the world's smallest.
Finally, the time to kill you
has come!
Try to kill me if you can!
He looks weak.
You always look up to me from below!
He doesn't look down on her.
Fight!
You can do it!
It's a good match!
Don't let a girl beat you!
- Go!
- Go, go!
Don't be beaten!
Mahiru's crushing victory.
His neck twisted. Is he okay?
The last hook was rather strong.
She still tries to kill him.
The way he fell was like in a manga.
The three winners get a reward.
The Hiroshima speciality,
Okonomiyaki,
is topped with 15 oysters
in this luxurious dish,
Mashi Mashi Oyster.
Nice, it's Hiroshima.
How does it taste?
It's huge!
The oyster is huge.
It's delicious.
It's fleshy.
It really goes with
the green dried seaweed on top.
Delicious!
Ms Murakami's food review
is easy to understand.
Isn't Yoshiko's huge?
Amazing!
As big as my ear.
Like your ear?
The part on the edge
is like oyster mushroom.
Oyster mushroom?
There's no oyster mushroom.
The taste of the top part is light,
but if you eat the oyster
with the sauce,
it makes the flavour rich
and it's absolutely delicious.
- What?
- It should be us to go, "What?
- Exactly.
You two have the dish.
You can just eat it!
Next, it's the latest sport.
It looks like some kind of sport.
The creator, Mr Motomura
is waiting for them.
It's a kind of sport called SASSEN.
SASSEN.
It's a kind of sport?
We use IT to recreate
a real match between samurai
in the modern world.
It's digital swordplay
with next-generation sensor.
Next-generation sport, SASSEN.
SASSEN.
They'll fight to see
who hits the opponent first.
There is a sensor on the sword,
so it can judge accurately.
Let's use this to have a match.
It sounds fun.
If we have a one-on-one match,
Oniyakko and I will surely lose.
The one who loses most
will do bungee jump.
What?
It's strong.
I can't do it.
I can't do it either.
I won't do it.
I'll be blown away at once.
Their reactions don't match.
The two seniors can't fight,
so Okarina, who doesn't mind
doing bungee jump,
and Ganbareruya, who are scared for
real, will fight against each other.
The rule of the real match is,
they'll hit
the four people running away
as many times as they can
in 15 seconds.
I see.
Machan...
Machan is angry. Machan is angry.
Will we start from Mahiru?
Decide it yourselves.
She's full of fighting spirit.
All of you.
I'll beat you up.
What? Pardon?
Ready...
Start!
Don't grab!
Stop!
Sorry, I went outside.
Okarina grabbed me!
- You grabbed her, Oka?
- I did.
She kept hitting me.
Okarina grabbed me!
Because you kept hitting me.
No one said we can't grab.
She grabbed me,
so I lost those counts.
She grabbed me.
I grabbed you to do that.
Fight fair and square!
Grabbing you is fair and square.
You shouldn't grab!
I'm going to grab you
the whole time you hit!
Do that, then. I'll hit you even so.
I like her face just now!
- She's furious.
- Wait... Calm down.
It's like a fight between siblings.
Next, it's Okarina's turn.
Ready...
Start.
Bring it on.
What?
It has become a different sport!
Stop!
They were having a fight.
What sport is this?
It looked like judo
when you locked arms.
I grabbed you,
because you grabbed me.
You grabbed me, so I did it back.
But I hit you 18 times.
You only hit me 18 times.
Yoshiko is going to do it.
Is this sport like this?
The last one is Yoshiko.
Ready...
Start.
It's brutal.
It hurts!
It's dangerous...
Yoshiko, hang in there.
Stop!
Oh, no, she fell!
Yoshiko ranks the lowest,
so she will do bungee jump.
- Do it for me.
- There's no way I can.
No matter what happens,
this is something I can't do.
- Please!
- Absolutely not.
They've come to the neighbouring
prefecture, Okayama,
to Washuzan Highland.
The facility is built on a mountain.
I see.
She'll feel like she jumps down
from an altitude of 170 metres.
In addition, there is a blast
blowing up there.
I have to do it.
Can Yoshiko jump?
I have to jump, right?
I have to jump!
Do my best!
I can do it! I can do it!
I can do it!
- She always says it in the bath.
- What?
- I have to do it.
- "You can do it, Yoshiko!"
- She says it on her own.
- Even in the bath?
Courage, guts!
- I won't be beaten.
- You can do it!
I won't be beaten!
She jumped!
I won! I won!
She's basking in her sense
of achievement,
but there is a big problem.
Yoshiko, did you film
with the GoPro?
She looks like a rhinoceros beetle.
You look like a rhinoceros beetle.
Did it film your face?
- I won't be beaten!
- When we check...
I want to see her face.
Her face went out of frame
at the best part.
Oh, give me a break!
There are cameras that function
properly nowadays!
Let's climb a mountain next.
The mountain is easy to climb.
You say it's easy, but it has never
been easy on this show.
Is this okay?
You're wearing a funny hat.
I'm only wearing
what I was provided.
They start climbing the mountain.
- I'm Sumiko Nishioka.
- What?
I'm Barbie-ko Barbie-oka.
Someone has come to tell
everyone I worked with
at The Quest that she got married.
Who is she?
It's me!
It's what her senior did.
Barbie announced her marriage
with an ordinary man in April, 2021.
Wow, good for you!
- Well...
- Congratulations...
I must thank everyone
at The Quest.
- What?
- Why?
My Achilles tendon.
It happened in June, 2019,
at the banquet
of the One Art Training Camp.
"June 2019,
at One Art Training Camp"
Her Achilles tendon
tore at this moment.
But her boyfriend moved in with her
to look after her,
they got closer at once
and finally got married.
Achilles marriage.
She calls it Achilles marriage.
It's Achilles marriage.
Barbie joins them and they start
climbing the mountain again.
After climbing 30 minutes...
They see a scenery
that resembles the Alps.
I think it's okay to climb up!
This is a scenic place
that only those in the know, know,
Mount Kurotaki.
It's 266 metres above the sea,
but has a view like this.
In front of their eyes,
it's a stunning scenery of the whole
Seto Inland Sea and Shikoku.
This photo will surely look cool.
Yes, it's a good photo.
It looks like
we're at an amazing place.
It's a vast place--
- What? What, Yoshiko?
- What are you doing?
Are you scared?
What's the matter?
It's dangerous. What are you doing?
No...
No... Ms Muu should be at the front.
It's okay, it's still okay.
- I'll hold you together.
- It's scary!
Next, they came to Kure Port.
There are huge destroyers
and submarines lining up,
it's the main base of the Japan
Maritime Self-Defence Force.
This time, you'll receive
a special training by the Japan
Maritime Self-Defence Force.
What?
I heard the self-defence force's
training is the harshest.
I didn't come here for that.
Ms Barbie, you're a crucial member.
This is the Submarine Training
Centre's Commander Mekada.
Almost every one
of the submarine crew
was trained at
the Submarine Training Centre.
You're going to experience
that today.
You'll know about the ship,
establish teamwork,
and train your mind and body.
This will be the training.
Any weight limit?
- No, don't worry.
- Don't worry?
Now, their training begins.
- Barbie, yours...
- It's pretty.
- I've got a heart shape.
- So cute!
Oh, jeez.
You've gotten changed. Attention!
It starts suddenly.
This time, Instructor Miyazaki
will train the ladies.
When you reply, say yes,
or my pleasure. That's all.
"My pleasure"?
When do we say "my pleasure"?
When you're made to do
something tough,
and you don't want to do it,
say, "My pleasure!"
What?
It's the opposite of "no"?
Even in the Japan Maritime
Self-Defence Force,
only the selected members
can get in a submarine.
And the Submarine Training Centre
here
is the school where all submarine
crew members are trained.
They'll finally start learning.
It's amazing!
We've entered a place
that's very important.
This is the submarine's
controlling room.
The submarine's centre gives
commands and controls the vessel.
This is a Oyashio-class submarine's
underwater control training device.
The actual length
of the whole Oyashio is 82 metres,
the controlling room is at this part
of the huge vessel.
First of all, how does a submarine
surface or sink?
Actually, a submarine's hull
has two components.
The wall is built like a huge tank.
By letting seawater into the tank,
it loses its buoyancy
and it can sink.
I see.
When it has to float, seawater is
pushed out the tank by air pressure
to gain buoyancy.
Please pull. It moved, right?
Something is moving!
This resembles the state
of sudden surfacing.
How can you stand?
We're like Michael Jackson.
When a submarine is underwater,
there's something very dangerous.
It is flooding.
It's scary...
The submarine's machine room
is recreated here,
trainings to fight floods can be
done at this special facility.
Wow, it's scary.
Isn't this bad?
The crew members will show us.
A submarine is affected
by water pressure all the time,
erosion caused by impact
and seawater will cause flooding.
"Teamwork"
It's important for a team to work
together to stop the spraying water.
Ready, go!
Oh, no!
- There's a lot of water!
- Amazing.
A maximum of 200 tonnes of water
is released at one time.
The members receive
realistic training every day.
Amazing!
We can't do it.
I was speechless.
First, the basics.
Get used to water.
Push the water back
when the whistle is blown,
block the hole by hand.
It's difficult.
They stop it by hand.
When the whistle is blown again,
return to the original position.
Everything is normal.
Yoshiko is deployed.
Please set the output at maximum!
The output is raised 20 percent.
Can she do it?
Yoshiko uses her face
to confront it.
It's scary!
It must hurt...
She managed to do it.
Everything is normal!
No, it isn't!
Now, it's time
for practical training.
They'll use
these three kinds of tools.
Use this board patch
for a large crack.
Hook the T-shape part in the crack
to stabilise it.
They are emergency bands,
they're put over the pipes
to stop the water.
This is a wooden plug.
It's put into the hole
and hammered in with a hammer.
Can they stop the water spraying
from everywhere?
- You can do it!
- Go!
The whole team is deployed.
Let's go.
First, Mahiru uses her body to block
the strongest spray.
They'll use a board patch for this.
They go near the crack
when Mahiru is stopping the water.
They match the timing
and put the patch in,
and press it down at once.
Wait.
Is it okay?
Good.
Ready, push!
- It's in!
- It's in?
They stopped one place first.
On the other hand,
they'll stop the pipe's leak.
Bands with different widths
are prepared to match
pipes of various widths.
Push it down harder!
Lastly, Mahiru will hammer
the wooden plug in.
You can do it!
- It's difficult.
- Don't be beaten!
Don't be beaten, Machan!
You can do it!
Don't be beaten!
Finally, she successfully
stopped the water.
Everyone, salute!
Everything is normal!
It was amazing.
I was really impressed
by the good work.
I thought we must improve too.
- My pleasure.
- Okay.
It's what you say
when you mean "no."
That's all for the tour to solve
the problem of lack of exercise.
Barbie, congratulations
on your marriage.
Congratulations!
After Imoto.
We were a duo after all.
I'm so happy.
Your Achilles tendon started it?
Yes, that's right.
Because that happened,
we got much closer.
He isn't the impersonator, right?
- Mr Hiromi Go's...
- Yes, I said that started it,
some people assumed I got married
to the actor who played Mr Go.
"Hiromi Go's impersonator"
It isn't him.
It isn't that guy?
I thought you did!
Some people think she did, right?
Yeah.