The Quest.
First in today's show is...
The Advisor Challenges
My Gold Medal.
This is our usual project
to check the physical strength
of our 57-year-old advisor.
The stage this time is Shikoku.
He will try different activities
that require him to move his body.
Mr Degawa,
we'll report something to you.
What is it? You're scaring me.
We'll add a new Degawa Girl
after Yumeppe.
What? Another Degawa Girl will join?
- Yes. Yumeppe had an audition,
right?
- Yes.
- We chose one more girl there.
Wait. You shouldn't.
If another new Degawa Girl joins,
the three old girls
will surely get angry again.
Yumeppe joined. Surely, she brought
a breath of fresh air here.
If I compare it to blood,
it used to be too thick.
Who is the new Degawa Girl?
"This show was broadcasted
on the 20th of June, 2021"
Welcome to The Quest.
Today, it's
My Gold Medal in Shikoku,
and Go to the End of the World.
Wasshoi!
Hello, hello, hello.
Hello!
Hello, everyone.
First, it's Advisor's
My Gold Medal Tour.
- Another new girl.
- Surprising.
Actually, last year,
before the pandemic,
they were going to let
two new Degawa Girls join,
she already had an audition
at that time.
- She was chosen.
- Already chosen.
- She waited for a year.
- I see.
We're going to have more than
the original Bond Girls like this.
There are going to be more and more,
and it will end up like AKB.
Like DGW48.
In various places
like Malaysia and Thailand.
DGW48. I like it.
Yeah?
Isn't she pretty? We will go
no matter what the old girls say.
We don't need any new girl.
You could've said that.
It's a huge one.
- You can do it, Miyazon.
- Yes.
- Okay, let's beat it with this.
- Okay.
Five hundred and fifty kilometres
away from Tokyo,
a new Degawa Girl joins.
My Gold Medal Tour in Shikoku.
We've come here!
- Kagawa!
- Oh? Three?
The opening starts with Degawa
and the three old girls.
The project this time
is My Gold Medal,
but there's an announcement!
What is it?
Madame isn't here,
Yumeppe isn't here.
- Do you know what that means?
- What?
Something happened to Madame?
She didn't die!
I didn't say she died.
- Someone will drop out?
- I know!
Ms Kawakita is graduating!
You're horrible!
So mean! What's wrong with them?
Seriously!
Now, we'll announce the news
to the three girls.
Actually, this time,
a new Degawa Girl has come.
- What?
- Again?
- Wait a minute.
- Yes?
Mr Degawa said nothing about that?
- Me?
- Yes.
We don't want any new girl,
we already have the girls here.
You could've said that.
Exactly!
There's no way I didn't say that.
But you're grinning now.
They told me a new Degawa Girl
will come to film with us.
I went, "What? Again?
Show me a photo, then."
The moment Mr Takei
showed me his phone,
I threw it away.
That has to be a lie.
You said it.
I went, "We don't need this
new girl!" and threw it away.
I'll check when it's on air!
Show me the data.
- There you go.
- Here's the photo.
The truth.
Let's go.
Isn't the girl lovely?
We'll go no matter what
the old girls say.
The new Degawa Girl, come here!
She's shining.
- She's cute.
She's really fresh.
Hello, nice to meet you.
I am Mayuu Yokota.
Mayuu Yokota, 21 years old.
A winner of Miss Seventeen,
the young actress has appeared
in various dramas too.
Mayuu, tell them
what you're doing now.
I now work with Non-no magazine,
I made my first appearance
in autumn, 2020,
and was on the cover
for the first time.
Impressive!
It's the cover that Ms Kawakita
has never been on.
Don't say that.
Me too. Me too.
First appearance, first cover.
What? Is that so, Akane?
What about Maria?
- I had been a cover girl.
- Amazing!
Is it like, if a model is on a
cover, then she is fully qualified?
Yes, maybe.
We call it cover girl.
- What are you, Maria?
- Vivi's cover girl.
- And you, Akane?
- I was a cover girl.
- And you, Mayuu?
- I was also a cover girl.
- And you, Princess?
- Don't you dare ask me. Really.
Now, it is the regular
Degawa Girl Interview.
We'll start the interview
with the new Degawa Girl.
I am Mayuu Yokota, 21 years old.
I'm from Tokyo.
- Did you go to university?
- I didn't.
Good!
Yes!
I'm not beaten yet.
I call Mayuko "Mayuko,"
but she will be Mayuu,
and they sound similar.
Then we can have Mayuu and Mayu B.
That's not right. Why?
Why would you change mine?
Mayuu, what do people call you?
I have no specific nickname.
- You're Yokota, right?
- Yes.
- Yokota.
- You'll call her Yokota?
So mean! That girl is the scariest.
You don't want to be called Yokota,
right?
It's totally okay.
I'm sure everyone will call her
Yokota very soon.
When you're asked whose idea it was,
say it was Maria's.
Okay.
You hosted Hirunandesu, right?
What? You hosted Hirunandesu?
I did.
So you're in Nanchan's faction?
This show is Ucchan's.
Which faction are you in?
Ucchan's or Nanchan's?
- She can't say.
- The most difficult question.
I'm in the Weekend Ucchan faction.
I'm impressed.
I'm in Nanchan's faction
on weekdays, obviously,
and absolutely Ucchan's on weekends.
- Me too.
- Okay.
She's good at this, right?
Learn things like this gradually.
I will.
As a Girl, what is the thing
nobody can beat you at?
How do you advertise yourself?
I play guitar as a hobby,
- and I brought my guitar here.
- What?
I'm nervous.
Do your best.
The sound of "I love you"
Good.
Makes me feel I can become stronger
If this hadn't been
her first appearance,
the quality would have made us
edit the whole thing out.
Don't say that.
Their faces.
Nice.
That was cute.
Anyway, it's connected,
so put the guitar away.
Okay.
And pretend it didn't happen?
Look forward to when it's on air.
Finally, the main part,
My Gold Medal.
We'll first warm up by doing
the latest activity.
We've come to Tadotsu Marina.
Customers can experience
various latest activities here,
but this is what
they'll do this time.
A huge red swim ring
is tied to a water scooter.
It's spinning.
It started spinning.
The is the latest activity,
Hurricane Boat.
If he can stay there
and not fall for one minute,
he gets a gold medal.
Yokota, are you scared of this?
I love it.
She likes it.
But if only one person sits
on the Hurricane Boat,
it's not balanced
and it doesn't spin.
So they'll compete in teams of two,
and the winner will aim
for a gold medal with Degawa.
First, it's Hotta versus Tani.
Let's have fun!
No, I'm really sick of it.
The water scooter starts.
Oh, I hate it!
It's scary already!
Spinning starts.
Can they hold on to it
for one minute?
Oh, they're doing their best.
Impressive.
But...
Hotta falls.
"Hotta out!"
Wait! It's cold! I fell! It's cold!
Someone, help me!
I actually wanted to enjoy it
for a longer time.
It's very fast!
All the flesh of my face
somehow went here.
- Does it really go so fast?
- Really!
She exaggerated it.
Again. She's doing it again.
- Akane, are you lying?
- I didn't!
Next, it's Kawakita versus Yokota.
What's this? It's scary!
Spinning starts.
This is fast!
- Impressive!
- It's fast.
It's fast! It's fast!
The disc accelerates.
And finally...
She's floating?
Kawakita falls.
It's freezing!
So Tani and Yokota will aim
for the gold medal with Degawa.
Gold! Gold! Gold!
It's coming.
Now, let's go.
Gold Medal Challenge.
Spinning starts!
It's floating!
Isn't it the fastest so far?
Have a look at this fresh reaction.
And the old girl's reaction.
How many more seconds?
And no reaction.
Ten seconds left.
Hang in there!
They can do it.
It's faster.
This is bad.
One minute is over.
He successfully won a gold medal.
Hurray!
We did it!
The start is very favourable.
- See you.
What? What do you mean?
We'll leave here...
Wow, again!
Excuse me.
We'll have udon and go home.
Nice!
- Do your best, Yokota!
- I will.
Bye.
Isn't that impressive, Yokota?
Just 10 minutes ago,
they said they'd get a gold medal.
They don't look back at all.
The old girls somehow livened up
the atmosphere for the new girl.
My Gold Medal Tour.
The next destination is Tokushima.
Here we are,
Tokushima!
How do you feel
after trying to be a Degawa Girl?
I feel helpless.
Well, this is the usual system
when we do it,
so you can't afford to say
you feel helpless.
I won't say it again.
That's quick.
Did you brush me off?
You met the three old Degawa Girls,
didn't you?
What do you think about them?
They make much more noise
in real life.
Good. Good, Yokota.
You've only watched them
on the television, right?
What's your impression of them
behind the scenes?
I thought Ms Kawakita pays a lot
of attention to her surroundings.
She's totally different
behind the scenes.
She's totally different?
She went, "Mr Degawa,
should I grill some meat?"
I was supposed to do the job.
What about Akane?
She's good at keeping
the distance she wants.
Wow, she's analysing!
She isn't good at keeping
the distance,
she's just not interested in
people.
What about Maria?
She was just like
what I saw on the television.
What was your impression of her?
She's free-spirited,
even when she left, she went,
"Yokota, film a video with me.
I named you, so let's film a video!"
She's laughing.
She didn't exactly name me.
What's your impression of me, then?
Did it change after seeing me behind
the scenes? Like another side?
It didn't change.
Like you can't talk smoothly.
The next challenge
of My Gold Medal...
is diving.
You'll go free diving,
and catch abalone.
- You get a gold medal if you can.
- Again.
The sea area to the south
of Anan City in Tokushima Prefecture
is well-known as
a treasure trove of abalone.
We have the assistance
of a local fisherman, Mr Ikeuchi.
By the way, how deep
is the water under this?
About four metres.
Wait.
According to the captain,
amateurs can dive three metres down.
If you catch an abalone
at three metres, it's a gold medal.
Three metres is rather deep.
As usual, Yokota will check it out.
It's freezing!
It's cold!
- It's cold?
- I'm scared!
The sea is scary!
You didn't release the air.
Now? Now?
Let some water in.
The cold will kill me.
I'll go.
How is it?
Oh, she's gone.
Yokota dives swiftly.
She went nearly as far
as the bottom of the sea.
Impressive!
- Did you see beneath?
- I saw it!
Did you go to the rock?
Yes.
Captain, does it mean
she went three metres?
- Yes.
- Impressive!
Degawa finally goes in.
- Let's do three rounds.
- Okay.
I have three chances. Okay.
The first time of doing
the challenge.
Do your best.
He splashed a lot of water, but...
Please do catch some abalone.
He floats up right away.
He is chubby,
so the buoyancy is high.
Captain, how many more metres?
Two more metres.
Two more metres? That means
I only dived one metre?
Yes.
So he wears the weight for diving.
Teacher, the weight--
not teacher, Village Chief.
Captain!
Not teacher, Village Chief.
He puts 10 kilograms
on Degawa's body.
Wait, Captain.
Can I really come back up?
- You can come back up.
- Really?
- I need to keep treading water.
- That's right.
That's about right.
Tread water.
I'm treading water hard now.
Let's stop that.
What treading water?
But if you don't do that,
you can't really sink.
I can't sink?
Now, the second time of
doing the challenge.
Wow, he's going straight down!
Amazing!
He's going there.
But he can't hold his breath
and floats up quickly.
I saw it!
You saw it?
Darn it! Almost! I almost got it!
Nobody cares,
but he looks like Oba-Q.
What is it? The pink one?
Teacher, help me.
The next one is his last chance.
What will Degawa do?
I'll tie 10 kilograms here,
and two kilograms on my head.
He can't tie weight on his head,
but he'll do the last chance
with 12 extra kilograms.
I really might not
be able to come back.
- That's how determined I am.
- Yes.
- Watch carefully!
- Okay.
As a Degawa Girl--
Oh, this is really heavy!
The problem is, until he peels off
the abalone and brings it back,
will his breath last?
Make it this time!
You can do it!
It really looks like he is going
towards the spot.
After all, the captain pushed him
from above.
He has his hands on the rock
with abalone.
He only has to pull it out
and rise up.
But...
He ran out of oxygen
right before he got it.
When we checked,
we see the abalone he finally took
slip out of his hand.
I let go of it!
He did not get a gold medal.
Really, the moment I thought
I got it,
it slipped out of my hand.
You were careless
at the last minute.
I'm so frustrated.
They go to have lunch.
Shikoku is famous
for its Sanuki Udon.
Here at Menya Shichifuku Bettei,
you can have some unique udon.
It's here.
So long.
It's so long.
It's Ippon Udon
which is 1.6 metres long.
It is thick and long,
so it is a lucky item
for praying for longevity.
What will I do?
You get a gold medal if you can
slurp one noodle.
Oh, a gold medal if I can eat this
without cutting it?
The director, Takei, shows him.
He's doing it.
As you can see,
he keeps slurping the noodle,
and puts all of it in his mouth
without cutting it.
Try and do this.
But it's just slurping it.
No, it's not.
People who know it, know.
Those who don't, don't.
It's well-known that my throat
is like a baby's.
- Yokota tries it first.
- Ready, start!
You can do it.
Oh, she's slurping.
She's slurping it.
But Yokota can't slurp it at all.
- You can do it. Oh, no.
- You can do it.
Three, two, one.
It's over.
She failed.
Why?
Did you eat or keep it inside?
It was in my mouth.
You didn't swallow?
When I try to chew, it comes out.
That's why you slowed down?
Yes, there was no more room
for more noodle.
No more room.
You suddenly talk like Tokyo people.
Finally, it's Degawa's turn.
Ready...
Start.
Is this okay?
Degawa is only moving his mouth,
but he can't slurp the noodle.
He isn't slurping.
You can't slurp noodles?
I don't slurp when I eat ramen.
Like...
The udon noodle got stuck.
- You eat bite by bite?
- Yes, bite by bite.
Bite by bite...
Can I try slurping now?
Can he do it?
Why is that?
The sound is loud,
but the noodle goes up
and down into the soup.
It's enough.
I can't slurp.
The last challenge
of My Gold Medal...
takes place at Yoshino River that
runs across Tokushima and Kochi.
What you'll do is to float here
from the upper stream.
What is floating there?
Impressive!
Hydrospeed.
It's a river sport
that originated in France.
They'll wear fins
and go down a rapid stream
on a single-seater rubber boat.
It's close to the water surface
and the activity is powerful.
If the boat doesn't turn over
when he goes down the rapid stream,
he gets a gold medal.
I see.
We have the assistance
of Mr Higakure and Mr Yagisawa.
They are both tough men
who were winners
in international
rafting competitions.
Wow, impressive!
The two gentlemen...
Is that a facility?
What do you call that?
Shoppy shop?
Are you both from the shop?
I'm the owner.
He's an active athlete.
Oh, you're still active?
Is the river here relatively rapid?
It is said to be the most rapid
in Japan.
What?
Oh, no.
My palms got very sweaty.
It must be rather bad
if it's Japan's most rapid.
They're taught how to ride the boat
at once.
Push the front part
when the wave comes.
- When it comes.
- You push it?
Push. But if you don't look
at the wave until the end,
you'll be blown away easily.
Okay, let's go, Yokota!
Let's get a gold medal!
Yes!
Yokota starts first.
Okay, let's go!
The teacher leads, just in case.
It's scary.
Can she do it?
She looks very happy.
Then...
it knocks over.
Oh, no.
But she managed to hold on
to the boat
and survived.
Yokota is recovered.
I thought I'd die!
Really.
Was it tough?
I don't know what I did!
I have no idea at all.
Is it difficult?
If Yokota's boat was knocked over,
isn't it difficult?
Now, Degawa goes!
Do your best!
It has started.
Entering the zone.
Degawa is tossed about by the waves,
but he manages to hang in there.
But...
Oh, it flipped over!
You can do it, Mr Degawa!
It knocks over.
Mr Degawa, hang in there!
He failed.
Did you swallow water?
I swallowed a lot.
- You swallowed a lot, right?
- Yes.
I swallowed about a whole bottle.
Me too.
Really, it felt like I was put
in a washing machine.
It felt like I was spun
in the washing machine's drum.
The only thing that's clear
is I swallowed one litre of water.
But Degawa will try once more
as he wished.
He'll do it at the difficult part,
here at the downstream just now.
Okay, let's go!
- I won't let go!
- You can do it.
I'll get a gold medal!
The teacher goes in front,
and behind him is the show's
producer with a camera.
Can he do it without
the boat knocking over?
"Degawa"
You can do it.
Degawa charges in.
Can he overcome the rough waves?
It knocked over? No, it's okay!
He was hit many times
by the strong waves,
but he managed to hold out.
Impressive.
The goal is near.
Hang in there!
At that time...
Oh, no.
The roughest wave, Producer Attack.
An accident!
But he didn't lose balance
and reached the goal successfully!
Amazing, Mr Degawa!
Even though he was obstructed
by one of the crew in an accident,
Degawa won a gold medal.
Are you okay, Mr Degawa?
That was 1.5 litres.
- Well done, Mr Degawa.
- Thank you.
I swore I wouldn't let go of it.
That's all I thought when I did it.
So it's very difficult
to tell you what I did to win
the gold medal specifically.
I only endured it.
The teacher also said it was
the most rapid stream in Japan.
When the first rapid current ended,
the next one came immediately.
I couldn't let my guard down.
Then, Degawa can't recall
an important word.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay. What's the matter?
- Yokota?
- Yokota, Yokota.
Yokota...
So, it's Yokota from Tokyo
and Yumeppe from Fukushima.
Please take good care
of our new Degawa Girls.
This is the new Degawa Girl,
Mayuu Yokota.
Nice to meet you.
"Mayuu Yokota"
What do you think after filming?
It's always been my dream
to appear in The Quest,
so I'm happy my dream came true.
Yokota, you watched the episodes
Yumeppe were in, right?
Yes.
Was there any pressure?
She made an impact by
speaking in Fukushima dialect,
so I was at a loss what to do
because I have no special skill.
- You can play the guitar.
- The guitar.
That was brilliant.
That was mean!
I did more things like dancing.
You did many things?
Right? To be honest, the three
old girls also did other things,
like physical fitness test
that whole day,
but at that point,
we were told
several takes wouldn't be used.
And as we thought, that happened.
Even the three old girls said
they'd be edited out because of me.
It's your fault?
Because I performed badly.
No, that's Takei's fault.
It's none of Yokota's business.
Yokota just went all out to do it.
They should've edited Takei out.
You're so cool!
Okay, this is the next part.
Go to the End of the World!
It's Miyazon.
Yes, this time,
I'll try to catch marlin again.
It's when you got lots of help.
It was a pity the last time,
that even with everyone's help,
you couldn't catch any.
But at that location,
there was something I could catch.
What's that?
I became the sightseeing ambassador
of Yonaguni!
Because of that?
Because of that.
- The term of office is three years.
- It's long.
Yes. This time, as part of my job,
I will try to catch a marlin
that's over 100 kilograms again,
and as the sightseeing ambassador,
I will introduce the attractions
of Yonaguni.
I'm impressed.
You don't have to be from there
to be a sightseeing ambassador.
I don't know the requirements
of sightseeing ambassadors.
Okay, let's go.
Go to the End of the World...
The Quest!
The mission doesn't finish
until he achieves the goal.
Go to the End of the World.
Yonaguni is 1,900 kilometres
away from Tokyo,
the island is on the westernmost end
of Japan, near the country border.
Last time, we came to Yonaguni
to catch marlin, right?
I really fell in love
with this island,
and our guide was Yassan, right?
Yassan is the famous guide
in Yonaguni who helped us last time.
He told me to be the sightseeing
ambassador if I love it so much.
I told him I couldn't do it,
but he called me when I was in Tokyo
and said I could.
A week after the call ended,
he said, "You got the job."
I actually became the sightseeing
ambassador like this.
Do you do any activity in specific?
I'm going to.
The amount of marlin caught
in Yonaguni is the largest in Japan.
He can't call himself a sightseeing
ambassador without catching one.
He joins the fishermen at once.
This isn't our first time meeting.
Captain Ichinari and Captain Tanaka
also helped us last time.
Last July, they spent eight days
and over 60 hours fishing,
but they couldn't see a marlin,
let alone catch one.
It figured it out?
- It did.
- What?
Darn it!
As a result...
Recently, people say you can't catch
fish on Mr Tsugu's boat.
I just happened not to be able
to catch any, right?
That's right.
How about this time?
I brought two people who went
marlin-fishing for the first time,
they caught a 150-kilogram one
and a 130-kilogram one.
- They fished for the first time?
- Yes.
They came after watching The Quest.
I couldn't catch any at all
and they still came. How optimistic.
They set sail
and aim to catch a marlin.
Catching a fish that's over
100 kg is the mission this time.
We'll do our best.
He's our sightseeing ambassador,
and he's working so hard
for our island.
The fishing ground of marlin
is 20 kilometres
to the south of the island.
I'll get the lure out and pull.
Marlin-fishing is done by trolling.
A rod is set up at the stern,
a bait fish or lure is drawn through
the water to lure marlins.
Then, suddenly...
It bit!
- It bit! Did it bite?
- It obviously shook.
It bit.
Wow, this is rather...
The line is pulled
at a very high speed.
Please stand by.
It's a revenge match.
A big chance suddenly came.
At that time...
It broke?
Watch out.
- It broke.
- It broke?
It broke.
The fish broke it?
The line broke unexpectedly.
It was broken.
It suddenly broke.
How big was that?
What size of fish can the string
pull up?
It can easily catch
a 150-kilogram one.
That means the one just now
weighed 200 kilograms?
There's a chance.
There's an enormous one.
Okay! Come, marlin!
Now, he suddenly got excited.
He's motivated.
Okay!
That's unique.
But he was excited
only at the start.
In the end, nothing bit
in the six hours that followed.
Let's go tomorrow.
Yes, let's do our best.
This is amazing.
Now, Sightseeing Ambassador Miyazon
will introduce the attractions
of Yonaguni.
First, it's the largest moth
in Japan, Atlas moths.
He has come to Ayamihabiru Museum
in the eastern part of the island.
It's a protected species,
so you don't see it often,
but they emerged today,
so I'd like to have a look.
His guide is the specialist,
Ms Sugimoto.
The Atlas moths emerged,
is it like having a festival here?
I assumed it would be
in a huge insect cage,
but they're just here.
They have an interesting habit
of staying still,
it's the only rare characteristic.
The wings that mimic the head
of a snake are unique.
They are really this big.
- Viewers can't feel it.
- No.
My hand is huge.
I have my phone.
This is huge too.
Also, cuisine in Yonaguni
as recommended
by the sightseeing ambassador.
He came to a diner run by a family
of fishermen on the island,
Uminchu Shokudo.
Its selling point is dishes made
with fresh fish caught
by the fishermen in the morning.
This is a restaurant
Miyazon regularly visits.
Will you make my usual dish for me?
Every time I come here.
I can eat as many as three plates.
What is the dish in Yonaguni their
sightseeing ambassador recommends?
This is it!
Wow! Thank you, as always.
It's here.
Spaghetti Aglio e Olio!
This is the Number 1 dish
in Yonaguni.
I love the thin noodles,
and no extra ingredient is added.
Simple is best.
It's absolutely delicious.
It looks delicious, but...
I've come to Yonaguni.
- Is this ordered most often?
- It is.
- More than marlin?
- Yes.
Mr Tsugu,
this is really delicious, right?
It is, I put it on rice
when I eat it.
Someone loves it more than me.
Day two.
Again!
Another letter from the children.
He received an encouraging message
from the local primary school kids.
From Daichi Kawata.
"Mr Miyazon, please do your best
to catch a 100-kilogram marlin."
"We'll all root for you,
you can do it if you try!"
Mr Timon D?
"You can do it if you try!"
He sets off with
the children's encouragement.
They said the same thing.
Look over there,
maybe the waves today are high.
The water is splashing
quite high upon the rock.
But it's said it's easier to catch
marlin if the sea is a bit rough.
Good.
I'm confident we'll catch one.
They don't want to miss this chance,
so fishermen go towards the offing
ahead of us.
How many boats went there?
About 15 boats.
Which boat will they come to?
But unlike his expectations,
not even the bonito and yellowfin
tuna used as bait are seen,
let alone a marlin.
- What about the boats around?
- Nobody got in touch.
I think nobody caught any.
Isn't it wrong
if no boat caught any?
So many sailed today.
Why is no fish showing up?
Dolphins.
They're cute if you see them
at aquariums.
They eat the bait
right after we put it there.
Dolphins chase after fishing boats
and skillfully eat the bait
hanging from the rod.
That's why there is no marlin.
We can only go to a place
with no dolphins.
But after that,
something unexpected happened.
We caught a marlin after that.
But it was only the second day
of filming,
we wanted to do something about it,
so that it wouldn't end in two days.
As the sightseeing ambassador,
I thought we shouldn't end it here.
So we'll play the video in which
we catch the fish at the end.
I don't have to say it,
but in that case,
all the people on the island
knew we caught the fish on day two,
so when they watch this,
they'd think the day isn't right.
Opinions will be divided.
I should say it at a time like this,
so that I won't feel guilty.
This is my way of life.
So I'd like to show you the lovely
things on the island.
Thanks.
So we'll show you sightseeing
information Miyazon recommends.
First, sea water of Yonaguni
is cooked in a kettle
to make Yonaguni Sea Salt.
Three-star Michelin restaurants.
The chefs there use the salt here.
- How long has it been boiling?
- It's the 10th day.
- You boil it for 10 days.
- That's right.
We boil it gently,
so it has a bitter taste.
It brings out the flavour
of the ingredients.
It makes vegetables taste sweet,
and makes meat juicy.
And the sea salt made miraculously
in 2020 is...
the giant salt crystals here.
The particles are huge.
The crystals...
One crystal is... Look, this big.
How about the taste?
It's irresistible.
It has more flavour than saltiness.
My concept of salt crumbled.
Maybe we can't make this again.
It was produced as an accident
under various conditions,
the salt of miracle
is sold at 200,000 yen per kilogram.
On the other hand, the island's
main crop is sugar cane.
Sugar cane in Yonaguni
is processed to produce raw sugar.
Oh, it's here!
Rather than transparent,
it's more like green.
The juice is...
poured into a big pot.
Their sightseeing ambassador
tries raw sugar making.
It looks like this
when it is simmered down.
Okay!
Pour it into the mould! Go!
That big pot simmered down
to so little.
It's ready after it is cooled
overnight and solidifies.
Raw sugar!
What is it? Something like
a huge piece of caramel?
What does the handmade raw sugar
taste like?
It has a nice crunch.
My filling will be damaged
if I'm not careful.
Is this what raw sugar is like?
- Good? Hard?
- Hard.
It's similar to sweet.
The hardest among
the ones you've made so far?
I didn't fail, right?
But you can use it to cook, right?
None of them says clearly,
but it probably was a failure.
Also, a mystery in the sea.
In 1986, a huge undersea structure
was discovered
in the southern part of Yonaguni.
It was named the Yonaguni Monument,
but was it made by humans?
Or did it form naturally?
There are two theories.
I've come to the Submarine Ruins!
Also, a mystery in the sea.
A huge undersea structure
was discovered
in the southern part of Yonaguni.
It was named the Yonaguni Monument,
but was it made by humans?
Or did it form naturally?
There are two theories.
I've come to the Submarine Ruins!
It's like a castle.
This is the Yonaguni Monument.
What you can see now
is only a small part,
but in fact, this is the structure
shown here.
It is 250 metres long
from east to west,
and 150 metres long
from north to south.
Its height is 25 metres,
it's the size of one castle.
He goes to the most famous point
called the Main Terrace.
If this wasn't underwater,
it's just like a castle.
There are flat surfaces and vertical
walls that are 23 metres long.
There isn't even one stone
in the area, and it's unnatural.
The 90-degree straight angle here.
It makes you think
it was made by humans.
This part is the pillar,
those are holes where something
was inserted in the past.
It feels like
people used to live here.
If they are things made by people,
it means that 6,000 to
10,000 years ago,
a civilisation that built high-level
stone buildings existed.
The history of human civilisation
will be changed greatly.
Is it artificial?
Or did it form naturally?
I think your opinion
will be divided,
but isn't it more romantic
to not make it clear?
I went to a zoo with my friend.
I saw a lion and went,
"It's dangerous! I'm scared!"
"There's no way I can win
if it attacks."
My friend went,
"No, the most frightening one
is mankind."
We went to the polar bear zone,
there was a huge polar bear.
I went, "It must be strong!
If I fight it,
I'll stand no chance. It's scary!"
He went, "No, the most frightening
one is mankind."
People have to make
everything clear.
In the end, when we left,
I thought mankind was scary.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
It's the main topic, marlin-fishing.
This is day two of filming.
Because they encountered dolphins,
it was hopeless to catch marlin
in that situation.
Is there a way to deal with it?
We have to go somewhere
without dolphins.
It bit!
An unexpected hit
under this situation.
It bit!
You can do it!
Please.
Can I hook it?
They drive the boat fast
to surely hook the needle.
And then...
This isn't mahi-mahi!
I feel that this isn't a mahi-mahi!
- Totally different.
- The weight is totally different.
Oh, no. I can't reel it in at all.
Only Miyazon knew
when he confronted the fish,
something conveyed through the rod
made him feel it was a big fish.
Do it slowly, be patient.
I swear I'll catch it.
Good.
Thirty minutes after it bit,
there was finally a change
in the battle
between the boat and the sea.
It jumped.
It's a marlin.
The marlin is jumping!
The marlin finally showed up.
You can see it.
It's closer than 20 metres.
It struggles in every direction.
It isn't easy to deal with...
The line comes out again.
I pulled it up and it started moving
when it got closer.
I have to start reeling
from scratch again.
I swear I'll catch it.
Good.
The battle of advance and retreat
lasted for over an hour.
I have a stomach ache now.
It's number two.
I must catch it soon.
I either catch it
or embarrass myself.
It's over there.
It came out.
Marlin's attack.
It's scary.
Scary!
You can do it!
Oh, no! The string
is very slack now!
Now, let's settle this!
Okay! Come!
He squeezed the last bit
of his strength.
The captain knows.
I see it.
Finally, the marlin is at the stern.
For now, I've reeled it in.
And it puts a full stop
to the long battle.
All right!
- His fighting spirit.
- Great, Captain!
So cool!
Captain suddenly roared
this time again.
All right!
Miyazon is a bit creeped out
this time as well.
Mr Tsugu stabbed it with a harpoon
and you smiled.
I smiled.
It wasn't filmed.
Mr Tsugu shouted "Darn it!"
last time,
and the island's people
kept teasing him.
Darn it!
He said he got many calls
after that.
People told him it was funny,
so he said he wouldn't let us
see that this time.
At that time, I thought,
"He messed up."
All right!
It was a battle.
The deadly struggle
lasted for an hour and 20 minutes,
and finally, they killed the marlin.
I finally caught a marlin!
Oh, thank you, Mr Tsugu!
We did it!
Mr Tsugu.
It's a valuable one.
It will stay in my memory
in my life ahead as a fisherman.
Anyway, what a relief!
Thank goodness we caught it.
They transport the marlin
to the port to weigh it.
Will it exceed their goal,
100 kilograms?
Have a look at this. It's huge.
How heavy is it now, really?
What?
97 kilograms.
He couldn't achieve his goal.
Mr Tsugu, please hold it
for a bit longer.
It is over 100!
No, hang on.
This one is huge!
97 kilograms.
It's thin.
We pulled so hard, but it's thin.
Can we feed it water?
Shall we put reinforcing bars in?
Put reinforcing bars in?
Let us have a meeting first.
He suggested to put
reinforcing bars in.
Okay, let's go again!
After that,
he held out for three days,
but he couldn't catch a fish
over 100 kg before it ended.
Can I say something
that bothered me?
Look carefully at the photo
I took with Mr Tsugu.
Mr Tsugu weighs 115 kilograms.
The marlin is bigger than him,
why is it 97 kilograms?
The marlin is obviously bigger
than Mr Tsugu.
Is this an optical illusion?
Lastly, he goes to greet
the island's children
who rooted for him.
This day is the graduation ceremony
of the local Kubura Primary School.
Congratulations on your graduation!
Can I say something
as the sightseeing ambassador?
Graduates, congratulations.
Thank you!
At Kubura Primary School here,
you worked hard to study
and exercise,
and you have graduated.
You are the treasure
of Kubura Primary School.
Please walk on your new path
with confidence.
Separation certainly isn't sad.
There is separation, that's why
there are new encounters.
With gratitude for your parents,
teachers and friends,
please start going
towards your new dream.
Congratulations!
Sightseeing Ambassador,
Anzenmanzai's Miyazon.
Are they going to go
to separate schools?
They'll go next door.
What do you mean "go next door"?
That's the middle school.
After children graduate
from Kubura Primary School,
they will all go to the adjacent
Kubura Middle School.
Oh, thank goodness.
Only a different building.
Always cheerful and happy.
Let's do it! Let's do it!
Let's do it!
Thank you, everyone in Yonaguni.
That's all for Miyazon's
marlin-fishing.