Whoa!
It's pretty!
"THE QUEST"
"This program was broadcast
8th November, 2020"
The Quest has begun.
Tonight, we have Imoto's Japan Tour,
and Lotti Nakaoka's QTube!
We have two sections!
Yes!
First, here is Imoto.
Where did you go this time?
I went to Nagano Prefecture.
- That's a nice place.
- It was very nice.
It's a prefecture where many
active elderly people live!
Sorry to say this, but you'll
only see old men in this video.
Seriously?
A lot of healthy old men.
That's great.
"Imoto Japan Tour in Nagano"
Wow, it's pretty.
It's all red.
Here are yellow and green.
Beautiful colours.
I've got to do it.
"Lotti Nakaoka's QTube"
"Fun video challenge
in Nara and Mie"
The goal is to cover
all 47 prefectures of Japan.
This is the rare animal hunter
Imoto's Japan Tour!
This time, she goes to central Japan
to Nagano Prefecture, which is
adjacent to eight prefectures.
Hello, hello, hello. This is Imoto.
I'm visiting Nagano Prefecture
right now.
Can you spot me?
Here's our usual "Find Imoto"!
- The centre.
- I see her!
- I'm right here!
- I'm right here.
- She's on a bike.
I am currently
- riding a bike above a pond.
- Interesting.
It's a rare activity which
is actually the first in Japan,
called Kogidasu.
You can go cycling
10 metres high in the air.
It's fun!
About 80 percent of Nagano
Prefecture is mountains and plateau.
The biggest goal of this trip
is to see a breath-taking view
of Japan Alps.
You can see incredible autumn leaves
only during this season in Nagano.
I'd love to share that with you all.
Let's get started with Nagano Tour.
First, she visits a famous person
all the locals know about.
This person lives in Karuizawa Town.
Is that him?
I see a signboard,
and it's quite obvious.
Is this the person?
With bees?
At the store, there are photos
of old men covered in bees.
We can see the man growing older.
He looks older in this one.
He looks the youngest in this one.
Was it when he started?
It looks like he's begging the bees
to not sting him.
He looks nervous.
But over here,
he looks more at ease.
He's like, "I'm okay now."
In this one,
I can see he loves bees.
He loves bees a lot. The amount
of bees also increased.
Here is the master of bees.
Yoshizo Ogiwara, 79 years old.
Do you put bees on your body
like in the photos?
Why did you start doing that?
Actually, I often have people
visiting me to film TV shows.
A lot of people visit.
Someone said, "We've all seen people
gathering honey,
so please do something different."
That sounds selfish.
So it all began because
of a TV crew... or the media.
- They pressured you to do it.
- Exactly.
You were trying to entertain them.
He unwillingly started
covering himself in bees
for TV crews to have good shows.
You get stung by them, don't you?
Yes, I get stung a lot.
Oh no.
This isn't funny.
Today, I would like to show you
me being covered in bees.
Thank you.
I'm not sure what will happen
at the end.
That's scary.
To make it clear, we repeatedly
told him not to do it.
But he really wants to show
his new skill
that he obtained, just for us.
It's called "honey bee hat."
Let's take a look
at his incredible skill!
There are so many!
Bees are starting to cover up
his upper body right now.
They're sticking to him.
The honey bread man's friends
are Western honeybees.
Using their habit of swarming
the queen bee,
he skilfully guides
his 30,000 honeybees.
Oh no!
Look at his neck! It looks crazy.
He's smiling.
With a peace sign.
He places the queen bee
on top of his head,
and waits for 10 minutes.
Incredible.
Finally, the honeybee hat
is finished.
It doesn't exactly look like a hat,
but it's nice.
It's a masterful skill that one can
only do with bees' trust.
However, it's not just him
who is fascinated by bees.
Next, we'll introduce masters
at catching bees.
With the average age
of 70 years old,
they are members of Ina City
Local Bee Association.
Now, we'll do sugareoi.
Sugareoi?
We call the local bee "sugare."
They have nests underground.
We'll dig them up
and we'll all eat them.
Sugareoi is a tradition in Nagano
where they look for bee nests.
But how will they find
nests underground?
I see something.
This is common squid,
and it attracts bees.
This is the bee
that they call sugare.
They give them feed with a mark
called "itome."
They eat the feed and bring it
back to their nests.
By chasing the bees,
you'll know where their nests are.
I'm not sure where the bee will go.
That's why we'll chase them.
Whether there will be a tree
or river, they'll chase the bee.
They'll even dash through fields
and mountains.
Please fly.
- Start.
- Here it goes!
As soon as the bee flies,
elderly guys start sprinting.
Everyone is very fast!
I never thought I'd be slower
than people in their 70s!
They could be going
in the same direction.
- The nest is that way.
- Get ready.
Get ready.
Here it goes!
By releasing bees from where
they lost track of them,
they'll try to find the area
where their nests are.
Is this fun?
Yes, we do this all day long.
I guess that's the secret
to staying healthy.
Nagano has one of the best
life expectancies in Japan.
Where is it?
Elderly people are incredibly
healthy and quite active.
We'll keep chasing it this time.
Don't lose track of them.
Let's go!
They've chased 10 bees so far.
Here it goes.
Is it here?
Finally, they found the nests.
We could've never found this
on our own.
There's no honey in sugare's nests.
They're looking for bee larva,
which is very nutritious.
So that's the nest of local bees.
Exactly.
This is huge.
- Whoa!
- Here it goes!
It's massive!
- Let's show it.
- Yeah, please.
- There's more below.
- It's huge.
The nests underground
had nine different levels.
Bee larva is a precious source
of protein in Nagano,
which is not facing any seas.
It's a traditional dish that has
been loved by locals for many years.
It's a bit creamy.
Very good.
This is power food.
You all looked like boys
in elementary school.
You had eyes of young boys.
There's nothing more fun than bees.
Next up is a company from Nagano
which is number one in Japan.
It's Kashiyama Kogyo in Saku City.
What kind of company is this?
At Kashiyama Kogyo,
we manufacture vacuum pumps.
In terms of dry vacuum pumps,
our company has the second
largest share in the world.
Second largest in the world?
Vacuum pumps are a device that
removes air and creates a vacuum.
Vacuum is a space filled
with gas at a pressure
lower than atmospheric pressure.
It means that it's a space
with thin air.
The pumps are used by liquid crystal
and smartphone manufacturers.
When making electronic components
such as semiconductors,
they work under the vacuum state
where impurities in the air
are as non-existent as possible.
Today, we prepared an experiment
using the vacuum state.
You prepared all that for us?
It'll look great on TV.
The logo is much bigger now
compared to when I visited before.
The logo is much bigger now.
First is marshmallow,
which is a typical example.
Here's a vacuum quiz.
What will happen
to these marshmallows?
Ms Oshima! Please answer.
Under vacuum state,
they go like this!
and they shrink like that.
They get smaller.
What happens when marshmallows
are in a vacuum state?
They're expanding!
Really?
- They're getting bigger.
- It's the opposite?
Wow, they're expanding a lot!
Marshmallows under normal state
contain a lot of air,
but under a vacuum condition
there is no pressure,
so the air expands, which makes
marshmallows swell up.
Now I'm going to add air.
When air is added,
they shrink smaller than before
because of the absence of air
in the vacuum state.
They expand and then shrink.
In the vacuum state there are almost
no molecules to transmit vibrations,
so no sound is heard.
I don't hear it anymore.
I don't hear it at all,
though it's vibrating.
Does that mean there's no sound
in the space?
That's true.
Next, Japan's top vacuum pumps
and Imoto have a battle.
The battle takes place
in a baseball stadium.
This one is called a vacuum cannon.
We'll do an experiment where we'll
throw a ball using a vacuum pump.
I see.
We'll place a ball over here,
and pulls it with a vacuum pump.
We'll place a plate over here.
By hitting it strongly
with a hammer,
air will suddenly flow
into a vacuum.
With that momentum,
the ball will be thrown out.
That sounds scary.
What will happen?
How fast will the ball be thrown?
It's a tie in the bottom
of the ninth inning,
with bases loaded and two outs.
Here I go.
- Imoto the batter gives it a try.
- That's scary.
Here comes the first pitch.
One!
Go!
It was so quick!
Strike.
That was so fast!
208 kilometres.
208 kilometres?
Humans can never get that speed.
When it was launched, it only took
0.3 seconds to hit the net.
There's no way she can hit it
with a full swing.
Shall we do a bunt?
So I'll hold the bat at the ready
the entire time?
It'll be at 200 kilometres per hour.
Ouch! My fingers!
My fingers!
It's just a married couple
joking around.
It'll be hell.
Here comes the ace relief pitcher
of Koshiyama Kogyo.
That tube is twice longer
than what we had.
It's four metres long.
What happens with four metres?
One time, it went through the net.
It went through the net,
and flew into that side.
Seriously?
Will we have the world record speed?
It's an experiment of the century.
- Here it comes.
- Come on.
Three.
Two.
One.
I couldn't see it.
I only heard the sound.
It was 271 kilometres per hour.
What was that?
Seriously?
It so fast it's funny.
I'm scared.
This won't be a fair battle.
So Imoto will be given a handicap.
The pitches are 90 metres away
from home plate.
Will it be a strike,
and she will strike out?
Or will it be a wild pitch?
Or will Imoto hit the ball?
Here comes an important pitch!
Here I go!
Come on.
All right.
- Come on?
- What will happen?
Three.
Two.
One.
It went near the edge.
The ball pitched from the centre
didn't curve at all,
and reached Imoto
within only one second.
"It took one second to reach Imoto"
One!
Whoa!
Imoto was hit with a pitch.
The Quest team miraculously won!
I wasn't expecting that.
That was scary.
Without the protector,
I would've been dead.
But I'm glad.
It's a good way to end this section.
- Really?
- Yeah.
This was probably
what we all wanted.
Now that we're exhausted,
let's relax in a hot spring next.
Nagano is number two in Japan in
terms of the number of hot springs.
Hello.
This time, she visits a hot spring
which is very rare in the world.
We have a matchmaking hot spring.
Matchmaking hot spring?
Shosenkaku, a hot spring hotel
located in Nagano City is known for
their matchmaking hot spring that
they've been offering for 35 years.
In Nagano,
mixed baths are not allowed.
But many men have a desire
to go into a mixed bath.
There is a small shrine on the wall
dividing two baths,
and when you pull strings,
the door opens
and they can talk to someone
on the other side.
By the way, the strings are only
attached on the woman's bath side.
It cannot be opened
from the men's bath.
There are actually thee couples
who got married
after meeting in this hot spring.
There might be a man waiting
on the other side.
I'm nervous.
Of course, there won't be men
all the time.
They have to be at the same place
at the same time,
which sounds like fate.
Oh! I see someone.
Someone is there.
I see his hands.
Looking at his skin, he seems young.
Here I go.
Feeling nervous,
they meet for the first time.
Here it is.
Let's go to the mountain together
to see autumn leaves.
Wait,
He's a geezer.
Where are you going?
Karasawa Cirque.
Karasawa Cirque?
It's famous for autumn leaves.
It's very pretty.
But I'd be happy to see autumn
leaves with you, Mr Nukita.
Before that,
we'll go pick rock tripes
growing on rocks.
That sounds fun.
- They're tasty.
- Really?
That sounds autumn-like.
Let's go pick rock tripes
the geezer loves!
They arrive at Kitaaiki Village
with a population of 700 people.
Mr Katsuji Ide
is a mushroom picking master.
We're here to pick rock tripes.
Are they famous in this area?
They're kind of famous.
But not many people like it.
They're tasteless.
Well...
But they're legendary mushrooms.
Well, actually they're moss.
I've never tried it before,
so I'm interested.
It's autumn now.
Mushrooms are great in autumn.
We can pick rock tripes
all year around though,
so it's not specifically good
in autumn.
Is that so?
Really?
It is believed that rock tripes
were food of hermits.
In the ancient times, it was
believed to bring immortality.
They're called legendary because
they only grow on steep rocks
higher than 1,000 metres.
It's difficult to pick them.
I see.
Impressive.
They're all over the rocks.
Here are rock tripes,
which is a kind of moss.
They grow very slowly, and grow
only one millimetre per year.
Because it's so rare, it's sold for
15,000 yen per kilogram.
It's a luxurious food item.
I see very large ones.
I'll put water on them.
Get them wet.
Since they get dry on a sunny day,
they crumble if you pick them
right away.
It's like climbing a mountain.
She'll harvest them
after sprinkling some water.
It looks like it's her job.
Okay, I'll take a large chunk.
Go for it.
Imoto finds a rock tripe
which is about 70 years old.
That looks great.
This much?
All right.
Now, let's eat
the legendary rock tripes!
The master's wife is going to cook
the rock tripes.
She soaks rock tripes in water
and sprinkles salt on them.
She then stir-fries them
with sugar, sake, and soy sauce.
It's the local tradition to eat them
with rice.
Let's eat.
She went through all the trouble
to pick them. How do they taste?
It's good.
It goes very well with rice.
The flavour is soaked in well.
It's like seaweed paste.
It has a great texture.
- It's thicker than seaweed paste.
- That's true.
It's good.
Master doesn't pay attention
to rock tripes,
and starts grilling something
on charcoal.
Are these matsutake mushroom?
That's right.
I can smell them.
- Let's eat.
- Nagano Prefecture
is the number-one producer
of matsutake mushrooms in Japan.
She takes a bit bite into
the autumn food.
Mr Nukita is behind her.
So good!
It's 1,000 times better
than rock tripes.
Don't say that.
- It's incredible!
- Here, they have an intruder.
Ms Imoto.
Helmet young man.
Flower.
Kids in front of TV.
I'll make flowers bloom for you.
Ta-da.
This young guy who messed up
on national TV
is actually someone who works
at Kitaaiki Village Office,
named Kota Sakamoto.
They're flowers made of wood.
What?
He isn't behaving strangely
because he wants to stand out.
Where did you come from?
Three days before filming,
he told our crew members
who were visiting the village,
that not just rock tripes,
but their flowers made of wood
shavings should also be on the show.
But our crew members told him
that The Quest isn't
an informative show,
and it's tricky to deal with topics
that are not funny.
So he gave it a lot of thought.
On the day of filming,
he then proposed a bit
that would be funny.
He even wrote my lines.
I'm talking to the mushroom master,
and someone suddenly appears,
so I ask, "who is that person?"
Then Sakamoto runs to me
and says, Helmet Flower.
He does that here.
You had to say no to him.
You should've said,
"Sorry, but we can't."
Their speciality looks great,
though.
Do you want us to cut this part,
then?
Do you think we should?
Do I think you should cut this?
This is what he believes in,
and he loves his hometown.
When it's too much of that,
it becomes madness.
Thank you for waiting.
At last, let's go to the famous
autumn leaves spot!
Thank you for waiting.
At last, let's go to the famous
autumn leaves spot!
It's a place called Karasawa Cirque
located in the North Alps.
It's 2,300 metres high.
The distance is about 15 kilometres.
It'll take six hours to get there.
It's been a long time...
since I walked in a mountain
with a proper outfit.
But she has already walked
this path many times before
when she camped for Manaslu,
and also on 24 Hour TV.
She realises that
this part won't be aired,
so she doesn't say a word,
and continues walking
in a matter-of-fact manner.
After six hours,
she arrives at Karasawa Cirque,
well-known for its autumn leaves.
That was so quick!
It's so pretty!
It's all red!
I see yellow and green.
Beautiful colours!
Amazing.
I also see colourful tents
which are typical
of Karasawa Cirque.
Cirques are valleys
formed by glacial erosion,
which look as if carved out
with a spoon.
Incredible.
Around the cirque,
there are Hodaka mountains,
which are all about
3,000 metres high.
These leaves all look red.
This is Betula ermanii,
which has a golden yellow colour.
Japanese rowam
has a fiery red colour.
The contrast between the leaves
and the monotone background
makes a breath-taking view that we
can only see on a mountain.
That's all for Nagano Japan Tour.
Next up is this.
Lotti Nakaoka's QTube.
Yes!
I went to my home prefecture, Nara.
- Really?
- Yes.
You're now a top-class comedian.
Are you going to panic because
you're a top-class comedian?
Mr Uchimura, you say that a lot.
But it has never made it
on internet news.
- Seriously?
- Nothing.
It's all quiet.
But he's a top-class comedian.
Hello, this is Lotti Nakaoka.
I'm visiting a factory
in Nara Prefecture right now.
What am I making now?
This time, Nakaoka will promote
a speciality from Nara Prefecture.
This thing is famous
in Nara Prefecture.
The thing that I'm making will
come out from here, so take a look.
Here it comes!
Here's the answer.
- It's a sock.
- Really?
Nara Prefecture is the number-one
producer of socks.
Charix here was built to promote
their socks.
Just by choosing
a colour and cycle for five minutes,
customers can easily knit
their original socks.
- Cool.
- I want to try.
At the end, the tip parts
with a hole are sewn together.
I'm going to try it on.
They become a shape
we're all familiar with.
All right.
Isn't this great?
Lotti Nakaoka QTube.
Nara is a great place!
I'll do my best!
All right.
We'll go to Mie Prefecture now.
What?
What about Nara?
For Nara...
- This is it.
- This is it?
He arrives at Ise Shima,
Mie Prefecture.
First, he'll try challenge videos
from around the world.
Nakaoka basketball spin.
He's trying this
on a burning hot iron plate,
which has been heated up
under the scorching sun.
Be careful.
Nice.
Oh no, it's extremely hot.
It's extremely hot.
First, he puts a basketball
on top of the iron plate,
and balances on his chest.
This looks scary.
Here I go.
Can he spin and have
the ball under his back?
Good luck.
- Go!
- You can do it!
- Wait.
Here it goes.
Hot, hot!
It's too hot.
This isn't good. Seriously.
This part hit for a moment.
I went like this, and this.
It's possible to do it.
But this is too hot.
It's seriously too hot.
I'll turn now.
Let's try again.
Good luck!
Here I go.
You can do it.
Oh no.
It's getting hard.
Turn around.
Ouch!
Here I go.
Wait.
It's hot!
No, It's too hot.
He tries something else
on the burning iron plate.
Anna Maria from Italy will remotely
teach him how to do it.
I'll show you a challenge
which will be very easy.
From standing up, sit down,
and stand up again.
But don't put the hands
on the floor.
It looks easy, but is it actually
difficult to do?
He tries this on a safe area
on the burning iron plate.
But if he can't stand up
after 15 seconds,
there will no longer be
a safe area.
Will Nakaoka beat the challenge
within the time limit?
It's scary to be barefoot.
It's incredibly scary.
Ready, set,
go!
This challenge is easy
until he sits down.
But standing up without using hands
is quite difficult.
It must be difficult.
Five seconds left.
- Oh no.
- This isn't good.
Wait!
Nakaoka tries desperately
to keep the safe area.
I should be ashamed.
I should be ashamed of what I did
as a QTuber.
Let's try it again.
Good luck!
Will he succeed this time?
- Go.
- All right.
Nakaoka wants to avoid the burning
hot iron plate as much as he can.
He builds up momentum.
Go!
- Go!
- You can do it!
This is the last part!
It's so hot!
You stupid!
It was hotter that he could handle,
so Nakaoka attacks
the director in charge.
This isn't good.
Something flew in.
It's so hot that I couldn't help
taking it out on someone.
They threw the towel roughly.
He's a top-class comedian.
- They threw the towel like this.
- He's a top-class comedian.
They're always like that.
On a table.
It's like a mum
throwing cloth over a table.
It looks just like that.
Next is a challenge video, where
he'll win a prize if he succeeds.
Nakaoka, staircase, paper catch.
He'll win a prize if he can catch
paper before it falls on the floor.
We'll try this at Shima
Mediterranean Village,
on a Greek style staircase.
What I'm concerned about is...
the wind blowing between
the buildings.
Here I go!
He'll win a prize if he can succeed
in one try.
Start.
Where is it?
Paper is not coming down at all.
Seriously?
Is this okay?
He catches it easily.
I caught it.
Here's the prize he was promised.
Fake one-million yen bills.
I don't like it at all.
That's not what we mean.
There are 100 bills in this,
so throw them all in the air.
We'll give you 1,000 yen each
for bills that you'll catch.
That'd be amazing.
He'll use a blank pile of bills
often used in films.
I see.
He'll receive 1,000 yen
for each bill that he catches.
Go get it.
It'd be better to spread them.
He could be rich after this!
The show has never been
so generous before.
Will Nakaoka win a lot of money?
Here I go!
Hurry!
You can do it!
1,000 yen.
It's just 1,000 yen.
I'm sorry you had to see me
like that.
I'm sure my parents
would hate to see me like that.
Next is a video that's going viral
in the world.
Using coins laid
on a piece of board,
he'll show a message in the air.
Here's what he'll use.
They're coins from the overseas
filming trips of this show.
I see.
But I know many people put coins
in a donation box.
You're the only ones
who brought these home.
What kind of message
will Nakaoka send?
It'll be a message for one
of the people at the studio.
Let's see who
his message will be for.
Wait.
What's going on?
For when it goes up,
do I have to flip letters?
Yes, letters need to be flipped.
The size and weight
are also important.
Iceland.
It's a coin from Iceland.
Africa.
What's this?
Horumon Construction?
Corporate?
It's from an amusement arcade.
All right.
Here's a message from Nakaoka
to a certain person at the studio.
Congrats.
The Quest.
Regular.
Degawa.
Awesome.
I can see it clearly.
Nice.
I'll do a portrait.
He'll finish this
with a self-portrait.
You put too much hair on your head.
I wasn't paying attention to that.
Can I make it more realistic?
- Here.
- I've got a bald spot here.
Look at that.
I get Twitter and Instagram
direct messages
from people trying to sell me
hair growth formula.
I've got 10 messages so far.
For some reason,
I've also got one message
asking if I've got mould
in my washing machine.
Why did they think I'd have mould
in my washing machine,
and send me a direct message?
Next is a video with a great view
that went viral on social media.
Sky diving shot
with a 360-degree camera.
Nakaoka visits
Ise Shima Skydiving Club.
This is Rhys, the instructor.
No Japanese?
- Zero.
- Zero? Okay.
Country.
- New Zealand.
- He's from New Zealand.
I see. You know...
Conversations like this
with foreign people...
remind me of my trips.
But there's no interpreter because
they'll still in Japan.
So they'll use an app
to translate their conversation.
How long have you been skydiving?
How many years has it been
since I diving?
Me?
Twenty-three.
23 years.
You're experienced.
Have you ever failed?
Skydiving airplane,
the engine blew up.
Skydiving airplane engine blew up.
Seriously?
- Does that really happen?
- The voice sounds funny.
First, please enjoy the view of
Ise Shima shot by a normal camera.
"Nakaoka skydiving in Ise Shima"
Oh no.
I'm getting really scared.
I've got to do it.
I have to.
Nakaoka has a fear of heights.
He goes up to 3,000 metres
above the ground.
Okay.
There he goes!
It's perfect weather,
without a single cloud.
Below them, the beautiful ridged
coast of Ise Shima spreads out.
Nice.
Look at his face.
I can't recognise him now.
Are we not there yet?
This feels nice.
Really?
Next, here is a video shot
by a 360-degree camera.
The image looks distorted because
it's a 360-degree image composited
together to fit the screen.
Amazing.
If he looks down.
It's the Earth!
Amazing.
It looks exactly like the Earth.
"Earth"
The blue sky without clouds
looks like outer space.
The deeply indented coastline
resembles large continents.
Awesome.
You really are a top-class comedian.
Next, he'll try amazing tricks from
videos from all over the world.
He'll catch a flying disk
while facing his back to it,
let it pass under his crotch,
and put a plastic bottle
on top of it after spinning it.
The person who will throw
the flying disk is
Mr Maeda, who used to be
on the national team.
Let's do it here.
Let's have him throw one.
Here we go.
Wow.
I couldn't do it at all.
What?
I'll pay attention to this.
If he pays attention
to the plastic bottle...
he can't even catch a flying disk.
It's so hard.
Even after trying for two hours,
no success.
This isn't good!
"After three hours"
That was close!
Ouch.
That looks painful.
It's the plastic bottle
and the flying disk.
Both of them miraculously
hit Nakaoka's head.
Compared to how this part
normally looks,
it's swollen to twice larger.
I'm receiving quite a bit of impact
each time.
It's been 4.5 hours
since the filming started.
Finally, the time has come.
Here's the first shot.
The timing was off.
It's too fast.
We've messed up.
He does a bit of
Cook Poko impression.
All right.
Then...
I did it!
Though the plastic bottle bounced
at first,
Nakaoka finally caught it.
That's incredible.
It's a miracle.
I did it!
See? I did it, right?
Right?
Yes!
Yeah!
We're behind schedule, so we'll
go to Nara to play volleyball.
Really?
The last part is a special project
called Karada Week.
It's a collaboration video with
high school students in Nara.
The last part is a special project
called Karada Week.
It's a collaboration video with
high school students in Nara.
He'll collaborate
with the volleyball team
of Nara Girls' High School.
They've competed in Inter-High
28 times before.
They also ranked eighth
at the spring competition.
It's a strong team
with a brilliant record.
They'll try "receive quick change."
They'll start with a serve,
and each member
will put on a jacket.
Can six members put on a jacket
without dropping the ball?
All right, let's go!
Okay.
No, serve.
First, let's see
Nakaoka's receiving skills.
All right.
Did you do a trick?
You did, didn't you?
I'm an amateur but I can tell.
Serve a straight shot.
She did a trick.
Was that a natural one?
Now they'll change clothes quickly.
It's a success once they put
both arms through the sleeves.
Be easy on me.
He's good.
Nice.
There's no way I can do this.
Let's have a member try.
Yurina in the second grade will try.
Yurina.
Her receives are great.
However...
You can do it.
It's hard.
What we know now is
that even for elite volleyball
members like them,
this is quite challenging.
Go!
Then, a strong player appears.
You can do it.
That's right.
Awesome.
Nice. It looks stable.
Manami, you look stable.
Let's have her give us some tips.
Bring the ball high up,
and put your right or left arm
- One arm first.
- through the sleeve.
Keeping tossing the ball
with one arm.
Then put your arm behind.
- That looks incredible!
- With Manami's advice,
the students quickly improved.
Now the pressure is on Nakaoka,
who will be the anchor.
With the coach's guidance,
he learns the basics.
Then...
It's too low.
Wow, he's getting better.
You almost got it.
He'll soon get it.
It's too high, so once you put in
one arm, keep it down a bit.
He's never even tried this.
Let's do the actual challenge.
With high school students
in Nara Prefecture,
I want to show you all
that we're all trying our best.
Let's do it.
- Let's do it.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Receive quick change begins now.
I wanted to look cool in front
of the girls' volleyball team.
The first person is
the tallest attacker of the school
with the height of 171 centimetres,
named Kotona.
- Nice.
- She first shoots up the ball high,
and puts one arm through the sleeve.
Incredible.
This part is tricky.
Next, while tossing with one arm,
she puts another arm.
Next is the team clown Sayaka.
It looks stable.
You can do it!
Okay!
Nice.
You're doing great.
Everyone is so good.
It looks very stable.
Very good.
- They're very calm.
- You can do it.
Here you go!
Okay.
The third person is Manami
who's always stable.
She's stable.
Manami.
Her receives are some of the best
in the country.
She's very good.
Give me a minute.
Okay.
Yes!
The fifth member is Nanaka,
who's in third grade.
She's the captain.
This year, games and practises
were cancelled due to COVID.
Even then, she led the team
as the captain.
You can do it!
Go for it!
It'll be okay.
Use one arm.
That's right.
She's very good.
Awesome, great job.
She did a great job, and now
she'll pass it to a junior student.
You're doing great.
The ball is now passed to Yurina
in second grade.
She looks very calm, and doesn't
show that she's under pressure.
All right.
Now it'll be my turn.
He must be so nervous.
Pressure's on the sixth player.
She puts her arms
through the sleeves.
Wait for me.
Stay calm, okay?
Okay, come on.
Will Nakaoka succeed?
From there?
All right!
You can do it.
Failed.
This is really disappointing.
There's little time left before
the students leave the school.
Here, Nakaoka has a suggestion.
Can I ask you a favour?
I will shoot up the ball high
the second time.
I'll wear my jacket,
so could one of you
receive the ball?
Looking at the time,
this will be their last try.
For the last time, everyone will
chase the ball Nakaoka shoots up.
Let's do this!
Let's do it!
What is this?
Look at his face.
One person's mistake
is everyone's mistake.
Everyone is ignoring him.
Nobody responded.
Everyone is doing a great job.
It's amazing.
The volleyball team
of Nara Girls' High School
stayed late to finish filming.
They want to keep the ball in the
air until the end, no matter what.
- On no!
- It's fine.
It's fine, it's stable.
- This isn't good.
- No, everything is fine.
You're doing great.
He's talking a lot.
Can Nakaoka finish the job?
What's up with his face?
Okay!
Wait a minute. Slowly.
Let's calm down.
All right.
Come on!
You can do it.
Take it.
That way.
The ball goes to an unexpected
direction, but Kotona covers it.
Nakaoka has finished
putting on the jacket.
So it'll be a success if Nakaoka
can toss the ball at the end.
They're all great.
Yes, we did it!
At the end, it was just like
playing volleyball.
But Nakaoka and high school students
united together and did a great job.
Yes! We did it!
To the volleyball team
of Nara Girls' High School,
thank you very much!
Can we consider this a success?
I'm sure they all worked very hard.
But please don't play cool
in front of high school girls.
All right.
What's that face?
Let's do it.
See? He's trying to be cool.
He was, wasn't he?
That wasn't my intention.
I was just being serious.
After you spoke,
you made that sharp face.
He really did.
At the end,
when he was trying to look cool,
though usually his hair looks messy,
he tied his hair tightly in front
of high school girls.
Very tightly.
Like Antonio Banderas.
That's exactly right.
He usually never ties his hair
because it's very precious to him.
- Because it makes people laugh.
- In front of high school girls,
why didn't you eat bread too?
I wanted you to eat it there too.
In that part, I wanted
his hair to be messy.
- That's not possible.
- I'm disappointed you tied it.
He also had a nasty face
when it was about money.
When he was catching bills.
He really had a nasty face.
With a grin.
Wait, perhaps he's not
a top-class comedian.