For more, please visit: http://tofupandas.tumblr.com/matsumotoke
Subbed by: Otviss
Do you know what this is?
Wow, it's an electric eel!
Wow, it's big!
How many volts does it give off?
About 800 volts.
800 volts?
You'd die
You'd die definitely
So we created this thing here...
So we wanted to let you feel
how the very food we give it feels like...
You're gonna get to feel the current together.
Ugh, that's scary!
THIS IS SO FREAKING SCARY!!
Let's get to it then..
Aah! This is so freaking scary! So scary!
No! no! no! I can't!
I'm not kidding, this is bad
Alright so the food is gonna come out from behind here
Okay, it's dropped
Oh it found it!
You broke it!
Hahahaha you broke it!
That hurt!
This is...
Subbed by: Otviss
Let's decide which one of you has to do it now then
No no no no...
After 3 people experience how this is, There's gonna be one safe person.
That's just strange! We won after all
Exactly! We won already
We won already
No this is something you just gotta experience
Let's do rock-paper-scissors...
This is no good
Let's get this over with
Who will become an electric eel's prey?
Hang on a second, this is not good at all
Let's go! ROCK PAPER SCISSORS!
YEEEEEESSSS!!!!!
Lil bro you did it
Ugh just why!?
Let's raise the volts!
No! Why!?
Let's raise the bar
No that's not happening. In that case let's make the head chief do it too...
No... I... It's really bad
Why!?
Of course it's like that. Chief you're gonna do it anyway
No seriously, I don't deal with electricity very well
Me too!
That's just an excuse people say
Head chief, we're friends it's okay, lets go
That's enough now, let's go
Kenji and the Head chief
Shocking experience
will get a
Okay...well..okay we'll do it but...
please let me know if it hurts though, please?
You're being too selfish, it's weak electricity
Whether it hurts or not... I mean it's electricity after all
It's like getting a taste of electricity basically
Okay let's go. You can drop the food now
Alright, starting with the food now
Not yet you guys, not yet
Not quite yet
It hasn't noticed it yet
It hasn't found it yet
Haha it's bad isn't it
Not quite yet
It hasn't noticed it yet
It hasn't found it yet
Oh it's still tingling
Yeah it's still stinging
That was amazing...
I'm thinking of lowering the strength from now on..