The following program was produced with
the utmost consideration toward safety
and features dangerous activities which
were supervised by stunt professionals.
Do not attempt to reenact any
of the activities performed.
The final round in this great battle
between Hamada's and Junior's armies
is about to begin.
Last Round
It will decide whose army
will reign supreme.
You Will Die,
round four.
Sumo Death!
YOU WILL DIE, ROUND 4
SUMO DEATH
What?
-"You will die"?
-We're definitely going to die?
They're telling us we'll die.
Wrestle each other with your cars
and push the opponent out of bounds
or force them to retire.
Really?
He was eating steak earlier.
-Really?
-Let him eat whatever he likes.
-You were watching him eat?
-Yep.
"Sumo Death Laws"
The competitor who pushes their opponent
out of the square
or forces them to retire
will be victorious.
The two armies will use their remaining
battle cars in a judo-style tournament.
The army that annihilates
the other army's battle cars
will be heralded as the victors.
The losing army
must sacrifice the life
of one of their foot soldiers.
-One of us is getting killed?
-Killed?
What do you mean we're getting killed?
One foot soldier will be killed.
By foot soldiers, they mean us right?
We're the foot soldiers.
-They're going to kill us?
-What do you mean?
We're getting executed?
Here are the battle cars
for Junior's army.
Junior's Army
Battle cars
In the "Road to Hell" round...
Look at that. The front of the Jaguar
is falling apart!
The front of Matsuoka's car is damaged.
The Jaguar was forced to retire.
At the end of the Romantic Flight round,
the Audi had to be retired.
Once the cars take flight,
they are automatically forced to retire.
Plus, since they lost
the Romantic Flight round,
they had the Mercedes taken away
by Hamada's army.
Junior's Army
This means they now
have five cars remaining.
They must fight the pervert barbarian
from Osaka with this fleet of battle cars.
Volvo V70, BMW 330i, Mercedes-Benz S320,
Alfa Romeo Alfa GT, Lincoln Navigator
Here are the battle cars
for Hamada's army.
Hamada's Army
Battle cars
Due to the fierce battle
during the Road to Hell round,
the Toyota Century was forced to retire.
The front of the Century has sustained
a lot of damage.
In the same Road to Hell round...
He can't stop. He can't stop!
Is he okay?
The car is on its roof! Is Sata okay?
Yamamoto's beloved Beetle
was also retired.
Plus, in the Romantic Flight round...
Whoa! That was amazing!
It bounced off the other cars
to cover more distance!
The Nissan Fairlady Z was retired
at the end of this round.
Hamada's Army
Now they have six battle cars remaining.
Nissan Fuga, Toyota Celsior,
Nissan Skyline,
Honda Crossroad, Toyota Corolla Van,
Mercedes-Benz SLK230 Kompressor
They have a numerical advantage
over Junior's army.
But Junior's army has...
Monster
...a monster in their army.
We've got the Volvo, Alfa Romeo,
BMW, Mercedes,
and the Lincoln remaining.
We've still got the Lincoln.
The Lincoln will do well here.
Lincoln Navigator
Weight 2500kg - 304 hp
It's really powerful.
It's a matter of
who will drive the Lincoln.
Right.
But up until now...
Mr. Muto's been driving it thus far.
The driver's seat is on the left as well.
I think it would be hard
if you weren't used to it.
However, I might be able to beat
all of their cars all by myself.
All right, then!
It's fine, let's go!
That's fine. Let's do that.
Why don't you all go have some tea then?
Yeah.
You'll pummel them all, then.
Right.
Lincoln Navigator
New car price 10 million yen
The giant from Junior's army,
the Lincoln Navigator.
It weighs 2.5 tons.
It's such a sturdy car that it is
often used to move VIPs in the U.S.
It is, without a doubt, the strongest
weapon that Junior's army possess.
Engine 5.4L V8DOHC / 304 hp / AWD / AT / 2500kg
We have six cars
compared to five for them.
Right.
It would be troublesome
if they bring out that car
from the outset.
You mean Muto's Lincoln?
Yeah.
If that happens, we'll need to pummel
that car in the first half
so we can end up winning in the end.
By the way, Nagisa...
Yes?
About your car,
do you want to fight in it personally,
or give it to someone else?
The Fuga.
Right.
It doesn't matter who drives the car,
so...
Yes...
I do want to drive it myself, but...
Right.
I really want to win this battle.
I see.
That being the case,
I want to let the person who's been saying
they wanted to drive the Fuga
from the beginning drive it.
-Mr. Ozawa?
-Me?
Yes.
What will you do, Mr. Ozawa?
They are Nagisa's feelings, after all.
He was saying that all along.
Are you sure?
In that case, I'll deliver the final blow
using your car.
What do you mean by final blow?
You need to win first.
You just have to win.
I'll win.
They're going to bring out
Muto's Lincoln first.
I've lost two in a row
to the Lincoln today.
Right, you can't lose for a third time.
I need to give a good final performance.
Hey!
What are you going to do?
What do you mean? We're going to fight!
Are you giving up?
Of course not!
We've already decided.
We're going with
the Lincoln.
There, see!
We're starting off with the best!
Seriously?
But they're finished if we defeat him.
That's true.
Are you sure?
Yes, the Lincoln.
All right!
We're going to trample your team.
Nagisa, are you okay to send the Fuga?
Yes, let's send the Fuga!
Really?
The Fuga?
Yes, the Fuga.
You've already lost the fight!
No, no.
We don't know that yet.
The driver is
the man with a face that could kill!
The Century broke down, so...
It's not Mr. Hamada?
Lincoln Navigator
New car price 10 million yen
Representing Junior's army, Keiji Muto.
His battle car is
the Lincoln Navigator.
Engine 5.4L V8DOHC / 304 hp / AWD / AT / Weight 2500kg
Nissan Fuga
New car price approx. 5.7 million yen
Representing Hamada's army,
Hitoshi Ozawa.
His battle car is Nagisa's car,
the Nissan Fuga.
Engine 3.5L V6 DOHC / 280 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1680kg
That is a Nissan Fuga.
Fuga.
Nagisa was duped into buying
the Nissan Fuga by Hamada's army.
It's really similar to the car
that my ex-boyfriend had,
so it feels really familiar.
It feels natural and comfortable.
Now, through this smoke-like dust,
the small red Mercedes tries to catch up.
The back of the Fuga
is still under attack!
Only one month after being purchased,
the Fuga that has worked hard for Hamada
is now up against
the strongest opponent there is.
-Hey, Nagisa.
-Yes?
Sorry your time with it was so short.
It really was.
You've only driven it twice, right?
I've only driven it twice.
It's only been a month since I bought it.
You must have been so excited
before you went to bed last night.
That's right.
I was really enjoying it
this morning, too. The weather was great,
so I thought it would be
a great day to go for a drive.
For the ending of our show, Tokyo Drive,
I was planning
to go to my hometown in Amagasaki.
I see.
Lincoln Navigator versus Nissan Fuga.
The difference in weight is 820 kilograms.
Nissan Fuga
(Hamada's army, 1680 kg, 280 hp)
Lincoln Navigator
(Junior's army, 2500 kg, 304 hp)
Will Hamada's army annihilate
their opponents
and take Junior's castle?
This is the final round.
You Will Die, round four.
Sumo Death!
Out of all the battle cars
that competed in previous rounds,
this round will be fought by the cars that
managed to survive the first three rounds.
The unbeatable Pro Wrestling Master
Keiji Muto
Muto will be up first.
I think the one who stomps
the accelerator wins.
But the one driving the other car
is Mr. Ozawa.
Yeah, he's a big fan
of the frontal assault.
Come on.
Here's Ozawa.
The man with a face that could kill
Hitoshi Ozawa
Just you wait.
I'll fight with everything I've got.
I will pummel him.
Bring me my weapons!
I wonder if he's up
to his old tricks again.
Ozawa's got a bazooka.
What?
What's that on his left shoulder?
It's a bazooka!
Now he's armed himself with a bazooka!
I can't win unless I use
all the weapons I've got.
He doesn't get the point of this battle,
does he?
Wow, it's so big.
Come on.
It's got a lot of presence.
It really does.
Mr. Muto.
Yes?
How do you feel facing him?
I feel very confident
after seeing their car.
I see.
Please chat amongst yourselves.
Please don't be so aggressive
that you hurt yourself.
Just hang on.
You mean he might get away from me?
The field isn't too wide,
I don't think that's going to happen.
Because you're close to each other?
Yes.
This leopard print thing
is really annoying.
Can you take it off?
What's your strategy?
I'll avoid hitting him head on.
-I see.
-Right.
I'll avoid him, then attack
with grenades and the bazooka.
As expected.
Then I'll attack from behind!
As expected, they're familiar
with the ways of battle.
Keiji Muto is used to being in battles.
Let's go!
-Come on!
-All right!
The battle between
the Lincoln Navigator...
Stare-off.
...and Ozawa in Nagisa's Nissan Fuga
begins now!
Ready, fight!
Ozawa has gone left.
What does Muto do?
He doesn't slam into Ozawa.
He pushes Ozawa slowly.
Slowly.
You're doing well!
Push, push!
One loses when a tire goes out of bounds.
Muto's Lincoln Navigator
shows us the power
of a four-wheel drive vehicle!
You can't let him push you!
Reverse, reverse!
What's that? It's a grenade!
He's already using a grenade on him.
Ozawa's laughing! Such an evil laugh!
It hasn't exploded yet. Now it does!
It exploded underneath the Lincoln.
Did he do it?
It exploded!
Go! Go!
That's dangerous!
In the meantime, Ozawa has reversed
and nudges Muto's side.
They're laughing!
Now Muto has taken the center position.
Wow, the front of Nagisa's white Fuga
is getting more and more damaged.
Let's go, Muto!
Go, go!
Come on!
Will he run or turn around?
He has turned his back!
Muto's going to push him out.
Will Ozawa be beaten by the power
of the four-wheel drive?
He's turned the steering to negate that.
It seems to have little effect
against this monster.
He's managed to escape!
They exchange positions.
Can he take the back position? No...
Wow, it has sustained more damage!
Mr. Ozawa!
Come on!
Muto tries to reverse to get into position
to push Ozawa out.
But Ozawa tries to block him.
Muto nudges the side of Ozawa's car.
Muto's going for it now.
A battle between a 54-year-old
and a 55-year-old.
He's brought out the bazooka!
The bazooka exploded in the car!
And Muto pushes Ozawa out of bounds!
WIN Lincoln (frontal push out)
Nissan Fuga
The bazooka exploded in the car!
What the hell happened?
Useless bazooka.
What happened?
What just happened?
It exploded in the car!
Come on!
Junior's army wins.
Muto wins!
Once again,
Ozawa has experienced
an explosion in his car.
SENTOSHA
Here, Ozawa takes out his bazooka
as he tried desperately
to turn the tide of the match.
But, unfortunately...
Right there!
It has worked against him again!
Therefore, Muto from Junior's army
wins the first battle.
SENTOSHA
The bazooka exploded in the car.
That'll impair your vision.
Why did it explode in the car?
He could've gotten away
if he hadn't used the bazooka.
Are you okay to keep going?
No problem at all!
I can keep going till the end!
Go ahead!
I'm not going to worry
about making the show dramatic,
and just keep winning, okay?
-That's fine!
-Right.
-It's still alive, Nagisa.
You can still drive it.
You can drive home in it.
You can drive it home today.
Yeah.
But it looks so battered.
My weapons didn't work for me today.
You fired a bazooka in my car.
That really was amazing.
From this battle, Hamada's army has lost
one of their battle cars.
The two armies begin the second battle
with five cars each.
SENTOSHA
5 vs 5
What are we going to do?
How about we keep slamming Muto
on the driver's side?
And then we'll get Muto...
We'll kill off Muto first.
That's too cruel.
Let's smash them, okay?
Yeah!
Why are you making him do it?
That's a phrase he made famous!
Yeah!
Iwahashi, what do you want to do?
Do you want to drive yourself?
I'd be happy to let anyone drive
if they wanted to...
But it's your car full of family memories.
You should drive it yourself.
You've driven over someone already.
Right.
What's with that?
Just get on top.
I'll do it.
Do it for us.
You just need to get on top
of the Lincoln.
Do you have any advice for me?
Rather than taking him head on...
I should attack him from the side?
Yes.
Like Ozawa did earlier,
you can squeeze past to get around him.
I see.
Ozawa got around him a few times.
The rest is up to horsepower.
Okay.
We're going with...
Iwahashi!
No problem!
We'll call a doctor.
Think we can't win?
We'll take on anyone or anything!
We're sending out the Honda Crossroad!
Awesome.
A four-wheel drive?
He'll do it for his family!
Honda Crossroad
New car price 2.9 million yen
The uncontrollable hitman,
Yoshimasa Iwahashi.
His battle car is
the Crossroad packed
full of family memories.
Engine 1.8L SOHC / 140 hp / 4WD / Weight 1480kg
I want to keep it well maintained.
I really want to drive it
for a very long time.
A very long time?
Yeah, my wife loves this car as well.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Iwahashi was also duped into
joining Hamada's army.
But, as the competition progressed,
Iwahashi awakened as a battle car racer.
Iwahashi attacks from behind!
He's driving up the side of Shoji's car!
Iwahashi completely drove
on top of Shoji's car!
Damn it!
Although they are both
four-wheel drive cars,
the difference in weight
is 1,020 kilograms.
Is it a four-wheel drive, too?
It's a four-wheel drive!
These kinds of cars are tough!
He might climb on top of that car again.
Muto, please be careful
of their sideways attack.
Yeah, I know.
He'll be coming to get you on the inside.
Right.
This is his own car, isn't it?
Don't worry about that.
I don't have to worry?
No, you don't.
I understand.
Yeah!
You shouldn't do that!
It makes me feel sorry for him.
I clocked up 30,000 kilometers
in two and a half years.
The uncontrollable hitman
Yoshimasa Iwahashi
I've got a lot of memories in this car.
I took my family to the Atami hot springs
in this car.
I drove my wife's parents
in this car as well.
Salary.
Zero.
If we could just get rid
of that Lincoln...
This is a battle between Muto
in the American car with a powerful engine
versus Iwahashi in the Honda Crossroad.
Here, Muto sits proudly
in his Lincoln Navigator.
Thank you!
Iwahashi shows his appreciation
for his car
full of wonderful memories
with his family.
He must have realized this could be
the end for this car.
Muto, on the other hand,
looks very confident.
Now, Iwahashi prepares himself
to risk his life with the Crossroad.
Come on!
-It's his own car, right?
-Right.
Yeah, it's his own car.
Muto might be in trouble if he gets hit
from the side.
Honda Crossroad
(Hamada's army, 1480 kg, 140 hp)
Lincoln Navigator
(Junior's army, 2500 kg, 304 hp)
Have a look at them,
they are both four-wheel drives.
It's like a lightweight champion
versus a giant.
Their size difference is quite evident.
We're now ready for battle.
Stare-off.
Ready...
Go!
Fight!
Now, Iwahashi turns to the left.
Iwahashi has exposed his side
for Muto to attack!
The door is getting pummeled.
Tough it out!
Will Muto finish him off in one go?
The Lincoln Navigator
is pushing him steadily.
The left wheel!
The left wheel goes out of bounds.
Junior's army wins.
WIN Lincoln (frontal push out)
Honda Crossroad
Muto pushes Iwahashi out of bounds.
That's two wins in a row for Muto!
Yeah!
That was quick!
Really quick!
Yeah!
Such a quick victory!
He was waiting for us to make a move.
Yeah.
He's watching us carefully.
You can't let him take you from the side.
That's right. That's it.
He stopped after going to the left
and let him attack from the side.
He should've kept going
and taken him from the other side.
Shit!
SENTOSHA
From the outset,
when Iwahashi turned to the left,
he exposed the right side
of his car to Muto.
This ultimately led to his defeat.
Along with the memories of his family,
the Crossroad starts to crumple up.
In the end, it couldn't withstand
the sheer force of the Lincoln
and the left rear wheel went out of bounds
and the match was over.
Muto and Junior's army win two in a row!
Junior's army wins.
SENTOSHA
The opponents are getting weaker
and weaker.
Hamada's army now has four cars remaining.
Is it impossible to defeat
this monster vehicle?
SENTOSHA
5 vs 4
How about you, Yamamoto?
All right!
Shit.
I'll take the Corolla.
The Corolla, right?
You don't know what will happen.
It's hard if he doesn't let you
take him side on.
I'm not sure what to do.
Can you take him from underneath?
Yamamoto, maybe.
I'll wait and see what he does.
Good.
That's right.
We always make the first move.
I'll think about what to do
after he makes his move.
That's a good idea.
We'll see what Muto wants to do.
Right.
Making him surrender would also work.
Toyota Corolla Van
New car price 1.5 million yen
Resurrected after ten years,
the Golden Boy,
Keiichi Yamamoto.
His battle car is the Toyota Corolla Van.
Engine 1.3L I4 DOHC / 82 hp / FF / 4MT / Weight 930kg
The weight difference between the two cars
is an astounding 1,570 kilograms.
This delivery van
is Yamamoto's battle car
which defeated Harada's Audi
in the Road to Hell round.
Yamamoto had his beloved Beetle wrecked.
Now, his Beetle is destined
for the scrap heap.
Resurrected after ten years of silence,
the Golden Boy, Keiichi Yamamoto
Sata's back.
Hey.
How is everything?
Sata, who underwent
a medical assessment returns.
We were worried about you.
I've just got some bruising.
I'm okay because I work out a lot.
Yamamoto's going to fight now.
Who's fighting?
We're up against the Lincoln.
Sorry, but, can we use your car?
No way!
It's not happening!
Have a look at this.
The difference in power is evident.
Does that delivery van even have a chance?
The cars are so different.
The cars are too different.
I have no intention
of taking him on directly.
Yeah!
Yamamoto, let's wait and see, okay?
Understood.
Thank you.
Hamada!
Yeah?
You're going to fight us with that car?
Just look at it.
It's a delivery van.
You never know!
It's like Arnold Schwarzenegger
versus Danny DeVito.
You can't underestimate a Toyota.
How's Keiji Muto's knee holding up?
Isn't he giving up already?
Don't make fun of his knee!
Then let's do it even more.
Now, this is literally
David versus Goliath.
Yes.
It's okay if I win in one move
like last time, right?
Muto, how are you feeling?
I'm very confident.
Yeah!
Stop it! It's sad!
Toyota Corolla Van (Hamada's army, 930 kg, 82 hp) vs
Lincoln Navigator (Junior's army, 2500 kg, 304 hp)
It's time for the battle to commence.
Wait and see. Just wait and see.
Watch.
It's scary if they get desperate.
Stare-off.
Ready.
Go!
Come on!
What will he do?
They start slowly this time.
Muto attacks straight on!
He pushes and pushes.
Muto takes Yamamoto out of bounds
in one big push!
He pushes and pushes.
Muto takes Yamamoto out of bounds
in one big push!
He pushes and pushes.
Muto takes Yamamoto out of bounds
in one big push!
Junior's army wins.
Yeah!
WIN Lincoln (frontal push out)
Corolla Van
It really is something else.
It's the strongest!
It's done!
Instant death!
It's three wins in a row for Muto!
There was nothing Yamamoto could do.
The front has crumpled up, too!
You're kidding!
This keeps on happening!
This is impossible!
It's like Goliath.
We're up against a heavyweight!
How could that happen?
SENTOSHA
In the beginning,
Yamamoto steered to the left
and tried to go around Muto,
but Muto took no notice of that
and attacked straight on.
This is just the difference in ability
between a four-wheel drive
and delivery van.
The difference in power is evident here.
To protect Junior's castle,
the monster wreaks havoc!
It's three in a row for Muto!
They're so weak!
The Lincoln is so strong.
Three cars left, right?
The champion Lincoln wins three in a row.
Hamada only has three cars left.
SENTOSHA
5 vs 3
A grand battle
between battle cars.
This battle will conclude
when one army
has no battle cars remaining.
Your turn, Juichi.
Let's go.
It's gotta be you.
What's our strategy?
Can you start really quickly and go around
to his driver's side?
I see.
We couldn't do anything last time,
when we waited for him to attack.
Right.
We have to make a move.
So we go around to the driver's side?
That's the left side, right?
So, I go forward...
I go left then go around to the right.
I see.
It was impossible.
Yeah, we know.
I was watching him...
He had a smile on his face when
he was driving straight at me.
I tried to avoid him
but there was nothing I could do.
It was hopeless.
He came slowly at me, laughing.
It's impossible.
I'll try to avoid him as much as possible.
Right.
I'll give it a good go.
Good luck!
Nissan Skyline
New car price 3.1 million yen
The best driver in a thousand years
according to himself,
Juichi Wakisaka.
Engine 2.5L I6 DOHC / 200 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1400kg
His battle car is a Nissan Skyline
with bamboo-spear mufflers,
it's a car modified to suit hooligans
from Chiba and Ibaraki.
The difference in weight
between the Skyline
and the Navigator is 1,100 kilograms.
Nissan Skyline
(Hamada's army, 1400kg, 200 hp)
Lincoln Navigator
(Junior's army, 2500kg, 304 hp)
Junior's army's champion,
the Lincoln Navigator, keeps picking off
the battle cars from Hamada's army
one by one.
The next driver, Juichi Wakisaka,
is one we have high expectations from.
There's not much I can do
The best driver in a thousand years
(according to himself) - Juichi Wakisaka
if he catches me from the side.
I can't help it.
Here's Muto in his Lincoln Navigator.
Look at him.
He looks very much like
a sumo wrestling champion.
The unbeatable pro wrestling master
Keiji Muto
I'll make it a good battle.
He does look confident, Juichi Wakisaka.
Mr. Hamada?
Yes?
The Lincoln is really big!
Of course, we knew that.
We've been saying how cute you are,
Mr. Muto.
Really?
Did Akina say that, too?
No, not Akina.
She didn't?
Akina is the only one who hasn't.
It's just Akina.
Only Akina? That's a shock.
-Yeah!
Muto has just been sitting in his car.
Yup.
He just needs to step on
the accelerator a little, and that's it.
Yup.
There's not much damage
to his knee either.
Juichi is planning to feint
towards the left,
then go around to the right
and attack the side of the Lincoln.
Can Juichi defeat the champion by showing
us his technique as a race car driver?
In this Sumo Death round,
the self-proclaimed
once-in-a-thousand-years driver
will take on the pro wrestling master.
-Here we go!
-Come on.
Show us your technique!
They're ready.
Stare off.
All right!
Ready...
Fight!
Juichi Wakisaka feints left as planned,
then he goes around to the right.
He has managed to get beside Muto,
as planned.
He's good!
He's done well!
What does he do now?
Juichi is right beside Muto.
Once in this position,
Muto is unable to attack.
Hey, Shigekazu! What do I do now?
What should he do?
Is Muto panicking a little?
Muto is panicking a bit.
Juichi Wakisaka is starting
to control this match.
Look out, look out!
When Muto makes a move,
Juichi also moves to run parallel to Muto.
Muto can't escape from this position.
It's looking good...
It's good.
There is no escape in sight for Muto.
It's really impressive to watch.
Juichi Wakisaka shows us
his technique right here.
Good.
Muto is forced to make a move.
And again,
Juichi positions himself to the side.
Look out!
Juichi is beside Muto.
He is trying to frustrate Muto. Wait!
Will he take Juichi from the side?
No! That's great driving!
Juichi reverses to the other side.
Magnificent!
Wow, he avoided that well.
Yeah.
Juichi Wakisaka is frustrating
the champion, Muto.
What does he do now? He reverses again.
The wheel spins.
Muto crashes into him from the side!
Juichi's in trouble!
His goggles are falling off.
Look out!
Reverse, reverse!
Come on!
Go, go!
Muto, the champion,
is now in a winning position.
From this position he pushes Juichi
out of bounds!
WIN Lincoln (frontal force out) - Skyline
Muto wins four in a row!
Junior's army wins.
Yeah!
So close!
Even though he tried so hard!
Well done, Mr. Muto!
Yes! I won.
Magnificent!
An amazing performance by Muto.
Wakisaka competed well,
but he couldn't overcome the champion.
SENTOSHA
Fight!
In the beginning,
Juichi feints left as expected
and positions himself right beside
the Lincoln's driver's side.
This seemed to frustrate Muto a lot.
Juichi was able to show us his technique
as a race car driver.
Here, it seemed Muto would take him
from the side,
but Juichi showed us his stuff.
From the side-by-side position,
Juichi couldn't move quickly enough
due to the wheel spinning,
and from then on, it was all Muto.
He didn't relinquish his advantage
and claimed victory.
Is he going to annihilate Hamada's army
one by one?
Muto wins four in a row!
We just can't attack him.
That's right.
Muto, you're amazing!
Come on!
It's because the car is amazing.
Mr. Muto is, too!
Hamada's army is on the verge of defeat.
Only two cars left.
SENTOSHA
5 vs 2
But the pervert barbarian
doesn't give up so easily.
Hamada goes for unusual tactics.
What if there were two of our cars?
What do you think?
-I see.
-It might work.
Right?
It will take away his concentration.
We'll send out our last two
for this match.
Can you still drive?
No problem.
We'll have Juichi and Seiji.
Seiji, you take the other car.
Me?
Let's go with two cars in the last match.
They're the strongest pair.
Excuse me.
Hey!
Junior's army?
We only have two cars left
and we can't really compete with
just one car,
so can we please fight with two cars?
What kind of way to ask
for a favor is that?
That's not good enough.
Right.
You're asking us
like it's only a suggestion.
Yeah.
I'm asking you nicely. Please.
How do you feel about that?
What?
You're asking us
while you're sitting down?
Look at him.
We're sorry to make you do this, master.
I represent all of us to say...
Please...
Please let us compete with
two cars in the final match!
We decline!
Come on!
Hey!
Our master is asking you!
All right, all right!
Okay, okay!
Okay?
Thank you very much!
All right!
We're sorry, master!
With a weight of 2.5 tons,
the invincible monster,
the Lincoln Navigator advances.
The two cars competing
from Hamada's army are...
New car price 8 million yen
Engine 4.3L V8 DOHC / 280 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1800kg
The Toyota Celsior, total weight 1.8 tons.
New car price approx. 4.8 million yen
Engine 2.3L I4 D HC Super Charger / 197 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1380 kg
Mercedes-Benz SLK Kompressor,
total weight 1.4 tons.
In the last round,
Hamada's army will compete with two cars
against Muto, the ultimate champion
from Junior's army.
Here are the battle cars
that lost their lives
during this grand battle at Mount Fuji.
War is such a cruel thing.
One army will claim victory
atop the sacrifices they made.
I'm going to attack
right from the beginning.
Here's the Chihara Family's mad dog,
Seiji Chihara.
Seiji Chihara's record today has been
impeccable, winning all three match ups.
Wow, look how close Seiji is!
Seiji won!
Round 1, stop at the very last moment
Win
Yeah!
Round 2, The Road to Hell - Win
The battle cars are ferociously jostling
for position.
Oh, the car has spun around!
It hit Fujimoto!
And here, Seiji completes the race.
Seiji from Hamada's army
has claimed victory!
Fly, Fairlady Z!
Whoa! That was amazing!
Round 3, Romantic Flight - Win
He bounces off the cushioning cars
and gains more distance!
Could the Chihara family's mad dog,
Seiji Chihara, bring about a miracle?
Are you okay, Mr. Muto?
I'm good. When I win,
can we organize a swingers party
with me and my wife
and Shoji and his wife?
He's just spouting crazy stuff now.
Can you organize a swingers party
if he wins?
Yeah!
He's joking right?
Well, Shoji said yes!
Who's getting in that car opposite Muto?
Seiji, at the moment.
Then, Seiji, use your headlights.
Put your headlights on high beam.
Blind him, okay?
That's a good idea.
On high beam.
Good tactics.
Take his eyes out.
That's good.
But that Mercedes is so small.
If Muto goes for Seiji first,
Seiji will fall and even if you attack him
from the side, it wouldn't move at all.
Yeah, we were just talking about that.
Right?
You put your headlights on high beam,
it will blind him,
so he probably won't move.
Yeah.
Then, how about we put the Mercedes
opposite the Lincoln
then I take him from the side?
I see.
Then I'll put my headlights on high beam.
Let's do that.
Yes.
Let's swap the positions of the two cars.
Right.
As expected, the pervert barbarian
is being his deceitful self.
As you can see, they are up to something.
They are swapping their cars around.
They've moved that car in front of me.
Junior!
Yes!
It's just a suggestion,
how about we make this the final battle?
The army that wins this match
will win the battle.
What?
Can you not count
the number of cars?
How many cars do you think we have?
We could run a secondhand car dealership
over here.
We'd just like to get the battle
over and done with.
No matter how it goes,
I can't see us losing this match.
Yeah.
Then it's no problem, right?
Yes, we'll accept!
Then it's the last match!
Everything will be decided here.
The Mercedes is so small.
I'm coming, Miki!
Is he really trying to sleep with my wife?
The car opposite the Lincoln
has its headlights on high beam.
It's Juichi Wakisaka.
On Muto's right is Seiji
in the black Celsior.
He's flashing his headlights.
The undefeated champion
from Junior's army, Muto.
Come on!
Let's see a complete victory!
The swingers party is coming up.
They've all got high beams on.
Trying to blind each other,
so they can't move freely.
That's right.
Can Junior's army
overcome Hamada's tactics?
Stare-off.
This is the final battle.
They've all got high beams on!
Ready!
Fight!
Here they go. Muto goes for Seiji!
Juichi's Mercedes pushes
against Muto's car.
But the Mercedes is not powerful enough
to move the Lincoln.
Push, push!
Take him from the side!
In the meantime, where is Seiji?
Seiji and Juichi seem to be
in each other's way.
It's hard for him to take a direct hit.
The man with a full beam
in his face is Juichi.
He gives instructions to Seiji
to come around.
Take him from the side!
And here's Seiji's Celsior!
Even Muto must be concerned
about having to counter two cars.
But his car is so much more powerful.
The Lincoln Navigator.
That's so dangerous!
It's only a little further.
Go, go!
Now, it looks like he's going to deal
with Juichi's Mercedes first.
Its wheels are spinning like crazy!
Just a bit more!
Take him from the side!
Go! Go!
Will he go out of bounds?
But now Seiji attacks him from this side!
Seiji smashes him from behind!
Seiji has hit Muto in the rear wheels.
The suspension's broken!
The back wheels are gone!
All right!
Come on!
You're doing great, Seiji!
Seiji hits him again!
The mad dog strikes!
The wheel has fallen off!
With the wheel removed,
the chassis has touched the ground.
WIN Mercedes & Celsior (outside leg trip)
Lincoln
This means Muto is defeated!
Hamada's army wins.
Yes!
Yeah!
This was a great battle!
We won because Muto's wheel fell off.
Look at that!
What happened?
Hamada's army wins.
All right!
Wow, they won by wrecking Muto's car!
They have taken Junior's castle!
SENTOSHA
Here it is.
Seiji, who betrayed his own brother,
Junior, to join Hamada's army
shows us his mad dog qualities.
Right here!
Seiji cuts off Muto's leg!
And in that moment, the battle was over.
It's like Japan defeated the U.S.
Yeah!
You were great!
Amazing!
Fantastic!
You were great out there!
Hey, Junior's army!
Hey!
After coming this far,
a wheel falls off?
Was it the back wheel?
Yeah, the rear wheel.
It's not even the front wheel.
Yeah, the back wheel.
Hamada's army is victorious
in this great battle.
The losing army must sacrifice
one of their foot soldiers.
That is the unbreakable rule
of battle cars.
What's going on?
I can't move an inch!
Am I being sacrificed?
Am I going to die?
Muto, die!
No!
Boom.
That's so hot!
It's so hot!
Muto's dead now.
Dead indeed.
Keiji Muto from Junior's army
died in battle.
He was 54.
The remaining soldiers will be
made to live in disgrace.
Who knew that the tire would fall off?
Damn it!
The cowards only aimed at the feet.
They only aimed at the feet.
So embarrassing.
They've got some heavy pieces of stone
on their laps.
Stop it.
What's this?
They're getting pelted with stones.
Oh, no, I'd hate that.
I feel so humiliated.
Please stop!
Damn it!
That's terrible.
Stop it!
Fujimoto's getting peed on!
I will never forget this
for the rest of my life!
Never!
Throw some more!
Why just me?
The names of these heroes
were inscribed at the bottom
of Mount Fuji.
Hamada's army wins Sentosha
SENTOSHA: Battle Wheels