The following program was produced with
the utmost consideration toward safety
and features dangerous activities which
were supervised by stunt professionals.
Do not attempt to reenact any
of the activities performed.
You can hardly see anything
on this dusty road.
Akina's right behind her!
It's tail to nose!
They're actually touching!
Akina's pushing her!
There's another explosion!
Fujimoto is terrified!
The battle cars are ferociously jostling
for position.
He can't stop. He can't stop!
Is he okay?
The car is on its roof! Is Sata okay?
Sixth Battle
"Road to Hell." Three more matches to go.
At the moment,
Junior's army is leading by six points.
It's your turn, Shoji.
Okay.
I'm off.
See you soon!
Come on, Shoji!
Iwahashi, you go hard, okay?
I'll go all out!
Go and burn him down!
Burn them to a crisp!
I'll get to the front and...
I'll definitely get to the front and...
Then what?
You were just repeating yourself.
I'll get to the front and...
You said it again.
He's gonna dash and run.
Alfa Romeo Alfa GT
New car price approx. 5.4 million yen
The reckless man who often shouts out
his wife's name, Tomoharu Shoji.
This battle car
is an Alfa Romeo Alfa GT.
Engine 2L I4 DOHC / 166 hp / FF /
Semi-Automatic / Weight 1480kg
Honda Crossroad
New car price 2.9 million yen
The uncontrollable hitman,
Yoshimasa Iwahashi.
His battle car is his own car riddled
with family memories,
the Honda Crossroad four-wheel drive.
Engine 1.8L SOHC / 140 hp / 4WD /
Weight 1480kg
On this "Road to Hell," many battle cars
have already sustained extensive damage.
In the next race, that one man
will line up in his black Crossroad.
You're planning on going home
in a hired car today, right?
No, I'm going to drive this home!
I don't know about that.
Of course I'll go back in that!
Oh, I don't know.
Seriously, it's a car riddled
with family memories.
I'll get away quickly.
You'll run?
I'll run and not look back.
Your airbags will probably be deployed.
No way...
Show me your four-wheel drive qualities!
Watch those airbags.
Hey, Iwahashi.
Yes.
What's your strategy?
My strategy?
Yes.
I'm thinking shoot out
and speed like hell. Is that okay?
I see.
If that's your plan, that's fine.
But you have to win, okay?
Yes. It may sound stupid,
but I want to go home
in a car that's in pristine condition.
I'll run and won't look back.
It will also depend on how your opponent,
Shoji, decides to go about it.
The reckless man who often shouts out
his wife's name - Tomoharu Shoji
But this Alfa Romeo is...
If I can get in front, it's in the bag.
The uncontrollable hitman
Yoshimasa Iwahashi
In the last round,
I had some issues with the clutch.
It felt like it was getting stuck.
But I've gotten used to it now,
so it's fine.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Are you really okay?
-I'm perfectly fine!
Bad luck for Shoji. The camera
that films his face is inoperable.
Is the clutch okay?
The clutch is okay!
The car and the clutch are fine?
The clutch is okay, all is good!
Tomoharu Shoji (Alfa Romeo Alfa GT)
vs Yoshimasa Iwahashi (Honda Crossroad)
Iwahashi's black Crossroad
is a four-wheel drive car,
which handles off-road tracks really well.
By comparison, Shoji's red Alfa Romeo
is a sports car.
Bad luck for Iwahashi - the camera
that films his face is again inoperable
You would be tempted to think
that the four-wheel drive will have
a distinct advantage on this sandy track.
Can Shoji overcome this
by putting in more power?
Three...
Go!
Two... One...
Here's the start. Shoji shot out in front.
He's in front!
Shoji has taken the front position
and Iwahashi is on his trail
in his black Crossroad.
In the cloud of dust, they...
Oh, they've touched.
Iwahashi has bumped the back
of Shoji's vehicle.
He's gone on the attack!
Good boy! Keep it up!
Is he okay? Iwahashi has stopped.
The Crossroad has stopped.
In the meantime,
Shoji opens up a big lead.
He's making this count!
Iwahashi's Crossroad is finally back
on the move.
Keep going!
We're onto the angled bank area.
We can see it in the back.
The black body of the Crossroad.
It's hard to control a vehicle
in this slippery area.
Wow, is he all right there?
Iwahashi nearly went off-track,
but he somehow managed
to get back on course.
Iwahashi is right behind Shoji now.
He bumps Shoji in the rear again!
Iwahashi is on the offensive!
He is bumping into him from behind.
He's bumping into him!
He is attacking from behind. Whoa!
He's mounting the side of Shoji's car!
I wonder if Shoji is okay.
Get it!
Is Shoji okay?
Iwahashi drove all the way on top
of the driver's side of Shoji's car!
He's on the move.
He drove all over Shoji!
He's all over him!
Go!
Iwahashi's nuts!
Shoji's okay, he's on the move now.
And Iwahashi crashes into him
from behind again!
Shoji's facing the wrong way now.
And amongst all the explosions,
Iwahashi shoots in front. That's amazing!
He's uncontrollable!
He's the uncontrollable hitman, Iwahashi.
He has come out of it on top!
Look out! He has lost control
Iwahashi somehow gets back on track.
Iwahashi's going all out!
He doesn't care whether the car
gets damaged or not.
He crosses the finish line now!
And Shoji's car is nowhere to be seen.
WINNER
Yoshimasa Iwahashi - 1m24s
We've won!
We've won! But that was so dangerous!
You look so surprised!
Here comes Shoji. Is he okay?
He is furious! He crosses the finish line,
but he's very angry.
Shoji, are you okay?
Yoshimasa Iwahashi - 1m24s - +10p
Tomoharu Shoji - 1m36s
Damn it!
You scared everyone! Hey!
You scared the hell out of everyone!
SENTOSHA
Let's have a look at the replay.
Iwahashi had been driving defensively
up to this point.
Starting here, however,
he went completely out of control.
Iwahashi was on the attack!
And look at this...
He drives up the side of Shoji's car.
He mounts Shoji's car doggy style!
Iwahashi from Hamada's army
has completely come alive!
So scary!
This is battle car racing!
SENTOSHA
Hey! You scared the living daylights out
of everyone!
Are you okay?
It was so dangerous!
Your car nearly crashed through
the driver's side window!
Hey!
I thought I was going around you,
but I was actually driving over you.
-I'm sorry!
-It was terrifying!
Your front wheel came through my window!
Good job!
Nice!
-Amazing.
-Yes!
Amazing.
It had better four-wheel drive qualities
than I thought!
That's good!
It did better than I expected.
All right!
Congrats!
It was more of a four-wheel drive
than I thought it was.
-You did great!
-You were great!
I got so excited, I was in the zone.
I see.
I thought, "I don't care if I die."
You didn't care if you died?
You were on the attack.
You were on top of his car!
I was on top of him, and apparently,
my front tire came through his window.
He was really angry with me.
It was just one front wheel, right?
If it happens again,
push it out from the inside.
Yeah, just push it out.
Hamada's army - 24 points
Junior's army - 20 points
Hamada's army takes the lead again.
And finally, the human explosion machine
enters the "Road to Hell."
Seventh Battle
It's your turn now, Mr. Ozawa.
Good luck!
Let's go.
Don't you lose.
Can I throw some explosives?
No?
You can!
I can, right? Okay!
Let's go, Mr. Muto!
We're still behind by four points.
Can I drive nice and steady? Real steady.
I have a gold driver's license.
I've never had an accident
or any infringements.
You can drive safely if you like.
Just for a change.
It will be different.
Just once!
Lincoln Navigator
New car price 10 million yen
The unbeatable pro wrestling master,
Keiji Muto.
His battle car is a top class SUV,
the Lincoln Navigator.
Engine 5.4L V8DOHC / 304 hp / AWD /
AT / Weight 2500kg
Toyota Century
New car price approx. 12 million yen
The man with a face that could kill,
Hitoshi Ozawa.
His battle car is the luxury saloon car,
the Toyota Century.
Engine 5L V12 DOHC / 280 hp / FR / AT /
Weight 2000kg
Junior's army will want to make up for
that four-point difference.
But now, here comes the man
who threw a live grenade
at the opposition in the last round.
The man with a face that could kill.
The man with a face that could kill
Hitoshi Ozawa
Here's Ozawa.
He's got something in his hands.
He's got something.
Here we go.
I gotta pummel that Lincoln.
The unbeatable pro wrestling master
Keiji Muto
Here's Muto from Junior's army.
And again,
he is slowly transported to his Lincoln
on the back of a utility truck.
That looks a bit sad, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Looks like he's being taken out
with the trash.
Like he's being thrown away.
Should we add some sad background music?
Yeah.
Let's have a competition on who can choose
the saddest music to go with that scene.
And here's Ozawa.
Oh, he's got a grenade in his hand again!
How's it going, Mr. Muto?
I'm going to drive safely this time.
Yeah?
I think you've filmed
enough dangerous scenes already.
Right.
Let's race like adults.
It looks like he got in the car
with the grenade.
Is Muto aware of that?
Hitoshi Ozawa (Toyota Century)
vs Keiji Muto (Lincoln Navigator)
The battle is about to start
between Japan's top executive-class car
and America's giant monster SUV.
Let's go, Mr. Ozawa.
Okay.
Let's go!
Three... Two...
The engine power
is basically the same for both cars.
The weight is two tons for the Century,
compared to 2.5 tons for the Lincoln.
How will the 500 kilogram difference
affect the outcome of the race?
Here they go!
Ozawa goes to the front.
That's so dangerous! Ozawa!
Ozawa goes to the front
That's so dangerous! Ozawa! Is Ozawa okay?
Oh, my God!
Ozawa cuts loose right from the start!
Wow, they've already bumped into
each other.
The Lincoln Navigator and the Century
have already made contact.
Ozawa reached back.
He's holding something in his left hand.
He's holding a grenade in his left hand!
He's driving one-handed
while he carries a grenade
in his other hand.
He's going wild. Amazing.
They can't see anything in the back now.
Look at this!
No one can see through this cloud of dust!
In this cloud of dust...
Wow, he continues to drive one-handed!
If you consider this, his driving skills
are very impressive.
But it's Muto who is currently
in the lead.
But here comes Ozawa.
Trying to control the unruly Century.
Here comes the Century!
He's right on Muto's tail.
Wait, what happened?
What just happened?
This is the view from the car.
It exploded!
The grenade just exploded in the car!
It exploded next to Ozawa! Is he okay?
Is Ozawa okay?
He's still driving!
Amazingly, Ozawa is still driving
even though a grenade just exploded
in his car!
Wow, it doesn't worry him at all!
How frightening!
He's the human explosive!
Here they start colliding with
each other again.
The front of the Century has sustained
a lot of damage.
Go!
Ozawa doesn't seem to mind that.
Wait, wait!
He's colliding with
all sorts of things now. Very dangerous!
Stay away from that man! He is dangerous!
Wow, Ozawa's wrecking everything in sight.
Hurry up!
Hurry!
Ozawa, you idiot!
Now, can Muto take advantage of this
and reach the finish line first?
Is Ozawa going to come storming back?
Oh, there's another explosion!
That's hot!
Here he comes from behind.
He's going wild again!
He hits Muto from behind again!
It's so hot!
Muto keeps saying that it's hot!
Look out, look out!
The giant rock hits him!
But the Lincoln Navigator is sturdy.
And here comes Ozawa again from behind!
But Muto finishes first!
And Ozawa follows him to the finish.
The winner is Junior's army!
WINNER
Keiji Muto - 1m36s
Keiji Muto - 1m36s - +2p
Hitoshi Ozawa - 1m38s
That was so hot!
Yeah, Muto!
The fire was so hot!
Muto!
How did it go?
It went well. I drove nice and steady.
-It went well.
-Yeah.
-That car's power was really amazing!
-Right.
SENTOSHA
Go!
Let's have a look at the replay.
It was already an eventful start
to the race.
Here!
See Ozawa fly!
He is nearly sideways there.
He has amazing driving skills
to be able to keep control of that car.
Well, Ozawa is known
to do his own stunts in movies.
And here Ozawa looms from behind,
trying to keep control of his Century.
It was around here
that a grenade exploded in Ozawa's car.
Right there!
This is the moment.
Right here.
Amazingly, Ozawa keeps driving
even after being blinded
from the smoke from the explosion.
Terrific driving there.
While Muto's Lincoln barely shows
any signs of damage,
Ozawa's Century shows extensive damage
to the radiator and suspension.
It's close to breaking down.
There's another collision!
This is a painful defeat
for Hamada's army.
Well done.
I tried pretty hard.
You did well.
You did your best.
I was trying to throw a grenade,
but it exploded in my hand.
Is your hand okay?
I'm fine.
You don't need to take grenades with you!
Why were you carrying it with you?
It exploded in your hand?
I was trying to throw it.
Then the car spun, so it exploded
while I was trying to regain control.
The car filled with smoke!
Look, my sunglasses are dirty!
So that's why they got dirty.
Right.
All things considered, you did great.
Those marks on your clothes
are from the grenade?
It's not from the dust!
It's from the grenade!
Hamada's army - 24 points
Junior's army - 22 points
With the final match remaining,
Hamada's army is leading by two points.
For Junior's army to make a comeback,
they must win the final match
by at least three seconds.
Last Battle
Here we go, Mr. Harada.
Yes.
The time has come.
Right.
The scene is set.
Yes.
Let's finish up by winning the last race.
-Go for it.
-Yes.
Let's go!
It's all on you now.
Let's go, ETC!
I'm Mr. ETC!
Yeah!
Audi Allroad Quattro 2.7t
New car price approx. 8.6 million yen
The hero who makes your blood curdle,
Ryuji Harada.
His battle car is an Audi Allroad Quattro.
Engine 3.2L V6 DOHC Twin Turbo / 255 hp /
4WD / AT / Weight 1860kg
Toyota Corolla Van
New car price 1.5 million yen
Resurrected after ten years of silence,
the Golden Boy,
Keiichi Yamamoto.
His battle car is the Toyota Corolla Van.
Engine 1.3L I4 DOHC / 82 hp / FF / 4MT / Weight 930kg
Compared to the Audi,
a true four-wheel drive
with a 255-horsepower twin-turbo engine,
the Toyota Corolla is a manual car
with only an 82 horsepower engine.
Will this even be a contest?
Finally, the last battle
on the "Road to Hell" has arrived.
Hamada's army has a lead of two points,
which only equates to two seconds.
Resurrected after ten years of silence,
the Golden Boy - Keiichi Yamamoto
Here's Yamamoto.
He is still disheartened from getting
his own Volkswagen Beetle
trashed by Sata earlier.
I guess he's wondering
how he's going to get home.
SENTOSHA
Here's the replay of the incident.
Sata was driving Yamamoto's car,
given to the program
by his comedy partner Kato,
and he couldn't turn the slippery corner
and went straight into the dirt wall.
The car overturned.
A substantial amount of the loan
on the car had still not been paid off.
The Beetle is now destined
for the scrap heap.
Has Yamamoto recovered from the shock yet?
SENTOSHA
If you look closely,
that man's eyes look ready to kill.
If you look closely?
Yes.
The hero who makes your blood curdle
Ryuji Harada
Have a look at that.
That's where the crash happened.
Scene of the Beetle's accident
How it ended up there, I will never know.
Yeah, I know.
Ryuji Harada (Audi Allroad Quattro)
vs Keiichi Yamamoto (Toyota Corolla Van)
We're massively disadvantaged
with the car.
That's right.
But Yamamoto will do it for us.
It's kind of...
He'll do it?
He will.
Harada from Junior's army
gets into the black Audi.
Here's Yamamoto.
What's that?
There's something that looks like
a black pipe on the right side of the car.
Mr. Harada.
Yes.
You need to win by three seconds.
What?
We'll win if you can win
by more than three seconds.
Three seconds.
-I can run and not look back?
-Yes.
Let's win by a big margin.
Be careful of the dust cloud, okay?
Okay.
It's all or nothing. Please let us win.
Here we go, Yamamoto.
Yes!
Let's go.
Good luck.
Three... Two... One...
Go!
Here they go.
From the outset, Harada from Junior's army
has gone full speed.
If Harada can finish ahead
by at least three seconds,
Junior's army can make a comeback
and win this round.
Harada accelerates here
to head straight to the finish line.
By comparison, Yamamoto
in the delivery van cannot keep pace.
He's so slow.
The gap is less than three seconds
at this point.
He needs a bit more.
It's not three seconds yet.
Is Yamamoto still disheartened from seeing
his beloved Beetle destroyed?
Is the gap closing?
Yamamoto seems to be catching up a little.
Here's Harada.
From the bank,
they come up to the slippery area.
They need to be careful here.
This is where Yamamoto's Beetle
met its terrible fate.
What's that? Something shot out
from the black pipe!
And there's an explosion!
Same thing has happened to Yamamoto.
It's mud! A mud ball is being shot out
from the pipe!
It must have confused Harada,
he has slowed down a little.
Yamamoto in the delivery van
has closed the gap.
And look at the fire!
Yamamoto really managed to catch up!
With his Beetle having been destroyed,
he's giving a great performance
in the delivery van!
He's chasing the back of the Audi,
waiting to pounce!
All right!
Yes! Yes!
Still less than three seconds.
Even if Yamamoto loses,
if he follows Harada like this...
It's a really good race!
Oh, he made a move!
Yamamoto from Hamada's army is in front!
An amazing performance from Yamamoto!
Look at that concentration.
What happened to Yamamoto!?
And he crosses the finish line!
WINNER
Keiichi Yamamoto - 1m01s
Yamamoto from Hamada's army
has won the race!
The winner is Hamada's army.
This means that in this moment,
Hamada's army has won
the "Road to Hell" round.
Keiichi Yamamoto - 1m01s - +5p
Ryuji Harada - 1m06s
Second round - Hamada's army wins
So cool!
Amazing!
He was amazing!
No!
Damn!
No way!
Something just...
Something just popped out of there!
But I won!
I won!
SENTOSHA
Here's the replay.
There were mud ball guns
set up in both of their cars!
Compared to Yamamoto's delivery van
with much less power,
Harada's Audi was a four-wheel drive
suited to driving on off-road tracks.
The difference in quality
between these cars was evident.
However, as we will see, here,
Yamamoto passes Harada on the inside!
Yamamoto took his chance when Harada
went wide in that corner.
An amazing performance by Yamamoto!
Hamada's army claims victory
in the "Road to Hell" round.
The two armies are now head-to-head
with a win and a loss each.
Hey, Junior!
-Yeah?
-Give us one of your cars.
Come on.
We don't want to.
Then...
We'll give you back this crap car
that you gave us.
We'll give you back Katsumata's car.
We should take it.
Really?
-It hasn't been damaged yet.
-It's really quick, too.
It was so close.
It was really close.
We'll lose the Fairlady Z as well.
We'll take the Fairlady Z
as the reincarnation of the Beetle.
Let's take good care of it.
That's right.
Right.
Can I drive it home today?
I don't have an electronic toll card
anymore, though.
I won't take the tollways.
I'll take the ordinary route
without tolls.
Just pay the toll in cash!
Yeah, just use cash!
I'd like to pay all toll charges
with my ETC card.
Just pay cash!
Although Yamamoto's Volkswagen Beetle
is headed to the scrap heap,
Hamada's army was able to claim victory
on the "Road to Hell."
The devious Hamada celebrates his victory,
just for a little while.
Yippee!
The army of zombies that survives
even after a grenade explosion.
The tables have been turned.
Those barbarians are unbelievable!
How could anyone survive
a grenade exploding in their car?
Forward! Let's go!
We'll defeat them! It's now or never!
The impregnable Junior Castle.
Is it about to be taken?
Junior's Army - Mercedes-Benz Kompressor, Volvo V70,
Jaguar XJ Executive (retired), BMW 330i
Junior's army had the Fairlady Z
they won in Round 1
taken away from them
with their loss in Round 2.
In addition, the Jaguar Executive
had to be retired
due to the damage sustained in Round 2.
Now they have seven battle cars remaining.
Mercedes-Benz S320, Alfa Romeo Alfa GT,
Lincoln Navigator, Audi Allroad Quattro
Hamada's Army - Nissan Fuga, Toyota Celsior,
Nissan Fairlady Z, Nissan Skyline
As for Hamada's army,
the Volkswagen Beetle and the Century
were retired at the end of Round 2.
That leaves them with six battle cars.
The team with the most battle cars
in the final round
will have a distinct advantage
in the final battle.
Volkswagen Beetle (retired),
Nissan Laurel (removed),
Honda Crossroad, Toyota Century (retired),
Toyota Corolla Van
Will Chihara Junior
be able to protect his castle?
Or will Hamada,
the pervert barbarian from Osaka,
come and take Junior's castle?
You Really Might Die, round three.
Romantic Flight.
YOU REALLY MIGHT DIE, ROUND 3
ROMANTIC FLIGHT
This is a battle car
long jump competition.
The army that jumps further will win.
Any battle car that participates
in this round
will definitely be forced into retirement
due to the massive impact from the fall.
The run up to the jump is 30 meters.
The battle will be decided
by how far the cars are able to fly
after accelerating
off the top of the 150 centimeter ramp.
We're jumping this?
It's quite high here.
This is the most dangerous of all.
That's really high.
It is high.
Only pros can do it.
Who's going?
-Can I give you my opinion?
-Yes.
Don't you think we always do well
when Seiji goes first?
That's true.
Yes.
How about the leader competes
in this challenge?
The leader takes responsibility?
You're just trying to weasel out of it.
Imagine Mr. Hamada in lots
of safety gear going for that jump.
-He would be good at it.
-No way!
He would be great.
And it would look so funny
with your tiny little mustache.
No, no. I think Seiji is our man.
If Mr. Hamada wants me to do it,
I'd be very happy to have a go.
Hamada's army
Seiji Chihara
I think it helps that you got
a screw loose up there, too.
You knew?
He's not afraid of anything.
That's right.
I really need you to jump very far.
Why?
What is it?
Well...
You know how you're supposed
to jump off that ramp?
The closest car to the ramp is my car.
Really?
Don't worry about it.
You need to jump at least
further than my car.
You know my car is quite heavy
in comparison.
Yes.
It would make quite a dent.
If you can jump over my car, it's fine.
If you carry a lot of speed, it's fine.
The back of the car is undamaged.
At the moment, the rear is untouched.
It's unscathed.
Yeah.
It doesn't matter anymore,
as the front half is wrecked already.
It doesn't matter, but I don't want
to add to its suffering.
I guess.
Fujimoto, let's go!
No!
-Fujimoto!
-No way!
Why don't you want to do it?
I have my daughters to care for.
Please spare me from this.
Then Shoji.
I can't do it either.
Why?
I still have a mortgage to pay.
You know, you don't have to pay
the mortgage if you die, right?
-I'll get edited out if I die on the show.
-No, you won't.
Amazon will even show someone dying?
Sure, it'll be fine.
I can't do it. I've got kids, too.
How about Itakura?
My grandma told me not to do
anything too dangerous.
Is it the rule in your family?
-Is it an Itakura family motto?
-Yes...
-Don't...
-Do anything dangerous?
Yes, it's from my grandma.
It can't be helped then.
Then it's gotta be that guy.
What the hell are you doing, Mr. Harada?
Mr. Harada?
What's wrong?
He's trying to smell the airbag.
It really stinks.
What? It stinks?
We were going to get the person
who smelled the airbag
to do this challenge.
This was always the rule.
In that case, it's me then.
Right.
Junior's army
Ryuji Harada
Okay.
Please fly like a dragon.
Then I'll show you how a dragon flies!
All right!
It's decided then!
Audi Allroad Quattro 2.7t
New car price approx. 8.6 million yen
Representing Junior's army,
the hero who makes your blood curdle,
Ryuji Harada.
He'll go on a romantic flight
in the Audi Allroad Quattro.
Engine 3.2L V6 DOHC Twin Turbo / 255 hp / 4WD / AT / Weight 1860kg
Pretend that you're already in the car.
Could you do a test flight?
Go!
Jump!
Here we go! He jumped!
Mr. Harada, you need to be
more aerodynamic. Like this!
You need to retract the landing gear.
Go!
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
You won't be the one jumping.
The car is.
What are you doing?
-What are you doing?
-I'm fine now.
What are you going to find out
by running up like that?
It was a test run!
In this Romantic Flight round,
first on the runway is Junior's army.
each team will have
one representative who competes.
Junior's army, Ryuji Harada - Test run
This is Harada from Junior's army.
There is a ramp waiting
at the end of a 30-meter stretch.
We can see three cars
on the other side of the platform.
These cars will act as cushions
when the battle cars land.
If they weren't there, the battle cars
would need to absorb a lot of impact,
endangering the lives of the foot soldiers
competing in this round.
They will act as cushioning devices.
Oh, there's Yamamoto's Beetle.
Yamamoto's Beetle
that Sata managed to wreck.
This will be its final act.
It's looking good.
Good.
Good, good.
It's good. We want to give him a push.
Harada's Audi has a 3.2 liter
twin-turbo engine.
It is very, very powerful.
This is a long jump competition
using battle cars.
How much speed can they gain
after the start?
This will be an important factor
in this round.
The representative for Junior's army
is Harada.
We are nearly ready to start.
He needs to enter the platform straight.
It's really dangerous if he falls.
If I can't enter the jump straight,
is it better to brake?
Or is it better to keep going?
After the jump...
I think you can hit the brake
as soon as you've made the jump.
I mean, before the jump.
When you realize you're not straight
going up the ramp, what do you do?
Then you should adjust the steering wheel
to make sure that you're straight.
You're okay with that?
You're okay with that instruction?
Seriously.
It's not like you drive cars for a living.
How are you doing, Mr. Harada?
Yes, I'm ready to go now.
How are you? Are you scared?
I am scared, but...
It depends on if you can keep your foot
on the accelerator.
You need a lot of courage.
-You need to let off somewhere, too.
-Yeah, that's true.
If you let off,
you won't be able to jump as far.
I've lived 46 years
and experienced a lot of things.
I think this is a culmination
of all of that.
Wow.
-You're going to show it to us.
-That's great.
Mr. Harada.
-What are those?
-They're wings.
Wings?
So he can fly far.
I see.
Please present these to him, Junior.
-Here we go.
-Does it go on the door?
They go right next to the door handles.
Let's fly! Oh, it's attached.
It looks like it will fly very far!
It does, too.
-Mr. Harada!
-Yes.
We're wishing you luck!
-Good luck!
-We'll be watching!
Let's go!
Thank you!
This grand battle is taking place
in Susono near Mount Fuji
to decide who will reign supreme.
You Really Might Die, round three.
This round is called Romantic Flight.
Now the battle is about to commence
between two courageous foot soldiers
from both Junior's army and Hamada's army
to decide who can jump the longest
and who is the most courageous.
In this Romantic Flight round,
they will be risking their lives
in their battle cars.
First to compete
is Ryuji Harada from Junior's army
who was the only one
to put his hand up for his team.
Look at the wings on his car.
Can he fly?
Oh, the right wing just fell off!
The right wing came off.
Harada is completely unaware of this.
He is at maximum concentration.
Now he just needs to go full throttle!
Three... Two...
One...
Come on!
Go!
There he goes without his right wing.
He stomps hard on the accelerator!
He accelerates! Harada takes off!
What is the distance?
Is he okay?
How is he?
You're kidding!
Oh, my God!
The Beetle's okay?
The Beetle's okay.
Okay!
It was a good jump!
It didn't hit the Beetle.
SENTOSHA
Of course, the distance
that the cushioning cars moved
after the impact will not count.
The distance will be measured from
where the front of the battle car touched
the back of the second cushioning car.
Are you okay?
Mr. Harada, are you okay?
Ryuji? You really flew.
It was a good flight.
Amazing!
He's okay!
Are you okay?
-The impact was massive!
-Is he really okay?
You were great!
How was the impact?
It was massive.
That bad?
You'd think so.
The parked cars moved this far forward.
Nice flying!
That was amazing!
Nice!
Thank you very much.
The results are in
for Harada from Junior's army.
He flew 7 meters, 77 centimeters! Amazing!
Yeah!
Mr. Harada, you're amazing!
Thank you.
Seven meters? I thought it was
more than that. I see.
Amazing!
Seven meters?
That's crazy!
He jumped quite far.
Harada recorded an enormous jump
of 7.7 meters.
Can Hamada's army
surpass Harada's Romantic Flight?
Now, this is
Harada's Audi that performed
that great jump.
You can understand why, once you take
flight, the car is automatically retired.
This battle car literally risked its life
so that Junior's army could be victorious.
The battle car chosen by Seiji Chihara
from Hamada's army
is the Fairlady Z they reclaimed
in the last round.
New car price 3.5 million yen
Engine 3.5L V6 DOHC / 280 hp / FR / AT / Weight 1440kg
Although the car weighs only 1500 kg,
it's powered by a 3.5-liter engine.
Hamada's army, Seiji Chihara - Test run
The distance recorded by Harada
was 7.7 meters.
Seiji from Hamada's army
will be aiming to surpass that distance.
Should I drive more to this side?
Yes, like that.
He's veering to the left.
He is.
Seiji has a determined look on his face.
Oh, I see. The width of the platform
is quite narrow.
And Seiji is now driving
the Fairlady Z, not the Toyota Celsior
he was driving earlier.
Wow, it's narrow.
The ramp is just barely wide enough.
That's close.
He needs to reach this at top speed
then drive off the ramp and jump.
When you compare this Fairlady Z
and the Audi,
the engine power is the same, yet
the Fairlady Z is 400 kilograms lighter.
You can say that this car was made to
compete in this Romantic Flight round.
This car really is powerful!
Amazing!
You're good.
You're driving right in the middle now.
You're doing well.
I feel confident now.
That's great.
That's good.
Wow, look at that acceleration!
I've got it now.
Looks like he's got the hang of it now.
-That acceleration is amazing!
-It's amazing!
Yeah.
It accelerates so easily.
It's so scary.
Go on.
We'll put the wings on so it can fly.
Seiji, we'll put wings on, okay?
Thank you.
The members will be happy, right?
Of course.
I think this will jump really far.
Thanks.
Good luck!
Wow. He's so fearless.
To jump at that speed.
I think he'll jump real far.
Right?
He just needs to jump further
than the back of that second car.
Yeah.
Oh, it's the front.
He just needs to get on top of that car.
That's right.
He needs to go beyond that.
We'll win if he goes beyond this point.
That's amazing.
Stories about this great battle
between Hamada and Junior
at Susono near Mount Fuji
will be recorded for thousands of years.
Many battle cars have come and gone.
Seiji Chihara teamed up with Hamada,
the pervert barbarian from Osaka,
after he betrayed his own brother,
Chihara Junior.
Oh, Harada's Audi from before
is one of the cars acting
as cushions for Seiji.
Three...
Two...
One...
Harada's record was 7.7 meters.
Seiji's going for it!
Come on! Fly, Fairlady Z!
Whoa! That was amazing!
Yeah!
That was an astoundingly massive jump!
He did it!
Great!
That was great!
What?
That was so scary!
SENTOSHA
Let's have a look at the replay.
Seiji's Fairlady Z shows
an amazing acceleration here.
And here he jumps!
He's gone all the way beyond two
of the cushioning cars,
the Beetle and the Audi!
He's crashed into the third car.
That's so far!
You jumped so far!
That's amazing!
Awesome!
That was amazing!
That's amazing!
It was a great jump! Beautiful!
Absolutely beautiful!
This is a great car!
It really is a fantastic car!
So, Harada's record was 7.7 meters.
How did Seiji Chihara do?
Wow! 13 meters!
With that unbelievable jump,
he's won the Romantic Flight round!
Hamada's army wins Round 3
That was amazing!
Oh, wow.
I'm glad we won that car back before.
It's a great car.
It's off the charts.
Hamada's army wins two in a row.
The losing Junior's army must hand over
one of their battle cars to the victors.
You need to give us the Lincoln.
No, no.
We won by a massive margin!
I have no choice.
We'll give you Akina's Mercedes.
Mercedes Benz SLK230 Kompressor
Junior's army - Hamada's army
I'm sorry, I have to hand over
Akina's Mercedes.
What's wrong with you? Stop this, Junior!
They're giving us the little car.
You're giving us your smallest car.
It's the smallest one!
The grand car battle.
With Seiji's crazy big jump,
Hamada's army also won the third round.
Let's kill them off now!
We must take Junior Castle now! Fight!
Fight! It's now or never!
Junior's Army
Junior's army has now lost
the Mercedes-Benz Kompressor,
in addition to the Audi
that was retired after the last round.
They now have five battle cars remaining.
Volvo V70, BMW 330i, Mercedes-Benz S320,
Alfa Romeo Alfa GT, Lincoln Navigator
Hamada's Army
While Hamada's army did add the Mercedes
to their fleet,
the Fairlady Z had to be retired
after the last round.
They have six battle cars left.
Nissan Fuga, Toyota Celsior,
Nissan Skyline,
Honda Crossroad, Toyota Corolla Van,
Mercedes-Benz Kompressor
Muto in the Lincoln Navigator!
The first battle - Junior's army's victory
Now, they just need to hit the brakes!
Muto's stopped.
Ozawa crashed into the wall!
Did he even touch the brakes?
Yes!
Harada, wow, one centimeter!
I'll kill them all!
The second and third battle
Hamada's army's victory
The battle cars are ferociously jostling
for position.
Oh, the car has spun around!
Whoa!
He's mounting the side of Shoji's car!
Damn it!
Come on! Fly, Fairlady Z!
Whoa! That was amazing!
That was amazing!
Stay put! Protect the castle at all cost!
The last battle will be
a one-on-one sumo battle
between each team's remaining battle cars.
The army that annihilates the other army
will be victorious.
The door is getting pummeled.
Muto is going in for the kill!
He's going in for the kill!
Now he's armed himself with a bazooka!
Oh, it's getting smashed again.
The bazooka! Use the bazooka!
He is getting pushed out.
Will he lose to the power
of the four-wheel drive car?
SENTOSHA: Battle Wheels