Welcome to Wednesday Downtown!
Let's bring out our first presenter.
It's Teruyuki Tsuchida!
This time I've brought a theory concerning an influential figure from my agency.
So why from my agency?
Ohta Pro?
Yes, Ohta Productions.
Do you know who it is?
It could be Kuniko-san.
Ah yes. There's Yamada Kuniko-san.
Could be Dachou Club.
Ah, there's them.
Those guys aren't influential.
Not influential?
"Those guys" is inappropriate.
So, the person I want to present is this.
Ah, Tsuru-san?
It's Tsurutaro.
Oi!
It's Tsurutaro-san.
He's starting to look like driftwood.
So thin.
That's right.
That's scary...
So, this time I've brought a theory concerning Tsurutaro's body.
Tsurutaro Kataoka is the #1 entertainer at passing through tight spaces.
Would he be number 1?
Well, with how he is now, perhaps.
His body really is paper thin now.
And he does yoga, so he's flexible too.
I see.
If you put up him up against other thin people, he'd definitely get through small places.
No, but that's...
We looked for gaps that ordinary people wouldn't even dream of.
And these entertainers entered them so fast. This is groundbreaking footage.
I see.
Coming up, the entertainment world's emaciated all-stars passing-through-gaps showdown.
Then,
the theory that there's someone over 2 meters that's culturally inclined.
I'll protect you, Rion.
Kuro-chan's reality love project, Monster House episode 2.
Because I have Rion all to myself.
Translations: ShinobiSubs, WDT Project (Shion, Ekiben), CatZombies.  Timing: ShinobiSubs, KannibalKlown, GakiDave.
Assembly and QC: GakiDave
Is Kataoka Tsurutaro really the number one celebrity in the world at passing through tight spaces?
Celebrity passing-through-gaps decisive championship!
Let me introduce the contestants.
First, with a body fat ratio of 7.2% - literally skin and bones...
Yabe Taro-san!
He should be a good challenger.
Progressing away from selling her looks, working throughout the industry...
...a body that is fully-stacked, but scandalously skinny...
...it's Kato Sari-san!
She's thin but has a bust.
Quite the chest there...
This is quite the demerit, eh?
And the one taking her on...
The flat-chested skinny pole dancer Makino Suteteko.
Fatigued from all the mental associates, the "mental bag of bones"...
...from the comedy duo "Impulse", it's Itakura Toshiyuki!
You're pretty ripped, eh?
You've been working out, I see.
The touch of your hands, Tsurutaro-san...
...is freezing! Are you ok?
Cold, but I'm fine.
And last we have the king of getting in gaps...
...the skinny yoga master, Kataoka Tsurutaro!
He's really showing it off from the side!
It's the easiest to understand.
I don't really get your feelings of pride, though.
I mean, look.  It's like you're taking on homeless people.
They make their way to the first stage.
Here it is!
That's impossible!
This is so narrow!
The Level 1 stage gap is...
It can't be done!
...between Yamada-san's house and this restaurant.
That'd be scary!
An opening of just 24 cm.
Is this ok?
This looks too tight!
That's narrow!
It's pretty long, too, isn't it?
This is the first stage?
As you can see, if we take this issue box, and place it in the gap...
It's the same width.
The first challenger is...
...with a body mass of 41kg, Yabe Taro.
The gap the same width as a tissue box - can it be cleared?
I'm going for it!
I'm a little bit scared.
Ah...scary!
This is spooky!
I can't see anything around!
Ah, ah...I'm in!
OK!
The first stage is cleared!
Yabe-san, how was it?
It's better if you go through quickly.
Be quick about it, eh?
The next challenger is Makino Suteteko.
Here I go!
Ugh, this is scary!
I'm in!  I'm in!
My voice...my voice is echoing.
Even with walls on both sides she progresses on smoothly.
Yabe-san is waiting for me.
I did it!
I cleared it!
I'm happy for her.
Even though it has nothing to do with me.
There is a real sense of achievement.
Yes there is!
Next, with a bust of 105cm, Kato Sari.
I can't even get my head in.
Her hair is quite wide.
The bust is problematic.
Watch out!
She can only barely get in.
There is going to be friction on those nipples!
You've gotta be slim for this!
Although the rest fits in, her bust is making it difficult.
Amazing.
But even with her chest chafing against the wall...
...she is able to progress.
I did it!
Kato-san has cleared it.
After this is a succession of clears.
Then it is finally time for the master Tsurutaro to challenge it.
It's pretty intimidating when you see it right before you.
63 years of age and into piercings, the veteran senpai...
...makes his way into the gap.
The yoga master takes his extreme trained body and advances on...
Yogi Tsurutaro has cleared it.
It feels strangely satisfying to make it out, huh.
It's like being reborn.
So here we have level 2.
Where are we?
We're in Atami.
It's really necessary to come all the way here?
No, you see...
...if we hadn't come all the way to Atami, then...
And so we come to the second stage in Atami.
Here it is!
Wait wait wait...
...it's narrow and dirty!
Level 2 is situated between two restaurants...
...with a width of 17.5cm.
With a gap that small, it has never been cleaned.
A grimy condition.
Level 1 was the width of the box.
It won't even go in now.
It won't go in?
It won't fit at all.
Because of the pipe.
And thus first is our top contender, Yabe Taro.
There hasn't ever been anyone in here before now, right?
It appears that way.
I'm going for it!
This is tight!
It's tighter than you imagine in here.
It is seriously tight.
Can he get his
head through?
Watching this is making it hard to breathe.
After you get past the entrance it becomes easier...
or so he thought.
Is the wall rough?
Yes.
Not only that, but it's really dirty!
Eww!  What the hell?!
This is super gross!
The dust and grease has been accumulating for ages...
...making it a difficult fight.
It's pretty tight here.
Ah, it's dirty!
Yabe Taro somehow clears Level 2.
Next is Kato Sari with the giant rack.
My breasts are getting crushed.
They're getting smooshed.
He's really
checking her out!
Ah, I'm in!
And so, even with the chafed chest...
...Kato Sari manages to clear.
Even with the tight entrance gap...
...they all manage to clear the challenge.
And so they progress on to the third stage.
What the hell?
Here it is!
That can't be done.
Level three's hardest point is the opening - only 15cm wide.
Can they fit through the 15cm gap?
This is actually the exit.
The exit?
We have to come from that way?
This time the course is actually an L-shape.
An L-shape?
Entrance
Exit
This time the entrance and exit are not in a straight line...
...they are in an L-shape.
It won't fit at all.
What about lengthwise?
Lengthwise there is a 1-2cm gap.
This is a bit scary.
Even the yoga master is intimidated by Level 3.
What happens next?
Going down this part is no problem.
First to challenge is Makino.
There she is!
Up to this point is easy.
I can do it!
This is fine to here.
It's pretty wide there, huh?
It's the last part.
Then she arrives at the toughest hurdle.
It's only 15cm wide.
I'm so close yet so far!
Really...
...this might actually be impossible.
She is only able to get her head and legs out.
This looks like a joke.
I'm not joking!
This is really tight!
This looks tough.
Ah....crap crap crap...
I wanna get out!
I can't...
It's hitting my spine.
And so Makino falls at the Level 3 boss.
So frustrating...
I can't make it.
I'm so sad...
Next is Kato Sari.
Do you really think, when you look at this gap...
...even one of those great jugs is going to make it through there?
Wait a minute, did you say "jugs"?
It's been a long time since I've heard anyone say "jugs".
And so the big-jugs Kato-san arrives at the exit.
You can do it!
Your head is out!
Is this gonna be ok?!
Should I hold the camera?
This is a nice shot.
Kato clears getting her head out.
Next is the problematic jugs.
Wait, my belly button piercing is getting caught!
Your belly button ring?
I can't move from here.
It's impossible?
That's bad.
She looks like Hyokkorihan.
T/N: Hyokkorihan is a comedian who always appears on stage like this from behind a wall.
We will have to leave you here.
Can you get your chest out, then your hips?
My pelvis...or should I say...
Where are you stuck?
My belly button piercing hurts.
Your belly button piercing?
And so the staff assist.
Can you take off your mic?
Let's take off the mic.
Staff: But the piercing...
Staff: Hmm...
How did we end up like this?
What should we do?
I'm getting worried now!
Wait a sec...it's pulling tight.
We will have to get a saw and cut it.
I can't go back, either.
You can't go back any more?
An unfortunate circumstance forces her to give up on clearing it.
And after 15 minutes of trying...
...she is finally able to return.
And now the ace Yabe Taro steps up.
Here is it!
Ah, the hips are bad.
It's too tight.
You can make it!
But really...to end up trapped here forever...
That's dangerous.
It's dangerous.
Yes it is.
The risk of living here forever...
...but then...
If I go up...
By ascending the pole, the gap opens up slightly.
He changes his escape route.
It's a bit wider up there.
It opens up.
He did it!  He did it!
You did it!
Yabe Taro magnificently clears Level 3.
What are they celebrating? I don't get it.
You really are the ace!
Up! You have to go up!
Utilizing the newly discovered technique, the clears continue.
Magnificent!
You did great!
And last is the Yoga Master.
An unbelievable sight for someone who is over 60...
...he makes his way to the goal.
Here?
Kataoka Tsurutaro makes an elegant finish and clears Level 3.
And so these are the remaining three contestants for the final stage.
It's 10pm at night when they arrive to the final gap.
Here it is!
What the heck is this?!
How long is it?
Close to the area of Level 1...
...this is an even tighter 16cm gap.
Not only that, but the exit is also a demonic course.
The remaining contestants take on the final stage:
This mere 16cm opening.
First up to take the challenge...
Wait this is dangerous.
This is the entrance?
But unable to fit his head in the opening...
This is awful.
I didn't think this would be the hard part!
There's no way.
I can't fit in at all.
Unable to enter at all, he forfeits.
Yabe-san, please do your best!
I will go first and research the course!
Do your best, Taro-chan.
And so the next one to take it on is Yabe Taro.
Awaiting him at the exit are the skinny associates.
This is tight as heck!
So narrow!
This guy's amazing!
He's actually in it!
Here I go.
It's clean!
The walls...
The walls are so clean!
But the real challenge is the end.
I've finally arrived to the goal.
But here, blocking his way...
...the demon air conditioner heat exchanger.
Will he be able to overcome this beast?!
It's impossible.
Impossible?
It's impossible to pass.
Ouch!
This is killing me!  My shoulder!
You can make it if you climb up, can't you?
Am I allowed to?
He heads toward the space in the sky.
Ah, I can't do it.
Unable to move freely in the tight space, he reaches his limit.
He is unable to use his lifting power.
You can't bend your legs in a space like that.
It's impossible.
Give...I give up!
The top ace Yabe Taro reaches his limit and retires.
Finally the Yoga Master is up.
The expert of nauli aims to clear the final challenge!
T/N: Nauli is a yoga movement involving massaging the internal belly organs in a circular motion.
This part is only 8cm wide.
But here...my ribs are holding me back.
He slides in with zero effort.
What is he doing?!
He's over 60!
And then...
He should be able to do it, right?
He makes his move in going upwards.
And so, thanks to his years of expert training in yoga...
...he is able to move his body upwards, even in such a confined space.
Here comes the nauli.
Unbelievable!  He has conquered all of the courses!  Champion!
Kataoka Tsurutaro!
Tsurutaro clears the final course and confirms...
...he is the best at traversing tight gaps.
Give us a winning nauli!
That's an amazing nauli!
So, if you can nauli, you can clear anything.
He proved it true!
How was it?
That old man...
He is a veteran star of our company!
In a place I used to live in a few years back...
...it got burgled by someone, and they got in through a small gap.
It must have been that old git!
He must have known nauli.
Ah, I called him an "old git"...
He is an honorable senpai.
That nauli is something else!
I'm amazed he got out!
Everyone at the company wanted him to refuse, but...
It was better than I expected!
By the way, with the first location in Tsukishima. Downtown, you two...
Do you not remember?
Eh?
Actually, when you were filming "Downtown Now" out of the studio in Odaiba...
...when Tsurutaro came on as a guest...
...it was that store's gap.
The store on the right.
It's a coinincidence...
A coincidence.
So, on a Downtown program with Tsurotaro-san as a guest...
...if you change the staff, this is what the content turns into.
It's completely different.
Our next presenter is...
Oh, it's Daikichi!
Please welcome Hakata Daikichi!
Thank you for the introduction.
Now, I'd like to ask all of you a question.
Considering all of the people you know, including friends and the like...
...how tall is the tallest person you know? What would you say, Kawakita?
185 cm
A man?
Yes, a man.
Does that person play sports?
He plays basketball.
Ah, so he plays basketball.
What about you, Jinnai?
Well, it would have to be Koyabu, wouldn't it?
He's about...189 cm.
That guy...
No, well, wouldn't it be Onigiri?
Yeah, Onigiri, a younger comedian in Yoshimoto.
It's gotta be Onigiri, right?
A former volleyball player.
He's 190 and...
I found out that he is 193cm.
He's big, ain't he.
So this time, I've brought a tall person theory, which is...
There exists someone over 2m who is "culturally inclined."
Now what do I mean by "culturally inclined"?
It means that in school clubs and the like...
...they never played sports or did athletics.
They didn't move their bodies.
Really, the theory is that no 2m person is in the "going home club."
They didn't do that, did they?
Actually, I think an important point here is even if you didn't want to...
...the people around you would force you to.
I think that this pattern is common...
...but is it true of all people more than 2m tall?
There's also an image that tall people don't like fighting...
...and cultural clubs don't recruit as aggressively as sports clubs.
I don't know about this...
Theory: There exists someone over 2m tall who is culturally inclined.
We come now to Kato Shipping, a logistics company.
The boss is so tall that his head can be seen from another room.
What the heck!
Staff: How tall are you?
Expensive suit.
I'm 2 meters tall.
2 meters tall?
Right. 2 meters.
WOW. LARGE.
Staff: Have you been a big guy since you were young?
When I graduated middle school, I was 190cm tall.
I was 2m when I graduated high school, and...
But was he involved
in sports?
I thought I might end up around 220cm.
Well, I used to play volleyball.
Ah, volleyball.
Right, this is him in 1992...
...appearing at the Barcelona Olympics.
That's the dream, isn't it?
The dream indeed.
A former representative on Team Japan, Minami Katsuyuki.
So of course he has sports experience.
An absolutely electrifying 2m athlete.
We then come to see the workers at this pharmacy.
With this 2m tall pharmacist, Hanashio Kaga.
A pharmacist?
Staff: Do you have any sports experience?
Indeed.
I did play basketball.
As expected.
I played from about fourth grade until college.
I played for about 12 years, all told.
Staff: Why did you aim to become a pharmacist?
Well, I had no talent, and...
...I wasn't very coordinated.
I was better at studying, plus...
That's too bad.
...I was good at chemistry.
So I decided to go in that direction.
He was originally more culturally inclined...
...but because of his height he played basketball all the way through to college.
And now, this 2m+ university student.
Wow, a Benz.
From first grade to my first year of college, I played basketball all the time.
Staff: And did you have a reason to quit?
Well, I got bored of it.
I thought it would be good if I didn't go pro...
...so I quit.
Staff: What is life like at 202cm?
Staff: Do you have any trouble?
It's full of trouble.
For example, you might be with a friend in Shibuya.
It's great meeting up because they can find you easily...
...but I've been used as a landmark for people to meet up.
Something like "There's a crazy tall dude by me in Shibuya!"
"I'll move a little closer to that guy."
"I'll be there"...I've heard phone calls like that before.
He sticks out
like a scarecrow
He is tall.
Maybe it's because I'm narrow-minded...
...but I find it frustrating.
And now this 205cm person working at a construction company.
In 2008, he appeared at the Beijing Olympics.
An ex-volleyball player.
Staff: Why do you think you've grown so tall?
In my case, my parents were both tall.
Dad is 185cm, mom is 175 cm.
My younger sister is 186 cm.
Staff: 186cm?!
My great-grandfather was 190cm.
I heard no clothes would fit him.
There are basketball and volleyball players over 2m.
Meanwhile...
...in Tottori, we found a soccer player over 2m.
On the Gainare Tottori team...
...a 205cm J-Leaguer: Hatanaka Makito.
Staff) How long have you been playing soccer?
I started in first grade,
I played basketball and volleyball, since I was often invited.
But, you know, I really liked soccer.
Staff: In soccer, what is good about being taller?
In formation, for corner and free kicks...
...you have a higher chance when you're in a group of people.
Then we have this 2m soccer player...
...who attends Hosei University.
I'm a goalkeeper, and...
...the ball comes in high.
In terms of taking high goals head-on...
...I think I need the height.
And this survey revealed...
TEXT
...the sports people over 2m do most frequently.
As expected, basketball and volleyball take the lead.
Now we'll look at the maximum height of Japanese athletes from various sports.
First, basketball.
Okayama Yasutaka, who was 227cm.
He was also selected for the NBA draft.
He is currently the tallest Japanese person.
Is that so?
Then, volleyball.
Otake Hideyuki, 208cm
Currently the tallest person to represent Japan at an Olympic games...
...with the tallest ever height in any sport.
I see
Now, baseball.
Baba Shouhei, 209cm.
Later known as Giant Baba.
Of Japanese pro baseballers over 2m...
...there has only been Baba.
Continuing now with sumo.
Akashi Shiranosuke, 252 cm.
Really?
The Japan Sumo Association has recognized him as the first yokozuna
What?
Can't be true...
...but we don't know when he lived, or if he really even existed.
There are many unclear parts. It's legendary history.
Did he really exist?
Now, we'll check the maximum heights...
...of some sports where being tall might be useful.
Table Tennis
Muramatsu Yuuto, 180 cm.
Gymnastics
Tsukamoto Junki, 178 cm.
Marathon
Horibata Hiroyuki, 189 cm.
Figure Skating
Tanaka Hiroshi, 180cm.
No one here is taller than 2m.
So, if you are looking for someone over 2m who is culturally inclined...
Right, that was
the main topic.
Right.
The person we found with the shortest history in sports...
...was the swimming instructor of this gym.
206 cm Fukazawa Koji.
Staff: Did you always do aquatics?
I started from baby swimming at 0 years old and swam until 8th grade
Staff: Is it an advantage in swimming if you're taller?
There is.
When I jump in...
...I can get ahead of everyone because of my height.
My hands are big...
...and my feet are also big...
so I can push more water out of the way. It is advantageous.
Staff: Did you do other sports after you quit swimming?
I did basketball.
I had a recommendation to go to Akita Prefecture's...
...Noshiro Industrial High School.
I quit on the court..
...and I dropped out in my second year of high school.
Staff: You dropped out of high school?
I dropped out, yes.
I'm a middle school graduate.
Staff: You didn't go back to high school?
Yes, that's correct.
Result: There are no culturally inclined people over 2m, but there are 2m tall middle school graduates.
So there really weren't any.
There aren't any, huh.
They don't exist?
He's the one with the shallowest sports history.
I learned a lot of things from this survey of Japan.
Being born with a height of 2m or more...
...decides your life's path, to a degree.
It seems you'll always end up doing sports.
We put together a spectrum of different lives...
...and put it into a VTR...
...and Hamada laughed a lot at them.
He really laughed a lot!
Here's our next presenter, please.
It's Tamura Kenji!
It's a pleasure.
So, everyone...
Aren't you doing "everyone's theory"..?
Not today, Hamada-san!
Don't you remember that fun thing has begun?
It goes on?
It started last week.
Is it really ok to call it "fun"?
What do you think?
I think it's frightening.
You do? I do too actually.
Of course it's this:
It's our project about six men and women living in a shared house and experiencing love.
And see if love sparks between them.
That usually happens.
It does.
I said there are six participants...
...but one of them is actually Kuro-chan.
So it's actually a love-reality with five sparkling young boys and girls and Kuro-chan.
What love can there be with Kuro-chan?
Everyone's serious about it, right?
They are, and the whole show is still in progress.
From which point of view should we watch this?
By the way, what we saw last time...
...was almost horror.
Anyway, if that's the first time you're watching this, here's a quick and easy recap from last time.
So, our six participants have started
living together inside this shared house.
On their second day, they had a barbecue.
And all the girls wore swimsuits.
They wore swimsuits, yes.
And Kuro-chan looked at them with some frightful eyes.
Kuro-chan also got alone together with a girl...
...and confessed...
Two of them, actually.
That's right, Jinnai.
Even though he knows everything is getting recorded.
That's what he did.
On that day, he went for two of them.
I can't believe it.
He's a monster.
I know maybe I shouldn't say this, but...
...I think that I like you, so...
...I like you the best, for real.
This time I've decided to be honest with my feelings.
You're the one I like the most, Ran-chan.
But Rion-chan and Ran-chan are interested in Taiga-kun.
Taiga-kun is a 20 years old good looking man.
But he never actually dated anyone before,
so of course he's never had his first kiss.
He's never kissed a girl before.
I think if Kuro-chan wasn't there,
everything would have gone so good.
Are you hating on him already?
Kuro-chan? Of course.
Maybe a miracle could happen.
I think... it won't happen.
He did all of that even though he knows he's going on TV.
I mean, what are his chances of success?
Yeah, but the girls haven't see it on-air yet.
So he knows they can't find it out yet.
What do you usually have for breakfast?
Fruits or a smoothie.
But how?
Just like a model.
Well, I've been thinking about my health and body.
What a great man.
They're trending recently.
He's trying to impress her.
No way he drinks
smoothies.
Wait up, where are you two off to?
"You two"...
To Kawagoe.
Is it a date?
Well...
...something like that.
Have fun, ok?
Thanks!
We're going!
Have fun!
We're going.
They're so excited.
Are you doing something today, Ran-chan?
I was thinking about going to grab a bite with Taiga tonight.
Isn't that unfair?
How come?
Why you didn't ask me out?
You wanted to be asked out?
Well it's...
It's kinda...
Isn't it obvious?
He's really disgusting!
I thought...
You were all about Rion-chan.
He's already fed
up with her.
Nuh-uh, I told you right?
He's being exposed.
Rion-chan is a friend.
He's going for both
of them.
A friend?
And what's the boundary line on who you can call a friend?
A boundary line on friends?
I guess it's about I would kiss them or not.
But if you say it like that...
...even if you don't want to date someone...
...can you kiss them? Can you hold their hand?
Understand?
You meant that?
Yes, yes.
What can I say, if I don't like her, I can't kiss her.
It began.
What the hell is this?
All these flashy images...
It's 'cause they're
fashionable.
It surely is fashionable.
There's not a single time
Kuro-chan appeared here.
Oh, Ran-chan...
At this point it's still good.
This is good.
She's cute.
Oh, nice.
But this...
Is he doing pachinko?!
Don't look at other's
won balls!
What the hell was that
footage of him looking
at the pachinko balls?!
That's Toki-no-Kane (bell of time).
That sounds good!
Toki-no-Kane?
That's amazing!
Look! Hand towels!
That's a nice date.
Oh, towels!
They're so cute!
May I?
This part seems to belong
to a different tv show.
"A different show" what?!
He's fast.
This is so wholesome.
So cool!
These two are nice.
It's a footbath.
Amazing!
This feels good.
It does.
What do you think about Kuro-chan?
He's a cute character, I mean, the way he moves around, his high pitch, he's cozy.
I think his personality is really good, but...
...but he really looks like a... middle aged man.
Rion-chan sorry, I was late.
He said he's old.
Thanks for coming.
Oh, you're cute!
You're kinda black-themed.
She clearly did!
Yes, it's because you're Kuro-chan (kuro = black)
Really? For that?
That's why I chose black.
It's a double-Kuro-chan!
They got an appointment?!
You're so cute.
What the hell?
Wanna go to a place? I have it reserved.
Eh? They're on a date?
Oh, I want to.
Let's go, it's over there.
You made a reservation?
Yes, I did.
Here's to Kuro-chan and Rion's first date.
Cheers!
I can't bear to watch
this anymore.
Really, who can?
It's good!
I don't know how
should I watch this.
Yeah, right?
So, I know I was going to meet you today...
...and I thought this could make you happy, so...
If this guy gets drunk
it's gonna be awful
What's that, what's that?
Open it.
Can I?
Oh, it's so cute! What's this?
This is actually cute!
This is so cute!
I'm so happy!
It must feel good to
receive one of this!
This is a candy bouquet
Candy bouquet?
They're an "R", is it for "Rion"?
An "R", of course.
Can he do such things?
- It seems so.
I'm so happy!
I've never received something like this before.
This makes me so happy.
So that makes me the first one...
...to ever give you a candy bouquet.
What's his problem?!
Ugh, come on...
Woah, looks good!
It really looks delicious!
Let's eat then.
I don't like this.
So good.
Is it?
But even the lunch you made was good.
He's exaggerating.
You think so?
By the way, since when...?
He's sweating so much!
I mean, when did you start being intersted in me?
To be honest...
The hell is this guy?
He pisses me off.
...when we first met, I thought you were so cute.
Oh, that makes me happy.
And I was like, "I want to ask her out".
Eh? For real?
But he's intersted in
like, all of them.
Yeah, because I wanted to make princess Rion happy.
Thank you.
Kuro-chan that's...
...a really touching thing to say.
But seriously...
...I really want to...
...protect you, Rion.
Thank you.
I'll protect you for real.
You're really nice, you know?
Protect her from what?
The image I had of you totally changed.
'Cause I've been called a liar since last year?
But you see...
I never told a lie which could hurt other people.
That's true for sure.
Even if you're being tricked often,
you've never tricked anyone yourself.
Yeah, that's because I don't want to hurt anyone.
Maybe this girl
is strange too.
Sorry if I'm so blunt.
Don't worry.
Let me pat your head a bit.
Geez, you're really cute.
That scream...
Your reaction was really cute.
I don't really know
how to watch this
I've never been treated like this before so... I'm kinda happy.
How should I
watch this?
Should I root for him?
Cheers.
Oh, I feel relieved.
This is good.
The big sis is going
after the younger boy.
So what do you think about...
Kuro-chan?
- Kuro-chan?
Well, he's gross.
Last time he went and told me like "you're good"...
She said it
loud and clear.
I've been told that and I really wish he would stop.
He doesn't seem to be
much interested in her.
What about me?
Uhm... I think you're nice.
Really?
For real? Alright! I did it.
He's handsome.
Our dinner was delicious.
It was, right?
This girl picked
the wrong guy.
No need to say
that, right?
Amazing! This...
Beautiful, right?
It's beautiful, so dazzling.
Yeah it's amazing, it's a 360 degrees panoramic view.
Rion...
...can I hold your hand?
This is embarrassing.
Too fast, too fast!
Hamada-san?
- What?
Do you think he's
gonna assault her?
For real, though
he's really rushing this.
Oh look, we're holding hands.
What if... he's actually
good at this?
Though you can see everything from here...
...all I want to look at is you, Rion.
Amazing, Kuro-chan...
He's drawing closer.
For real? This
is impossible...
So...
He's getting
closer and closer.
I really want to say what I'm feeling, so now...
And I think I've come to a point in
which you're to only person I can see.
Way too fast!!
What's that way of
saying it? Creepy!
You know...
Maybe you need some rehab?
The hell is he sayin'?!
I mean, when you meet someone you can feel nervous.
The hell is he
talking about...
So it's really important to look into each other's eyes.
I think we should practice it some more.
He's so creepy!
Practice, you say?
This is unbearable!
Look into my eyes.
I'll give you some rehab.
Oh man, oh man.
The hell is he doin'?!
What are you doing,
Kuro-chan?
This is rehab!
- Oh shit.
I have no idea.
Uwaah! Gross!
See? Too fast!
What is he doing..?
Don't surprise me like that!
By "rehab" you meant this rehab?
I was wondering what you meant by that, heh.
Were you nervous?
I was nervous, yes.
Disgusting.
More like, it caught me off guard, it's embarrassing.
He's really creepy...
You still need some rehab, don't you?
I guess that's it.
I'm actually sweating
right now.
What the hell...
It was fun tonight.
I've never been in such places before.
I mean, in such fancy place.
This all revolves
around fanciness.
I'm a bit tired, maybe because I ate so much.
Must be the alcohol flowing.
Are you drunk?
I don't really know.
I'm a bit drunk myself.
I'm in a good mood.
You know, when I get to...
...have a drink with someone I like or such...
...and then I get drunk...
...I start feeling like I want to kiss them.
Ran-chan...?
Is it gross?
Nah, not at all.
Really?
For something like this...
I mean, it's just that and...
What is "that"?
Wait, wait!
What's this?!
Hamada-san!
That was his
first kiss, right?
I'll hit the convenience store and then I'm going home.
That was unexpected.
He got assaulted!
See you...
What an unexpected
turn of events...
She does that and
leaves like that?!
He is perplexed!
This guy's face...
His face was just...
What was that? What a huge shock!
He was so stiff like "what just happened?"
I mean, that was...
...Taiga's first kiss!
Yeah, it was...
Yes, probably
It was rather awkward.
He was so stiff, yes.
I mean, normal, proper people are like... slower? You know...
...slower, yes of course.
Development-wise.
What the hell is "proper people" supposed to mean?
Things are developing so fast.
Way too fast!
Maybe too fast.
Are you a slow attacker, Hamada-san?
Of course I am.
Oh, but...
That may be true.
I think I got it.
I mean, if you think about that...
there are just two guys, right? So...
Wait, you're not counting Kuro-chan, aren't you?
You straight up excluded him.
I mean, there are only two possible guys for them.
You were saying "gross, gross" too much before!
You've said the harshest things!
But really...
I mean, there could be tension between the girls
'cause they may want to aim at one of the two guys.
Ok, but don't you think Kuro-chan
and Rion date felt genuinely nice?
We can't know until we watch the rest, she may
never come back to Monster House after this!
She may be mentally shocked!
So, how will the love life of our six participants go on?
There's still more to watch now!
There's more of this?!
Yes, the second half.
So, how's the share house?
Its atmosphere is really great...
...'cause I get to live with someone else.
I see.
You'd know if you were inside it.
Who's this?
What's this now?
That's his favorite
junior colleague.
Rion's pajama were really cute.
I want to see it again.
This suddenly
feels like a skit.
Do you have a photo?
I do not.
Why?
You're right.
I tried to take one while pretending
to take a selfie, but I couldn't.
Oh, so you did.
So a pretend-selfie... for sneak photography?
It's not sneak photography.
I need it as data.
Data?
- Yes, material.
So I can remember more clearly.
For instance, if she changes hairstyle or such...
...I can look at the photo and be like "oh, yesterday they weren't like this". I can tell the difference.
Is this the girl?
Yes, look.
So it's this one.
That's her in the morning.
This is seriously
voyeurism!
It even makes sound when I take one, I should set it to mute.
That's scary.
That's a crime!
So, is there someone you like in there?
To be honest I'm currently...
...interested in both Rion and Ran.
But which one of them is your first choice?
He's the worst.
At the moment it's Rion.
You see...
I think I really started to like her.
Are you sure?
I really want to change her life.
Don't do that!
I really like Rion's face and...
He should date
this dude instead.
To be honest...
...she seems kinda dumb, doesn't she?
I even went on a date with her
You did?
I did, yes
I couldn't make it on my first date, but I think on
our next one I'm positive I'll get a kiss from her.
Is he for real?
Are you trying to get your hands on both of them?
If you say it like that...
- Yeah I mean that, if it goes well...
I'm more like "they're both good"...
But what if they find you out...?
If Rion-chan does...
I think I can manage to find a way out of it by talking...
...about Ran-chan.
She really seems to be strong willed.
This guy is horrible.
But I think she's softer on such things.
He's the worst.
For real.
He sucks.
He's really the worst.
I'm home.
Oh, hi.
Are you alone?
Yes, no one's there.
There's only Taiga, he's watching TV.
Were you playing guitar?
Just practicing.
Hey, have you...
What is it?
...been on a date with Ayu-chan?
We went to Kawagoe.
Really, Kawagoe?
Moreover, about Kuro-chan...
You had dinner with him?
I did.
How was it?
Normal I guess, we had lots of conversation,
he then said stuff like "I'll protect you".
Really?
I think it was kind of... heartening I guess...?
He kind of made
an impression.
Was it nice overall?
Say the truth!
I don't know, it kinda...
Did something happen?
Maybe I'm overthinking it, but...
...it felt like he was about to kiss me.
She said it.
And this is difficult to say, but...
Should I say this...?
His mouth really stunk.
Did it really?
Yeah, it was something out of this world... like a rotten egg.
Come on!
I had no idea!!
Like a rotten egg?
Yeah, kinda.
But such thing
was so obvious!
Like those you forgot to dispose of.
Say, Rion-chan...
...about Taiga...
What do you think?
I think he's simply cool, I mean...
...I mean, I think of him like a guy I'd be interested in...
...and I'd like to talk to him alone some more, but...
...you know...
Taiga, huh...
I'm home.
He's back.
With a mask.
It's for his
stinky mouth.
There's an hell
under that mask!
What are you up to?
What about you?
I had dinner with my junior colleague.
Oh, I see.
Say...
You had dinner with Ran-chan, right?
I did.
How was it?
What's his deal?
I guess...
...it was fun.
Well of course it was.
Be honest...
How far did you two go?
Why does he
want to know?
I bet you'll tell everyone!
What are you saying, I mean...
...I'm not a loose tongue like that.
His tongue is
loose, we know it.
Ok but... don't tell anyone.
It also stinks.
I won't.
We... kissed.
You kissed?
Yeah, it actually came from her.
He's shocked
Wait, isn't that unfair?
What's unfair?!
Is that true?
Yes, it's true.
But you said you were interested in Rion-chan,
does it mean you're done with her?
Well, I don't really know it myself yet...
Understandable.
It may sound bad but...
...I haven't decided yet, I don't know what to feel.
Oh, he's puzzled.
Well, to be honest...
Of course he is
...I don't think it's good to two-time a girl.
Hey, hey, hey!!
If you two-time a girl, you'll end up hurting both of them.
Are you for real?!
That's the only possible outcome.
He's unbelievable.
About that...
It's true I've dated Rion-chan...
But you know, it was more of a... light-hearted thing.
It didn't felt like that to me.
It didn't right? But I went on more dates.
Is he trying to
toss her away?
So I think I know better than you.
I guess you have a point.
Also, one more thing...
...but please keep it as a secret.
To be honest...
...I've...
...kissed Rion.
What the hell!
- You did not!
Are you kidding me?
Why is he lying?!
It's true.
Is it?
I wasn't planning on telling anyone.
This is absurd.
But I thought "I can't lie to him".
This guy is insane.
This guy is
incredible.
I feel... confused.
Hey, let's keep our two kisses a secret, ok?
You didn't kiss her!
Really, Taiga...
...I'm tight-lipped, you know.
Don't tell it.
More than that, I don't trust you, hehe.
Come on, man!
This is unbearable.
Sorry for calling you.
It's ok.
I kind of...
...want you to keep this as a secret...
But I thought I had to tell it at least to you, so...
...apparently...
...Taiga and Ran-chan...
...kissed.
They did?!
- Yes.
What the hell?!
He really is the worst.
It's "Monster House" after all.
It really is a monster house.
This is a real horror movie.
The monster is on a rampage!
He really is going berserk.
He is, really!
This is incredible...
How will things go on?
I think he'll consider quitting TV when this will be over.
How can this end well?
Yeah, I wonder how things will go on...
I think the staff...
...is currently digging up a very deep hole...
...for the ending of this.
You mean for him?
Next time, parents and children work together to clear a challenge.
A real parent-child escape room.
Stop!
Then,
Theory: People are 50/50 split on life in prison or life on a deserted island.
A theory that divides studio members in half.
Then,
I'll protect you if anything happens.
Monster House episode 3.
Because I'll protect you.
I'm crazy into you.