Suiyoubi no Downtown
has begun!
MC: Hamada Masatoshi
(Downtown)
Welcome everyone
Matsumoto Hitoshi
(Downtown)
Takizawa Karen
Fujii Takashi
Today, we have a
big crowd of presenters
Come in!
Ah, it's true, wow
So many of them
Yes, it's Chocolate Planet,
Kotōge, and Kasuga!
Presenters
Osada
Shōhei
Matsuo
Shun
Kotōge Eiji
Kasuga
Toshiaki
(Chocolate Planet)
(Audrey)
(Viking)
Hello!
Toose!
Well, this lineup means that...
It's what we look forward to
every half period:
Everyone's Theories
Special
★Subbed by fmck fansubs★
reddit.com/u/fmckfansubs
patreon.com/fmck
OK, who's first?
I'll start →
if that's okay with everyone.
So everyone--
There was a bit of a tussle there
Like a little skit
Anything funny...?
Chocopla were silent but...
Ah well,
Could we go first please?
Is that okay? We...
Hold on...
I'll go first
Well...
Um...
I did say funny, right?
Matsumoto-san
Didn't you hear me?
Could you break their right arms, please?
You don't need them, do you?
Not anymore
You don't need arms like that
(Kasuga) They don't
So everyone,
you've probably already noticed but →
one theory has already started
Oh, really?
And it's this:
Theory: When hit by an actress light on maximum, you can't be identified
It's been bothering me for a while.
It's hard for me too
I think everyone knows
what an actress light is but
It's often used by
older actresses
Actress light: A common name for illumination that lights up your face to hide wrinkles and make your skin look better
and is a bright light
that gets rid of wrinkles and
makes skin look better.
So this actress light,
What do you think?
How does this look on screen?
Here it is on the monitor
Wow!
(Fujii) It does it that much?
That's amazing
I never knew
Like a luminous body
It's emitting light, isn't it?
That's how it is
But if I'm looking like this you're visible
Yes we see you
And so for all our viewers
we'd like you to predict
her identity for a while.
And we'll play the VTR
with you like that too
"Who's this actress in the corner?"
While wondering who it could be
they can enjoy the VTR too
Really? OK
The VTR of Everyone's Theories that I chose
Here they are!
Everyone's Theories
as chosen by Kotōge
First it's...
Theory: The scariest thing is if a person is there after turning the power on after a power cut
The target this time is...
A regular of the "a person's there" series,
Matenrou
Anthony
He watches TV while playing
with his phone for 30 minutes
While a relaxed Anthony→
is in the toilet...
Toilet
Closet
A man hidden in the closet
trips the breaker so it seems
there was a power cut
Huh?
What?
Huh? Oh... so dark
The breaker's tripped
Sure enough...
Who? Who?
Who are you? Who are you?
No, this is so so so scary
Is this Suiyoubi? Is it?
Downtown?
Prank Reveal
This is pretty bad you know
What is this?
I mean really...
But what a relief. I was so scared
It would've been so bad if it weren't Suiyoubi
And um
Could you use the person you usually use?
It was someone completely different and I didn't know who it was
It wasn't the usual guy so I was like ... 'who?'
'Is he just some weird guy?'
And why am I holding an umbrella?
When...
Everyone's Theories
as chosen by Kotōge
Next, it's...
Theory: a pro wrestler can keep his fountain opponent down until the count of three
And so, our challenger is...
Staff) Pleased to meet you
Pleased to meet you
Pro Wrestling NOAH's
Marufuji Naomichi
A top wrestler, affliated with
Pro Wrestling NOAH, it's...
Marufuji Naomichi
And his opponent is:
Ōiso Long Beach's
Fountain ( Height 4m)
A fountain at Ōiso Long Beach,
with a height of 4 meters
Q. How do you feel about your opponent?
It's quite something
It's a very assertive opponent, isn't it?
Well, Marufuji is now
going over the rope→
and is in the ring.
This is a no-time-limit match
and will consist of a single round.
Who will the winner be?
Alright, let's go
Pro Wrestling NOAH's
Marufuji Naomichi
Ōiso Long Beach's
Fountain
The starting gong has rung!
Right now, the
fountain has fallen.
If he can get the 3-count
it's victory for Marufuji
Let's go!
Come on!
There goes Marufuji
One, tw-
He's been flipped over!
One, two-
Ahh, he's been flipped over
(Referee) One, tw--
He's been flipped over!
He got to the count of 2.9
Flipped over at 2.9!
The fountain is victorious!
Marufuji's challenge failed
Everyone's Theories
as chosen by Kotōge
Next, it's...
Theory: There are no houses in Odaiba
(TL note: artificial island in Tokyo Bay)
And so...
Staff) Good morning
Good morning
Akatsu, who's familiar with earning money on foot, will walk around and investigate
Ah, you don't see them, do you?
It's all just multi-story buildings
So I'll probably just be walking around all day
Investigation start
I'm usually looking down when I'm walking
I'm happy I'm looking for something big today
No, it's just big buildings so far
Just multi-story buildings everywhere
As expected, the only
thing he sees are...
towers and commercial property.
But...
Isn't that a house? Over there
Look
That's a proper house, isn't it?
But, after having a proper look...
This building and ship are connected
Ah! "Museum of Maritime Science"
And then...
Isn't that a house?
Oh no
It's not. Tokyo Bureau of Sewerage
Tokyo Metropolitan Government Bureau of Sewerage
Aomi Wharf Pump Station
Apart from those 2 buildings,
he finds no other buildings
that look like a house.
8 hours since
filming started
This soft cream..
is really..
Umahooooo!
(combining the words 'tasty' and 'phoenix')
All that remains is
this area
What was that just now?
And then...
You're currently living in Odaiba?
Yes
And do you live in an apartment or a house?
There are no houses in Odaiba
There are no houses in Odaiba?
No there aren't
Are you positive about that?
I am
Do you have any idea why?
It's probably because the city made it all
It's the city's so you can't buy any land?
No you can't
So you can't build a house
Correct
Apartment block
construction allowed
No residential
buildings allowed
That's right. The
city planning regulations
do not permit the construction of houses, meaning it is impossible to build one in Odaiba
That would've been easy to research
I know, right?
You can only buy apartments in that building
Only the top part is for sale
Is that so...? Wow...
Everyone's Theories
as chosen by Kotōge
Next it's...
If it's over the phone even an old fart can make the person on the other end think he's a child
For this investigation,
Yura-kun (age 7)
Kaito-kun (age 7)
We'll have Kaito-kun
call his friend Yura-kun
During the call,
Yasuo-kun (age 88)
he'll hand the phone over to Yasuo-kun, an 88-year old pretending to be a child→
and we'll find out if he can
make him think he's a child.
So let's get started
What's up, Kaito-kun?
What are you doing now, Kaito-kun?
I'm at home now
Is it okay if my friend Yasuo-kun comes over to play?
Sure
Really? Well he's here with me now so
I'll give him the phone
OK
What will happen?
How do you do?
It's Yasuo
Are you Kaito-kun's friend?
Yep
So what are you doing there?
Playing a game
Battle Cats
Ah, I've got that you know
Oh
Let's play it together
Sure
Can I come play at your house next time?
OK
I'm giving Kaito-kun the phone, OK?
So next time we'll go play with Yasuo-kun, OK?
Yeah
Do you think you could be friends with him?
I think so
He didn't notice at all
Youko-chan (age 8)
Yasuo-kun (age 88)
Hikaru-chan (age 8)
But when it comes to
a girl who's one year older...
This is Yasuo!
Yasuo?
Are you really?
Yasuo
Hey, mom. Seriously...
His voice is totally wrong
She's so grossed out
His voice is so strange for someone his age
Then...
Hey, Youko. Is Yasuo-kun really there?
Are you sure? Is he really really really really there?
Yep
And so, the result is that we made her think he's a spiritual being
I see
She was scared, wasn't she?
She could tell something was off
Spiritual was a very
accurate word to use
Right? It's like 'Am I the
only one who hears him?'
That's how she felt
But we don't know if he's really there or not
That's scary. Seriously,
he was on screen so much
Because he was so clearly
on screen for so long
Karen-chan, what did you think?
They were all fantastic but→
But in the end the
first was just too funny
Theory: The scariest thing is if a person is there after turning the power on after a power cut
Having him in a t-shirt
was just perfect
If it were a suit, the reaction
would've been different
I see, I see
and it would've been a mistake.
So you're saying
it was just right
Fujii-san, how about you?
The theory that there are no houses in Odaiba
When there's such a clear reason
Theory: There are no houses in Odaiba
they could've found out straightaway
That's right
During that ice cream thing, Matsumoto-san was saying 'we don't need that!'
But he was walking around
for 8 hours so...
Please put up with it just once
"Umahoo"
Just once...
Please endure it
What is that? Is saying
umaho trendy now?
No no,
it's not trendy
And it's never going to be
Well now, she was always
completely white in the corner
but it's time to reveal the actress
who was lit up by the actress light.
Lighting person, if you would
Here we go.
The answer was Satō Hitomi-san!
Satō Hitomi
How long was that on for?
We did it for a pretty
long time, didn't we?
I can't see properly right now
I'm not surprised
Your eyes are messed up
My eyes are shot.
Seriously.
Next, it's...
Everyone's Theories
as chosen by Chocopla
Here are the theories we've chosen
Theory: If put on hold you'll wait 10 minutes
even if it's a call from your senpai
They'll be put on hold
It happens
How about you Fujii-san?
Say Hamada-san called you→
and said hold on
a moment,
how many minutes
would you wait?
I couldn't wait for 10 minutes
10 minutes is long!
10 minutes is long
It would be like 'Has he collapsed?'
Or passed away...
Hey!
You'd just be worried
If he usually doesn't
make you wait that long
(Fujii) He doesn't
I see, I see
Theory: If put on hold you'll wait 10 minutes
even if it's a call from your senpai
For this investigation,
Senpai
FUJIWARA
Fujimoto Toshifumi
Senpai
Panther
Ogata Takahiro
Senpai
Haraguchi Akimasa
Kōhai
COLOCOLO CHITTYCHITTY PEPPERS
Audrey
Kasuga Toshiaki
Nadal
Kōhai
Igo Shōgi
Nedate Taichi
we have Kasuga,
who loves to wait,
Nadal, who'll probably
hang up immediately
and wildcard Nedate
as our three entries
It's time to call the kōhais,
who've been invited over
for a fake show
OK, I'm calling now
Good evening
Hello?
Hello
Heh!
You know the Ogata squad YouTube?
I'd like you to do an impression for it
I'm thinking of doing another event
I'm working on a few things
Ah, I see, yes
After each of them has
started a realistic conversation...
Can you wait a minute?
Ah, sure. That's fine
OK
Ah, Nadal, hold on a second
Sure
One sec
Hold on a moment. Sorry
Sure, sure
And then they put them on hold
So, how long will he wait?
I'm so excited
Let the on-hold endurance race begin!
Yikes, he looks like he'll hang up quickly
Well, he'll wait 5 minutes won't he?
He's still holding the phone
He's swinging his legs. I think he's annoyed
But it's still fine. We've passed 3 minutes
All three groups get off to a good start
I'm sorry. I'm starting to pity him
This is long for Nadal, isn't it?
He's done 6 minutes
Huh, what?
Ah, he hung up
He suddenly hung up, he suddenly hung up
And so the pair of Fujimon and Nadal are
eliminated after 6 minutes and 13 seconds
Prank Reveal
Wha...
Wh- what is it?
You hung up, didn't you?
After 6 minutes
6 minutes!
I'm the one who should say that→
with such energy
(Nadal) Wait a minute
You could only wait 6 minutes?
I'm your senpai but if it were you...
No, that's wrong
That's wrong. Wait a minute
6 minutes is a shock
No, it was 8 minutes. I saw it
6 minutes
It was 8 minutes
Evidence
Please look, because it was 8 minutes
Is that alright?
I'm checking. It's fine, isn't it?
Sorry... Maybe it was 6 minutes...
It's 6 minutes
It was 6 minutes. I'm sorry
Let's check the remaining 2 groups
We've passed 10 minutes
10 minutes is done!
10 minutes, we did it, we did it, we did it
They clear the theory's 10 minutes without problems
Hasn't he been like this from the start?
So we'll continue the investigation and see how long they wait
He's not looking at his phone. Only the magazine
Kasuga waits with the call
on loudspeaker
In contrast to this,Nedate
keeps his body in a phone call position
Hold on, he's whistling. He's not angry at all
He doesn't stress about waiting.
Because he's whistling
Ah is that it? The holding music
Is he joining in with the hold music?
But after 20 minutes have passed
Nedate starts acting strangely
Hello!
Huh?
After saying nothing for 20 minutes...
a sudden "Hello"
Hello!
Ahh, this is scary. Doing hidden camera is scary
And then...
Bro, bro
Huh, what?
He's broken
Bro, bro
He's alone, isn't he?
Bro, bro, bro
Staff) What's going on?
I don't know
He's never even called me bro
(Satō) He hasn't?
What's taking you so long? Hey, Ihashi
Ah, he's doing impressions
Impressions...
He's doing impressions, isn't he?
It seems before Ogata put him on hold,
he was practicing impressions
And he keeps going,
passing the one hour mark
Idiot! Idiot!
Idiot!
Who is this?
I'm sorry, sir
Huh?
What?
While he continues practicing
unidentifiable impressions...
Kasuga stays focused on reading a single magazine
At this point,
3 hours have passed since the start
Seriously?
That's amazing
And then...
I have a question
Am I able to give up?
I've got work quite early tomorrow
Due to a work commitment, Haraguchi gives up
They finish after
3 hours and 4 minutes
Haraguchi and Kasuga eliminated
That was so long
No, no. What? What is it?
So long
What's long?
3 hours is long
No...
Why didn't you hang up?
Because you said "hold on a moment"
So I waited
And so the only one remaining is a man
who probably isn't aware of the handsfree function
But Ogata has a problem too
So today I got up at 5am
And first thing tomorrow I'm shooting in Sendai
So is it okay if I take a small nap?
If I don't sleep tomorrow's going to be impossible
Staff) You won't give up?
I won't. Because
he's doing his best for us
So he has a nap with his phone still on hold
And then after that he does 2 hours of
impressions, holding his phone throughout
The weirdo Nedate
Well he is a freak with this isn't he?
Then, after 5 hours of being on hold
finally...
Ogata-san, I'm sorry. Goodbye
Nedate suddenly hangs up and
starts preparing to go home
Staff) He hung up, he hung up
Woken up by the staff,
Ogata rushes to confront him
And then...
What's wrong with you?
What's going on?
It's not about what I'm doing
Huh?
It's 3:10am you know
Staff) Why didn't you hang up the phone?
I was waiting and creating impressions
I wrote all these impressions
There's so much here. Woah
Were you really watching me?
Only the first half. I was asleep for the second
Sleeping?Are you crazy?
And so, the Ogata squad should not be underestimated
On-hold challenge
Ogata & Nedate
Haraguchi & Kasuga
Fujimoto & Nadal
Yes, that's all from us
Beating Kasuga-san
Right?
Nedate went on for five hours
But Kasuga-san's 3
hours was long too
But if Haraguchi hadn't given up there
he'd do it forever
Yes, that's true
Yes.
Because I was told to wait
What goes through your mind?
Well, it's as I said...
I'm told to wait so I wait
Do you get a thrill out of waiting?
Do you ****?
Yes more ecstatic the longer it goes on
"I'm waiting!"
I'm not thinking "I feel so
good!" while I'm waiting
Everyone's Theories as chosen by
Chocolate Planet
Next it's...
Theory: If you win a contest, people you don't remember at all
will contact you, Part 2
We previously investigated this with
the champions of 2016's King of Conte, Rice
I've got someone I don't know
So have I
How about this year's winners, Kūki Kaidan?
We strike right after the live broadcast finishes
Staff) Have you checked your phones yet?
Staff) Since winning
Ah, I haven't
I haven't
So, can we look now?
Staff) Yes, you can
Umm...
141 messages
(Suzuki) On LINE, yes
97 messages
Some are from friends from my hometown
There's also news about an event at the Pachinko shop
There's 3 of those so the real number's 138, not 141
Staff) How about from people you don't remember?
People I don't remember...
People I don't remember... Wait a moment
I remember them all
I also remember all of mine
Sorry
Staff) No, it's totally fine
Sorry...
Yes
This...
You've come to check if people we don't remember have contacted us after winning, haven't you?
Staff) Yes
Staff) But there's not anything wrong with that
Sorry. Really...
I didn't think we'd disappoint people so soon after winning
Everyone's Theories
as chosen by Chocolate Planet
Next, it's...
Theory: Harvesting the bontan fruit is also called bontan hunting
TL note: As well as being a fruit 'bontan' is a word used
for puffy pants, associated with 1980s high school delinquents.
Bontan hunting is the practice of hunting down those wearing
them and robbing them of them; mainly associated with high school manga.
Also, hunting and harvesting are the same word in Japanese
So we checked the sightseeing website
of somewhere known for producing bontans,
Kagoshima-ken's Akune city
Bontan hunting / processing experience
The "Bontan" is a large fruit that was sent 230 years ago as a
thank you for helping a Chinese ship that had
washed ashore off the coast of Akune.
Have fun harvesting the famous Akune Bontan.
You will also be able to try your hand at processing.
And found it
Bontan hunting experience
If this isn't about
the fruit,
it'd look something like this
Bontan hunting experience
Bontan hunting / processing experience
The "Bontan" is a large fruit that was sent 230 years ago as a
thank you for helping a Chinese ship that had
washed ashore off the coast of Akune.
Have fun harvesting the famous Akune Bontan.
You will also be able to try your hand at processing.
And you can also experience processing here
Bontan processing experience
Ah, really?
No, no, no
And then we checked a local newspaper too...
An article titled
"bontan hunting in full swing"
And so...
TBS Announcer
Yoshihara Ami
Bontan hunting in full swing
We had an announcer read it out in a news report-style for us
On the 11th, the Ozaki district of Akune City, which is known for its production of bontans,
held its 8th annual Ozaki Iki Iki Festival under the auspices of the district's Village Development Committee.
Parents and children enjoyed bonton hunting.
In the bontan garden next to the community center,
children harvested large bontans with the help of local residents.
Pork soup and onigiri were served
and agricultural and
fishery products were on sale.
The village of bontans was
bustling with activity.
Everyone's Theories
as chosen by Chocopla
Next it's...
Theory: If you're sleeping somewhere extremely noisy, if it becomes quiet, you'll wake up instanty
And so...
Woah, it's cold
Huh, where is this?
Akatsu has already been
awake for 20 hours
We're going to have him
sleep at this construction site
I'm going to sleep outside in a place like this?
All we tell Akatsu is that he has to go to sleep
I won't be able to sleep like this
Let the investigation begin
Staff) Please begin
Goodnight
Shut up
Just shut up!
It's noisy and there's vibrations too
It's so close
But 30 minutes later...
Akatsu is in
a deep sleep
Head of Sleep EEG Laboratory
Wada Chihiro-san
Wow, he's asleep!
We've confirmed he's asleep by checking his brainwaves
so will leave it like this for a while
1 hour later
It's almost time to stop the noise
If he wakes up within 10 seconds of the noise stopping, the theory is considered proven
Let's see what happens
Everyone's Theories
as chosen by Chocopla
Finally, it's...
If a young comedian starts talking exactly like Nobu,
his senpai will warn him
We'll have some young comedians come to the office for a review of their material
No one's going to come see us like this
You can't just say he's red
Investigation details:
A young comedian will rip off Nobu's tsukkomi style,
and we'll see if the senpai comedian instructing him will warn him
Helping us with this is someone whose accent
is similar to Nobu's Okayama-ben,
Mamaland (est. 6 years ago)
Tsukkomi
Kame (from Hiroshima)
Boke
Murasato
this young comedian
from Hiroshima.
And the senpai we'll be targeting is...
Good morning.
Nice to meet you
Kimura Yūichi
He'll say it
Kimu will say it
Kimura usually works at NSC (Yoshimoto New Star Creation) and is known for being a harsh critic
Will he say anything?
Yes, hello
We're Mamaland. Nice to meet you
So yesterday I was about to
sleep and got into bed
I glanced at the ceiling
and saw something
Rustling, sticky-looking
and gleaming black
Oh.. a bodybuilder
No, no!
Why would there be a bodybuilder rustling around in my ceiling?
(Kame) No, it was a cockroach! Don't they
say if you've got one there's a hundred?
In that case I know how to get rid of it
Seriously? Tell me
A spider will eat it for you
A spider?
One as big as an iPad...
An iPad?!
That's huge isn't it?
Yep, and covered in thick hair
Hey, that's scary
Dripping
That's the Wet iPad Tarantula!
(Kame) It's the most dangerous one
(Murasato) Just leave it in the room for 10 minutes
(Kame) Just forget it.
I'm fine with the cockroach
What do you do with the spider?
It rustles in the ceiling doesn't it?
Hey, get back on topic
(Kame) I'll have just swapped a cockroach for a tarantula
He's thinking about how
much he's imitating him
As he's subjected to successive hits of Nobu-style tsukkomi,
Kimu has a suspicious expression
And then...
Hey that's long
Yep and about as thick as me
It's huge
And it's known for its pattern
Pattern?
Yep, its whole body is paisley
No, a snake's too individualistic
(Kame) Isn't that the Paisley Snake?
After some tsukommi that seems like
it was somehow left out of a Chidori performance...
We're done.
Thank you very much
They finish their performance here
Will he warn them as expected, or not?
You like Nobu, don't you?
Would I say I like him? I suppose
We're from the same area so...
Ah, really? It felt like Hiroshima-ben
I think I might seem a bit like him
Hmmm
But what about doing tsukommi with your fist clenched?
(Kame) Ah, yes
Well.. . like...
Nobu does that too, right?
Yes, I suppose so
Staff) So you're saying he's a bit like him?
I looked at where he was from and was like "Ah Hiroshima". I have friends who are like that
'That's just how it is' I thought
Many people are like that
Like how people say 'what the hell' in Osaka-ben
If you've always spoken like that then there's no helping it
Yes, this is how I usually speak
Surprisingly it appears he wasn't that
bothered about him speaking like Nobu
However...
How is it being called "Mamaland"?
There's a "Laland" already. Doesn't it bother you?
Um, it does. There's Mamatarte-san too
I think it's good to have some flexibility
He's very sensitive to their being named similarly to other groups
Yes, that was our last one
Matsumoto-san
how was the last one?
As we expected,
Kimu...
wanted to throw a plastic bottle, just how Kinoshita does it
He's not that scary
He's not like that
He wanted to hit him in the eye with it
No no...
He wouldn't go that far
So he's mellowed out
He instructed us too
when we were at NSC
Oh, really?
We were able to meet him then
and he was fairly scary then
Right?
He's been very kind
since we graduated though
Karen-chan, what did you think?
One really made an impression with me
the Bontan one
Theory: Harvesting the bontan fruit is also called bontan hunting
I really loved it
There's so many words like
that in Japanese, aren't there?
So I'd love for you to keep doing it
And explaining something complicated
with pictures was really helpful
By the way, do you know the reason
why the students are pulling the bontans off?
Ah, umm...
I don't know
You didn't know!
But you laughed so much
You didn't know but were able to enjoy it
She really enjoyed it
Next it's...
Everyone's Theories
as chosen by Kasuga
Yes, here are Everyone's Theories
that I chose
Theory: If you ask someone who definitely looks over 80
how old they are and they reply 'I'm 60', you'll still answer 'you don't look it!'
I see
That's right
You can't say 'you look old'
Well, that's right
Yes
So we investigated if they'll still say the usual phrase 'you don't look it'
Theory: If you ask someone who definitely looks over 80
how old they are and they reply 'I'm 60', you'll still answer 'you don't look it!'
And so...
Thank you! Hello!
It's Panther's Ogata! Hello
He's in the same clothes
We've made a fake show where he interviews older people on the street to discover their health secrets
We send in this 89-year old grandpa
who couldn't possibly be 60
Let's see what happens
How old are you now?
I'm sixty
Si... Sixty?
Yes
Ah... but... you're young, aren't you?
Taken by surprise,
all Ogata can say is...
'you're young, aren't you?'
Then Ogata worries what he'll look like in his 50s if this man is 60
You're 60?
Yes, I am
Seriously?
Yes
So do you ever get told you look older than you are?
I'm told that
You are, aren't you?
Is this on purpose...
That's a sweater someone who's over 60 would wear, isn't it?
Do you think?
Is it not on purpose?
It's nothing like that
Huh?
If you're 60 then...
He's still going!
Taka-san, Ishibashi Takaaki-san...
I was born in 1961
So compared to me...
You're 16 years my senior
Ah, 16 years... Ah, I see
Huh, so that means you're the same age as Tunnels-san?
That's right
Wow
Well I guess comedians are young
So he did not say "you don't look it"
He was so persistent
Yes, Ogata-kun didn't say it
I thought it'd be fine since 'you don't look it' can mean something else
Well, that's right
But he just said 'you're young'
Yes, because he clearly wasn't 60
Satō-san, what about
if it were you?
I'd probably say 'you look adult-like'
'Adult-like'
'Adult-like', is it?
Like 'you seem like an adult'
I don't think that's how it works
(Osada) That'd make
sense if it were a teen
So there still more
Everyone's Theories that I've chosen
Here's the rest!
Everyone's Theories
as chosen by Kasuga
Next is...
Inffective megaphone theory
The megaphone's known for distorting your voice
and making it harder for people to understand you
So for this, we'll have someone known for having a loud voice, Oideyasu Oda, use his real voice
And someone known for being quiet, Harusenbon's Haruka, will use a megaphone
They'll face the judge, Koga Ken→
and we'll investigate which can be heard from farther away
The words they'll be shouting
will be decided by lottery
(Oda) Shine muscat
Shine muscat
Gasoline stand
('gas station')
Starting with a distance of...
First is Oideyasu Oda
with his own voice
Shine
muscat!
I've got it
'Shine muscat'
It was very clear
Next is Harusenbon's Haruka
with a megaphone
Gasoline stand
Huh...?
I heard 'goshuin stamp'
Everyone's Theories
as chosen by Kasuga
Next is...
Theory: that fried snack is called 'churros' 50% of the time, 'churritos' 30% of the time, and 'churro' 20% of the time
We investigated the 143 shops that we were able to confirm sell this snack on restaurant review app Tabelog
Breakdown of what the fried snack is called
Churros
Churritos
Churro
Note: Chain restaurants count as one shop
First, the most familiar name, 'churros'
With places like Disneyland,
and restaurants specializing in 'churros'
98 shops use it with a percentage of 68.5%
Breakdown of what the fried snack is called
Churros
Churritos
Churro
Note: Chain restaurants count as one shop
Next, 'churritos'
TOHO Cinemas
Churritos
Places like
movie theaters...
and zoos often use it
Tobu Zoo
Breakdown of what the fried snack is called
Churros
Churritos
Churro
Note: Chain restaurants count as one shop
And finally it's 'churro'
TL note: It's a blurred photo of Mister Donut
It's used at 4 shops including that well-known chain
Breakdown of what the fried snack is called
Churros
Churritos
Churro
Note: Chain restaurants count as one shop
And so the final results are as shown
Churros
Churritos
Churro
By the way, it wasn't on Tabelog, but the three large convenience store chains use the word 'Churrokkii'
Churros
Churritos
Churro
Churrokkii
But why do so many different names exist for it in the first place?
We asked this shop which sells churritos
Kinoshita Eiji-san
It's originally from Spain and Portugal
and it's fried snack called a 'churro'
And then over here,
splitting it into pieces and dipping it in chocolate sauce→
is how we generally eat it
so from that the plural 's' got attached
'Churros' started from that
Originally in Japan the registered trademark
was probably by Nissin Foods, I think
so because the word 'churros'
was already a registered trademark,
Churros
Nissin Foods registered trademark
…no one could name it
that anymore
And that's how the word 'churritos'
started being used in Japan
Churritos
Zeal House registered trademark
Churros
Churritos
Nissin Foods registered trademark
Zeal House  registered trademark
And then to avoid these, the word churrokkii was invented
Churros
Churritos
Churrokkii
Nissin Foods registered trademark
Zeal House  registered trademark
Yamazaki Baking registered trademark
Yes, it's a snack that's been pushed around a lot
due to a grown-up sitatuation
Everyone's Theories
as chosen by Kasuga
Next it's...
Theory: When asking people around Kōrakuen who owns the instagram account "yuri_ebhihara", half will say Ebihara Yuri and half will say Yūri Ebihara
(area famous for boxing)
↓
↑
(model)
(Russian ex-boxer, a.k.a. Yuri Arbachakov)
So we started asking people who came
to see that day's boxing match
Kourakuen Hall
Posts:
Followers:
By the way, this account
in reality of course
Posts
Followers: 806k people
Following: 491 people
belongs to the model Ebihara Yuri, a.ka. Ebi-chan
Staff) We're asking about this Instagram username
Staff) Who do you think it belongs to?
Ebihara Yuri
Yūri Ebihara
Ummm.. Ebi-chan
The ex-model from CanCan or AneCan
Ebi-chan
The model Ebi-chan
Ebihara Yuri-san
The celebrity Ebi-chan. She was cute
It's Yūri Ebihara, right? The former boxer
But that can't be. He wouldn't be on there
And then after that too...
Yūri Ebihara, from the Soviet Union
Isn't it the boxer Yūri Ebihara-san?
Yūri the boxer
Just as expected at the holy land of boxing, Kourakuen
there were a fairly high number
of people answering Yūri
Ebihara Yuri
Yūri Ebihara
Yūri Ebihara, right?
The model Ebihara Yuri-san
Yuriyan Retriever
Ebihara Yuri
Our results from asking 77 people:
Don't know
Yūri Ebihara
Other
37 people said Ebi-chan,
and 17 people answered Yūri.
And there was someone else too...
So?
Staff) This is a certain person's Instagram account
Staff) Do you know who owns it?
Yes, it's my son's
Staff) Your son's?
Yes
Staff) Who is that?
He's called Kanaya Yūri
He's got a match today at Kourakuen Hall
Kanaya Yūri
When the boxer Yūri Arbachakov debuted in Japan,
he debuted with the name Yūri Ebihara, you know
So the Yūri from Yūri Ebihara
is how my son got his name
Everyone's Theories
as chosen by Kasuga
And finally...
Theory: You do the kind of survey where people on the street give their opinion by putting a sticker on a board and ask people which musician they'd rather hug. If the board already has 99 stickers on it that voted for Hotei Tomoyasu and 0 for Fukuyama Masaharu, it's possible someone will go with the flow and vote for Hotei
This is really evil
Which musician would you rather hug?
Hotei Tomoyasu
Fukuyama Masaharu
Huh? There's no one
No way... I'll go with this
It'll be bad if I don't vote for this one
Huh? This shouldn't be
So, while people are doubting the vote totals, as expected the only one getting votes is Fukuyama
But then...
We got one
(Staff) Hotei-san?
Yes
Staff) So do you like Hotei-san?
Of course, yes, I like Hotei-san
Staff) And Fukuyama-san?
I like Fukuyama-san too, of course. He's wonderful
Staff) But why did you not vote for him?
No, it's just... well...
Well... everyone voted this side
Like...
I didn't have the courage to put the sticker here
So the result is that some people
are easy to influence
Yes
That last one was so evil
Hotei theories
are a favorite of ours
And, also. This show...
Have we finally been stopped from using Disneyland photos?
It was a drawing, wasn't it?
It was
Well, it happens
So...
We've even been banned from the land of dreams now?
Is that how you see it?
If only Yūri Ebihara's photo was the one we couldn't use
★Subbed by fmck fansubs★
reddit.com/u/fmckfansubs
patreon.com/fmck
Next week, if a female celebrity you haven't seen for a long time has had loads of plastic surgery,
Nīyama Chiharu
Anzai Hiroko
it's hard to say anything
Looking forward to working with you
<Thank you
You haven't changed at all
Nice to meet you
<Yes, nice
to meet you
Then, unsuccessful comedians face off
We find out who's the best at taking bentos from backstage home
That's enough. That's enough.