I see
Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
So today we have prepared various theories for you
Matsumoto... Matsu... who're you?
Finally, Yoshimoto has decided on a successor
Wow this is exciting
What a historic day!
-Thanks for your kind words
Surely there's no way
That is, to tell the truth
Sitting opposite Hamada-san is genuinely awful
It's really scary
-Why do you say that?
It's like a car is constantly tailing me
The pressure is really not to be underestimated
Matsumoto is really quite remarkable
So, it's time to get started!
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
It's Morita!
Chief!
Thank you for having me
Chief, chief!
Thank you
-Thank you
You know, I recently heard something
A ghost's lifespan is 200 years
Does everyone know this?
A ghost?
What is this lifespan you speak of?
A ghost is not completely dead, right?
Otherwise it wouldn't be appearing on this side
Appearing as a ghost in the world of the living
The life span of this state is 200 years
Heh...
So, seeing ghosts of primitive people
Oh yeah!
-Indeed!
You never hear of such a thing, right?
-No!
It's weird that they have never appeared
-That's right
Seriously?
So, everyone
So, what I bring to you today is...
A related verification
Really?
The theory I've brought is this:
It is actually difficult to get a person to say "heh?"
I see
After listening to what you just heard
"Heh?" wasn't all that common a reaction
Some said stuff like "Seriously?"
-Indeed
So it's like this
"Ha?" or something like that.
Yoshimura was the only one that actually said it
He said "heh?" perfectly
200 years, that's all
Heh?
So, is it true what you said about the ghost?
Regarding that...
It's a lie
Heh!?
That's unbelievable!
No, no, wait a minute
You're saying "unbelievable", but first of all...
Do you actually believe in ghosts?
As far as i'm concerned,
I like to share this type of rumor
When people hear stuff like this
I always get this "heh?" reaction
But, as it turns out, actual rumors can't be broadcast on TV
So all the information we used this time is just patently false
I see
-Fictitious
So, how many "heh"s can we get from them?
Let's find out
It is actually difficult to get a person to say "heh?"
And so, the instigator is...
I'm in charge
I see
Morita
Who is being targeted?
A junior of mine called Hyouroku
Hyouroku?
Sounds like a folk tale
A person with great respect for Morita
He has appeared many times as a solo artist on Goodbye Live
Looks like the type to say it
Hyouroku
Isn't this just an "heh?" type face!?
So cunning, seems like it'll be really easy to accomplish!
Let's say it is
This time, to complete the verification Hyouroku and Morita are gathered
In the lounge of a fake show in which the former and the latter are starring together
How many "heh?"s can be elicited?
How many times
He's quite out of touch, that guy
So even if it's a small thing
I think he'll say "heh?", yeah
The time limit is 30 minutes
He'll probably say "heh?"
Seems likely
Hyouroku wore a very bright jacket
But TBS is really...
I thought I'd never come back here again
-How come?
No no, how to say...
Think he'll say it
Speaking of which, you are now, what?
You're not doing comedy anymore, pretty much?
Although I want to-to do it, but, yeah...
He's cute
"LOVE it!" seems to be the one
I'll be on the Sunday episode
Eh——
Eh
Is Kawashima on it?
Of course Kawashima will be there
But it seems other comedians wont be
Who will be?
-Probably an actress
Eh——
But it's really good
Too bad!
I think it's Meru Nukumi, I think its been decided
Eh——
This is an "eh?" person!
Although this junior does not say "heh"
He is definitely the type that says "eh-"
Next
She... she's a woman, right?
Yeah, a woman
Eh—
Don't you know her?
I'm sorry, I can't think of the person
This person does not know anything
He seems to be more out of touch than expected
He doesn't even know her
Does this guy not even watch TV?
Didn't Michopa go on TV?
-Oh, Michopa!
You know Michopa?
-Michopa, yes, I do
But the word Michopa...
It can't be broadcast in the northeastern region
Eh? Why?
The word "Michopa"?
Where is it in the northeast, Akita or Yamagata?
Very strong, Morita
He's pretty good at this
"Michopa" means "male genitalia"
Such a load of nonsense
I don't know if it's the dialect or what
-Eh-
Very impressive
Bullshit comes as natural to him as breathing
So Michopa can't even be seen on TV in the Northeast
Ah, is that right?
-Yes
Eh—
But Michopa herself seems to have no idea about it
Then, if people in that region talk about Michopa...
If the interview is "Do you know Michopa?" then
"Do you know XXXX", it'd be like that
-Yeah, yeah, yeah
Eh—
"Huh? What are you talking about?" This sort of thing
+1
Seriously!
It's like that
Hyuoroku can't not say it
Although the "eh" series was carried out
What's the score?
In ten minutes, not even a single "heh" has been elicited
Next
I'm going to go to the bathroom for a little bit
-Okay
Here I was also considering the "eh" problem
Here, Morita came out of the room and found the staff
Indeed
He's been saying "eh-" all along, right? That guy
Yeah
It's always "eh-"
What to do
But saying "eh-" is pretty much the same, right?
He didn't say "heh" though
The staff is really strict
That guy believed everything without question!
Show business is so hard. Seriously, right?
Ah...
I remembered one thing
Isn't there someone named Asakura Mikuru?
Ah!
Did you know that there is an AV actress with the same name?
I didn't know
Her name is Asakura Mikuru
Eh-
How to say,
No way!
The porno thing,
Wanted a heh
It is possible to hear it from the mouth of Hyouroku
That thing, how to say, it's kind of like a porno but...
Ah, a parody, right?
What is it? - That...
The one that's like "RICHIN"
※RICHIN: a fashion brand for girls
How could you think of that
"RICHIN" is the same. It does seem to be a thing.
"RICHIN"?
What's so funny?
I think Asakura Mikuru appeared in "RIZIN"
You couldn't not be happy being with a guy like this
Do you like H-videos?
I don't have the courage to watch
No courage?
-Hmmm
So you don't watch AV?
I've seen, i've seen them
-What the hell?
So weird
The pair become stuck on the topic of porn
What the hell?
Male genitalia-like face
Do you know the "Boin"?
"Boin" is boobs
-Yeah, yeah
In fact, an individual boob is called "Boin"
Understand?
Where did this all come from?
So when you talk about both boobs, you have to say "Boin Boin"
Oh really
That's why you should say "I want to play with a girl with boin boin"
Well, it's true, if you think about it
There doesn't need to be two for it to be a boob, right?
Isn't there only one child?
-Yes, yes
So actually by growing a something here...
-Yeah
His brain is wired very uniquely
You know China has it's "one child policy", right?
Because of that they have a single boob
Heh~
It appeared!
It appeared
A very straightforward "heh"
Thanks to the most false lie so far
1 "heh" finally comes out after 15 minutes
Have you ever seen Mastuko? Matsuko Deluxe
No I haven't
Matsuko-Deluxe is really big, right?
Oh really
So sure enough, it's still a lot of work to walk
So Matsuko uses a segue in TV station corridors
Is that so?
-Because it's really hard to walk
Heh～
How about this one...
After one came out
Mr. Maric  -
-Yeah yeah yeah
Did you know that he and Mr. Children have the same mentor?
And his house address is Mr. 1
Eh—
Still eh
Although the lies are getting more and more outrageous
This one fails to show even a shred of doubt
He really accepts all of it
5 minutes left
That's awesome!
Hyouroku is a remarkable person
But then again
Recently, Downtown's Matsumoto has been off resting, right?
This is a secret OK
So you can't tell anyone
What happened was... Hamada was arrested
Eh?
-That's right
What about?
Apparently he pulled a gun out of his bag
Oi!
Ah, is that right?
-Yes, yes
Is that so...
Eh...the bag... the bag contained...
A gun in the bag
Heh~
Appeared!
Weakly squeezed out a "heh"
What's more
Speaking of...
Takeru vs Nasukawa Tenshin
At the end, Nasukawa Tenshin said he wanted to quit
Morita is so good
Too strong
So he's been replaced Black Mayonnaise's Kosugi
What? Isn't Ko-ko-kosugi the one that said "he-ha-"?
The "he-ha" one
How can I put it...is this a little too big of a play...
Unpromising?
I don't know. I don't know
Heh~
He said it!
Certainly said it
So we expose the whole thing
What's this reaction
Wh-wh-wh-what's that? This is
As if you've never seen it before
What do you think it is?
I don't know, it's...
Scary scary
What is it again? This theory
It is actually difficult to get a person to say "heh?"
It is actually difficult to get a person to say "heh?"?
It's so hard!
Heh~
"After heh"
It's an "after heh"
So what the hell is going on here?
Why is it now!?
The results are, Morita scores 4 "heh"s
If eh is included it would have been about 20
Seriously
The next challenger is...
He'll probably be pretty good at this
Alco&Peace's Hirako
His target is
His junior, Time Machine No. 3's Yamamoto
What will the result be?
How will it go
Have you met with Kusanagi recently?
Kusanagi, not really been in touch
The same company
Kusanagi called me recently
He was filming on location and called me on location to say,
He bought a Galande
Mercedes G Class
Eh~
Eh, on not that one?
Good at it
Miyashita
-Didn't Miyashita buy a Tesla?
His Tesla was scuffed up
After he got out of the car he realized it was scuffed
Quite good at it!
Indeed
He was on a "Let's go see a foreign car" kind of location shoot
He does look like the kind of person who would say "I'll take this one"
Seems the type
He has some of his own money it seems
Seems to be saving a lot of cash
-Heh~
He had a large stack of cash with him
This is a heh-man
With lies shrouded in seeming truthfulness, two "heh"s appear early on
A heh-man!
What's more,
Not like Hyouroku
Hitori is also very successful
This guy is like a professional liar
Ah because of "Asakusa Kid"? I watched it
It was interesting
-I had tears in my eyes
I actually went to Asakusa yesterday, and it was really great
Did you know that the story itself is actually based on Tamori?
Eh?
Hitori actually shot the story of Tamori
He requested it of Tamori
"I want to make a film about you, Tamori!"
Tamori didn't even wait for him to finish before refusing
"I've not lived a very pleasant life," he said
But Hitori said,
"It doesn't matter, regardless of what the story entails,
You're an extraordinary man!"
After saying that, Tamori smiled and said
"As long you don't add anything to it, it's fine."
So true
So awesome
Without using any BGM and so on as a condition
Good at it
Heh～
Just shoot it in a normal way
Hmm~
Under these conditions
A different noise
At the end when the credits roll
There's a song played on the trumpet by Tamori
-Wow...
Heh~
That one is OK
It doesn't say "Tamori" on the credits either
The type of person who says heh
A lot of talk!
Heh~
A very long heh
Show businesses is amazing
Super long
Although he has successfully gotten a lot of "heh"s...
Did you watch the NASA press release? The news just came out in the evening
NASA
It confirmed that although there is no heaven in the world, hell does exist
Too much, right?
NASA said that?
-Yes
Did you know that the international rules of shogi are being changed to make it OK to repeat two moves?
Impossible
Starting to fail
No, it means that a two-step move is going to be OK
You can't. If you can repeat two steps, it's not...
It's too fake, right?
As the believability of the lies gradually decrease
The number of "heh"s also began to plummet
And so
Ota Pro seems to be retreating from show business
They've proposed entering a new field, said "i'll do denim instead"
A big lie
Well, if Levi's could do it, it's possible I guess
Can Ota Pro make denim and sell it?
Throwing accurate and reasonable remarks at crude and poorly thought out lies
That's true
The greatest truth of all
Do you know the new flavors of Giggles coming out next year?
※Giggle-kun (garigari-kun): Japanese lollipop brand
On the offensive again
I don't know but i'm sure its quite unexpected
It has the smell of petrol
I'm sure it won't sell
They're now whispering words to each other...
So here it is time to reveal the truth
In regard to "heh"
In my understanding, Hirako is a person who loves to lie and blow smoke
I just had the feeling of "Ah~ here we go again with this stuff"
A suspect's expression
So, Alco&Peace's Hirako scores 5 points
But the results are pretty good
The final challenger is
Knights' Hanawa
Who is your target?
It's Master Oozora Yuhei
The one everyone knows
A senior manzai talent
Who knows?
Master Oozora Yuhei
This is bad
Even holding a musical instrument in his promo picture
3rd tier, right?
Who cares?
Because he's 70 years old
I think he probably doesn't understand youth culture
I don't think i've even seen him using a phone
Probably doesn't know how it works
So it might be good to go down that kind of route
I see
It's been a long time since you've been on TV like this, right?
It's been a long time
How many years has it been since TBS? About 7 years?
Very nice looking person
Before was it for manzai work?
Yeah manzai
In terms of us, we come every day
Mm-hmm
There is a late night TV shopping program
Oh I know the one
I'm on that show
I do that one live
Ah, is it a live broadcast?
Heh~
About 6 days a week, working from 3:00 a.m. to 4:00 a.m
Sometimes until 5:00
It's very hard work, you don't get much sleep
So gentle
Basically, I don't sleep, I just go directly to the next job
But wasn't TBS in decline for a while?
There was a time they made a lot of money in Korea
Isn't there a group called BTS?
That was originally a TBS group
Heh~
Originally a group selected by TBS through auditions
No, it's not
Then a guy named J.Y. Park came along
-Hey~
And changed the TBS into BTS
Now this group is quite hot in the United States
They earn a load of money
Heh~
Royalties and such
A lot of high quality "heh"s
Fascinated by everything
The level of a master
Oozora Yuhei hits a "heh" streak
And so we enter the previously mentioned topic of phones
Signal...is your phone a smartphone?
It's a tablet, I have both a cellphone and a tablet
You don't have a smartphone, do you?
I have a smartphone
You have both a smartphone and a tablet?
Yes, yes
An unexpected error has occurred
The master is actually a wealthy man who owns both a tablet and a smartphone
So youthful!
However,
I don't seem to have any signal
My cell phone signal still has signal, it's normal
He knows all about signal
I'm connected at least, I can tell there's WiFi
Ah here it is, it feels right to say it like that
Prior to the age
Cute
You know, people below the age of 60 can see it, right?
I can see the Wi-Fi signal hovering around
The signal in this place is pretty pleasant-looking
Oh really?
Heh~
Is this some kind of good guy competition?
This guy is too good for this
Already looks like a good guy competition
So does it go "poof" if you walk into it or something like that?
If you hit into it it just brushes past you
Heh~
-You can't see it anymore, right?
Can't see it at all, no
Usually in the lounge people can always see it
Looks so happy
"The signal's strong today," so to speak
Heh~
He's a model contestant
As the lack or possession of IT knowledge is tested
A big move leads to 3 consecutive "heh" explosions
After this also
I've been an M-1 judge for 4 years
Did you know, the scores are already determined beforehand?
It must be like that, right?
Before the show starts we're given the script
It's not like that, master!
This is really suspicious
Like "Matsumoto gives 0 points, Uenuma gives 0 points", that kind of thing
Everyone looks at it beforehand
It's true
Master!
Why, master!?
Must've been decided long ago
It's not like that!
Why do you think that?
5 minutes left on the clock
Impressive
No matter what it is, it all works
Next is the final sprint
Recently there are more and more manzai newcomers joining Manzai Talent Association
It's a good thing
Like Kaminari and such
So apparently big things are about to change
I've heard that this summer Downtown are gonna join Comic Talent Association
Wouldn't that be great?
The atmosphere in the association is quite good now
If changes don't happen, the atmosphere in the association won't improve
But in the end...
But haven't they said they want to disband? Dai-bon Sho-bon
Eh？
Really?
-So i've heard
That XXXXX I went to a party with them
Dai-bon's seniors and XXXXX's relationship seems to not be very good
Relationship with XXXXX is not good either?
Ah?
Didn't XXXXX have an argument with a mentor at the Manzai Newcomer Awards?
Don't say anymore!
Went in a strange direction
Stop it, stop it
Really...
As horror stories about Dai-bon that even he doesn't know begin to come to light
Stop it now!
What's this all about?
The truth is now revealed
I'm really sorry, master, we've actually pranked you
Prank?
This is actually...
Cute
Wednesday Downtown
Eh? But my hair is super messy
I often have messy hair myself
That's not the point
By the way, the number of "heh"s...
You achieved a total of 21
So strong!
I must have an addiction...
The result is
Oozora Yuhei, please be extra careful about getting scammed
Impressive
Finally, the previous lies mentioned Matsumoto and Hamada
Today, sure enough
With Matsumoto on a break currently, it makes all of this look pretty suspicious
With Matsumoto off today,
It looks like Hamada is a scapegoat for a lot of things
What scapegoat? What am I a scapegoat for!
All of this news is probably going to leak in about 2 weeks
Let's welcome the next presenter
Zun's Iio!
Hello everyone in the bend, thank you for having me
Let's get right to it
The agency i'm a part of belongs to an office called Asai Planning
One of the great seniors there is Sekine Tsutomu
What does everyone think of when they think of Sekine
Imitation or something like that
-Indeed
Imagination
-Yes!
Someone who can create imaginative stories
That's right. 15 years ago, I witnessed Yuuka's parents steeped in an illusion
Inside their minds?
So, this time I bring you a theory about Sekine's specific skillset
This is it
There is no successor to Tsutomu Sekine's art of impeccably introducing members of the public
Nostalgic!
We all know the show "It's Okay to Laugh", right?
This is Sekine's swift description when a member of the public is features
He would say something very appropriate to the characteristics of that person
He'll say it instantly
-Right
"Three meals a day, all pasta" or something like that
Yeah, yeah
Very impressive
-Just one sentence
The art of Sekine Tsutomu must not be lost
So this project is to select his successor
Sounds interesting
The 2nd Generation Sekine Tsutomu Tournament!
This time, comedians were asked to try
The art of describing people who appear one after another with a short phrase
Sekine could really do it well
5 extras are randomly selected from a group of 20 people
Is that Hyouroku?
Definitely not
By the way
Thanks for having me
Sekine himself is the judge and will score the contestants' performance out of 10
A true successor
The first challenger is
This is bad, these feet spell something bad
Thank you
I'm looking forward to it
He is really on this show a lot
Audrey's Kasuga, who was also a regular on "It's Okay to Laugh" as the same time as Sekine
You're the first up
Well it makes sense, since I have some experience
I will be the successor to Sekine's style
Is that so
So let's get started
It's hard to watch
So, please welcome the first person
BGM: Hiromi Goh - Oyome Samba
The song!
The music is the same as the original
Visits several fortune tellers in a row before getting the desired answer
It's good
-Good
8 points!
A feeling of sincere yet slightly naive
The kind of person who doesn't express their own opinion that much
This hits the mark perfectly
Let's move on to the next person
Caught a T-shirt thrown out by Hase Hiroshi at a wrestling match
I can't believe he came up with that!
This is good
9 points!
Had a nightmare yesterday
This can be said about anyone!
4 points!
Ah this one isn't good
This "had a nightmare yesterday" is too blunt and thoughtless
Being more specific about the nightmare would be better
For example
Had a dream that all his teeth fell out yesterday
If you put it that way
It would be a 7 or an 8
Expanding on what nightmare it was would be best
Able to beat someone up the first time they meet them
Too much!
-Too sloppy
This one's too much
The person being evaluated will probably feel bad after hearing it so it's not good
It's important to not hurt people's feelings
That's for sure
Because the other party is not in the industry
If it's a comedian then it's fine
But you shouldn't do it to a member of the general public
There are still rules
Only by possessing the quality of consideration
And not hurting the participants can one become the heir to Sekine's style
But Kasuga isn't aware
Husband embezzled a large sum of money
This is a prime example
A public servant in Aomori
Too much!
But it's still kind of interesting
In summary, Kasuga's total score is 32 points
Thank you
Well done
You had some good answers and some not so good answers
I can't believe there's some that weren't good!
It only takes about a second, right?
You only have that amount of time to say something
But your performance is more impressive than I expected
Really?
Can Sekine please say one?
If I were to say one...
The third one is a little on the heavy side
Only the wife's whining and gout cannot be overcome
Not bad for him
-Good
Awesome!
If you just say "suffers from gout," it'll seem a little harsh
It would be too direct
So add a little bit of the wife aspect first
The demonstration of a pioneer
The next challenger is
Thanks for having me
This'll be good
The Great King of Kansai, Laughing Rice's Nishida
Nishida is very interesting
Good-looking face too
Like a person in a Chinese ink painting
Please can the first person enter
Already going!
Always ready. It's a habit
This one is difficult
Still using mixi until now
※mixi：Social media platform established in Japan in 2004
This is a good one
Not trying too hard to be funny is a good approach
Brought back a dog that was completely different from the one that ran away and kept it
Whoa!
She's indeed emitting the aura of regret regarding letting it run away
Beaten by son with a violin
This is no good
Such violence is not allowed
Same person
Offered Chicken McNuggets to the statue of The Buddha Jizo
Differences in food culture
Good!
McNuggets are so effective
The combination of "The Buddha Jizo statue" and "Chicken McNuggets" is great
Massachusetts Institute of Technology
This is great!
Looks good with the glasses and looks like he has a good brain
It's also good that it ended at MIT
Interesting
Despite points lost for having violent elements
He surpasses Kasuga with 36 points
If only he didn't say the violin
The next challenger is
Thank you
Kano Eiko
So, let's have the first one on stage
This MC is a firecracker
An assistant producer on Funny Manga Dojo
Whoa!
I want to score a 10 on this one
But nowadays, young people don't know "Funny Manga Dojo"
※A program broadcast from 1974 to 1994
Therefore 2 points were deducted
In my heart it's 10 points
Installment fees are covered by us
This is a bit of a no-go
5 points
A little underworld hint, right?
So what should you do with scary-looking people
This one is...
Heaving a sigh, was supposed to quit 3 years ago
Who would say such a thing
It's kind of the opposite
Fuji Takashi would certainly laugh at this
Even carefully washes no-wash rice
8 points
She does have that atmosphere of carefully washing rice even if it doesn't need to be
Sells cicada shells for 10 yen
7 points
Raised a cat that immediately ran away
This is 6 points
I'm not really getting the same feeling
In summary, Kano overtook Kasuga with 34 points and reached second
The next challenger is
Thank you
Razor Ramon RG
So, let's have the first one on stage
Often resents blow drying her hair after showering
This one needs a bit more of something
Despite having a person she likes, she won't admit it
This is bad
It's too straightforward
Next,
Loves to wear red clothes in his spare time
Too weak
It's not red, it's burgundy
Too similar
Despite using analogies, Sekine isn't impressed so the score doesn't raise
Next, please
It's actually a centre parting
I think this is good
The phrase "actually is" gives it substance
It's a good one
But the total score is 31 points
And so, he's in last place
More. I want to do it again
I wanna repeat
Wow - dammit - it's too tough
And, the last challenger is...
Naked Eye Lifting 1.0, hello everyone
Zun's Iio, a direct junior and descendant of Sekine's style
If Iio isn't there who else would come?
Let's have the first one on stage
Can't be completely honest two nights a year
Not bad for a guy like you
Whoa!
This "can't be completely honest" is great
And 2 times a year
Baseball team made it to Koshien in the second year of high school
7 points
I've also used this
When the person doesn't have much characteristics that stand out
Just focusing on unrelated events
Didn't just say "Baseball team made it to the Koshien"
So it makes it a bit funnier
There is a shortcut to the park that only he knows
Fantastic!
8 points
This is great
Despite the loneliness... the day after tomorrow, I'll be back home
This is funny
"Despite the loneliness" this
With this emotion at the beginning, you can feel the power of the line
Never had to worry about his children
This is good
Raising children is difficult
And he also has this look of tenderness
In summary, the final results are shown
Iio, with an average score of 8 or more, claims the top spot
Awesome!
Pioneer, Hello Mr. Pioneer
"Can't be completely honest two nights a year"
That's a great one
Oh really, thank you
The person from Cameroon?
Can you do one for them?
For example,
Used to seeing elephants
Worthy of you
In summary
Zun's Iio is decided as the second-generation
Iio is great!
-Thank you. I'm so sorry
I'm sure you've been watching
-I've been watching
But i'm a bit embarrassed to get first place in the VTR
It was great!
What do you think Hamada, 2nd generation, 3rd generation
I think it can be done
I hope some new people will step up
Kawashima, you should too
Join in
I'd like to see it
You're so impressive on "Love it!"
You can take Matsumoto and Sekine's crowns!
Next is "everyone's theories!"
Tonight's presenter is...
Hello everyone
-Jinai Tomonori!
Jin!
-That's right, Jin is here!
Without further ado, do you know about "T-shirt tips"?
Is that the folding method?
-Yes
I saw it on tv
-Yes?
Fold it quickly
Yes, yes, yes, yes
-We're aware
I have a T-shirt here
I will demonstrate a common folding method
Come bird... like this
"Come bird?"
Mr Jin!
-Mr Jin!
Mr Jin's got a screw loose!
No, that's not true. Good job
-Yeah, right
Cute
Here we go, everyone watch this folding method
Here we go. Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, right?
Mr Jin!
Fast, right?
-It's neat
We can often see this on life style programs
-Indeed
But who actually invented this technique?
-Who did?
So, this time, the theory is:
The mysterious origin of the t-shirt folding technique
Ah
-It is mysterious
Who was the first to use it?
Not some guy in a store?
"Some guy in a store"
Excuse me
The store staff member came up with it
Sekine will be angered
They have to finish folding quickly. It can't take long
That may be so
Don't really know
But I haven't seen much of it in stores
-It's true
I've never seen a clothing clerk do it
-Yes.
No one has ever used this method of folding, right?
But this method should be the fastest
The mysterious origin of the t-shirt folding technique
Do you know the tips for folding T-shirts?
Pinch the T-shirt at the seam to fold it?
We all know that
Pick up one side of the T-shirt and the other side and fold it in one go
I've seen pinching the clothes in two places to fold it
Many people have seen such tricks but not tried them
It's true that it's always on TV
90% of the people are vaguely aware
When was it born and how was it popularized by TV programs?
We used the TBS library and web to research
Hard work!
We found it was featured just 8 months ago in August 2021
There is a program that introduces this technique
Very recent
Indeed
It is as follows
Asa
Asa's weather forecast
Do you have clothes that have not been folded yet?
Today i'll introduce you to a quick way to fold clothes
Grab here and here and then do this
It's folded
Old people and 3-year olds get to know about this technique
We continue to investigate
Is it necessary?
On Midday West! in 2021, a former clothing store manager introduced clothes storage tips
How to fold clothes in seconds was introduced
It was also featured on TV Tokyo's 2020 "Seven Colors Perfect Day!"
2 years ago
The presenter marked symbols on T-shirts
Are carefully described the method
That method
In recent years, this has been featured in morning and afternoon lifestyle programs
In 2020 it also appeared on a variety show
Super convenient 2 seconds to fold clothes trick
This voice is Iio
This method was introduced by cleaning professionals on TBS "Papa Johnnys WEST"
2 seconds from the time I pick it up
What happened
Young people don't know?
Awesome
Although times change, young people can still be impressed in 2020
This shows the importance of constant reintroduction
We continued to review earlier programs
And found 23 programs since 2010
Around 2010, lifestyle programs were a big hit
A piece of cardboard, you put it on, you fold it, fold it again
Fold this way, then this way
Ridiculous tricks like folding clothes with cardboard
A variety of T-shirt folding tips crowded TV  at the time
However, as we continued our investigation
More and more clothes
Murakami mother and son's super fast T-shirt folding method
It stopped at 2009's "Fast Life Guide SHOW"
The folding method that was introduced every year suddenly disappeared from earlier programs
Until we discovered it again 4 years prior in 2005
More?
The originator of lifestyle programs, "The Ito Family's Table"
Ah the Ito Family
After appearing in 2003, it became the No.1 tip of the year
And even appeared on the show 3 times in one year
And there was no show that introduced the folding method earlier than this program
So, the trick was introduced by this program
Therefore, it this it's origin?
We interviewed the chief director of the program at the time, Amamiya
Did your program come up with this folding method?
Yes
This little trick was invented by our program team
As expected, the "Ito family" is the source of the trick
Independently developed eh?
At that time, a housewife wrote to introduce the technique of folding bed sheets
We thought this technique was good
But thought whether we could change the object to something else to make it more useful
At that time I was in the midst of T-shirt collection mania, I had probably over 200 of them
This inspired determining whether it could be modified for t-shirts
That's how it came about
So, the origin of that folding method was about 19 years ago
It came from a program!
It aired on August 26th 2003
Do you usually use this folding method?
I always roll up my T-shirt
I have too many T-shirts so they can only be rolled up otherwise its impossible to store them all
I can't believe I'm not using it!
My home is too small, they can only be rolled up for storage
Thus reveals Amamiya's status as a member of the Rolling School
A professional father will not use this method
Usually no one uses it
Yeah...
What!?
Scary, a sudden appearance!
Drug Screening
Thank you for your hard work
-Hello
What is this?
I have a few spare clothes with me
Bringing clean clothes?
Yes, I keep them on hand to change
A technique appears!
A standing fold
A man who usually has no concern for storage casually uses this method
The origin is the Ito family, whereas it's only user is the Kuro family
Kuro family
-An unexpected development
That's awesome
-It is, isn't it?
When the staff investigated, it found that, aside from Kuro-chan
Kotouge and Zakoshi both use it
Baldies love to use this trick
Seriously!
It should be called "the bald people folding method"
Only bald people fold clothes like this
What was up with the violent cardboard method
I can't believe they use cardboard boxes
Didn't you see the cheers in the studio?
The Age of Peace
-Bubble era?
A crazy era in which folded clothes can be an event
Those people don't fold clothes like that at home
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03