THIS PROGRAM WAS PRODUCED
UNDER THE SUPERVISION OF MEDICAL EXPERTS,
TAKING INTO CONSIDERATION THE HEALTH
AND SAFETY OF THE STAFF AND CONTESTANTS.
Charge!
Takeshi's Castle has been revived
after 34 years.
The exploits of the deadly attacking army
have been full of laughter
and tears,
as well as other strange emotions.
It's been a spectacle
of great proportions.
I made it!
I will destroy you!
Takeshi's army fought like demons
on the defense
and kicked the attacking army
to the ground.
There you go!
THE COUNT
BEAT TAKESHI
And Takeshi, the count,
has reappeared after 34 years.
What are you doing, stupid?
I'm not some singer with a flashy costume.
The attacking force is
plotting the fall of Takeshi's Castle.
The story is about to reach its climax.
ARMY VS TAKESHI
The final chapter of Takeshi's Castle
is about to begin!
TAKESHI'S CASTLE
THE COUNT'S TOWER
Count, we have the Devil's Domain next.
-It's so nostalgic.
-You remember it very well.
This game has been made
more difficult, too.
I'll show you how hard it's become.
Let's watch!
-There's the film director.
-The film director?
I need to say hello to him.
NAOMASA MUSAKA
Director, good morning.
Thank you for having me here today.
Good morning!
What is Mr. Musaka doing?
The attacking army has been advancing
in two separate directions.
There are 60 survivors.
Twenty-seven of them
will take on the Devil's Domain.
You have done well, my elites.
Now you will take on
the Super Devil's Domain.
-Wow. It's rotating.
-Yeah.
-What's that?
-Not many of us are left now.
You can do this. Good luck! All right?
Oh, no! Not good! This door won't open!
SUPER DEVIL'S DOMAIN
DIFFICULTY RATING: 126%
This is the Devil's Domain.
There are devils lurking inside.
-Also, look! It's become harder.
-What?
It's rotating!
It's rotating.
You'll never know which way to go.
-Let me tell you again.
-No need!
-We're gonna crush them, got it?
-Yes!
Hey, you! Don't let anyone through!
HIROOKI GOTO - JUSHIN LIGER
NATSUKO TOURA
I won't let you through.
Just see if you can get past.
-Right!
-Don't get smart with me!
The Devil's Domain, which caused a fury
at Ueda Castle,
has become much harder
with the addition of a rotating maze.
Once you get in there, you won't know
which is the way to the goal.
I'm YoYo and I'm hyper,
so I'll run straight through!
Charge!
They're standing on top.
No fair. They can see where you are
from there.
They'll find you.
-You need to run fast.
-Yeah.
-She made herself fall. I see.
-That's how it works.
She dug herself into a hole.
He's laughing.
Looks like he's having fun.
Charge!
Good luck!
MASATO YOSHIHARA (28)
It's time to show you what we've got.
Yeah. Please show it to us.
START - GOAL
Get him!
THE FOURTH STRONGHOLD
SUPER DEVIL'S DOMAIN
NINJAS ON TOP ATTACK THROW WATER BALLOONS
-He escaped.
-He's fast.
-They've got him.
-Run! He couldn't.
On his good-looking face.
They're ganging up on him.
No need to throw him like that!
-It's so rough.
-But the way they throw him is funny.
It is.
HAVE YOU WATCHED TAKESHI'S CASTLE?
Yes, since I was a child.
I really enjoyed watching it
with my family.
Erica is from Spain and loves cosplay.
It says "Foreign Five," but it has become
"Foreign One" now.
Charge!
Good luck!
-I don't think anyone can make it.
-Right.
SUPPORT ENGINEER, SPAIN
ERICA MARTINEZ, 30
Get her!
GOAL
-I fell!
-Oh, no!
So close.
Erica from Spain...
-She did well at avoiding them.
-Nearly there!
-If it had rotated a bit more...
-Exactly!
If she had opened the next door,
she'd have reached the goal.
Almost there!
If only you'd opened the door
a few seconds later.
-I chose the wrong door.
-What a shame.
In Super Devil's Domain,
apart from the rotating maze...
DEVIL #1, 2, 3, 4 - UNCLE MUSAKA
PARKOUR NINJA #1, 2
... there also are more devils
chasing the challengers.
WORLD RANKING BEACH TENNIS PLAYER
NAOAKI YAMAMOTO (32)
Many challengers are caught
right at the start.
So many of them!
Will anyone be able to reach the goal?
This is a very unreasonable game.
POLE CHAMPION
KEIKO TAKEMOTO
I feel like I've been
in a dream world all this time.
Maejima has loved Takeshi's Castle
for 18 years.
TAKESHI'S CASTLE
HISTORY MUSEUM
He runs a website with all kinds
of information on Takeshi's Castle.
There's lots of data
on the Devil's Domain.
He's well prepared.
I'll conquer the Devil's Domain...
It gets out of control.
I'll turn the sound on when I shoot it.
Sure.
-He's a rabid fan.
-Yeah.
He's a Takeshi's Castle fanatic.
It's not like that!
What is he doing?
SATOSHI MAEJIMA (35)
-That's Toka's gag.
-I see.
Toka's gag...
-He knows which way to go.
-He's prepared.
He runs through strategically.
-Look for him!
-Go, go!
GOAL
He did it!
What?
Fantastic!
DEVIL'S EYE VIEW
Look for him!
-Did he clear that?
-The devils were just behind him, though.
-Amazing!
-Did I clear it? Did I?
Maejima displayed surprising agility
and escaped from the devils.
You cleared it, no doubt!
-Great job!
-I did it!
He is a rabid fan.
I did it!
I'm such a big fan of Takeshi's Castle
and wanted to clear no matter what.
-I'm so glad I survived. I did it!
-Congrats!
If I clear this,
I'll get a free beef dinner.
-Who will buy it?
-I'll get Peking duck.
Barbecue for me.
We'll get the rest of them!
Charge!
Good luck!
Here I am in Takeshi's Castle!
I'll do my best!
MIYUKO ISAKA (21)
I've got you! I'm the one who got you!
Already?
I got her!
No!
-Why is he there?
-Oh, no!
-All right. Here!
-That's too bad.
That's too bad.
The remaining members
of the Female College Student Team
were caught instantly.
They won't get a nice dinner, after all.
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
EVE HANIUDA (22)
-I bumped into Mr. Musaka right away.
-Did he get you?
"I got her!"
So sweet.
Here he comes.
Kasuga, do you have any plans?
-Any plans?
-Yes.
I just need to get through.
I just need to go from here to there.
Toos!
Kasuga betrayed Takeshi's army
and joined the attacking army,
but failed to live up to expectations.
Will he be able
to perform better this time?
Good luck!
Looks great. It's a nice house.
Let's visit this house.
Super Devil's Domain.
Please let me in. Toos!
All right.
-What was that?
-I hope he clears at least one game.
It's like my own TV program
where I visit houses.
COMIC, AUDREY
TOSHIAKI KASUGA (43)
-Hey...
-He closed the door. Run!
The devils are gathering.
Run away! Run!
What? Is he running away?
They've got him.
Get him!
Let me go!
Don't move!
They've got him.
This is Kasuga's
fourth consecutive failure.
Now he'll be kicked out of
Takeshi's Castle after being of no help.
Get out!
He was airborne.
This is what a traitor gets, stupid!
Kasuga! Just float there forever!
You were calm at first,
then you were running like this.
FAILED
Well...
I had no chance at all...
So far, the only survivor is Maejima,
a rabid Takeshi's Castle fan.
HIROAKI SHINGA (62)
Will this be the end of the elites,
despite what they've already been through?
IDOL
SHION IIZUKA (23)
-She's gonna fall!
-Oh, no!
TOKYO ENGEKI JOSHI
YUI CHITOSE (23)
Oh my gosh! I look so ugly!
AJ ERENDS
HARUNA FUJITAKA
JULIANA NO TATARI, LEADER
AYU ENATSU (36)
BEACH TENNIS PLAYER
KEITA ISEKI
POLE CHAMPION
KEIKO TAKEMOTO
RADIOLOGIST
TOSHIHIRO MATSUMOTO
I feel fantastic!
There you go!
The last challenger
from the attacking army is...
It's him.
Yamaguchi, a super high school student
who has cleared all the games so far.
He's a keen runner who became
the Nagano champion in the 100 meters
when he was in his third year
of junior high school.
-Are you enjoying Takeshi's Castle?
-Very much.
It's the most fun
I've ever had in my life.
Really?
Charge! I'm counting on you!
Let's go!
HARU YAMAGUCHI (16)
Haru! Haru!
HARU'S FATHER
MINORU
GOAL
There!
-He's fast!
-This way!
Awesome!
Wow! He did it!
-Haru! Haru!
-There!
-There he is! This way!
-He's fast!
He's so young.
-What was that?
-Others would just fall once outside.
He's amazing!
What? Blow the whistle?
I did it!
This high school student got through
the maze in only eight seconds.
He has now cleared the sixth stronghold!
It seemed like you jumped at an angle.
I thought they would catch me
if I went back.
The devils were right behind me,
so I jumped.
-You cleared it beautifully! Congrats!
-Thank you!
I did it!
In Super Devil's Domain,
the attacking army did very well.
Two challengers survived.
TWO SURVIVORS
-Please let me play this character again.
-Sure.
-I'll reject other offers.
-Thank you.
Count, I'll be back.
Thank you for having me today.
The battle against Count Takeshi
is almost here.
Do your best to advance!
What was Mr. Musaka doing here?
Because I asked him
to come to Mt. Midoriyama,
maybe he thought this was a film shoot.
He thought this was an acting job?
Yeah. Isn't he having a big fight
with his agent right now?
Next, we have
The Bridge Over the Battlefield.
This one has become much harder, too.
Let's take a look!
SUPER BRIDGE OVER THE BATTLEFIELD
DIFFICULTY RATING: 142%
The bar is on a rampage in this game.
This time, this man is the one in charge.
COMIC
EIKO KANO
To say the least,
the whole reason I got into showbiz
was to use that bar.
It will be the culmination
of my entire 20-year career
to perform with that bar.
What does that bar mean to you, Eiko Kano?
It's my family.
So hot!
You surprised me!
-You got me!
-It's done.
My back feels so hot.
You have done well, my elites.
This is Super Bridge over the Battlefield.
-Isn't it really high?
-Yes, it is.
It's a tough one,
but I believe you can do it. Go for it.
Charge!
General Tani is so energetic. "Charge!"
This is Super Bridge Over the Battlefield.
It's nicely lit.
-We don't know how it got super hard.
-It's very high.
But we'll be super hyper, too!
-Thank you.
-You aren't very excited.
Charge!
-Let me try. Thank you!
-Good luck!
ATHLETE
YUME MOSES (34)
He's so fast.
He went down.
-It's quite high.
-It is.
Aren't you going too fast?
Didn't he go too fast?
In this game, you need to line up
the "Bingo" triangle with the surfboard.
Yume Moses went way past the finish line.
This team with an average age
of 50 have gone all out.
The Hibiya Club
takes on the challenge next.
Are you still up for it?
-We're tenacious.
-Yes, we are.
That's the only good thing about us.
We'll try our best!
Charge!
I'll try my best!
HIBIYA CLUB
TOSHITAKA HOSOI (55)
Good luck!
Too weak.
What?
You should've pulled back the bar, Kano!
This is so uncool.
You need to push yourself much harder!
Kano also knocks them down.
That was so uncool.
Are you really up for this?
Let him move farther down!
Charge!
I'll try my best!
It's a girl.
Maybe I'll let her go through.
NURSE
EMIKO KANNO
Is she getting close?
No.
PRO WRESTLER
JUSHIN LIGER
-Do you want to finish the game?
-I'm scared!
-Do you? No, you can't.
-Stop it!
-Wow. That's dangerous!
-It's so high.
Charge!
I'll make a miracle happen!
ROCKET NEWS 24 WRITER
MASANUKI SUNAKOMA (41)
PRO WRESTLER
TOGI MAKABE
What are you doing?
Next, MANARUTAI, a comedy video creator
with one million subscribers,
takes up the challenge
for the attacking army.
Hey! Don't throw my luggage!
-This is why we set up MANARUTAI.
-Yeah.
For this reason, we attracted
one million subscribers.
-We'll make sure we all will clear it.
-Yeah, do it well!
No one can escape my bar!
Come on!
We've got one million subscribers!
Charge!
MANARUTAI - TAKKA
What?
There? He pushes you over there?
It's Makabe.
There you go!
Both Dai and Keita failed miserably.
COMEDY VIDEO CREATOR
MANARUTAI - DAI
-Do you want me to push you back?
-Yes, please!
-Since you're so close...
-Sure. Please!
No way, stupid!
COMEDY VIDEO CREATOR
MANARUTAI - KEITA
No one in the attacking army has cleared.
How about a Sasuke finalist?
Charge!
I'll make a miracle happen!
SASUKE FINALIST
TOMOHIRO KAWAGUCHI (40)
Please don't... Yes, yes.
Please! Yes, right there!
You've crossed it!
-Did I cross it?
-Yes, yes. No, go forward!
-No! A little bit this way!
-What?
-What are you doing?
If you push too hard, you'll fall.
Charge!
I'll stop right there!
BUSINESS OWNER
TOMOYA NAKAMURA (45)
He went through.
-He can't make it.
-He's good!
-He will make it!
-Looks good!
Is that okay?
NAKAMURA'S SON
TOMOKI
He made it?
-So close!
-He did it?
What?
-Almost there.
-That should be okay.
Only this far away.
-What?
-What shall we do? Shall we push him back?
Push him back!
Shall I?
Okay! Okay!
Okay, fall now!
-What?
-No way!
That's too harsh!
-Too harsh!
-Why?
Just that by much? He failed?
Isn't that acceptable?
How hard does it have to be?
Since he touched the bar a little,
he had a very good speed.
-I see.
-That bar was actually good.
Isn't this acceptable?
This is all right.
It's not acceptable to have to be
lined up perfectly in this game!
That will never happen!
Is Takeshi's Castle that unreasonable?
-You shouldn't say that.
-But enjoy yourself.
Sure. I'm happy.
-Well done! Thank you!
-Thanks!
No one in the attacking army
has cleared so far.
Will there be anyone who can stop
at the perfect spot and clear the game?
ACROBATIC VIDEO CREATOR
AUN - KANTA
GRAD STUDENT
DÁITHI Ó HAODHA
Takeshi! We want your head!
-Give me a wedding present!
-Fall down!
SPARTAN RACER
RYUTARO AIHARA
Come on, baby!
STUDENT
RYOTA YOSHIDA
Thank you!
KAWASAKI ELEMENTARY SCHOOL TEACHER
KOTA SAKUMA (29)
It doesn't matter to me!
ALBERTO DE CELIS ROMERO
All right.
HIBIYA CLUB
TETSUYA NIKI (38)
They're mean!
DANCER
AKINKO (32)
Let's see a miracle.
The miracle is in my hands.
Good luck!
The last challenger is Mayaya, who's been
looking for love in Takeshi's Castle.
-She's been looking for a boyfriend.
-I see.
God of romance, bless me with love!
Charge! Good luck!
I'm Mayaya! I'll get only "bingo"!
DANCE DUO
MAYAYA (35)
Mayaya. What's gonna happen?
-She slowed down a little.
-Yeah.
She can't make it.
Please! I'm sorry!
-You're quite far from the finish line.
-Wait! You're such a handsome guy.
-Me?
-Yes.
You think so?
-He has a mask.
-I like you a lot!
-Really?
-Sorry, no!
Please stop it. Please!
-I like you so much!
-Is he adjusting it?
No, mister!
Are you deeply in love with me?
I love you from the bottom of my heart!
She said she loves me!
It can't be true.
They just met a second ago.
Mister, please stop. Be nice to me.
Is it a "bingo"?
Let me see what a winner sees.
-Okay!
-Ready?
Bingo!
What? Really?
Did she clear it? She did it!
She cleared it?
Just like that?
Bingo!
If she cleared,
then so did that guy earlier.
Bingo!
Mayaya stopped farther
from the finish line.
Somehow she talked Liger into it
and she cleared the game!
What's going on?
I'd never said "I love you"
to anyone in my life.
It was your first time?
I said "I love you" for the first time.
You did?
You're saying he's the one for you, then?
Yes, he is. I'll marry him!
-Really? Congratulations!
-What is this?
Thank you!
What is going on?
ONE SURVIVOR
She's the only one who survived.
The challengers are being wiped out
one after another in these fierce battles.
Will anyone make it
to the battle against Count Takeshi?
-Count, how was it?
-What was that?
Why did she call him a handsome man?
She can't tell if he is.
He wears a mask. But it was a tough game.
-It has to be perfect.
-No chance.
-Shouldn't we have a bonus area?
-Yes.
We should've let the first guy
go through instead.
It was a tough game. But now we know
that kind of thing happens.
-I see.
-For your information.
-So if you beg for it, you might clear it.
-What kind of game is that?
The next game is also controversial.
Loser Resurrection.
-Let's have a look.
-Okay.
It's the final battle of Takeshi's Castle.
Only two strongholds remain.
To increase the forces to bring down
the main castle,
a Loser Resurrection took place.
I don't want Takeshi's Castle to end.
After being together for such a long time
every day,
I've grown very fond of you all
and I'm already sad to say goodbye.
We'll be shooting shortly.
God, I'm so nervous!
At this new stronghold, 50 people will try
to return to the front line.
MUDDY SPLASH
DAISUKE SHIBA
In this muddy pond,
there are these capsules.
If you open them,
-you'll find "Win."
-Or "Lose."
They are Mogrider.
-Who will win?
-Who will it be? Good luck!
-Muddy Splash.
-Start!
Go, go!
If you find a capsule with a "Win" note,
you'll return to the front line.
FIND A CAPSULE IN THE MUD
AND BRING IT TO MOGRIDER
He's fast.
-He's got it.
-The capsules are hard to find.
All right!
You need to bring it to him.
THE FIRST 30 PEOPLE TO FIND ONE
RETURN TO THE FRONT LINE
Only 30 people.
-I've got it. It says "Win"!
-Hurry!
It does?
Yes!
RETURN TO THE FRONT
Already?
It says "Lose"!
-"Lose."
-You can go back if you don't get a "Win."
-There must be a lot of capsules.
-It's great.
She did it!
You did it!
You need to get a note that says "Win"
from the muddy pond.
Only those lucky few can go back
to the front line.
That is this game, Muddy Splash!
-It says "Lose."
-Damn it!
It says "Lose."
Our staff just want them to get dirty.
-"Win"!
-Yeah!
He did it. There he goes.
He's a Sasuke member.
-Please!
-It's "Lose."
It's "Lose."
NURSE
EMIKO KANNO
BOYS AND MEN
YUKIHISA TAMURA (31)
Wow. We can't see his face.
I did it!
RETURN TO THE FRONT
Getting muddy is fantastic!
-We all did it!
-We did it!
I did it!
RETURN TO THE FRONT
There is a long line
to wait for the judgment.
All you can do is hope
you get your turn before other winners.
Even waiting in line, you'll lose
if 30 people get through first.
-Hurry!
-Five more!
Hurry up!
Only a few more will get through
to the next stronghold.
FIVE MORE PEOPLE
I watched you on Sasuke
when I was in junior high school.
Sorry, Mr. Yamamoto. It's "Lose."
Hurry up!
-Hurry up! Come on!
-It's Cherry.
Cherry, shut up!
Not many left.
TWO MORE PEOPLE
-I don't want to lose.
-This one's a "Lose."
I know you don't wanna lose.
ONE MORE PERSON
-It's over!
-Is it?
They've counted 30 people.
I had this one, though...
FAILED
I wish he could've read it out quicker.
He was talking nonsense.
He's so right.
You were too slow.
Oh, dear... He's being attacked. Oh, no.
They took Shiba...
But I'm a successful comedian!
It doesn't matter, stupid!
Because you work too slow,
we couldn't get our turn.
You're talking nonsense!
It's "Lose."
MASATO YOSHIHARA (28)
I have no luck!
HIBIYA CLUB
YOSHIO YODA (60)
I didn't make it.
It's "Win!" Damn it!
SASUKE
TOMOHIRO KAWAGUCHI (40)
It was "Win!"
Mogrider was angrily retaliated against
by the eliminated members
and, along with a pin microphone,
were covered in mud.
Is the pin microphone okay?
-No. It's broken.
-I see.
It's bad, right? I'm not sure, though.
So, 30 people returned to the front line
from the mud.
The final battle is almost here.
30 people have returned.
The attacking army has succeeded
in bringing challengers back.
There're two more strongholds left.
Go for it, challengers!
Are there more challengers
who returned to the front line?
So many chances in Loser Resurrection.
Many losers are back, too.
-It's like... in Asakusa.
-Asakusa's...
There were more and more people
until it grew to over 20,000.
Like going back to wait in line?
Shiba from Mogrider
was pushed into the mud afterwards.
I think it broke a pin microphone
and he was told off.
That's different from the old comedians.
The old ones would say, "Stop it!"
while taking off their microphones.
-"Stop it, stop it!" and remove it.
-Right.
While shouting "Stop it,"
they wound it up and gave it to the staff.
They even wound it up?
The attacking army is just one battle away
from a showdown with Takeshi.
You have done well, my elites.
Look at the game behind you.
It's Super Strong Arms.
We also have From Right and Left.
I believe you can do it.
Good luck. All right?
SUPER STRONG ARMS AND FROM RIGHT AND LEFT
DIFFICULTY RATING: 120%
I won't let anyone through.
Remember that! I have three!
MOGRIDER
DAISUKE SHIBA AND TOMOSHIGE
-And four!
-I'm scared.
COMEDIAN
YOSHIAKI UMEGAKI
-Is that Umegaki?
-Yes.
MR. SHACHIHOKO
-She's a big name.
-All right!
-Is he Shachihoko?
-Leave it to Takeshi's Castle!
-Ms. Akko?
-Akiko Wada?
She's here, too?
COMEDIAN
KOUME DAYU
It's Koume!
-Damn it!
-It's Koume.
What's happening?
-Awesome!
-Look at them!
Three men dressed as women.
Two tough games have been combined.
Only one challenger has cleared
From Right and Left so far.
It's the toughest game yet.
The attacking army has reached the climax
of the battle against Takeshi's army.
Only challengers who clear this game
will go through to the finale battle.
How will the challengers do?
The first challenger is from
acrobatic video creator group AUN,
who have put on quite a show so far.
I will conquer this!
ACROBATIC VIDEO CREATORS
AUN
Kanta is the only one in the group
who has survived.
With the skills that got him
through Strong Arms so beautifully,
will he be the first one
to clear this game?
Charge! Good luck!
-Wait for me, Takeshi!
-Okay!
Kanta! Kanta!
THE SIXTH STRONGHOLD
SUPER STRONG ARM AND FROM RIGHT AND LEFT
CROSS THE WOBBLY BRIDGE
WHILE DODGING THE BARS
He made it through!
ACROBATIC VIDEO CREATOR
AUN - KANTA
Fantastic!
He did it!
Great! You did it!
Our first challenger
has cleared Strong Arms.
Next, he takes on From Right and Left,
which only one person has cleared.
SUPER STRONG ARM AND FROM RIGHT AND LEFT
MR. SHACHIHOKO SPRAYS THEM
WITH THE BUBBLE MACHINE
CROSS THE WOBBLY FABRIC BRIDGE
WHILE DODGING THE BARS
You can do it!
KOUME DAYU CONTROLS THE BARS
-He's gonna make it.
-Incredible! Almost there!
Keep going! Go!
-Fantastic!
-I did it!
Amazing!
Yeah.
He did it! Great!
What? He did it.
Oh, no! Damn it!
The first challenger, Kanta,
cleared this tough game beautifully.
He conquered the wobbly fabric bridge.
He dodged the last bar well.
He will go to the final battle.
A job well done!
You idiot! You let the first challenger
clear the game!
Make sure you don't
let anyone else through!
ADDITIONAL RULE
In anger, Takeshi's Castle has activated
an additional rule.
All right! I'll change
the direction of rotation.
CLOCKWISE
COUNTER-CLOCKWISE
There you go!
Umegaki has changed
the center bar's direction of rotation.
This increases
the rate of failure to 150%.
What will happen to the attacking army?
Wait! The direction has changed.
-What?
-That's not fair!
What is this?
-You're kidding!
-That's tough.
I wanted to learn from him,
but they've changed the direction.
Takeshi's Castle is scary.
Charge!
I believe in myself and try my best!
IDOL CAFE WAITRESS
YOYO
No! It's so scary!
No!
I want to clear this and
bring down Takeshi's Castle.
A super high school student,
Haru Yamaguchi,
has cleared all games so far.
Will he be able to clear this
and go through to Yabusame again?
I'll change the direction again!
See if you can make it.
Now all the bars are rotating clockwise.
It has reached maximum difficulty.
DIFFICULTY RATING: MAX 200%
Their rotation has been changed
to go that way.
HARU'S FATHER
MINORU
-It's true.
-Oh my gosh. The rotation!
No one noticed.
-It's the right level.
-Is it?
It's just right for Haru.
-What a dad.
-It's right for him.
Let's go!
Haru! Haru!
HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
HARU YAMAGUCHI (16)
-Oh, no.
-Seriously?
-Even Haru couldn't...
-He couldn't?
Even our super high school student
couldn't clear this unreasonable game.
Haru has been eliminated.
FAILED
What's your goal for Takeshi's Castle?
My goal is to bring down Takeshi's Castle
and break it down!
Crush it!
Charge!
I'm Mayaya!
Kiss, kiss, and cheese. I'll do my best!
Mayaya the goddess! Mayaya the goddess!
DANCE DUO
MAYAYA (35)
What?
-I thought...
-What was that?
FAILED
Come try the Takeshi's Castle dance!
Takeshi is up!
They're all in a trance.
Good luck!
-Looks fun.
-Go for it.
Marina Takewaki,
a home exercise video creator
with over three million subscribers,
takes on the challenge next.
-Over three million?
-That's amazing.
She looks hopeful.
I'll try my best!
-Go for it!
-She looks great!
Marina! Marina!
Takewaki, what will happen?
HOME EXERCISE VIDEO CREATOR
MARINA TAKEWAKI (33)
This set is huge!
She can go through there.
If you stop there, it pushes you.
See, she got pushed.
Watch out.
I'm scared!
What will she do now?
-Maybe climb over the top?
-Watch out!
-She almost fell.
-It's a miracle.
That was so close.
Okay!
She couldn't hold on.
-So close!
-It's tough.
The queen of home exercise,
Marina Takewaki, showed excellent balance.
She couldn't get over the third bar
and sadly failed.
-I'm gutted.
-I bet.
-I'll do more exercises.
-You will?
I need stronger legs
to be able to jump over the bar.
If you'd jumped bit more,
it would have been different.
Right. I need stronger legs.
Don't give up during this tough game.
Onwards!
Charge!
CHARGE!
IT COMPANY PRESIDENT
YASUYUKI HATTORI (46)
ENGLISH TEACHER, VENEZUELA
GABRIEL FLORES (30)
EX-JAPANESE NATIONAL FOOTBALL TEAM PLAYER
RAIMU SENGOKU (25)
Grandpa! Grandpa!
TAKESHI'S CASTLE MUSEUM DIRECTOR
SATOSHI MAEJIMA
Tell me how you got through it.
Let's go!
HIBIYA CLUB
IPPEI SUYAMA
SUPPORT ENGINEER
ERICA MARTINEZ (30)
MAYAYA - CHIITAN
Next, Team Sasuke, which has conquered
various strongholds so far,
will take up the challenge.
Well done! You don't have
to spread your legs so much.
Will one of them be
the second person to clear after Kanta?
I will clear this for sure!
DOMINATED SASUKE TWICE
YUJI URUSHIHARA (43)
This is dangerous!
Why?
-How did that happen?
-He couldn't see it.
-It's coming down from above.
-That's good.
-He did it.
-One more!
-He made it.
-Well done.
-He's good, as expected.
Keep going!
I'll take you down.
Hello!
-This is hard.
-But it's fun.
It's that wobbly fabric bridge
you need to cross.
Look at those bubbles.
Go!
Wow! Great!
Waiting between the gaps
is a good strategy.
Watch out!
-Watch out!
-Oh, no!
I guess...
No mercy.
Bars hit your face from all sides.
As expected from a Sasuke team member,
even as he was pushed down, he persisted.
He reached the halfway point
of the very difficult From Right and Left.
Almost there.
He was good.
The most hopeful Sasuke member,
Morimoto, also known as Sasuke Jr.,
failed miserably.
SASUKE JR.
YUSUKE MORIMOTO
Even the finalist, Mr. Hioki
couldn't clear
this extremely difficult stronghold.
KITAGAWA ELECTRONICS, STORE MANAGER
MASASHI HIOKI (41)
Why did you fall?
Were you listening to it?
The nastiness of Takeshi's Castle
has gotten to me.
It was tough.
Next, parkour athlete Sato
will take on the challenge.
I'll be careful this time
since the final battle rests on this.
Show us how cool parkour athletes can be.
Indeed!
I'll make sure I get to the end.
CHAIRMAN OF PARKOUR ASSOCIATION
JUN SATO (30)
Good luck!
-Good!
-That's a good idea.
Watch out, it's coming!
Watch your head.
Come on!
All right! Let's go!
-Stay calm.
-I hope he wins this game.
Go for it!
Keep going!
There he goes.
You'll lose your balance!
What's he doing?
Oh, it's him shooting the bubbles.
Go!
Watch out! All right!
That's a narrow gap.
Oh, no!
-Keep going!
-You can do it!
Oh, no! Look!
He's using the gap.
The length of each gap is different.
It's a miracle.
He took it on his shoulder.
What will he do now?
He didn't make it.
No mercy. He's spraying water on him.
He must be gutted.
-On a wobbly soft fabric bridge...
-He couldn't make it.
Sato, a parkour athlete,
displayed excellent balance.
-It's amazing.
-Yes.
-But it got so wobbly afterwards.
-Yeah.
He was given the Fighting Spirit Award
for his effort getting close to the goal.
It's hard to be hit in the face.
The last challengers are
from the Female College Student Team.
They've fought in all the battles
but haven't cleared any games.
They've managed to survive,
earning them a Fighting Spirit Award.
CAN THEY MAKE IT TO YABUSAME
BY WINNING THEIR FIRST GAME?
I got her!
Since we've come all this way,
we need to go through to the final.
We'll do our best!
Good luck!
All right, they're cute.
I'll give them a special treat.
I'll let them rotate counterclockwise.
Now, the third bar
rotates counter-clockwise,
making the game easier, since the girls
don't need to jump over them.
How lucky for them.
I don't wanna make my teammates cry.
Katomiri! Katomiri!
FEMALE COLLEGE STUDENT TEAM
MIRI KATO (21)
-It's dangerous.
-Everyone fails here.
-It's hard to see.
Yes. Then the bar pushes you.
It pushed her butt.
The bar pushed her butt.
FAILED
Isaka is the second challenger
from their team.
She made it to From Right and Left,
but she fell into the water right away.
The last challenger is Haniuda.
Good luck, Eve!
It's Eve.
EVE HANIUDA (22)
-That's good, she's following the bars.
-She'll be fine.
She can do it.
-It's a good idea to follow the bar.
-Yeah.
-Not good.
-She'd better wait a bit.
She's doing great.
Keep going. Well done.
Push the button. Go!
Go for it!
-It's Akko!
-"It's Akko," he says.
She stops in between them.
That gap is narrow.
Watch out.
She's doing well.
That's good.
-She's slim. She can get in there.
-Yeah.
-All right.
-Will she make it?
Watch out!
Will she make it? She will!
She will do it.
-There's a big bar, sometimes.
-Yeah.
-She did it!
-She made it.
Fantastic!
-Did she make it?
-Did she?
Did I do it?
Nice job!
Haniuda moved
without shaking the bridge at all.
She successfully completed
a super version of the game
that Team Sasuke's members could not!
Incredible! Even Team Sasuke
failed at this game.
-Great job!
-That was excellent.
-Thank you very much!
-We really wanted someone to clear it.
-I'm so happy!
-Thank you.
-Thanks for the energy.
-Sure.
-Do your best again! Good luck!
-Yes!
You did it!
Two challengers cleared the game.
Along with Sato,
the Fighting Spirit Award winner,
they will go to the final battle.
THREE SURVIVORS
Three of them went through.
-Three?
-Yes.
-People are still surviving?
-Because we made the game a bit easier.
-Yes.
-It was a tough game.
-Yeah.
Now, Count!
-It's time for the final battle, at last.
-All right!
We would like to ask you
to join the fight and take them out!
-How about that?
-What?
-Can't you?
-Don't be silly. I'm over 75 years old.
Aren't you gonna fight?
-We'd like you to join us.
-Yes.
For this occasion, I have...
That's what modern technology is for.
I've got someone else ready.
I wanted you to fight them yourself,
but I hear you have an amazing helper.
We'll go there, for now.
-Let's go.
-Who's the helper?
-We'll go, now.
-Let's go.
Let's bring them down.
-We've finally come here.
-At last!
We did it!
What'll I do?
It's different and I feel the tension
in the air. It's nice, though.
It feels like the final battle.
The parkour athletes
will get on a machine at the end.
Like "I'll be right back."
It's probably not the most suited to him.
Captain Kimura has joined the army, now.
The fighting spirit of the attacking army
is at its strongest.
You might have good luck, right?
I can't wait to see this.
At last, it's time
for the very final battle.
All right!
The attacking army?
Hayato Tani and Subaru Kimura!
We'll bring you down instead!
Come and get us!
-Wait and see!
-Yes!
For such an important stage of the battle,
did you think I hadn't prepared anything?
-What?
All right.
Now we'll find out
what Count Takeshi has prepared.
TENSHIN NASUKAWA
Fantastic!
How about that?
He's your opponent. Surprised?
It's Tenshin Nasukawa!
-Here he comes!
-What an amazing helper we have!
-We've got a real tough guy.
-I know!
-All right!
-Nice to meet you.
Right this way.
-Thank you.
-Welcome, Mr. Tenshin Nasukawa!
-Thank you!
We have an amazing guy!
What made you come here today?
Mr. Takeshi told me
it'll be the match of the century.
Did he say that?
Yes. He asked me to win it.
That's why I came here.
-You're the man for a big fight.
-Sure.
-He's so reliable.
-Because he's the strongest man.
-Yes, he is.
-Sure.
-So great.
-Count!
-Were you surprised?
-There was more to it than that.
-He'll be a fierce attacker.
-Of course.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
-I'm counting on you, boy!
-Thank you!
-"Boy."
-Thanks. I'll do this for Mr. Takeshi.
-General Tani!
-Yes!
We have Tenshin Nasukawa with us!
-I'm so surprised by who you've got.
-Sure.
Our three survivors are quite tough, too.
I see.
-Three amazing challengers.
-Could you say a few words?
Tell them.
I don't know how strong
Mr. Tenshin Nasukawa is.
But I'll be sure to bring him down!
-He's up for it!
-He said he doesn't know who you are.
He's pumped up!
I also will bring
Mr. Tenshin Nasukawa down!
This is great!
-She's up for it, too.
-Yeah!
What the hell!
I can't beat him with my fist,
but if we're shooting balls, I might win.
I'll try my hardest to take him down!
You've never been told that before, I bet.
-Isn't it annoying you?
-Yeah.
I'll make sure I bring you all down.
Get ready.
-All right!
-Let's go!
For the final battle of Takeshi's Castle,
the game is Super Yabusame.
The attacking army has tried Yabusame
three times so far.
TAKESHI'S ARMY WINS
Each time, they failed
to hit their target with the ball.
Thank you!
In this final battle,
Yabusame has evolved.
What a surprise!
Takeshi's army's machine will now move
at the same time as the attacking army's.
They can't miss a moment
as they pass each other.
For both of them,
it will be more difficult to aim.
The attacking army will win
if they get a ball into the red target.
Takeshi's army will win
if they hit the challenger's target.
But if both teams either succeed or fail,
it will result in a draw.
The attacking force has to aim
at the small moving hole in the machine.
They saved the toughest game yet
for this very last battle.
As if in anticipation of
the battle's intensity, it began to rain.
A little higher.
Last time, Ryu went
during the first round.
This time, it's Kanta.
-The color of your shirt is so different.
-Right.
But it represents his effort.
It's the symbol of challenges he faced.
-It used to be white, though.
-It can't be helped.
Kanta has given a stunning performance
and had a great deal of success.
Can he defeat
the formidable Tenshin Nasukawa?
-I'll do my best.
-Good luck!
-We're counting on you!
-All right!
You can do it!
-Those three are quite tough, too.
-Yes.
I'll try my hardest.
I'll take him out so that
the other two don't get a turn.
-Do your best!
-Thank you, I will!
Super Yabusame, round one.
SUPER YABUSAME
DIFFICULTY RATING: 200%
Here we go!
Let's begin the first round of Yabusame,
the final version!
Three, two...
Go for it!
...one.
All right!
THE ATTACKING ARMY FAILED
He didn't make it.
TAKESHI'S ARMY WINS
All right! Fantastic!
In the first round of Super Yabusame,
the extreme difficulty of aiming
at the small, fast-moving target
required split-second timing
and even Kanta couldn't do it.
Unfortunately, he couldn't even hit
the flame around the target.
On the other hand, Tenshin hit the target
on the moving machine,
as expected of a fighter's eye.
-Well, Mr. Tenshin. Fantastic!
-What an amazing guy.
-Thank you. I did it.
-You did it.
-I think your first ball hit the target.
-Probably.
-Great work.
-Just as planned.
-As planned?
-You won so easily.
-Be sure to bring down the other two.
-Sure.
-So reliable.
-Fantastic.
Super Yabusame, round two.
Takeshi's army came from there.
I've got a microphone for the first time.
I'm so happy.
Their target is so big,
but mine is so small.
I think it's all up to chance.
I'll make a miracle happen.
As the general,
I'll be sure to defend Takeshi's Castle.
-Keep up the good work.
-Let's go.
You must be aiming at the hearts
of cute male college students, too, right?
I shouldn't have said that, right?
I know...
Can Haniuda make a miracle happen
by bringing down Tenshin?
-Are you gonna win?
-I will get the ball in.
-Let's win!
-Yes. Thank you!
Let's begin.
The second round of Super Yabusame.
Three...
...two...
...one.
-She didn't get one in.
-It didn't hit her.
Did you see it?
Surprisingly, the attacking army's target
is intact.
If Haniuda got the ball
into the opponent's target, she wins.
Unfortunately, she made
some great shots, but missed the target.
Haniuda was so close
to bringing down Tenshin.
In the second round of Super Yabusame,
both sides missed the target.
It's a draw.
Super Yabusame, round three.
At last, we've reached
the very last battle of Takeshi's Castle.
The attacking army
of around 400 challengers
tackled a total of 28 strongholds.
With the help of their fellow members,
they've reached the final battle.
Only this Yabusame remains in the fight
against the hated Takeshi's army.
The last challenger is Sato,
a parkour athlete.
Will he achieve their long-held goal
by winning this duel?
See for yourself. Watch closely.
-I've come this far, so I have to do it.
-Wonderful.
-Okay.
-Great!
-Good luck!
-I can do it!
Charge!
All right!
This is the very last round.
I'll make sure I shoot him down.
This is the third round of Super Yabusame.
Let's begin!
-Three...
-Go for it!
...two...
Let's go!
...one.
The final battle of Takeshi's Castle.
It looked like Tenshin hit the target,
but because a bouncing ball hit it
from behind, it's invalid.
So, if Sato got the ball
into Tenshin's target,
it'll be a dramatic victory.
Well, he hit a ball directly at the flame.
But he couldn't get it into the target,
so he failed.
The attacking army fought well,
but, sadly, they've been defeated.
The winner is Takeshi's army.
-Our count!
-Count!
Oh, my. Well done.
Thank you.
-I protected the castle well.
-Yes.
We should do this every week.
-Every week?
-If we do, our staff will drop.
All right. Shall we shout it now?
The winner is Takeshi's army!
We did it!
It's sad that we lost,
but thank you so much for your great work!
-Thank you.
How was it?
I could see the target,
but it was hard to aim at. It was tough.
Sometimes it's up to luck
on Takeshi's Castle.
I hope you guys will try again.
Let's one day bring down
the impregnable Takeshi's Castle!
All right!
Good. Charge!
This is how Takeshi's army
drove out the attacking army.
-Well, well...
-How was it?
-He was good, right?
-We had an amazing helper.
-He was fantastic!
-We won easily. Thank you.
-They were no match for him, were they?
-No.
You know what? I can honestly say
that I'd bet no one
can clear Super Yabusame.
The last one was the toughest yet.
So, this season, no one could conquer us.
What shall we do next? Another season?
Another season?
-We'll do it.
-Yes!
In another 34 years' time.
That would be nice, too. But...
Will the wait
for next season be that long?
It's up to the viewers.
Yes. We hope they all enjoy it.
See you next time.
-Hopefully in season two.
-Thank you so much!
See you!
-Thank you, Count!
-Thank you!
Thank you for your great work.
Around 400-odd people attempted
to overthrow Takeshi's Castle,
but they were unable to do so
and were wiped out.
For this era of the revived
Takeshi's Castle, the story is over.
Until we meet again, goodbye!
It's all over. Thank you so much!
It was so much fun.
You did so well.
-I'll make a Yabusame machine.
-No way.
-Takeshi's Castle was fantastic, right?
-Yeah.
Takeshi's Castle is the best!
I really wanted to win,
but everyone worked very hard.
So, this is all okay.
On this show, you can have
a wonderful experience.
Cherry. Good!
I've made lots of friends.
Even with the person with a painted nose.
Japanese people are so kind.
Thank you very much.
Did you get it?
Could you please let me stay? Please!
We came all the way from Nagoya.
-I didn't know we'd work so well together.
-Seriously.
-I feel like crying.
-Honestly.
So cute!
It's fun, because it's not scripted
and everyone's completely serious.
It's up to us if they clear
or fail the game.
I will get through hard times
since they're nothing
compared to Takeshi's Castle.
I enjoyed Slip-and-Slide Quiz so much.
I've had a lot of fun in this experience
that might be once-in-a-lifetime.
The most fun I've had in my life.
Goodbye!
-Don't fall in love with me!
-Fall in love with me!
We had so much fun!
Thank you so much!
See you, Chiitan!
Just seeing the gate of Takeshi's Castle
makes us extremely excited.
This is fantastic!
I want to make a program called
Osamu's Castle like this one.
You've said that you wanted
to do it in the future.
This is the new Takeshi's Castle.
I'm from the old Takeshi's Castle,
but it feels the same.
Okay?