Welcome to Wednesday Downtown
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Who is it?
It's Bakarhythm!
Bakarhythm
-Yes
Straight to the point, have you guys ever wanted to be in the world of a TV show?
Have you, Ano?
Well, yes I suppose so
Give me an example. Which one?
Hanazawa Naoki
So which character do you want to be?
The stubborn Naoki
Is Naoki characterized by stubbornness?
Isn't he a more complex character?
Is he stubborn?
-Not really
So today, we bring you such an experience
What?
-This is what it is
A mind-numbing prank of not being able to leave the world of a mystery drama until the culprit is found
In other words, they'll be involved in a mystery drama-style murder case
But it differs from usual pranks in that
It doesn't end until the culprit is found
Knowing this
Even though its obviously fake, they still have to find the culprit to bring it to an end
How do you feel about this kind of trickery, Degawa?
Well, it's, uh, it's, uh, it's kind of funny, but, uh, it's, uh
Sorry... didn't get it at all
So, the person we're calling out for a fake location shoot is
Diane's Tsuda
This time, he checks in one day early at a simple hotel in Nagano Prefecture
The next morning he'll be swept up in the world of a mystery drama
I'd like to introduce myself. I'm Sasaki, the director
I'm Marui, the cameraman
They then have a 30-minute meeting to discuss the itinerary for the next morning's fake location shoot
So tomorrow is all planned
-Yes
8:00 here. This is the cafeteria, so meet here at 8:00
Ok, got it
Let's just make a quick note
Lest you forget, though you shouldn't
Okay, got it
Can stick it there
I see
After receiving a note with the next day's meeting time, he is dismissed
Tutting as he comes back
What is this? Don't even have a bath
Started complaining right away
That was fast
After cursing the accommodation, he falls asleep
Now, on the second day, the curtain rises on the mystery drama
Good morning. Thank you
Did you sleep well?
Just slept a little
-Oh, really?
I was watching football
Good morning. Coffee
-Thank you
Enjoy your meal
Why are you in a bad mood?
Very suspicious
Staring straight at him
You don't have to stare like that
At this very moment
Marui isn't here. I'm sorry
Ah, it's totally fine
Just one more moment, please. I'm sorry.
-It's okay
Noone's picking up the phone, so...
I'll go straight to him.
-Ok fine
Why're you so tired?
Mr. Marui
I'm opening the door
Ah, Mr. Marui!
Are you okay?
Whoa scary!
Mr. Marui has collapsed in his room!
Tsuda, can you come over here for a minute?
-Mr. Marui?
Worried
-Natural
Helping seriously
Something's holding the door shut
But I can see his feet.
-What?
Can you help me open it?
Eh, you want me to do it?
What's going on?
Can you open it?
-No...
Looks like there's an umbrella stuck in there
Oh, its open!
Eh eh eh?
Ah, scared the shit out of me. Eh, what? What? What?
Mr. Marui
-Eh?
Eh, there's a knife...
Killed...
An easy to understand scenario
He's laughing!
Eh eh?
Tsuda...
-Eh?
Because this is a strange scenario no matter how you look at it
Tsuda is immediately convinced it is a trick and couldn't help but laugh
Is he dead?
Saying something like "Is he dead?"...
Eh, really?
What a pain
It's a pain in the ass, getting pranked like this
Hey... wait
Mr. Tsuda...
No, it...
Wait a moment!
Ahhhh, you scared the shit out of me. What's going on?
I'm a doctor
Just by chance
Wait a minute what's going on here...?
A doctor
What...
No, what's going on...
He's dead
What the hell is this...
Eh?
It's weird, isn't it?
I don't know what's going on, though
But the cause of death
Must be the stab wound from this knife
Of course... what the hell?
Judging by the stiffness of the body
Looking for the cameras
The presumed time of death was 3:00 a.m
No...what ... what are we talking about...
The exact time is unclear
But it was around that time
No... he...he ...
Is he okay? He's alive...
Please don't touch him
But that... blood... it's weird
Please calm down
I'm already calm
What kind of situation is this?
Let's get organized
Organize... organize what?
Let's all go back to the cafeteria
Why?
Call an ambulance or the police
Everyone...
-Call the police
Let's all go back to the cafeteria together first... then call the cops
Do as you're told
What is this...
Let's go
It always happens like this
And "Let's go"...
Can't help but go along with it
Yeah
Otherwise it'd be over
Although Tsuda was commenting constantly at this inexplicable situation
This trick has a special mechanism that it won't end until the culprit is found
Quite interesting
So Tsuda's actions will be ignored
What's going on here?
Why haven't the police been called...
Why are you sitting in my seat all of a sudden?
Anyway, let's call the police first
Go ahead
No good...
The phone line's been cut
Eh? The phone line
You all have cell phones, right?
Cell phones too... no signal
My cell phone is fine
Oh, really?
-I can't get a signal either
I've got three bars
There's no signal
It's not like there's no signal
There's no signal in this world
Under these circumstances
No good
Because of the heavy rain, the river's flooded
It's fake, right?
The bridge is washed away
Eh?
No, it's just a little rain
Can't get out
The only bridge connected to the city...
They're on an island
Contact with the outside world and means of transportation are disrupted
The hotel itself is a huge escape room
The setup is just a little cheap bit of that
Tsuda
What?
Well...
What's going on? What's going on?
The bridge is broken. No can leave
The people who have been here since yesterday
Including the dead Mr. Marui, are all still here
That is to say...
In other words
What about the culprit?
"What about the culprit?"
Passing him the ball
I'll say it again
The bridge is broken. No one can leave
What an idiot
The people who have been here since yesterday
Are all still here
That is to say...
What about the culprit?
"What about the culprit?"
Ah, that...
You mean, like, "the culprit is still among us"?
Now you say it
Eh?
What?
It's nothing to do with us, and I don't want to stay here any longer
Sayuri, come back
Just a minute
The bridge has been washed away so cars can't get across
There's a car outside
Does that mean we're stuck here?
Cars are making noises outside
Tsuda, can I have a word?
Really, it's so early still...
Tsuda, can we go to the 2nd floor?
-Really?
What the hell? It's so early still...
Seriously, what's going on here...
This guy is definitely the culprit
Here... here for what?
Well
How about we resolve the incident?
Why?
What for?
You want to avenge Mr. Marui's death, don't you?
No, what's it got to do with me? It doesn't matter
I don't have any memories with him
Forcing Tsuda, an overly aloof man, into the role of detective
First is to confirm the alibi of the entire staff
Let's go.
-Can we go?
Go solve the incident
Why do I have to be the one to solve it...
What... what program is this exactly?
Please.
-With this?
Is it okay to ask?
What should I ask?
Name and what they did last night
Ah, like this
That's all that needs to be asked
Get the alibi
I'm sorry
You're the owner, right?
-Yes, I am
Can you give me your name?
I'm Terashima, the owner.
-Ok
Last night, I was watching a movie in my room
"Watched a movie."
What movie?
Pocahontas
Pocahontas? Why that...?
It's not the kind of movie you'd randomely watch
Watched Pocahontas
Here's the alibi for the others
Three people
played poker
Watched a
movie alone
No comment
No comment is suspicious
You two asked us
Yeah
What about you two?
Uh, yeah
You are the director...
Sasaki
My name is Miyu Sasaki
What were you doing then?
I was using a GoPro for location shooting
Ah, checking the GoPro?
-Checking it
On the computer...
A recording
Ah, that's it...
Ah, it's the way it looks in the room
Selfie. Ah, 3:08
About that time
Ah, about that time
That's an alibi, isn't it?
That should do it
So, Tsuda
Eh?
What were you doing?
Me? I was sleeping
In bed...
Went to bed after watching football
Doesn't that mean you have no alibi?
What?
Shouldn't everyone be asleep at that hour?
I mean, you've been point the finger at everyone else
Scared me! What are you doing?
I think you're the culprit
No, no, no...it's inexplicable
But it makes sense, doesn't it?
Why does that make sense?
Your reaction is suspicious
What, how?
Why am I the culprit on a TV show?
Why are you so quiet all of a sudden?
You're the one who said "TV program"
Suspicion of Tsuda cannot be cleared for the time being...
So the first step was to establish everyone's alibi
The next step is to find the evidence
Wouldn't it be better to investigate Mr. Marui's room again?
That's right
Let's go see if there's any more evidence
Where?
Let's go
I'll come along
Ah, the doctor, right?
You're Mr. Hasegawa, right?
I'm Takuro Hasegawa
Let's go
Let's find out what other evidence there is
What? Evidence?
Maybe even fingerprints...
Ah, I've got my fingerprint checker with me
Why would you bring it?
Why?
Dr. Hasegawa had a fingerprint test kit with him for some reason
The culprit's fingerprints were lifted from the handle of the murder weapon's pocket knife and the inside handle of the door
Tsuda
This fingerprint. Did you find anything?
Something from the fingerprints?
The hell do I know?
A culprit... exists
Found out someone killed him
Tsuda
This fingerprint. Did you find anything?
Again?
She'll never stop asking questions
It's like a game
Is there any other...that is to say any other reason?
Wait a moment
The fingerprints here are the same as here, right?
Ah, 1, 2, 3, 4
There are four fingerprints
Think about it
Left-handed
It's true that he's left-handed
He's kind of happy
Stabbed like this
So there's four prints on this, which means the perp's left-handed
Eh? Really?
Yes, we're making progress
What's next?
What, are you looking for a lefty?
Is there any other evidence here?
-Eh?
There's more
They checked Marui's backpack for evidence
Anything?
Shinshu Daily News
Death of a member of the Mountaineering Department
Tsuyoshi Ito (19), a second-year mountaineer at Suwa University in Nagano Prefecture, fell from a mountain
Fellow travelers called the police
The owner of the hotel where Mr. Ito stayed talked about the dangers at the site, saying...
Ah, Mr. Terashima
The owner of this place. It's in the paper
Anything else?
Is this Mr. Hasegawa?
This one
Looks like Mr. Hasegawa, right?
I mean, everyone's in the paper, right? Everyone who's here
There are also women
You're right
1234…
Well, everyone downstairs is in the picture
In other words
What?
The men...
Do they know each other?
Yeah
Let's go downstairs first and summarize
This story is getting more and more backstory
People who behave strangely when investigating alibis
Mr. Yamada, right?
Mr. Yamada didn't say anything
The strangest ones are Mr. Yamada and Mr. Terashima
What's so strange about Mr. Terashima?
Watching a movie...
Who would watch Pocahontas at 3:00 in the morning?
What aroused Tsuda's suspicions was
Yamada, who kept quiet about last night's action
And Terashima, who claimed to be watching a movie alone in his room
Then they deduced from the traces at the scene that the culprit was left-handed
In other words, the culprit is...
Mr. Yamada
His right hand is bandaged
Not left-handed
Instead, the culprit had to use his left hand
Mr. Yamada's right hand was injured, so he had to stab with his left
In other words, the culprit is...
Mr. Yamada
Let's go to Mr. Yamada's room and ask him for confirmation. Come on
Bring this?
With or without.
-Either...
It's because it's already been decided how it's going to develop
No answer
No?
-Yeah
Huh? Scary
The door is open
Can we go in?
Ahhhh! Eh!
Dead?
He's dead
Hey, he's dead!
Hey, Mr. Yamada is dead
What's with the Kansai accent...
It's ruining the atmosphere...
Confession
He's confessed
I'm the one who killed Marui
The accident...no, I should say incident...28 years ago
He was going to tell the truth about the day Ito fell to his death
I was so angry, I killed him
That is to say, as expected...
The culprit is Mr. Yamada
Yeah
And then, unable to bear the burden of sin, he died
The incident is resolved
Well, that's the way it is, isn't it?
The incident in Tsuda's mind has been resolved
However
The victim and the killer are dead
Doesn't get it
Can't figure out what's wrong with it
What is this?
It's not about the incident
What to do?
What can I do to end it?
Yeah, well, the fun's not over yet
It means that the matter has not been resolved
Tsuda, did you think of something?
It's just that the...
Mr. Yamada is dead
Tsuda told Dr. Hasegawa what he had previously learned
Here, that...
All the people here are related to the events that were published in the newspaper
Mr. Hasegawa is one of them
Then Hasegawa confessed
This time, everyone was actually called to the hotel after receiving strange letters
As well as hiding the relationship between them due to the threat of a fall accident back then
At this time
Did something happen?
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that
Lately, the electric switch has been tripping on its own
Yesterday, between 2:30 and 6:00 in the morning
The circuit breaker's tripped, too
Eh?
I don't know if it's bothering any of you?
Taking notes now
The circuit breaker tripped?
I didn't even notice
Oh, I'm so sorry
What's the secret?
That's when the two came to Yamada's room again to investigate
Tsuda
-Yes
I'm thinking
Yamada didn't commit suicide.
-I see
I see
It's...
-He was killed
I think that's more likely.
-Yes
The culprit is someone else
For some reason Tsuda seemed to have finally made up his mind at this point
Maybe there's some evidence left here too
This one's a little weird
This light
What's so strange about this clock?
It's not running. It just keeps flashing
Blackout...
The power's out, so it's out.
-And then
And...
This mirror is weird, too
What's going on? What's wrong with this mirror?
Eh?
I think there's some kind of number written here
What does it say?
It's "1114," right?
This is the message of death, isn't it?
It's a death message
"1114"?
November 14th?
November 14
Yeah
Birthday?
Whose birthday is it?
The elevation of the mountain?
1,114-meter mountain
Too short?
Is this "1114"?
Look at it from a different angle
Want to use a mirror?
If you look in the mirror...
"Miyu"?
"Miyu" "Sasaki Miyu"
It's Miyu
But Miyu was busy at the time of Mr. Marui's murder
There's an alibi
Clock, that...selfie in the room
Then Tsuda checked the video image once more
Wait a minute, please
The power's out at 3:08
The power's on in here...it's on, which is weird, right?
So happy
Tsuda, this is a great discovery
Oi!
And then there's this suicide note...
It's like its written by a woman
Is there any handwriting to compare it to?
Ah-
Ah-what's there? What's there?
She wrote something
Want to go look for it?
-Okay
The one he got the day before
It's not in that script?
Yes, the one with the meeting time
She took it, didn't she?
No, that'd be weird
Not here
Not here...
Nothing else?
Please think back
Oh, wow. I was in a daze at that point
Eh...
Ah, the paper with today's meeting time on it
He got it
So funny
Ohhhh!
Aaahhhh!
Ah, scary
This
This this this this this this this
That's what happens when you think carefully
Let's compare.
-Wow
Whoa, scary
Ah- scary!
8 is the same
It's the same 8
It's a very distinctive feature
Look!
28 years and 8
8 is the same as this...
I'll go get everyone
Okay
-I'll have everyone gather in the cafeteria
Please reveal the real culprit.
-Okay
It's a pep talk
This guy can be a real pain in the ass when he really gets going
One moment, please.
-Okay
Eh, what's this feeling...
And now, the prank is finally coming to a climax
Detective Tsuda, the first part of the serial hotel killings
Mr. Yamada was killed by someone
Like a movie
Next to Mr. Yamada's body
Was this suicide note
Kansai accent is completely gone
It looks like it was written by a woman
I got a note yesterday
This is Ms. Sasaki's. You wrote it
Then, Mr. Yamada's desk was left open
Dining... dining... dining message
Dying message
"Miyu" in katakana
You can tell it's "Miyu"
In other words
You're the one who wrote this suicide note, Ms. Miyu
The culprit is you
Although Tsuda was so impatient at first...
He's now a full-blown detective
What are you talking about?
I have an alibi...
You showed us this alibi video
A famous detective who brilliantly solved the alibi ruse
So you shot this video at some other time and put the clock on it
The video was not taken at that time
Isn't that correct!?
He's tough
Now that i've been exposed, there's nothing I can do about it.
-Oh, oh!
I didn't realize that the handwriting would reveal it
But i'll never forgive
How could you forget Ito from the former mountaineering group?
Well...
It's your fault my brother is dead
So realistic
The real killer, Miyu Sasaki, is the brother of Miyu Ito
It's because the mountaineering group, especially Yamada and Marui, made fun of him
That he fell to his death
And so, she wanted to kill everyone involved on that day
With Miyu's confession, the incident came to an end...
Please atone for your sins
When you get out, i'll be happy to do more location shoots with you
It's like a closing statement
Miyu, you must turn yourself in
Can they still shoot together...?
Please atone properly for your sins
-Miyu Ito!
Ah, ah, the police
I'm arresting you on suspicion of murder.
-Oh, that was fast
That's it. That's the end of it
Tsuda.
-Yes?
You've done a great service
No no. It's sad...
A sad turn of events
If another incident occurs, please continue to assist us
Well, please don't get me involved again
In Summary
Look forward to Detective Tsuda's next case
Well well well
The famous detective Tsuda
What do you think, Goto?
Very interesting
There's a part of me that was simply curious as to how it was going to play out
As well as seeing Tsuda get more and more into it
Hamada called out, "Oh yeah, the notes he got the day before"
This guy really enjoyed it!
What do you think, Matsumoto?
I hated it
Tsuda's just no good
The main character isn't very good
The main character's no good. He's too noisy
The ending didn't conclude very smoothly either
True
But there was a lot of hints. They kept repeating things
It's like a game where you repeat the same line over and over again
Let's welcome the next presenter
Who is it?
Einstein!
Appearing from that side is really scary
-Yes, indeed
It's like a month's worth of food
It's been a long time, everyone.
-Long time no see
Protruding chin, tiny glasses, chronic rhinitis, thinning hair
I'm everyone's jaw, Itada
What the hell?
-What are you reciting?
What was that?
Well, recently.
-Can you tell me what you're gonna say in advance?
Speaking of which
-Yes
Have you been told you have bad breath lately?
That's why you're hosting?
That's too much information. I'll do it.
-Is that okay?
So, have you ever been told you have a bad breath?
No, and I've been wearing a mask lately.
-Yeah
Today we have a hypothesis about bad breath. Here it is
Even if you eat a lot of garlic and meet someone, it's surprisingly difficult for someone to point out
Yes, it's very possible
Would you say anything, Ano?
I don't think so
If I tell them they smell, they'll be hurt.
-That's right
Considerate people don't say such things
Hamada looks like the type to say it
What do you mean?
Like you'd say it even if it didn't stink
Even if you eat a lot of garlic and meet someone, it's surprisingly difficult for someone to point out
We want you to conduct a surprise interview after eating garlic
Will there be a camera?
-Yes
You can choose where and who you want to interview.
-Okay
It only ends when the other person says, "Did you eat garlic?" or "Garlic stinks"
You have to get the person to say the word "garlic."
-Yes
So, we get the three of them to eat these garlic-filled dishes right away
Whoa
I can clearly smell the flavor in my mouth after eating garlic chips
I'll just focus on the garlic chips
We'll just have to go straight to this
They'll surely realize
It's not going to affect my work after, right?
I'm gonna freestyle with a rapper
What kind of job is this?
For a supposed TBS year-end special
The unannounced interview will be "What's was your toughest job in 2022?"
Seems like a real thing
As long as the person points out the problem in the interview, it's a pass
Just find a senior
It stinks
If it was the other way around Fujimon would definitely say something
So, Fujimon and Iguchi roam TBS
While Komiya heads to the Yoshimoto Head Office
They split up to find interviewees
At this time
Okay, okay, okay. Here it is
Suddenly, Magical Lovely are found while filming Love It!
However, it is necessary to keep a certain distance from the other person during the interview
No perverse proximity
The subject of the interview is what was the hardest job you ever experienced
Filming at a ski resort in just a pair of shorts
Yeah, the ski resort. It was like an indoor ski resort
In just a pair of shorts
Seems they can kind of smell it
Obvious smell
The smell of garlic quickly gave Murakami the impression that something was wrong
Bathing in the smell of garlic
Anything else? Noda?
Ended up with a bad result when doing SASUKE
You've been practicing, haven't you?
-I've been practicing
I'm trying to build muscle for SASUKE, to practice, to learn, to challenge
Where did you get to?
Murakami has gone completely silent
Well...
Not the beginning
I can't believe I went out so fast.
-Went down so early
Murakami is very bothered by Fujimoto's bad breath
But it wasn't pointed out until the end of the interview
Okay. Okay
No, no, no. No more
What did you eat yesterday?
-You realized?
Did you eat garlic?
Why didn't you say that? Why didn't you say that?
There's a camera recording
I thought it was your normal state
What do you mean by "normal"?
I thought it was common
On the other side, Iguchi captured this trio
They said they wanted to be weighed, but they're both 106kg
I couldn't
-Yes
It was very traumatizing, and they're still the same weight
Not even pointed out at the end
I thought it was Anri
I just finished.
-What a mess
All mixed up.
-Yeah
Why have you just eaten?
The same goes for Komiya who met Yasushi Ishida at the Yoshimoto Head Office
A big senior
Something stinks
You knew it.
-Yes, but it's not polite to say that on a first meeting
There's a reason for that, too
All three groups smelt it, but it was still hard to get them to point it out
If you're not close, you won't say anything
At this point, the next thing Fujimoto saw was
Ishida seems like he's going to laugh and comment
Got one
-Yes, hello
NON STYLE's Ishida
One that you found hard
-Physically tiring
There was an Osaka Castle Dream Festival that lasted 9 days
Yes, yes, yes, yes
I did 54 shows in nine days
Fifty-four?
The stinky "54" is flying out
I was on so many
It was super exhausting
-54
So exaggerated
Despite increasing in an attempt to elicit a response
This time the other side didn't point it out either
Is your nose clogged?
I have paranasal sinusitis
-An infection?
Didn't realize
Then they found Alco&Peace, Gerard, and New York
Shinya is about 40kg for three people
It doesn't even look like they're going to point it out
So, Iguchi ate five more chunks of garlic
Hello
Mukai's here
Doesn't look like the type
A member of Panther is encountered while recording
It feels like you've done a lot of work.
-Sort of
Outside.
-Yes, yes, yes
The studio, and all these broadcasts
Broadcasting is the toughest
Don't you think something stinks?
What do you mean, what's going on?
Stinks!
What? What stench?
It stinks
What? Sorry, sorry, sorry
What? What stench?
Garlic odor
-Garlic odor?
Yeah!
Oh, its you
-Stinky! Stinky! Stinky!
Thank you
-Stinks so much
So, finally some success
Truth Revealed
It's also surprisingly difficult to say "have you eaten garlic?"
No no, its too much
You'd have to say it
Honestly, I couldn't even listen to what he was saying
Elsewhere with Komiya
He found Rice
Sekimachi is just like a middle-aged woman
Are you trying to popularize that line from the beginning?
I've been doing it for about 5 years or so
Really?
Maybe the next time we come back will be two years from now, so I have to try
It had to be said
What was your toughest job?
Probably LIVE STAND
Yoshimoto's big comedy festival, LIVE STAND
Touching their noses
Comedy festival
What's up?
Doesn't it stink?
It stinks
Do you stink, Komiya, or is it outside?
Yeah? Is it outside?
It's hard... "LIVE STAND" in front of thousands of people!
It stinks. Wait
It stinks so bad I can't even talk
Also
Did you eat the garlic?
Yeah!
So Komiya also managed to pass
Everyone's so fast
Komiya's a good choice since he's a junior
Yeah, it depends on the person
As expected, both groups commented on their juniors
I'd say it to my juniors
Fujimoto, a veteran with few seniors to talk to easily, is in a dangerous situation
You're a senior, it can't be said
Next, we met Kasuga, who wanted to say something, but the result was the same
Nowadays
The other guy didn't even flinch
I won't eat garlic, i'll put it in
After the garlic, Fujimoto's next target is...
Okay, here we go
You scared the shit out of me
Scared me
He'll say it
Despite being a junior, we have high hopes for Daisuke Miyagawa
He'll surely say something
He's got to say something
Hello
-Hello, what's up?
Daisuke, it's been a long time, hasn't it?
-Long time no see
You scared me. What's going on?
It's a TBS year-end special.
-What?
Can I interview you?
-Yes
Wait, can I tell you something?
-What?
Sorry
Of all the jobs you've had this year.
-Stinks, what is that?
Seriously, what's going on?
What?
-Don't you smell the stench?
Stink? What?
What's wrong?
It stinks
No, I'm sorry
Daisuke you...
It stinks! What's that smell? It stinks!
It stinks, doesn't it?
-What?
It stinks too much
-Let me do the interview
What? I'm pissed off
What's the problem?
-It stinks
What are you laughing at?
You're definitely bad. You've got stomach problems. You're overworked. Your breath stinks
Stand up. What do you look like?
-I'm serious
Stop talking for a second
Why is that?
-Your mouth stinks
What? Can an interviewer be like this you asshole?
That's too much!
It is, but it just stinks
I just smelled it and I almost threw up
What's this?
-Agh!
You're so rude
No, no, it's not right. It's not right. It's not right
No, no, no, no, no
It stinks. Seriously, what?
What the hell?
-Something's wrong.
Tell me what your hardest job has been
Let me think
Yeah...
"Yeah" stinks
No, no, no
Seriously, what did you eat? Seriously, what the hell?
Can I have one breath please?
It stinks
Garlic and meat?
He said it!
-What are you doing here?
So Fujimoto finally passed after the sixth try
Daisuke, you're the first to point it out.
-No way
Probably because i've been speaking to juniors
But if you think about it, you're a junior too
When I think about it, he's a junior too
Excuse me
In summary
The juniors basically don't point out problems
Very fun
Why is it so funny to see people get hit by bad smells?
Yeah, really
Daisuke's reaction was very funny
I met Fujimoto on that day
Just wandering round the TV station
You met him while they were filming?
He stank
-Really?
Did you say anything?
When I met him, I greeted him
I said something smelled bad, and he said, "Don't worry, its because of Wednesday Downtown"
He explained
I thought you wouldn't say anything
That's a good point
Even I would say it stinks
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03