Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let's get on with our first presenter please
Youichi Okano
The Final Moustache
Final?
-Not exactly a moustache, right?
It's not a moustache
Glad to be here
Have you ever received or given a red packet?
Yes
Of course, given and received
How much do Downtown give?
To be honest, 10,000 yen
New Year's red packets?
Yes, yes
10,000?
For 100 people it would cost 1 million
I thought you'd give more
Sorry, that's a bit strange
Really?
10,000 is not enough?
That's pretty impressive too
Sorry, it's my personal opinion
※Not speaking politely
Who're you speaking so informally to?
Whispered, quickly and quietly
Better get to the point quickly
Sorry, it's my personal opinion
Today we bring the theory related to the giving and receiving of money
It's hard to get people to accept 10 million
It depends on the reason, right?
Any reason will do?
Yes, different reasons are used
I see
If it seems unreasonable then it may be difficult
If its the person's savings then they wont take it, right?
Indeed
This is the fun of rich people
Yes
This time the challengers are these three
Why this expression?
The theory to be tested this time is this
What is this?
Eh?
Whoa!
This is real money
Whoa
"It's hard to get people to accept 10 million"
Ho
Now please call out the person who you think will take the 10 million
Ok
The challenge is to see how many people will accept it in 5 hours
Getting them to take it?
If the other party accepts it, it counts as one point
Suddenly called here to give him money?
Consider your own reasons
Oh, I decide
Need to find a few people to accept
Yes
Anyone?
Are my juniors ok?
Of course
That's okay, right? There are a lot of poor juniors
The number of people I know is very small
Whether they are juniors or seniors or contemporaries
My juniors are all money-minded
I think it will work
But after all, it's 10 million
So, the 5-hour challenge begins
Ogata goes first
Didn't eat, did you?
-No
Awesome
Ichikipuri, one of Ogata's juniors
Cheers
After the cheers, the 10 million challenge starts
How is work now?
Less growth since coronavirus
Barely getting by
Barely
But you're really funny
I really like you as a person.
-Thanks
I hope you can succeed
Thank you.
-So...
You come from a small town, your parents must be worried about you
I have been with you as your senior
Yes
See you three or four times a week
A bit forced
I think of myself as your big brother
The padding is too obvious
I also consider Ogata...
-We're together
It's clear there's something to say
I think we are friends for life
Yes
After showing that their relationship goes beyond just junior and senior
The 10 million offer is put forward
So strange to just give them money
Wait a minute
Wait...hey, wait!
Take it
What the hell? No, no, no, no.
-I really like you as a person
What is this?
10 million
I'm treating you like a brother
Scary. Scary. Eh?
-What?
This isn't right, is it?
I'll leave that to you.
-Is this for real?
Of course it's true
It's true
What's happening all of a sudden?
-Take it
Its ok, you can have it.
-No, no, no, no
It's scary.
-Why?
What's so scary about it?
-It's scary, okay?
We are brothers, right?
-No, no, no, no
Brother, right?
Brother, yes
Although we are brothers, this is too sudden
The chief is giving you money because you've worked hard
You should take this
This is between men
I'm talking to you as a man
As a man and as a brother
The thin excuse of "you work hard so I'm paying you"
Ogata strives forward
What's going on here?
-Eh?
What's going on?
I also make a lot of money
I just haven't told you that I make a lot of money
I earned...
"King's Brunch", I get more than 3 million for one appearance
Eh?
-I earn that much
What a lie!
Ogata makes up a bold lie and continues to persist
I have everything
Have a house, have a car, have a bike, have a dog
So weird
I've got it all!
Money is no longer useful to me
Really
Here you go. It's okay
Let me work on myself a little more
I'll try to make as much money as you
So I can't accept it
I will work hard to earn this much
This money has been earned through your effort
I can't take it
You're such a nice guy!
Ogata's moved!
Ogata's not suitable for this
Sorry, I can't take it
I will try my best
Don't cry!
You're really too good of a guy!
Don't cry, there's no need to cry!
I'll try my best.
-10 million for you. I hope you'll work hard
Thank you
I'll try my best
I really hope you can succeed
Somehow both of them shed tears
Because a bizarre situation has developed
We explain everything here
What?
Eh?
Downtown is watching
Great!
Thank you
This guy's tear ducts have collapsed
Don't cry, what is wrong with you!?
Ogata is crying too
This guy is really...
This didn't go according to plan
You've been weird
This is not a project to make people cry
Next is the first person Nagano called out
His junior, Whistling Naruo
This approach is conducted in a similar fashion
Well, I hope you'll take it today
Wow, it's very impactful
Eh?
10 million
What do you mean?
Shut up and take it
Why're you giving it to me?
I'm telling you, I actually made a lot of money
Exactly the same
How stupid!
-The same approach
It's not like "I'll take it if that's the case"...
I have a higher appearance fee than Sandwichman
Wait a minute...wait a minute. What's going on?
Really?
-Yeah
I can make that much by swinging by hips 4 times
What do you mean "swinging your hips"
Doing this joke
4 times?
-In just 4 times
I usually do 25 at once
You can make 2.5 million dollars for a commercial performance?
-Yes
I have a high fee
Really?
Ogata's appearance fee was supposedly 3 million
Whereas Nagano's commercial performances supposedly net him 2.5 million
A total dream
Then I'll be honest
I also received it from some senior
Money?
-Money
How much?
10 million, 10 million
After that, there was no pressure, and I immediately became popular
All my work increased in quality
Who was it? Can I ask?
Summers
It is better to be specific
Although interspersed with falsehoods and lies
No, I can't take it. It's too much
It's scary
No, wait
No, I can't accept it
No way
This side ends with the same result as Ogata's attempt
Wouldn't take it
That pig is pretending to be cool
10 million certainly want it, you pig
How can such a person earn 2.5 million
Kasuga called out...
His junior HEY! Taku-chan
I thought your store was still open
Ah, Oni Soba?
-What time does it open?
Open until 9:30, right?
For Taku-chan, the comedian and soba restaurant owner
Kasuga launches his noodle-focused offensive
I don't have any favorite ramen
Yeah
I hope someone can do something about this
"I hope you can open a ramen store I like"
And so
I will provide the funding
Will provide funding?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah
So, this
Oh!
It's serious
I've got goosebumps
Great, right?
So with this money
Go do what you're good at
So...
Is it possible?
Of course you can
-Ok
It is not necessary to return the capital
Here's your money
Sorry about that
I accept
I'll be sure to report on the follow-up
It's heavy. It's awesome
That's not right!
That's weird, right?
Readily accepted
Eh?
Something wrong?
No!
-10 million back
You took it
Yes, I did
I thought it was about time
You've been waiting for it? What do you mean?
What do you mean you've been waiting for it?
I thought this day would come
Someone
-Someone is bound to come
Finally!
-Finally got it
Someone was bound to give it to me
Finally
So Kasuga's challenge was successful
Managed to get 1 person to receive 10 million first
The second person called out by Ogata...
It's impossible for Ogata, right?
He is also a junior, Mizuki Watase
Super surprised!
It's okay. Take it
Anyway, I...
Just take it, it's fine
You can take it
Take it. It's okay
Ah?
-Really
How...
I can't.
-It's okay, it's okay, it's okay. Take it
Wait a minute
Don't do this
You don't have to fight yourself
It's okay. Take it
This kid is a bit scary
So many strange people
It's okay
No, no, no. Absolutely not
Why?
Ogata, I can't
It's Ogata's hard-earned money
It's okay, I haven't done much for it
Really
Ogata, come on
I'm shaken inside
What's wrong with you?
-Give me a slap
Why? That's scary
Please give me a slap
Really?
Just do it
It's okay to be shaken up
Absolutely not, absolutely not, please give me a slap
Otherwise I won't be able to get along with you in the future
What a disgusting relationship!
I can't do it
Please
Here I go
-Ok!
Here we go.
Why?
Why did you hit me?
Why're you hitting me!?
This guy is so scary
Why do I need to be hit
Therefore, Ogata's second challenge also failed
That's a shame
And for some reason it ended with a slap
Nagano's second person is...
A junior, Dayoshi
With this money, life is secure
So you can work on refining your abilities
And then hopefully you will become the man who earns more
I'm really happy
Dayoshi was completely fooled by Nagano and shed tears
Then
Ok, got it
Although it's bad to say
I probably shouldn't
No, you can
No, no, no, no, no, you can't not take it
Don't you want it?
-Yes I do
No, this can't be done
"This is the 10 million that Mr. Nagano gave me to put here."
"Watching this has inspired me"
That's not like me
Yes?
Yes, it is.
-That's right
However, I want the best for you
I know
Ok, I understand
I hope you'll buy some drinks
I'll take it.
-Good
Nagano also achieves his first victory here
Meanwhile, Kasuga goes for his second
Hi-Hi Iwasaki, a former member of the firm
Giving seniors money is super rude, right?
I'm not lending you this or anything
It's just a gift
For you to use
I want to see you spend it
I can't believe I'm so bothered by receiving money
No, there's no way I can take this
No matter what you say, I can't
No?
No way
In that case I hope you can use it elsewhere
Therefore, the result after 2 people each is shown above
Ogata has yet to succeed
The third person he found was also...
It's scary!
10 million
-It's scary
I can't understand it. It's scary
It's scary!
After that...
It's a lie, right?
This is a fake bill, right?
It's not a fake. I just got it out
-Really?
From a Japanese bank
You can't get it from Japanese banks, right?
I went to pick it up
On the other hand, Nagano...
I've never told anyone but I make more than Sandwichman
Eh?
Similar to Koyuki
Really?
Similar to Shinohiro
So you'll take the money, right?
Okay, then
I'll take it. I'll take it
Taking it? Ok
Surprisingly, he succeeds twice in a row
The 3rd person that Kasuga, who has now lost the lead, faced was...
Seriously, this...
Fake, right?
Abarenbo
This is money for you
No, no, no, this is not okay
I want you to use it
No, no, no, no, no, impossible
Although rejected...
He's changed since he drank
After drinking many of his favorite drinks...
Mobile Phone
The old one
-Yes
Direct contact
Just say it
So...
I'll take it, then
Does not seem to be a sober judgment
Anyway, he took it
But that's when Kasuga's time limit ends
Overall, he scored the above
Due to time constraints, Nagano also finished
That is...
While reconciling with Shinichi
Did they really make up?
Nagano's last target was Shinichi, who he previously severed ties with
That is, 10 million
Took it out so fast
I want to support Shinichi
And I hope you have fun!
Really?
-Really
What would you do with the money?
This guy will take it
High-rise apartment, right?
High-rise apartment?
-High Rise Apartment
Move house?
Where? Where?
Minato-ku?
Minato-ku
It is better to increase the unit price
There was no resistance, and he took the $10 million
I should get a ton of girls
You will?
-Yeah
Again!?
You really can't do that
Keep digging traps for me
I can not survive this year
Wednesday just keeps coming
Take responsibility
Wednesday, this program is really finished
A program that sours relationships
Can I say something too?
This show is finished
It's still fun to watch
And the fifth person called by Ogata, the last target
An old friend, Nedate
You haven't bought anything you wanted, have you?
-Yes
You especially like cars, right?
Really like
You like them so much you imitate them, right?
-Yes
I had a car all throughout university
Really like them
What kind of car do you want?
The most wanted?
-The most wanted
Civic
Civic? Lame choice
The previous Civic? It's an older model so it's more expensive
One Civic, not the ordinary kind
You know the one in Initial D?
If its in D it must be expensive, right?
Very expensive. 5 million or so
I really want it.
-I see
After the perfect setup
The final 10 million challenge begins
I know. Then use this money to buy
Gross!
Use this.
-No, no, no. What is this?
What?
-Scary
What is this?
10 million
No, no,, what 10 million!?
What does it mean?
I'll give you 10 million, with this money, buy the car
No, no, no. What the hell are you talking about all of a sudden?
No. No
What's going on here?
Why? Why?
-Why are you giving me money?
What is it?
-I like you as a person
You're gross
What's gross?
-This is gross
We know each other very well, don't we?
Can buy Civic is very good, right?
-No, Ogata, take it back
Why not?
I want to buy it myself
I want to buy the car myself
After that, they argued for 15 minutes about whether to buy a Civic or not
Not much time left
You're a man, right?
So, Ogata begins to rush ahead
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, Ogata
I told you to take it!
I can't take it.
-Take it!
Seriously!
They use brute force to forcefully push the money to the other
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, sorry, Ogata
10 million, I really can not accept
-Take it. It's okay
Ogata, please don't do this
It's too shameful to take someone's money
What is there to be ashamed of?
Really, really...
-I told you to take it
No, I can't
Just put it in there
What the hell do you want?
Take it over there!
Take it, please!
Ogata, please don't do this
Take it!
What's going on here?
I just want to give it to you. Take it
Ogata, honestly
Take it
-Tell the truth. Tell the truth
Honestly, it's dirty money, right?
It's dirty money, right?
-It's not dirty money
This is definitely dirty money, right?
-Why?
Definitely dirty money
Right?
This is definitely dirty money
Do you think I would do something like that?
You're dangerous.
-What's so dangerous?
This must be dirty money.
-How could I give you dirty money?
10 million is really not important to me
I made a lot of money, hundreds of millions
I don't want it
-Go buy a Civic
I really don't want it, Ogata
I'll buy it myself
I really like you as a person
Don't say it. Take it
I'll buy the Civic myself
No, no, no, I'll buy it for you
You're dreaming!
-Stop it. I'll buy it for you
I've told you so many times already
That's enough
I can't buy a car with your money!
Why are you so reluctant to accept it?
I'm giving you 10 million, with no risk
You can buy a Civic
I said I can't buy a Civic with this money
Why can't you?
Because I don't want to buy it with the money given by others
Just get it!
That's my goal
To buy a Civic
Please use it on your family
We are family, right?
We're family, right? Aren't we family?
Family, of course
That's why i'm giving it to you
If a family member says they want to buy a Civic
For me to be able to afford a Civic, it is the family that gives me encouragement
It's not to get a hand out like this
Right?
Ogata has a daughter, right?
Will you buy her everything in the future?
She says "Daddy, I want a car", then give her $10 million?
Will you raise her like that?
That's what you are doing right now
Imagine your own daughter, Ogata
When your daughter says, "Daddy, I want a car," will you buy it for her right away?
Will you buy her a house if she wants it?
If she buys it with her own money you'd be more happy, right?
What would you do
-Yes...
Daughter working herself
Says "Dad I bought a car", you'd be more happy, right?
Then think of me as your child
I will also try to tell you, "I bought a Civic with my own money, Ogata," right?
Yes
That's family, right?
I know...
Scared me!
Ogata, this is too tough
But in my heart...
I'm very moved
He's not swayed by 10 million
I'm touched
When he said that
"If you really care about me, don't do this"
I can't say anything else
Having earned millions already really sounds like just a dream
How can you earn it?
How could I earn so much?
Is it a lie?
-Of course
That's too much Ogata
-Sure!
That's too much
Really
I am still 5,500 yen for 1 appearance
Don't go around saying your fee, ok?
15,000 yen for a six-hour shoot
Don't talk about your salary
To sum up, the winner is Nagano
Okay, what do you think?
I see, that's how it is
Yes
Why did Nagano take it out like that?
This way
-So quick
The speed of adding ginger to a bowl
Sushi restaurant?
Sushi restaurant owner's speed
Only HEY! Taku-chan is gross
Yes, a businessman
So disgusting
Bad expression
Shouldn't Ogata have cried at the end?
Not sure
I kind of wanted to cry
Really?
-Yeah
I hope it'll be made into a movie
Movie title "Civic"
Let's welcome the next presenter
Magical Lovely!
Hello everyone
The two magical lovelies have gathered
Thank you
Today we are together
Yes
Let's do it
Although it is Saito's joke
I will abruptly bring this up
Last year's M-1 competition
The top batter Mogu Rider
Do you remember what sketch they did?
I remember, it was very impactful
Remember?
Hamada, of course, also
You should remember it
No way! Really?
Which part did you think was good?
Nice tempo
Very rhythmic indeed
Last year's winner, you know who it was, right?
Of course
The one with the bald guy, right?
There are still comedians who don't care so much about M-1
Even in this way you can be skilled at manzai
That's awesome!
They performed a segment about Kenichi Mikawa's "Scorpio Woman"
So this time
We bring a theory about this song
Please take a look
The lyrics "No, I'm a scorpio woman" can be spoken under certain conditions
Seems tough
-I also think it is difficult
Ask "What sign are you?" This kind of question is fine
But its hard to tell if someone's a woman or not just by looking at them
I don't even know how to ask
This time it will be difficult
The lyrics "No, I'm a scorpio woman" can be spoken under certain conditions
Wait a minute, I don't have a clue about this theory
These three, who know nothing about the theory, were gathered
All of you gathered today have one thing in common
We staged a segment about Kenichi Mikawa at M-1
Due to the connection, another Mikawa has come
※This one's stage name is Mikawa.
That should be the case
Kintaro also
I also...
At this time we reveal the task
The lyrics "No, I'm a scorpio woman" can be spoken under certain conditions
No way no way
It can't be done, can it?
So, these three have been selected to test the hypothesis
There is a true Scorpio woman
It's Ms. Mikawa
MIKAWA, MIKAWA
Is it a Sagittarius man?
Is it an Aquarius woman?
What a great segment
It's a Virgo man, right?
No, I'm a Scorpio woman
A Scorpio woman!
-What do you mean?
They will ask the questions the same as in the sketch
To get the respondent to say the phrase "No, I'm a Scorpio woman"
They can't go home until they succeed
Therefore
Each group went to a place of their own choosing
And started asking questions
This is the Lumine Theater
Shinjuku
There should be someone who understands
Just target these people and ask questions
Comedy fans should have seen the M-1
They immediately start to ask
Looking for people who would know
Hello, can you cooperate?
Just a moment, okay?
Do you know who we both are?
I'm a fan of your work.
-Great!
I think we can do it quickly
What's your sign?
Cancer
"What's the sign of the zodiac?" That's now how you should ask!
Bad brain
You are so stupid!
Tomoshige is a pure idiot
An argument occurs almost instantly
So, what should I ask? What should I ask?
Let people say "no" first
For example, if you ask "Is it Cancer?"
If the person is a Scorpio, they'll say "no".
-That's it!
It's obviously the same logic as their own skit
Inexplicably, Tomoshige cant wrap his head around it
Doesn't get it
Is it a segment acted without understanding?
Just reading the lines
Elsewhere, Kintaro
First of all, you can't ask "Is it Scorpio?"
Not bad
You have to ask a sign other than Scorpio
Are you a Capricorn?
Yes
Eh? Correct?
If its correct you'd react like this
Are you a Capricorn?
That's awesome. I am
Caught a Capricorn
Two questions accidentally right in a row
A small miracle
On this side
We are doing a project to guess people's sign
I guess... Pisces?
No, I'm a Leo
So it's Leo
Leo
No. Wrong guess.
-Then can you announce the correct answer?
Virgo
Ah
Not true
For some strange reason, Mikawa simply asks people their sign
Taurus?
Not true
Which one?
I'm a Scorpio woman
Because its Mikawa asking?
Nice answer
A shame
Mikawa has an advantage due to their look
But received a slightly incorrect answer
Hi！Nice to meet you！
Are you an Aquarius woman?
Not true
Are you a Pisces woman?
Are you a Leo female?
No
-No?
Are you a Scorpio female?
-Right
Hey!
-Guessed right
It's over. That was the wrong way to ask the question
What a pity!
Really a Scorpio?
So stupid to ask like this
Wow, that's a shame.
-The answer is "yes"
If you ask "Are you a Scorpio woman?" As expected, the answer is "Yes"
If you guess right they wont say "no"
"Yes, I am a Scorpio woman.
It's become like a strange uncle asking
-A strange uncle
At this point it's been two hours since the start of the questioning
The problem is 'no'
The "no" at the beginning
-And then "I am"
Have to have "No, I am"
These are not statements that occur in everyday life
-True
People who are asked answer "no" and do not say "no"
The point is to get the respondent to say "No, I am"
The challengers are caught in the quagmire of getting the respondent to say 'no'
The comedy theatre is over here
Lets ask a comedian if we see one
Maybe there will be someone who understands
They checked the appearance list of Yoshimoto Lumine on the spot
What's her sign?
Birthday November 7th
Scorpio
So she's a Scorpio woman!
We were on M-1 together so she must know our segment
Her intuition is also very strong, she should definitely say it
Shall we contact her
We can't ask her to come down, right?
-No.
I'm so anxious
That's no good
On the other side is Mikawa who changed locations
Must also be older
Are you a Libra woman?
Yes, the people who know the song is better
No, I'm a Leo woman
This is the way to do it, right?
But it's close
A very perceptive pedestrian who understands this melody has appeared
So Mikawa progresses
Over here
Are you a Pisces man?
He is a Pisces man
Ah this Pisces
-I'm a Pisces
The special power is activated
- Guessed it right again
Guessed right
Kintaro has an impressive correct rate
But is still at the starting line
Eh?
Isn't that Soshina?
Brother, wait!
-Wait!
What is it?
Sorry
We are looking for Scorpio women
I'm sure you can find one
You have to make the respondent say, "No, I'm a Scorpio woman."
There must be such a person
You wouldn't say that, would you?
Universe's Hana is a scorpio woman
So we're waiting for her here
It's break time
Is it break time?
-It's break time
Universe is finished, too.
-Then she might come down
Possible
Five minutes after Soshina leaving
Ah!
Hello, Seshita!
Another star!
I was going to walk past as if nothing had happened
Go straight around you
We just saw Soshina
Is Universe there?
-Yes
We're just waiting for her
We are fans waiting for her
She has fans now?
-Yes she does
I was watching before I came out
I don't she's in the lounge
Eh?
Gone already?
Then it's pointless for us to wait here
When Hana goes to Lumine
She takes the same route home every time
-What route?
No one knows
I wonder where she's gone?
There's a door specifically for Hana
Maybe she'd come this way.
-Is it true?
I'll ask women of the same age group to ask
Same age group and above
I'll tell you right away that your sign is Libra, right?
Wow, that's a good guess.
-Ah!
Enough, seriously!
Why is she so good at guessing?
At this point, this group give up waiting for Universe
We must ask people to answer "no"
If someone says "no"
We have to work out how to get them to say it
"Wrong" is a great phrase
So Mogu Rider's plan is
I am a Gemini man are you too?
No, I'm a Leo man
Good plan
I am a Gemini man are you too?
No, I'm a Capricorn woman
This is a good way to ask
I am a Gemini man are you too?
This should be fine now
No, I'm a Leo man
I am a Gemini man are you too?
No, I'm a Cancer woman
Keep asking!
They've now developed a fixed asking style
At this point it's been four hours since the start of the questioning
The two have the advantage
5pm already
Hello
I watched your hilarious live show earlier.
-Huh?
Seen our show?
-Yes
Can I have a moment of your time?
-Just a moment
This is the right time, the right place and the right people
Ok
Seen last year's M-1?
-Seen it
I'm a Leo man, are you too?
No, I'm a Gemini man
Idiot!
Incidentally, are you like me?
No, I'm a Scorpio woman
But we don't know if she's a real Scorpio yet
Really?
Wait wait
Wait a minute. Oh, wait a minute
You really are?
Are you really a Scorpio woman?
-Really
Great! Great!
Yeah, it's over?
Is it over?
Impressive
Yeah, it's over
Easy with this fixed pattern question
Okay? Is that okay?
No, I'm a Scorpio woman
We don't need this bit
Just let them have some fun
So, Mogu Rider win after 4 hours and 15 minutes
And after asking 27 groups of people
Kintaro is unexpectedly talented
She may use it in future
What show's gonna use that?
Guessing
At 6pm
What sign am I, please guess
Gemini
No, I'm a Scorpio woman
Then we are the same
What's she doing?
What's going on?
What is my sign?
-Guess your sign, right?
Astrology
-Libra
No, I'm a Scorpio woman
Little sister, are you a Capricorn woman?
I'm Scorpio
What a shame!
On the other side
What blood type man am I?
Type AB?
No, I'm a type O blood man
Why blood type now
What sign man am I?
A Scorpio man
No, I'm a Gemini man
What kind of conversation is this?
Using an approach like an English textbook
Telling passerbys all the key points of the answer
Indeed
Are you a Sagittarius woman?
No, I'm a Libra woman
Ah, Libra
It's 9:00 p.m
This is too funny
Kintaro is now disguised
I'm doing an imitation now of the signer
To make others make a mental connection when I ask them
Are you a Capricorn woman?
No, I'm a Scorpio woman
Thank you
Super happy
Can I see your ID card?
Want to know if you are really a Scorpio woman
I am a Capricorn
I think it is better to go along with what you say
What about cooperating with her?
Sorry
You are a Sagittarius woman
What a scary way to ask
No, I'm a Scorpio woman
Right? Finally, I'm glad I didn't give up
It's finally over. Thank you
Don't seem very scorpio-like
But I'm actually not a Scorpio, i'm a Cancer
Really? Hey!
-I just went with it
These two are played by fake Scorpios
Both fakes
Both sides are fake
Guess my horoscope
Try guessing
Cancer
No, I'm actually a Scorpio woman
Wait a minute. Let's follow this
This time I will ask you
Are you an Aries woman?
No, I'm a Scorpio woman
There we go!
This one looks like the real thing
Where is the birth year, month and day
Ah, here we go!
Yes!
What a torturous location shoot
Great!
It's really late
In summary, Kintaro completed the challenge in 9 hours and 10 minutes
After asking 75 groups of people
And finally
It's already the second day and we still can't see the end for Mikawa
If this continues
So, the staff
Decide any more would be waste for the viewers
Thus, we ended things here
It's impossible
In summary
Laugh until you're satisfied
I don't even know which version this is
I see
It's torture, this time
It is indeed a torturous shoot
What do you all think?
Understanding the rules for some of them seemed difficult
That guy
He may not understand it now
He was still wondering what kind of an outing that was
He still remembers at least
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03