Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
It's okay, we're being paid
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Hello everyone
Savannah's Takahashi
Thank you
Quite often in cartoons
When people are drinking and suddenly burst out laughing they spray the water
Has anyone actually had this experience?
When you're about to laugh, you'll feel a little bit of water coming out, so it wont all shoot out
It won't spurt out, you'll just swallow it
In relation to this, the theory I bring this time is:
In reality, spraying a drink when laughing or being frightened is quite rare
The first thing that must be done is to drink a little bit
Then something will happen
This difficult verification will depend on timing
It's quite difficult
It's very difficult. What do you all think?
I've had it come out of my nose because I've been holding it in
Don't say things like it bursting out of your nose that exceed the concept
It's way beyond this theory
So, later
The laughing or surprised water spray challenge
And the widely known air cannon is used in an experiment
To attack artists an invisible stench
Out of standing or sitting, which is more painful to do for a long period of time?
And, can anyone beat Naoki Iketani at Naoki Iketani-style push-ups?
In reality, spraying a drink when laughing or being frightened is quite rare
First to be tested is the "surprised" scenario
Once the target pours water into their mouth
Bento lunchboxes placed in the room will explode to frighten them
The first target is
Noro Kayo
Gained weight again!
That's bad
To ensure water is drunk
She is forced to run as part of a fake stamina test program
Looks like a wrestler
How is your strength now?
Already the limit...
Can I take a break?
-Absolutely
It is forbidden to drink inside the gymnasium
So you can go to the break room
Just go to the break room now
Looks super angry
Really thirsty... ok I know
She naturally goes to have a drink
Looks exhausting
When frightened, will the water in her mouth spurt out?
Indeed quite large
Just now ... are almost flying to the eyes ...
What are you talking about?
Always panting
If only she could drink in peace
Just fell down
No spray
The timing was right...
A beautiful fall but no spray
So the project was revealed
It's scary!
What the hell... scared the hell out of me
I almost cried
This is Wednesday Downtown
No way!
She's happy about it
How did this happen? Why me?
If you are frightened when drinking something, the water will spray out of your mouth, that sort of thing
It didn't spurt out... I drank it down
Did you drink it?
-It's gone
As the shock was too much she drank it all instead
The next second target is
Tiring!
Sakura Inoue
This one is also made to be thirsty enough to go to rest room
Timing, please!
Selected the plastic bottle
Drinking...
Use this opportunity to get fired up!
Scary scary scary
Talking to yourself?
What just happened was really something
What was that?
-A time lag
This kind of response?
Jumping through the air in fear
It sprayed out!
Sprayed, sprayed!
Sprayed on the floor
It's just a little different that expected
It's not what I thought it would be
And then the third target is
Harry Sugiyama
What kind of candidates are these?
His run has a superfluous feeling about it
Hot hot hot
Drink up! Drink up!
Where are you going?
Talking to yourself is scary!
Everyone is talking to themselves
Shit... tsk
Sugiyama, you can do better, right?
This is really something!
This is actually more interesting
The falling type
Yes, and a bit leaked out
What a pity, I want to see a fountain
How much is enough?
Loads more
Flamboyantly stunned
A waterfall of spray comes out
Hey? What is this?
What are you doing?
Time to explain this project
You saw that, right? I spewed it out, didn't I?
Yes you did
So wasn't it what you wanted?
Isn't it all over me?
It really scared me...
Seriously, i'm gonna die
Although different from what we expected
But this verifies that spray will occur when being scared
And that everyone will fall to the ground in fear when they encounter a benevolent explosion
So, how will the "funny" scenario turn out
This time, the target was called in with a fake plan to conduct an on-location shoot after getting drunk
At the table where getting drunk, the others will attemp to make the target laugh
Attempting to make the target laugh is...
FUJIWARA's Haranishi
Stop it!
Haranishi is preparing intently
The targets are...
Oh, his partner
No... wait...
This...
This is unbearable!
Quite unpleasant
A common scenario for group artists
It's hard to be alone with each other
And so, a temporary departure
Well...yes...
If the camera is on it is okay...
But just two people alone...
It's true
Absolutely not!
After 15 minutes of convincing a reluctant Fujimoto
Super reluctant Fujimoto
He accepts on the condition that his agent comes with him
Obon Kobon style - START
There is no such style
In addition, this time, if the setter judges that it is no longer possible to amuse the other party
They will use "bill" as a code for giving up
My back hurts!
Eh?
Can I have the bill, please?
So fast
What are you doing?
A one-hit gag to get things going
And a quick exit
What did you see?
Did you notice the staff?
So what do you think this is?
Down, right?
-Down is correct
Found out too soon
This is Down
So the project was explained
Next
Who will spray water at this joke?
It's impossible with this
Well its just a one-shot gag, just once chance
I've seen that "poof" thousands of times
I thought it was powerful enough that you'd think it was strange and laugh
So I settled on this
You use something as simple as "poof" to elicit a response?
I probably trust "poof" a lot more than I trust you
In your eyes i'm super low, then
Are there other people doing this?
How can it end like this?
The VTR time is way too short
You've shortened it
To continue the verification the target will be changed
It's impossible to spray water
I thought i'd be able to do something funny to make it happen
You're practicing "poof"?
You're practicing my "poof", but you said it wasn't funny
Ah, it really came out
How about this? How about this?
-No, it'll just scare people
This would make you laugh, right?
The audience will be scared, don't do it
No way! That was a real "poof"
The next target for the FUJIWARA group to challenge is
Viking's Nishimura
I get the impression that he doesn't laugh much
Hey... camping?
Not camping, just work
Not a camping trip?
-Not camping
The atmosphere seems a bit more relaxed
So, Yoshimura
-I'm Nishimura
Nishimura, Nishimura
-I am Nishimura
It's a trap!
Doing faces now
A bit strange, huh?
Weird vibe
Weird emotions.
-Not weird at all
Just drink more
I'm not much of a drinker
I'm a little drunk
Yeah
After this
Haranishi
-Thank you very much
Thank you very much. Thank you very much
Nishimura, please
Thank you very much.
-Thank you very much
Weird drinking game
At this point it's almost time for the next target to arrive so it's forced to end
So difficult
Nishimura you're coming over here now
Eh? Eh~
-Offensive side
Me attack? So just now you were pranking me?
I was pranked?
Haranishi pranked me
The target moves to the offensive side afterwards
So you're an attacker now
-Wow~ tough!
So the next target was
Omiya, that...
-I'm Komiya
You don't need to do such a old joke
Omiya... it's Omiya
I was wondering if you would reply with something like "I'm Shima"
Can I feed you some air?
Eh, what what what
Air, air
Feeding air?
Aren't you a bit too far gone for recording?
The store manager just recommended it to me
How is it possible to recommend air?
Hand Hair Spice
If you're gonna do that then please really pluck some hair
With me you don't joke back you just criticise
No, I'm sorry. I'm sorry about that
Don't just do the ambulance sound, do a bit more movement
-So strong, so perceptive.
Although everyone is playing dumb, no spraying is occurring
Has anyone ever told you you have bad breath?
-No, i've never heard such a thing
When you put the beer in your mouth
Gargle a little bit
Dirt on the tongue will come off.
-Never heard it
What's this rumor?
You'll see
Impressive
What are you guys doing here?
You're too drunk!
What are you doing?
-What are you doing?
I'm sorry, it's because I laughed out loud
Not bad
It did spray out
So the project was revealed
-It worked!
What worked?
What is this success about?
But he held a bit in...
But I guess it doesn't matter
Just a little bit
Does below 100% not count as success?
As the result was slightly less than expected
And somewhat stoic
The verification continues
Komatsu, what did you do today?
Who'd spray at this?
What did you say?
-Komatsu
What does Komatsu mean?
Is that Ota?
{Ota: Yutaka Ota, a former Japanese national team fencer who won the silver medal in the men's foil final at the Beijing Olympics on August 13, 2008, although he lost 9:15 to Germany's Kleblinck, but it was a breakthrough for Japanese fencing at the Olympics.
Ota, right?
{Phishing: A scam in which users' accounts, passwords, and account information are obtained from electronic communications disguised as well-known trusted corporate media
Here, Otake is confusing Fencing with Phishing
Phishing
Phishing…
Otake displays his "talents" without an ounce of regret
What is the name of that fortune-teller, do you know?
Do you know what they are called?
Like this?
It's a stick thing, right? Like that, right (the chopsticks)?
I don't, no
-Neither do I
I can't believe he's amused by this kind of thing
This makes him laugh?
Although it didn't spurt, it came out of the mouth, and so it was a success
In the challenge so far, the results have varied
The next targets are
That Canthony.
-I'm not Canthony. I'm Anthony
Hey, Anthony?
It's Anthony. Why don't you know my name all of a sudden?
You've never done this joke even once before
Movie Capital
What is Movie Capital?
Ah, sorry, it's Hollywood
Too different
-Putting a spin on it is good
What is Movie Capital
Let's settle the bill then
Is it not doable?
Can we please pay our bill?
Settle the bill for us, please
The final target of the day is...
Panther's Ogata
All drunk, right?
They've drunk quite a lot
Where's Ogata today?
-I am Ogata
I am Ogata, what is this all of a sudden?
I am Ogata
Drink up, drink up
Now, right?
Please wait, I haven't caught up yet
Sorry, I'll have another drink
Definitely had more
Where are you looking?
Is that ok?
Cheers!
Ah, what are you doing?
That can't be done to seniors, right?
With an armpit appearance by Anthony, Ogata's weakness is discovered
So
Hurry up!
What's going on?
Stop it!
Super defenseless
Stop, hey, don't come again
What the hell is going on?
What exactly...
In summary
There are indeed some people that will laugh and spray
What do you think, Matsumoto?
I don't know, I don't understand what the hell was going on
But it was pretty interesting
The people drinking water had it pretty tough
The bento blast
I can't believe someone would say "get fired up!" to themselves
And FUJIWARA's unexpected relationship
-It is really bad
You both hate it when you're alone too, don't you?
As soon as you open the door, you'll be overwhelmed to a certain degree, right?
Yes, it is pretty annoying
I hate talking
And I hate having to talk to Hamada alone
I always feel like he's gonna come over and kiss me
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's Chocolate Planet!
Hello everyone
They're always here!
You should just stay here
Why are you dressed like this?
Good question, I've brought a small prop with me
When it comes to small props I must be mentioned
I am the king of small props
Is he OK?
So, what do you see?
What the hell?
-Don't see anything
Can't you see anything? What about when I open it like this
Oh, awesome
Isn't this one of Chujiro's?
※Yonemura Chujiro: After graduating from Tokyo Gakugei University, he was a physics teacher at a metropolitan high school, and then founded Yonemura Chujiro Science Production and began appearing in magazines and TVs. The reason for starting the show was that he used to hate science, so he wanted children to learn science happily.
Yes, yes, it's Chujiro's
This is the air cannon that we have all seen before
This time we bring a theory related to this air cannon
Oh yeah?
Please take a look
If the air cannon's air is colorless, there is no way to dodge it
What?
The smoke just now, you could all see it
That means it has color.
-White, right?
If you don't add anything, what you put out is just a cloud of air
Indeed
If it's just a cloud of air, you can't see it
There is no way to detect that air mass
Because it is colorless
-Yes, colorless
Then who can see it when you broadcast it?
Instead of color, we are adding a smell
A very stinky type of smell
If you get hit, you'll smell it
-So that's how it is
There's no way to avoid it
This way no way anyone can hide, right?
The volume just went up!
Yes, yes, yes, yes
That's the theory we came with
If the air cannon's air is colorless, there is no way to dodge it
There is no way to avoid it!
For this, individuals are called out for a fake shopping show project
Yes, there is no way to avoid it
And the air cannon commonly seen in science experiment programs on TV is used
And will be launched by this sound operator during the shoot
Although there is no color, the stench will be unprecedentedly strong
The first target is...
Hello, I'm Mikako Tabe.
Yoshiko
This has nothing to do with Mikako Tabe
How dare you!
So delicious
So dirty
After nearly an hour of serious shopping location shooting
It's quite real!
It's almost time to give Yoshiko a shot of the air cannon
Here you are
-Thanks
Wow, it looks really good
Please take your time.
-Okay, thanks
Is the lighting OK?
-Yes
Then start eating one.
-Okay, I'll eat it
That box is really...
-Didn't notice?
It looks so delicious!
There's already smoke in it
Yes, but its invisible
Here I go
It's steaming hot!
What will happen?
That stinks!
What the hell is this?
If there's color then they'll be able to avoid it!
What's going on here?
So~ stinky!
It stinks!
The next target is...
Hello everyone, I'm Nadal
Nadal
White teeth la
Quite popular
Like Yoshiko, after almost an hour of shopping outside
He receives an air cannon one-shot to the soul
This is shrimp, right?
This is a crab.
-Excuse me
At least it was in the shell category
Wow, shellfish is really delicious!
What will happen?
Ah, stinky stinky stinky
What? What? What? What? What? It stinks!
Super stinky!
What are you guys doing?
Ah, stinky stinky stinky
What? What? What? What? What? It stinks!
Super stinky, what are you guys doing?
Ah, stinky stinky stinky
What? What? What? What? What? It stinks!
Super stinky, what are you guys doing?
Damn, that stinks. What the hell?
That's enough, that stinks!
What are you doing? It stinks, right?
What do you think it was?
It stinks. Is it shit?
Being smoked at close range surely cannot be avoided
You'll be smoked, certainly
There's nothing you can do about it
Really can't be avoided at such close range
Next, individuals are tricked to participate in fake commercial performances
In the middle of the show, the air cannon will be fired from a distance of 15 meters
In the middle of the performance, will this inconvenient situation cause them to react? We will see
The target this time is
No problem
Akira100%
This is concerning
Sketch: Unarmed detective
Sheriff, thanks for your hard work
Is this the scene of the convenience store robbery?
The one over there is the store manager?
Store Manager!
It's about to launch
Wait a minute, there is something on the ground
It's blonde hair
Wait, there's one over there
There are also blondes here
Store manager, do you have any blondes here?
Difficult to time
Yeah, can only aim when he's standing
What? The part-time worker who quit is blonde?
Woo, woo ah, stinks...
That guy's a-
Oooh, stinks...
That guy's-
I'm sorry...
That guy-
What? The one who worked here before was the blonde?
Woo, woo ah, stink...
That guy's a-
Must not be a normal kind of stench
Indeed
Despite being in the middle of a performance
He lets out a series of violent dry heaves
Next
Excuse me, have you seen any blond men around here?
What? They went over that wall and ran across?
Sheriff, let's also go quickly
He can't work out where the stench is coming from
Next...
Must be pretty disturbing
Don't argue
Too loud is very-
I know, I know, I know
Wearing-
This is really the best thing to wear
Uhhhh- sorry sorry sorry
Then I'll take it off
Despite stench after stench, he manages to finish his 15-minute performance
Oh uh ah thank you thank you
The plan is revealed
Thank you!
I'm sorry
Any thoughts?
Ah, it's great that everyone was so enthusiastic about the show
It seems he hasn't realize this was all a set up
Is there anything that felt wrong?
Something wrong?
Something a little concerning was...
A smell...
Uh that... if it was someone in the audience then I shouldn't be saying this
A nice man
In fact, this is not a commercial performance, but Wednesday Downtown
What!?
This prank is too lethal, right?
The next target is
He won't respond much, surely
Mr Playing Cards
Doesn't even talk
The man who doesn't say a word
What reaction will occur in the face of a sudden mid-show stench
What the hell is this thing?
Gently pushed away
A wave of the hand
Presumably due to the stench
How can such a thing happen?
He fluffs an important part
The last target is...
Hello everyone
It's Ikesaki
Ikesaki
Unprecedented! The single artist of amazing wind and fury!
The man who both loves and is loved by the humor!
Sunshine!
This is a big deal!
Ye——————！
Justice-
That stinks
In summary
It seems like the colorless air cannon could be useful in the future
How was it?
-Very interesting
You can't hide from it, right? There's no way to hide from it
There is indeed no way to hide
Why?
-Eh?
Why do you have to do such things?
Well, the results were quite strong
What would you do if something like this happened during a performance
If you encounter something like this when performing...
If it was manzai then you'd probably talk about it
If it is a duo, they'll both think its the other one's fault
They'll think thats the reason
I'd think "Is this guy taking a dump?"
I'd probably be pretty worried
Be brave and see how the veterans deal with it
Try it with Obon Kobon
-No please no
They'd probably start fighting
They will fight because they suspect each other
"This old man's finally shitting on stage"
Now its time for Everybody's Theories
Tonight's presenters are...
Alco&Peace
Without further ado
When someone reaches the status of the guests tonight
They are bound to have a lot of work of sitting around watching video's like tonight's show
That doesn't sound too good
-You are too bad
This is people that are already at the top
Sitting in a situation like this
How many hours do you think you could stay seated for?
Sitting the whole time?
The plane trip to foreign countries takes a long time
-Indeed
That's true
-You get tired of sitting
In relation to this, today we bring you this hypothesis
Out of standing or sitting, which is more painful to do for a long period of time?
Hard to say
-It's really hard to say
Sitting all the time is very tired
-Is it?
Two hours in the car, your butt hurts
True
Its very tiring having to stand while going through so many ero-videos that don't appeal to you
Just leave then
Out of standing or sitting, which is more painful to do for a long period of time?
So, the validation is conducted in this studio
The four challengers are
I think it will be very miserable
This cast
First, the challenge is decided by drawing lots
Sitting on the floor
-I can move while standing
Can't move while standing
Standing but can't move is too tiring
What's going on?
Oh, no, no.
-Can't move, right?
This is super easy for me
-Sitting in the chair
By the way, the chair is this one
The chair is at the lower limit of what can barely be considered a chair
Accidentally standing is more tiring than you think, right?
Once I hit 40 I want to sit in a soft chair and act as host
This time it's a combination showdown
The duo who stays until the end wins
The challenge begins
It begins
Is Anthony sitting in the right position?
Sitting on the ground, hands cannot touch the ground
If I sit cross-legged, my legs will go numb immediately
My weight will instantly slow down the blood circulation
Not good, this position is also a little strange, i'm getting some numbness
Only sat for three minutes
You're not going to die, are you?
Hands can not touch the ground
You don't have to be so nervous at the beginning
I can stand on both legs separately
If I get tired I can change legs
Feet cannot leave the ground
So maybe it is more difficult to sit
My friends back home
And others think that when we test such theories
There's a break in the middle
If we actually had a chance to rest it wouldn't be so bad
They're huddled together
By now, an hour has passed in a harmonious manner
This light looks so nasty
Surprisingly, it is completely fine
At this moment i'm not as tired as expected
I'm suffering
Anthony looks pretty tortured
I'm feeling slightly tormented
I didn't expect my butt to be so sore
Really?
You're impressive to stand for an hour and not feel anything
Totally comfortable
Restlessness begins to set in for the seating team
Two hours after the start
Is this the toilet?
▼  They can go to the toilet once every two hours for One minute
▼  But must keep their position
In there
How to go to the toilet
Can I stand up to open the door?
Should be able to?
And then I can only sit down to piss?
-Yeah
Then the time reaches 12:30
It's already midday
There are three capsules in this room with menus written on them
Please find them
I'm super hungry
I'm hungry too.
-Can't you give it to us properly?
Only three so one goes without?
It's lunchtime
Find the hidden menus in the room
And get the corresponding lunch
Sakai can look for it then
There's one!
Inside that, put your hand inside
The Alco&Peace team get the first capsule
Find more
Not only that
Ah, there's one below
This is something only Anthony can get
No, it's out of reach
Use your feet to reach
The sofa's gotta be moved to reach it
That's it!
Great!
One more to go!
There is a good chance that it is in here
Dangerous!
I'll hold it for you.
-What?
There it is, there it is
Hey, is there one there?
Found it! But out of reach
I see it!
-It's out of reach!
I got it.
-Great!
Found it!
Curry Rice
Superb
Cup Noodles
-Also good
Bento
-Wow!
No, no, no. One of them is mine
Your sense of survival is really too weak
I didn't think it would be so easy to steal it from you
Why should we give it to you?
You are not in a position to blame me
You didn't do anything
I found it!
Then don't tell them!
Get it yourself, isn't that better?
It's too high I can't reach it
The final result of the discussion is...
Sakai gets cup noodles
Otoni and Hirako share the curry rice
And Anthony, who refused to compromise, took the bento box
You can eat at the table
Yes, I'm eating here
You're good
-Yes i'm good at looking after people
Thank you
Want a bite?
If we were in the movie, you'd be the first one to die
After eating, 3 hours has passed from the start of the verification
But it's really good to be able to stand the whole time
I'm getting a bit of a reprieve now, my fatigue level has dropped from 3 to 2
Only 2
Just now it was 3.5, now it's about 2, and time is going faster
I'm about 6
Standing all the time is good
I feel more relaxed than before
However
It's been 4 hours
I'm feeling fatigue of 9.5. It's bad
Seriously, I'm really dying, its 9.5
Really?
I'm really in pain
At this stage
Anthony on the floor's pain level seems to have increased dramatically
The floor isn't even soft
-Yes
It's over. 9.85.
-This is bad
It's impossible
It's great to be able to walk around
You'd be jealous!
I want to walk!
-The view is completely different
I want to see it too
Look at me and tell me what it looks like.
-Ok
A different angle is good
-Indeed
8 hours and 30 minutes have passed and no one has admitted defeat
Amazing
-8 hours?
I'm sorry.
-Huh?
Let's have dinner together before we go
Do not give up, Anthony!
Time for dinner.
-Great!
This time there are no teams, you'll cook and eat together
So, the two people who can move cook dinner
Everyone's gone, and suddenly it's painful
Lonely, isn't it?
Hirako, who cannot move, has pain in his legs and feet at this time
Next
My back is not working
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
No, seriously
Let's eat, let's eat
Let's talk after dinner, Anthony
Don't overdo it
Anthony, don't!
Wait wait
It's not a good time, is it?
-It's almost time to eat
Sit up, Anthony!
Great job!
Safe
He's not a baby!
Where do you hurt?
It hurts everywhere. It's starting to hurt in the neck too.
-Neck?
Neck, back, waist and legs
Every part from top to bottom
Pain all over my body
No, Anthony!
Hurry up and make dinner!
OI, YAKISOBA!
OK
Ah, I can't!
Check it out. Yakisoba.
-It looks delicious!
Anthony, eat
Can I eat it?
So gentle
It's okay, eat it
Anthony can only forget the pain when he eats
This guy doesn't given up easily
Is Anthony still alive?
I'm fine, i'm fine
Let's eat this ramen too!
Do you have chopsticks?
Heh~
Quickly answer to "i've got some"
-I've got some
Say "Yes" loudly
I can't take it anymore
Anthony!
-What have you done?
You've held on for so long already!
ANTHONY!!
Seriously?
Ramen!
-Anthony!
I can't
Anthony!
Sitting on the floor, Anthony loses after 9 hours and 39 minutes
Still very impressive
Whoa it feels super weird
Super weird
Feels like being on a train
After sitting for so long and suddenly standing up you look so big
Anthony looks weird
Was he this tall before?
I feel a really powerful shaking
It's shaking!
This room is not tilted, right?
-No.
Sure enough, sitting on the floor is torturous!
Hands can't even lay on the ground is also tough
I feel like Haranishi couldn't sit on the floor for a second
He's the kind of person who can't sit still?
Another two hours have passed since Anthony's defeat
The time is 10:00 p.m
Finally
Fatigue and a feeling of fullness cause Hirako to be attacked by the Sandman
Bed time
I can't hold it any longer
Standing still without moving is too tough
It seems that you two will have to battle it out
Well, that's fine for the moment
But it won't last much longer
Torturous
Can't even imagine the torment
Already asleep?
Moved?
Wow, this is really...
The end
Standing and dozing, Hirako lost his balance
What a tragic exit
Defeated in 13 hours and 34 minutes
After eating, the soles of the feet were nourished
So it felt like I could still hold on a little bit
Are you relaxed in this position now?
Super relaxed
I guess it that's how it'd be
So now it's a duel between Sakai and Otini
How is it going now?
Pretty exhausted
The minute you stop walking your legs will stop working
The heel is especially uncomfortable
My back and butt is surprisingly tired
At 0:00, midnight, the calendar is turned forward a day
And we ask them what they would like to eat
As a late night snack
It's delicious! It's so good!
After 15 hours and 20 minutes
It's after 1:00!
I can't do it anymore
Otini, I can't
I really want to use my hands as support
-No.
Can I please?
-What?
Can I ask you?
It's also hard to give up
Don't look at me
What's going on here?
I'll leave the rest to you. I'm sorry
Too tiring!
Standing and walking Sakai is defeated in 15 hours and 37 minutes
Impressive you could stand that long
Too tiring!
Now it's too easy, super comfy
That's for sure
At this point, the winner is decided
And Otini attempts to complete 24-hours
Wow~
But
Like a little baby
Thirty minutes after Sakai's defeat
Sleepy Otini is also attacked by the Sandman
It's easier to stay awake if you have someone to talk to
Oh no
-He's gonna fall!
I'm going to be scolded again
Otini, sitting in a chair, is defeated after 16 hours and 10 minutes
We won't scold you
In summary
If it wasn't Otini, the 24-hour mark might've been reached
What do you all think?
Sitting is easier to hold on
It was awesome! Like a blockbuster movie
In the end, there was lots of "Don't look at me" and "I can't do it"
There was a sense of teamwork too
-Yeah
It was a great story
If anyone says "comedians are useless"
I'll beat them up
You're in that headspace now?
After all, we went through this theory together
It gave rise to many emotions
So, that's that. But we also have another theory today
More?
I presume everyone has done push-ups before?
-Yes
Matsumoto is good at them because he is a meat daruma...
What a venomous tongue!
You're saying strange things today
Because his muscle is very well developed, I mean...
In a good way, right?
Yes, I say this with great respect
When it comes to the basic technique its like this, with the hands as support
You bend the elbow and go down
Yes, yes
Yes, that's it
On the TBS former program
Sport Man No. 1
Was there cheating in regard to this?
Push-ups were performed on this show in a peculiar way
Really?  -Yes.
Someone did?
Please take a look at this evidence
On the right Nakayama bends his arms flexing arm
But Iketani next to him
Doesn't seem to be moving his elbows much
Yes, indeed
Ah, he's not using his arms
Pretty sly
Indeed
Only the chin?
-Jaw only
Super happy, but too cunning
Why is this being brought up now?
Someone needs to intervene
Now?
In the final days of the Heisei era
Yes, you can't leave it until after the next year
Exactly
-Yeah
So, the theory is this:
Can anyone beat Naoki Iketani at Naoki Iketani-style push-ups?
You've already said it!
He's already obviously the best!
Can it be proven?
Can anyone beat Naoki Iketani at Naoki Iketani-style push-ups?
First, we ask the man himself
What "Naoki Iketani style"? First of all...
Look, he's getting angry
We've been doing push-ups like that since we were kids
Although very concerned about the "we"...
His brother also does it, right?
Yukio too
-Yeah
As he doesn't seem to realize, we ask the question again
There is an impression that "it is a bit cunning"...
No no no no
It's not a trick!
This place is stiff, right?
It's not about that, though, it's about going down
So I think its a standard push-up
So
This time, we apply Naoki Iketani's so-called "standard" to the rules for a competition
Whether the arms are bending or not is of no concern
Instead, the person who presses the button more than once with his or her chin wins
So, this is Naoki Iketani-style "Quick Muscle"
It's "Iketani Naoki style", because it has my name on it
I don't think I can lose
Yeah
You have to win
Challenging this founder are 3 people who are proud of their muscle
First of all, the first winner of Sasuke
Who once did 307 push-ups in 3 minutes
Kazuhiko Akiyama, the world Quick Muscle record holder
This is a good one
I hold the record with confidence
But I think I can exceed 307 times
The next challenger is
The man with both flesh and chin, Antokino Inoki
Ah, this is a good one
Just the right type of potential for this competition
Naoki Iketani-style, that's not a push-up
He'll witness the chin difference
The final challenger is
There he is!
The injured Katsumi Yamada
3 minutes of push-ups changed my life
I participated in the Kinki Regional Competition and won there.
Then I was called up to take part in Sasuke
He cares a lot, then
So, Yamada and the other four
Employ the system in a competition
Quick Muscle in the style of Naoki Iketani
Naoki Iketani style push-ups
Who will be the winner?
Cares a lot!
The result...
3 2 1
Now the 3 minutes of hell begins
Who will be the king?
What will happen?
First of all, Iketani doesn't bend his arms and only moves his face up and down to press the button
Look at the Iketani-style Quick Muscle!
To not be called "cunning"
Tonight this man is the rule
This man cannot lose. How about it, Iketani?
However, Quick Muscle world record holder Akiyama
Is going at a speed that exceeds that of Iketani
That's fast!
No bending of the arms at all
Only small movements to increase the count
Not bad for world-class Akiyama
He's showing a nice understanding of the Iketani-style rules
And quickly exceeds 130 times
So fast!
Is this a push-up?
Not push-ups at all
So, what about the injured Mr. Sasuke, Yamada?
What's going on?
What are you doing? This guy...
For some reason, he is the only one doing actual push-ups
Although he shows strong power, his count is growing slowly
Next: Antokino Inoki
It's almost not push-ups at all
He is just using the stretch of his jaw to increase the count
This is not Iketani-style anymore!
Will this be allowed?
However, there is no problem at this time
Only with this rare chin and his sense of competition
A very impressive chin!
So, one minute has passed
Akiyama leads the pack
He will soon reach 300
Then, our own Iketani, followed by the black horse Antokino Inoki
How is Yamada?
He's been overtaken too far
Yamada, go for it!
Is his suspicious injury okay?
So,
Half of the time has now passed
They're doing the same thing
So, at this point it's 1:30
Will the creator Iketani be able to hold on and catch up to international champion Akiyama?
2 minutes have passed
At about twice the speed of the normal Quick Muscle
Several people experience head and jaw fatigue they had never experienced before
Next
3 2 1
It's over!
Naoki Iketani-style push-ups: the winner is Akiyama with 544 times
What you just did was not push-ups, right?
Yeah
In summary
Although it wasn't a push-up, Akiyama won
So... the results
The person that can do standard push-ups the best can also do Iketani-style push-ups very well
That's right
Yes, indeed
It's easier than push-ups, right?
Yes, you just have to move here
Is Iketani unchanged from the records of that time?
Good question
He's been doing it since the old days, Iketani-style
I see
What good did this serve in the end?
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03