determined to inform in the crowd
has a debt of about one used domestic car.
Welcome to a 2-hour episode of Wednesday Downtown
Thanks!
It's a special episode
Let's welcome our first presenter
Who is it?
It's Milk Boy!
Hello everyone, we are the Milk Boys
You're just doing the opening of your manzai!
Thank you very much
Now picking up the film wrapped around the outside of the crab stick
What the hell?
-Thank you very much
No amount of this stuff is too much
The film?
-Yes, film
Although very sudden
What is posted on SNS will be written as network news at least once
Even if things are trivial, they will become network news
You made a weird "nyu" sound
You have to understand a little bit I am nervous
Don't make things too tense
There's still something down there
Thank you very much
Now picking up soggy algae
Thank you very much, there isn't much of this type of stuff
Thank you very much
I can't not pretend something is happening coming here
So, we bring you a project about network news
It is this:
Can't go home until being talked about on network news
Sounds tough
I see
What is it?
This involves deliberately doing something to make the news
And they can't go home until they achieve it
Intentionally difficult
Yuuki can go home right away then
※He got in trouble for a cheating scandal
Can go home immediately
Words will also become network news
Every time you say something, it turns into news
So, posting on social media
They can't ho home until they get on network news
And
Entertainer, athlete and historical rankings
A ranking of the popularity of Japanese people in the past and present
And Dancho vs. Kasuga patience challenge
You can't go back without being listed in the network news
Everyone is very happy!
People who can easily be covered
Indeed easy to be in the news
The above members are a collection of people with different likelihoods of being on the news
Good selection
I'm on a hot streak
I can be on the news
Indeed
I put my feet like this and lie down
I just say hello and i'm on the news, it's over, I can go back immediately
Bye-bye
Big star!
For today
There's 3 strong 2 weak
Indeed
No problem, right?
It's okay!
How can such people get on the news?
And so, the challenge begins
First
Is it okay to just tweet as usual?
Straight away
Kuro-chan is impressive
Can you tell us what content you are posting?
Can I send "Michopa~" now?
Eh, "Michopa~" will make the internet news?
Sometimes
Really?
"Michopa will hate it, don't do it" or something like that
Michopa~
Should work
Known for his cumbersome operation, Kuro-chan
Immediately, he sends a disgusting filtered photo
That's weird. Will that work?
Can we go to TBS first?
What's going on?
Want to see who is in today
After I combine with other artists, it'll be easier
When standing on Kamaitachi before
You could see my underwear
That became network news
"SUNDAY JAPON"
Some others
Wada is here now!
Great! If you take a selfie with Wada it will be 100% popular!
This person is really...
-Not respectful
That quick?
Definitely will make the news
There is no appointment for anything!
It's fine, Sanma and Takeshi Kitano,i've taken pictures with all of them with this thing
She's messing around
Ah!
Good morning
Awesome
What's happening so early?
Social distance, distance!
Keep your distance!
You're working really hard, so early
Yes, can't get too close
So cute!
However
What's going on?
Went to a meeting
You're too scary
Couldn't get a photo
Obviously wanted to take a group photo
Eh?
Wait wait
What's going on?
I was followed by him now
Really?
Eh, now he's my follower, so cute!
Never uses honorifics
Having a meeting inside
Have a look
So stalkerish
What's up?
You'll be told off for this
This kid is crazy
This will make the news
Really knows what she's doing
Now that Wada is following me, he'll definitely see this tweet
You are so loud, seriously
Before it becomes network news, I might get beaten up
But
But wait, it's 9:00
I have to go live
There's a show with Ahn Mika and Chris Matsumura as MCs
Wait, let's go over there
So, Fuwa leaves the scene temporarily to go to a live broadcast
First i'll look at the news
Then
If there is something I can copy, i'll copy it
I'll send a tweet with something similar to become news
Ah, Hiromi
Hiromi claims to be a "Tokyo Disneyland virgin"
Ah, Matsumoto Hitoshi
Playing a smartphone game debut
And that makes news?
Ah!
Takuya Kimura has failed to quit smoking
Should I quit smoking?
So
Okay, tweeted
At the age of 20, I started to smoke 2 packs of cigarettes a day
decided to quit smoking
This is the last one of my life
Can this make the news?
And
I have debt too
I want to inform the public that i'm in debt for a used car
Seems likely
Informed Twitter about quitting his smoking
So, let's see what happens
It'd be better to write the amount of debt
Yeah
Sari Kato said she left her daughter with
someone else and went on a one-night
trip to a hot spring by herself, and was
criticized for it
There will be criticism today, too, it seems
The makeup is too exaggerated
By the way, recently
What are the things about you that have become network news?
I cooked muffins that looked like roasted mushrooms, or something like that
What's wrong with this person?
"Roasted mushrooms" and so on became the internet news
The place where Sari Kato goes is
A 120 square meter photography studio
The rent is up to 1,030,000 yen
The studio was rented for a video shoot, right?
That...
A multi-purpose meeting in the studio
A multi-purpose photo studio
Why is this person so rich?
How does this person make so much money?
Really want to know
In this strange location, how will she try to get the public's attention?
My daughter's toy is a Givenchy bear doll
In 30 minutes, it was on the news
Her Dior bottle also made the news
Pitching news related to luxury goods seems to be easy to make online news
At the time of the webcast
There are definitely people who ask, "Whose clothes are these? Please take a full body shot" and other questions
So, the very first pitches were
Detailing the day's outfit and price to the public
The kind that can immediately make the news
Star Matching
This way
The total amount is out there
Will it work so soon?
About the same as a normal monthly income
The total is 13,770,080,000 yen
Monthly income?
Most people's general income
Who's? Who's?
Ready to post to instagram
Today, I was told by my manager that i'm
like a walking department store, so I calculated
the total amount and made it public for
the first time
Today's outfit is 13.8 million
Should be close
One of the two weaker people...
We've gotta see this
Joyman Takagi
I get coverage sometime
"I saw Joyman?" on Twitter there are many such tweets
When i'm just around
Ordinary people also tweet "Joyman is here"
So, aiming for the common man
I'm gonna go to the front of the company and try and attract some attention
No, no, no
In front of Yoshimoto Kogyo, he starts his battle to try and get someone to tweet about him
Why?
He's looking
What's going on?
If I go to an idol's house it should be easy
Isn't Rina Hashimoto a good choice?
Rina Hashimoto?
The black diamond
Her words will be in the news
What the hell?
She's also my type
What the hell is this guy?
So this will definitely be covered
I'm calling
So
What is he doing?
Hello
Ah, hello, Rina?
Sorry to call you so suddenly
What is it?
Can I come to your house? I'm on a shoot
Eh, well, no
Not really?
Eh why why why?
-No way
Asking so suddenly, of course not
Although sudden
But it's for Wednesday Downtown
Despicable!
So bad
Under the pretext of program planning
Just for a moment
Stalkingly negotiated for 5 minutes
No hesitation at all!
Wait, I really just woke up
That' fine that's fine
I'll come over
Let's say in 30 minutes
In 30 minutes? Got it
Really just got up
Not a single word of respect for him
So, during the journey
Wednesday Magic
Should I do my top 5 girls?
Or 7, like God 7?
Kuro-chan's Girl Ranking
Also posted on instagram and Ameba Blog
Kuro-chan's hands don't stop moving
Impressive
"How much would you do an AV for?" I've been asked that
The fee mentioned at the time was over 100 million yen
But if I was actually interested, the real thing
Would actually be a lot lower
She can't decide what to send next here
A different type of monster
Rina, can I come in?
Really!?
So gentle
Can I take a selfie with you in your pajamas?
"Rina's pajamas are so cute", something like that
It'll definitely make the news
So, sorry, can you put on your pajamas?
Me?
Yeah
How does he know where she lives?
Really?
Shame on you!
I'm sorry, i'll do anything you want after
What kind of relationship is this?
So, after forcing her to change into pajamas
The photography session starts
That's good, that's good, that's good
I can't believe she really let him shoot
Pajamas... I'm
sorry to bother
you! The pajamas
of Rina are also
lovable~♪
I've gotta go now
I will come back
Only stayed for 10 minutes
Kuro-chan was soon driven out
Even so
2.5 hours have passed since the start
The contributions of the 5 members posts are shown below
Impossible
What is this for?
Good morning
Nothing happened
Although Disneyland is reopening,
for those who haven't been there
yet, let Kuro-chan as
Donald Duck heal your hearts
No one has been successful yet
Fuwa and and Sari are the ones to watch
Morita and Joyman?
No, those two people do not have a chance
They'll be doing it for a week, right?
At this time
Ah!
Eh?
Aren't I up already!?
Got up while not even paying attention!
Scary scary
What's happened?
Impressive
The "God 7" article
Really want to beat him up
Kuro-chan Introduces His "God 7" List of Favorite Girls
So fast!
Who is in first and second place?
It's in the news!
Thank you very much!
As before, Kuro-chan's followers are trolling him like crazy
"The comments such as "I don't think he's in anyone's mind," and "It's like Death Note..." keep coming
That's not true
They should be very happy
Although Fuwa said she would never lose
No, no, no, the popularity level is completely different
I'm not like that noisy woman
So, 2 hours and 42 minutes after the start
Kuro-chan finishes first
Sorry, this is Kuro-chan
I'm already in the news
Eh? It's a lie, right?
Sorry, a genuine news publication
Really? It's in the news?
I'm up!
What is this tone of voice?
How did you make the news?
What made the news?
My top-7 ranking of girls
I just needed to rank 7
Really?
-So fast
Eh, wait
I can't believe i'm not in the list
What's wrong with you?
Why do you want to be in that ranking?
Everyone, go for it!
It's too weird to try to want to be in that ranking
Okay, I'm hanging up
So noisy!
This condescending attitude
Really seems like they're trying to be funny, so noisy
There's no use for them, it should just be all about me
Such a shame. I want to be number one
We're too slow
Its my manager and driver's fault
It's definitely not my fault
Scary face
Here
So scary
Sari has an appointment at 11:30
Who cares about you?
What do you have to do?
Date
So I have to stop for the moment
What!?
Regardless of the ongoing shoot
Due to a lunch date with a man, Sari Kato's shoot is temporarily halted
On the other hand, Morita, is at TBS TV
It's gonna be tough for Morita
Ah, Milk Boys!
I could meet Milk Boy
Really?
We have known each other since we were in Osaka
Excuse me
Good morning
It's been a long time. I'm Morita
Yeah, we know. What's up?
What is this?
Long time no see
We played together several times at a public performance
Indeed
We've seen each other a few times
I never thought I would see you here one day
Yes, in Tokyo, indeed
Its very emotional
I just met Milk Boys, who I performed
together with to just a few people in
Osaka, at a TV station in Tokyo. I
never thought that the day would
come when we could meet in a
lounge several times bigger than the
shabby stage. I want to cry a little.
Let's drink together when we can
Super long
Mixing Asakusa Kid with Nagabuchi
A heart-warming story
Surprise happenings can make the news
I want to go home with this, really
Then, after 4 and a half hours from the start
Joyman Takagi's attempted public sighting led to no results
Too bad
I'll try uploading my own and getting someone to cover it
Where is Joyman?
A change of strategy
On the other hand, after the 90-minute live show
Fuwa is finally back
Why didn't you share anything?
I planned to post while there
But they just kept talking all the time
I couldn't look at my phone for even 1 second
Okay! OK
I like Toshiya!
I've tagged him
And
I was shooting when Anh Mika came in
Ah, Ahn Mika
Nice yukata!
What's going on here?
There is no wall here
There is!
No wall
She did a mime
This'll surely be big
Magic Chris Matsumura!
Chris Matsumura is still Chris Matsumura after his transformation
Videos with collaborators
Been ages since I've seen Chris Matsumoto
Are shared continuously
It's here.
RT Where is Joyman?
After 7 hours
It's now 3pm
Sari Kato returns from a date
Where are you going?
After checking the phone
Ah, news!
This would happen
Real amount
But this will not be without repercussions
So, 7 hours after the start, Sari Kato goes home
I've made the news
It's a lie, right?
Really?
-It's a lie, right?
The first and second place is a Kuro-chan and Sari Kato...
Japan has entered a not-so-good era
You are too rude to say that!
Two people are finished
Where should we go?
Today is the election for the governor of Tokyo, right?
Yes, today is July 5th
Yes, this is the voting day for the Tokyo governor's election
I want to take this opportunity to vote
Really, it's not for location shooting
So
Finished
Disguised in order not to cause trouble for the voting office
Went to vote
I'm off to vote
What's going on here?
Did it!
I always perform my national duty
Really, if I had posted about this, they would have got 500 million votes from young people
Eh, did you take a picture?
Didn't take any photos 'cause it was so dark
So now I'm going to take pictures in front of the metropolitan hall
Great! A particularly good shot!
Great! Took a great photo!
Great, right?
What a great photo!
This is a really good photo
Indeed news worthy
Too photogenic, right?
It's really something
A Japanese girl, right?
Full compliance with national
obligations, everyone go and
vote!
Tweeted
This is good!
Just 10 minutes later
Ah, already on 10,000
There's 10,000 likes.
-10,000 likes?
It's a big deal, isn't it?
At this speed, I think it will definitely be on the network news
Eh, first in the retweet list now
Awesome
Great, the first in Japan!
The second is Tomosaku Maezawa
The first is Fuwa
And all very good comments
"It's a good thing that influential people are calling for more votes," and so on
All positive comments
I can do anything for Wednesday Downtown
On the other hand, at the same time
How about gossip?
Morita, this won't work
For example
Roppongi
Has bars where you can XXXX
There
XXXX has gone there
That's bad
How about that type? Hints
Actress's instagram
I take the same photo at the same place
"These two are dating, right?" and so on
The rules for this are very strict
Sorry...
Impossible
All the things I want to do are forbidden
Against TBS' rules
Morita's ideas continuously hit a wall
Cleaned up the streets because I had a little time! End of my first job as a PR ambassador!
Litter picking volunteer
The exact opposite of Twitter
No, no, no
Cigarette butts
Wanna smoke
Report to everyone! Already confirmed to
play in next year's Molkky Worlds! I'll win
the championship next year!
If I get 5,000 likes, i'll never
say a certain word again. If
there are 10,000 likes
i'll ban another word
The two weaker ones keep making mistakes
The last person in the top 3, Fuwa
How about it?
We're on!
At this point she contacted a certain person
Really happy
Really great
That is
Look~~
finally met, my ancestor ♥♥♥♥♥♥♥
Shinoraa♥♥♥♥♥♥
A person Fuwa worships
Shinohara Tomoe
I've loved her since I was three years old
I imitated her look
We are one heart, one body, twins
Will a collaboration between young and old personalities make the news?
However
I'm off to my next job
You are busy!
The big celebrity, Fuwa, is off to do a variety show
If I see Wada in the lounge here, i'll be sure to take a picture
I'm off
But ten minutes later
Eh? Fuwa
Don't break the door
What's going on?
Up!
Sure enough
I saw it while walking down the road
So, Fuwa can go home after 10 hours and 50 minutes
This news is quite good
By the way, this post is now up to 40,000 retweets
With 284,000 positive comments on Twitter
And the other 4 submissions of the day
Other than the one of Chris Matsumura the other three made the news the day after
Also made the news
It proves she's a hit
Here, she speaks with the other contestants
So
Seriously!?
Did everyone make the news?
Scary!
Fuwa is non-existent
Right now Takagi you're better looking than Fuwa
That's right, Takagi, who was beginning to think he'd never be able to go home
Made a big move to dye his hair pink
The one from Exit's dyed hair was in the news
Ahhh
Went to the beauty salon.
Seriously asked them to dye it like EXIT
So how was the response?
Turned pink!
If I take a photo with him together maybe that could work
But he just took a photo of himself
Takagi's photo could make it
At 9.00pm
Will it be on the news?
Undoubtedly, news updates are slow at night
What's going on?
Ah, EXIT retweeted it
I didn't expect to they'd retweet it
Such a good guy
Is that all you do?
I really want to go home today
I'm on the news. Sorry. I'm really sorry
Seriously!?
I got on the news first
Really?
Joyman Takagi took 14 hours and 16 minutes to make the news
I was retweeted
Wow, really?
I have no news whatsoever
Is there anything else you can do?
Not at all
Maybe change your name
That's too much, isn't it?
Change my name
Change my name just because of Wednesday Downtown
It could be the second failure since Ontony
The time has past 00:00
At this point, the pitch ends
So
This is the place you are staying today
This place is scary as hell
What is this?
Staying overnight in a cheap hotel somewhere in Tokyo, bound by the rule that he can't go back
So cheap
-Don't say cheap
Wow first time seeing a room like this
I'm not going to die of oxygen deprivation, am I?
Don't say that
What do you think so far?
Quite interesting
Is Morita the only one to watch in the second half?
A bit unbalanced
It feels like it will be very short if Morita is alone
I feel like I don't want to watch it at all
Does it end here?
Good morning
-Good morning
I kept hearing the sound of rain
The sound of rain, followed by the sound of rain
Adjusting the air conditioner is hard as hell
3-tatami room
Is it cold?
Cold and hot at the same time
It's really hard, so annoying
Not on the news yet?
No
By the second day his hands are already tied
What to do to be on the news?
I can't do that one? Talk about not getting paid for that one show
Which show?
A very popular variety show
I received no answer at all when I called the person in charge
Eh?
Always avoiding me
It has been delayed for two or three years without payment
It's okay for me to say it
After all, the notice fee is owed
After all, it is the president
But because the TBS Broadcasting regulations prohibit such things
Instead, he first checks the day's comedian news
High Heels Momoko and her kid out shopping
So cute
What the hell, why does this make the news?
Stop it
A reproduction of the side dishes of the restaurant
Very interesting
Confusion about what to do
Morita, becomes irritated
Can I smoke?
Eh, you haven't quit smoking?
No, I can't, really
I can't keep going without smoking
If this continues
Although I decided to
try to quit smoking yesterday,
I couldn't bear it. I'm sorry
for all the people who
supported me.
Quitting smoking lasted only one day
It smells so good!
He then uploads a video of the burn marks caused by past cooking
In two days he has posted 7 times
Despite posting on Twitter multiple times, he's yet to hit the news
Name change?
It doesn't matter anymore, i'll change it to something like St. Louis, whatever
Hey, hey, hey.
-Stop it
Nothing has been achieved by the 34th hour
But then, Morita comes up with a plan
He is waiting for someone
The other person is...
Here we go. Here we go
It's Fuwa, Fuwa, right?
The big celebrity Fuwa
What are you doing, need my help?
Fuwa, you're a freelancer, right?
Yeah
Why don't you join our office, please?
Fuwa, seriously you have to join us
It will definitely make the news
Fuwa, please, if you join it'll definitely make the news
You're really worried about another day
I can't
How could I possibly join your agency?
Pitching the attempted scouting that was simply rejected
Fuwa also retweeted, "I said it was okay to have a meeting with the office since they open at 10, but I refused."
I said it was okay to have a meeting with the office since they open at 10, but I refused
Sure enough, she's funny!
That hotel again
Why? Really
Just now, thanks to Fuwa, it's been viewed by more than 10,000 people
But still not in the news
So annoying!
Sell my organs?
As the time hits 9.00, a third day becomes apparent
Wait, eh?
Wait a second, Look at this, on Friday
Goodbye Light of Youth and Milk Boy's reunion, comedy fans are moved to tears
How about this one?
The time difference is huge
I'm on. I'm on
Great!
Unexpectedly, a submission made 32 hours ago becomes the news
It took a long time
Sure enough a gossip magazine saved me
Anyway, if I become popular
If Friday reveal a scandal about me i'll still forgive them
So, after 37 hours and 30 minutes, Morita can finally go home
Ultimately, it happened, we were on the news
We are also guilty of not being in the news
Great! By the way, the inclusion of Fuwa was great!
Her rejection of Morita's offer also later made the news
If it was Chris, he wouldn't be able to go home
He didn't participate this time
Let’s get on with the next presenter please
Jinnai Tomonori!
A divorcee
I'm divorced ... still making jokes about this
This time I bring a special project
First take a look at this
Ancient and modern Japanese people popularity ranking
This is it
Three years ago, one of the most famous people in Japan was revealed to be Ichiro
※Ichiro Suzuki Japan's most famous baseball player, now retired
This is another survey on the popularity of Japanese people
Last time, deceased individuals were not counted
This time, some famous people who are no longer with us are included
So modern and ancient figures
Historical figures are also allowed?
Of course, such as Sakamoto Ryoma and so on
This is a project of what the result would be if this comparison is made
The results will be interesting
After this, the ranking of Japanese people's popularity will be revealed
Ancient and modern Japanese people popularity ranking
The program team incorporated various categories of celebrities
1000 people were picked randomly
From the late teens to early 70s
A questionnaire survey was conducted in Japan
The same applies to this survey of Yoshimoto artists living nationwide
Together with the general population's survey, its a total of 2,000 questionnaires
So, the top 100 Japanese celebrity popularity rankings are created based on the questionnaire
So let's start with the 100th place
Essentially a really nice person
I think they are positive
I think it's a comedian
But inadvertently also seems a little melancholy
Seems like they challenge a lot
And they're often successful. I think it's awesome
I'm not sure about this person either
What's the name?
No... i'm not sure then
Really don't know the name
They play an instrument?
The one with the guitar
It's Miyazono
Miyazono
In 100th place, Miyazono
He enjoys wide popularity in the under-fifties age group
At the age of 60 or 70, there is no presence
Total popularity is 65.6%
In ninety-nine is Junji Takada
The opposite of the previous in the lower age groups
In particular, only 20.2% of those in their teens are aware
It can't be helped
Total popularity is 65.9%
So, ninety-eighth place is
Always smiling and able to respond to any kind of weirdness
It's as if they were born to do comedy
Married to a TV announcer, right?
They do that
Himura
With a characteristic appearance, Himura of Bananaman is ranked ninety-eighth
With a popularity of 66.1%
Ninety-seventh place is Shohei Ohtani
Ninety-sixth is Sakagami Shinobu
After that, in ninety-fifth place is
Heard they're a very capable person
But seems to like women maybe a bit too much
Huh? Who is this? I've seen him before
Which textbook was he in?
Seems like literary kind of thing
Originally, the Prime Minister, of course, the former
On the previous thousand yen bill, right?
Ito Hirobumi
Ninety-five Hirobumi Ito
Here, for the first time, a historical character joins the list
As opposed to the 40-somethings who used the old 1000 yen bills
The difference in perception with the under-thirties is obvious
The total is 66.5%
The other rankings from ninety to one hundred are as follows
Comedians who are active on variety shows and idols are all on the list.
Next is 90-80
Veteran artists such as Osamu Tezuka, the god of manga, Hagimoto Kinichi, and Takashi Okamura
Also, two members of Arashi
Among them, the eighty-first ranking is
He is the man that women of our time long for
Is he the one who imitated Junichi Ishida?
The person with the rolled up knitted sweater?
Junichi Koishida?
Junichi Koishida can get here?
Showa's Big Star
How is that possible
Police...?
Looking through blinds like this
Yujiro Ishihara
The eighty-first person, Yujiro Ishihara
Awareness rate among people in the 50s and 60s is over 90%
Only 12.8% of teenagers are aware of him
The overall total is 71.2% awareness
Next is 79-70
An entertainer, politician, actor, musician, former boxer and the 10,000 yen bill
※Fukuzawa Okekichi was printed on the 10,000 yen bill from 2004 to 2024, and will be replaced by Shibuzawa Eiichi
Appearances by prominent individuals across a wide range of categories
Next is 69-60
With Kei Nishikori, Naomi Osaka, two of the world's most active professional tennis players
And two surprising ones
I think i've seen a program about him, something to do with a vault
Tokugawa Ieyasu?
No
Like...
-Emperor Tenchi?
It's the monkey, isn't it?
What is the name of the one nicknamed Monkey?
Toyotomi Hideyoshi, right?
So it's him...
Sixty-seventh is Toyotomi Hideyoshi
A popularity rate of 74.9%
And this one in sixty-third place is
Always trying to achieve his dream
The man who established the Edo Shogunate?
Tokugawa Ieyasu
Two superstars of the Warring States period made the list in the 60s
Next is 59th to 50th
Baseball players such as Hideki Matsui and Katsuya Nomura
And a leading figure in Japan, Masayoshi Son
Ranked at the fifty-sixth position is
Thinks about future generations
Very interesting and very good at talking
And stomach not so good
A comedian
He has the impression that he is very good at improvisation
Had an accident on a motorcylce
Chihara Junior
Great, Junior
Awesome!
-56th!
The 56th place is Chihara Junior and the 54th place is
Above Ieyasu
The ability to take everything in a funny direction
Quick-witted
Yoshimoto's commenter, right? The one who interviews in various places
Became popular by doing interviews that no one else would do, right?
Crawfish caught in the mouth of the one
Degawa
Very happy, thank you very much
Fifty-fourth is Degawa
A higher ranking would be acceptable
The two people in the studio are on the list together
But who is in-between?
Whose father?
Junichi Ishii...
-Who is it?
Junichi?
-Father
No
Whose father are they?
In our days, he was seen as a big boss
Nagashima
Fifty-fifth is Shigeo Nagashima
An unexpected combination
Famous people in Japan from the past to the present
Next, 49-40
Among entertainers and former sports players
The forty-first is
A world champion, right?
Pro wrestling
1 2 3
Anthony's...what is it again?
It's Antonio Inoki
Forty-first Antonio Inoki
Widely recognized for his participation in a variety of activities
The only pro wrestler to make the list
Next is 39 to 30
From Takuya Kimura, Shingo Katori, Yuzuru Hanyu, and other national stars
To Madame Devi, Ken Watanabe and other big names have come together
Among them, the 30th is
How can I put it? I have the impression that they were involved in some interesting things
Killed
Takeda likes him.
-Ah yes yes yes
"The Dawn of Japan is Near"
Do you know the name of this one?
Not good at history, sorry, I don't know
Sakamoto Ryoma
Sakamoto Ryoma with 86.0%
His popularity in Kochi Prefecture is 100%
However, in the country overall he is ranked thirtieth
Next is 29-20
Her popularity rates exceed 85
Twenty-sixth is
He is on TV and seems to be very strict with his juniors
After being hit by this person, you'll become a star
Looks very horny
Has the impression of shouting "results are published", right?
That's right!
Hama-chan
No one wants to be called "horny-looking"
Masatoshi Hamada 86.4%
Very popular with people in their 30s and 40s
Successfully places 26th
However, there are also such people
This man is... a manzai guy or something?
Can't remember
But I think this person is certainly not a bad guy
This person is a member of the group "Downtown"
Ah, is that right?
I don't know them
Don't know Downtown, impressive
Next in twenty-first place is
Ah, this is my favorite person, has been for a long time
I am so happy
Is a genius and hard worker
A big name
Last year, AI at Kohaku
"Flowing"
It's Misora Hibari
The twenty-first is Misora Hibari
A female Showa singer who has overwhelming popularity among people over 40 years old
But the teenagers do not know her very well
Indeed, not even half
Sure enough, the awareness of the teenage population is not very high
Overall statistic is 87.3%
Now is 19-11
First of all, 19th place is
Does collaborations on Youtube
Due to the epidemic, I started to pay attention to this person
The one who caused social unrest
Koike
Yuriko Koike 87.7%
Who was successfully re-elected in the previous municipal elections
Tokyo's Leader ranked 19th place
18th place is
Tetsuya Takeda 87.8%
17th place is Darvish Yu with 88.3%
16th is
Big body but small capacity
Sweet potatoes
Seems to like dogs
There's a dog on a leash, right? On a bronze statue?
Saigo Takamori
His bronze statue can be seen in Ueno, 89.4%
15th is
Very interesting, god of comedy
Often see his comments on Twitter
Should be a very gentle person
Comments frequently on news
Although he plays dumb, he also has a serious side
Muscle
It's not just muscles, right?
Hitoshi Matsumoto
That's amazing!
-90%!
Hitoshi Matsumoto with 90.4%
Second in Japan in terms of number of Twitter followers
Overwhelming popularity in the age group from 20s to 50s
The first person to hit 90%
Incidentally, the answer from the person who doesn't know Hamada is
Ask him
Isn't this person Kiyohara?
In 14th
Prince Shotoku, with 90.5%
13th is
Ichiro with 91.1%
12th is Kato Cha with 91.2%
After that, in 11th place, failing to make the top ten, is
Well, that... ah
Ug, that, that... that...
Last time, uh...
Son starred in a TV series
Former Prime Minister
Son is an actor
Slutty hair
Prime Minister Koizumi
Junichiro Koizumi with 92.3%
Impressive, still popular
The man who has retired from politics but still has a high reputation
Has a big gap in popularity with his sons
Solidly in 11th place
After that, we finally hit the top 10
Who is the most famous person in Japan?
So, that's everything up to 11
There are some unexpected results
Sakamoto Ryoma is a surprise
Junior is very impressive, 56th
It's awesome
Degawa, Nagashima, Chihara
Simply the best clean-up batters
I'm really not well known in the grandparents' generation
Well, yes, it's true...
-Although I love them so much
Even if you say so...
But the fact that more than 50 people don't know Downtown is incredible
Confused with Kiyohara
Yes, how can I get confused with him?
Finally, here is the top 10
10th is
Nobunaga Oda with 92.4%
9th is
This person, most people like him a lot
I often went to the KOMA theater when he was there
Often appears in Toei's yakuza movies
Often imitated by people
He's been on Kohaku, right?
Still alive, right?
Still here
Kitajima Saburo
Kitajima Saburo 92.5%
Although not well known amongst teens
He has over 90% awareness among people in their thirties and beyond
A successful ninth place
Next in eighth place is
Very popular
Although not very handsome
It still makes people think "this person is very popular"
The top comedian in Japan
Loved by everyone
Ken Shimura
Eighth place is Shimura Ken with 92.8%
84% of young people
The comedy king who is adored by everyone from children to the elderly
High awareness from the teens to the seventies
Solidly in the top 10
In seventh is
Tsurono Takeshi
Ah, no, ah...
Name ah ... can not think of it
No chance
Lip syncing?
That and stalking
Rings a bell while saying "order", something like that
Masahiro Nakai
Masahiro Nakai 93.2%
Confused with Tsurono Takeshi?
A national level top idol
He is now ranked seventh as a representative of Japan
Next in sixth place is
Already a big name
Speaks very strongly
Very tall, manly feeling
Short hair
Wada Akiko
Sixth place Wada Akiko 94.0%
Very high level of recognition
Ranks sixth
Next in fifth place is
He is famous all over the world and has the impression of being very cultured
What's the name again? I'm not sure
Can't remember
"Tadashi?"
Takeshi Kitano
The first of the big 3 of comedy to make the list
In fourth place, slightly ahead of Takeshi, is
Constantly talking
-Keep on talking
When he's on TV he doesn't stop
The most distinctive part is his mouth?
Comedy monster
Hmm? A monster?
Sanma
Visibility among the forty-somethings
Is the highest of any age group with 99.6%
He successfully lands in 4th place
Now, the final stretch of the ranking
Who is the most famous person in Japan?
In third is
A graduate of Seikei University near here
Japan's vegetable-beating uncle
Small but cute mouth
Shinzo Abe
Third place is Shinzo Abe
The longest-serving Prime Minister of Japan, no less
Impressive
Not 100% though
Awareness of 95.5%
Not 100%
Who else is there?
Next is 2nd place
The 2nd most famous person in Japan is
A very feminine person
Has this impression
Talks almost without breathing
Seems almost inhuman
Tetsuko Kuroyanagi
Tetsuko Kuroyanagi with 96.8%
As the number one TV actress in Japan, she has been active for over 60 years
Successfully places 2nd
So, the most popular in both modern and ancient Japan is
Hosts, and communicates very well
A big name
Glamorous sunglasses
Tamori
Tamori with 97.4%
It's been six years since the end of "It's okay to laugh"
Although he isn't on TV every day anymore
His popularity is still overwhelmingly high
He shines in 1st place
I see
It was Tamori
The one who doesn't know Downtown
Must know Tamori and Tetsuko Kuroyanagi, right?
Should do
Bring that man to me
Wanna beat him up?
I want to ask that person a lot of questions
Like do you know this or that  person?
Surely he knows omelet rice or curry rice, stuff like that, right?
Surely, right?
Cheeseburger or something
Cheeseburger could be a bit iffy
"It's something with cheese in it," or something like that
Let's welcome the next presenter
It's Kendo Kobayashi
Do you all know these two?
Of course
These program has realized these two are extremely odd
Kasuga is incredibly good at staying put when told
Yes.
-Speaks strange languages too
Basically, we know
These two have been found to have unusual endurance
Dancho did a verification of riding a bicycle for 24-hours
And a competition in -15 degrees in the snow in thin clothing for 2 hours and 20 minutes
As well as surviving in a sauna at 80 degrees with clothes on for 56 minutes
"Surviving"...
Kasuga was proven to be even more obedient than dogs when being told to wait
He waited for staff for 6 hours and 39 minutes
He was told to wait, so he waited
Incredible
I've looked at him differently since then
So, we put these two together and came up with this project
Dancho vs Kasuga endurance duel
Finally its time to pit them against each other
One-on-one
Degawa was also involved in this shoot
Yes
-Really?
With fear and trepidation
Both are very unyielding
I was concerned enough after seeing the 24-hour bike ride
Downtown were also shocked
-Yes, yes, yes
If it's an ordinary program such as Shinuske's
Everyone would have congratulated him and been very moved
Very moving
-With female guest tears brought to tears or something
Its obviously so hard to ride for 24 hours
Sorry I messed up at the most important part
Sounds like the sound of cicadas flying over
Like cicadas chirping hikihikihi
The commentary for this matchup is brought to you by Degawa Tetsuro
To be honest, for me, I am more interested in this than M-1
Thank you
I think it's going to be a great match and I'm looking forward to it
We also look forward to your commentary
This time, the first one to win three games from these nine competitions will win
The initial competition is
So the first to choose is Dancho
Lets start with the super hot bath
-So quick!
Super hot bath
-So quick, so quick
Not bad
It was the first thing I saw
It's decided, then, super hot bath
Dancho uses his superb sense of variety shows and chooses the hot bath
This is called the 'super' hot bath
Because it's hotter than the average variety hot bath
And the heating device will start after entering the water
Eh?
-Eh?
It won't cool down
This time, because of the two electric heaters, the water temperature will rise one degree every minute
First time i've heard some heating rules like this
It's already hot, right?
So one degree is already a huge difference
So
First, the water is tested
By Degawa, the first person to get into the tub
Well, i'll rely on past experiences to judge
I should be able to last 30 seconds to a minute
Although I do not know the specific temperature first
Is the temperature known? The usual hot bath
Real temperature? Real...
The real temperature is about 46 degrees
For me its 46, for our group leader its 44
Everyone is different?
Our leader will be angry if he's told
If you're feeling unwell it'll be lowered to 42
Isn't that just a normal shower?
The temperature is just right
So, Degawa will now test it
46 degrees is hot enough.
-It's hot enough
Can already feel the heat
It is still fine
So scary!
Hey, don't push me in!
Remember social distance, we can't
Eh, what?
People should keep distance from each other!
You can't push me in because of social distancing, right?
This is bad. No, no, no
If i'm not pushed I can't react!
So fast.
-Hot, wait...
Eh eh eh eh, Degawa?
Isn't this stupid, Wednesday?
What? What?
What's going on?
Not 30 seconds at all
Sorry, it's hotter than I thought it would be and it scared me
How many degrees? How many degrees?
-49 degrees
Two seconds is all it took to get red
Can you see this? Please document this
Really red
Really burnt, so quickly
After learning about the power of hot water
I'll go second
Dancho is up first in the super hot bath duel
So, Dancho will try it first, please let us know your thoughts first
I won't retreat until a layer of my skin comes off
So cool
Nothing interesting to say at all
So, Dancho will go first
Scald it, scald it, scald it
Go, go, go!
Dancho has entered the water of 49 degrees
Awesome
The temperature is rising
Awesome!
How long can he put up with it?
Butt on the ground!
Good sitting posture
Not moving a muscle
Probably doesn't want to move
Oooh wow, over 30 seconds now
Eh, has he stabilized?
Not moving for more than 40 seconds
Isn't it too fast, isn't it too fast?
Temperature is up up up up up
It rises one degree each minute
No no its hotting up already
Now the warming device water temperature has exceeded 50 degrees
No, no, no, it definitely went up already
It's gotten weird. It's gotten weird
Then
Getting red
So strong, two minutes
No no, this is more than 1 degree, more than 1 degree, more than 1 degree
It's gone up again!
The water temperature should be over 51 degrees
Up!
Ah i'm burning!
Come out, come out!
Up again!
The soup is boiling
Exactly how long will he last?
This is really...
You can do it!
What's the count? What's the count? What's the count?
3 minutes 3 minutes 3 minutes 3 minutes
3 minutes, up again!
He wants to pass 3 minutes
Is it up to 3?  -Not yet, 55
56 57 58 59 3 minutes
Oooh wow so strong
Dancho sets a record of 3 minutes and 1 second
So red!
Completely red, there's no bit that isn't red
I've never seen anything like this
So strange so strange, what's happened to the chest here
The armpit is especially bad
Incredible
Dancho seems to have more sensitive skin than the average person
You have to pay attention to where you put your foot and the surface of the water
This piece of water is so hot
The hot water will flow upwards
A medical examination of the Dancho's skin then takes place, after which the duel continues
Next, Kasuga takes on the challenge
It's too hard to top
I see
Ah, I see!
It does feel hot here already
What exactly do you want to feel, Kasuga?
Ok
I'm going!
So, hot bath, here I come!
Not easy for Kasuga either
I see...
That's how it feels...
It's not often that you see Kasuga like this
It's not hot at all!
Really...
Foot foot foot foot!
It's been heating up since then, right here
Indeed! Although invisible to the naked eye, the temperature did rise
The temperature changes in a flash
I see, I have never experienced something like this
Please take care of me for the first time...
Ah... it's really hot
Just like Dancho, Kasuga also survives the hot water to over 50 degrees
Ah, it's true, what Dancho said is true
He is an honest person
Its true about the top
From the feet to the top
I see-
Ahh...!
-It's 2 minutes and 30 seconds
Hold on a little more, a little more, a little more, a little more.
Wow is he coming out? Is he coming out?
Ah--! It hurts!
Ouch!
It's not often that you can hear the words "it hurts" in the bath
The feeling has changed from "so hot" to "so painful"
10 seconds left. 10 seconds left!
-Can he beat Dancho's record?
Wow, it's getting there
Wow, he's over!
So hot-!
I don't feel anything on my side anymore
It really feels like being whipped
Look at the color of his side is completely red
It's hot! These swimming trunks!
Really impressive!
The first round goes to Kasuga
The rule is that the next matchup is chosen by the loser
This thing Kasuga is very good at, of course, I am also very good at it
Underwater breath-holding duel
Ah, here it is!
So the second round takes place in a pool
The 2nd round is Dancho vs Kasuga in a breath-holding duel
Please offer us a few words, Dancho
Well, 15 years ago
I had a similar match with Kasuga
So i'm looking forward to this
Indeed, these two previously faced off in a diving competition before
Well, I won the "hot water" part anyway
So I hope Dancho will pick up the pace
In short
He seems to be really angry
Didn't think it was funny at all
Degawa also tries this first
I’m OK—
You'd definitely be ok like this!
-Absolutely
30 seconds is average
Finally the time has come for the duel
Tap me every 30 seconds
Pat me on the back
Every minute?
-Yes
Okay, the one minute countdown begins now
Doing it at the same time
The battle has already begun with this first minute
The two adjust their breathing to prepare
10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1
An amazing image
Their breathing before going under is really impressive
This is one hell of a battle
Seems tough
It's 30 seconds
They are both motionless
No way, right?
It's now 1 minute and 30 seconds
Not long after, they've now survived 1 minute and 30 seconds
Seems like they'll pass 2 minutes
So scary
This is the underwater image
That's awesome
1 minute and 50 seconds, almost 2 minutes
Kasuga...
These two still haven't come up
But Kasuga is starting to make some small movements
Although Kasuga's body is moving slightly his head hasn't
Dancho is incredible
It's true, Kasuga is a little shaken. 2 minutes and 20 seconds.
-It's over, it's over, it's over
Kasuga looks like he's struggling a bit
Is Dancho also struggling?
It's over. Is Dancho okay? He's shaking a bit
Is he shaking?
-Ah, it's moving
Kasuga is out
Dancho's done it
I'm OK!
-Let's check the time
The time difference between the two is about 10 seconds
I’m OK
In the underwater duel, Dancho stayed under for 2 minutes and 43 seconds and Kasuga for 2 minutes and 32 seconds
The winner is Dancho!
The winner of the second round is Dancho
So, Kasuga will choose the 3rd round
Yes, I'll go with oden. Let's have some super hot oden
The rules are simple, eat these three super hot ingredients in order, the faster one wins
What do you think, Degawa?
-This is a big deal!
This is like a steam train
Here we also let Degawa try it out
Degawa experienced it all
Wow!
It's still bubbling!
Wow really incredible
Wait a minute, I can't get it up.
-They're all in one big pile
Look at this and you'll understand
-Even the fish cake is impossible
Indeed
Okay, I'll eat it
Really eating it!?
Wow, this is too hot, right?
It's too hot!
Wow it's scary
Whoa! Hot!
Okay, that's tough
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry
Ah, it's really hot.
-You should cool it down
Seriously, I've never eaten something so hot before
I've done something similar before
But one time I was asked to-
The third round is the super hot oden duel
The patience of our staff is really awful
The staff doesn't allow for anything
Prepare - Start!
It's a great feeling a great scene.
-It's boiling
Is it from the egg to the fish cake?
-Start with the egg
Wow we are off, Kasuga is eating it!
How hot are the eggs?
What the hell is wrong with this guy!
-Seems to be a strategy to cool it down in the mouth
Sure enough these two people are too good
That's awesome
It's definitely super hard on the mouth right now
Kasuga is awesome!
Just putting it in your mouth is impressive enough, right?
How to say... i'm moved
After Kasuga, Dancho is now also chewing!
Wow that was fast!
No way!
Eat the fish cake next!
Hey, hey, look at Dancho
Kasuga is now ready to eat fish cake
-He practically swallowed the egg
You can't eat this in one go
This guy is amazing!  Wow it's awesome!
They both have the same expression
Bad bad bad
That's awesome...
Dancho is flailing
It's really awesome
There's a gap of just one item
Their mouths look very distorted
He's still stuck on the egg
Just one egg... an egg is so painful
Whoa, Dancho!
-Kasuga is now on the radish
It's too fast!
You can't, it's impossible to eat it!
Dancho still hasn't put the fish cake in his mouth
Oh, Dancho's put it in!
Stuffing it in!
I've never seen chopsticks used like this...
-He's shoving it in
Dancho is using a great move, he's stabbing it
On the other side, Kasuga is struggling with the final boss: Radish
Dancho is still trying to catch up on the fish cake
Okay now both of them are on the radish stage! Dancho has caught up!
Who will be the winner?
Dancho's method is good, eating around the edges
Ah, Kasuga put it in! Will he swallow it completely?
Dancho also stuffs it in!
Who will be the winner? Who will it be? Who will it be?
The one who swallows first is the winner!
A hot battle
Dancho is struggling with the heat of the radish
Who will be the one to swallow it all first?
Okay-! Thanks for the meal!
Please show the camera your mouth
Kasuga wins!
Your mouths must really be in a bad state right now
Yes, i'll have to be careful what I eat tomorrow
So, the scores are currently 2-1
The fourth competition chosen by the loser is
This elastic band endurance duel
I think maybe i'll go with this
-I got it.
Think calmly and carefully think about playing this with how your mouths are right now
Huh? Oh...
This endurance duel involves both people pulling one end with their mouth
First, Degawa tests it out
Hey? Coughing?
I'm sorry, I'm out of breath... sorry, sorry
With no way back, Dancho's choice, the elastic band showdown, begins!
Kasuga is powerfully pulling away gradually
Oh, I see
Dancho is now handing over the reigns to Kasuga
They're both close
This is a true battle
Now Dancho is leading the aciton
This kind of protracted war is too tiring, right?
Ordinary people, their jaw wouldn't be able to handle it
And so it goes on, one after the other, in and out
Whoa, 10 minutes?
They are really both after victory, you can feel it, right?
So, after another 10 minutes, finally
Wow, Dancho is pulling like crazy!
Ah, damn it!
Too much force, right?
What just happened! What's going on!?
Dancho won!
A great show, look at his sweat
It escaped, it escaped me
Now the two are tied
What is the final stage chosen by Kasuga?
I'll choose the acupuncture board one
Hey, what's this?
-I don't understand it either
Then the final battle is the upright acupuncture board not moving duel
This one is probably the hardest
Foot acupressure boards are placed on 2-meter-high pillars
They must stand on them barefoot until they can stand no longer
The rules are as simple as that
Ah, it hurts...
Ah, it hurts... this could be over very early
Even these two are super powerful, surely they can't stand it for that long
Probably everyone but Dancho and me thinks so
-It's true...
Finally, the final showdown will be held. Who will get the title of King of Endurance?
Climbing up you can really feel the height
-This is quite high
It's much higher than it looks from below.
-It's not the same at all, right?
Also very narrow, just a tiny bit of space, makes it seem worse
So, please take off your shoes!
This could be over straight away
Ow...
I can't believe Kasuga has such a pained expression
So let's start the final round!
Here we go
Kasuga's expression is interesting
His face has completely changed
What the heck is this...
How does it feel?
No pain no pain no pain
It doesn't hurt, it doesn't hurt at all
How to say, the positioning is important due to the different parts of the feet
Moving it slightly feels better but its also risky because of how narrow the space is
Well, its pretty complicated
If this was a normal variety show that'd definitely be cut out
Sure enough, these two are incredible
Generally speaking, if nothing happens, you will be upset, right?
But those two people are very calm, not afraid at all
Instead of fear they're calm
So, nothing really happened and 30 minutes passed
It hurts when you move your feet
Ah, its a bit scary
If you move even a little, it will be very painful.
-It's true
It is tough
Kasuga is struggling
The position just now was quite good
In order not to let the pain build up, the two move ever so slightly occasionally
Dancho
-Yes?
Which is more painful, being on a bike for 24 hours or this?
For me, the bike is easier
Because you are moving, its more painful to not move
Yes, the pain in the feet is increased with the restriction of not being able to take a single step
This matchup can be said to be tough on a mental level as well
The soles of the feet are so uncomfortable
It is also hard to move the surface of the foot
Constant pain
It hurts when you move around.
-Yeah
You have to move although it hurts
The intervals between shifting become shorter
Honestly, I would never do this sort of thing, really, I would never do it
I've never said no to anything before, but this, I really couldn't do it
Not funny at all
It is just standing
Hate things that aren't funny
That was close...
In order to reduce the pain, Kasuga spreads his weight to the edge
But almost lost his balance
Just like that, 2 hours passes
Sweaty feet.
-Right? It's obviously barefoot.
It's getting wet.
-It's wet
Ah, you're sweating just standing there?
The soles of the feet are sweaty, the soles of the feet are so sweaty
Ugh, it hurts too much, it hurts too much, damn it!
So cool
Ah, not good, don't be so angry
Tsk, so irritating
So, 2 hours and 30 minutes passes
It's hard to stand in place for two hours
-Yes, it is
It hurts...
Even these two can not hide the pain and fatigue
I was watching
What time is it?
-It's about 9:40 p.m
9:40
Let them rest tomorrow
2 hours and 20 minutes to go
Until Monday.
-Monday
I'm setting a goal to make it to Monday
Wow, no!
Let's celebrate a new day!
For the man who can continue to ride on the bike for 24 hours
And the man who waited for 6 and a half hours without saying a word
There is no end in sight...
How is Kasuga doing now? Any thoughts?
Well, in any case, we've really stood for 3 and a half hours
After standing here for 3 hours, i'll never forget the shape of these rocks
If you put it like this, it will hurt and so on
Different places have completely different pain
Wow... damn it!
Hey, why, why, why, why?
-Just now his foot moved
Wow, a complete oversight
Ah, really slippery feet
-Scared the hell out of me
It really hurts, right?
-Yes, it hurts
Painful from the beginning
We are competing in "endurance", so it is impossible for "no pain"
From the first round it was like this, there is no "not hot", it was super hot!
We are just holding back!
So in the Endurance Showdown
The winner is Dancho, congratualtions!
Okay, after watching VTR, what do you think?
I thought i'd react like "you can do it" and "amazing!"
But watching it I was really close to tears
It was really like a fight to the death
They were so serious
Hamada is also good at this, next time let him do it
Really?
-I want to see it
Just now in the pool, they should've let them sink
That won't work.
-You can't broadcast that
You want to see that, don't you? You can laugh at that, right? "They've sunk!"
Hamada-, are you still living 20 years in the past?
Yes, he is the "Comedy Time Traveler"
"Time Traveler"? "Back to the Future"?
That's right, "90 points for violence!" in those days
※ゲバゲバ 90 points! : A variety show broadcasted on Japanese television from 1969 to 1971
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03