Special thanks: u/HouseiGIFsTumblr for uploading the raw
This is my first typeset, so the timing might be off at times
And because I don't really understand japanese, the sentences might be off timing, sorry!
Translation: u/pecha_yu_betcha
Typesetting: u/Robbert_Fruit
Okay, let`s begin with this episode of Golden Biographies.
Today we will take a look at a duo.
Today’s guests are a very popular comedy duo.
Hosei, you have known them for some time, right?
Know them? I would say I spend time with them at least once a week for the past twenty years.
I probably won't learn anything new about them today.
Yes well, we have these two on standby, let's take a look.
This could be interesting.
It really smells like flowers. Right?
Right?
What?
It smells of flowers.
It smells of flowers?
It's really strong.
You see how they are talking now? That makes me really happy.
They didn't talk like that before?
They didn't.
I don't really have the image of them being so popular but let’s go and take a look.
Maybe my nose is stuffy?
It's so strong that even if you have a stuffy nose you should be able to smell this.
Then I have no idea.
Really? That’s strange.
Yeah, I really can’t smell the flowers.
Alright, they are waiting so let`s get in there.
Today`s guests are these two known as Kokoriko.
E/T-Thank you for having us.
This is a first for me.
Is it?
Yes, a first time for me.
This show looks at the lives of celebrities and discusses with them their accomplishments and struggles they deal with: "Golden Biographies."
He told me that I could do it all by myself, so he decided to leave.
It was so difficult.
That is a good time to write your will.
He said he was quitting, so I asked if there was any room to work with Takeshi's group.
Today we look at Kokoriko and the course of their career.
These two began working together in their 20`s with a history even before that.
I think I wasn’t taking it too seriously.
The biggest crisis in the history of their famous comedy duo.
He said "what were you doing" and grabbed me by the shirt and we started punching each other.
…And the medias publications of Endo`s divorce.
Well this was one reason for the divorce, but I never really said that.
And they will discuss even bigger never before mentioned secrets from other people in their lives.
They really were there to help me,
they asked me "what do you really want to do with your life?"
Additionally we will hear from members of the show that worked with them.
He would focus on one thing and that was all he would concern himself with.
He would say well today is the day for me to have the kid,
and we would talk about things like that.
Today we will speak uncensored with Kokoriko.
Okay Let’s get started by introducing our guests Kokoriko. Thank you for being here.
E/T-Thank you for having us.
So Hosei you said you see them almost every week?
Yes, I have seen them almost every week for the last 20 years or so.
Yes, that’s right
So, you must know a lot about them.
Well they feel like a part of my family.
E/T-Thank you.
Their partnership has continued for over 23 years. Let’s take a look how that has gone on this graph which shows happy and unhappy.
So for happy or unhappy from 21 to 26 the graph is as follows.
This is interesting because we actually asked for their answers separately but they both show the exact same pattern. It is astonishing.
Well the two of them were constantly together so they must have had the same feelings.
You could definitely say that we were neighbors as well.
So you two were classmates, right?
E/T: Yes we were.
From the early days of elementary school...
They were both from Osaka and have been best friends since elementary school.
When they were 20, Endo suggested to Tanaka that they try their luck in performing.
They moved to Tokyo where they auditioned for the Yoshimoto organization and passed. Which is where they broke into the scene.
It was there where they broke into the scene.
So we did the audition and then we were just kind of there,
but then about half a year later we performed for the V cinema.
*V-cinema is a direct to video industry owned by Toei
Both of you?
Both of us, yes
That's amazing.
Well at that time it was honestly so easy for us.
That's right but at 22?
Yes, this performance just a few months after their debut they made it big with this performance that we have prepared, please look.
You know what I’m going home.
What are you talking about? You are just going to leave me to do this alone?
How can you say that when you have no experience?
Did you say something?
These roles lead them to more opportunities to act
and it was at this time that Tanaka said he realized his dream to be an actor.
I was actually just along for the ride since he asked me to go with him.
I didn't think I was a good comedian or anything,
but I went to Tokyo was acted in a few films and performed in front of a live audience.
While I think I really only got them to laugh 20 percent of the time the feeling it gave me was so joyous.
Their reaction?
Yes, the way they reacted to my writing, to make them laugh that feeling made me so happy.
So you wanted to ride that wave?
I wanted to ride that wave yes.
So that was how you got into comedy but what about Endo? Did you ever write anything?
Yes, I did but when I would show it to Tanaka he would say that it was wrong
from there all I really did was work on the logo for Kokoriko or things like that or names of the shows and things like that.
Yeah that sounds like something you might do I think you would be good at that.
So, at this point I would like to show a bit you two did, this is important so let’s take a look.
Here we take a look at a piece done by the young duo.
Here is our performance: The Mosquito
You're amazing!
Oh its nothing.
No you're amazing!
I said its nothing.
You are so cool!
No it was nothing.
Wow it's huge!
That`s embarrassing.
No that`s a great piece, isn't it stylish?
"Stylish"?
Yes, very stylish.
This is stylish?
You must have been happy to get those laughs.
Yes
The first year for these two was a great start however the graph shows a sharp drop over the next years, why is that?
So in only half a year we hit it off well, right? So, we thought it would just keep up like this.
We thought we could just play like this in the world of television, but it proved to be much hard that this.
In these years we really did not have any work.
Here we had some juniors, we were in Ginza when that performance stage was made
and the pair London Boots number 1 and 2 and the duo Penalty also appeared at this time.
This was the first time we had the feeling of groups following us and the inertia of it, especially with London Boots(LB)
J-Yes LB was quite the spectacle, they were something coming in after you two. We actually have a piece from them that we would like to watch.
Hello this is London Boots number 1 and 2.
This group which began two years after Kokoriko is the group London Boots one and two
they came in to the scene out of nowhere and were known for having a very close relationship in private as well.
We asked them what their impression of Kokoriko was at the time.
So when Tanaka asked me directly to come have a drink with them it was actually three years into our career.
I think it takes some time for Tanaka to warm up to people,
and I was unsure if he was holding back when we were spending time together.
After we started going out and drinking together I feel like we got a lot closer.
Tanaka was a really fan of eating bread.
Yes, he loved his bread.
When I went to his house one time I remember he must have had 2 or 3 toasters.
I felt that one toaster is more than enough right?
It looked like as if he were living in a house where knock off products were made.
I feel that when he gets fixated on one thing he tends toget stuck on it.
I remembered thinking "I hope he isn't doing anything illegal" and he seems to be doing fine.
And what do they have to say about Endo?
For me, probably, he may be  the one person I respect most in this world.
I mean of course he is comedic and interesting which is why he can still operate in this field world. but in private as we were eating
he really was there to help me, he asked me what I really wanted to do with my life.
I told him that I wanted to work as hard as I could while the work was available and try to stay in the acting world as long as possible
but Endo said to me that he wanted to make "Endo`s perversion school"
I was laughing as I listened but he said he was serious and that he truly wanted to make this school.
So, I asked him why and he said that he felt that Japanese peoples displays of affection needed to be more intense
and that it would benefit the world and he kept talking about it and I remembered thinking I will never meet another person like him in my life,
and thought it was just incredible.
There you have it.
One moment,
did they make any other comments than that?
That was basically the main point in the comments that were made: Endo's perversion school.
I mean it was a long relationship with countless conversations I am curious as to why he only thinks about that one.
Well, he did say you are the person he most respect even with your perversion school.
3 years after their debut, they still had no regular spots on tv while their fame was growing Kokoriko's happiness sank with it hitting bottom at age 24.
What were things like between the two at this time?
So we started at 21 and had decided that after three years if we could not become regulars on any kind of show we need to quit
and it was right about that time that our limit was coming up
and that was probably the worst time in our relationship as a duo and in private as we would blame the lack of work on each other.
And I am sure that first break you got made this time that much harder to cope with.
I’m sure that did not help.
That may have been the only huge fight in Kokoriko to ever take place.
Here these two nearly broke up the duo in this terrible fight.
He said what do you think you are doing?
And we started hitting each other.
3 years after their debut as Kokoriko but as they had no steady work they started to have issues and ignited a fight that nearly broke up the duo.
So this is really the only big fight that ever took place in Kokoriko up to this point.
This was some fight huh?
We were grabbing each other’s shirts and then we started punching each other.
Each other?
Yes.
This was after a performance?
Yes, we finished a performance and during our conversation of we should do this bit or that bit
and I had usually decided what we were going to do but was having trouble making a decision that day, so I was telling him to give me a moment.
That is a big decision though.
So eventually what happened was right before we were supposed to go on stage, I made the decision and we went right on stage
to do the bit, we had no rehearsal or chance to work on it
and I messed up the sequence and it went off the rails and we basically just left the stage like that
and that was when he started by saying "why couldn't you make a faster decision?"
I tried saying that I was having trouble making up my mind but we were having trouble communicating
so a lot of bad things came out and it was soon before the time limit we had given ourselves
so Endo said we might as well end this, and I said "what are you talking about?"
There we exploded and had a go at each other and really started punching,
but that was really the worst fight that we ever had.
The most serious fight you ever had?
Yes it was.
The duo had no work and a terrible relationship and were on the brink of breaking up,
but they were able to get out of their situation with this…
But here it looks like is where you started to rise back up. Why is that?
When we agreed to quit if we did not become regulars on anything, in Shizuoka there was a program Shizuoka Kanekuro.
What in the world is that show?
Well it was a live Friday night show in Shizuoka that was live on Friday at five
which is where they got the name and that is where we started to make regular appearances.
And that was the gig that started to get you both out of this slump?
Yes, and this was what lead us into Gaki no tsukai so yeah this helped us to get out of that funk.
You were called to Gaki no tsukai and Iitomo from this?
That's right we were.
That's amazing.
Yes it was incredible to see the momentum they picked up from that show.
From really having no work to getting to that level.
I told you that that "your duo is great" you know
"and that if they were able to get out in front of the entire country they would surely pull through"
but I wasn't sure they could do it.
But in spring of the next year they had become regulars
but then I didn't think it was good
I was so upset about it I had an aneurism.
They appeared in the shows "Warateiitomo", "Gaki no tsukai" and even more shows as their popularity grew and became regulars on 10 different shows
and it shows as their happiness chart shows a spike during this period let’s see what happens from there.
Okay so from 26-35 let’s see what happens, so here we see a split in this period.
So, first Endo you plateau here.
Yes well everything continued going as it was with Iitomo and Gaki no tsukai so then I was looking to land our own show which was the dream of dreams
and that is when our Kokoriko show "Ougon Densetsu" started
As an actor to have your show is really just the dream.
Your name is even in the show title.
So yeah with the name Kokoriko's "blah blah blah" it’s just a dream.
I mean you look at the paper and to have your name there and we did that in our 20s.
That is incredible. then to talk about your show we have some people that worked with you,let’s take a look.
Yukiesan!
Thank you for having me. I’m Yukie Sakaki
Meet Yukie Sakaki, an actress of 15 years and coworker on the Kokoriko show.
We asked for her impression of these two when she first started working with them.
At first you know they told me that although they were on during golden time this was their first time and asked for me to help in any way I could
but there was no time for that at the
beginning but I said "just leave don't worry about it"
and that if it was something that Kokoriko was doing that it would be fine
and things like that to help them relax and they really did well,
good for them. They really grew.
So now let’s hear her impression on their personalities.
Well they are like younger brothers to me.
Tanaka was living close to where I was,
and his wife was such a lovely woman and their child was so cute and lively.
Tanaka was probably the quietest one of the group especially when you got their family together.
So, when I would see him in the city shopping you know in passing
it was like he was focused on something in the road.
Then for Endo even when we were doing the show
whenever a girl he liked would appear he would always say something about her,
and he was very easy to read
I'm sure he likes a strong woman.
That was what she had to say.
Thank you very much.
So you are running your own show. So yes, that would keep you pretty happy right?
Yes nothing but appreciation for what I had.
On the other hand Tanaka went back down, why is that?
Well yes, I mean of course I was happy to have the show
but the jump from one show to ten had me question myself like am I going to be okay.
So you were experiencing some anxiety.
You could say that
but even from our debut I always felt like without really developing my skills I was just getting older
and getting more work and I had the privilege of performing everyday
but felt like I lacked the right tools for the job
like I was not properly matched for the amount of work I had which is what caused that.
So the anxiety birthed of all this worked that suddenly came is what this drop is.
Yes that’s right.
At this time the Tanaka felt the duo was so busy they were having trouble communicating with each other
and wasn't sure if they had the right tools for the job, but what did Endo think at this time?
Endo, what did you think at this time? did you know about the doubts Tanaka was having?
We really didn't even have time to stop and think about how we were feeling as we weren't really communicating at this time.
So even though you did not have much time together your work kept coming in and increasing.
This maybe the wrong way to say this
but I really think that I wasn’t taking it too seriously when I think back on it now.
Just you?
I mean for our duo.
That Kokoriko was in no trouble with keeping the show?
I mean I knew that this show was not the end of our career, that this is good for where we are
and there will still be more as long as nothing crazy happens this will continue which was really was my mindset was at the time.
If it wasn't, I feel that I would have probably noticed the trouble Tanaka was having.
Yes to see this separation of happiness within the group and not notice.
Hosei, did you notice the bad terms Kokorico was having?
Yes it was so hard for me to be around you two at that time.
The bad part in our relationship.
The bad part in your relationship you say?
I would come to the stage and Tanaka would sit in front and you would sit over to the side
and I had no issues with either of you so it wasn't a problem for me
but during taping you two had no back and forth so we really had no group conversation
I had to either speaking one on one with Tanaka or one on one with, you and I seriously feel it was that way for about 8 years.
Sorry about that
At 26 years of age they became very rich and popular,
but it was divided as Endo was having a good time of it and Tanaka was experiencing a much different feeling.
But at 29 tanks graph shows a spike in happiness let’s find out why that is.
But here Tanaka you rise back up here, please let us know what happened here that caused this.
This is where the Kokoriko miracle type show began which was a golden time show we got
and as we did the show we made our own sketches, it was just too fun.
That is where we really started.
Your show in golden time and that made you both happy.
That really made me happy. I mean I still had my worries, but the joy was overpowering
You also appeared in movies?
Yes at this time I made appearances in movies
and that also made me so happy the ability to act was something so fun for me
and I relearned my enjoyment of acting.
The movie Tanaka is referring to is the movie "Minna no ie."
Well that’s what a job is right?
Your ambition enlightened me but if you are saying this now I may have some things to rethink.
Please make up your mind this week. If you can’t I will find someone else.
Here we see Tanaka in another feature film by Karasawa Koshiaki
where he was received an academy award in the new actor category which put him center stage for future projects,
but why did Tanaka who was a comedian decide to start acting in movies?
So here what happened was when he was in Gaki no tsukai
Tanaka was taken aback by the way Hamada would lose it during pranks.
I mean he would just lose it out of nowhere.
He would you know be holding a badminton racket and start hitting Tanaka with it or just punch him.
When that happened Tanaka started to tear up and cry.
That's true
And this director noticed him and thought that is the man he wanted for his movie.
So, you acting career was thanks to Hamada attacking you?
Very much so.
He wasn't pretending to attack you he really was going at you?
Yes, he really was, and I was really crying.
But maybe he was watching you thinking this guy can really act.
No he said I was very pure.
Next we will take a look at Endo who also peaked up here in happiness along with Tanaka
where at 31 he met another talented person Chiaki and they wed.
Tanaka also got married the following year to an actress he had worked with named Koji Tashie.
They both were very happy during this period.
So at 31 Endo got married and Tanaka married at 32,
in addition work is going wonderfully and you were also helping out Hosei as well.
He really must have appreciated that right Hosei?
Yes, I was very happy, but I was wondering about myself.
I mean they were both married
but I wasn't invited to either of their weddings...
No that wasn't it at all.
Didn’t I say we were like family
and felt like what kind of people don't invite their family to their wedding!?
I’m surprised to hear this, very surprised. What happened there?
I never had a wedding party.
So, there was no party but there was, in my immediate family,
I know Hosei is saying we are family, so it’s tough to say this
but we took some pictures, but it was just a few people
and I know he said we are family but…well
I'm sorry.
You had classmates and such there, right?
I saw these pictures.
Who was in there? What relation did they have?
Well there was Yamamoto...
Yamamoto and Takeshi were the only ones, right? From that group.
No there were more your junior classmates and others,
you don't know do you? I looked at them and had an aneurysm.
You have a lot of aneurysms!
It seems like he remembers this well.
Whatever its fine, I mean you have this big gathering but whatever I was busy at that time anyway,
but Tanaka really bothered me.
What happened there?
Well for me, I as well had no official wedding party.
We did plan on having celebration, but we were in the middle of so much
we decided to finish the paperwork ahead of time and well
we just decided to have a small gathering of close friends…
well yes family,
and frankly I did not even invite Endo to this event.
Yeah, I didn't go to his gathering.
The idea was to have another date where we would hold a large event and that was our plan,
but that didn't actually happen…I’m sorry.
I saw your pictures as well.
You look at a lot of pictures.
Well yes, we took pictures there.
Didn’t I see Ryo there?
Ryo…was not there.
He wasn't
No he was there
Someone who looked like him at least,
Maybe your father looked like him.
He was there.
May I say something?
when we were not doing well and had no money we would still help Hosei this was what 25 or 26 we started getting on Gaki no tsukai
but there was no money and when we would get together we collected a bunch of Nintendo games
and Hosei said that if you were to sell these games you could get some money and he told me to go sell them.
There were a dozen or so games that I took and sold but it only amounted to 90 yen
but he kept saying he was so hungry so I think there was a Korokke that was 60 or 70 yen and we bought it
and Hosei said alright lets split this and went to rip it and it came out more like 60/40
and he handed me the larger piece
and looking back on that I feel so bad thinking I did not invite a person that would do that for me.
Right? Right?
I am filled with remorse.
That would cause an aneurysm.
Yes, he is and he's wonderful to spend time with.
I was surprised he could only sell them for 90 yen I mean what a poor salesman.
Nintendo game software.
The duo both got married and work was going wonderfully and may be considered the high point in their career.
Okay so at this point both private and work lives are going great we would like to hear what this person has to say.
Thank you, this is Yashima.
Now we will hear from one of the actors that was in the Kokoriko miracle type show its Yashima Norito
lets hear what he had to say about the duo
Tanaka is, well coming from me as an actor he is, well, beyond me in terms of acting ability and has a high level of quality as an artist
he idea of "I want to do this" is very noticeable so no matter what was going on he was able to focus and become an excellent actor.
Endo, I feel did not really have a passion for acting.
so he was good or bad or…
Well he wasn't good.
I have no idea what he thinks but I don't think he was interested in the idea of acting by itself.
I think he enjoyed the atmosphere of the stage.
In addition it appears that recently these men have been gathering in their private lives as well.
I think they both like children.
Endo gives off the vibe off being like a father
and Tanaka who would more play with the kids like "I like this do you like it?"
and that would be the difference inthat case, but yeah, they both like kids.
I have had Tanaka come visit our home and I have also had Chiaki come visit our home
and Endo after work would say things like "today is the day you are staying with dad" and things like that would go on in our house.
So, on those day Endo and I would give a number of kids’ baths and when we would do that you can tell if someone is used to doing these things or not
and I could tell Endo knew what he was doing like he played a very active role as a father taking care of the kids.
Getting together as a family.
Yes
So everything is going great you are 35 popular rich.
Let’s see what happens from 35-44.
Wow 36 looks like a terrible time why did both of you drop so quickly?
Falling back down! what happened to this duo?
I knew I was going to see less and less of my daughter.
same as before, and I'm a lazy bum.
So, Tanaka please tell us what happened.
Yes this is really when miracle type finished and in addition all these other shows that had us on also all stopped at this point
and the end of all these shows is what started the plunge.
You had never experienced something like this.
Exactly
I mean if a show starts it will of course end but this was the first time having your show end.
Yes and the shock of that was one thing and our joint effort with the end of our sketches.
That is where I met my wife and had all this teamwork and all these programs we still wanted to do and to see that all come to an end was just shocking.
I see so this wasn't just the show ending there was a lot more to that.
Yes that’s right.
Their show and others all came to an end and sent Tanaka into a mental spiral downward.
What about Endo, why did he fall into despair?
So Endo your graph shows an even further fall.
That was the divorce.
Really?
Yes married young and well I think anyone can agree but divorce..
This shows you were married 5 years.
I believe it was 5 and a half years.
That really sent you down to the bottom here? only five years in? was it really that bad?
Well looking back on it now...
Right I mean now at this point it looks like you two are doing well.
Better than when we lived together.
Well you are filming things together right?
It’s much easier when you don't have those problems living together, but at this time I couldn't think about the future or wasn't thinking about it
and the birth of my first daughter was a big thing at that time I mean the wedding was big too
but the fact that I was now a father and I was putting 100 percent into raising her
and I knew I was going to see less and less of my daughter and that caused it.
So more than the divorce with your wife it was the thought of losing time with your daughter.
Well yeah Chiaki and I discussed many things and could continue to communicate as adults
but to discuss this with a child they can’t really process it the same and that really hit me
and then on Christmas day or Christmas eve it was scary that we decided to separate on Christmas eve
and we signed the paperwork that night and the atmosphere in the home was just so bad
and I was getting hungry so I figured I would go out to eat and as I was going out to eat
I remembered that there was a senior of mine that had helped me out quite a lot during the marriage
and well I thought I would call Sanmsan but he was doing a live show...
...and does a live show on Christmas eve where he discusses loss and things like that but I had completely forgotten about that
but before the show started Sanmasan and I called him and said "Hello this is Endo" and he said "hey what are you up to."
This was before the show started?
Before it started, and I told him about the divorce and after a pause he said "you pass!"
then he asked if I would talk about it on the air. I told him I had no problem about it,
but I didn't think it was okay to do that without telling Chiaki about it,
but yeah at that point it was just the worst.
I see now how the graph goes down like this.
Yes so just straight down.
Not that this was not the end of your rough patch though, we have another video about an event that happened at that time.
Next we will take a look at the events during Endo's divorce.
I told Endo this is dangerous, this is not good, but Endo went on to say that he is going to lose all his money.
In 2007 Endo and Chiaki divorced and was forced to live separately from his 4-year-old daughter which caused him so much stress,
but even after that Endo faced another problem.
I'm still a lazy bum, the epitome of typesetter trash
Here we have LB to discuss this other event.
So the way he was handling his money was well not good I guess,
no matter how much he was earning he would talk about how he would gain money by spending it on investments
in like some bizarre dreamland of handling money
here we told him "this is dangerous, this is not good" but end went on to say that he is going to lose all his money.
I was surprised I saw him in our break room I was so surprised.
I knew yelling at him wouldn't work so I simply said to him you're being an idiot.
So what happened?
well the start of the divorce was also in part because of this. I would get money and had this guy who told me about an opportunity
where I could double my money in two weeks and Chiaki would say "no you can really make money like this"
and said "you have to stop this" and yes at this time I was secretly doing this and then she caught me doing it
and that’s when things started to get worse.
So how much money did you spend on these investments in total?
Well even if you can't say an exact amount can you give us an idea.
Say it like it were your annual salary, like a baseball player.
The other day my mother brought me a pamphlet and I said "what is it?" and she said "this is such a lovely home"
and I said it sure is it was a duplex made of concrete and it was being resold and I think I would have been able to buy it with the amount I spent
I wished I could have bought it for her or not and I still think about that to this day.
You are an idiot.
Divorce, separating from his daughter, money troubles, Endo was in despair,
but here he was saved…
All these things I had kept to myself and was just keeping it all in and then when I got divorced
one thing that saved me was well Tanaka,
I mean we didn't talk so much but with the divorce and all I had to tell him about it anyway
so I told him "you know I am getting divorced" I thought he might get angry with me like "I told you you rushed into it" or something but instead he said
"hmm? that’s interesting" like in the world of performers I thought he would be the one to get angry about something like that but instead.
Well like what is there to do.
I was sure he was going to yell at me.
You must have been happy with his response.
So yes speaking with Tanaka at this time really helped me.
What saved end was his long time best friend since elementary school Tanaka 23 years together who have gone through everything together and now…
their charts are matched here.
So here at 41 it looks like you both have leveled out, but this even has a much deeper meaning than in the start.
Yes there was so much that happened and yeah to go through it all and end up here.
You wouldn't say up here either just right in the middle is interesting.
Do you have anything to add at this point you turned 41 and this happened to return you to 0.
you had all these experiences, I mean obviously the zero here is very different from the zero here.
Actually for me the zero here is not so different from this one, well at this point it was like I want to make it big and that was really all I thought about
from there many things happened but then returning to 50 I kind of feel the same thing that I want to get big again.
By yourself?
No the two of us, I want us to make a big return.
What do you think Tanaka?
I agree and feel the same. The 0 at 41 is our 20th anniversary as a duo
and looking back on those times and the feeling of getting back out there is something we have been talking about.
At this point to say let’s do it again...
Yes Endo said "let’s go for it" and in that sense, I think the feeling of starting again from 0 is the feeling and reason behind us both placing our mark at 0.
Going through it all over 23 years, this duo has now decided to once again get out there and returned to the ideas that first got them started.
The duo will once again move with the same purpose that held them those 23 years ago.
So finally we have prepared a piece for you two looking to the future.
I have a great feeling about these 2 moving forward.
When the two of them get together I would love to see them make more sketches the ideas that only the two of them could create together.
The atmosphere they create together or even in a group I would love to see what they could add.
Recently TV programs have become a little more subdued, and to see the true Kokoriko that crazy duo, to have them both,
the perverted Endo and the strange Tanaka come out with something new is something I want to see.
Well yes it looks like this is the perfect condition, so what is in the future for Kokoriko?
It feels like people are reading a lot into this.
I see so it’s hard for you to say anything specific right now?
Well you know we still have many things to discuss and while there are those that say we aren't serious
yet, there are those that in a good way are not looking at us too hard and I think that will allow us to come out with new material.
Tanaka what do you think about Kokoriko?
Yes, well it is an opportunity to discuss so many possibilities so to have the two of us create something new.
We want to see that.
So yes something like that just like the 0 up there where we first started making our sketches,
so we are looking back on that and thinking on that to get going again.
Hosei, any words for your brothers?
I would love to see more bits from you guys, I really do.
I spoke with Masa some weeks ago and he said that the Kokoriko duo is like a one plus one equals three combination,
but if the feeling is more like one plus one is 1.9 you should stop while you are ahead.
but the strength of the duo where you would say you two are three is truly remarkable and I feel you can do it again and I really hope you get back at it.
Please continue your work Kokoriko thank you for joining us today.
All: Thank you very much!