New advertisement for SmartNews featuring Downtown
"Half-price coupon"  // "Free coupon"
"No.1" // "Rain cloud radar"
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Look! They're giving half-price coupons on SmartNews!
What a bargain!
You love coupons like this, don't you?
Yeah...
But...
I love you even more
Macchan...
Download now SmartNews to get your half-price coupon for Domino's Pizza
I'm gonna try SmartNews' lottery for a free coupon
Please, win!
Here I go
SUCCESS
Alright!!
Free stuff! Free stuff! Free stuff!
Download now SmartNews and try to win a free coupon for a gyuudon at Yoshinoya
They say SmartNews is the most downloaded news app
Popular, isn't it?
It's also the easiest to use and most used, no.1
SmartNews is...
Like us, isn't it?
No.1 in user-friendliness, number of use and downloads: it's SmartNews
Hamada! Don't forget your umbrella!
What?
SmartNews' rain cloud radar says it's about to rain soon
Matsumoto...
See?
Matsumoto...!
Download now SmartNews and access
the rain cloud radar to always know when it's going to rain