It's Nasubi ♥
Can people live by only winning prize contests?
The challenge is to win prizes by phone or post card entry
The goal is a 1 million Yen in prizes
The man that continues this challenge is Nasubi
To fill in the details so far...
January of this year was the start (1998)
And suddenly 9 months have already passed!
Up to this point, the total prize value of winnings is 559,374 Yen!
He continues writing postcards to earn 1 million Yen worth of prizes!!
By the way, are there any viewers that have noticed Nasubi's transformation?
This is before the transformation
And this is after!
That's right! He's sun burnt!
This sunburn happened in an un-aired episode!
That was...
Midnight of that day...
The producer appears!
The producer is still scheming!
He must have the keys!
Is this really ok?!
With the light in his face Nasubi awakes!
But he is totally clueless to the situation!
He knows from experience the light summons an evil monster...
Have you realised?
Yes?
Then Nasubi...
Huh?
With Nasubi's uncertain voice,
does he assume he's reached the goal?!
I have won some seriously premium items...
Hirosue Ryoko signed poster
It's obvious that's the situation right?
No.
SHOCK!
Then the producer...
Eyemask
We're moving house again?
June 28th broadcast
This circumstance occoured once before and lead to the moving to a new home
Again, he is made to wear headphones with super loud music
And not forgetting, he is wearing the black leather shoes he won previously also!
Nasubi is lead outside...
And taken on a road trip!
Is he moving house once again?!
Nasubi's car journey continues through the night into a new day!
And continues for over 12 hours!
Haven't we been driving for way too long now?
Nasubi is getting anxious!
We continue across a massive bridge!
Suddenly Nasubi...
Maybe I should try and nap...
And he falls asleep once more.
He continues to sleep for another 5 hours!
When he opens his eyes just where will he be?!
In a boat!
But Nasubi thinks...
An earthquake?!
He has no idea how to judge where or what he is on
Ah, the breeze feels great!
I'm kinda getting splashed with water here
That's when...
Is this a boat?!
He finally realised!
Even so, this is really taking a long time...
I'm kinda scared
Unable to see, he is stricken with fear!
Just where is Nasubi being taken to ?!
His journey will soon be over...
He finally arrives!
It's okay to remove the eyemask now
After a drastic jump, what's the first thing he see's?
The sea!
Wha.. Where? Is this?
That's when...
It's the inflatable ring I won
Right?
You don't get it?
We're going swimming in the sea? ♥
Correct
After this the staff reveal the true intention of this distant journey...
Summer holiday
Uhahaha!♥
After continuously writing postcards daily inside for 9 months of the challenge, it's a present from the staff!
Summer holiday!
This is really a summer holiday?!
He's super ecstatic
Then upon seeing the sea, Nasubi...
Sea water is salty, right?
Salty!?
To this point Nasubi hasn't won any salty foods at all!
I want some side dishes!
A flavor with impact!
Something greasy!
That's when...
Can I go and give it a little taste?
He wants to drink it!
Well then, please exscuse me!
Wait!
Before that...
The mic will get wet so...
Please use this waterproof one ♥
I'm going in then!
SALTY ♥
SALTY ! ♥♥
It's good!
Can I go once more?
Sea!
Sea water!!
So salty ♥♥♥
Denpa Shonen presents Nasubi's summer holiday at the coast festival special movie!
Nasubi is deeply moved by the long lost taste of the sea water
Then the staff inform Nasubi...
Here
Camera
I have to film myself?
Tripod
Yeah ♥
How long is this holiday planned for?
As long as you want ♥
Huh?!
As long as you enjoy it ♥
Upon hearing that Nasubi...
Well let's enjoy this holiday for a while then!
But then Nasubi realises some things...
What about food?
Apparently there is plenty around ♥
You mean from the locals?
Then the staff inform him...
It's a deserted island!
Ah.. It looks like people would live here you know!
That's right, this is...
Please take off the eye mask
Deserted island!
Denpa Shonen's
R-Mania escape from a desert island!
R-Mania where actually able to escape from this deserted island where Nasubi now is!
This is where R-Mania where dropped off,
and Nasubi is here!
Of course, Nasubi knows nothing about the island!
But seriously, what should I do about food?
Like I said, the island has loads!
Ehhhh!
There's a shit load of shellfish!
R-Mania where able to scavange plenty of food to live on from the sea and mountains
I have to forage for it?!
But one thing is already prepared...
Please wait a second!
Previously
won rice
In preparation for this holiday the staff have packed all the useful winnings for cooking and making fire
BBQ set
Sake can
and cutlery
Towel
Lighter
You said 'preparation' but it's all my stuff!
If you go on a leisure trip, of course you'd take your own stuff!
So that's how it is
But what about water?
Just for you
I was wondering how you where going to bring the kitchen here!
Purified water from the filter he won
Enjoy your holiday then!
You're really leaving?
Wait a second!
Hey!!!
But then!
Ah! We forgot!
The staff return to see Nasubi
What is it? Are you worried I'll be lonely?
You need your diary!
Bye!
Nasubi
They seriously left me...
3 dairy books now on sale!
Please enjoy the entries from Nasubi's over sea dairy!
I wonder if it's set right? (Camera setup)
"Of course I was expecting that from the staff of Denpa Shonen"
"They sailed off into the horizon across the sea."
Troublesome!
"Anyway I can't pass up this chance to swim in the sea and bask in the sun!"
"This summer holiday is going to be super fun!
Let's enjoy this summer holiday to the fullest and really have fun!
♪ It's Nasbi's private beach! ♪
♪ I'm the only one in the sea! ♪
Let's get in the sea, yay!
The first time this year Nasubi has gone in the sea
Waaa! The sea! Sea water! Summer holiday! Yay!
Nasubi frolics happily in the sea ♥
But...
"The inflatable ring that I won has transformed me from a useless swimmer to sailing like a boat!"
He can't swim.
And then...
The first time this year sun bathing!
"But today's weather is cloudy"
Then...
I'm not catching a suntan at all!
Ok! Let's go for a little wander instead
The expedition footage with Nasubi and tripod starts!
Zun ♪ Zun ♪ Zun ♪ Zun ♪
What's that over there I wonder?
He comes across a rocky area...
"As I'm walikng along I'm sure to find some seafood as a side dish for tonight's dinner!"
There's nothing but a load of Wharf roaches
I need to come up with a plan!
I can't eat these Wharf roaches
It doesn't look like there is much around here to make into tonight's side dish
Then Nasubi notices something about the sea
The tide is coming in now, it should rise some more...
Nasubi notices the tide rising up
As expected of a deserted island...
But when he's walking...
Oh?!
It's an onion!
Onion discovery!
R-Mania made the same onion discovery and made it into a daily staple!
Either way, finding an onion looks like it will be ok!
The next thing he finds on the walk...
Oh?!
Look over there, it seems to be an oil drum?
But this oil drum!
Behind me is forest and infront is the sea! Amazing!
The oil drum R-Mania made into a bath!
I wonder who's been burning this?
A bath?
Who bathes in a drum in this day and age...?
Don't be stupid!
Next, Nasubi ventures into the forest...
Oh?!
It looks like some kind of cabin...
Cabin discovery!
Looks like they were making stuff in here...
That's when...
What the fuck's this?
R R R R R R R R R R R R R R R R R R R R R
This is!
Good morning
While R-Mania where staying on this island, every day they were here, they marked this board with an 'R'!
Upon seeing this, Nasubi...
I dunno what the shit this is, but it's spooky
Some kind of witchcraft?
I don't wanna be finding this sort of thing!
Fear
I, Nasubi didn't see anything ok!
Please don't let anything weird happen!
What was up with that RRRR?
BAD VIBES!
And then!
This is bad I can't see the sea at all
Am I lost?
Is it the curse of 'R'?!
Nasubi has lost his way in the forest
It was a bad idea to come in the forest
He continues lost in the forest for over 2 hours!
Ah! I found the sea!
He finally came out at the coast.
And returned to his drop off point
The area scouting is completed
Alot of time has passed and it will soon be dark
I'll have to cook dinner on a fire so first I should search for some wood to burn
He spends over an hour searching for kindling
Stuff he found earlier
Bucket ect...
Firewood gathered
But Nasubi...
Gathering wood is hard work
Exhausted.
But then!
Observe
A rabbit!
This rabbit...
Mama is fitting!
Let's go with Mama then?
During R-Mania's stay on the island they adopted a family member, the wild rabbit Mama... Could it be?
See ya Mama!
When they left the island, this was the final farewell
We're really grateful for everything!
But Nasubi...
He's surprised by Mama.
"What the fuck was that just now?"
It's time to prepare dinner
First is to put the rice and water in the can...
Using the lighter he ignites the kindling in the BBQ set
Rice cooking starts!
Then...
Uwah! The can is burnt completely black!
High intensity fire!!
No! Please stop!!
Rice cooking finished...
Has he just wasted a serving?
Itadakimasu!
But what about the flavor?
Mm?
It's great ♥
After this Nasubi...
He washes the onion he found in the sea...
Cut's it with the knife he brought and then flame grilled!
Finished!
The taste of the onion?
It's delicious ♥
I'm alone on a deserted island but it seems I can cope quite well!
Later on that night
Nasubi writes in his diary...
"The rice and onion was delicious, another 2 or 3 days of this and I'll become one with mother nature!"
The first day of Nasubi's summer holiday is over
The next morning
It looks so refreshing!
He's awake.
Eh?! He slept on the beach?
Nasubi starts the 2nd day of summer holiday!
"It was like being born for the first time, the rays
from the sun engulfing me as I opened my eyes...
I am Nasubi."
Yawn
Good morning
"Today is completely different from yesterday"
"I can see far into the horizon of the completely blue sky, is it going to be fun I wonder!"
Today Nasubi again...
Sea swimming ♥
That's cool!
And then...
Ah, this is great!
Sunbathing ♥
Forgetting everything he enjoys the summer holiday to the max!
Then...
Mm?!
What a feeling, I'm starting to tan!
I'm tanning right?
He certainly has tanned!
I'm tanning nicely and becoming even more handsome!
It feels great to be out in the sun light!
I could stay like this forever!
I'm so happy!
Summer holiday
is great! ♥
All Nasubi does is sunbathe all day
Then...
It seems like low tide right now
Let's check out that rocky area from yesterday and find some seafood!
This is where we searched yesterday
It doesn't seem like there's anything here but...
Just then!
Oh?!
Here here here!
Shell discovery!
This gives me a good feeling about this area!
Let's have a little look at what we have here
One shellfish GET!
Looking good huh!
As the tide is completely different to yesterday, he shares the same good fortune as R-Mania finding plenty of shellfish!
Ensure you have the relevant fishing permits or permission!
Check it out!
Then straight after...
Flame grilled.
Please observe! Looking so tasty bubbling away!
And so...
Let's eat ♥
Eaten.
Delicious!
"It's free food so today, tomorrow and after that you can gather as much as you want!"
This island is
the best!
Summer holiday is
There's nothing more to say!
"This island is like a magical paradise..."
But the absolute worst conclusion is awaiting a completely oblivious Nasubi!
Nasbi is enjoying summer holiday on the same deserted island as R-Mania
Summer holiday is
the best!
"This summer holiday isn't over yet! The island still has alot to offer!"
That's when!
A boat appears!
Its the staff boat arriving to see how Nasubi is doing!
How's the holiday?
No matter how you look at it... It's great!
Summer holiday is the best!
That's when Nasubi...
It's okay to stay a little longer right?
Sure
But after this, the staff will tell Nasubi something that will instantly change his attitude!
During your summer holiday...
What will you do if you win something?
Huh?!
Isn't someone caring for it?
What do you mean?
Well, er.. for example, one of the staff takes my place in the room...
When the postman comes, they can receive it and say 'oh, thank you'...
We never considered it.
What if I won a car though?!
This is no time to be casually laying around!
We have to get back right now!
But what about summer holiday?
I don't need that shit at all!
Nasubi's summer holiday...
Only a one night stay!
Please support Nasubi @hamatsutomoaki he now a charity fund raiser from Fukushima
Subs/timing by iiharima 07-2016