The Owarai Laboratory
The show starts now   -Yes, got it
It's the 6th time now   -Yeah, the 6th time we're doing this
The 6th time of chaos
By watching previous contests, they can grasp the concept of how things work
As well as things which have never yet been done
So I feel like the contestants themselves are upskilling too
An ever-evolving battle
I believe that the atmosphere could still be tense, but without any useless anxiety
It has become a high level "tournament"
This is experimental, definitely experimental, this time, again
What is the highlight of the 6th experiment?
Season 2 "Point System"
Season 3 "Zombie System"
Season 5 "Helper system"
So, for this time...there will be many female contestants
"Female comedians" more than ever
I wonder what will happen...
In addition, umm...
How should I put it...
There will be some aggressive male comedians
I look forward to seeing the chemical reactions between them
It must be interesting
Some want more of it, others dislike it, but...
I believe there won't be any extreme dirty jokes this time
Well, it's game over if you dare to do dirty jokes among a bunch of females
It will simply become an adult video
So I believe that's not going to happen
Finally approaching the...
Well, I'm expecting to have a champion contest
(Season 2) Winner - Kotoge Eiji from Viking
(Season 3) Winner - Yamamoto Keiichi from Gokuraku Tombo
(Season 4) Winner - Kukky from Yasei Bakudan
(Season 5) Winner - Hollywood Zakoshisyoh
It's probably going too far to have a 100 million cash prize
Putting it the other way round, it might be interesting to have no cash prize for the champion contest
*A Fall's Appetite (食欲の秋) is a term in Japan which describes the abundance in food during the season of harvest
Although we use to say "A Fall's Appetite"
However, I'm having remarkably small appetite recently
All that I'm eating is udon with deep-fried tofu
That being said, I would like to offer you an invitation
Could you prepare one million yen
and gather at a designated location?
I shall reinitiate Documental
I have prepared a reward of 10 million yen for the winner
Of course, participation is voluntary
For those of you who wish to participate, I shall inform you of the time and location
Awaiting your reply
It's getting colder in the morning and at night
Please take care of yourself and don't catch a cold
Sincerely, Matsumoto Hitoshi
THE PARTICIPATING COMEDIANS ENTER
That's such a big bag
So that's how she looks like
This is her first appearance, Yuriyan Retriever
I'm Yuriyan Retriever from Yoshimoto
I'll keep calm and carry on
Yo   -Nice to meet you
So I'm here to give you something, Yuriyan
This is it
I'm being invited?   -Yes
I've been waiting this for so long
I'm so happy! Hooray!
This gal cares nothing about others
All that she's thinking about is herself
We'll see how far she can go on her own
*Yuriyan is famous for being able to speak English very well, because she loves watching English movies
The Smashing Bilingual Girl*
Matsumoto-san said to me "you are the one"
She suits Documental, doesn't she?
She has a strong heart too
To be honest, female comedians usually have a stronger heart than male comedians
"The W" champion
Female comedian
No.1 Tournament
How much was the cash prize for "The W"?
It's 10 million...
How did you spend those money?
Well, I only did it once a month, but...
I spent it all on dango, and I ate them all
I don't mind losing this money at all
For being able to appear on this show
How will you spend the 10 million this time?
I want to get laser hair removal
Someone's coming
Who will it be?
Nice to meet you
Kurozawa-san
I'm so happy to see you
I'm Kurosawa Kazuko from Morisantyu
Anyway, I'll try my best!
Hello
Kurosawa is someone who reads between the lines
She's interesting as long as she don't read too much between the lines
If she thinks too much and reads too much between the lines
She ends up crying
What happened, Kurosawa?
She's crying   -What happened?
Crying all of a sudden
Seriously, what happened?
It's truly a male‐dominated society
A male‐dominated society...
I'm shy with strangers...
Shy with strangers?
A meat that sings and dance
I feel regret
For being unable to give good results in front of Matsumoto-san
I have to admit my inadequacy
There's not much chance to talk with other comedians
I have only talked with Tsubaki Oniyako and Oasis about health while having dinner together
I'm so nervous   -Same here
But I'm really happy, it has been a male-dominated society before, so I'm really happy to see more girls
Other comedians are thinking like "so that's all she can do"
And that really makes me suffer
So I will let them know, "this gal is insane"
Let's take the chance to laugh now
Here comes the 3rd contestant
Didn't bring much
Wow, so happy, another girl
I'm so happy
So it's a kitty party
Why does Kurosawa keep saying "so happy, so happy"?
I get it, so it's a kitty party
Women-only...   -Many females
I'm Kondo Haruna from Harisenbon
I'll definitely take the 10 million back home
This is for you
The 3rd contestant is a female comedian too
For me?
Me?
She has a strong heart too
I'm not sure how should Haruna position herself in Documental though
I'm the daughter of a civil servant
And I'm being raised by really strict parents
So if my senior invites me
I have no choice but to accept it
I just have to accept it
The Counter Fantasista
I'm sure going to laugh
Will it be fine? They're all easily amused
It's gonna be interesting to see Haruna break down
As a hidden theme, I want to make Matsumoto-san laugh
I've actually enrolled in comedy school to become a Boke
*Haruna is the Tsukkomi of Harisenbon
So I want to challenge myself and seek opportunities to join other's Boke this time
It's your second time right, Kurosawa-san?
Yeah, but I don't need to be shy with strangers this time, so I'm really happy
I actually think Haruna is really strong
You were a bit shy with strangers last time, right?   -Yes, I was
Here comes the 4th contestant
Nice to meet you
Women, women-only
Women-only...
Daigo must be shocked
I'm a man though...
Yeah, suddenly a man among women
It's not supposed to be a women-only contest, right?
I'm Daigo from Chidori, and this is my second time
I will win
I will enjoy
I will not lose
Good morning
Do you recognize this?
I do
Isn't it too fast?
Why is Daigo invited?
Because the producer wants to make sure that there's always some popular comedians
Well, you should have noticed this already, but...
I'm weak
I'm super weak
(Season 4) The second dropout within 4 hours 30 minutes
The rough and shy baldy
But I do feel regret about the last contest
I will try to be aggressive and attack more this time
I do want to take revenge
Wait a second, this can't be true
I thought there would only be one girl at most
I didn't prepare anything last time
So this time, not anything fancy, but I've prepared something
Well, you'll probably be like "why the heck", but...
I've actually...
Removed my pubic hair
And I have some beautiful paintings on my balls
I have no idea when to show it though
So the best case scenario is that someone will take off my pants
It was never like this before
Exactly   -Yeah
So they did this to prevent the predominance of men over women
Don't call us women, call us girls please
Daigo's face looks funny
This is incredible   -Nice to meet you
It's a kitty party, completely a kitty party
I'm Tomochika from Yoshimoto
Instead of being nervous, I just want to do what I want to do and accomplish my goals
This is for you   -Yes?
Documental
I'm looking forward to it
This is something that I really want to join
She is a woman of principle
And she is mentally strong
The Protean Imitation Queen
My style is basically to imitate and become someone else
So from this perspective, I'm quite similar to Akiyama-san
So it's tough if Akiyama happens to be joining too
I think there should be more female comedians
There wasn't much before, right?
Friends who I usually hang out with, Haruna from Harisenbon, Yuriyan, Ooshima-san
If these people are joining, it must be hilarious
Tomochika-san don't laugh at all, right?
I've never laughed since I was born
That's so true
Tomochika never laughs, right?
She is probably one of the contenders for the championship
When I'm not into it, I don't laugh at all
But when I'm into it, I can laugh for a week
What I'm concerned about is...is it fine to just aim to win?
If you ask me, do I want 10 million?
Not really, to be honest
Well, I mean, of course I want it, but...
It's kind of a collective gameplay, right?
I want to attack aggressively, score the most points, and finally win the 10 million
Why am I the 4th person to enter the room?
Exactly, why not the last one...
It makes sense if I enter after her, so it's all men thereafter
But then I'm in between the girls...
They're quite concerned about who the other players are
Hello everybody
Good morning   -Amazing
This combination is so rare
It sure is rare
So it's not a women-only contest
Hello, I'm Maeda Ken from Slimclub
I will enjoy the time with other comedians and win the contest
Hello   -Hello
Hooray!
I'm actually betting on Maeda
This should be a stage for him to unleash his talent
Seriously, I like Matsumoto-san so much
But I've never won any championship in front of Matsumoto-san
Neither the M-1 contest
Nor the IPPON Grand Prix
I really want to win in front of Matsumoto Hitoshi
Husky Voice Mutant
I believe he will work hard
To compensate for failure of his duo partner
He was neither attacking nor laughing
His partner was unbelievable
According to what he said
"That place has no Owarai, mental is all there is"
He then said "I have neither Owarai nor mental"
"All I have is a body sitting there"
I've actually been fasting for 4 days
It's a jinx
Whenever I do fasting, good things happen
When I did fasting for 3 days, I got into the finals for the M-1 contest
When I did fasting for 10 days, I became a regular member of Tantei Night Scoop
So this time, I've been fasting as well
I'm not mainstream, and I'm not capable of being mainstream
So I believe that with my participation, Documental will become something different
So they are male comedians liked by females?
Maybe the male comedians liked by female comedians
Yeah, they are both genuinely nice
Agreed, they tend to treat us as comedians instead of females
-This contest is going to be exceptional   -Yeah, definitely exceptional
Here he comes
What should I do?
So many girls?
He's a male comedian that likes females though
No way, don't talk to me like that
I'm Jinnai Tomonori from Yoshimoto
I really want to stay till last this time, at least the last 2 or 3 people
Hello
Hey, isn't this too fast?
Well, last time, Jinnai did nothing and went home
No wonder people say he's not interesting anymore after he's married
When you enter that place, you no longer know what is interesting, or what is not interesting
It's just true chaos
Chaotic place
Mister Hidden Boke
But he's definitely a fast learner
So I believe he will prepare himself this time
What should I do?   -This is amazing
Probably a lot of veteran will be joining today's contest
So my tactic is to expand their Boke and find a way to counterattack
I want to let everyone know, even the Tsukkomi type of comedians, stand a chance to win
I'm definitely going to laugh, I hate being Tsukkomi-ed
Having these members to work together is interesting
Here he comes, a familiar face
He's almost like a regular member
So strange to have these members
He's the Mister Documental
Fujimoto is going to make me laugh
Yoshimoto creative agency, I'm Fujimoto from Fujiwara
This time, seriously, I'm aiming to win the contest
Okay, okay, this atmosphere again...
I knew it, here it is
Here it comes
Fujimon, he's a familiar face, the man who is disliked by everyone
Come on, there's no need to dislike him that much
Matsumoto Hitoshi is not a fair judge, he's being too kind to Fujimon. I love Documental, but I want a fair contest
Matsumoto Hitoshi is clearly being too nice to Fujimon.
Everyone can see he's laughing a lot.
He's being too kind to his junior
I don't think he'll win the contest anyway
The show is interesting, but the judge is being too kind to Fujimon. If the same thing happened to other comedians, they'll definitely be out.
In my opinion, it's a safe
Barely safe
He has the ability to expand other's potential
So yeah, I enjoy it when he's here
How many times have you been here, Fujimoto-san?
4 times!   -That's too much
Many people say to me "you're so interesting" because of Documental
Many people say that to me, however...
Seriously speaking, the number of job offers didn't increase at all
Well, I had three days off in a row recently
Come on, I've been so active in Documental, and yet I'm having three days off in a row? Isn't that strange?
People seem to see me as a byplayer
I always hear people saying "he's definitely not the protagonist"
Speaking from my heart, I really want to be the protagonist
Yeah, that's how I feel now
So just two more people
Yes, two more people
He's barefooted
So hot...
Come on, what the heck are you doing
Waste of bullets
It's not even started yet   -Not yet?
Ouch, ouch, so hot
Well, maybe this is his tactic
I'm Jimmy Onishi
I'm the No.8 hostess in Shinjuku Nichome, Kubukicho
Jimmy-san, hello...   -Hello
Wait a second, this is...Jimmy-san...
What's that?
This is for you   -Here it is again
You know what this is, right?   -Yes, at the moment I see it
I have to borrow it from Yoshimoto,
how else can I even prepare 10 million
Please borrow me 10 million for Documental
10 million yen
For Matsumoto-san's Documental
Documental?   -Yes, Documental
It's him again...
He's really interesting, however funny people are always easily amused
Well, it's probably difficult for him to win the contest
I'm easily amused
So I'll try not to laugh and improve my defense
Why are you always attacking before it's not even started yet?
Well, I just want to alert myself right from the beginning
Oh, I get it   -So to remind yourself that it's getting serious now
I've dedicated all of my salary to Documental
It even shows up in my dreams
Did you win the contest in your dreams?
No, not even in my dreams
People are only concerned about the "thing" in front
But actually, our butt is also something to be aware of
So this time, anal is the main point
Are you a hostess this time?   -Yeah, hostess
You won't laugh later if we talk about it now
You'll eventually know why my face is red
Why did you say it then, dude
Come on, this is going to make me laugh either way
Probably everyone will be surprised by this contestant
So, I've prepared this contestant for you all
Strong presence, very strong presence
Nice to meet you
They all have to stand up
He is the person who I don't want to see here the most
I'm Murakami Shoji
First thing first, I'll try my best
Excuse me
Hello
Is this from Machan?
I never watched Documental, but I've heard of it before
Too late, dude!
Come on, it's already the 6th contest, you're asking me to join the 6th one?
Sorry for being discourteous...
Well, I'll join though!   -You're joining?
Amazing, right?
For the first time in Documental's history,
my senior is joining the contest
Well, I really like him
He's really interesting and I always hoped he could join
But I bet he'll laugh immediately
Showa Gag Geek
So late
Offer
I wonder if Machan is already feeling tired about Owarai
*Matsumoto is hosting a show called "Wide na show", which reports and comments on news
It's not time for you to report news yet, right?*
This is a battle between me and Matsumoto Hitoshi, the man who built up a generation of Owarai
I'll give it everything I've got,
everything that I've learnt in the past 43 years
I hope I can at least last for 30 or 40 minutes
Why are you having a one-tone dressing?
Stop it, that's hilarious!
As an old man into my forty-second year of career, I'll try my best and go all out
And I hope the audiences can feel the passion running through my veins
I'll put up a good fight with the experience that I've gained in my 42 years of career
Well, just look forward to it
Please don't speak with a voice like that   -Eh?
Come on, don't let others repeat themselves
No...I've actually...umm...
Sorry, I don't want to talk about it now
Why did you end the conversation?
Please stop it
I hate those curve balls from Shoji-san
He's so angry
Why is he always angry when he enters the room?
It's so interesting to have these members   -This is awful
I can watch this forever
This is just chaotic
This is incredible, right?
Yeah, this is gonna be awful
Shoji-san don't know Jimmy is going to be here, right?   -No clue
And of course, Jimmy don't know as well, so it's impossible for anyone to team up
So I wonder are you guys feeling nervous right now?
Of course we're nervous
Shoji-san's husky voice is already so interesting
This must be awful
Maeda's voice is husky too
Exactly, this is a crush of personality
For having a husky voice too
The husky brothers
I can't take this anymore
Shoji-san, are you really fine with this?
I think your defense is really weak   -Yeah, he always laugh
I laugh a lot   -And you have a smiling face
So please remember to keep a poker face
It's game over if you laugh
I know about the rules
I really think your defense is weak
And your attack is not strong as well
I'm really worried about you
That's what makes us laugh
But I do want to watch him on stage, so please work hard Shoji-san
Yeah, I'll try my best   -Yes please, Shoji-san
What about the battle between the girls?
Tomochika is probably strong, in my opinion
It's like "how many characters does she even have?"
And I never saw Tomochika laugh at other's gag
You're right   -No way, that's not true
But actually, Tomochika always laugh at some lame gags
Yes exactly, I've always been laughing at Fujimon's gags
Yeah, those kinds of lame gags
You're gonna make him angry
Yeah, he's lame
But good type of lame, right?   -No, she didn't say that
He always makes us laugh, right?
I have the impression that Yuriyan doesn't laugh much too
She doesn't laugh at others' gags, but she laughs at herself
Yeah, I laugh at my own gags
She's always like that
These girls are all so strong
Can you please put out the candle?   -Yeah, seriously
No, I want to let you guys wither
No way, we won't
You've been laughing so fast last time
And I actually think highly on Maeda   -I'm so happy, thank you
But Maeda is actually really weak, seriously
I really like to watch people Boke, so...
-For Jinnai, he's not interesting anymore after he's married
-Who are you talking about? Please stop it
Everyone knows that
I'm in a gud...good condition
Although I can't even say "good condition" clearly
-Are you really in a good condition?
-Seriously, please stop saying those kinds of thing
Anyway, please give me your one million yen
I actually wanted to watch more of these 10 people talking   -Eh?
That's how interesting it is, the personality of these 10 people
It's in an envelope...
Hey, come on, Jimmy
Is this really one million?   -Yes it is, one million
Then why did you take it out of the envelope?
We can just put it together like this...
Okay, this is it
So this adds up to 10 million
And this is the one million from me
And this is the 10 million prepared by the staffs
Brand-new notes   -Wow, amazing
Please work hard and fight for this
We all know about the rules, right?
So I'll give you cards
You could be out immediately, if the laugh is too excessive
Only if it's too excessive, but this never happened in the past
If you go too far, you'll be out
You can't have a smiling face, right?   -Nope
Need to keep a poker face right from the beginning
But this is my neutral face though
Then please keep it like that
Can we shuffle seats?
Do that after it starts..   -It makes no difference though
So we're not always sitting here?
You can move around as you like
Could we go to the toilet?   -Yeah, it's over there
He never watched this?
Because there's many girls this time, so there's no camera over there
Thank you very much
Well, I'm not talking to you though, Haruna
How come?
You're the least relevant one in the room
I don't have that thing!
That one just now was awful...
Please stop this...
Kurosawa, please don't cry today
Please don't cry
That's gonna make others laugh too
There's many girls today, so no problem
It's fine to cry?   -Yes, it's fine to cry
She cried last time, and said it's a male-dominated society
Yes, thank you for helping me last time
I'll give cards to people who try to muddle through too
For example, if you keep drinking water
Or keep smoking cigarettes   -Yes, that's inappropriate too
So keep these things in your mind
Let's get off to a slow start this time   -Yeah, let's take our time
Please let me make one thing clear, 6 hours is just the time limit
It can finish in just 2 hours as well
Although it never happened in the past
It's completely fine to finish the contest in an hour
Someone can strike a fatal blow, and kill everyone in the room
Catching the whole herd with one throw   -Exactly
I'm looking forward to that too
Come on, no one has that kind of killer technique
Good luck everyone   -Thank you very much
It's still fine to laugh now, right?
Ah, I can't take this anymore
-Are you gonna put out the candle?
-I'll put it out once the contest starts
Once the contest starts? That sounds weird
Give me a break, I'm gonna laugh at the moment it starts
You're definitely going to wear something, huh?
You're definitely going to wear something, like a wig, right?
You made yourself easy to wear it   -Yes, I'm going wear it
About time to...
Documental Start!
I'll put out the candle now
It started   -People are not looking at you yet
It started?
Yes, it started
What are you going to do with the candle?
I'll put out the candle now
Excuse me
So hot
Are you okay?   -That's dangerous
Are you okay?
Why did you light the candle so early then?
Are you done with this?
Jimmy-san, let's go slowly
You're going too fast right from the start, seriously
We have plenty of time, you understand me?
Yeah, he's right
It scared me
You're going too fast
We have 6 hours, Shoji-san
Exactly
Let's tea (calm) down and keep going*
*Yuriyan did a word play with tea (Ocha) and calm (Ochi)
Calm down, you mean calm down, right?
Let's get off to a slow start, okay?
Let's discuss this first
Let's discuss how to spend the 6 hours
Yeah, let's talk
Jimmy-san?
You're going too fast
He's incredible
Jimmy-san, that's not how you use it
Put it around your upper arm
It's gonna squeeze your neck
This is how we do things at Shinjuku Nichome
*Shinjuku Nichome is home to the world’s highest concentration of gay bars in a single area
You mean that Shinjuku Nichome with many gays?   -Yes, gays
So you are gay too?
Well yeah, I'm kind of mixed
Mixed?
Yeah, only half of me, so...
It's gonna squeeze you hard   -Too dangerous
We're worried about you   -You better not do that
Yeah, don't push yourself too hard
Is my face turning red?
Oh, I see, so that's why...
I can feel my face turning red
And yet, you're still squeezing it
That's dangerous   -Please stop it, Jimmy-san, seriously
Your face is turning red
Even your eyes are turning red
That's pink...k...k...   -Jimmy-san, too dangerous
Seriously, please stop it
Look at my eyes, I have pink ass (eyes)*
*Jimmy did a wordplay with conjunctiva (Ketsu-maku) and ass (Ketsu)
(Pink ass?...)
Pink ass, I have pink ass
What the heck is a pink ass?
Jimmy-san, this is seriously inappropriate
Come on, he laughed
Did Daigo laugh?
Maybe Daigo...
Daigo and Fujimon is close
Are you done with the candle   -Yeah, I'm done with it
I'll Shoji (dispose) of it*
*Jimmy mistaken Sho-ji (Matsumoto's senior) for Sho-bun (Dispose of it)
Shoji of it?
Shoji of it? You mean dispose of it?   -Yeah, dispose of it
What the heck is Shoji of it   -That's impolite
He said Shoji of it
-(Shoji-san is drinking so much water)
-Are you done with your red face too?
Huh?
-Are you done with your red face?
-Yeah, I'll count (remove) my makeup now*
*Jimmy mistaken remove makeup (Kao-otosu) for count (Kau-n-to)
Countdown?   -You're counting on something?
He said remove his makeup
Can you speak clearly just for once, please?
I am speaking clearly
Please take a seat, just take a seat
Did you buy these yourself, Jimmy-san?
Yeah, for bandage
Bandage?
It's bondage   -Oh, bondage...
Is he okay? Can he endure it?
It actually doesn't hurt, right?
Can he endure it?
You rigged it, so it doesn't hurt, right?
He probably loosened it
It doesn't hurt at all
That's very disappointing
This is just cunning
Why did you do this...   -It doesn't hurt at all
Not at all, I can't even feel it
So hard!
Hard?
What do you mean it's hard?
You mean it hurts?
It doesn't hurt, but it's hard?
What's so hard?
Not necessary to give cards for this though
Well, let's see how it goes
Maybe the candle isn't hot too, can we test it out on you, Shoji-san?
This is a court trial   -Yes
Tell us if it's hot   -This is a Sullivan (court trial)*
*Court trial (Sai-ban) and Sullivan have similar pronunciation
I wanted to say that too
Huh?
He said Ms Sullivan
He said court trial, then he said Sullivan, and I wanted to say that too
She's Helen Keller's teacher, right?
Is that even worth mentioning?
What's making you so excited?
I just wanted to tell you guys about this...
Let's do a Ms.Sullivan
Hey, hey, hey you
Leaving me alone like this...don't treat me like a lost child
No idea what you're talking about
Your skin look so old
You said I'm old?
You look slimmer
You idiot!
I'm a 63 years old in my prime, dude!
But you're supposed to retire at 65 though
But in terms of aby-lity...   -It's ability, please say it clearly
Are you ready?   -Yes
Is it hot or not?   -We can't tell if it's hot or not
We can't tell
Is it hot?
Shall we try one more time?
Is it hot or not?
No idea
We can't tell if you just say "eh"
I don't know either, because this half of my body is dead already
It's dead?
But it's moving a lot though
Then why did you ask him to do it on this side
You said it's dead, but...
But it somehow came back to life, and keeps moving
No need to say those lies
We still don't know if it's hot or not
It's definitely moving, right?
A fox...
Why a fox...
Let's stop this
His hands are shaking...
Let's shift our focus away from Shoji-san and Jimmy-san for now
Agreed   -You're right
So only this half of your body is dead?
It feels so good
It feels good?
Tomochika is so strong
Really strong
There's girls here too
No worries, I'm wearing something inside
It's a fishnet tight though
Fishnet tight...
It says "hole"
A hole
There's a lot of holes
You mean the holes of the fishnet tight?
Yeah, the holes of the fishnet
Or do you mean the hole of your...?   -Ass
That wasn't really interesting
We can clearly see your balls
That's no good, there's many girls here
I'll remove my makeup
Before that, we can clearly see your balls
Looking from the side...
-If you got sued for this, you're definitely gonna lose
-Yeah, in this day and age
If Haruna or Kurosawa sue you...
Did you put some coins inside?   -No, I didn't
How does testicles...
How does testicles look like?
You didn't see that?
Nope   -You never saw testicles before?
Nope
It's a round thing
How does it looks like?
Tell us how it looks like
Testicles?
What happened to your voice?
It's so husky
Husky testicle
So it's a hus-ticle
We're thinking the same thing   -Yeah
He's washing his face like an old man
You're wearing something inside
Are you okay?   -I'm fine
Why are you wearing this kind of cloth?
With stretch fabric...
But I love this kind of fabric too   -Oh, really?
That's how gangsters wear in private life
Only gangsters wear like that
That's you, idiot!
He's a gangster?
It's you
No way, it's not me   -It's you
Just look at what he's wearing
He's just being sporty
It's him
No way
Gangsters won't be here
Did you catch a cold?
A bit, my throat   -How come?
Well, it suddenly turned cold
There's so many people with husky voice today
Three people
I'm just having a nasal voice though
I'm having a nasal voice too
No, you're not
You're natural-born
You sound like you've drank some magma
Magma?
When I first met Norio-shisho
He said to me "did you eat sand for breakfast?"
Norio-shisho asked me "did you eat sand for breakfast?"
And he said "it's not something that you should put in your mouth!"
Norio-shisho?   -Norio-shisho
You two are close, huh?
Yeah, we are really close
Are you taking off your clothes?
You're belly is bulging in a good way
Because it's full of my gags
Oh, really? Please show us then
Just a little bit though   -Okay
We will learn a lot from that
Yeah, you're right
Lesson from a veteran
It's already his fourty...   -How long have you been a comedian?
My mic is...
You don't need that mantle, Jimmy-san
No...well...it's Shoji-san's turn now, so...
No worries, it's fine
That makes us curious
Actually...I...umm...want to have a deep talk with you guys
Eh? What's that? I want to watch that
No, it's not something to watch
He's balding in an unusual way
What do you mean?
You're right, it's strange   -Where?
You're balding in an unusual way
The front part of your head   -Oh, over here?
It took all our attention
You're balding in front too
Because I got an electric shock
In my head
You got an electric shock?   -Yeah
-Then you should end up having more hair, right?
-No...well...it's not that kind of electric shock
He sticked those electrode pads on my head
Then the doctor switched it on and I went like "ahh"
Shoji-san and Jimmy-san, why are you guys always telling lies that distress yourself afterwards
No, I'm lying, this is true, I really got an electric shock
Why did that happen then?
Please help Shoji-san wear the mic
What's that thing?
There's a hole   -Something is out...
Why only one side?
That shirt must be old
You're always wearing it?
It's really pinkish...
Of course, I don't hang out with girls
Let's guess if it's in the hole or not
So let's guess if it's in the hole or not
I'll be the dealer   -Okay
And we'll be betting
It's in
It's not in
It's not it   -It's not in
Oh, it's not in
Hooray!
It's not in
What about this time?
Wait a second...
Do you know if it's in or not, Shoji-san?
Please bet with us, Shoji-san
Am I Akina, dude?!
It should be Yukina (Fujimon's wife)
Akina is Hamaguchi-san's wife
You mixed them up
You changed my wife
It's Yukina
Come on, how could you get it wrong?
If he did it to Akina, that would be wicked
If Fujimon-san did it to Akina...   -That's a big issue
I'll be in big trouble for that, so...
Please say it properly
Please say it properly, Shoji-san
Am I Yukina, dude?!
Too late
Please help him wear the mic
It's dangling
Daigo is very close
I have to give him...
A yellow card next time...
It's stuck?
Do you think it's in the hole?
Well...let me think...
I'm not the goodwill ambassador of nipples, dude!
Please wait for a while
Please learn to wait
How long have you been a comedian? Please learn, Shoji-san
That one is definitely out
No way, that one should be safe
No, you completely laughed
I didn't laugh   -You clearly laughed
Matsumoto-san will make the decision
Maybe he'll see it differently
Well, to be honest, everyone is having a smiling face
I've been made aware of it
However...   -Look
In particular, Fujimon and Daigo is very close   -You're right
That being said...
I didn't see Shoji-san's face clearly
That should be safe   -No way
All I said was "ta-ha!"
So you said it!
Saying "ta-ha" is just a habit
Well, let's take a look
Let's take a look, Shoji-san   -It should be safe
I'm not the goodwill ambassador of nipples, dude!
Please wait for a while
Please learn to wait
How long have you been a comedian? Please learn, Shoji-san
He laughed at that one, right?
No, I didn't laugh
It's just "ta-ha"
Shoji-san...
Yellow card   -That one is out
But it's just yellow   -He said "ta-ha"
You clearly said "ta-ha"
Laughing out loud is not allowed
So it's not allowed to say "ta-ha"?
Yeah, please don't say it
Why would you want to say it?
Let's continue and good luck everyone
Thank you
Shoji-san knows the rules now