Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!
Has the entertainment world had a big change with the arrival of the Coronavirus or the new stay-home culture?
Well, I have been drinking and having interesting conversations with different celebrities about this.
Like "This and that happened the other day." or "This other thing happened at the stage.".
Just stuff like that.
I feel those types of discussions are lacking.
So time to chat?
Goto, please sit down.
And I'm sure all of them have
thought deeply about comedy individually.
So...
So I think their individual powers have been strengthened in these times.
Right...
-Whoa, Master Kiyoshi.
-Good morning.
Has he always had this body?
His pecs are amazing!
He must be working out.
Even though you're not talking!
This dude is not talking!
He's not talking!
Abareru you get the yellow card!
Damn it!
Bastard!
Is there "Re"?
So for "Re"...
I really love this one.
"Throw away the shrimp and take the soup."
He laughed so hard!
He's gagging!
Yellow! This is your last chance.
He got the name wrong.
I'm thirsty.
That's right, he doesn't remember Okuyama at all.
He doesn't.
I do not think so!
-Huh?
The size of his eyes is amazing.
I don't think so.
I mean, Momoi couldn't remember the name of the movie producer at all.
I mean, I'm also in the wrong there.
I don't think so.
You were calling her Okumura all the time.
We told you it's Okuyama but you kept saying Okumura.
I don't have those thoughts!
What is he saying?
He is wrong.
Huh? It's a goblin.
He's crazy.
-It's a goblin.
-What's his deal?
He's a crazy student.
-He closed it.
-He's been held back 80 times.
-He got held back 80 times.
-Right.
Failed student.
Maybe that person has a hint.
Here come the scientist.
That's great, you can do it because you're young.
Momoi always has it.
I want Momoi to go home.
Did he mistake Okui's name with Okuyama?
That's right.
-No, it was Okumura.
-Oh, Okumura...
Okuyama, right?
-Okuyama?
-Right, Okuyama.
Another experiment?
It's water.
You went for that one?
Huh? She stopped.
Huh?
She's gonna say something.
Solo travel in Mutsu province.
Stop that already.
Two.
That one again?
Did you go to Mutsu recently?
Hello Momoi.
You have pretty good lighting there.
It's the one I use to take photos.
Did you bring that yourself?
It was just there.
That's great.
-Getting good lighting like this is the most important thing for this type of job.
-It's super bright! and she talks with anyone.
That's how it is.
She's very sociable.
-Older celebrities all have lots of experience.
-It's the same for people in the service industry.
I would really love it if someone did some impersonations.
Shall I do some?
My heart is very big so...
Seiya how about you do it?
Would you like to see some of my impersonations?
-Of course!
-How about you do her?
Me?!
Yes.
-I impersonate her? May I?
-Or course, try it.
-Of course, you can do it.
-In front of the real person?
Ehm...
How come there's this many people?
Don't you think that wasn't bad?
Here comes Master Nikaku. (Editor's Note: 1)
His personality is a bit...
Who is he trying to imitate?
You know how you eat whenever you get hungry?
Yes.
Right.
Don't give me that, "I don't think so" crap.
But I do.
You're wrong.
-He's got his mouth taped so he can't speak.
-It's not the same guy.
It's not the same guy, it's a different one.
That's super scary.
This guy definitely eats humans.
He eats humans.
What's with him?
Amazing.
-So scary.
-That was so scary.
-Why would he do that?
-He's not saying a word.
What did he come here for?
Why is he here?
Going home?
Who are you?
Please tell us.
I'm Sasaki.
-Sasaki?
That's Soshina's actual surname.
-I mean, I am Sasaki.
-Hmm... Sasaki...
What's your name?
Suzuki.
Suzuki?
Are you Suzuki Sasaki then?
Do you have any hobbies?
Cycling.
That's so normal...
Yes.
Huh?
-I'm going.
-What'd he say?
He said "yes" and went back.
Yes?!
I'm going.
Could I try this thing I saw on the internet?
-Sure, sure.
-What is it?
-What's wrong?
-It's just something I saw.
You can apparently improve your reflexes with this.
You just have to put his tape-like stuff and your reflexes will get better. (EN: 2)
-Runners put it on their soles or on their Achilles heel.
-Right! I've seen that.
Below the ear as well.
You're going in the neck too?
-Could I borrow this for a moment?
-Sure.
The bamboo sword?
Just smack me and I'll stop it.
Me?
Alright, then Goto please do it.
I...
-Like catching a falling sword.
-Right.
I'm going, okay?
Yes, please go ahead.
Alright.
Come!
It was only the first one...
It was only the first one.
Too hard.
It's like...
-You went for the final strike.
-You're hitting him like it's the finals of a match.
That was a final strike.
I mean, I don't know sports...
Sorry.
Also, it's too fast.
Just try it a little slower.
-Slower?
-Don't know if I can do it.
-Just try it out.
-Like this?
-A bit faster. Just like that.
And you're too quick to pull it back. It was unfair.
You're too fast with the follow-up strike.
I see.
Go when I say so.
Go!
Not even close.
-I'm twitching.
-Your face is convulsing.
-Isn't he hitting him harder?
-Goto! He's convulsing!
-This is bad.
Oh my god, Goto! What did you do?
You damaged your underling's face.
Doing it with a pet bottle was hard but doing it with a bamboo sword is ridiculous.
But you told me to do it!
Why do you go like that when you're in pain?
Why do you convulse?
It's just stress. It's stress from the pain.
Whenever I'm in pain I go like this from the stress.
Are you alright?
Sorry, then please do it three times in a row.
-I see.
-Are you really fine?
-I'll match your timing.
-I just have to stop it once and that's it.
-You look really cool.
Here we go.
Go!
Go! Go!
Ouch! Ouch!
You should quit it.
Where are you going?
He's convulsing again.
Bang, bang.
-You had a pretty good rhythm going on there.
-It was like a gospel.
-It looked like your breaths had synced.
I think you can do it with the roles reversed.
-That was like a chorus.
-Oh, reverse?
You look at the first one and then you try to catch the second one.
-Right, let's try that.
-Yes, you look at the tempo first.
You give up on the first strike.
So you eat the first one and then you try to catch the rhythm.
Right.
-Eat the first one.
-Eat it.
Go!
-Three times?
-Yes.
Go!
4, 2, 3...
Tragic...
I might barf...
-You look like a weird Nabeatsu.
-I might barf. (EN: 3)
He's getting dizzy.
You have to grab it quickly.
-Oh, the Master...
-Can I borrow his power?-Sure.
Go ahead.
3 times?
Yes!
Come on Goto.
Goto won't do it.
I mean, I'm the underling now.
He's the big Master.
Now that he's got the mask on...
I can't be hitting the great Master, even if it's only a mask.
The Master's mouth today has been looking like one of those head shots you get.
3 times.
And eat the first one.
Go!
What are you doing?!
Quit it already!!
He's playing Master Kiyoshi properly now.
I don't mind killing you.
"I don't mind killing you"?
You can't.
Sorry.
That's scary.
I mean...
Isn't that Kubota?
Didn't he get a Medal of Honor? (EN: 4)
Try it.
What's gonna happen if Soshina hits the master?
You have to succeed or he'll get mad.
3 Times?
Here I go.
I'll just die!
I'll die.
What am I gonna do if I lose the 10 million and get my skull fractured?!
-Okay... Okay...
-What are you doing?
Okay!
A weird role?
I'm Kiyoshi Nishikawa!
That startled me.
-Huh?
Oh, it's that thing.
I'm Kiyoshi Nishikawa!
Master Kiyoshi?!
-Whoa that's scary!
-I'm Kiyoshi Nishikawa!
40 years later? 40 years later?
I'm Kiyoshi Nishikwa!
-Huh?
-Huh? Which one?
-That guy?
-Master Kiyoshi is making a lot of appearances today.
This is not Kiyoshi, is he?
-Is he not him?
-Who's this?
Who?
I'm Kaiou Kaku! (EN: 5)
-Kaiou Kaku?
-Oh, the one from Baki?
I'm Kaiou Kaku!
-Who is he?
-The Master from Baki?
I'm Kaiou Kaku. I mastered martial arts in China over 4000 years ago!
-Awesome.
-I'm Kaiou Kaku.
-Are you strong?
-He looks super strong.
-He's super strong.
The ultimate martial art does not require strength.
You will receive great injuries by one single strike.
-Right.
The ultimate weakness is the only thing that can neutralize all attacks.
That's right.
-A leaf won't be affected by my punch.
-Huh?
-Right, cause he's not trying.
So, now I will show you the ultimate weakness.
You're talking just like Sunshine.
I will do zero damage.
This is called "Shaolin".
So please hit me.
This is the guy from Baki, he also negates all damage.
Momoi can you hit him?
Actually, a strong person would be better.
-Then, let's go with Junior.
-Right, Junior.
-Yes, I haven't done this before.
That's true.
I...
-Junior, do it like in Baki.
Junior has been doing this for a long time.
What about Abareru?
I don't think so.
When did he say that?!
You have to time it.
His weakness is amazing.
Oh, his weakness?
-He's already weak.
-That's amazing.
-Won't it hurt?
I will take everything.
I can already tell, this guy's amazing.
He's a pro.
How hard should I go?
With everything.
-Huh?
-Junior, I'll do it for you.
-Junior's full force would be bad.
-I'll do it instead.
I mean if you really want to you can do it.
Alright, here I go.
-Can I go?
-Here I go.
Okay.
-Ready?
-Yes.
It didn't work at all.
Shaolin.
This is Shaolin.
Sure.
Ready? Ready?
-On the face?
-On the face?!
The face?!
Ready?
Here goes.
I'm going for the face.
Shaolin.
Huh?
-He's hurt.
-It didn't work.
-I mean, he said so himself...
-Abareru, you go.
It seems to me like it did affect him.
This is Shaolin.
Right?
Abareru, go for the face.
Whoa, it fell off.
That was dangerous.
-So unsafe!
Scary.
So scary!
This is scary.
-Scary.
-It's so scary.
-Why?
-Is he 130 years old?
This is what he looks like?
I think he is hurt.
We should do a bit more.
Just do it harder.
-I mean I hit him pretty hard just now.
-Right...
-But you didn't go full force.
-In the face?!
Are you okay with that?
Should be fine.
It's his "weakness".
Oh, he fell.
Is he alright?
-I don't think he's fine.
-Doesn't it hurt?
-It's hurting him.
So it doesn't hurt?
It has no effect, this is Shaolin.
Amazing.
Shaolin.
So are you just going home?
I won't.
Huh?
Soshina, what's up?
I thought he would say something funny.
I mean, it looked like he wanted to go home but couldn't because it was awkward.
-He should go home.
-It was nothing.
I mean, it's fine.
-Huh?
-Oh!
Year 3 Class B. (EN: 6)
I had warned my students of this...
But I took some drugs!
Who did the drugs?
Year 3 Class B.
Ehm... It must have been Shu.
Hello, I'm Kyosuke Himuro. (EN: 7)
-Oh, Himuro!
-Himuro!
-I'm here now! Everyone! Enjoy the party!
I will read the Tarot cards for you on this special occasion.
-Tarot?
-You can read the Tarot cards Himuro?!
-Let us hear you sing.
-Right!
I will read the Tarot cards.
Yes.
-Oh, huge cards.
-I'll read the Tarot cards for you.
Whoa.
What would you like me to read?
I would like to know about work.
So you want me to tell you about your work?
Alright, pick a card.
-Alright then, Soshina, go ahead.
-Take your pick.
Then... This one.
This one?
This one!
Hotei has turned into a skeleton.
(EN: 8)
You will wear shoes full of mud next year.
Thank you.
-Hotei also comes up!
-You will wear mud filled shoes.
Ask about anything you want.
-Alright then, let's go with love.
-Love?
Alright, love.
This one.
Oh, this one!
-Oh, I did it!
-Hotei is...
-Oh, this is love related.
-Hotei is flirting with Kumiko Yamashita.
-Kumiko Yamashita?
-Yes, he's flirting with Kumiko Yamashita.
You are racing along the Mevius Highway...
You'll fall in love.
You will fall in love.
-You will fall in love.
-Isn't that good?
You will fall in love.
You go.
Me?
Then, I choose health.
-Health?
-Yes.
You will die!!
I'll die?
He'll die? But it looks like such a nice card.
It looks really good.
Judgment.
Are you okay?
It's like the one I pulled.
-Sorry, could you do Momoi?
-Oh, sure.
You're spitting a lot so be careful.
I don't like these kinds of things.
-Pick a card.
-I don't want to die though...
What are you asking?
-What is it?
-Ehm...
Acting?
Acting...
-That's fine.
-Well, it's all work-related.
Oh, this one...
Hotei is upside down in this one.
You will go crazy after the Honky Tonky.
What does that mean?
You...
You will be popular.
I'm so glad.
But she's already super popular...
-She's selling really well.
-She's already a star.
-She will be popular.
I hope I get that acting luck.
Hold on, who are you?
I'm Kinpachi, the drug addict.
Oh, right.
Hold on.
What would you like me to read?
-How will my pancreas turn out?
-Alright, good!
Pancreas?
Here I go!
Is he worried about his pancreas?
He must be.
alright!
Huh?
Hotei is fighting with a lion in summer.
You will die.
Oh no, he'll die.
How about you read your own future?
Of course, I can do that as well.
Ehm... Let's see...
Let's see how my next album will do.
-How will my album do?
-Sure.
Alright, I'll read the cards.
-Huh?
-What?
I will die... overseas.
Die?
There's tons of death.
Everything is death.
Everything...
Everything will die.
There's one card left though...
Can I go then?
Oh, go ahead.
-Please pick a card.
-Alright.
What would you like to see?
Then... About my big brother.
-Your brother?
-Yes.
-Here we go.
-Okay.
Complex.
This a complex.
Amazing.
Complex has turned up.
This is good.
Oh, it's good!
What does it mean?
Seiji will die next year.
Die?
-Everyone dies.
-Why is everyone dying?!
-That's such a bad omen.
-That's too soon.
-This fortune reader is so tasteless.
-I thought he'd give us good news.
What's Master Seiji's cause of death?
-Master Seiji?
-Why do they call him Master Seiji?
He's not a Master yet.
What's Master Seiji's cause of death?
Necrosis.
-Necrosis?! He'll rot to death?
-Necrosis.
Master Seiji?
Seiji...
Will he be alright?
-What's wrong?!
Are you okay?
This guy again.
He's back.
It looks like he entered my body.
-You liar!
-He infiltrated him.
He's in my body.
What's that?
What is this collage-looking thing?
It's super scary.
It's a monster.
A monster.
He came into your body...
And he's controlling you.
-He's possessing you!
-Oh no! Oh no!
This guy is scary.
Y-You can punch me.
You too?
You can punch me!
-There's a lot of punching today.
You can punch my face!!
You too?
Please drive it out!
Should I volunteer for this?
-What's with this?
-Should I volunteer for this?
-Please go ahead.
Is there a point to this?
Drive it out!
Alright, I will.
Where?
Around here.
That's your body though... Is that okay?
-So she's killing it, right?
-Right
Go ahead.
Get out of this person!
-Go, go, go.
-Go.
Harder! Harder!
Get out of this person!
-You have to drive it out.
Harder! Harder!
-Get out!
-Harder!
-Go!!
-Get out!
-Harder!
-So long...
-Get out!
-Harder!
-It's so long... Super long.
-Get out!
-Harder!
-Thanks!
No one's laughing.
I can't believe no one laughed after that.
They won't laugh.
Of course.
Oh, hello... I will be doing some ventriloquism.
Ventriloquism?
Yes.
I've been doing shows all over the country.
-What is that?
-This is Mr. Penis.
-Nice to meet you.
-Mr. Penis?
That person over there, please pay attention.
Mr. Penis?
Yes, Mr. Penis will answer your questions, no matter what you ask.
-Alright, please ask a question.
-Where did you come from?
From North Kyushu.
-Huh?
-A penis from North Kyushu...
I came from North Kyushu.
How old are you?
-Huh?
-How old are you?
How old? How old do you think I am?
I mean, it looks pretty clean... So maybe it's in its teens?
What did you say?
-You're pretty clean so...
-I'm so happy.
Huh?
It made a sound.
Like a hissing sound.
Will something come out if we praise it?
Are there any other questions?
What kind of girls do you like?
-I love every girl.
I love her.
-Thank you.
It's making that sound but nothing is coming out.
It's such a failure.
He's doing something.
-What's happening?
-What's going on?
-Is there any other questions?
-Ehm...
What is written on your shirt?
It's Patagonia.
Nothing is coming out.
It's dripping down your elbow.
I'm sorry.
I get all sweaty when I'm nervous.
Disgusting.
Life never goes as you'd expect...
Does it?
What are you looking at?
What is your name?
I'm Kyosuke Himuro.
Huh? What's that?
I bet the hole is off center.
Can I look at the opening part?
Please do it.
Huh?
Here comes another one.
Who are you?
Eat the bread!
Huh?
Oh, he said, "eat the bread".
Poor thing.
Oh, here it goes.
Oh, he's doing it.
Eat the bread!
Poor thing.
-That's so sad.
-Yeah, that's sad.
It's so big too.
The crown, I mean.
He must hate bread.
Eat it...
Soshina, you should give him some mandarin.
Is a mandarin any better?
-Thank you, thank you.
-Here's a mandarin.
It's a mandarin.
Here comes the mandarin.
Oh, he's going for it.
-He's going for it.
-Juice is coming out.
Eat the mandarin!!
That makes a pretty loud sound.
That's true.
That's kinda scary.
-Eat the mandarin...
-Is he an idiot?
-Does he not get what a mandarin is?
-It hurts...
-Maybe it's too hard.
Himuro...
It's a hard one.
Himuro, it's looking at you.
It's going to Himuro.
No, no.
This guy is a star! He's a star!
Don't do it! No!
Eat Himuro!!
Image down.
-Image down...
-But the image is not down.
-Right, not at all...
Huh? Isn't he looking at Momoi now?
Oh no, it's looking at Momoi now.
Oh no.
No! Stop it!
Don't eat Momoi!
She's a star!
That hurts!
Ouch!
Ouch, it hurts!
Stop!
I'm telling you, no!
Don't you know how to hold back?
That's true.
Now that I think about it...
It was super loud.
-It was super painful.
-It must have been.
You held back when you pecked yourself but not with me?
SK-II. (EN: 9)
That's the wrong way of saying SK-II.
-What part is she getting mad at?
-How do you say it?
For a clear skin, SK-II.
-Oh no, he's acting like a boy again.
He just completely hid behind the chair.
He did!
You laughed!
I heard you chuckling.
-You definitely had a smile.
-Huh? Who was it?
Huh?
Oh, isn't this pretty bad?
-Of course it was Seiya.
-Whoa! Hold on!
But we couldn't really see it from this side.
-He was hiding it.
-But some of these cameras must have caught it.
But you knew you were laughing, right?
I mean, I held it back with my nose.
-It wasn't like a full out laugh.
-No way.
-No way, no way.
Momoi, I'm sorry.
-It hurt so much.
-Poor Momoi.
The sound it made was so loud. It was hilarious.
You held back when you pecked yourself but not with me?
SK-II.
That's the wrong way of saying SK-II.
-What part is she getting mad at?
-How do you say it?
For a clear skin, SK-II.
-Oh no, he's acting like a boy again.
It was his nose.
For a clear nose, SK-II.
He laughed with his nose.
I don't know about this one... It got away from me.
-I will leave it to everyone's judgment.
-Oh, it got away.
I really only did that with my nose.
-My face was like this.
-But did you find it funny?
Not at all.
Hey!
But you were laughing.
It felt like I was studying in a library.
-I mean, you're immediately out if you smile even a little bit next time.
-I'm sorry!
I'm sorry everyone, you can take me out if I falter even a little bit next time.
-He's safe for now.
-I'm sorry.
-Alright, he's in orange.
Just tell me again if you found it funny or not.
I really didn't.
-Why?
-Why are you asking again?
He was pretending to do it.
This must have hurt.
-It really hurt.
-It's super painful.
Ouch!
-This must hurt.
-Of course.
This definitely hurts.
Seiya really doesn't know how to hold back.
I'm so sorry Momoi.
-And she's like a veteran, senior woman celebrity...
-You should really quit it.
What kind of stuff are you pulling here?
Please give me an insurance card.
Aren't you listening?
I'm asking you, what are you trying to pull here?
Please give me a certificate of residence.
Look...
-Huh?
Huh?
A scary person has entered.
-Good morning.
-Junji?
It's the Master. (EN: 10)
Hello.
Good morning.
Aaaa, it's that thing.
-Huh?
-What?
I came on a summer night.
-Huh?
-The taxi...
-Is that Junji Inagawa?
-Oh, a taxi came in the night.
The taxi came and the woman smoothly raised her hand up.
-So it's a ghost story.
-It came slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly...
And she had a bad feeling, she didn't like it.
-I can't understand most of it.
So a taxi came and there was something there.
So I thought, "What is that? I don't like it".
But it came slowly, slowly, slowly, towards me!
That's what I thought.
And that thing...
What does it mean?
Her accent is amazing.
And the thing stopped right in front of me.
-Huh?
-Is she targeting me?
And it came slowly towards me.
-Her voice feels ready for the punchline.
-And I was like, "What? That is weird.".
-That was...
-She's still doing that voice.
I thought that was weird.
-Weird...
-And maybe it was...
This kind of face.
-It was a duck face.
-A duck face.
-That was cute.
-Not scary at all.
-She was playing a cute girl.
That was great.
Yes, like this.
-It was like you were splitting something up.
That's right.
It was just a meeting.
-That's what I thought.
It was a normal meeting for Soshina.
We just met.
The fact that Abareru thinks this is funny is hilarious to me.
Right?
Huh?
It's a goblin.
-Excuse me...
-Three eyed, goblin...
He's turned into Hiei. (EN: 11)
Do you have any other shapes for sunglasses?
A different shape?
Oh, he needs three lenses.
I have a dry eye.
My eye is dry.
For his third eye!
-I have a dry eye.
-It's Mitsume Kozou.
-He's missing one lens. (EN: 12)
Do you know where they might sell it?
Not really...
I've never seen anything like it.
So not here?
-There isn't.
-Where should I go then?
-I really haven't seen anything like it.
-But it has to be in the city.
You should stretch out your legs, it's important.
-Why are you trying to look for a store close-by?
-A nearby place...
-If possible... Within west Tokyo.
-Just go to the suburbs.
Is it because he stands out?
West Tokyo?
-West Tokyo?
-Yes, I live in west Tokyo.
That's far.
-West Tokyo...
-And in the city...
Anyways, I haven't seen anything like it.
Sorry, I'll come back again.
He's got such a bland character for a three-eyed brat.
Huh?
-Are you looking at me?
-He's right, what a bland character.
Everyone is looking at you right now.
-Can't you see us?
-Everyone's looking at you, Abareru.
Alright!
That startled me.
-Me too.
-Let's play a game.
Oh!
The continuation?
Let's play a game.
Let's!
Let's do it!
Just drop them...
This guy's games take too long.
The last one was a hit.
So we have 3 more left.
-Are there three more?!
-Which one is good?
We'll do "Exploding Ice Gag Battle"
Both parties will take off their tops.
Each one will take an ice rock.
And they will start screaming gags at each other while they melt the ice on top of their nipples.
What?
And...
You lose if you can't bear it any longer and step away.
Or the one that laughs first loses.
They won't laugh.
-And the one that steps away...
I mean you don't have to explain that the loser is the one that laughs.
That's the point of this show.
-Is this guy an idiot?
-That's just this show's rule...
-I mean, you laugh, you lose.
-This guy is an idiot.
-So, furthermore!!
-You'll lose if you laugh, that's obvious.
So the person that steps away after doing this...
Has to scream out the name of the hot food he or she wants to eat the most.
-You're always adding those weird rules...
-I love food.
-This is the "Exploding Ice Student".
-Huh?
-What?
-Are you out of breath?
-Huh?! What?!
-He's pissed.
-You just said "Ice Student".
Explain to me what he just said.
-What's wrong?
-What's the matter?
That's "Exploding Ice Gag Battle"
I mean, have no idea what the rules are.
So you have to melt the ice?
The one that melts it first wins.
The first one is the winner.
-Please aim for that.
-So you melt it on the other person.
Yes, you melt it on your opponent's nipple.
Now let's move on.
Huh? So that was the explanation?!
-I see, so you're explaining each one.
-I want you guys to pick. Though I would love to do every single one...
-Let's just hear everything out.
-I mean, let's hurry up and play.
-I mean, we saw this one already.
Then let's do it.
-The explanations take too long.
-Alright! Let's go!
-Let's do the "Ice Gag Battle".
-It's really hard to understand.
-We have to see it first.
-Are you doing it alone?
I will battle someone in a trial match.
Isn't he perfect?
-You're already naked.
-I see.
And you also have lots of gags.
Is that okay?
I mean, Goto hasn't done much today.
I did the popcorn thing.
It was super hot.
-You haven't done anything today.
-Didn't you see my balls?
But you haven't moved at all today.
I mean, I had my balls out.
Didn't you look at them?
Which one of my balls was out?
The right one.
Then you did see it.
-Let's go.
-Alright, let's try it out.
I really have no clue what we're doing.
In the end I didn't understand the rules.
-It's huge.
-It really is.
Alright, let's go with this one.
It's in close quarters.
-Sorry, can I hear the rules again?
-When should they start shouting the gags?
While we are both melting the ice on each other's nipples.
-We'll both start shouting out gags.
-At each other?
Yes.
And the one that melts it first is the winner.
It's super long.
It's cold so the person that steps away first has to scream out the name of the hot food they want to eat.
So can you come back if you scream the name of the food?
No, you lose.
So you shout the name of the food and you still lose?
There's no point in screaming then.
That's just the game.
Huh?
Is that where you get excited?
By screaming out names of hot food?
I don't get it.
-But Seiya has strong nipples.
-But I'm pretty tired today.
-This guy is an idiot.
-Set...
-Huh? Set?
-What?
-Alright.
-Set.
Closer.
Yes.
That's good.
-That's too close.
-Ready?
Put it on.
It's super cold!
Cold!
Ready.... Start!
Yay! Yay! Gag!
Balloon! Yay! Yay! Yay! Yeah!
A job where you touch electricity.
Sizzle, sizzle, sizzle, shoulder Yakisoba.
Gachon!
They're not human anymore.
Take that!
Boom! Pow! Contact!
-Aiiin!
-Here it is.
-I only have one gag.
-He's out of gags.
-Super Aiiin!
-Nabeyaki Udon!!
He lost.
That's good.
He named a hot food.
Was anyone excited about me shouting "Nabeyaki Udon"?
I just thought he lost...
-I don't have any gags, this is hell for me.
-Anything is a gag.
You can take someone else's gags.
They were doing it after the second one.
You can't think of gags with ice on your nipple.
You'll shout the hot food again?
Alright then, let's change it to the name of the place of your first kiss.
So I have to yell the name of the place where I had my first kiss?
Yes, you scream it.
-If you're at your limit you scream the name of the place.
Where was I?
Ready... Start!
Okay.
Whoa.
Crack! Swirl! Swirl! Crack! Peanut!
-His face is convulsing a lot.
-He must be pretty stressed.
I-I... can no longer be in this unit.
That was the lawyer Yokoyama. (EN: 13)
Who's gag is that?
It's not a gag.
Motivation switch: on! Boom! Psssh! Calpis!
(Jp Drink)
Good.
What? I told you I'm in the wrong.
-Who?
-Who's that?
It's Kenshiro Matsunami, when he threw the water. (EN: 14)
-That's not a gag!
-I don't have any gags.
A gag! Pop! Bang! Nipples!
This is like a children's show.
OhaSuta.
(Variety Show for Children)
Children would love this game.
What happens now?
Safe!
-Safe?
Such loose rules.
-Is that really safe?
-He really hasn't set any rules.
-Next up is Kubota.
-Come on!
-What should I do?
Gag... Gag...
Come on! You can do it!
I'm sorry, please let me go now.
What's that?
Well in my village those who didn't work would have to pay with their eye.
That's the gag.
-Good!
-That's scary.
-That's so scary.
-It's not a gag.
Crack! Pop! I drank elbow water! Delicious!
Shut up! Take this you idiot!
-Whoa, what happened?!
-What? What? What?
I messed up and it came out the other way.
I messed up.
-Huh? What?
-It came out the other way.
I messed up and it came to me.
-That's the worst.
-Awesome.
Must've hurt...
He's failing at everything.
Kubota is really messing everything up.
So that means he lost?
He won?
He didn't say the place of his first kiss so he lost.
The first place?
The place of his first kiss.
I mean I can say it.
Even if you do, you still lose.
Is it too late?
I mean, you can try saying it.
The changing room at Uniqlo!
Such bad manners.
Your first kiss?
-What?!
-Good for you!
That's weird.
What about you, Goto?
-I...
-Say it out loud.
Out loud!
Next to Suma's aquarium!
-Next to?
-Outside?
-At the beach.
Oh, so while looking at the sea.
Junior, what about you?
Aggression!
Next to Morinomiya station!
-Next to? It's the "next to" series.
-See! Outside!
-But there's tons of cars passing by.
-Next to...
There's tons of cars there.
Momoi, what about you?
Bar's toilet!
That's so gaudy. I see...
They must have taken her there.
-A bar's toilet...
-That's pretty rare...
Did he say anything after the kiss?
I don't remember what I said but outside...
He yelled, "Masayo we're going home!".
That's my real name.
Oh, your real name.
What kind of work did he do?
I think he started working straight after high school.
-That's pretty normal.
-Was he like a construction guy?
-What's with that way of asking?
-He may have done some of that work.
I mean, everyone does some kind of work.
-Shall we move on to the next game?
-Huh?
-Are we doing another one?!
-What?
Is there more?
-We still have time.
-There's 2 more left.
Then explain the rules first.
These seem to be very different.
Oh, the "I want to smell my dad's fart" game?
Well...
The player will make this pose.
Right.
And we will put a whoopee cushion here.
Then the other person will grab an ab roller.
This.
And because you want to smell your dad's fart...
You go like this.
And try to activate the whoopee cushion.
And you have to yell your father's name if it makes a sound.
In my case I would yell Katsuo.
"Katsuo, thank you!"
Like that.
And the person on the floor also has to yell something out.
That's the game.
-That's so complicated.
-What was that?
-I didn't get any of that.
-I'm clueless.
-Let's drop it.
-I don't get it.
Look at Abareru's face.
Of course you would make that face.
The player wants to smell the fart!
-Right, right, I get that.
-You're father's fart, right?
So you go like this, right?
Your dad is opening up his legs and you go in to press the whoopee cushion.
Then you're happy, so you yell your father's name.
"Katsuo, thank you!"
Then your dad has to scream something back to you.
That's the game.
-That's so random.
-But what do you shout?
Is there a winner in this?
No, it's just that kind of game.
-We can decide what to shout.
-It's like I'm in a dream.
This is too much work.
But we can shout the same things as the last game.
This guy is pissing me off.
It can be anything.
Out!
I think!
I think there is!
Kimura is here.
They must have added random sounds here.
That's right, there were different sounds before.
They completely ignored Ikezaki's game.
Cha!
Nishio! It's Sumiko!
-It's Nishio and Sumiko.
-It's Kiyoshi Nishikawa.
-These are not gags.
-These aren't gags.
Matsumoto sure makes weird stuff.
It wasn't me though...
1 and a half hours...
-I actually made a movie. Would you like to watch it?
-Sure let's see it.
It's like a game...
I wanna see.
-A game?
-It's like...
-Making a game is pretty hard.
-That's amazing.
-I tried making something.
Is it a game?
It's more of a playful video.
-A playful video?
I see.
So it's not a video game per se, right?
I just want you to feel like you're playing the game.
-CR?
-It's like in Pachinko.
-You love Pachinko, don't you.
-I do.
-So it's always been my dream...
-That's too close.
Too close.
-Here we go. It's starting.
-CR Oniyakko Tsubaki.
-Here we go.
It's a spinning one.
That hand-made style is so cute.
It's like a flip book.
Please hit it big.
-Big fail.
-Huh?
-There's a line.
-Don't cry, aren't you a man?
"Ki Ki Ki Ki Ki Ki"
Oh, it has great performances.
"I'm coming! The enemy is at Charles de Gaulle Airport!"
"You can only talk after you have defeated this Furoshiki wrapped Tsubaki."
-Oh, it's a reach?
-Maybe...
It's a fake out!
Alright!
I'm coming! The enemy is at Charles de Gaulle Airport!
-It's hot, so hot!
-"Three time you have given me the box of cakes. My heart is dancing. I shall grant you the final secret techniques."
-"It's been a while since I last had a Chicken skewer!"
-The performance is amazing!
Once more!
-"I'm coming! The enemy is at Charles de Gaulle Airport!"
-Here it comes!
-"Three time you have given me the box of cakes. My heart is dancing. I shall grant you the final secret techniques."
-"It's been a while since I last had a Chicken skewer!"
"It's so delicious today as well! So hot!"
-"Three time you have given me the box of cakes. My heart is dancing. I shall grant you the final secret techniques."
-"It's been a while since I last had a Chicken skewer!"
"It's so delicious today as well! So hot!"
-She just said, "so hot".
-Is it hot?
Ah! A freeze!
-Here it comes!
-"The recording of this 26th episode was made in April, on a totally normal day."
-Is it here?
-Ah, she's saying it!
We're hitting the jackpot.
-Here it comes.
-This is it.
-It's her husband.
-Amazing sequences. Huh?
-This was filmed on the fly.
Clinking?
Candid filming is so cool.
It is.
That's true.
He's dropping them in.
-Everything is related.
-So we'll hit the jackpot if this hits?
I wonder...
After all, this was all made on the spot.
His face...
This sequence is kinda scary.
So long!
-There's a lot of time with nothing.
-Right?
-Amazing.
Wasn't this the "hot" section?
He did say that before.
Listening to this for a long time might hurt.
-It's so long.
-So long.
-Oh, here it comes.
-He it comes.
No way.
-Huh?
-What happened?
Something happened.
Huh? He was filming from above?
-What's that?
So we got it?
He's laughing really hard.
He's gonna show us!
Here it comes!
Show us!
Here it is! Here it is!
They're making us wait.
Dai is laughing already.
Show us! Show us! Show us!
-Show us!
-This is so long.
We already saw this.
They're teasing us too much.
-All matching!
It's a big win!
"Big win! Congratulations!"
"You did it!"
"I knew it!"
"Let's keep going!"
"Brother, I know you could do it."
It's changing! It's changing!
-It was so long!
"-Congratulations!"
"Demon Rush!"
"Enter!"
"Aim for the right."
What's this?
It's a big win
-Are you singing this yourself?
-That right.
This is a home run.
Oh, we got it.
This is a different one.
It's so intricate.
Aho Mild Kuni.
"Takai 5 Carats."
Don't write the lyrics with three people.
He's riding a unicorn.
Unicorn.
Kouhei Doshima?
-That's right.
-That's amazing!
Tons of people were involved in this.
-This is the real deal, isn't it?
-That's right.
I see...
So cute.
It's so cute.
-What round is this?
-It's kinda nice.
This looks like it'll become popular.
It's so long.
What's this?
Mukai from Tenshin as well?
-Mukai as well?
-He helped with the story.
Ehm...
With the composition?
-It comes up in the story.
-Oh, there's a story?
This is for another Anime.
-What are we looking at?
Right, I have no idea.
-Pachinko?
-It's only about 13.
Oh, it's two people now.
Oh, are you singing this as well?
-Yes, yes.
-Yes, I'm singing here.
I told you.
Pay attention.
[To be continued.]
-Huh?
To be continued?!
Are there pending episodes?
-It was so random.
-What's that round thing?
-So random.
-Isn't the round thing the jackpot?
I didn't really get it but that was long.
You're right, it was long.
I mean, they tend to be long lately.
The one with the husband was super long.
Huh?
-Huh?
-It stopped.
-Hold on.
Is there more?
-Huh?
-Is there more?
That's all.
-No way.
Huh?
You laughed at your own joke!
Oh my god.
You've gotta be kidding!
I held it in!
That was close!!
-I was so close!
-That was scary!
So close!!
I was so shocked.
What was that just now?
-What was it?
-What was that?
-So scary!
-Why did you laugh?
I pulled through.
You looked so happy.
-Everyone was making such a big fuss...
-Of course.
Of course we would, it was so long!
I already knew there was nothing else once the ending song kicked in.
What?!
I mean, let's look at the replay.
I'm sorry, I can't...
Why would you play the ending?
Huh? Hold on.
Huh? What?
Is that it?
-That was it.
-No way.
She just laughed.
You laughed at your own joke!
It's fine, it's just her first time.
-Yellow for you.
-I'm sorry.
Alright everyone, it's about time.
-Are we getting the 20 million?
-Whoa, it's pretty tight this time around!
Ehm... 20 million!
Alright!!
Just one hour left!
Let's go!
-It's such a close battle.
-I've got to go to the bathroom.
Me too.
This is a great battle.
It's gonna be crazy.
Alright, let's go.
-Excuse me!
-Huh? What's wrong?
I actually prepared some footage myself.
I made a game.
-Which one?
-Could we watch it all together?
-Which is it?
-It's a game.
-Footage?
-Alright, please take a seat.
Where are we watching it?
-Se... Soshina over here.
-Se?
I just messed it up a bit!
One time is fine!
Don't get all riled up!
You wouldn't want me to call you Ishio, would you?
You can call me Iwao. (EN: 15)
Why would you call me Ishio?
Why would you take that Kanji?
It would be, Iwao, not Ishio.
I would be shocked if you called me Iwao.
-So stop it.
-Are you guys alright? You shouldn't fight like this.
Huh? Oh, sorry about that.
Shall we play the game?
-Sure.
-Let's keep it light and friendly.
Why did you choose that name, Soshina? (EN: 16)
Me?
How did you come up with it?
You should turn it off.
-This is bad.
-Oh no.
Are you leaving?
We just saw everything...
-Ehm...
What's up with Goto?
I wanted to start comedy as a humble man, so it was my way of saying, "I'm just a normal man, but please take care of me".
That's why I chose Soshina.
Were there any other names?
Gagagigo or something like that.
Whoa, that's crazy.
What does that mean?
It's...
-It's a monster's name. It's a character from my generation.
Or also Soccer.
-Soccer?
-Soccer...
-That's amazing.
-Your favorite sport?
-Aikata Soccer.
-That's amazing. (EN: 17)
-Aikata Soccer...
-Where are you going?
-Hold on.
-So you might have named it Seiya and Soccer?
-That's right.
-From your name Myoujou Shimofuri?
That's right.
-So you didn't know Seiya yet?
-Soccer would have been amazing.
He was already Soshina when I met him in high school.
-You met him back then?
Soccer would have been amazing.
Were there any other names?
Is that all?
-Not right now...
-What's wrong? What's wrong?
Not now.
Huh? Is that a third person?
Mitsudomoe? (EN: 18)
That's good.
Let's do a little bit of gaming.
-No one can beat that high score.
-This guy looks pretty strong.
-Round one.
-900 million?
-Fight.
-The high score is 900 million.
-Is it Abareru vs Bozu?
-Abareru vs Bozu.
Bozu...
-Bozu?
-He's pretty strong.
-You can do it.
-His kicks are pretty effective.
-That's amazing.
-Oh, a low kick.
The low kick keeps coming.
Headbutt!
Oh, he's been caught.
He's getting beat.
He's caught.
Where are they fighting?
He's gonna lose, he's about to lose.
Abareru!
-Oh no, oh no.
-That's bad.
-Oh no.
-It's over.
He lost.
He lost properly.
You lose.
-Oh, Bozu won.
-So strong!
-Round 2.
So strong!
-Fight.
-Hold on, let's see what happens.
It's bad.
He's doing some damage.
He can do it.
Oh, make sure he doesn't grab your head.
-Oh, he's learned his lesson.
-Go, go, go!
Good, good, you can do it.
What is that?
Huh? I can't see it.
What's that?
He inhaled it.
A smell?
He's brought out a smell.
-He's losing HP!
-Hold on!
He's losing HP.
-What's that?
-What is he smelling?
Oh no, oh no, oh no...
That's a crazy color.
So weak.
-"You lose!."
-Bozu must be really strong.
Oh, continue.
-Continue.
It's the uninhabited island photo.
-What should I do?
-We need some coins.
We need some coins.
It's from that time he got bit by a mosquito.
-When the mosquito bit him.
-We lost because there's no coins.
Oh, it's impossible without coins.
Coins...
-I didn't bring any with me.
-That last face is that one, isn't it?
-Do we need coins?
-Huh? Is that it?
-Is that it?
Fight!
Huh?
Here it is.
-Again?
-You can still play?
Here we go again.
Oh, he's pretty strong.
But Abareru is way bigger...
-Low kick?
-Is this another reach?
You should do more low kicks.
You shouldn't get caught again.
Again... Run away.
This is bad.
He's got you again.
Can't he somehow get out of this?
How many times is this gonna play?
Whoa, he got screwed again.
You have to strike back or you're done for.
See, he's destroying you.
This is such a boring game if you can lose like this.
Losing like this is so unpleasant.
Abareru, you lose instantly.
-I lose if I get caught.
-Can't you get away from it?
If you get caught and they spam 'Y' it's over.
It's a new game.
But there are only 2 characters.
I mean, try not to get caught.
Is he gonna make you smell that thing again?
You can do it! You can do it!
-Go!
-What if you step back?
-Step back.
-Push it away.
-He's smelling it.
-This is the same thing.
-Push it away.
-We just saw this. We saw this already.
We saw it already.
Is there something else?
Maybe after this?
Is there something after this?
-I'll try running away.
-Run, run.
No way.
-Damn it!
-Run away!
Why did you show it twice?
Is there something else?
He just showed it to us twice.
Coins, coins.
-Coins!
-Someone, coins!
-Coins! Coins! Coins!
We don't have any!!
-Someone, coins!
-Coins! Coins! Coins!
We don't have any!!
No coins.
We don't have coins.
-The opponent's level was too high for me.
The computer?
-It was the same match twice.
-Who were you playing against?
-It was online.
-Online?
-Yeah.
Were you fighting against someone?
I mean, it was the same fight twice!
It was online, so...
-It was someone overseas.
-Where?
The U.S.
Such a simple answer...
-Oniyakko, may I do a bit of an exam on you.
-He doesn't play the Boke much in those situations.
-An exam?
Yes.
Me?
Is that like a metal detector?
Oh no...
You have metal there.
She doesn't have any.
-But it just made a sound.
-What? What?
It makes a sound when there is no metal.
-So there's no metal?
-No metal!
No abnormalities!
Abnormalities found!
-Huh?
What do you mean?
There was something in the crotch area.
You have something in your crotch, don't you?
What does she have?
What is in there?
-Huh?
-It's a crotch diary. (EN: 19)
Huh?
-A crotch diary.
-No way.
-Do you know what she's talking about?
I do have it.
Huh?
How about you try it with Kubota?
He's also got something.
-You do?
-All done.
-He has?
-What do you have?
In your crotch...
You have a crotch shark. (EN: 20)
Like a sharksucker?
I don't have such things.
Try it with Junior.
How about Junior?
I don't think there's anything there.
The sound is different.
What does that mean?
What's it mean?
It's so long.
For real.
So long.
What does it mean?
-Huh? Which is it?
-What is it?
Does it mean there's something there?
-What's in there?
-Something's in there.
Here...
We have a My Number Card. (ENL 21)
Why?
It went off by itself.
She's examining her own body.
Exam?
How about you do it on yourself?
Sure.
Huh?
She laughed...
So scary! So scary! I'm scared!
I'm sorry.
What happened?
Alright!
-Kuwata...
-Was that my lucky strike?! (EN: 22)
Why?
-Was it Kuwata?
It was Kuwata's face.
Kuwata's face? It's her counter!!
-But why?
-She was laughing so hard.
It was uncontrollable laughter.
It looked like he was holding back a laugh.
It looked like he was doing a Kuwata impersonation and that made me crack up.
You thought he was setting you up.
How about you do it on yourself?
-He's really holding back.
-It's true.
Are you holding it in here?
-He's doing it a little bit.
-It's really Masumi Kuwata.
He's really doing it.
That's just Abareru's face.
She laughed so hard.
That's my normal face!
You laughed at my resting face.
It's just his normal face.
-Right?
-It's just a normal face!
He looks like he's holding back a laugh.
I was holding back a laugh.
-This point goes to Abareru.
-Alright!!
I'm her counter!
-Yellow.
-That's right.
Let's go!!
But this is amazing in itself.
No one has dropped out yet.
Alright!!!
That's amazing.
We'll go for the 20 million.
It's the power of the 20 million.
Lick, lick, punch!
Are you talking about Krillin?!