(Editor's Note: After some research, I found that "Dondake" can actually mean "how much?!", "how many?!" or "'til when?!"; It can also be used as onomatopoeia)
Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!
Jokes in general
have been changing lately, right?
They sure have been changing.
Of course.
Nowadays people are more sensitive,
and many want more seriousness.
Hello there!
— Mikitty!
— How much?!
Chance is pretty bad news.
Yes, it is.
This is bad!
In that sense, this show is
some kind of resistence.
For real?!
If you think I'm lying,
just take a look at Sandwichman's offer,
at least once.
I don't think he'll show up ever again.
That makes sense.
I wouldn't go on this show either, to be honest.
You can't do this, Fujimoto.
I can!
— Mikitty!
— How much?!
— Mikitty, Mikitty!
— Shoulder throw!
— Mikitty!
— How much?!
All things considered,
you just get a yellow for now.
This is a yellow!
Alright!
Now we're getting into it!
Yeah, you're right, you're right.
With this, huh?
— It's getting tighter.
— What was that?
No one should laugh at something like this.
Alright, here we go.
What were you trying to do, Fujita?
Well, getting ready...
I was thinking of getting ready for dinner.
—Wanna give something a try?
—Ah? Sure.
Sure, something. Alright.
Ah, that's right. You're older than Kobayashi, right?
He's older.
When I met him he was a few years above me
Kobayashi, you...
How annoying.
We're in the same generation.
Yeah, I know.
But I thought he was in my same generation, too.
Sorry to bother you.
Everyone.
Ah, something's here.
—Woah, awesome!
—This much just for dinner?
Who's eating?
That's right.
I'm getting hungry.
It's a full banquet.
Your sideburns are...
Pretty interesting today.
—This?
—Yeah.
I just admire someone and...
Who is it?
This American guy from a soap opera.
I saw him and I thought he looked awesome.
—Who is it?
—He's...
You might not know him.
Well...
Does anyone here watch "The Walking Dead"?
I do.
It's Eugene.
Eugene? I know him.
Do you want me to show you?
No, I'm fine.
I just really like Eugene.
Marutai Ramen!
That's the best one!
Can we prepare that?
Prepare? It's already pre-made.
What's the soup?
This is pork rib.
—You brought that?
—Yeah.
Directly from the pig?
Not directly, it was kind of pre-made.
Marutai ramen sure is great.
It's delicious.
My dad used to eat it all the time.
For lunch on Sundays.
How do you use this?
How did you do it?
Fujimoto-san's dad was attacked—
attacked by some thugs and got killed, right?
Why don't you just put it on the screen?
Please do it!
—Am I wrong?
—What's this?
We're doing a quiz.
A quiz.
—Fine.
—Who's taking the quiz?
Until the ramen's done.
—This right here?
—Yeah.
That guy looks pretty old.
—Ah because of his neck?
—Yeah.
Really? He's not that wrinkled.
Isn't that Sanma-san?
I'd say he's young because of the clothes.
You're close. He might be around that age.
Isn't it Bannai-san?
Who is that?
Ah, looking at it now!
—What's that?
—His jawline is...
It's like squarish.
Isn't it...
Isn't it Makoto-san from Sharam Q? (EN: Jp Rock Band)
He's— He's older than that.
Taisei from Sharam Q.
—Taisei-san?
—It's not Taisei.
Hatake-san.
He's not from Sharam Q.
He's not linked to Sharam Q.
Nanbara-san?
Yes.
—Nanbara-san.
—Nanbara?
—Kiyotaka-san?
—No.
Sugiyama Kiyotaka?
He doesn't have anything to do with Kiyotaka.
Nanbara bang bang bang!
Huh?
I think your taste is a little off.
I was just wrong.
Too hard?
It's a shame.
This is Seko-san.
The former SB.
Woah, no way!
Seko the marathon runner.
No way.
Who's this?
We already saw him.
That's a sweet potato?
Even if you scroll down...
Why don't you turn around just once?
I think we might be in trouble here.
It can get pretty hard depending on the person.
Here we go. One, two... three!
Girolamo?
Me!
That's Koba-san!
He looks like Koba-san!
Girolamo?
—He looks like me? But still...
—He's a lot like Koba-san!
But the teeth are too pretty!
He's kind of...
Look at his wrinkles.
—Yeah.
—That's Shimizu Kentaro-san?
The beard is kind of...!
Kiyohara?
It's not Kiyohara-san.
—Little Kiyohara.
—Edamame-san?
Tsumami Edamame-san has this white beard too, right?
But I can tell you he's kind of related to Koba-san.
Related to Koba-san?
He looks quite older.
What's his connection to Kobayashi?
Maybe Choshu Riki-san? (EN: Jp Wrestler)
Correct!
His jaw is pretty clean!
That's a good expression!
He has great teeth!
Really great teeth!
When he goes all "I'm not pissed!"
You know he's never said that?
Yeah, Choshu Riki-san has never said it.
Then what does he say?
"I ain't pissed at all."
That happens sometimes.
For instance in Sazae-san,
wait, no, not Sazae-san.
That character, Hoshi Hyuuma...
...he's actually never flipped a coffee table.
For real?
—But there's this opening—
—Ah yeah, that happened once.
What about Sazae-san?
In Sazae-san, whenever Namihei gets scolded,
they almost never say "you dum-dum!"
But that "you dum-dum" isn't as famous.
Same thing goes for "adultery is culture."
He doesn't say that, right?
Yeah, not really.
But I think Iketani from Joyman
has always said "what's with this guy"
as his catchphrase.
He has, yeah.
"What's with this guy?"
That's all he says.
Every time.
He gets the "what's with this guy?" medal.
It's fine.
"What's with this guy?!"
You spit on me. Gross.
—Now Mikitty.
—Mikitty!
"What's with this guy?!"
Mikitty.
Mikitty!
-What?
-Junior... Junior.
-What's wrong?
-Who? -What? -Where?
-What?
-Junior... Junior.
-What's wrong?
-Who? -What? -Where?
—What?
—"What's with this guy?!"
—Who?
—What?
Mikitty!
I am so very sorry!!
What? What?
What's with this vest?!
What's he doing?
I gathered the world's colors.
—Asahi Kasei?
—Yes. Asahi Kasei. (EN: Jp Chemical Company)
That's what the world's colors look like?
The world's colors?
Yes!
I had Saturday Night Live in mind.
How so?
Okay, I'll try to make that sound.
The sound.
—Sound?
—I'm going to imitate it.
—A vocal impression?
—Yes!
Okay, um...
I'm going to make the sound of an owl,
while making the face of an iriomote cat.
Okay, everyone take a look.
Yes. I'm making the sound of an owl,
while making the face of an iriomote cat.
Whoa...
That's incredible.
No way.
Now it's a cuckoo clock.
He's great!
I can do one more.
I'm going to do the sound of Itsuki Hiroshi-san, (EN: Jp Singer)
when he does the sound of a Formula 1 car.
He's great.
Seiji, are you looking?
You weren't looking!
—I'm looking, I'm looking.
—Do it for Seiji!
I was looking.
I saw the end.
—Do it in front of him.
—Take a good look, Seiji.
This is Kondo Masahiko from the pit.
Chihara Seiji-san! (EN: Kondo is a Jp Singer and former Racing Driver)
Schumacher is the clear favorite this year! (EN: British Racing Driver)
He's using the EF43 engine this year.
This way, this way.
Junior, come on!
You suck at this!
That was too stupid!
It was hilarious.
What was with that pop?!
That was the faintest grin!
It was too bad.
That damned pop!
It was faint but you were smiling!
It was hilarious.
Okay, that was obviously Junior.
But I want to look at someone else.
We can leave that for later.
Let's look at Junior first.
This way, this way.
—There's nothing to say.
—Yeah, I think there's nothing to say.
He even laughed a little.
Yeah, he even laughed.
You ended up reacting to that?
You lost at a damned pop?
There's also...
The brothers, you see.
I saw Seiji.
Let's take a look.
I'm pretty sure Seiji was smiling too.
I didn't see Seiji at all.
You smiled?!
I'm in the clear!
You were smiling!
Don't tell me you believe this bullshit!
You're just trying to save yourselves!
You were definitely smiling!
So all things considered...
Junior gets an orange!
Too quick!
And Seiji gets...
That's too strict!
So of course, those points right now go to Chance.
Thank you very much
—He got a lot right now.
—He got two points...
He got two points, yeah.
So uh...
To make sure you don't get away with the e-cigs,
if you overdo it, I'm taking them from you.
That's too much!
We have to watch out.
This is too much!
—Alright, alright!
—Let's laugh before the bell rings.
It grew too much.
Ah that's right!
You made that yourself?
Sorry, I ended up laughing.
—Don't worry about it.
—Sorry.
—You don't add any condiments?
—No egg?
It's just regular plain.
There are like three full plates in here.
You can eat all that?
That's Marutai Ramen.
But don't you like...
gain any weight with that?
But I guess thin people can eat something like that.
I get it, I get it, I get it! (EN: Fujimoto's comedy duo partner's gag)
You suck at this!
Look at his bones...
You really suck at this!
How is it?
Delicious!
I get it, I get it, I get it!
You can complain, you know Fujimoto?
This is your partner...
That was Haranishi-san, right?
Yeah.
You don't know him?
No, I didn't get to see you right now.
Can you do it again?
I get it, I get it, I get it!
You really should complain if you want to, Fujimoto-san!
That's your partner!
Why don't you tell him?
Seiji looks like he's about to laugh!
Look...
Fujimoto-san could do it.
And then he twists his hands, like that.
He's not moving.
He doesn't say anything!
Do it!
I get it, I get it, I get it, I get it!
He's overdoing it.
That's one time too many.
So uh...
—You don't move right there.
—It has to feel compact.
This is the part that's important.
Look? Here. It doesn't change. See?
—It won't work if you don't do this.
—Ah, I see!
You reject it, like this.
You're doing it wrong, Junior-san?
I get it, I get it, I get it, I get it.
Like that.
You stop at the end.
I get it, I get it, I get it, I get it.
Your direction is wrong, Junior-san.
The direction's wrong.
It's pretty wrong.
You have to do this.
—It's good?
—It's great!
That's hard.
They reject like this...
Try doing just that at first.
Ah, that right there!
I get it, I get it, I get it, I get it!
What the hell are you doing?!
You sure get along.
Being from the same generation must be fun.
Fujimon is worse than I expected.
I guess only the partner can get the gags right.
That means Fujimoto can get all of Haranishi-san's right?
He can.
Can you do that knee thing, too?
I wonder about his coordination.
—You go like this.
—There he goes!
Can you do it, Junior-san?
—That's gross.
—That's awful.
That looks like a hermit crab.
He's a stick insect.
—Stop it!
—Stop what?
Stop playing dumb.
I'm telling you to stop.
Why? Everyone from the same generation can do it.
That's right.
Do that rai rai thing.
This sucks.
This is too awful.
Even considering he can't do it, it's awful.
The Chiharas don't have any coordination. That's it.
—Chance.
—Yeah?
Were you ever on "Gokigenyo"? (EN: Guest-based Jp TV Show)
No, no, no.
No way.
I'd be filthy rich if I had.
Pretend you did, pretend you did.
Alright, go it.
Okay, please start, Chance Oshiro.
I wonder what we're getting.
Okay!
Love stories!
Love stories!!
Um... I'm...
When I was 23, I left Tokyo,
and without knowing anyone,
I worked in a convenience store in East Nakano's Yamate road.
I had the night shift,
and then around 3 in the morning,
the same woman with a pretty face would stop by.
And so, well...
I kind of fell in love at first sight,
and since she always stopped by,
I always thought she was so beautiful.
And she always bought some highlight cigarettes.
And so, since I knew she wanted highlights,
whenever she stopped by,
I would take out the highlights before she asked for them.
And so that pretty woman was like...
Always...
"Oh you remembered what cigarettes I like!"
"Thank you very much."
She would look at my nametag and go
"That's Oshiro-san, right?"
"Yes, thank you very much."
So then, my shift leader
asked the pretty woman
if she wanted to hang out with us sometime.
And she was like
"Sure. I'm a little busy right now, but around August I could stop by."
She was like "okay, let's do a double date."
I could just think that I was super happy.
And so, that woman would always come at around 3am, right?
"I'm going to be singing live on TV
at around 4am today." she said.
So I was like "Oh so she was a musician?"
"Really? I can't see it, though."
Since we didn't have a TV at the store.
She said "Oh so I'll bring you a tape or something next time."
"Thank you very much" I said.
"Right, I'm sorry!"
"You haven't told me your name yet!"
"What's your name?"
"I'm Sheena Ringo" she said.
I didn't know her back then, of course.
So, eventually, I got fired from there.
And Sheena Ringo-san kept becoming more and more popular.
So eventually Tamaki Pinch-san took me to this uh...
sexual service called "Sheena Ingo" in Kabukicho.
The girl was actually named Sheena Mikan-chan.
So uh...
And so there was a Sheena Ringo track playing on the radio.
And there I was thinking that the girl I loved was so successful.
"What the hell am I doing here?!"
"Meanwhile Ringo-san keeps selling more and more!"
I kept thinking over and over.
And meanwhile Sheena Mikan-chan just said.
"Wanna do a sixty-nine?"
Seiji, it can't be helped here.
No, that was you.
It was a great story.
—Was that true?
—Yeah.
—Incredible.
—For real.
It was just a good story.
You even said there was a song playing, right?
Was that true?
That was a good story, right?
Okay, so.
It was the one that goes "In the morning near Yamate road"
"I touch my cheek in Yamate road."
That one!
That song is definitely about me.
—No way.
—I came to buy a cigarette.
"You open the cigarette box"
In Yamate road.
And there was some Pinch guy that appeared at some point?
Who was that?
Tamaki Pinchi-san, right! He's an upperclass guy.
I don't care.
So who was it...? Who laughed?
Ah, it was Seiji.
—I knew it!
—It was terrible.
He contorted his face,
and held it in for quite a while.
Well, let's just take a look.
So eventually Tamaki Pinch-san took me to this uh...
sexual service called "Sheena Ingo" in Kabukicho.
Come on...
—See?
—There he goes.
He's beet red already.
And so there was a Sheena Ringo track playing on the radio.
And there I was thinking that the girl I loved was so successful.
"What the hell am I doing here?!"
"Meanwhile Ringo-san keeps selling more and more!"
I kept thinking over and over.
And meanwhile Sheena Mikan-chan just said.
"Wanna do a sixty-nine?"
He's eating ramen again.
—Seiji is doing horribly.
—That was pretty bad, Seiji.
Your face looked like Ebizo's glare.
You managed to hold it in, though!
I wasn't smiling. Not at all.
No good, at all.
The Chihara brothers get an orange.
We're not even an hour through.
The point goes to Chance Oshiro.
Guess you'll have to plan things over
in the zombie room.
You can't do that.
So I partnered with Tamaki Pinch-san,
and became Chance.
So you were Pinch and Chance?
That's how it was?
Alright, here we go!
Wasn't that with Okawa Kogyou?
There we go, there we go.
With Okawa Kogyou?
—There he goes eating.
—For real!
Those are three dishes!
Tamaki Pinch Chance?
We were Tamaki Pinch and Chance Oshiro.
What was the group's name?
Right hearts 800.
Right hearts 800?
I was the right heart.
Ah, that's right.
Because the heart's in the right?
—Really?
—Yeah.
So, Tamaki Pinch's name came from
him being a national 800m champion.
The heart's in the right?
So you became Right hearts 800.
Right hearts 800.
—That's a great name.
—You did manzai?
Yeah, manzai.
Where's the punchline?
No way.
What are you doing, Fujita?
I'm preparing one more dish.
—I can still eat
—For real?!
I can eat until I'm full.
—No way.
—It's too good.
Marutai is delicious.
Um... uh... well...
So Tamaki Pinch was—
I really don't care.
Why are you looking at me?
Let's get along come on.
We're from the same generation.
I can't hear you at all.
So what kind of jokes were Pinch's specialty?
Why are you running away?
Junior. Why are you running away?
Let's get along!
You know Purupuru perorinpa?
I think you could...
Purupuru perorinpa?
What am I supposed to say after Purupuru perorinpa?
Purupuru perorinpa is just...
—What's he doing?
—That's the crab.
—The crab! crab crab!
—What's that supposed to mean? (EN: Another one of Haranishi's Gag's)
Crab crab crab!
From crab to xavier!
How the hell do you do it?
What the—
Ah, like this!
Crab crab crab!
From crab to xavier!
Lower, lower...
Have you never even seen the Xavier thing?
How the hell do you do it? Do it.
Crab crab crab crab...
From crab to Xavier!
Hey you...
You're a complete failure to Haranishi.
Try to remember it properly
Hey... fuck you.
If only you remembered it,
you wouldn't be such a failure as a gag guy.
—Hey, everyone.
—What? Gag?
Are you guys washing your hands?
—Ah because of the virus?
—You really should do it.
Are you stupid, Fujita?
This guy's a complete idiot.
This is a pretty strong gel.
It stinks!
This is too much!
It's awful.
Stop this, come on!
What's that?!
This is fucking hell!
We'll have to smell this all the time.
This stinks!
Come on, leave it for later!
And we still have a lot of time!
This is shit?
It really smells like shit.
It's a strong disinfectant.
This... fights poison with poison.
What's this...?
—I dipped some shit in water.
—This really stinks!
I won't be able to eat anymore,
so please stop it.
You sure can eat, huh?!
Please stop this. I'm eating.
How much!
It stinks too much!
Mikitty!
What's with this guy?!
—This stinks.
—I can't take this...
It stinks.
Haranishi-san?
You talking about Hara Nishio?
—This smells like shit.
—I can't get it off!
I can't get it off my hands!
It really stinks.
This is too much!
You have any siblings, Chance Oshiro?
Ah yes, I do.
Who are they?
I have an older sister.
Sister and brother.
Sister and brother?
Who's your brother?
My brother didn't take a bath for half a year in high school.
—That's filthy.
—Yes.
And he doesn't clip his nails.
That's filthy.
One time we forced him to shower with my mom,
and the water was all black.
—That's filthy.
—Yes.
And he would bite his own fingernails.
That's gross.
And he would take his toe nails,
and stretch them all the way.
They were all ingrown.
And so at night, when I was sleeping,
I could hear some scratching coming from the floor.
And so I'd open the door, and I'd go:
"What are you doing?"
"I'm going to the bathroom."
"You're not wearing tap shoes?"
"I'm not."
Once he went to bed, he wouldn't wake up at all.
So mom put construction paper between his skin and his nails.
And used a cutter to clip them.
So she clipped them one by one.
She started putting more strength into it,
and ripped it off, and my brother started bleeding.
And so eventually even a deep-sleeper like him woke up.
He jumped out of the bed, and started shouting.
It was like the ending of Zatoichi. (EN: Character in an extremely popular Film series and TV show with the same name)
He was like "clack clack clack!"
He was saying that out loud?
No, it was the sound of his toe nails.
Ah sorry, I suck at telling stories.
How did he make them sound like that?
He was barefoot.
Barefoot against the floor?
They were all ingrown...
And so his nails were all...
Yeah, yeah.
And so he was like...
Yeah, all around here.
Fujimon, you're smiling?
Hey.
—I'm not smiling.
—You are.
Stop saying that out loud.
Um... please zip that up.
Ah, I'm sorry.
Which one?
Okay, that's enough.
That's enough.
Give me a fucking break!
What the fuck's this?!
What's with that?!
What happened?
Why are you just screwing me over?!
—Why are you making me laugh?
—That's war.
He's making me laugh...
That's not true!
—It was a general attack.
—That's not true!
I just stood in the center and—
Why is that Haranishi?!
That's not Haranishi-san...
It's not.
—It's really not.
—It's Gucci Yuuzo. (EN: Jp Personality)
You thought it was Haranishi-san?
You laughed because you thought it was him?
You always thought it was him?
That's how much you love your partner?
—Haranishi-san...
—You thought it was Haranishi-san?
Everyone was thinking that.
You didn't know who was going to show up, Fujimon.
You're all accusing me falsely!
That's too embarrassing.
It's too embarrassing.
Matsumoto's laughing too.
I can laugh, though!
That was a self-conscious accident.
That's not self-conscious at all, man!
—He just has a victim complex.
—A victim complex for sure.
But he does look a bit like him.
Haranishi and Gucci Yuuzo look alike.
So he knew they looked alike and targeted me...
Let's look at it. It was terrible.
That's pretty bad.
He's completely laughing.
I thought he was trying to bring me down.
Just pick a picture that makes it clearer
that it's Yuuzo.
Fujimon! You get an orange!
You laughed out loud,
which is pretty unusual lately.
I'm sure you have plenty of complaints to write for this evaluation,
right Fujimon?
You know I'm not gonna say anything.
What are you saying?
You're gonna say "that wasn't funny at all."
And that's why I'm getting an orange?
—Yeah.
—"Yeah"?!
"That wasn't funny at all" is something he'd say, yeah.
That's too strict!
Come on.
It started!
No, no.
Just make it...
...at least a picture that's clearly Gucci-san's.
Depending on the person,
that could be basically anyone.
Think about it.
You really think I planned it and printed this?
Of course you did!
You could make him look thinner!
Are you telling me to lose weight
just for Gucci's image?
Open it from above.
How does it look from above?
When he opens it from below?
Well, I think it's fine when I do it like this.
It looks different from below.
Try opening it from above.
Don't say it like it's an AKB song.
"Mariko from above."
It's "from below"!
No. It's "from above."
Don't turn this into a romantic thing.
Let's stop this. Let's stop this!
It's "from above"
Do Gucci from above.
—Which one?
—Do Gucci from above.
This is perfectly fine. See?
What do you think?
When you do it like that,
it's definitely Gucci.
It's Gucci from above.
Haranishi from below.
Depending on how I open it,
it looks like Gucci.
Is it Haranishi the lower it gets?
Yeah, yeah.
So if I do this it's Gucci...?
That's definitely Haranishi!
That's really Haranishi-san.
It's definitely Haranishi.
Do it so we can tell it's Gucci.
That right there.
That that!
It kind of looks like Oochi from this angle too.
Why are you bringing Oochi up now?
There's some Oochi from above, too.
Is it Oochi from the side?
You could also turn Oochi into Daichi.
It changes depending on the name.
He won't stop eating.
He was really hungry.
Wanna play a game?
Didn't Coo just smile a little right now?
Coo smiled, right?
I didn't smile.
He smiled while doing it himself.
Hey, wanna play a game?
Fujita, you're an idiot.
This has bluetooth?
Yeah.
This reminds me of those Lumine Quizzes.
I told you we'd be playin a game, right?
You sure get along, huh?
You're a really handy guy, aren't you?
You love stuff like this.
You're busy right now, right?
Both him and Rossi are busy. (EN: Rossi is Cookie's Comedy Duo Partner)
Rossi usually looks pretty free, though.
—Is Rossi doing anything?
—That's a sad story.
Stop it.
You want to cry?
Why would I cry?
Because it's sad...
Rossi isn't doing anything, right?
What?
He's working.
Working, working.
Rossi's busy?
He's obviously not busy.
He's obviously busy!
He's been busy for a while now though, right?
Yeah, a little.
—At least he's doing what he likes.
—Good for him.
He's doing some baseball thing, right?
—Who?
—Rossi-san.
He doesn't play baseball.
He watches "camp report" a lot, though.
Who told you that?
Stop slurping that.
We're talking.
That's too loud!
Are you sucking someone off?
—He's not.
—I'm not.
—You can tell, right?
—But that sound...
It was just an example.
I think I prefer the term Lingus.
—What?
—Lingus is better.
What's that?
Cunnilingus...
That reminds me of Maeda Akira. (EN: Jp Promoter/Wrestler)
Don't bring Maeda Akira up just like that.
What's with that vest?
He was talking about it earlier.
—He likes it.
—He loves it.
It looks like a pro wrestler's.
It has that half-assed vibe.
It has a half-assed quality.
Why are you so loud?
What's wrong with your earlobes?
Did they get torn or something?
Ah yeah, a thug came by and...
—That's sad.
—That's a sad story.
He attacked me with a stapler like—
When was that?
—When you were working part time?
—Yes.
No way... do this!
Who will hold the remote?
Ah then, Seiji-san.
Can you do it? This is the remote.
Take it.
This won't appear on screen.
Just push this key to start.
Here we go.
—You're moving?
—Yeah.
I don't really know the controls.
That's amazing.
I don't get it. It's hard to use.
Watch out.
I don't know the controls, so...
Can someone do it?
I don't know this controller either.
Do it, Koba-san.
I can't do it.
You can do it, Koba-san!
You can do it!
Watch out, watch out!
Go, go, go!
Koba-san...
No good, huh?
Who can do it?
Fujimon!
Fujita, you do it!
Fujita, Fujita!
Go, Fujita. Do it!
You're holding it wrong.
Go, go!
Let him be. It's gonna be the same.
Go!
Jump, jump!
—Go!
—Take some impulse.
Is that how the game's supposed to work?
No way, everyone's falling the same way.
Go, go!
Start, start!
It's the same.
—He did it!
— Go, go!
It worked!
There we go!
—Who was it?
Definitely not me.
Was it me?
Was I smiling?
No way!
I was biting my lips!
—Who was it?
—Koba?
I don't know!
I was biting my lips!
Sorry about this.
This is my own judgment, but...
It was just too funny.
Thank you very much.
Well, everyone was at least smiling a little.
So I think that generally...
Everyone is going to get a yellow.
—Everyone?
—Pretty much everyone was smiling.
No way!
How many poitns is that?
Well, people with oranges can keep them.
It won't turn into a red.
You were all smiling like it was new year's eve.
It might be a little premature,
but you're all getting a yellow.
Whoa, no way!
That's too much!
I think it works out!
From now on you're not gonna pull any unnecessary stuff.
We won't, we won't.
This will work.
You're gonna keep going?
I'm leaving this to Cookie...
Please stop this already!
Stop it!
Whoa, that's dirty!
Where is it?!
In the gulf!!