Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!
Documental might seem
like an individual battle
But it's actually a team effort.
Come!
Whoa!
What an awesome first hit...
So people tend to say that someone
Wasn't funny this time around.
And so I want this to be a godly run.
Ouch!
That hurts!
I think this time will be
godly with me around!
I'll make them say it!
It's gonna be godly!
I'll do it!
Alright!
Is this guy stupid?
That's not in the rules.
No, that's it. If you laugh, you lose.
Is he really stupid?
You can't smile, you're gonna lose
Let's keep going
Huh?
-Huh?
-Wait a second.
Anything else?
-It's over.
-No way!
She smiled!
Yellow, that's a yellow.
Come on...
Huh? She laughed.
Alright, Yuriyan.
A yellow.
That's right.
Alright. Wanna play a game?
I don't really wanna right now...
It's pretty short. I swear.
We've played plenty of games, though.
But alright, then.
If it's short then...
Alright, here we go.
We did the one with the nipples...
Aren't you guys
a little hungry?
Yeah, kinda!
Uh...
I brought some snacks.
I have enough for several people.
You know this?
"Comedian chips"?
-Yeah
-Never heard of them.
Never heard of them.
It's like the ones for baseballers
but with comedians?
They had some with comedians
So you can have this
I don't get it.
Open them up
You have one for each of us?
Sure, there's enough for everyone.
I wonder what I got.
No way!
I'm pretty excited
Can I open this?
Sure, go on.
No way!
That's a big one!
That's the best one!
That one must be rare
That's a normal one
Downtown is just normal?!
Well, depends on how you look at it
Yeah, I guess some are holographic
Pick whichever you like
So there are rare ones?
Can I open mine?
Sure, go on.
Alright, here I go
I guess there's about 20
No way!
Whoa!
Great, eh?
You like yourself too much
Well, I didn't get to choose it though
It was just by chance
It was a coincidence
Can I do it?
Junior-san
That one's holographic!
So Lee V is a rare one? (Editor's Note: 1)
I think that might be...
No, that would be rude.
Lee V?
--"I'll kill you!"
-It's so shiny
The one from Noheru
That's really sparkling
"I'll kill you!"
That's just...
I don't know him
Well, comedy history is quite complex
I got a shiny one too
They're not so special, huh?
Narumi-san
Just like that?
Narumi's holographic
Narumi-san
Stop making it seem
like she's in a commercial
Narumi
I don't think there's much impact
Press the button
One more time
Press it, press it
Press it
Sideways Narumi (EN: 2)
There we go!
Whose point was that?
The Sideways Narumi
Sideways Narumi!
Why did you throw that in there?
That one's holographic too
Sideways Narumi
It was the Sideways Narumi
Damn it!
That was close!
It was amazing.
But that was definitely Goto
-I sure smiled.
-Your first time?
-It is.
-Yellow!
Alright
Lots of yellows now!
I did laugh for sure
Sideways Narumi
There it is!
I feel like Seiya
smiled as well
You sure smiled yeah
Right now?
I really don't think so,
Matsumoto-san
I didn't smile
Well, whatever
Stop that
That sound's so bland
You're right, that's true
That's mean!
It's just sound
Don't put Vertical Narumi sideways!
Goto-san
Sound can't...
I'm falling asleep
You know...
Huh?
What happened, what happened?
That's scary
Freaking me out!
Whoa, that's creepy
He's still pitch black
You look the same
So you were painted black
It's the same
Huh?
Who's that?
Hello. I'm Janis... Joplin! (EN: 3)
She sounds like Nishioka Sumiko (EN: 4)
Janis Joplin?
-Me is
-Me?
Janis
Joplin!
That's Nishioka
Yeah, for sure
That does sound like Nishioka Sumiko
Me sing...
Wanna hear?
Sure!
I can't believe you can
play a Janis Joplin song!
Sure
"Sure"?
I...
Huh?
Now she said "I"
The song's starting...
That's too long
The quietest ukulele on Earth...
That's a long intro
Just sing
That's too long
Sing something!
You forgot the lyrics?
Are we there finally?
No...
I can't even listen
There we go!
I am Nishioka Sumiko!
So you were Nishioka Sumiko?
No, sorry.
I'm Janis Joplin!
How did you get that wrong?
What does that mean?
-What about the song?
-Mistake
I wanted to hear
a Janis Joplin song!
Now she says "I", huh?
I really love
Fried chicken...
Nice voice
But I prefer my pork
Roasted
My dream is...
to eat grilled Thai rice
Oh yeah! That's all I need
All I really want
With eggs- eggs- eggs
And when it comes to bread,
my brother works
in Saint Germain
At least once
You should give it a try
(?)
What I really love
Is booze. Oh yeah
That was...
Janis Joplin!
No way
I've never heard
that Janis Joplin song
What was that?
Janis Joplin...
It's called Foodshow
Foodshow?
Well, you know Janis Joplin?
Maybe "Mercedes Benz"
is a more famous song of hers?
Merdedes Bents?
That's not what I said
"Mercedes Benz"
Me?
You talking about me?
No, no...
about Janis Joplin
Mercedes De...
Why can't you say it?
It's "Mercedes Benz"
I don't think
that existed back then.
Of course it did!
Huh?
What's that sound?
An old fart...
A hustler? (EN: 5)
He has a 1 ball
Are you alright?
Watch out
He's shaking
He doesn't look stable
His hands are just...
Can he do it? (EN: 6)
Do it, now now!
Do it! Now, now, now!
You can do it! Now!
What's he doing?
I'm getting pissed off
It's not even moving
What's with this?
There it is
Huh?
Turn around
He's satisfied now
No way
I don't get this at all
Please say something
I really feel like
He's the hustler...
A round girl?
That's so gross
He's even throbbing
Round two?
Dick-kun?
A second round?
That's what this is?
Are they boxing?
It didn't work
It didn't work at all
You don't have to do that
What's with these intervals?
Now's time for the round girl?
What?
I don't like this
We don't wanna see you
He's not even a Girl
Get the hustler back!
Bring back the old man
I did it with the beat
He's so stressed
So stressed
It's like he's convulsing
Watch out
What now?
What was that?
Alright!
Let's play the "I want to smell my Dad's farts" game
Are we doing that?
Let's do it
He told us the rules already
That's a small one
Pretty tiny
More than I thought
Alright! Who's doing it?
Please choose, Ikezaki-san.
Alright...
Junior-san, let's do it
Alright, understood.
What should I do?
You stay here
-He's the dad?
-He is
So put your legs up like this
I'm staying here
Alright
Ah, that's right!
Sorry
I'd like you to wear some briefs
This is gonna take forever
We don't have time
This game's pretty messy
-Listen
-Like this?
Right
Leave it there
What about the roller?
That's the son
Soshina!
What should I do?
Uh... it's about here.
So stand up around here.
What's your dad's name?
Yoshihide.
Think that's Yoshihide
And you want to sniff his farts
Do you understand that?
And so...
Since you want to smell his farts, you do this...
That looks hard
And once you flatten this,
you'll smell his fart.
Alright
Then you can come back
But you can also stay like this
Really?
Once Yoshihide farts,
You have to shout "Yoshihide, thank you!"
Since you wanted to smell them
And Yoshihide has to shout something back
That's the game
That's a game?
Alright then
Let's do it, then.
Let's do this
Alright, the dad's farts smelling game
Ready, go!
Do it!
You need to be strong for this
Soshina's pretty weak, though
That's pretty risky as well
It tore
"Thank you"
"Thank you, Yoshihide!"
I'm better at soccer than you
There he goes
That's good
Soshina's still trying
to play it straight
I wanted it to sound like a fart
Right?
The sound was puny
That was close
Yoshihide's farts are kinda cute
Well, Yoshihide is dead, though
I wanna give it a try
So uh... can we give it a break with that?
Well, you're right.
Who's next?
Goto-san?
So once I do this and it makes a sound
Your dad's name
I have to thank him, right?
And I
What should I shout back?
How'd I know, you idiot?
To your son, yeah
I'll shout something good about you
Alright
This is pretty hard
It really is
Motonori, thank you!
"Uchi no Gaya ga Sumimasen" [I'm sorry for my work!]
The name of the show?
I've been looking after you since...
My dad would say that?
Are you eating?
This is a piece of...
Mieharu-san's poop for Goto-san (EN: 7)
For...
Mieharu-san's poop, yeah...
Mieharu-san's poop
Mieharu-san's pretty healthy then
That's a very healthy poop
In great shape
Is it good?
It's great
Well, that wasn't really funny, huh?
Stop it with Mieharu's poop
Sorry, I'm just watching
I think it was funny
Don't get in the way
when it's not even funny!
It was funny
It doesn't matter
if it's funny
I thanked Motonori
And then he apologized
for his reaction
Right?
He's pretty bad at reacting!
What was that?
You don't think so?
That sticks out too much
I think that's leaking a little
Hey!
What happened?
You know?!
You know who I am?!
-Who are you?
-I don't know
You always leave me behind
Leave you behind...
You always throw me away!
I think I've seen it in a forum...
Yeah I get it
What?
I'm parsley
Not a green pea?
Or a pepper?
He's a pea for sure
He has to be a pea
No, a pepper.
Pretty thick for parsley
His head is round
You always throw me away!
I like peas better
Who are you?
I'm a green pea
Oh no
He was right there
He was right next to him
Will you apologize to me?
Because we never eat you?
Can you apologize to parsley?
Back at parsley?
So you were parsley after all?
What are you? A pea or parsley?
I'm a green pea
Then don't go back
to saying you're parsley
Well, based on his overall shape
I think it has to be a green pea
All things considered
Well, feel free to be what you like
but tell us who you are.
I'm a green pea
He's shaking
That's too much
Is this a standup?
He just keeps going
I won't apologize.
I always eat you.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah, I think almost everyone does.
You don't?
Yuriyan doesn't
I'm sorry
I'm really sorry
He's looking at her boobs
That green pea is a pervert
A perverted green pea
I'm really sorry
He's staring so bad
He's staring too much
I'm really sorry
Oh that's pretty serious
Who's that?
He looks evil.
He's pretty bad
Someone like this is bad news
The green pea ran away
This guy's scary!
So scary
He's sucking on a chupachups
Sweets are great, huh?
He's shouting
Sweets are great
No one hates sweets.
Everyone likes them
I have one more
You don't want it?
You want it?
That hurts, I'm gonna break a tooth
It's like the dentist
Teeth shouldn't look like that
It sounds like the dentist
That's scary
Why did you put a candy there?
Huh?
I don't have anything to give back
Ah, he got him
That's sweet
Huh?
Is he Kuwata?
Green Kuwata?
Expecto Patronum!
He cast an Expecto Patronum
What? Whoa, watch out!
Watch out, man!
Stop that already
That's dangerous man
Anyone wanna pull it?
Of course not!
Five people
That's too many!
Please do it
I'm not taking responsibility
That's dangerous
Watch out, seriously!
Do it yourself
That scared me
Is he an alien?
Maybe it missed?
What's wrong with your nervous system?
That's dangerous, Abareru-san
Ouch!
Huh?
What happened?
Maybe one has something different
Like, the last one you pull
I see. Watch out
Two more left
It's my turn
That has to be it
This is serious!
You're right
This is it...
You go, Seiya
This sucks
I'm really sorry. Ready?
Okay? Here I go
Watch out, something's happening
You missed
He's crazy
-You missed.
-What's going on?
Aren't you smiling?
He's right, he's right
You're smiling, though
What kind of face is that?
Cracker toys are serious business
So I saw a portrait painter
in Shinjuku the other day
And he had a sample
Ah, yeah, I've seen that!
Like, with a drawing on it
So I bought one off him
He told me I looked like a famous guy
Wanna see?
This is it
The Pink no Denwa girls? (EN: 8)
That's them for sure
Definitely them
He had Pink no Denwa on display?
They're pretty outdated
Like Matsuko-san
Or the Three O'Clock Heroine
Nowadays that'd be Shimofuri or something
No, it was Pink no Denwa
Or Choco Planet
I also have these
Oka Yuuta-san
Yuuta-san's slower than the crab
He can't run at all
You're pretty mean
He's slower than the snail
He always takes a long time
to get to the mic
These guys are mean
He had this one
On display?
Where did you go?
To Shinjuku
They had Yuuta in Shinjuku?
This is even before NGK
You're right
A previous Shimofuri Myojo manager
Was also Yuuta-san's manager
And we were in the transition period
And so we got Yuuta-san's schedule
But it said "hospital"
from Monday to Friday
-Whose?
-Yuuta-san's
When I was still in Kishiwada
He asked me if
I was going to take a bath
So he was walking with me on the shoulder
Like from the shoulder
And the bath had like
these jet streams.
And he got in
I told him I was washing myself first
So he got in the bath
And the jet streams
thrust him around like
And then he hit the wall like Bomberman (EN: 9)
He was pretty thin, actually
Maybe the stream was too strong
It was
Against the wall
He hit the wall, right?
Seiya is smiling, though!
How was he?
I grabbed him and asked if he was okay
He said he was, and got back in
And got swung around by the jet stream
He even got hit in the face like
So I asked if he was okay
But he looked like Bomberman
He looked like Bomberman?
Sorry. What's that bullshit?
For real!
Well, that was Seiya, obviously
That was me
I couldn't hold it in
Alright Seiya, you're out
He's out
First one after we've gotten this far?
This is just the first one
I'm the first one?
You're all too good
Well, that's 20 million, so...
Damn it
I laughed at Yuuta-san's Bomberman?
Why did I laugh?
Seiya, so come to my room
And monitor this
Ah we'll watch it from there, right?
Good luck everyone!
Oniyakko-san, sorry about the crow
It's fine!
I'm the worst
I even knew that story
Kubota told it in Osaka several times
So he hit the wall like
Like Bomberman
I laughed even though I knew it
Figures.
Can I be completely honest?
To be honest, I was sneakily smiling all along
But nobody noticed so far
So even if I had won
I don't think I could've accepted it myself
So I was looking for a way to go out
Because I was smiling anyways
I never imagined we'd have so many left
Being the only one here
That was pretty serious!
30 minutes...
So I can laugh now, right?
You can laugh, yeah
Finally!
I'm so happy!
I'm laughing already
This is pretty funny
Yeah, being here is fun
Of course you're gonna laugh from here!
Yeah, that's right
I'm always surprised everyone holds it in
It's pretty funny
Huh?
What happened?
Who are you?
My name is Madame Cat (EN: 10)
Humans look cute when they take it easy
Madame Cat?
My owner was...
A woman of age...
"Was"
You see, she...
thought she was invincible.
Her worldview, huh...
But... she got hospitalized
for something trivial
Humans... can you bring that to me?
The ukulele?
You'll get hospitalized
if you don't take things seriously
Can she play like that?
Looks hard to play
Abareru-san's in trouble
Abareru's in trouble
Maybe she didn't practice
She stopped
You know fasting?
Like when you go on a diet
Ah, fasting, yeah.
You get thinner,
and it helps you detox.
You should give it a try
But when you get started
You can't eat any sour lemons
You'll get cramps and end up in the hospital
Meow
One cat
I feel like her character changed
Two cats
Madame Cat
She's making this up
One cat
Two cats
Madame cat
Abareru-san's struggling!
Remembering her master
Nagano-san too
Seeing lightning strike
From her master's shoulders
One cat
Look at Abareru!
Two cats
Madame Cat
-My stomach hurts
-Madame Cat
Yeah!
One cat
Two cat
Madame Cat
Humans... take care of yourselves
So that was Madame Cat, huh?
Who are you?
My name is... Madame Cat
No, Madame Cat was the one from earlier
Come here, Madame Cat!
What's going on?
She just left
Are there two of them?
She's coming
Meow
She forced her out
One cat
Two cats
Madame Cat
Yeah!
-Yeah!
-One cat
Two cats
-Madame Cat
-Yeah!
Humans...
And their snobbish attitudes!
With your dictionaries
or dietaries or whatever!
Right
He's reading it
Who's that?
A thin tengu
Thin tengu-kun!
I had never heard of you!
Thin tengu?
One cat, two cats
Madame Cat
-Madame Cat!
-Yay!
Thin tengu
Thin tengu!
Thin tengu?
Thin tengu-sama
He was my ally!
Your ally?
Did you...
come for the Broadway audition?
Who?
Who did?
Who's she talking to?
Did you two come for Bod—
Broadway's audition?
You said Bod...
I can't speak right
How rude
Why are you here?
You think I can't do it after all?
Of course not.
What's with that guy?
He has great eyes
I want to stand on that stage!
-You have a bright future.
-You think so?
You think I can do it?
Maybe you do, since you can speak at least
Get the green pea
Look who's talking
I know, right?
-They should use the pea
-Your perspective
Your perspective
Is very musical
But no one wears a cardigan like that!
Take that cardigan off!
Don't underestimate me!
Say something, manager!
Manager?
So he's the manager?
You can't let this slide!
Abareru's in trouble
I'm sorry
Just take it off
I'm sorry, manager.
Sorry about the cardigan.
It's not good, yeah.
Manager...
That's good enough!
Soshina's in trouble too
Ask the general manager...
Right?
The general manager?
General manager!
This guy? The green pea?
That's a green pea
Please enlighten us!
I've never heard something like that.
General manager!
-General manager!
That's your general manager?
I don't think so
Now you're doing that?
Finally
General manager...
He didn't say a thing
with Junior earlier
He's talked like three times
In that case...
Here he goes
Tell me what you can do
There he is
-Tell me
-General manager!
You can do anything!
If only we had a song!
Or a dance or a performance!
Right! If only we had a song, dance or performance!
You're right, but...
Song and dance won't save the world!
You know that, right?
No...
This is good
I don't know that!
What?
That's pretty lame
He smiled!
He laughed all out!
Damn it!
He laughed
He laughed for sure
What was that?
Damn it!
I don't get it either
I didn't get anything
What a shame!
What happened, then?
Abareru-kun...
Has been disqualified
He let it out
Damn it!
That's such a shame
It's really a shame
My greatest weakness is music
Who cares?
Music is my weakness!
Seems like it
You're right, but...
Song and dance won't save the world!
You know that, right?
No...
That's good.
I don't know that.
What?
That's lame
He smiled!
Let's go, Abareru-kun.
27 minutes left.
What were you thinking?
With the green pea?
I'm parsley.
Huh? He changed it once more
You don't laugh even when you can
You can laugh!
Laugh now at least!
At least laugh now!
A lot of points just vanished.
-They vanished.
-Ah really?
Yeah, yeah.
Abareru-kun had a lot of points
So him going out
is a big deal
Damn it!
What a waste!
This is the power of musicals!
No, no, no!
That's the power of Documental!
Well, it can't be helped if I laughed
To be honest, I was pretty close at times
But it was just so much fun
That's what I think
So while sometimes
It's pretty scary
Once it gets started
Time flies because it's just so fun
I'm not smiling
Wasn't that a smile?
Right
Here we go!
I love you!
Please go out with me!
A sudden confession!
That's good!
But even if you say that... um...
Do it!
You don't really know me.
I do.
You're from Suita, right?
No. I'm from Osaka
You got it wrong
It's a lost cause
You don't love me
You really don't
Bleh! I hate you!
She rejected him
I can laugh, right?
This is funny.
Yeah, you can.
Looking from here is funny
It's pretty fun
How long are you staying here?
What?
Madame Cat?
What's this? Stop it
Love?
And Peace
And power!
And shower!
People forget about me at New Years
What are you doing?
Watch out, watch out!
Soshina's in trouble!
Huh?
I think he definitely smiled, though!
He's not smiling, but almost!
Hang in there, Soshina!
He's about to fold!
Hang in there!
Can he do it?
It's now a festival
They made it a festival
Wasn't this Broadway?
Men of... Men of the world!
Make an E with your fingers!
And...
S!
P!
F, P!
Flat!
Huh?
What?
P
P!
F, P, P!
This is bad!
Soshina! Hang in there!
F, P, P!
He's like humming
F, P, P
Hang in there, Soshina!
F, P, P!
Hang in there!
Ah!
I did it
Thanks to you, Ikezaki-san
I almost died with F, P, P.
Was it my fault?
It was all thanks to Ikezaki-san
I took the Stopper role
The Stopper, yeah
Stopper Ikezaki
Don't get so mad, Saigo Takamori-dono!
Who the hell's Saigo Takamori?
I never saw a dog like you
wearing a kimono!
Soshina's in trouble!
Darling, are bicycles stopping
at the Tokyo Teleport Station?
They're not!
Why are you mistaking me for him?
That's a funny name
Sorry, you're from Pokasuka Jan, right?
Please sign this!
I'm not Pokasuka Jan
You idiot!
This man is not from Pokasuka Jan!
Huh?
Chess resident K!
That's right!
What the hell's that?
Chess resident K?!
That's too much
They're good
That's Goto-san, right?
I'm Chess resident K?!
This is so annoying!
-You're awful
-Do your numbers again!
Who even is Goto-san
It won't shut up!
I know, right?
This is annoying when he goes like
Sorry, Goto-san
Huh? Wait, Soshina!
Come on, Soshina!
Hold it in, man!
What happened?!
Hold it in!
He was smiling!
That's enough
Come on, that's enough
I tried to indulge you
But you're out, Soshina
He was smiling all along
That was close
It was too funny
It won't shut up!
I know, right?
It's annoying when he goes like
I'm sorry, Goto-san
Huh? Wait, Soshina!
Come on, Soshina!
In any case, the only ones clean
Are Ikezaki and Kubota
That's right
I have no points, though
What about the points?
For tears and laughter!
It's 20 million!
Alright! Let's do this!
Let's go, Soshina
Nice fight
Thank you
That was too funny
Goto-san's serious attacking
It's way too funny
I was starting to feel the pressure
And Goto-san raised the stakes always
Chess resident K
What's that?
Chess resident K?!
And it reminded me
Of the M-1 Grand Prix Football Hour manzai
that I used to love
You can always say you don't want to
No, Iwao's fine
I felt warm and it was just fun
Why did you call me "Ishio"?
Why did you change the spelling?
Tell me if you don't like the name Iwao, then!
I wasn't expecting that!
It felt really good
But it's still frustrating!
So frustrating!
Soshina did a good job!
But it was just pretty rough
Alright!
15 minutes!
20 million!
What game now?
Another game!
The metal wheel ball stopping game!
That's a new one
A new one
With your body, huh?
I think this one
has potential to be the funniest.
I think it has a lot of potential in general
You spin it like this
and while you stop it with your balls within 10 seconds
You have to name school stuff.
Isn't 10 seconds too long?
You earn the right to say things?
Right
Let's do it!
So I'm gonna spin it
Stuff everyone wants to say
I have nothing, really
So I'm gonna go from the top?
More directly?
This is pretty bad
Doesn't this seem bad?
It looks serious
Let's go from the bottom
Spin it
Are you sure?
10 seconds, alright.
Here it goes!
There it is!
It won't stop!
More! More!
Do it yourself!
He's doing it himself.
Many vice principals are perverts!
What the hell's this game?!
Why do you wanna do this?
It's the metal wheel
ball stopping game.
Then say something interesting!
Don't just blurt any stupid thing!
This is the the metal wheel
ball stopping game.
Wanna try?
Of course not, you idiot!
Do it!
Why do I have to?!
Because it's funny!
It's not funny, you imbecile!
Do it again
Why are you doing it again?!
Goto-san's attacking is great
We're out of time, man!
I'm sorry, since you two are older than me
To be honest, I'm a huge masochist.
So I love it
when you attack me
He's on the move
I want you two to do this
I'm gonna eat this,
drink some cola
Get wrapped in tape
and then get insulted
Insult me!
I want you to insult me
Insult you?
You alright?
So you're gonna hold it in?
Are we gonna spin you around?
No, you tie me up
and insult me
Watch out
You're not gonna drown?
He wants them to insult him
I'm sorry.
He can do that?
You idiot! You're so fucking gross!
I like him, though
You're so gross
I think he's pretty original
-So I don't hate him...
-Why do bastards like you exist?
It's hard to insult someone out of nowhere
And you have great comebacks
Junior can't insult him
And you have that hair dye
that looks like shit
I do think this is bullying.
I'm saying all the good stuff
everyone knows about you
Huh? Junior-san...
I think there's some depth
in being insulted without breaking...
Wait a second! I already swallowed it all!
Do this seriously!
Ikesaki's face...
Besides, I swallowed it!
No one asked you to compliment me!
Insult me!
I know about that
homemade porn you shot!
Where you dragged that girl
all over the toilet!
I know about it!
I know your wife watched it too!
What?
You're talking about
that old toilet licking porn I had?
That's right. I know you love
making girls lick toilets!
And tell your wife about this!
I was right next to her
when she was breastfeeding!
I thought you were
out of it
But you were just
watching my wife's tits all along?
Right, and I fucked her afterwards!
So thanks for that
What did you say?!
What?!
Don't go around
fucking your elders' wives!
She's pretty
She's beautiful
Then look at my wife
Junior-san's wife?
What an odd timing
Huh?
There it is...
Sideways Narumi
He took a picture of Sideways Narumi?
Goto-san!
No, you're not married
to Narumi-san
That's Narumi-san!
Huh?
Narumi-san... That's Sideways Narumi!
Junior-san?
Huh?
Junior-san!
What happened?
You're laughing at your own
picture of Sideways Narumi?!
You're laughing, right?!
At Sideways Narumi?!
He's swimming!
-Junior-kun! Junior-kun!
-That's Master Kiyoshi
Junior-kun, do you remember me?
It's Master Kiyoshi time!
I appeared when you least expected!
He's really holding it in!
I made Seiji-kun appear
several times
Goto-san's in trouble!
(?)
Junior-kun!
Do you remember me?
They're holding it in
No way! They did it.
They did it.
Only nine minutes left
Still nine minutes left
What's gonna happen?
It's 20 million yen.
That's too much
Right?
Who are you showing that?
He's pointing it to us!
Thanks for watching!
Don't point your cock
to the audience!
You get VIP seats!
Leave it!
No!
This guy's insane!
Point it at us instead!
Who's that guy showing his crotch?
It's you, Ikezaki...
-It's me!
-That's what I said!
Why not do Nishio Kasumiko or something?
He's just showing his crotch
-What?
-Goto-san!
-Never mind!
You think I shout a lot, right?
So uh...
What is it?
I brought a measuring device
A decibel meter?!
Decibels!!
They pick it up, and ring!
And do like peep peep
and it's like whoa and—
That hurtsaolin!
Hurtsaolin?
The power of nakedness
We're getting to 0 for sure
I'm gonna shout into this
And it'll show us the decibels
Well we have to do it then
Here I go
Here I go, yeah!
It broke!
Yeah! Whoa!
He's crazy
No way!
No way...
I broke it from being too loud
It exploded
Look at Junior
Yakko-san is out of it
-The decibels were too high...
-Really?
That's how powerful my voice is!
Leg passion!
You didn't even want me to try!
You were just gonna blow it up!
No, it just happened to break like that
You're taller, Master
Master Kiyoshi, you're huge
He grew up so much!
You're huge, Master Kiyoshi!
He's tall
No way!
What happened?
He's a talented boy, huh?
Now you can talk
Thank you so much
You suck at impressions
You're skeletal
And he does suck at this
You're so lanky
it's gross
Sorry, I've never seen this
I'm gonna go lickity lick!
Lickity Lick Boom!
Lickity Boom!
He went insane
We're going insane!
Isn't it okay to go insane?!
What was that?!
-Let's do this.
-Let's do what?!
Don't you think
I have huge lung capacity?
I have no clue
You have goosebumps
I'm not a goose, I'm a phoenix!
Blah Pikipiki do you have pistachios for brains?
-You went too far, idiot.
-Ah, my power!
Want me to bring you down?
Let's do this
First we plug this in
Sunsha-in!!
Open your mouth, please
It's pretty strong
So...
That's rough
We connect it to the hose,
and in this end that goes into my mouth,
We pour some liquid
And if I push it back, I win
Like this...
Alright then, let's do it
Keep it pressed
until it's off my mouth
Ah, alright
I think vertically works better
Like this?
That makes it stronger
This is annoying.
Here I go
Red nipple!
Put it in!
Sunshine!
What's that?
Can you drink that?!
I don't have to drink it,
I just have to...
Make sure it doesn't get there
Right
So that's how it is, huh?
I think the tomato juice
might end up looking
Like blood spilling from the sides
I'm in a risky position as well then
So we're seeing who has better
lung capacity.
That's right
Alright, let's do it
Right
Here I go
One, two...
NO way!
Whoa!
No way!
Huh?
Hey, have you seen my wallet?
I can't find it
He's an old man
This right here?
Is it this one?
Right, right.
Your wallet
Who's that?
Yeah, my wallet.
This is a sauce jar
I'm gonna smash
your head in with a log!
Whoa!
Can you please do it?
It's getting scary
Why are you doing that?
Why could he doing that?
That was amazing
Too much
It was too much
I thought it was amazing
You know this person?
I don't really know them
I don't know them
Really?
She's getting ignored
Fast-paced stuff is better now
What's he doing?
He's attacking.
What's that?
You can do that?
That's great
But can he do it in three minutes?
That one's from the game, right?
Yeah, the same one
We gather everyone
In three minutes?
We only have three minutes left
The pitch gets higher
with less water
How long is he gonna keep that up?
So delicious
Why did you waste our time here?
Yeah, he's got a point
On point
Ah, look at Madame Cat
Yakko-san, one moment
There's something I wanna do
no matter what
And I'd like to do it today
What?
You see I've never...
wrestled with a woman
So I wanna experience it
at least once
That's dangerous
Let's do it
Yakko-san will be fine, right?
Let's do it. I've done it for Itte Q anyway. (EN: 11)
Right!
Female wrestling
That's dangerous
Alright, ready?
Excuse me...
Here we go!
Start!
What's this?
Watch out, watch out!
It hurts, I'm going to...
Watch out
-Did you piss yourself?
-No...
She pissed herself
-She pissed herself?
-Are you alright?
I just heard her say she was going to..
Hey, you were
touching her chest, right?
No, I wasn't
You just did it like...
I didn't. Just her neck
-That's very serious!
-I only touched her neck
Because she was gonna fall
Don't squeeze Oniyakko-san's neck, man
The neck is serious business
Stop wrestling already
I'm sorry
This is serious!
Alright
One minute left
Here we go
They can still do it
One last effort!
You can do it!
Can I be Goku when Krillin died?
Sure
You're gonna act?
Do it, man
Are you talking...
Do something already
Are you talking about Krillin?!
Why did you wanna do that?
As a last gag?
Impressions are good
I don't even know
what they're doing
Impressions
Are you talking about Krillin?
Have you watched it?
Are you talking about Krillin?!
Are you talking about Krillin...?
Look at Goto-san
Are you talking about Krillin?!
-The 20 million...
-Are you talking about Krillin?!
All this for 20 million
You don't have to say it too
Are you talking about Krillin...?
Are you talking about Krillin?!
I'm sure no one's watched Dragon Ball
You're all shouting and stuff
But Junior-san hasn't read Dragon Ball
So it's all gibberish to him
Is that true?
No Japanese ever
No Japanese hasn't watched Dragon Ball
What now?!
Alright, let's deliberate
First time I've stayed till the end
I didn't notice
That was short
Good job, everyone!
That was great!
It really was
a deadly duel
I thought a little more time
would've been better
But these are the rules
we decided.
We have a winner.
Whoa, 20 million!
The person who gets the 20 million is...
Kubota!
No way!
20 million revenge!
Good for you, man
No way!
That's so good!
He got them back!
He did it!
The guy came back for his money!
He did it for this!
Can I really? I'm sorry...
He's crying over 20 million!
I think it's the first time I've cried like this
He got them back!
Well, that's right.
He came back for them
So good!
That's amazing!
That's good.
He got them back after so long
You deserve it!
I'm sorry
In any case, congratulations Kubota!
Congratulations!
Back to back!
I'm back, baby!
I said I couldn't die yet!
Time and time again
Maybe I should give a lecture
Thank you so much
Thank you very much, to you all
I didn't even cry at the M-1.
This is a first.
I cried at the end.
I'm sorry
He's crying over 20 million!
I wanna tell everyone
That even trash like me
Should aim to get some big cash
That's what I'd like to say
Good job
Good job, you guys
That was incredible
Yeah, you're right
It was a really close call.
It was very, very close.
Well, only Ikezaki and Kubota were clean
So it was those two
Here I go, yeah!
I broke it!
Sorry, I came here to lick
Lickity lick boom!
These guys are insane
But Ikezaki didn't get
as many points as Kubota
But I thought Ikezaki's
Stunt games were
incredibly fun.
But other people didn't react much
Gag balloon!
Not just the players
but the staff weren't laughing either
So I thought maybe
I was in the minority
You lose if you laugh
No one's laughing
So if you...
Yeah, but that goes
for Documental as a whole
What an unnecessary explanation
Is this guy stupid?
That's just the rules
The size of those briefs was just...
I never imagined that!
And the ball was like
completely black too!
You can just expose
anyone who complains.
That's weird
Like this on a video.
Like getting back at them?