Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!
To put it simply, we got...
into a bit of trouble.
Trouble?
In any case, it was vulgar.
That's not
the first time, though.
We used to think that Amazon
was this bottomless pit,
and everything went.
We don't know either,
so we want to find out today
what went wrong with you guys.
You're the worst, man.
Here we go!
I was cleaning up
and found this porno.
Show me!
It's one of these mags
That's nostalgic!
From long ago
And there's this older girl
She's an old hag!
Naoka...
Jimmy-san!
You like it?
That's quite...
Quite mature!
She's in her 50's.
Just perfect!
She's pissing?
Outside, right?
Seems like she's taking a big piss.
I mean, you like who you like.
I love this!
I'm crazy for her!
You like it...?
Is it wrong
if I like this?
She's thick.
This is good!
She's too hairy
It suited people back then.
—Take a look
I'm doing that.
She's stepping all over
her own piss, man.
But old pictures are good.
It's nice that girls back then
were thick and hot.
Way better.
Can you step aside?
You're pretty direct.
You've been all serious
for a while.
No, I just
respect my elders.
That's why you were
acting all formal?
That's enough.
You're too good.
Your humor's too good.
For real, you're brilliant.
Wanna team up?
Team up?
What about Rossy? (Editor's Note: 1)
There you go again, man.
Can I show something to you guys?
It's one picture.
I got a small envelope in the mail.
My real name is Sasaki, right? (EN: 2)
—My address was at the top.
—You're Sasaki?
Then what's Nadal?
—I'm Nadal.
—I'm talking about me.
Sorry.
Aiura...
Don't say my name out loud
what if I have a kid eventually?
Well... let's look at the picture then.
Can-can you
drop the glasses already?
What?
They distract me.
Are these weird?
I always have these on.
I showed them to you,
didn't I?
I had them on for sure.
What do you mean?
What do you think?
They look like a mosaic!
A mosaic?
Not at all.
He always looks like this.
Sorry...
Take a good look.
You're looking at me!
I'm looking at him!
Look at him.
I am!
Look at his mouth as well.
What?
What's wrong,
Jimmy-san?
Look at his teeth now.
He laughed.
What's going on?
Why did you do that then?
You turned it on me!
Even though
there were other funnier moments!
What the hell?
What are you doing?
There were funnier moments.
What made you laugh?
When he told me to see his teeth.
I looked at them .
So of course I laughed!
Of course not!
You don't laugh with just some teeth!
He was like "look at my teeth"!
So Matsumoto-san,
maybe you already noticed,
he laughed with that
the other time as well.
For real?!
You suck at this!
Let's put some pubes around the mouth.
Who put
these pubes here?
This is bad. Who was it?
It's pretty bad, man!
You can't put pubes
around your master's mouth!
This is definitely
unacceptable, for sure!
Huh? Kubota...
Ready?
I wonder if I can
do something like this
with Amazon?
That's definitely
Matsuda Seiko!
That's Matsuda Seiko!
Besides, Kubota has
always had those glasses!
These.
Sometimes stuff backfires
and I think I screwed up.
I don't care...
You're looking at me!
I'm looking at him!
I am!
Look at his mouth as well.
What?
What's wrong, Jimmy-san?
Look at his teeth.
He laughed.
You were smiling all along.
I was thinking that
I should press the button anyway.
Damn
I'm starting to feel
bad as well.
—That's too quick!
—That's too harsh!
Alright, alright
But you were smiling
at any random crap, man!
I thought it was funny!
So that's one point for Kubota.
Alright, yellow.
Kubota
hasn't done anything.
I looked at his teeth!
Teeth are normal!
You have a gap.
So when he first
showed them to me
See? It's funny!
What's funny about that?
This isn't even the main act.
The picture...
I want to see!
So I got a small envelope
with my address on it.
And then
What?
Huh? Huh? (EN: 3)
Whoa!
For real?!
That's creepy!
I wanted the Special Defense Force to
open it for me.
You haven't opened it?
I did, eventually...
So what was inside?
Two thick books.
Huh? Books?
I can't say.
Why?
You read Pro Golfer Monkey recently? (EN: 4)
Where?
In the streets
The streets?
You like golf, right?
You just burped, Inada?
I did.
Sorry, it's just that...
Inada has been looking
out of it.
Are you okay?
I'm nervous, so I have some
phlegm in my throat.
It's been stuck there
all this time.
Why don't you
just let it all out?
It's all stuck there
at the back like...
What?
What was that, Koumoto-san?
It's stuck at the back
so it won't just come out!
Inada didn't say that.
What are you gonna do?
What's that? Inada?
For real?
I didn't say that.
Uh, yeah, sorry
I got a new manager
A guy named Maki from Yoshimoto.
I know him, I know him!
From Yuriyan...
Yeah, exactly!
And Honoka-chan from a call-girl service. (Sex service)
Huh? What?
Honoka-chan from a call-girl service.
Honoka-chan?
I know her.
She's that M girl, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
How long does she take?
90 minutes.
How many orgasms?
Around three or so.
That's a lot, huh?
One every 30 minutes?
That's serious...
Mine is also 90 minutes.
How many times?
Around 25.
25?
That's so much bullshit.
You got the number wrong.
Stop... lying, man.
I'm sure it's just once.
For real how many times?
Just one.
Don't order 90 minutes, okay?
So the three times...
The three times is for real.
So she wrote a message.
Yeah, right here.
Onishi-san
thank you for today.
It was really fun.
Let's play together again.
I'm here on the weekends.
She liked you?
You hit it off?
She means "play"
in private, right?
No, she didn't give me
her number.
There it is!
This is just
the store's number.
- Why don't you call?
- It's the store's number.
Let's call right now.
No, no!
That's the store's number!
I haven't called yet!
No, no, no!
You should call.
Uh... next is Shimbashi.
Hayama-san.
Look! It's Hayama-san!
Hayama-san from Shimbashi.
That's a last name?
That's a name?
For real!
This is Hayama-san from Shimbashi.
You used it?
You used it right?
You did?
You used the coupon?
I'm asking if you did.
Did you use it, man?!
What are you talking about?
You used it, right?
You used it?
See?!
What was that?
I don't get this.
This sucks.
You shouldn't say that!
What happened?
You were so close.
That was a long time ago
I was told to use it.
It was a used discount coupon
that he gave to me...
You have it here?
You promised you wouldn't tell!
You used the coupon?
I'm asking if you did.
Did you use it, man?!
What are you talking about?
You used it, right?
You used it?
See?!
You were too close though,
for real.
Like Sigourney Weaver
with the alien.
Too close!
Breathing on his nose.
Well, Koumoto did try
to hold it in.
This is a yellow.
That's rough!
And a point for Jimmy-chan.
He's pretty scary.
He came in strong today.
He did.
Also, what was that
30 minute thing, Nadal?
For real...
I'm working on it.
I've been failing
pretty hard so far.
Hate to admit it, though.
That hurts to say.
You didn't have to!
Here we go!
That was close!
It worked out.
So was it an accident?
You didn't know Koumoto-san was here
so it was by chance...
I had it with me by chance.
Because Jimmy didn't know
Koumoto would be here.
- I think I got lucky today.
- You're good Jimmy-san.
Not to mention he had
one and then another.
And he called me over
right this way for it.
I knew I had it with me,
I knew I did.
Still talking about that?
So wanna play the
tofu woodblock...
The tofu woodblock game?
Tofu woodblock game?
What's that?
You stack up tofu like this!
Get a dish!
It's already on the table!
Are we gonna eat these later?
I'll prepare miso later.
Liar!
I'll get some more.
More tofu?
It's not just this.
Cut it
cut it in half, okay?
- You have bad manners.
- The table's getting dirty!
What manners?
- What?
- No, no, no...
- What's wrong?
- No, no, no... it's okay
- Where are you going?
- Bad manners...
The table's all sticky,
are there any wipes?
What's wrong?
The world is
all out of tapioca! (EN: 5)
all out of tapioca!
Out of tapioca
over the world!
The world is out of
The world is
all out of tapioca!
There's no more tapioca
no more, oh no!
The world is
all out of tapioca!
Tapioca still exists...
The world is
all out of tapioca
We need tapioca.
The world is all out of tapioca!
We're out of tapioca!
We need tapioca!
What's with those glasses?
He's allergic?
What do we do?
I have withdrawal syndrome.
You want to eat some?
I can't stand it anymore!
I need stuff running up the straw!
Bear with it!
I can't stand it
if no balls are going up this straw!
Withdrawal!
We're out
we're out of tapioca!
Wait, wait
Does this work?
As long as it goes up the straw.
It won't though.
The size is all wrong.
It's soft.
With a tapioca straw?
There it is!
It's working?
Ouch!
Whoa... that's something!
It won't go up the straw!
I need something bouncy!
We're out of tapioca!
What-what what about this?
I think we...
we had some tapioca!
You have tapioca?
I need something bouncy!
Anything works,
if it goes up the straw.
Here you go.
You're hairy.
I have some tapioca.
Thank you so much.
That stinks!
What's wrong?
It stinks!
The tapioca?
It stinks, yeah.
- Ouch.
- That stinks!
It's so stinky?
I want to touch.
No, don't worry, Ikko-san.
Are you going to stay as Ikko?
What?
No, just wondering if you are.
What? Who are you?
I'm Cookie.
I'm Ikko.
What's that?
Balls.
Can I touch them?
I don't really recommend it
but feel free to do so.
I want to give it a try.
There we go.
Fluffy!!!
Don't you have any tapioca,
Jimmy-san?
I have some.
Would my tapioca work?
Yes.
Mine?
My-My tapioca
It's prettier than expected.
For real.
I got a vasectomy.
Huh?
Really?
Was it expensive?
Around 300k yen.
That's expensive!
I didn't think the insurance
would cover it.
Of course.
Come on!
Ikko-san,
are you okay with this?
Okay? Okay?
I'll touch it.
So pretty...
Huh?
Ikko-san is touching him.
No way...
How much?!
Okay, okay, that's that.
"How much?" For real?
Ah, sorry.
What happened to you?
That's a big wound.
I've been sick.
No way, man.
Sick?
You wrap a bandage
around your rooster when you get sick?
Just call it a dick.
Rooster?
Okay, take care.
What about the tofu?
Let's play the tofu woodblock game!
The tofu woodblock game?
Wash your hands.
If you lose,
you have to get in here.
Where?
The pool?
If we lose?
If it falls, yeah.
It falls?
If the tofu falls.
If the tofu falls? Okay
I don't really care about this.
Why are you all running away?
What about the tofu?
Well, you're washing your hands, so
I don't have a towel.
I have one!
Do we need that much tofu?
I think we can all carry a lot.
We can carry a lot.
- So it's kind of like jenga?
- What's jenda?
- Jenga.
What's jenga?
You have a jenga right there.
Hamada-san has been...
- Jenga?
- A jenga.
With this, you lose if
You lost!
- You lost, you lost!
- No, no, no!
We haven't even said
"tofu game yay!"
- You lost, you lost.
- We didn't say it!
We haven't
But doing this is
practically impossible.
No, this is
totally impossible.
There's no way.
A blade...
Watch out, watch out!
Wait, wait
I'm cutting in half!
Watch out for wounds...
It's all a mess, man...
Cut them in half.
What about the money?
Okay everyone!
Tofu woodblock game yay!
We have to put them
on that place, right?
On this plate, yeah.
Take the lead.
Who should start?
What should I say?
Toshiba
- Toshiba?
- Toshiba....?
Tofu spinning game
Spinning game?
Tofu woodblock game.
We have to synchronize the yay at
tofu woodblock game yay!
With the right hand?
Tofu woodblock game!
Yay!
Clap clap! I go first.
Clap clap!
I go first
We go around like that.
Normally
Clockwise.
No, man! Stack it on top!
No way!
It's impossible!
Did you think this through?
Go back home!
I don't get it.
One, two...
Investment spinning game. Yay
Investment spinning?
Tofu spinning game
Wasn't it woodblock?
No, they're not woodblocks!
This is tofu!
You said woodblock game!
Tofu woodblock game
Tofu woodblock game yay!
We clap at the yay?
Right. Tofu woodblock game yay!
Clap clap yay!
On top?
What about the "me first"?
One from me.
One from Koba-san.
One from Cookie!
That's close! This is bad!
Damn it!
They're poorly cut.
- On top?
- No...
Huh?!
Can he put it next to it?
They're woodblocks, yeah.
On top on top on top on top!
Why not just next to it?
We'll lose right away!
We'll lose.
Not everyone will go.
Okay, let's do that.
- Where?
- Next to it!
You should be on house arrest
until you're 90, man!
I don't understand "90"
Why?!
- 90, right?
- 90 years old.
No, no,
wait a second.
You touched it!
- That's the one from cookie!
- Right!
- It's still on the place, so it's fine!
- You have to get in.
- I don't want to.
- You have to!
Ouch!
Come on!
Don't do that!
You have to get in!
It's still on top so it's fine!
That's no good!
This is a woodblock game!
Get in.
That's too cold!
That's the rules.
It's a woodblock game.
I've never heard
of anything like that!
You prepared it, did what you wanted
and now pour ice as you please?!
- That was just a test, right?
- That's how these games go.
So let's do this one for real.
Let's do this one for real.
Ah, watch out!
That's a boulder!
—Boulder?
—A boulder of ice?
That looks cold.
This is kinda...
Is it just the feet?
—No uh...
—Full body?
Well yeah...
without the mic of course.
Can we take off our clothes?
Can we leave them on?
Do what you want.
I think they'll be
really cold, though.
We going there?
You ready for that?
This is too harsh, man!
So if the tofu crumbles
we have to go in there?
That's that.
That's too much, right?
You go in,
and use this to pour more.
That's too cold, man!
We have to take the mic off.
You use this, get in
and then pour...
You went in.
I did, but, well...
Is it really cold?
I think it is.
What a mess of a game.
Why don't you take off
that cape?
Take off the cape.
This is too much.
Take this.
That stinks!
You just laughed right now!
You just laughed!
No one saw it?
He smelled.
And then laughed.
You even laughed out loud.
I don't get what makes you laugh.
You suck at this!
What makes him laugh?
I didn't see that coming.
He just laughed, right?
He laughed normally.
Let's take a look.
It was far too natural
and it's not like
you don't know the rules.
He laughed like he
didn't know them.
What a mess of a game.
Why don't you take off
that cape?
Take off the cape.
This is too much.
Take this.
That stinks!
What happened?
What was so funny?
No, I was just off guard,
let me off the hook!
What's your deal?
For real!
Just let me off the hook!
Alright, here we go.
That's the second one.
But you have to do it at least once
that tofu thing
The woodblock?
I'll do it properly.
And they're all stacked
so I don't know which
the main one is.
The first one.
They're stacked
as a default setting.
Give it a try,
do it properly.
Because this is getting annoying.
Let's start again.
Do it once.
Wanna use some kitchen paper?
If you do this...
That works.
The first time was fine, though.
Yeah, I thought
cutting them was a bad idea.
Now we have this much.
I see...
Why are you looking
so deflated?!
He's also
really pissed off right now!
I'm the same as always,
I was just thinking.
You're so depressed!
Wait!
Stop trying to
bring me down!
No, no
no one's doing that!
You're self destructing!
Alright, let's go!
Like Matsumoto-san said
this is too unstable,
let's do this.
Huh? Why?
It'll be hard to stack them.
That's the point
of the game.
Is that size okay?
Wait wait,
stack them right...
Wanna give it a try?
Ready?
They're unstable cut like that
so maybe this...
Tofu yay yay,
tofu yay yay
That's not it.
What's that "tofu yay yay" bullshit?
One yay too many.
I go next.
Like a demonstration?
Between them?
No, no, no.
We're all doing it.
With these new rules?
That was Nadal's test, right?
No, I think this won't work.
Let's do it like this.
That's too hard to stack.
That's fine, though!
Let's do it once.
Tofu woodblock game yay!
Yay!
Jimmy clap clap!
You say your name?
I don't remember the name.
Kobayashi
This is more stable, so...
You have to say your name
We should use bigger ones.
I'll do it like this.
Cookie!
I guess I'll use this one.
And make another foundation.
So gentle.
This looks bad!
That's dangerous!
Akiyama!
This is bad!
I can choose anything?
Even a tiny one, yeah!
As long as it's there,
anything goes!
Whichever's fine.
Watch out!
Watch out!!
This one?
Wait a second-
Akiyama-san?
No, that's my fault?
That was Akiyama's
No, that'll happen
if we stand around chatting.
Okay, Akiyama.
Of course not!
I mean, you moved the table
with your dick right now!
That was Akiyama's
That was Akiyama's yeah.
We need to decide a time limit
because it collapses with time.
Like just after stacking yours?
Yeah, right.
Otherwise we'll just talk and it'll fall.
That's so,
because tofu is soft.
I kinda get
what he means, though.
I do too
Okay, choose a time span, Nadal.
Alright. Ten seconds?
Ten seconds between what and what?
What's the limit?
Why not two seconds?
Let's do ten.
It's your game!
You should choose!
Bang bang and three seconds.
Sorry
—Bang bang and
- Sorry.
Bang bang?
Wasn't it clap clap?
What's going on?!
We need to
unify the chanting as well.
If we get anything wrong
Jimmy-san goes in.
Let's do that!
The rules are all messed up
so Jimmy goes in.
That's too cruel, man!
Alright, five seconds then.
Who starts?
Let's go with Kubota.
Just go with the chant.
Let's go
Tofu woodblock game yay!
First tofu
Ah, Kubota, you're out.
You have to say your name.
My name?
You didn't say it.
So if you don't say your name
you're out?
You have to say it.
I'm gonna cry.
Maybe I should kill you
Huh?
—Kill...?
—Let's go again.
That's good.
Ah, shut up man.
You were gonna kill him?
Let's go
I'll kill you...
He's kinda...
I haven't said anything!
Get serious already
I didn't say anything man!
—Did he say something?
—Yeah.
It stinks!
"Tochu"...
So I have to start, right?
Shut up, man.
What's "tochu"?
Aren't you out
JImmy-san?
You said "tochu", didn't you?
Okay, out!
So I'm out?
Let's get in.
You okay, Jimmy-san?
You should pump up your heartbeat first.
Watch out, watch out!
- Come on!
- This is bad!
That's scary!
Go on, go on!
You go this deep
What?!
Watch out, watch out!
Thank you
That's how it is.
Thank you, Kubota
Sorry, for real
Thanks for showing me
how kind you can be.
You should get closer
Thank you, man!
Thank you too
Don't get so close!
Don't get close, I'll kill you!
I'm thanking you,
sorry for everything!
Sorry
Don't get closer
I'll kill you for real
For real, thank you
I'm gonna kill him
sorry, here I go
Ouch!
That's hot!
Who was it?
Nadal, right?
Damn it!
I haven't even done anything!
It was hot?
That was too hot!
Come on,
that's too much!
It really is,
damn it!
That was weird.
When did it happen?
It was weird.
What's the big idea?
- Nadal!
- So it was me after all?!
Don't get closer!
Don't get closer,
I'll kill you!
I'm thanking you,
sorry for everything!
Sorry
Don't get closer,
I'll kill you for real
Sorry, really
I'm gonna kill him
sorry, here I go
Ouch!
That's hot!
Hot?! How is that hot?!
That gets hot?!
It does!
There's no way!
That's hot?
It is!
Gunpowder's hot
Jimmy-san's reactions
are always so...
I feel like he'd call anything hot.
So I thought he was saying
some nonsense.
You're right.
It's what it is.
Well, I guess...
you could stop or keep going.
Let's get one round done!
Let's get serious!
At least until he's still here!
I'm still here!
Huh?
I said I'm here!
But you'll be gone.
Pretty soon, yeah.
No way! I'm right here!
In like five minutes.
No way, no way!
Can we at least get serious
just one time and do this?
Here we go!
Let's do this!
We just have to stack them,
and that's it, right?
Yeah, just stack them.
With our names, right?
You say your name,
and stack them.
A name and then stack.
Yell it loudly!
Here we go
Tofu woodblock game yay!
Ikko
Soshina
Bald doll
Bald doll?
Okay, stop.
You're more than that.
Well, I'm balding.
What about your jaw or your skin?
Balding comes third, yeah.
My skin is fine already.
It's really not.
It's getting worse!
And the jaw?
My jaw sticks out a little.
Sticks out like a sore thumb.
Besides, you're not balding.
- I have more hair, but also less.
- What?
It comes and goes.
- Just leave it at Inada.
- Understood.
Say your own name.
Do it again, then.
Let's do it again!
From the start.
Okay, Matsuo-san.
Let's do it from Cookie!
Why me?
This is completely impossible.
He came up with the game,
and only just did something?
He sucks!
I want to see Cookie do it!
Alright, I'll do it.
But Nadal hasn't stacked his yet.
-You want to, right?
-Neither have I.
Do I still go now?
You haven't done it,
but I'm still next?
Me, Koumoto-san, Cookie.
Let's do that.
But Koumoto wants me
to go next, right?
What's with your tone, man?
Wanna do it, Nadal?
You all sound weird.
I want Cookie to go next.
You wanna go, right?!
After me, then.
Try again.
"Try again"?
Wait, what's this?
What's going on?
Why are we rotating?
-I want Cookie to go next!
-Let's go.
-I want Cookie to go next.
-That's it.
I want Cookie to go next, 'kay?!
What's with you?
You wanna go?
Rock, paper, schizzles!
Whoever wins
gets another try, 'kay?!
And turn arizzle, 'kay?!
I don't get it,
so I can't laugh.
That was close!
That was really close!
Ready, Cookie-san?
I go next?
I put this here, right?
Do I take it?
-Let's go from the "yay"
-Ah, right.
The cheer,
Jimmy-san.
Okay...
Tofu woodblock game, yay!
So underwhelming.
Ikuina Akiko
Huh?
No, man.
That's so wrong.
Cookie-san.
But Inada was spacing out,
so I could do that.
I wasn't spacing out.
Use yer right name.
What're ya doin'?
We're not playin' at all.
The hell you doin'?
Don't get that mad.
Jimmy-san, let's go.
We're not playin'!
Who was this?
What's with this tofu woodblock game?
Well, uh...
We just have to stack five of them.
Five?!
All of us?!
What's with this game?
What's fun about this?!
A game of just five blocks?
Um... I guess...
It's ordering others around.
That's the charm?
Let's do that, then.
So I just have to stack
five of them?
Who are they fighting?
You do it,
if you lose here!
"You"? Call me Cookie, man.
Cookie, do it!
Aren't these four already?
This is the last one.
This might work.
Just five seconds, right?
-And then...
-Five seconds, right?
There we go.
Five seconds after letting go?
Let go, let go!
Wait after letting go!
Let go!
Wait up!!
Let go, man!
Isn't he moving them?
Why are you doing that?
Let go already!
Cookie, you can let go.
Jimmy-san, penalize him!
In five seconds.
Cookie, let go!
Wait, wait,
wait wait wait!
I'll be the only one losing!
I'm keeping it in place,
it'll bounce if I let go.
Let go.
I'm telling you
it's gonna bounce for sure!
Let go, and raise your hands.
Just shut up,
and do it.
Why do I have to
lose no matter what?
It'll bounce if I let go!
What do you mean bounce?
Tofu doesn't bounce!
Let go, man!
Cookie, let go, Cookie!
Jimmy-san,
penalize him already!
With one hand?
Or both hands?
What?
Can I use both hands?
Let go already!
I'm not talking about that!
I'm asking if I can
use both hands!
Sure.
Really?!
Five seconds
after pushing down?
No way!
Let go!
Then tell us the fucking rules!
You can't do that!
Let go!
Are you fucking daft?!
You have to let go, man!
You're dumb as a brick.
You can't use both hands.
Just one!
You said it was okay!
You said I could
use both hands!
I told you to let go.
Let go, man.
Why do I have to carry the loss?
You're gonna lose?
"Carry the loss" isn't a nice way
to put it.
Why did you decide I would be
carrying it, then?
You said we should
stack them in fives!
It's gonna bounce, man!
It'll only bounce if you put pressure!
-Why are you doing that?
-Here we go.
You still have to wait five seconds
after letting go.
What happens if I win
after five seconds?
If you win, it's over.
I want it to end already.
Please end this.
Can we count the five seconds quicker?
I might die
for you bastards!
With that speed?
Yeah, it's quick.
I'm letting go, okay?
Here I go.
Wait
He only needs to let the right hand go.
Do it.
It's a really unstable balance.
It's gonna work!
This really feels like
playing jenga, seriously.
Wait, wait!
Don't do that!
No way!
It was gonna fall!
I'm not gonna let it fall.
No, no,
then you have to go in.
Are you stupid?
It worked!
It's gonna work!
1 2 3...
You can't touch it!
Wait, Koumoto-san.
Okay, done.
I haven't laughed.
Damn it!
It's working, it's working!
It's working!
That was long.
Why did it work?!
What's with this game?
Okay, so there were two people...
It might've been both,
or just one.
Cookie or Nadal!
I didn't smile, for real!
Nadal definitely smiled at some point!
No, that was just because
Cookie-san smiled!
You did because he smiled?
Nadal doesn't want to accept
he smiled!
It was just since that
beep beep sound started!
What "beep beep" sound?
The siren?!
I had never heard that.
There it is!
It's gonna work!
1 2 3...
You can't touch it!
Wait, Koumoto-san.
Okay, it's done!
He's smiling!
He's definitely smiling!
Okay, now what?!
To be honest,
I brought the most weapons with me!
No, no, no, you were just smiling!
In any case, Cookie, here...
Orange!
There it is.
One for the champion.
Nadal is still safe.
I'm gonna watch out from now on!
After what Cookie did, right?
Whose point was that?
It's hard to tell.
I laughed at myself.
So I can get a point.
What's with that?
Hmm...
It was pretty decent.
Looking back, yeah.
It was pretty good, actually.
What a polite
Documental!
For real
nothing seemed out of place.
It felt just right!
Admirable Japanese behavior.
Elegant and graceful.
My book was fine as well?
It was pretty high quality.
That's just a part
of Japanese culture!
I think Amazon-san would be glad
to import something like that.
It was a good show.
High class humor.
High class humor?!
With that picture book,
It kinda makes you want to
invite friends to see it.
Tell them to come right away.
That's great!