[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
I guess the show that is Documental has started to distance itself from the world of pure comedy and started to delve into the more mainstream world of entertainment.
-It's been a while!
-Shingo!
I think it's great to have comedians and actors mingling together.
We didn't want to limit ourselves so we just went all out.
Anyone can participate.
It doesn't matter what gender they are.
Even kids can participate.
And at the very end I would love to see a chimpanzee in there as well.
About last season...
You guys have to laugh hard when I say that.
I mean, you have to tell me that's too much!
A chimpanzee is too much.
There's no way we'd get that.
Actually I was the first to come in.
Did you guys hear any voices before coming in?
Everyone was laughing when I came in.
You three were laughing.
Kazunori is trying to do something.
He's fishing for: "Is he sleeping?".
It's Kazunori's first time.
-That part looks a bit like my home.
-Oh, really?
I was desperate.
You can't be doing that!
I mean, this is just a yellow card.
You chuckled!
You went like this!
Our first 1-minute laugh!
He might be the fastest dropout.
Only one minute passed!
But I think that was just an unavoidable reflex.
-Right.
-It's really dangerous.
I couldn't stop it.
We're all here together...
Alright, here we go.
Start!
Is the Oyakata gonna be alright?
He's in trouble for sure.
Look, he's already grinning.
He might also remember what he laughed about and do it again.
No one's talking.
Kazunori is sleepy.
-He's setting something up.
-He is.
Kazunori is sleepy.
-He's setting something up.
-He is.
He's been doing that this whole time but Musaka always gets in his way.
Well, sure.
Don't say that.
Should we put these in the locker room?
Right.
Everyone, you have to look at Katsunori!
No one's looking at him.
Yeah.
He looks so sad.
He's trying to do it again!
And everyone's gone!
Well...
They all went, huh?
We have to be careful.
If they were all comedians they'd stick around and see what happens.
That's the scary part about this iteration of the show.
That's right.
This kind of odd situation will keep happening.
Us comedians would realize what he's doing.
-Right, we'd know he's trying to do something.
-Yeah.
Us comedians would realize what he's doing.
-Right, we'd know he's trying to do something.
-Yeah.
So...
Huh?
Here he comes.
I took off my hat.
How's that?
How is it?
What do you think of that?
No way...
It's pretty funny.
It's funny.
If I was in there I would hate this.
I usually wear this.
The bags under his eyes are way too big!
They are crazy!
I mean, the wig does accentuate the bags under his eyes.
Right.
-He's trying so hard.
-Those bags under his eyes...
Oyakata is trying really hard.
But it might be a bit big for me.
Don't you think?
It's perfect.
Really?
Yes.
Oyakata is in trouble.
Yeah, he is.
Oyakata is always in trouble.
-His face is swinging up and down.
-Back and forth.
He really is.
He's putting on more stuff?
More stuff?
He's pointing! (EN: 1)
He's pointing!
Ouch!
Whoa, that startled me!
Sorry.
I'm glad I was wearing the helmet.
Yes.
-He went all out!
He hit him full force.
I can't believe he hit Musaka.
That was a good one.
Did they say we could drink anything?
Yes.
Right, they also said we could cook.
Should I cook?
Yeah, you look like you can cook.
Yeah, he can definitely cook.
I also want to see him cook.
Look at Oyakata.
He's already a goner.
Oyakata is having a lot of trouble.
He's in a daze.
Sorry about that.
-I want to get acquainted with this place already.
-Me too!
To this scenery and space.
-It's actually bigger than I imagined.
-It is.
I don't know why, but Oyakata just used a single sword to stab the bearded pirate.
For real.
That's so random...
Why?
I have no clue.
-That's so random.
-Did he stab the barrel?
I have no clue.
-That's so random.
-Did he stab the barrel?
Why? He's all alone.
I would have totally laughed if I'd seen that from a distance.
He's doing all of that alone.
3 years is a long time...
Yeah... Well...
Did you guys meet 3 years ago?
Yes, it was 3 years ago.
A balloon?
And it was in the middle of work too.
It's a whoopee cushion!
-Oyakata.
-He's inflating it a bit too much.
That's such an old gag!
And his lung capacity is zero!
Musaka is nowhere to be seen.
So slow!
He's so slow!
-You're right.
-He's taking so long!
He's going again.
Oh no.
He's dizzy!
-What the heck is he doing?
-He's getting dizzy.
So weak!
He's so weak!
I would have burst out laughing if I'd seen him.
So? What's he gonna do now?
What will he do?
Who is gonna be the victim?
-Oh, he's doing it himself.
-Right.
He did it to himself and almost laughed!
Oyakata, did you fart?
Yes.
I see.
He asked: "Did you fart?"
And he responded: "Yes."
He did it to himself and almost laughed.
But that was such a great sounding fart!
I would have laughed ages ago! I would be totally useless in there.
He should try it again!
I would never be able to hold back there. They are all so good!
- Looks like Katori is struggling too.
- It's so hard!
He's going again!
Whoopee cushion, second try.
Oyakata is crazy!
Will I ever get comfortable in this room?
Musaka is still gone.
-What will he do next?
-He's quite heavy.
He's quite heavy so it makes a great sound.
He's inflating it again.
Is he gonna sit on it again?
He's a big guy.
It's gonna make a big sound.
It didn't do anything.
It didn't.
No one's even looking at him!
It didn't go off...
No one heard it.
The cushion!
Kamiji is in trouble!
It's not working!
The cushion!
Kamiji is in such trouble!
They did so well not to laugh!
Again?
That's fine.
-Right.
-But I think this is good for him.
It's not working.
He's got no lungs.
But I think it's smart to capitalize here.
He's still going.
It's not inflating.
Why can't he get it to inflate?
Oyakata's whoopee cushion is not working.
Oh really?
I've been wondering about that.
He got it.
Oh, he's going for it.
Again?
It's already full!
He's so slow!
You can't inflate it anymore, man!
-No way...
-Here it comes.
He's gonna laugh!
Someone's gotta laugh!
It's not making a sound, huh?
It's not.
Nobody's laughing!
Hiro! Look at Hiro!
Is he okay?
He's running away.
Hiro!
Hiro is running away.
It got torn off.
It did?
What?
He's too heavy!
The whoopee cushion broke?
Yes.
That's why he couldn't fully inflate it.
I think it broke in the first try.
Yeah...
There he is.
Truly! Truly funny!
- Truly! Truly funny!
- He did his research!
- Takashi is in trouble!
- Truly! Truly funny!
- He did his research!
- Takashi is in trouble!
- Evil eye!
- He did his research!
Evil eye!
His appearance hasn't changed much.
I mean, his face is the same.
It really hasn't.
I'm getting sleepy!
Oyakata is in trouble.
He really did his research.
Evil eye!
What was that?
What is he doing?
Why is he hitting himself?
He's so kind.
I'm getting sleepy!
Ouch!
Who's that?
Is he okay? Did he hold it in?
-Katsu is in trouble!
-He's really going for it.
Katsu didn't crack.
Look at those tattoos.
What?
Who's that?
- Katsunori was in trouble there.
- And Oyakata too!
- That was close!
Kamiji was also about to crack.
Have you been doing it for long?
I started in my third year of high school.
So, 3 years?
You didn't do music before that?
No, not at all.
Oyakata is so proactive!
He really is!
You had no interest?
-That's so surprising!
-He's very aggressive!
You had no interest?
-That's so surprising!
-He's very aggressive!
Well, I think I must have been in middle school...
Again?!
He left, didn't he?
He watched it!
Right?
He watched Documental!
Can you play?
Huh?
-Kinda...
-Huh?
-Oh, Oyakata is asking him.
-Please teach me.
He's shining the spotlight on Hiro.
-I didn't think he'd be so thoughtful.
-Me either.
There's lots of different chords.
Kazunori is still sleeping.
Again?
Can you teach me an easy one?
He really wants to do that gag.
-He must have something up his sleeve!
-He really wants to do that gag.
Here and here.
You place your fingers here.
And then you get a 'power chord'.
Power chord?
It's a really easy one.
And then you can strum.
Like this?
Here and... This one's a bit hard...
You leave one open and place your fingers here.
Here and here.
He's teaching him.
Good.
Oh, you've got it!
Thank you.
What was that?
What the heck was that?
What was that?!
I thought he had something planned!
And he just leaves.
That's it?
That was it.
I see... I see...
We've got tons of different gags coming up.
Right.
It hasn't even been 15 minutes yet.
Hiro just can't move.
Look at Musaka.
Musaka is still going at it.
He looks the same.
He really does.
It was starting to hurt.
It's been a while since I've seen you, Shingo.
So I want to show you something cute.
What is it?
I have an amazing trick.
Katsunori, look.
Oyakata, please come and have a look.
You go like this.
Magic?
This is really hard to pull off, you know?
Here, I have a normal glass.
Like Wes-P? (EN: 2)
I think so.
Or like 5Gap. (EN: 3)
I'm a baldie so it slides right off my head.
It's gonna be hard.
You gotta add some water.
Right, he should add water.
It's gonna be hard.
You gotta add some water.
Right, he should add water.
Don't think he'll make it.
Shingo, here I come.
No way.
I knew that would happen.
Damn it!
One more.
It's pretty hard to pull off.
Cause it's too light.
Right, he has to add some weight.
I can definitely do it.
Really?
No way... Can he really do it?
Oh, he did it.
Amazing.
-That was amazing.
-Right? That's crazy.
I didn't think you'd succeed.
He did it... But so what?
Right?
It's not funny at all.
Musaka, please try it again with this.
Really?
This?
Can I do it wearing this?
Oh, the top...
I don't think this is gonna work.
It's not that different.
I... Well...
I don't know, but let's give it a shot.
I don't think I can pull it off.
This actually fits you perfectly.
I mean, this part is the same.
Oh, right.
You think so?
Hold on...
Okay.
But it's plastic...
I'll give it the good old try.
Huh?
It fell off already?
It's not staying on, right?
What's this sound?
It's like a Sumo Jinku. (EN: 4)
It really sounds like that.
Which means...
Oyakata?
It fell off.
I knew it couldn't be done.
I knew it.
My own head is way better.
He's making funny faces!
Funny faces!
Funny faces?!
It's funny faces after the whoopee cushion?!
And he's got the worst comedic timing, too!
Right?
He should have done it at the end of the song!
I thought he called me.
This might be a disadvantage for him.
Right.
Oh, the next one, right?
The next one.
Here it comes.
-Oh you're right.
-You're right.
He's got it all planned out.
Funny face.
-It's just another series of funny faces.
-Right.
It's funny faces.
He's pretty old school, isn't he?
Like he was only allowed to joke around in his elementary school days.
Oyakata?
Does he think that's funny?
Right.
Those faces are not funny at all!
I mean, that's the funny part for us.
I wish he'd stop.
Right, he should have stopped.
He's done?!
He was very expressive in the ring.
I used to watch his matches.
Thank you!
That was very precious.
Thank you.
Were you doing impressions?
No.
I was making funny faces.
Funny faces?
-Yes.
-He's brought that thing out again.
Isn't it broken already?
You don't have to.
It doesn't make a sound anymore, does it?
Alright.
It's fine.
-It's already broken.
-It's broken.
Oyakata and Musaka's gags overlapped.
Right.
Right, right, right.
Right, the timings.
With this?
Yes. Oyakata did his funny faces as you were about to do your trick.
Oh my.
Then, I should have waited for Oyakata to do his act first.
-I would have totally cracked up if it was me in there.
-Yeah, me too.
Right?
Those funny faces, man.
He's going full offensive.
Katsunori's sleeping.
Look at Katsunori.
Katsunori is trying that thing again?
Look at him! Look at him!
What is he waiting for?
He really wants to do this.
He can't get started if he doesn't get this one done.
Right, he can't quite move forward.
You know, this is his third attempt.
He has to do it now.
Everyone's here.
Guys, you have to watch him.
He's about to do something.
He has to do it now.
Everyone's here.
Guys, you have to watch him.
He's about to do something.
Are you sleepy?
Yeah...
I am.
Are you okay?
I guess it's just my age...
I just end up waking up way too early in the morning.
Oyakata is making some moves.
I'm just really sleepy.
Especially yesterday, I couldn't really sleep.
I woke up at 2 a.m.
What?!
I think I was way too nervous.
They're playing along pretty nicely.
You were awake all this time?
Yeah.
Oh my...
-Eye medicine!
-Oh, here it comes!
He wanted to do this!
Why'd he want to do this bit that badly?
You see, I...
I have small eyes.
We still don't know what it's about!
You're right.
Slim eyes?
Yeah.
He's got slim eyes?
He's having trouble because of his slim eyes?!
I shake so badly every time I do this.
Like this.
Want some?
Oh no thank you, I'm fine.
You know, I was very close to Mitsuo Senda. (Japanese VA)
Right.
I heard he was pretty close to your dad, right?
That's right.
And he's also friends with Director Nagashima. (Shigeo Nagashima)
Oh, that's right.
And Senda was always the MC for Director Nagashima's events.
Right?
-And your dad used to sing.
-That's right, that's right.
Musaka, please wear this for a sec.
Oh, you'll apply the eye drops with that?
Right, right.
How is it?
The drops will be easier to apply.
Right.
Let's try this again.
I'll put this on.
Again.
Place it on top.
What's that?
Huh?
It's Gokigenyou. (EN: 5)
-We haven't really talked much so...
-That brings me back.
So I thought we'd play this game and get to know each other better.
Okay!
Who should go first?
You should pick.
Oh, then...
Then...
I think we should go clockwise.
I'm starting?
Yes.
Alright.
Let's start!
Okay!
Alright, here I go!
What will it be?
-What will it be?
Out of the bat?!
Alright!
Talk about poop!
Talk about poop?
-In short: Poop Talk!
-Poop Talk!
Talk about poop?
-In short: Poop Talk!
-Poop Talk!
I'm so sorry.
But I mean, you can talk about anything as long as it has something to do with poop.
-Something to do with poop?
-Right.
Oyakata might be weak to this, don't you think?
It's childish humor.
Right, he might crack.
He seems like the type.
Let's see...
Hiro is our top batter!
I...
Well, I only do this at home but...
I have this unconventional way of going to the bathroom.
So, you know how there are those Japanese toilets? (EN: 6)
Well, since I was a child I have always been more used to Japanese-style toilets.
I was taught how to use a Japanese-style toilet first, so I guess that's why.
So I have to poop Japanese-style even in western-style toilets.
You climb on it?
I do.
On the toilet seat?
Yes, on the toilet seat.
I mean, I don't do it outside my home.
Right, right.
I just do it at home where I feel at ease.
But I do hear of this from time to time.
Of people who were raised with Japanese-style toilets.
So...
Actually, one time I was at a friend's place and as I opened the door to the toilet I saw his girlfriend holding onto the toilet tank.
She was doing it.
She was holding onto the toilet bowl and doing it facing the other way.
I ended up seeing that by accident.
Facing the bowl?
Right, facing the bowl.
Yes.
Do you also face the other way?
Yes, I do.
I see...
Yes.
Cause the Japanese-style toilet is facing that way.
So I can't do it.
Musaka has a grim look on his face.
Thank you for that story.
Sure, sorry...
Thank you.
Alright, now it's Shingo's turn.
Is Oyakata okay?
Please go ahead.
He looks fine to me.
Here it goes.
What will it be?
Ouch!
Sorry!
-What will it be?
-Are you alright?
-Dance!
Dance?!
Sorry.
It's fine, don't worry about it.
-This is...
-Sorry!
It's fine.
This is actually your expertise.
You're a pro.
So with this one you have to do a dance.
I'll play some music.
So we'd like to see your dancing skills.
He's pretty good.
Alright.
Right?
Let's go with this song.
I mean, of course he's good at dancing!
He sure is!
Can he do it?
He's dancing!
He's mixing in!
Everyone's in!
Even Oyakata.
This is wonderful.
But the song is over...
The song is over!
That's it.
Thank you.
That was quite something!
They're doing something.
-They're still going.
-They are.
It's like Usain Bolt's pose.
-Whoa, something's happening.
-Yeah!
A dance battle?
Very exciting!
I see!
They're going all out!
That was wonderful.
Thank you!
Thanks!
A pro dancer...
-Shingo's a very good dancer, isn't he?
-Totally.
Very good!
That was fun.
-Alright Yusuke, it's your turn.
-Yes!
-Please go ahead.
He's starting to move.
What will it be?
Whoa, this is a hard one.
What is it?
Talk about Hitoshi Matsumoto.
-In short: Matsu Talk!
-Matsu Talk!
It's the first time I heard that term.
Please tell us a story about Matsumoto.
Does he even have any?
I've only ever worked with him though...
Right.
You should have tons of funny stories about your time working together.
Well sure, we've been working on that show for a while.
But a story about Matsumoto?
He doesn't have any!
Actually, has anyone here met him in their private time?
Oh, he's dodging the question.
I have seen you around plenty of times.
He must have really had zero stories about Matsumoto.
He must have no stories to tell.
Ehm...
I actually saw him in the park near my former place.
He was actually wearing a mask.
He wore a black knit hat, with a black jumper and black pants.
His outfit was exactly that of Toshio Kurosawa. (EN: 7)
I saw him gently pushing a girl on the swings.
Did he have that 'celebrity' atmosphere?
He did.
I think everyone knew right off the bat who he was.
Now that I think about it, I did get some pictures taken with Matsumoto.
Pictures?
Hold on, I have my phone here so I'll show you.
Is that okay?
Sure.
I do remember taking some pictures with him after a shoot.
Let's watch it over there.
The TV?
Yeah, he's gonna mirror it to the monitor.
Oh, right, right.
Let's see the picture.
I think it was after Deluxe...
It was a while back.
He's gotta have something prepared.
-It does seem kinda fishy.
-Right?
But he sure set it up nicely after rolling that dice.
Right? He remembered.
Did you take this off camera?
Yes.
No way...
No way.
No, no, no.
No, no, it's Shuchishin. (EN: 8)
Why is Tsuruno here? (JP Talent)
That's Takeshi Tsuruno!
Huh?
He's struggling!
He's really struggling!
It just keeps going.
What the heck is this?!
Was Matsumoto blonde back then?
It just keeps going.
It's Shuchishin and Matsumoto!
Yes, at the time he was.
I think it was for a role.
Hold on, Oyakata is in trouble!
He's got some nice pecs!
Oyakata is about to crack.
He's trying really hard.
Oyakata is in trouble!
It doesn't stop, does it?
I think it was their debut song.
He was there, huh?
But the group was unbalanced.
He must have prepared for this.
Matsumoto was also part of the Hexagon family?
That's right.
I see.
Liar!
But that's the only photo I have.
-That was great.
-Thanks.
Nobody broke!
Right?!
They all did so well!
He must have been waiting for this exact moment to show those pictures!
Yeah, he probably figured this was as good a time as any.
Musaka, could you go next?
Oh, me?
Yeah, he probably figured this was as good a time as any.
Alright.
Please roll the dice.
You know I actually won the Grand Prize of the year when Kosakai was still the host. (Kazuki Kosakai)
I won the "Sad Story" section.
-The sad story, huh?
-I still have my trophy at home.
-It was a proper trophy made of glass.
-That's amazing.
Okay guys, sing!
-What will it be?
What is it?
Dance again.
Whoa, here we go!
-Dance!
It's dancing again!
Musaka's dancing, huh?
I can't dance...
What kind of music should I play?
I can't dance like Shingo, you know?
Sure...
I don't even know the basics of dancing...
That's good.
H-How do you dance to this kind of music?
Go with the flow!
That's great.
That's funny!
That's so funny!
I would totally crack!
Me too!
That's hilarious.
I would have laughed ages ago!
Any normal person would laugh at this!
He's trying really hard.
No one's laughing.
Whoa, it's just like those glasses he had!
Been a while since we last saw this!
That was amazing.
Thank you!
-Thank you!
-Good job!
I can't believe no one laughed!
I did my best.
It was pretty good though.
It sure was!
Oyakata, could you roll the dice now?
Yes.
Okay, let's go.
What will it be?
Ah, sorry.
What will it be? What will it be? What will it be?
What is it?
Wig.
Talking about wigs!
Talking about wigs?!
- Wig Talk!
- Everyone's got this, right?
Right.
Wig Talk...
Talking about wigs?
He's actually wearing a wig, right?
Wig.
Sumo wrestlers have to grow a Chonmage, right? (EN: 9)
That's right.
Actually people with thin hair do have to get hair implants for the hair bun.
-Really?
-Is that so?
That's right.
But Sumo wrestlers wouldn't wear a wig, it would fall off too easily.
You couldn't fight, right?
That's right.
I see.
But the curves of your hair are so pretty.
You know, I am a sculptor so I am familiar.
But those curves are so amazing.
This part.
Like a slot canyon.
-It's very pretty.
-Thank you.
Alright...
But it takes time, doesn't it?
- I would say it takes me around 30 to 40 minutes.
- Stop it with the hair talk!
- It takes that long?
- I would say it takes me around 30 to 40 minutes.
That's right.
Isn't it hard to sculpt that kind of hair?
It really is.
Especially since I mainly work on metal sculptures.
It would be much easier if I worked with clay.
But it's really hard with metal. You have to scrape and scratch the metal with the sander.
It would be impossible.
You'd never get something as beautiful.
Thank you.
Shingo, you also draw, don't you?
-That's right.
-He's very good.
I have been keeping up with your blog, Shingo.
Thank you.
It's very interesting.
He's really amazing, you know?
He could make a living with those drawings.
Right?
And those Arashi dolls of Ohno you made. (EN: 10)
It was back when Ohno starred in Maou as a regular. (EN: 11)
He apparently likes to go fishing.
And after catching a 365 kg tuna, he made a sculpture with some fishing hooks.
He was super happy about it.
And he came to me with a photograph of the sculpture the next day.
He's making sure Musaka doesn't notice.
He was super happy about it.
And he came to me with a photograph of the sculpture the next day.
He's making sure Musaka doesn't notice.
Why?
It was such amazing work by him.
Amazing.
That's amazing... You can even draw...
Look at Kazunori.
He's moving!
He's moving.
He's eating! Look!
He's making sure Musaka doesn't notice.
-But why?
-Why?!
Why would he care if he sees?
Thank you for that very special story.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
What are they cooking now?
This is such an amazing set, don't you think?
-It really is.
-It's really cool!
He forgot about the mayonnaise.
All those years I have been watching this show.
And I finally got to set foot in this place.
True!
It has left a deep impression on me.
We still have a ton of time.
We're about to hit the 1-hour mark.
-Not even...
-Right, we're about to hit it.
That's right.
-How long have you been making sculptures?
-Sculptures?
-He's asking about sculpting again?
- Well I'm 68 right now so...
And I started when I was 18...
It's been that long?
That's right.
After that...
-What's this? A horse? It startled me...
-Me too.
What's up? What's this?
He's out of breath?
Watch out, he's out of air?
Thank you...
What's with that mustache?
Are you alright?
Katsunori!
That mustache was something else!
You can't be drawing that kind of mustache!
I mean, we'd never do something like that.
-Us comedians would never draw a mustache like that, right.
-Right, we'd never.
That's something you should never draw.
That nose hair was super long, huh?
The one?
It went round and round.
It wasn't a mustache?
Was that a nose hair?
It wasn't a mustache.
A nose hair?
A mustache? I don't think so.
It was a nose hair.
Nose hair, huh?
Nose hair?
I mean, it doesn't really matter...
Did Katsu disappear again?
Where's he?
He's back.
-Oh, he's back.
-What's this?
He's here.
A rabbit.
Rabbit is here.
It's the animal series.
What is that?
Hold on.
They're ignoring him.
-Is that a rabbit?
-It is, it's a rabbit.
-Here it comes.
-Huh?
Mayo!
What was that?
Out of air?
Oh, he's out of air!
Thank you.
I'm truly thankful.
There's a smile!
Alright!
He smiled!
He laughed at his own joke!
He did, right?
Was it Katsu?
-Right.
-Katsu was the one that smiled, right?
-Yes.
He laughed at his own joke.
That always happens.
He must have cracked up at Oyakata's indifference.
And he was the one on the offensive!
But no one's laughing!
You guys are amazing!
We're holding strong!
You're not cracking!
Even though there were a lot of funny skits!
But sometimes the attacker ends up being the real victim.
-So I have to issue you a card, Takahashi.
-Right, understood.
Was he laughing?
He sneakily laughed.
I was actually itchy around here.
It was itchy.
Oh, are you telling me you weren't laughing?
That's right.
I really didn't find it funny at all.
Is that so?
Let's have a look.
I'm truly thankful.
That's right.
This exchange between you two was very good.
Thank you.
You rarely get to see this stuff.
You were totally laughing!
You had the biggest smile on your face!
He really did!
That hug and kiss must have triggered it.
That's right.
Yeah.
But you can't be smiling like that.
Right.
That's the show.
Alright, got it.
But I would like to praise his proactivity.
I think it's really good.
I would like you guys to follow his lead.
Alright then.
Okay!
-We'll do our best!
-We will!
But you guys have very good defenses!
Alright!
No one's laughing!
Is this yours, Musaka?
Yes.
Alright.
Shingo...
Yes?
I'm actually making some new promotional photographs.
So I would like to get your opinions.
What about this one?
Look.
Hold on...
I mean...
I don't look that different, do I?
Sorry.
This one.
Well...
Oyakata, what do you think?
I look the same, right?
I kinda look like Etsushi Toyokawa, no? (EN: 12)
Your hair is totally different though...
Really?
What about this one?
This is the second one.
Huh?
This one.
Look.
Isn't this one great?
I don't look that different in this one either, right?
You look quite cute here.
But the eyes...
The eyes look fake.
Really?
You really think so?
It's good, no?
It feels much brighter.
What about this one?
Have a look.
I mean...
Who?
I tried a bit of photoshop, is it not good?
I mean, it's cute...
-It's kinda cute.
-It is.
-It's like a different person.
Actually... Recently people have been telling me I look a lot like my father when he was young.
You really do.
Everyone's been saying that to me.
And your voice is really similar too.
Recently?
Yes, just the other day.
They actually mentioned my father's promotional photographs and how much I resemble him.
So I brought some with me today.
Whoa!
Well, they are father and son.
Is he planning something?
Like this one.
Let's see.
Oh, this brings me back!
Do I really look like him?
How about this?
He's holding a mic in this one.
"Even at my age, I still have an insatiable libido..."
"Mama, can I eat this?"
I must be the same age as him in these pictures.
"Now, I will ask all of you to kill each other"
Right...
He's younger than me here.
"I'm Mori... I smell shit on my hand even though I haven't touched any"
Does he really say this stuff?
I've been told I look most similar to my dad from this angle.
"Can I put my underwear back on?"
Does your father really say this stuff?
He ain't wearing any?!
"Shut up, middle-school graduate"
Rude!
So rude!
Does he really say that stuff?
I mean, he was a pretty strict father...
That's right...
-What does "Give me an L of this" mean?
-Huh?
"Give me an L of this"?
Katori is in trouble.
"We chose this place cause you said you wanted to eat Katsu-don"
Do I really look like him?
His face hasn't changed much since then.
He doesn't say this stuff, does he?
Well, he was a pretty strict father...
I think I look a lot like him in this picture.
But he doesn't say any of this stuff, does he?
He does.
"Insatiable libido"?
Well...
Back then he...
It was a different time, you know?
"Mama, can I eat this?"
It's Mori.
He must be saying that to his wife.
In which of these do I look most like him?
I think it's gotta be this one.
This one.
Oh, you're right.
Oyakata, try reading this one out loud.
Please go ahead.
"Now, I will ask all of you to kill each other"
Sho is in trouble!
He ran away!
That was such a great move by him!
Let's read some more.
-Katori and Sho were about to crack.
-Right.
"Even at my age, I still have an insatiable libido..."
-Katori and Sho were about to crack.
-Right.
"Even at my age, I still have an insatiable libido..."
Sorry Oyakata, could you...?
-Could you put a bit more emotion into your delivery?
-Sure.
-"Can I put my underwear back on?"
-Everyone's about to crack.
That was pretty good.
He talks a bit more loudly.
But they're doing well.
"Shut up, middle-school graduate"
Having Oyakata read this was such a great idea.
It really was.
They found a use for him.
Your father is a genius.
"Now, I will ask all of you to kill each other"
Scary!
That's such a scary line!
I brought the sampler.
I see.
What's this?
You can make some sound effects with this.
Whoa!
-Can we try again? But now we'll use the sampler.
-Oh, I see!
Hearing this from Mori himself would be scary!
"Mama, can I eat this?"
-Not like that.
-That's not quite right.
-It's wrong.
-Not like that.
What about this one?
Sure.
Here I go.
"I'm Mori... I smell shit on my hand even though I haven't touched any"
That was so close. He was super close!
His voice is a bit similar.
-His voice is identical!
-Yeah, it's a bit similar.
His voice is a bit similar.
-His voice is identical!
-Yeah, it's a bit similar.
You really sound like him.
You sound like Mori.
-To his dad.
-That's right.
You felt your dad's spirit in his delivery, didn't you?
I really did!
I really felt it when he said: "I'm Mori".
- How about we have him act out Mori a bit more.
-Right.
-We should.
- How about we have him act out Mori a bit more.
We need a bit more emotion.
You have to become Shinichi Mori.
We need a huskier voice. A much more loose delivery.
Here it goes.
Alright.
"Totoro was really there!" (EN: 13)
Hold on, I haven't played the 'ta-da' effect yet.
Wait for the sound to play.
Say it after the sound, okay?
You have to wait for the sound.
He's gotta imitate his voice.
Katori is in such trouble.
Oyakata chose another one.
Which one?
You have to turn into Shinichi Mori.
Alright!
Go ahead.
This is so rare.
Everyone's loitering.
They don't know what he's about to read.
Alright.
Everyone's about to crack.
- He's shuffling them.
- Oh, he's shuffling them!
Please give me the cue.
-Please give him the cue.
-The cue, please.
Alright, here it goes.
"Totoro was really there!"
I feel like you forgot about Shinichi Mori just now.
Right?
It was just the usual Oyakata.
"Totoro..."
- You turned back to your usual self.
- You want me to imitate Mori?
Yes, yes.
"Now, I will ask all of you to kill each other"
- That's the same!
- It's the same!
You have to act it out!
"Go home, take a shit and go to bed!"
"We chose this place cause you said you wanted to eat Katsu-don"
"Now, I will ask all of you to kill each other"
Again?
They are really good!
Could I have the Totoro one?
The one with the Totoro quote.
"Mama, can I eat this?"
I can't let it keep going!
Right!
It's too much.
Totally!
-It's been going for a while now.
-Yeah.
He's been doing it this whole time.
He's been grinning all this time.
I didn't laugh.
I was on the edge the whole time.
Who was it?
I didn't laugh.
He must know already.
All of you were about to crack so you started loitering, didn't you?
Loitering?!
We really did!
Everyone was just walking around in a circle.
And the incident didn't happen in a single moment.
I will now take out a card.
It's a yellow card.
For Katori.
Shingo?
You had it coming.
The crafty schemer drowned in his own scheme.
"Mama, can I eat this?"
I can't let it keep going!
I was the one who suggested Oyakata read this.
-But using Oyakata like that was a stroke of genius.
-It was the best!
And this will also help Oyakata in the future.
I see!
Alright, let's keep going.
-Yes!
What about that?
Ouch!!
That's right.
That's Gushiken!