Alright Matsumoto-san.
Good luck!
Yeah, I'm counting on you guys!
"Matsumoto Hitoshi"
"Fourth year of Documental"
—So this is your fourth year already.
—Yeah, that's right.
The entire premise is that you can't smile.
And not being able to laugh
is probably fun entertainment
that I think anyone could watch.
To put it simply, it's a battle
But if I had to compare it to something else,
I'd say it's kind of like wrestling or martial arts.
That's probably the best way to put it.
Yeah...
You push like this...
Right now content has become very sensitive,
and people are looking for seriousness.
And I think this show definitely
goes against that altogether.
—2000 pieces!
—2000?!
Stop it! I'm feeling it!
And if you think we're not being honest,
you just have to make the offer to Sandwichman again.
I don't think he'd ever return to the show.
That's how it is.
It's just a fun idea.
If that were me, I wouldn't go on the show.
But somehow, this show's... you know...
pretty vulgar.
But at the same time, the winners are always unexpectedly
kind of classy in their own way.
I did it!
I think our ten members
have a very documental-like
mental stability.
"The unflinching theoretical specialist"
"The eternal extra"
"Unbelievably supersonic"
"The shrieking macho psychopath"
"The full-fledged Afro-dite"
"The immovable backstage king"
"The uncrowned emperor of deceit"
"The very very very very late bloomer"
"The performer that kills performers"
"The destructive bulldozer"
"Hell's arbiter"
Good work back there.
Today I really feel
kind of exhausted from laughing so much.
I was almost crying. It was insane.
I ended up feeling almost like
I wanted to see the world like they did.
I kind of ended up admiring them somehow.
How should I put this?
When they faced the challenge of laughing sincerely,
I feel that it turned out really well.
It sure did.
Well...
It was amazing.
This is a garden where dandelions blossom.
And white butterflies flutter around.
The bugs enjoy their exercise in the summer, too.
Alright then, allow me to give you some guidance.
Would you gather a million yen for it?
We're hosting a "Documental".
The winner takes ten million yen.
Of course, you're free to participate.
Anyone strong enough to participate,
will be informed of the date, place and time.
I'm waiting for your reply.
Here's hoping we'll get to spend many springs together.
Matsumoto Hitoshi
"Enter the contestants"
Okay, that's the first one.
Huh?!
So this is how we're going to do it?
I know about it. I've watched it.
You can calm down somewhat when you do it for the second time.
It sure was fun, yeah.
I don't think
that Junior is the kind of performer
that naturally fits in "Documental" to be honest.
I think I can say it now that it's over,
But I know my own weaknesses.
And I was thinking that maybe I shouldn't have called.
I think it could be fun
to see Junior actually winning it or something, though.
(EN: Titles of each contestant are the same as the ones announced before)
I wasn't expecting this.
Alright...
There are many instances in this show
where people don't laugh as others keep trying.
I wonder what kind of laughter
Junior will be going for after knowing that.
It's the same as the boxing ring.
Everyone participating is completely different.
I'll use whatever I can,
and put up a good show.
That's what I've been thinking.
I see.
Well, well, well.
Junior!
So that's how it is.
Look who's here!
—Kinoshita!
—Stop that!
Good work.
Alright, alright.
Guess I don't have to read this.
Make sure to watch this time again.
"Don't you think you have a soft spot for Fujimon, Mastumoto?"
is something I've been told several times.
It's not that I have a soft spot for him in particular,
but I probably like him more than Yukkina. (EN: Fujimoto's ex-wife)
You see
the timing is incredibly important.
I don't really know why, but...
but after seeing something funny,
sometimes you don't feel much like laughing.
And I think that happens to me a lot in "Documental".
Of course, Fujimon knows
that he has a particular power when he's in the background.
And I don't think he intends to change that.
So he's set on winning somehow.
Maybe he also needs the money.
Please make sure you watch again.
I don't think you've ever been teased this much
by anyone else before.
I'm number one in the show business.
So I'm going to grab it this time and counter attack!
Everyone will surely be thinking "ah, good to see Fujimon's doing well!"
And that's just what I'm here to show.
Hey, did you bring the 1.03 million?
Why 1.03? It's just one million, right?
No, that's 30,000 short.
When you called me to talk about your divorce,
I had to call you back.
My long distance call ended up costing over 30,000 yen.
That's not my problem. Not at all.
—Pay up.
—Let me tell you something.
I was just in New Caledonia, and I didn't know.
It's not my problem.
Pay them up already.
What are you even talking about all of a sudden?
Hello there!
Oh come on. He came in through that door?
That was unexpected.
Yeah I guess.
We're not supposed to be using that one yet.
I think it's fine to make an entrance like that, though.
Hey.
Sheeesh! (EN: Might be "How much!". Not 100% sure)
Matsuo just...
keeps getting funnier and funnier.
So I'm really looking forward to his performance.
He might put up a good fight.
That's how I see it.
I'm feeling pretty confident
in participating in "Documental"
as Ikko-san this time. (EN: Ikko is a Japanese make-up artist)
Now people are laughing at his Ikko impression,
but it just makes me sick.
I just don't have a soft spot for it at all.
Even if I got the ten million,
I'd like to give at least seven million to Ikko-san.
Kind of like a deposit.
It'd be like a franchise.
No, you're not there yet.
Why?!
Come on, drop it.
I don't want it to be an impersonation making fun of her,
but rather a sign of respect.
Okay, do it once in front of us.
Okay.
Sheesh!
It hasn't even started yet.
You shouldn't do that anymore, though.
Why?
It's gonna get old.
—Yeah, maybe...
Wait... whoa!
Look, Junior-san.
Huh?
Who's that?
Shoji?!
—Good morning.
I'm counting on you.
I don't really know what you're going to do, though.
It's his first time.
I can't imagine your strategy.
You said "Documental"?
I'm so happy!
Mikitty!!
I'm happy, but also scared.
I entered this world because I admired Downtown so much.
The reason this is Shoji's first time
is that I didn't think he'd be so good.
To be honest, I thought that when he went all out,
he was on about a fourth grader's level.
Mikitty!!
He's on top of the world at the moment.
And I think that happiness
may end up creating some kind of spark within him.
—I'm counting on you.
—Shoji?
The two successful lovebirds of the entertainment industry.
Which one of you is the loser?
I've been playing the role of dad
a lot of the time recently.
But now,
I kind of want to show them my pride as a comedian.
I don't want to crush them with technique, but with feelings.
I have a one track mind.
I'll do my best,
and pull off the unexpected,
with my soul.
I think that I'd like to push forward with my soul.
You'd have us all beat if we were cooking stew.
That commercial was just—
Not yet!
It's not the time to talk about that yet!
It doesn't matter, though does it?
Leave it!
I'm telling you it's still too early!
—What are you getting so worked up for?
—He's totally lost it!
What are you so worked up for?
—He's too upset over nothing.
—I can't keep up with that.
So the commercial...
Stop it with the bullying already.
-Bullying?
-Someone's here. Look, look!
Who is it this time?
Fujita?!
Fujita!
This is looking bad!
You guys all look good!
What's that?
It's... it's that thing.
And here you were saying that you felt pretty confident
I didn't say anything, and I'm not confident!
I hope the other legends watch over him!
Too soon!
I really like Fujita.
And I kind of think he's adorable.
I've heard that Matsumoto-san really likes me.
At least that's what people say.
Don't say that here.
Also, I think that physically speaking,
Matsumoto-san likes me a lot better.
Get outta here!
This is his strength.
He's funny,
and he can do some pretty solid Manzai.
So maybe he'll be able to pull off something good this time.
He tends to play the tsukkomi much more than me,
so he's not just going to sit around.
He's going to go on the offense.
I don't think they're expecting anything from me.
Nothing at all.
I've been watching the series.
And it's managed to make me laugh in a way nothing else had before.
So like...
Considering I hadn't really thought about being on it before,
I've decided to take a completely new approach.
Fujimoto-san, can you do this?
I can!
I don't like this.
I'm telling you I can.
I really don't want to do this.
I don't want to go like this.
Why don't we stretch or something?
Really?!
Should've stayed backstage at Lumine.
This is Yoshimoto all the way.
Cheers!
Stop that!
—Good morning.
A red letter?
Lately,
we've been struggling
with several things.
I'd like this season
to be completely released
with Amazon, though.
Is it okay for you to be here?
Sure is!
Who are you...?
Who are you even talking to right now?
It's been eight years, huh?
Are you okay here?
Sure am. It's been eight years already.
I don't really remember.
I'd say his main attribute would be...
his high potential.
I think he'll be able to stand high levels of stress, too.
He can make things as chaotic as he wants.
So they want me to go there and make a mess, huh?
Even if you try to put up a show on your own, you have to make sure you're not doing it for the wrong opponent.
That's why comebacks have to...
hit them all at once.
Or you might end up bringing yourself down in the end.
Besides, counter-attacks seem to
be able to make people laugh, too.
I want to make them realize
that Koumoto's style is really unique.
I want to make them learn something new.
You heard them.
That doesn't matter.
I can't listen to what someone tells me eight years later.
I can see it already.
He does it in all his commercials and even on TV all the time.
—I think he'll be out right away.
—He just loves it.
—He loves those big smiles.
—I do.
—Speaking of which...
—Come on...
—The competition hasn't even started yet!
—The competition, yeah!
Hey, nice going.
For real?!
How many times are you gonna do this?!
Are you going to live here now?
Excuse me.
No one said anything, though!
It's here?
Okay, received!
I've been short on money lately.
And right now, business is going pretty bad,
and well I have to pay rent.
He's already well established.
At least I think he is.
This is something I heard at a certain massage place a while ago...
"You're..."
"...Japanese. No way. You're. American!"
Or something like that.
Those words gave me courage.
To be honest, I think Kobayashi is funnier
when he's kind of...
...surrounded by people more experienced than him.
It might be kind of difficult for him
to be surrounded by mostly people younger than him.
Every time I come here, I realize...
...just how complicated laughter is.
Everyone says
that time flies when you're having fun.
But frankly, I find it mostly exhausting.
You don't even see six hour shifts in the adult industry.
You're a regular now!
How many times has it been for you?
This is Junior-san's second.
—It's rough!
—I need the money.
Nine years... once in nine years!
Once in nine years!
In nine years?
No way!
There he is!
I'm sorry!
Good morning.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Someone good just showed up!
What's this?
Me?!
I'm a crackpot underground comedian!
This is from Matsumoto-san?
He's from the same generation as Fujimon.
He started performing at Yoshimoto 12 years ago.
When I was in middle school, I became part of the Yoshimoto's NSC 8th generation.
I got a little frustrated,
and my level kind of...
...started to lag behind.
8th generation!
He was part of the 8th but eventually became part of the 13th.
So we're coworkers too.
We had a lot of peers.
Yeah, lots of them.
I'm gonna do a coocoo clock now.
I guess he's more primitive.
I expect him to have a position
kind of similar to Jimmy-chan.
Great Kinnikuman.
"Kinnikuman!"
It may be a great chance for him.
If I end up going down,
I'm not going to live the life of the underground comedian anymore.
I'm carrying it all on my back.
We met at 14, 15 years old.
That's right.
—And Oshiro is...?
—One year younger.
At the NSC...
He's younger than Junior-san?
—He was 14, I was 15.
—When was that?
Second, third year of middle school.
Look at that.
I'm going to do a short skit.
It's been a while.
Skit: "Takeda-kun".
Takeda! Snap!
Oh! I got Yoshida!
O-hyo-hyo!
—This is...
—This is bad!
That must've been like 30 years ago.
30 years already?
What were you thinking 30 years ago?
The ninth one is here.
He did the same thing twice.
We could see you!
How many times has it been already?!
Give it a rest!
You've done it already!
It's been like six times already!
Excuse me.
I'm kind of used to it...
this red letter
Alright, let's do this.
I want to show them
that I'm going to be relentless and the best.
I'm kind of left wondering
why does he still show up?
He's a semi-regular at this point!
I'm thankful, though.
And my expectations have kept rising.
Quitting while you're ahead is really lame.
So I'll keep coming back until they tell me to stop.
I'd like to win it all, to be honest.
He's pretty good.
He's insanely good.
We have a hell of a lineup.
It's all Yoshimoto.
I don't want to see Kukky
try his absolute best and go for the win.
I want him to be out quickly,
and see him as a zombie.
If anything,
his zombie performance
might be pretty good.
Every time I put in my all from the beginning.
I have almost no defensive barriers after all.
I think playing offensively is the best defense.
It's just like boxing,
I want to at least create the opportunity to throw a jab.
Because you won't hit anything
if you don't throw the punch.
I never expected this lineup.
It's all Yoshimoto.
—You're in Yoshimoto, right?
—That's right!
The last one?
That's the last one, right?
For real?!
No, no, no, no!
Even the brothers didn't know about it.
It's here?
Thank you very much.
Ten million in front the family.
That's a lot of money.
Of course, thanks to our dad,
we saw a lot of scandalous things happen in private.
He looks happy to be on the show for the third time.
Most TV channels
have already banned us altogether.
And after a while,
we ended up on Amazon.
So we're two regulars down, huh?
Long time no see.
With two brothers here...
This is...
You have memories and everything together.
I may have some funny stories
to tell about this guy right here.
Just take each other out today, please.
Yeah, destroy each other.
How is it to record for six straight hours?
I've had to ride a bumpy bus in Africa for eight straight hours.
This is nothing!
We have toilets and running water, right?
We have food, right?
Even stuff to drink...
Seiji's here too?
Seems like he's watching the TV.
And Kukky too!
How nonchalant!
You sure look giddy today!
You jogging now?
I had enough with Sanma-san!
He's Sanma-san!
Okay everyone.
This is amazing!
You're all getting along!
This looks really fun!
This might be the first time we've had an atmosphere like this!
Really?
Right? Don't you think so?
Yeah, that's true.
We're testing each other.
—This is great.
—They usually walk in smoothly and...
It really feels like a dressing room.
That's right.
I guess it's because so many have been chased off the face of Earth.
Stop it!
I'm sure it's just your imagination when talking about me, though.
Imagination?
I think it's looking pretty grim for you.
Yeah, but we can't screw up again.
Sure.
I'm sure Amazon doesn't mind though.
Of course. Well... that's right.
About Amazon.
Uh... To be honest, I wasn't sure if I should say this.
This is Season 8, right?
And well, Season 7 got really good ratings,
And Amazon was very pleased.
They really want to keep "Documental" going,
which is a huge compliment.
So then we really got carried away and recorded.
The next season?
We recorded the next season...
And now it looks like it's not going to be released.
Did something happen?
What happened?
Amazon's higher ups said
that it was way too vulgar.
That's fine! And I'm not trying to make a point or anything,
just that even Amazon does have a line that we can't cross.
-I see.
-A line?
We don't know that line!
So no vulgar jokes?
No, no. You can joke around as much as you like.
It's really no problem at all.
It's just that you can't do absolutely anything.
I see.
But season 7 was pretty good.
I see, so you guys went a bit too far.
I mean, I'm even wearing an Amazon hoodie,
to show how sorry I am.
That's worse than I imagined!
—So you're being polite?
—I am.
I'm really being extremely polite.
So that's why he walked in all jogging and everything?
All nonchalant!
As an apology?
Kind of.
Besides, a lot has been going on at Yoshimoto
especially since last year.
Ever since Chance joined Yoshimoto.
He started this all!
First I've heard of it.
It might be true, though.
For real.
I'm counting on you all!
And well, since everyone today is a Yoshimoto comedian.
That's right.
It's like a full-on Yoshimoto performance.
Stop it! It all comes down to that?
What?
You're all pretty self aware, huh?
Great intuition.
What does that T-shirt say if you read it vertically?
—What's written there?
—Why do you care? It doesn't make a difference?
What's wrong with you, man?
It's still too early for this!
It's not early!
If anything, doing this right now might be better.
You're right.
You sure love scandals, right?
What's the deal with your big brother?
For real.
Okay, everyone! Please give me the money!
For real...
Oh come on...
I want this!
—I know, right?
—I really want it!
I can't count everything in detail, but I trust you.
One million.
One million...
Okay, here we have 5 million.
That's amazing.
That's tight.
It's pretty flashy.
Kind of excessive.
By the way, Chance. That's a lot of money, huh?
First time I've seen something like it.
Okay, there it is.
So I work in construction, right?
Yeah, construction.
This is from getting 10,000 per day.
—That's your salary?
—So it's a hundred days.
It's a hundred days, yeah.
That's too real!
From digging all those holes, huh?
By the way, here's my million.
Thank you very much!
So we need to add this, which gets us to 11 million yen.
So this is my million.
There we go.
And we're gonna put this in here.
No way!
—That looks nice!
—Every time I see it...
It's just too much.
I'm really giving this to you guys.
Well, to the winner.
It's 10 million!
No way! 10 million!
I really want it!
It's really impressive.
It is impressive.
Alright, that's that.
I ended up talking a bit too much.
Okay, six hours!
Okay, so I've been thinking of getting more strict this time!
At least that's the point.
You can get a direct red now.
If you get too careless.
He's completely screwed.
You've been laughing all this time.
Junior too, yeah.
That's just how I look, you know?
—That's no good!
—Not at all!
This is pretty bad news!
Wasn't that a direct red?
Well, I think Junior in particular,
you have to watch out and make sure your mouth is always slanting downwards.
Junior's screwed, for real!
You'd be out already.
Alright, then...
So no matter what happens, you can laugh or cry,
we're doing the whole six hours.
Let it end at four hours today, come on.
I think it's about time!
Also, I told some staff to be on stand by around here, so...
Make sure to use them if you need to.
Sure, thank you.
Good luck!
Seiji's watch is a Louis Vuitton and that's hilarious for some reason.
Well, I guess Seiji just likes that kind of brand.
Luxury brands.
Alright then. Let's start "Documental"!
There it goes!
Oshiro has been pretty strict since 25 years ago already.
That's just Oshiro.
I'm sure people watching are now wondering
just what is funny about Oshiro being that way.
But for us laughing works
kind of like a Mobius strip.
What's that right there?
A hat.
Yeah, a hat.
I was wondering if there was something inside but didn't want to touch it.
No, it's just a hat.
It's a bontang made in Okayama.
It's kind of stylish.
—Huh? Where is this from?
—Okayama.
—That's a school uniform?
—Yeah.
I had it custom made to look like a uniform.
It looks like a letter "M"!
—For real.
—Are you trying to advertise here?
For McDonald's?
And these over here, too.
Like the McDonald's logo.
Are you going to start singing, too?
You should write "I'm lovin' it" right there.
As a decoration?
They're not coming?
Who?
You weren't listening. I told you already.
Of course we're not going to run any McDonald's commercials.
That's good.
If we wrote "I'm lovin' it" right there,
we could call it a commercial.
I guess you're right.
This is your first time, Shouji?
It's also my first time, and I'm kind of happy to be here.
You watched things like this, Seiji-san?
—Sure.
—He doesn't look like it.
At all.
Huh? Really? I sure do.
But I'm always drinking,
so I never get to know who wins.
Call Mikitty to raise the curtain.
You sure?
—Let's make an announcement.
—And also,
get Ikko-san to support you.
Going through.
Okay.
Here we go.
—Mikitty!
—Sheesh!
—Mikitty Mikitty!
—Shoulder throw!
—Mikitty!
—Sheesh!
Junior!
I told you!
I told you about it!
That was too fast!
Too early!
He's the worst among us!
No way!
That's too fast!
Okay, Junior.
You were smiling normally.
Isn't that the fastest in "Documental" history?
I think it's probably the fastest.
That's no good.
We couldn't let that slip by.
What just happened, really?
How disappointing!
—Mikitty Mikitty!
—Shoulder throw!
—Mikitty!
—Sheesh!
He was way out of line!
What a spoiled brat!
To be honest, I was waiting for it.
But you're supposed to be more strict this time.
That's a straight red.
I was waiting for it, but it was way too much, and I couldn't keep up.
It was the fastest ever, while we were just raising the curtain.
-So what now?
-Yeah, yeah, you're right.
Are you really okay with that?
It's a yellow for now.
That was a yellow.
Alright! Now we're getting into it!
Never imagined someone would laugh at that, though!
Not on the streets!
No way, yeah!
Alright, alright.
What have you been doing all this time?
Sukkera Kecchi!!