Just for once, just for this time, in my whole life
I want to win this game
I believe I have a strong defense
I'll be fine even if people do some high-level gags
This is the time
I'm actually getting closer and closer to victory
This is the time for me to put 10 million right in front of my wife
The teddy bear who has always been humble
The cute teddy bear
The little teddy bear
I've already received an orange card
-Oh, yeah
-So he is out
Who brought this porno mag here?
This is gonna get me erect
What's wrong with you?
He's out
Don't give me so little
The pee is gonna stain my hand
You're laughing dude
Ah, here comes the alarm
You laughed right?
Let's start
If I don't win, this will just be an evidence of my labour
It's good to have that pee smell as your evidence of labour
-I'm so sorry for the inconvenience
-No problem at all
-You started cleaning it immediately right?
-You didn't resist cleaning it
You did those jobs before?
What the heck is a job that cleans pee?
Where can you even find those jobs?
-He means like a cleaner
-Yes
That's not limited to cleaning pee
Were you a permanent employee?
What the heck do you mean a permanent employee?
A permanent employee that cleans pee?
Never heard of that
-Did you laugh?
-No, I didn't
You laughed just now
-Yes, you did
Pretend to show off my muscles
But actually checking the smell of my armpit
That's interesting
Really?
Show us more
-Show you more?
-I feel like laughing
It's festival today!
Sore-Sore
Jori-jori (sound of shaving)
What a beautiful bikini line
Peekaboo!
So small
No, it's not small, it's just buried
It's not buried at all
It's as small as a turtle head
No way, it's big
No, Miyasako's was bigger
That's because he got erected
Huh?
It was so small, I want to see it again
So small
You're being hunted
Eh, why?
This is a battle
You have a weapon too
OUCH!
Ah, this really hurts
Come on, come on
AH! OUCH!
OUCH!
Gather up! My ultra power!
OUCHHH!!!
IT HURTS!!!
Ah, my urethra somehow opened up
That's enough
That's seriously enough
Please stop it
Did you try to pee?
Huh?
Did you try to pee just now?
That peeing thing belongs to me
-Belongs to you?
-Belongs to me
Yeah, the pee performance art
The pee performance art?
And the erect performance art is mine
It won't be interesting even if you do the pee performance art again
It won't get a laugh
I want to eat that steak again
It was so delicious
-Is it?
-Yes
It tastes so good
Maybe we can call food delivery then?
But the zombies will come soon
Ah yeah, you're right, there's zombies
They are on standby
They're gonna come in group
-We're unable to kill those zombies right?
-Yeah
-And it's fine for them to laugh right?
-Yes
There's no way to stop them
Those zombies...
We just have to endure those zombies
Yes, we have to keep on enduring
Come on, no one will laugh at a staring-out game now
Zombie time
That scared me
It's been quite a while
They have three people now
Hello, everybody!
Thank you all for coming today
Tokyo's sushi just tastes so good
Yeah, it's the home of sushi
I want to play the role of a sushi master
Ah I see, so I'll be the customer
Excuse me, can I come in?
Low ploblem
No problem?
Clum in
Come in?
Come in, come in
Would you like to have the chef's choice plan?
Well yes, I'll leave it to you
Here you go
A tiny and cold steamed egg custard
Who will even want that?
Give me a big and hot one
Here you go
A fat saury with it's entrails being taken out and then put back
What's the meaning of that?
It's meaningless to take out the entrails first
-Here you go
-Here it is
-It's fried chicken
-Fried chicken?
Fried chicken at a sushi restaurant?
That's weird
Here you go
Amberjack sushi with 800 types of secret ingredients
That's too much
Covered in curry
Curry?
Amberjack with curry?
Here you go
I'll make another sushi now
-Please guess what it is
-So I need to guess it now
Yes, for example it's not just tuna, it's here, tuna's cheek
Oh I see, so some rare parts
-Can I make the sushi now?
-Yes please
Here you go
-Please guess what it is
-I'll try
I have no idea
It's here of a dolphin
Don't give me those things
Here you go
-What is it?
-It's here of a hammerhead shark
That's gross
Here you go
-What is it?
-It's here of a anglerfish
That's disgusting
Here you go
What is it?
It's two squid sushi
Two squid sushi?
Two squid sushi at this point of time?
Be quiet!
-Look who's talking
-There's other customers here
The customer over there is Kakuei-san
*Tanaka Kakuei was Prime Minister of Japan from 1972 to 1974
-Tanaka?
-Yes, Tanaka
No way, he's dead
He's actually alive
Japan has a lot of these people
So Tanaka Kakuei-san is actually still alive?
The customer sitting at the corner is Ken-san
*Ken Takakura was a Japanese actor and singer who died of lymphoma on November 10, 2014
Takakura?
It's Shimura
Shimura
The Shimura-san who is still alive
-The customer sitting over there
-Yes?
He's Yu-chan
Yu-chan?
*Yūjirō Ishihara was a Japanese actor and singer born in Kobe
Do you mean Ishihara Yujiro?
It's Gidayu
Gidayu?
You mean Great Gidayû?
*Great Gidayû was an actor, known for Kikujiro (1999), Vivianne: Busô Jet (2017) and Suicide Bus (1998)
Who would even call Great Gidayu as Yu-chan?
Gidayu-san, you want to have the check?
The scene of Gidayu having the check
The first ever in the history of variety shows
The scene of Great Gidayu having the check
-180 thousand yen please
-180 thousand yenm?
What did he order?
Whelk sushi
Whelk sushi?
2000 pieces
2000 pieces?
For takeaway
I'm enough of this, let me have the check
3800 yen please
That's reasonable
That's enough
Thank you very much
Erect, dude!
I even used some lotions
Can't get erect
Erect, erect!
No matter what I do, can't get erect
He kept doing this back there
He kept doing this behind the door
Saying "Wait, wait, I can't get erect"
I've borrowed some lotions, still can't get erect
In the end, they just asked me to wear a condom
Because I can't get erect
I even did it in a new way like this
But still, it doesn't work
I've never seen someone doing it like this
We normally do it like this, but he's like this
Like a whirlpool
I've even tried to help him out
Because everyone was waiting for me to get erect
I was trying so hard to get erect
And the staffs came several times to check and report the status of my erection
To the senior staffs
I'm erecting a little bit now
That must be tough
Yes, it sure is
He can't get erect
It must be difficult to get erect
I actually thought he was going to pee like that
Ah, so with the condom?
Yeah, and the condom will become larger and larger
I can't even pee
-I thought about that too
-Huh?
Here comes the pee
What the heck...
Wait a second...
I'm the one peeing
Come on, dude
That's horrible
I'm sorry
I'm so sorry
What the heck are you doing?
Come on, dude
I was caught off guard
Don't go too far guys, we will be scolded
That was awful
I'm serious
And you two scattered your clothes around the corridor
So you were wearing your clothes before coming in
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Come on...
-Miyasako
-Yes
You laughed right?
Yes, I laughed
And also...
Itoda
You laughed right?
Yes, I laughed
Let's take a look
I can't even pee
I thought about that too
Huh?
Here comes the pee
What the heck...
So Itoda laughed as well
Itoda absolutely laughed
This is going mad
Pee zombies...
You guys tried hard, but...
Itoda-san and Miyasako-san
Out!
-I watched the exactly same gag at Lumine yesterday
-Yes, it's the same
The gag that made my daughter laugh so hard
-Has been reproduced in such a way
-That's terrible
This is the way to success
To make people do the Tsukommi
At the moment you did Manzai nakedly, it's already not successful
At that moment, we're no longer a Manzai comedian
Not much time left, let's restart
Damn it
He got me on that one
Come on, it's all about peeing
I wonder what will happen from here
Eh?
Good luck guys
Which way are we going? Oh, this way
There's nothing I can do about it, I laughed out loud
Huh? Here comes the pee
I haven't laughed this hard in a long time
I wasn't blown away like that in a long time
However...
I've decided to get an erect penis since that moment
Who brought this porno mag here?
This is gonna get me erect
Eh?
And indeed, I got erect
So personally, I think I've got the victory in this sense
Well...
I've done quite a few things that I wanted to do, however...
Nothing happened at all...
It's me, it's me
HAMBURGER
So I've prepared this for everyone...
I'm not satisfied at all
Because all I did was peeing
(If you're willing to smile for me)
(I will do anything for that)
-You two looked into each other's eyes right?
-Yes
Questions like "what will be interesting"
Or like "how to make people laugh"
They become really difficult to judge under that atmosphere
We don't know how many points we have right?
-Yeah, but Kurochan probably have a lot of points
-Let's start
-I bet you scored a lot of points
-No, I don't think so
No, Kurochan probably scored many points
Shall we do something?
-Yeah, let's do something
-We better do something
Let's do it
It's gonna end soon
It's so empty here now
Yeah, you're right
It's so empty
It's just so empty
Did something happen over there?
It's so cold
Yeah, it's cold
This is incredible
This scene is incredible
Umm...it's so hard to make people laugh
This is so scary
How would Nishizawa feel for listening to that
I can't find my glasses
Yes?
This...
Did you buy this one at a time?
No, I buy it in bulk
This looks like the Pietro salad dressing
Do you use it too?
No, not at all
How do you use it?
How to use it?
To make things slimy
And...
What I like is
To put lotion on my testicles
And grip it tight
Can I use my sword?
Ah, yes
Eh, it's over there?
It was quite soft
-But you're really strong right?
-Yes
What should I do...
-Can I hit you?
-Yes?
Can I hit you?
-Yeah sure, no problem
-Thank you very much
You two look alike
They all end up wearing the same color
Are you from primary school?
Not yet?
Not yet
Eh?
He's the crash test dummy
The crash test dummy
Where can you buy that costume?
So scary
What is it?
It's a photo of me during primary school
Look at the T-shirt
Family computer
-Eh, it's Famicom
-I miss it
That's amazing
Have you ever seen a Famicom t-shirt?
Nah
My dad took this photo during our family trip
My sister is biting my mom's hand
How could there be photos like this
-Ah...
-She's biting hard
And we were hold each other's hands
In front of the telephone box
There was only these telephone boxes at that time
We were hold each other's hands tightly
Eh?
And my sister is biting my mom's hand
But her face looks...
Let's get started
Zombie time
We definitely won't lose this time
We're gonna win this
Huh?
We definitely won't lose
No way, we should be the ones saying that
Do you know how many times our team won, dude?
It's not about how many times you won
People call us the ever victorious general, dude
We're never gonna lose
Come on, let's get started
Let's get started
-Get ready
-Wait a second...
Do it tenderly please
This is the thin one
Got it
You better change the adapter...
Iio-san does this kind of things too?
Yeah, it's shocking
-This is not like Iio-san
-Iio-san's testicles look so old
-He's an old man
-Yeah
Yeah, I'm already 48 years old
-I'll put it in now
-Okay
Can I go further?
Okay, got it
-It really went in
-Do it slowly
Okay, no problem, I'll do it slowly
Slowly please...
Hey bro, hey bro...
Ah, the air is coming in
Hey bro...
You stink
No, I don't stink
Do you need some lotion?
Yes, give me some lotion
Lotion is over there
Is this lotion?
Yes, it's lotion
Actually, quite a lot came in
Maybe put some lotion around your anus
Yeah, that's better
This is amazing
-Can I move your testicles a bit?
-Yes
Eh, so you need to move it first?
It's better to pour it from the top
Ah, it's amazing
This is hard
-Nobu's testicles look like the back of a kid's head
-This is dangerous
Did it go in?
It's going in, it's going in
A lot of it went in
-Jun-chan okay, Jun-chan okay
-This is dangerous
This is dangerous, it's coming out
AHHH
Iio-san, I'll pump it now
I can feel something inside
It's not coming out at all
Okay, okay
Pan-pan, okay
Pan-pan?
That was close
He farted a lot
That was massive
That was amazing
What the heck is this game?
Okay
-Fujimon
-Yes
Out!
Oh yes, we did it
You're almost there
You were so close
Nothing is coming out from Nobu
It's not coming out
Okay, okay
Pan-pan, okay
Pan-pan?
Nobu was peeing last time and now this, will he be fine?
We killed one of you, so no problem at all
I can't believe they did that
Okay, okay
That was just...
That's the kind of thing that can ruin your whole career
Well...
What I almost laughed at is...
Kurosawa
Listen to me...
She kept saying the same thing as if she's chanting
"I can't take this anymore..."
"I'm 39 years old, I shouldn't be doing these things..."
"I can't, I can't, I'm 39 already..."
"Should I just give up..."
"I want to give up..."
She kept saying these things over and over again
She is really verging on a breakdown
So Documental is really pushing people this hard...
10 million is right in front of us
-Well, but...
-What should I do...
Yeah, you're right
Let's start
This would probably be the last round
The winner must be one of us right?
One of us must be able to win the prize right?
If we can endure through this
Who should be the mood maker now though? Me?
I don't know too, but I'll try to do this
The one just now
Eh?
-Kurosawa is going to do that?
-Yes
-Eh? That anus thing?
-No way
-I shouldn't do this right? I'll be married someday
-Don't show it to us
It's better if you do it somewhere else and then show it to us
Don't show your anus in front of us
Okay, I'll do it over there
What you did here is going to stay forever
But I didn't score much points...
Nishizawa, do you know about my sweater?
What do you mean?
This must be shocking to you guys
It's super small
Eh, you've been wearing this?
-It's actually this small
-That's so small
-The fabric is incredible
-Yeah, it stretches a lot
-It's really small right?
-Can't believe you wore that
-It's so small
-This can't be true
-I've been wearing this
-That's so freaking small
It's becoming even smaller
Yes, it gets smaller and smaller
-Eh, as time passes, it becomes smaller?
-Yes
-It becomes like this in the end
-That's so small
Eh?
That's too small
You must be lying
Ouch, it hurts
How is it?
Well...
You did it?
I'm not sure about how to put it in
Eh?
Did you put it into your anus?
You put it into your anus?
Yes, my anus
-Are you sure it's your anus?
-Yes
-Of course, dude
-You mean she may put it in her vagina?
That's too thick for it
You know it's a delicate part of body right?
Don't say things like vagina to a girl
No, I didn't
You said it just now
No, I just said anus
"No, I just said anus"
He's mocking me
Eh?
-I didn't notice that
-Wait a second...
Finish!
Eh?
I was worried that you guys may think the end game buzzer is the sound of Kurosawa's fart and laugh out
This time
There is a winner
Eh, there is?
Thanks to the point system
The winner is
Kukky
-Oh yes, I did it!
-Congratulations
Oh my god, I did it
Is this real?
Eh?
-For real?
-For real
Kukky scored the most points
Eh? Really?
-Eh? You must be joking
-You're amazing
This is the first time in my whole life
10 million plus my 1 million, adding up to a 10 million prize for Kukky
Let's put it in the bag
Kukky is the winner!
-You're amazing
-I won for the first time ever
I'm going home with big money today
I can't believe this! This is amazing
You invested 3 million, and you get back 10 million
-You're right
-That's amazing
That was close
That's incredible, you're determined
This is really the first time for me to win the first place in something
First time in my life
We thought that you've been playing aggressive to win
Really?
-You deserve victory
-Ah, I'm so happy
Did you feel like you're going to win?
No, not at all
I noticed that my defense is getting weaker during in the second half of the game
I feel like I can't defense that well
And I tried to do something
I always kept this in mind
This is the third 1 million that I've paid
Ready
Go
I can't just keep on paying like a dumb ass
Ugh, boobs, boobs
I could have been working some part time jobs
In order to cover the cost
Where is the 10 million now?
I don't have it with me now
The staff took it back
I'm a bit worried
He said he need it for a moment, and took it away
Will it come back?
He seems to be a senior staff
Is that a scam?
I never saw that staff before
Not at all
I don't think he's from Amazon too
The player that deserves to win has won the game
He's a contributor
And I didn't want him to laugh too
So the contributor finally became the winner
Miyasaki-san did the erect performance art too
This is gonna get me erect
What's wrong with you?
Well, I don't know if I can talk about this
But...
He's turned on when there's many players
Different from the previous season
This time the main theme was peeing
I really think this is incredible
They all did this for Owarai
It's difficult for a normal person to pee under those situations
Even if you want to pee, it's difficult under those situations
Like when you're having an examination at the hospital
It's just won't come out when you need to
And yet, they're able to pee such an amount in front of everyone
Itoda is just insane
He's absolutely insane
That dude is wicked