What do you think about Zakoshisho being the favorite?
If I were a fortune teller, I would say this.
"Kubota will come back here as the winner."
This is a worst-case scenario.
I have a secret plan to defeat the enemy.
I worry that Kubota will plant more jokes than I do.
Make me an disciple!
Excuse me, can I get by?
The worst part is that I ran out of all of my jokes.
Zakoshisho without jokes is worth nothing.
But I am not really thinking about winning.
I would enjoy this again for a long time.
This is my best stage.
Documental - Season 10
Episode 5  “Champion is Strong”
"Rassun Gorerai"
He laughed!
Yellow card.
- It's the first time, right?
- Yes.
Don't stir this with your nipple, aaaaahhhhh!!
She laughed.
- He is laughing.
- Yeah.
Kotouge, you are dismissed.
Here we go.
There is 1 hour and 56 minutes remaining.
- Kotouge is gone.
- There are less than two hours left.
4 people.
- Can I do that?
- What?
I will do an impression of Excitebike.
(Note: 1)
- The NES one?
- Yes.
- What's that?
- It is a NES game software.
- Excitebike on the NES?
- Yeah.
That’s all.
This was definitely an Excitebike.
- I used to play with that too.
- Yeah.
What's that?
I'm Dean Fujioka.
(Note: 2)
- Dean Fujioka?
- Yes.
I'm Dean Fujioka.
And...
I am a motorcyclist.
Deeeeeeaaaaaaan....
Fujioka.
I wouldn't laugh at that.
I've had enough of Fujioka.
You can't make me laugh at that.
He is cold.
- There are not many jokes left of me anymore.
- Yeah.
They seem to be running out of jokes of their own.
Junior, do you want to go to that room?
I don't know what we can do though.
I'm going to physically examination you all.
Physically examination?
Okay.
Let's do it.
You are okay.
What?
Why?
This means you are fine.
If you are ok, this will sound "Ding Ding".
Then I'm next.
- Am I alright?
- Yes.
"Apologize, apologize. apologize, apologize!"
(Note: 3)
"Apologize!!"
No.
Junior-san.
- They don't laugh when I do this.
- I see.
"If pushing doesn't work, try pulling."
(Keep trying different ways.)
Pulling?
Try a toned-down impression of the mayor of Nagoya City.
Okay, toned-down impression of the mayor of Nagoya City.
More like, won't you exaggerate?
This is a normal impression of the mayor of Nagoya city.
And this is a toned-down impression of the mayor of Nagoya city.
Not much has changed.
That's toned down a lot.
What other exaggerated impression can you do?
I have a lot of them.
He brought his joke list.
- A toned-down impression?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I can do Shupei of Pecopa impression.
(Note: 4)
First, do you do a normal impression of it?
Yes, see this first.
This is normal one.
"I'm Shupei."
And this is the exaggerated Shupei impression.
"I'm Jupei."
You said Junpei.
- Jupei.
- You said Junpei.
- It's Jupei.
- Jupei?
If you exaggerate Shupei, does it become Jupei?
- Try a toned-down impression of it.
- Yes.
I'm Shupei...
It's toned down.
- It's toned down.
- Yeah.
Nobody laughs.
- I'm new to this, can I try that?
- Sure.
Junior-san, do you have any requests?
- Zakoshi, what was that impression you did a while ago? "If you do, you can eat shit."
- It's Timon D.
Try an exaggerated impression of Timon D first.
"We're Timon D!"
"I'll eat ball!"
"I'll eat this!"
"Strike!"
Zakoshi was close, wasn't he?
Try that in the Kyoto style.
- Try that in the Kyoto style, please.
- Kyoto style!?
Kyoto style...
"I'll eat this ball!"
"We're Timon D!"
"This ball is so tasty!"
"Ookini"
(Thank you)
What's the hell is that?
- It's Kyoto style.
- You just said "Ookini" at the end.
That's right.
I've never done this before either, can I try?
Of course.
Try an exaggerated impression of Katopan.
(Note: 5)
In New York.
"I eat in New York!"
Oh, I see.
Try that in a Chinese style.
"I eat in Sichuan!"
That was bound to happen.
Yes, the location will change.
- Yamamoto-san, would you like to try it?
- Okay, I'll try to do the same.
I've never done this before either, but I'll give it a try.
- Then try an impression of Fuwa-chan..
- Okay.
First, do a normal Fuwa-chan impression.
"Guys, don't be so serious!"
He does not know her.
Next, do an exaggerated impression of Fuwa-chan.
Okay.
Heigh-Ho! Heigh-Ho! Festival!
Festival! Festival!
That has nothing to do with Fuwa-chan.
Yeah.
So what do you want me to do?
To do that, you have to add the essence of normal impression.
- Sometimes Zakoshi doesn't add that essence, either.
- Yeah.
Do a normal impression of Hamada-san.
- Hamada-san?
- Yes.
This is a normal impression of Downtown's Hamada-san.
"Announcement of the results!!"
And this is an exaggerated impression of his.
Cock, cock, cock-a...
Cock-a-doo-cock-a-doodle-doo!!
There was no essence in that one.
He's the one who talked about the essence, right?
Then, try an impression of Hamada-san in the Heian period (10th century).
Cock, cock, cock-a...
Cock, cock, cock-a-doo-de gozaru.
His ones still have the taste that was present in normal impression.
Then may I practice that?
Then try to impression the less energetic Sota Fujii.
(Note: 6)
- The shogi player's?
- Yes.
- Sota Fujii.
- First, I'll do an toned down impression of his.
"I resign."
- He must have lost.
- I'm sure that happens to him too.
Then try to an exaggerated impression of Sota Fujii.
Oute!
(Checkmate)
Then try to an impression of returnee Sota Fujii.
GET!
Who's that?
Whose impression were you?
I think that was good.
You said "I resign" at the first one, so you should say so all the same.
Indeed.
Why is that guy talking about comedy theory?
- That's your way, isn't it?
- Yes.
That is exaggerated impression.
You guys did a lot of different things and it was hilarious.
- Let's chill out and chat a bit.
- Sounds good.
Let's sit down.
- One hour and 30 minutes left.
- Yeah.
I don't know what is going on with me anymore.
What am I supposed to do?
I don't know.
- The match has not finished yet.
- Yeah.
- There is still more than an hour to go.
- Yes.
We are not enough with our own jokes.
What should I do?
What are your memories of your first kiss?
I see. Let's talk about that.
They had not yet talked like this.
Kubota, can you talk first?
My first kiss?
When I was in the ninth grade.
I went to a lame clothing store that sold everything from women's clothing to youth clothing with female friend.
We were browsing clothes.
She went into the fitting room and I waited.
"Not yet?"
"Wait a second."
I opened the door to the fitting room and there she was, beautifully dressed.
"This is good, buy this."
She closed the door.
"Are you changing now?"
"Yeah."
But I couldn't resist, so I opened the door and kissed her.
In the fitting room?
I kissed her deeply in the fitting room.
I have never heard this kind of story from Zakoshi.
When did I do that? Hmm.
At that time I had a buddy and I lived with him.
One day, Messenger's Kuroda-san brought a woman he picked up to my house.
Kuroda-san had sex with her.
Then Kuroda-san asked, "Do you want to do that too?"
So I did.
Worst story ever.
That's when I had my first kiss.
I had always been a virgin.
How old were you then?
I was about 24 at the time.
Isn't that too late?
Did you have a high sex drive?
- Sex drive?
- Yes.
Was my sex drive strong again?
But I used to jerk off a lot.
I jerked off again and again.
I did enough to make it to the Olympics.
This is the story with Seshita of Tenjiku-Nezumi.
He has a strong sex drive.
More than 10 years ago, I was invited by him to join him because two women were coming and he asked me if you would like to come too.
When I went to his house, he was reading a comic book.
Later, two women came to the house.
We drank.
I can say this because it was a long time ago, but four of us had sex.
I am ashamed to say that I am a premature ejaculator.
I came first, so I was in the bathroom washing my cock.
Then I heard Seshita's voice saying, "He's a pathetic senior."
He seemed to be getting cocky.
And I left the bathroom.
He had a woman on his lap, his right hand rubbing another woman's boob and his left hand turning the pages of a comic book.
That's incredible.
They still don't laugh at this.
As I mentioned earlier, when I worked with her, I found a 0.01mm condom in her bag.
- You haven't had sex, have you?
- I have!
No, you haven't.
So I wondered.
But it doesn't matter if she has it.
You've had that one for quite a while, haven't you?
Yes.
You only had one of those, how long have you had it?
One week.
You've had it for a week?
One week ago....
- It would be difficult to say anything private.
- If you don't want to tell us, you don't have to.
But I will tell you.
Really?
I have my first boyfriend.
Oh, really?
But....
I broke up with him a week ago.
I feel sorry.
You broke up?
I tried to convince him, but he said it was impossible.
So finally....
I told him to just let me lick his dick.
That's not good!
Why aren't they laughing!?
It's crazy that they don't laugh at this.
So I told him to just let me lick his dick.
- I was told no by him.
- She was turned down by him.
"Why not?"
He was wearing shorts at the time.
I spread my little finger as wide as I could and touched his balls.
I put my hand in the gap between his shorts.
- And you broke up?
- Yes.
Then finally you could touch his.
You didn't have sex with him?
I only dated him for a month.
So you had that condom with you at one point?
- Yes.
- So you've never used it?
- I used it once before I started dating him.
- Really?
I had no idea...
Why didn't he let me lick his dick at the end?
That's impossible.
What was so wrong about Yuriyan?
He told me, "I just couldn't get myself to love you."
- Did something happen to him?
- I have no idea.
You've lost weight, though.
I see.
But let's forget and move on.
I would like to hear Yamamoto-san's story as well.
So, tell us about the time you were naughty in Hokkaido.
(Note: 7)
- Have you been naughty?
- Naughty?
Sugarcoat it and talk about it.
Sugarcoat?
Words that cannot be said directly should be said in place of the name of the dessert.
For example, "17 year old cream puff".
- That could just be an internet hoax.
- Yeah, we want to know the truth.
That day...
There was an amateur baseball game the next day, so we, as players, had to stay at the hotel.
I didn't leave the hotel because the next day was a game and there was a fireworks display in front of the hotel and lots of people.
Some of the younger players went to pick up women because of the fireworks display.
- Are they young comedians who are not that famous?
- Right.
Then I got a video call.
They said to the girls, "Look, it's Yamamoto-san."
They said, "Yamamoto-san, they are good girls, why don't you join us in the room for a drink?"
I ask them, "Are you guys old enough to drink?"
"Of course!", they replied.
So I allowed a few people to come to my room.
She asked me, "Can I invite my friend?"
I said yes.
Then two girls entered my room.
Apparently there was a problem with those two girls.
The girls were wearing yukata.
(Note: 8)
We were in a very good mood.
So I said, "I think it's time for each of us to go into our individual rooms in pairs and talk separately for 20 mins."
They said let's do it!
We split up into each of our own rooms.
But the girls stayed in my room.
It's a 20-year-old cream puff.
20 cream puffs?
20-year-old cream puff?
No, this is different.
How can I put it?
Is is tiresome?
- The story is fucking long!
- Fucking long!
And if you're going to talk that long, don't say the name of the dessert!
We can't tell you to "Say the name of the dessert!"
You really suck at this!
Did you forget all your skills in Miyazaki?
It's okay even if it's a lie, compare it to a meat wrap rice ball.
If you won't say the name of the dessert, don't say the end!
We can make jokes about it!
Fucking long!
It's just like the old lady's wartime story.
Your story is fucking long.
Fucking long.
You're a fart.
- You're a fart.
- It stinks!
That's no surprise
Fucking long.
What the hell was that?
"20-year-old cream puff."
What did he sugarcoat?
- That was a little long.
- Fucking long!
- I’m irritated.
That's all.
Is it finished?
- Zakoshi, can I see your joke list?
- Sure.
- That's a lot of stuff.
- Yeah.
- Do an exaggerated impression of Nagano.
- Nagano.
This is an normal impression of Nagano.
"If Kuwabata-Ohara is here, then this is Osaka."
And this is an exaggerated impression of Nagano.
- What was that theory this guy just mentioned?
- Where's the essence in this?
- He ignores all the theories.
- There's no semblance of normal impression in this.
What he said earlier and what he is doing are completely different.
- He was lecturing them on theories earlier.
- They don't laugh.
These guys don't laugh easily.
Yeah.
They have come this far, I don't think they will laugh anytime soon.
- Are there any videos you haven't shown us yet?
- Yes, would you like to watch it?
Let's watch that.
I brought a lot of videos.
But you guys won't laugh when you watch this.
- You guys don't laugh at easy things.
- Let's relax for a moment and watch this.
This is a subliminal effect video made for a solo live performance.
- If you watch this, you will lose your mind.
- Here we go.
"Subliminal Effect."
"Hi."
"I'm Piss shhh shhh Saburou."
"Huh?"
"That is a lie."
"Hello, I am Hollywood Zakoshisho."
"The solo show to be held this time is Season 12."
This is in the way.
Subliminals are shown repeatedly?
- Yes, this is an exaggerated subliminal video.
- Yeah.
- This is no longer subliminal.
- Yes.
The subliminal video is longer.
"This year we managed to put on a show."
How does he feel when he speaks?
Come on!
Don't slow down the video you fast-forwarded on your own.
- This is so messed up.
- I'm losing my mind.
This looks like a curtain pattern.
"I will do it with the same quality as usual, so I hope everyone who comes to the venue and you who are in front of your PCs will enjoy the live performance."
I hate this.
I hate this the most.
This one started doing those things.
- I hate this.
- Really so.
"This is a subliminal effect, right?"
"Yeah, it's a subliminal."
"It's a subliminaaaal."
"It's a subliminal, subliminal, subliminal, subliminal, subliminaaaaaaal."
"Subliminaaaaaaal."
Here it is again.
I hate this too.
- Me too.
- Yeah.
- It was a long video.
- You guys endured this.
- I'm losing my mind.
If anyone has a video you can play it.
- Doesn't Kubota have a video?
- I don't have a video.
- Then I'll play another one.
- I want to watch another one.
- Yeah.
- We can watch this.
- Yes, we can just enjoy this.
Entertainers sometimes hold apology conferences.
I made an apologetic video in my own way.
- Is that what you made it for, in case you did something wrong?
- Yes, please watch this.
"Apology."
This is important.
You must sincerely apologize for these things.
- You should never joke around in these occasions.
- Of course.
- Is this an apology video?
- Yes.
- You have feces on your head.
- That's an apology.
That's an apology.
Is he not speaking because he is so emotional?
I see.
He looked forward.
Again?
This again?
I saw this earlier.
This is an apology from me.
This is my heartfelt apology.
This is my apology.
Fucking long!
This is my heartfelt apology.
What part of this is an apology?
Why does it change color?
Why the change of color when you apologize?
There can be no apology by the sound of this.
Nice, nice!
You guys don't laugh.
This is not an apology.
This is how it is.
Let him apologize.
He has apologized most of all.
Me!?
You have apologized many times.
I am very sorry for what I have done to you.
When I was offered the chance to participate in this time's Documenl Champion Tournament, I wondered how I could make everyone laugh more than they did.
But I can't think of that at all.
At the meeting stage with the staff I told them I couldn't do it.
So I decided to at least have fun.
I figured I was going to leaving soon anyway.
However, since I was there, I decided to do something before leaving.
But only time passed.
I am truly sorry!
He apologized firmly.
What an honest man he is.
- He told us everything without disguise.
- That's good.
- One hour left.  Good luck to everyone.
- Thank you.
- See you guys.
- That was a good apology, though.
He has come this far with that in mind.
- The dessert thing was also terrible.
- 20 year old cream puff.
"20 year old cream puff.....No, 20 cream puffs."
- It didn't make sense.
- Yeah.
What will the four of them do in the remaining hour?
"What kind of work do you do?"
(Note: 9)
This is an impression of Akko-san done by Shachihoko.
(Note: 10)
"What kind of work do you do?"
I work part time in a Chinese restaurant.
Is that so?
Then that's good.
I didn't know that.
"What kind of work do you do?"
What kind of work do you do?
- I sing songs.
- Really? What kind of songs do you sing?
I sing songs.
What kind of work do you do?
- I do not know your song.
- What kind of work do you do?
- Don't touch me.
What would I be able to do if I went in that room?
- Matsumoto-san is going to that room?
- But should I stop doing that?
Wow, it's great.
- I'll do something you might like.
- Really?
- I'll do an impression of Kaminuma-san.
- Don't do that!
(Note: 11)
- Kaminuma-san.
- Don't do that!
This is a normal impression of Kaminuma-san.
"Miki is very hilarious!"
"They are really hilarious!"
"I like their comedy."
And this is an exaggerated  impression of Kaminuma.
Desaane.
Kaminuma-san is not like that.
What?
This is an exaggerated one.
- Shall I do an impression of Kaminuma-san?
- Please.
- Normal impression of Kaminuma-san.
- Normal Kaminuma?
Please say Kaminuma-SAN.
When I hear that name, I panic.
This is an impression of Kaminuma when she is on Chatting Cooking.
What am I supposed to do!?
What am I supposed to do?
Do you realize that this is a Champion tournament?
Then I'll go over there.
- I don't know what I can do.
- This is the first time.
- Okay, I'll leave the card here.
- Yes.
- This is the first time this has happened.
- I wonder what is going to happen.
They will be very surprised.
They will not understand the situation at first.
They will think he probably came to tell them something.
Oh, never mind.
You guys are hilarious, though.
They will not be able to grasp this situation.
They will have suspicions.
It's a...
Shall we play Shiritori then?
(Note: 12)
Ah, Shiritori.
The air of the room has changed.
Let's play Shiritori with the names of fictional Hollywood stars.
Fictional Hollywood stars.
Don't say the name of a real person.
Please tell me the Hollywood star's name who could exist.
Who to start with?
Okay, let's start with Kubota.
Let's say it at the right tempo.
Hollywood stars...
Polsed Lucamaniya
(ぽるせっとるかまにや)
- Huh?
- Polsed Lucamaniya.
Polsed....Lucamaniya.
Avil Cage.
(あびるけいじ)
You are wrong.
That's a "や" for the last letter.
Sorry.
Yavil Cage.
(やびるけいじ)
Okay, Yavil Cage.
Next is "じ".
Jun Chicken.
(じゅんちきん)
That's a "ん" for the last letter.
This is a Shiritori.
Why did you say the word ん in the last letter?
Chickenback.
Jun Chickenback.
(じゅんちきんばっく)
- What's with that family name?
- Chickenback.
Is there such a person?
Of course.
If you need to deliberate as you are doing now, please also tell us what the actor has performed.
Jun Chickenback?
What movie was he in?
The movie he appeared in was...
"A Newborn Lion."
- Did he win any awards for that work?
- Yes.
- He won the award for Best Supporting Actor.
- Really?
- Jun Chickenback?
- Yes.
Next is く.
Kusekusse Kusee
(くせくっせくーせー)
(Note: 13)
- Hey, that's wrong.
- That's wrong, Zakoshi.
- Kusekusse Kusee?
- Yes.
- Next is せ.
- Names beginning with せ...
Sempotarchi Tapo.
Sempotarchi Tampon.
(せんぽたーちたんぽん)
That's an "ん" for the last letter.
Sempotarchi Tapo.
(せんぽたーちたぽ)
That is not a name like a Hollywood star.
Is that so?
He was in a good movie.
Tapo?
Next is Po.
Paul Paul Paular.
(ぽーるぽーるぽーらー)
Paul Paul...?
Paul Paular?
Paul...?
Paul Paul Paular.
Paul Paul Paular?
Next is ら.
Lant Hihi.
(らんとひひ)
Isn't that a Mantohihi(Hamadryas baboon)?
The movie he performed in is Mantohihi(Hamadryas baboon).
The name and the name of the work happen to be similar?
His name was similar to Mantohihi, so he was appointed.
- Is he playing the part of a Mantohihi?
- Of course.
- Is the movie interesting?
- Yes.
How many hours is the film?
This is a short film.
So this is about an 8 minute film.
This film is available in several short story anthologies.
It is drawn from the scene of his birth in this film.
Lanto Hihi.
Next is ひ.
Hiku Hiku John Polnareff
(ひくひくじょんぽるなれふ)
No, no, no...
There are people with those names.
(Note: 14)
- Hiku Hiku? He's an unusual name.
- Yes.
Can I switch to wrestling moves?
Sure.
Then start with Zakoshi.
- What is the first letter?
- Say a wrestling move that might exist.
- Okay.
Don't tell me the wrestling moves that exist.
Piss Lock.
(しょんべんがため)
Piss Lock...
Yeah, that doesn't exist.
Next is め.
Let's say it at the right tempo.
Smear Feces to the Eyeballs and Press.
(めんたまぬりぐそつぶし)
Smear feces?
Smear feces to the eyeballs.
This is a technique that heel wrestlers do.
Next is し.
Feed Them to Shiba Dog.
(しばいぬくわせ)
- You're going to feed your opponents to dogs?
- Yes.
- The opponents are fed to the Shiba Dog.
Feed Them to Shiba Dog!?
This move involves calling a Shiba dog and having the dog eat the opponent.
That's scary!
Next is せ.
"45 minutes for you to touch my back."
(せなかまでよんじゅうごふん)
(Note: 15)
That last letter is ん.
Again?
Why?
"45 minutes for you to touch my back - Lock."
(せなかまでよんじゅうごふんがため)
Next is め.
Hey, what kind of wrestler's moves is that?
Destiny Shiba Dog.
You are influenced by hers.
Is Feed Them to Shiba Dog one of...
That is one of Destiny Shiba Dog's moves.
That's what she said earlier.
You are influenced by Shiba dog one.
It was pretty fun.
- It was a meaningful time.
- Oh, no one laughed.
It may finish with no one laughing anymore.
What will they do in the last 30 minutes?
Good luck.
- See you.
- Thank you.
Only 30 minutes left!
- Gosh!
- Yes, you have 30 minutes left.
They really don't laugh, do they?
They have to do it with all the limiters off.
They didn't laugh at all.
Perhaps there is no such thing as laughing in their thinking.
- There were several funny points.
- Yeah.
- He's come.
- He came again.
What do you want?
Ouch.
What are you doing!?
In the end, Fuwa-chan didn't say anything.
he is using words she won't normally use.
He probably doesn't know much about her.
Wht's this?
I'll do an impression of Noda Crystal.
(Note: 16)
"I don't want to grab the strap!"
Hey, your soles are too dirty!
He laughed!?
You laughed.
I would like him to watch the replay.
This needs to be checked.
Did Yama-san or Kubota laugh?
I would like him to watch the replay.
I didn't get a good look at it.
So I will check.
Who laughed?
Yamamoto-san laughed when I said "Hey, your soles are too dirty!"
Sorry if I'm wrong.
This is alright.
This was alright.
You don't do Fuwa-chan jokes?
This joke is incomplete.
- Is it still  incomplete?
- Yes.
That's not good.
Fucking long!
If you're going to talk, talk quickly!
So, was it alright this time?
Yes.
Anyway, Yamamoto was alright.
Here we go.
There are only 20 minutes left.
I do an impression of the clerk in Ganbare Goemon(NES).
The clerk in Ganbare Goemon(NES).
- There was a guy like that.
- Yeah.
There was a guy like that.
But now that guy is gone.
Hey, you're scaring me.
What are you doing?
- Hey, your mouth is bleeding!
- Don't bleed from the mouth!
- Yuriyan?
- Are you okay?
Lots of blood.
That just turned me off!
This is a mouth ulcer.
- You bleed too much from your mouth.
- Did you bite your tongue?
- This is a mouth ulcer.
- You were coughing up blood like when you bit your tongue.
If I were Chidori Nobu, I would say this.
(Note: 17)
Squid, squid!
Squid, squid, squid, two squid sushi!
He never says that.
Two squid sushi!
Squid, squid, squid, two squid sushi!
- They're awesome.
- How tough.
They are tough.
I'll do an impression of Viking.
(Note: 18)
Nishimura: "I haven't been to this school in a long time, so I miss it."
Nishimura: "Oh, that's Kotouge-sensei, who was my homeroom teacher!"
Nishimura: "Kotouge-sensei, long time no see!
It's Nishimura!"
Kotouge: "Who are you?"
Nishimura: "Don't you remember me?
It's Nishimura!"
Kotouge: "I don't remember you."
- That was like him?
- Yeah.
What if you exaggerate it?
Enough exaggeration already.
An exaggerated impression of Viking.
Is this alright or out?
Is this alright too?
I'll do an impression of the person in charge after I bombed on the local stage.
A comedian bombed on stage.
Afterwards, the person in charge came to the dressing room.
The person in charge is angry.
"Thank you very much!!"
"Thank you and see you next time!!"
- He is angry.
- Who does that?
I'll do an impression of the school principal who greeting the students.
He suddenly becomes louder.
"I hope you all know...."
"what a great school THIS is."
There is no one like that.
Can I try it?
New Year's greeting from a head of yakuza I saw on Youtube.
He suddenly spoke louder.
"Today is a celebratory day."
"I'm glad you guys are alive."
"It's a life or death world, so we have to work with gusto this year."
"Don't get carried away.
You know what I mean?
Then grab a glass."
CHEERS!!
Fuck, this is piss!
Someone tell me that in advance!
If I told you that, you would say, "Don't ruin my joke."
We all knew that!
They still don't laugh at this!
They never laugh?
Are you okay?
- Stop saying that every time.
- Are you okay?
Don't say that to me every time.
Why is he so angry?
Like last time, stop worrying after I make a joke.
"I'm Sumiko Sumioka!"
(Note: 19)
No, it's not.
It's Nishioka.
Nishi in Nishioka.
Sumi in Sumioka.
They eventually became one and Sumiko Sumioka was born.
Draw!!
Ippon!
- I'll do an exaggerated impression of 2700.
- What?
(Note: 20)
First, I'll do a normal impression of 2700.
"Right elbow and left elbow.
Look at these alternately."
And this is an exaggerated impression of 2700.
"Right piss and left piss.
Piss these out alternately."
- Stop flailing your dick.
- So?
- Please top flailing that.
- What are you asking for?
Say something!
Does it make sense to fix the microphone with a compress?
- What's this?
- I'm putting a compress right here.
- Really?
- Yes.
It's to keep the skin from getting rougher, isn't it?
- It's to keep the skin from...
- Shut up. What are you talking about?
- It's to keep the skin from getting rougher, isn't it?
- You've been loud all along, you stupid bastard.
- What the hell are you?
- Shut up.
- You shut up.
Hey, someone cut a hole in my chest and tie this mic on!
- Then I'll drill a hole in it like this, shall I?
- Do it!
That's enough!
Are you okay?
"Are you okay?"
What the hell are you saying?
"I'm fine!"
(Note: 21)
You aren't fine.
"I'm fine!"
Don't go next!
- "Let's go next!"
- Don't go next!
I've got a video of "I'm fine", so watch it.
Is he showing the video at this time?
Show me that.
- About 10 minutes left.
- A video of "I'm fine"?
Please show this.
Thanks.
"I'm fine."
Did you put a mirror in the middle of his face?
- "I'm fine."
- I'm fine.
Fucking long!
Why does it take this guy so long to say it?
Why he...
"I'm fine!"
- This is scary.
- Are you scared?
There are more.
Would you like to watch the others?
How about this?
Please show this.
- Quiz: Balls are Show by Shoubai?
- Jyow by Jyobai.
(Note: 22)
Let's get started!
Guess what he is making!
- What's he making?
- Surely this is something obscene.
There is a blur on something.
What's he making?
The correct answer was soy sauce.
It's soy sauce.
- Isn't this the juice from your ass?
- It's soy sauce.
It had nothing to do with the clues video.
- There are only 7 minutes left.
- And...
The anime has a preview of the next episode.
I made a video that I put together just a preview of the next episode.
Watch this.
The next preview of the anime.
Preview of the next episode
"Chimbou man came back to shit and piss, dangling Chimbou."
"Now a new legend of poop is revived."
"Next time, Fist of the Chimbou.
[The Saviors Hold Chimbou!]"
"You already have a pepper stuck in your urethra."
Preview of the next episode
"Finally, Chinko of the Balls General, the user of the piss-shit fucking stinks fist, began to shit."
- "Next time, Fist of the Chimbou [My balls were crushed!  Dick! Crush all the balls in a vise!!]
- Is this just a compilation of the previews for the next episode?
- Yes, this is like Fist of the North Star.
(Note: 23)
"Your Chimbou has already been run over with a road roller."
"Chimbou incarnated, Chimbou Reverse!"
"How does Chimbou-ro stand up to giant balls with amazing smells?"
"Next time, Fist of the Chimbou.
[Fist of shit!
Once I start shitting, I can't stop!!]"
"Let me put a pepper in your urethra."
"Let me put a pepper in yours."
- Wasn't that already put in there?
- No.
No one laughed at that either.
Does anyone laugh at this hour?
- It was funny.
- Right?
What's this?
What are you going to do now?
I'm fan lady. I will do Fan Lady at this time.
(Note: 24)
Turn on the faaaaan.
We are Rice.
(Note: 25)
Rice-san?
I'm Fan Lady.
Introduce me to a womaaaan.
Turn off the faaaaan.
Put lava in my urethra.
Put airsoft pellets in my urethraaaaa.
Put me in your urethraaaaaa.
Put a fortune in my urethraaaaa.
- You shudder when pull that fortune out of your urethraaaaa.
- Its fortune is excellent luuuuuck.
Let me tie that fortune to your urethraaaaa.
Now it is your turn to say.
Make that fortune a small fortune from a big fortune.
That's nothing match....
There are only two minutes left.
Look!
What should I look for?
What are you doing?
What the hell is that?
- What the hell is that?
- Did you just wet your bangs?
Did you just wet your bangs?
I will do an impression of AMEMIYA.
(Note: 26)
"I have tried this since early spring until I was satisfied with the taste of this just in time for summer."
"And today."
Why does he exaggerate that phrase?
- And today.
- You just repeat that part?
Is that all you do?
30 seconds left.
They have great stamina.
- Where are you going?
- Ouch!
We have to kill each other now!
It's over!
Great!
- It's over.
- I'm tired.
I was the most tired I've ever been.
I can't do it.
Champion is strong!
So strong!
- Everyone is strong!
- Everyone is not laughing!
Nothing works!
But I fought!
I have no regrets!
Thank you!
- You guys are awesome!
- Nice fight!
You guys have great stamina.
It was a masterpiece.
You guys fought well for 6 hours.
So...
The winner of the Grand Champion competition is....
Zakoshi!
Hell yeah!
Is it serious!?
Thank you!
You had a great number of moves.
He did not run out of stamina until the end.
Really?
Kubota was strong.
So I didn't think I could win.
- No,no.
- Your moves were tremendous.
You had a lot of moves and Chimbou.
This is a show where Chimbou is allowed.
I never said I would allow Chimbou, though.
- But maybe it is allowed.
- Thank you.
Kubota and Yuryan also did well.
Yamamoto didn't work that hard.
- I am so sorry.
- What's wrong with you?
I can only say that I am truly sorry.
Let me say one thing.
I am not trying not to laugh that hard.
I'd try to make some jokes, but my mind just went blank.
So I couldn't think about offense or defense.
Fucking long.
You were warned about the cream puff one, weren't you?
I am really sorry.
- I am so sorry everyone.
- Fucking long.
Matsumoto-san, I am so sorry.
You haven't made a single joke yet.
So the winner of the Grand Champion Tournament is Zakoshi!
I'm so happy!
- Perfect!
- Thank you!
I got this!
This is the third time I have won 10 million yen!
I am really tired.
They didn't laugh when I did that.
And Yuriyan...
Whenever I made a joke, she would always join in.
So I hated her.
I don't always score points if I make jokes.
- But it was good.
-It was perfect.
Niiiiiice.
- Thank you for the 6 hours.
- Thank you.
It was amazing.
Especially in the second half we enjoyed it a lot.
This is a quality that I think the viewer will be fully satisfied with.
They were really great defensively.
He won 30 million yen for a show.
Yeah.
But I think it's good.
It's hard to find someone who can do that.
He's not on a five-day weekend tomorrow, is he?
He probably has work tomorrow.
That is unthinkable.
Dedicated to all Gaki fans