THIS PROGRAM IS THE RECORD
OF A "BATTLE" AMONGST COMEDIANS.
IN ORDER TO PRESERVE QUALITY,
IT IS MOSTLY UNEDITED.
AS SUCH, VIEWERS MAY ENCOUNTER
EXPLICIT CONTENT.
What would it be like if you participated
as a player?
Well...
What do you think?
There's a certain element to consider,
that I can't really deny.
Them being polite to me
would interfere with the comedy.
That's pretty much unavoidable.
Now that I'm over 50 years old,
it's tough to work with young comedians
in their twenties and thirties.
I want to work with them,
but you can't tell if they really think
I'm funny, or if they're being polite.
That's the age I've reached.
That's hot.
Things like, "The mechanism of laughter."
And, "What is laughter?"
"What is it that we find truly funny?"
I think this program will make us consider
concepts like that.
I still haven't found answers
to questions like that myself.
-Jimmy Onishi!
-Damn!
You're out!
THE PREVIOUSLY ELIMINATED PLAYERS ARE:
JIMMY ONISHI & DIENOJI'S OHCHI
He let you go so many times.
That's still only two gone.
Two people out in one hour and a half.
-How's the pace?
-Pretty fast.
-Several of us have no more chances.
-You're right.
I have one chance left.
Losing Jimmy is huge.
Start.
It's a huge difference.
-He was dangerous.
-I'm going to smoke.
We have only eight left.
Kawahara keeps opening
new bottles of water.
Someone keeps taking mine.
I had one there, but...
you drank it, right?
Did you?
-Kawahara keeps opening new bottles.
-Fujimoto drinks from others' new bottles.
He's always been like that.
-Not always.
-I never realized that.
He never drinks from his own.
I wouldn't say that.
He looks strong.
-He looks like a demon.
-This is a strong one.
-This one's definitely strong.
-Please don't hurt me again.
He can't breathe through his nose.
-Please don't hurt me.
-Look at his eyes.
They're squashed.
-I still hurt from that fall.
-Can he breathe through his nose?
His mouth's open.
He can't breathe otherwise.
-It's wide open.
-It's stuck open.
That is funny.
He is scary.
-The mask makes him do it.
-Give up?
Shut up. Shut up.
"Shut up"?
Give up?
Shut up!
Why is he saying, "Shut up"?
What a bad actor.
He's so bad at faking it.
My bone's broken.
It's broken.
Shall I make something to eat?
-You don't mind?
-Not at all.
-No, thanks.
-I watch the show Cooking Papa.
I said, "No."
-You can only make hamburgers, right?
-My dad's a sushi chef. I'll make sushi.
-No sushi, please.
-I don't know what sushi is.
Why not?
Bake me some beans.
You always cook beans, right?
-What?
-With ketchup and...
Oh, here's a new one.
I use salt and pepper...
Soy sauce,
and the flavor of the ingredients.
That's pretty funny.
-Give up?
-Shut up!
"Shut up"?
How cute.
Heart-shaped eyes.
-Sorry I didn't bring my American cape.
-Why don't you use mine?
The mouth part is so small.
You sure have a lot of masks.
-That's so cute.
-Yeah.
He's doing it again. The third time!
Give up?
Shut up.
-He broke my throat bone.
-How many throat bones do you have left?
-He's got so many masks. More coming?
-You're all out, right?
-We don't need any more.
You keep eating that.
-He does.
-You like dumplings?
He likes bald, round things.
You like dipping them in sauce?
Kukky, he's back.
The masked man's here.
This wrestler is a funny one.
He's a funny one.
Not your typical wrestler.
-Does he really exist?
-Probably made it himself.
Is that really a lucha libre mask?
Does he really fight in Mexico?
What are the horns for?
That's intense.
-He's scary.
-Isn't he supposed to be zany?
Maybe he's just plain insane.
-They look alike.
-He's trying to say something.
What?
-What's this?
-"They're mother and child."
"They're mother and child"!
-That's Jimmy's line.
-It must be him.
-He's back.
-Jimmy came back.
-The next one is the last.
-Last one?
Last one.
That would have made me laugh.
What's up, Saito?
I can't stand the bugs.
They are gone.
Those bugs.
So that's what your scalp looks like wet.
There's more?
-We've had enough.
-That's a new mask.
Is it a different color?
It's a different color version of
the first one.
-It's a leopard pattern!
-Yeah, it is.
-It says, "M."
-What does that mean?
What does the "M" stand for?
"Masato." From the comedy group
The Bonchi.
Masato.
Masato doesn't wear masks.
When he eats lunch,
he does it really, really slowly.
Then he says, "Now I don't need to eat
three meals today."
He showed me the inside of his mouth once.
His tongue was tiny.
Really.
He has a really big mouth,
but his tongue is tiny.
That must be why he eats so slowly.
-Is his tongue short?
-It's not short.
It's a normal shape, it's just tiny.
I have a long tongue.
-Really?
-Yes.
I can stick it in my nostril.
Show us.
-That's super short.
-It doesn't reach at all.
Maybe you should aim for one nostril.
Not the middle.
Make your tongue longer,
or your top lip shorter.
Why did you lie? It doesn't reach at all.
-You must be too far away to see.
-I can see from here.
It's in my nostril.
Is it?
See, I wasn't lying.
-On closer inspection, it does reach.
-No, it doesn't.
It didn't reach.
-Anthony's been gone for a while.
-You're right.
Anthony, your seniors are waiting for you.
-Sorry.
-What are you doing?
-I had to wear something more comfortable.
-Going somewhere?
-You're looking fine.
-I didn't go out much this summer.
-He's mighty fine.
-Yeah.
-Let's brighten things up and play a game.
-Nice idea.
-Do you have one?
-I do.
We used to play it in the dressing rooms.
Can I take the mic off?
Sure.
-Should we do that too?
-No need.
-It's called "Analympics."
-"Analympics?"
It's a contest to see
who can show their anus the quickest.
I was the champion.
-Really.
-Wow.
I don't have any trademark gag to rely on.
I can't really think of
any great strategy.
So, I'm going to do what I used to do.
My seniors used to really laugh at
the silly things I did
when we were in the dressing rooms
at the comedy theater.
That's what
I'm planning to spring on them.
That's my only plan.
-First, you strip down to your underwear.
-Okay.
And then, the Analympics start.
-What cute underwear.
-They are.
Nice curves.
Can someone say, "Ready, go"?
You'll figure out the rules.
Here we go.
Ready, go!
Wait. I saw toilet paper...
Seriously. Stop being an idiot.
-Toilet paper?
-You have toilet paper stuck on your hole.
-No way!
-You do!
You didn't just show your anus.
You showed toilet paper crumbs, too.
-You had tons.
-It looked like termites.
-No way!
-I thought you had termites.
That is so embarrassing!
Kukky.
Hachimitsu.
-Saito.
-No way!
Let's take another look.
Because there are so many of you,
I didn't catch everyone,
so let me watch it again.
Then I'll decide the color of your cards.
Ready, go!
Something's there!
Saito's laughing, right?
It's kind of hard to tell, right?
And then who's the other person?
-Hachimitsu.
-He laughed.
-With his mouth open.
Ready, go!
See?
-Didn't I hold it in?
-Well, okay.
Decision made.
So, Hachimitsu gets an orange card.
Kukky is on yellow now, right?
-I have one yellow card.
-Then you get orange!
Okay, Saito is safe this time!
Yes!
-That was close.
-You're lucky.
I didn't laugh.
I'm wondering whether that toilet paper
was part of Daisuke's plan or not.
Will you show me?
-You want to see?
-Why do you have toilet paper there?
That's the big question.
Here we go.
Ready, go!
-He has toilet paper stuck on it.
-Why the hell is it there?
That would make anybody laugh.
That has to be the worst.
It's gross.
-The toilet paper part was embarrassing.
-That means you pooped today?
I did. Earlier.
Then you used a bidet, right?
I did.
The toilet paper absorbs the water.
From the bidet.
Then it sticks to your ass.
You end up with leftovers.
-That was gross.
-That was embarrassing.
-So, you were the quickest?
-Yeah. Want to try?
-I want to check for toilet paper first.
-It gets in the wrinkles.
Want me to check?
That's the only scary part.
How is it?
How was it?
-Any toilet paper?
-You have to tell him.
-Look at it.
-Take a proper look.
I have some? Seriously?
Saito, take a look for me.
-Saito.
-Is Saito out?
-Kubota!
-Do I have any?
-Kubota still has some lives.
-Check for him, Kubota.
-Those without penalty cards should look.
-Kubota, look!
Those without cards, take a look.
Look at him!
-I see some.
-Please show us properly. A bit more.
-Show us more.
-A bit more.
How's this?
You can't blame him.
Showing your ass is gross.
What was that?
Please wash your hands.
That hurt.
Did you stick a bunch of needles up there?
We wouldn't stick a bunch of needles
in your anus.
Only a bunch of needles can hurt
like that!
That's what I'm talking about!
We can hear you.
My butthole really hurts.
Seriously.
That rubber is really strong.
He's washing his ass.
Don't do that in the kitchen!
-Don't do that in the kitchen.
-That's disgusting.
Don't touch my anus.
Fujimoto, that's not cool.
-That's not right.
-But he still has lots of toilet paper.
That was the most painful thing ever.
Hurts more than when
that 750 cc bike hit me.
What a liar.
Is it all gone?
-Wipe it off.
-Yeah, wipe it off for him.
Is it gone?
Do I still have some?
Remove it.
Blow on my ass.
Blow on it.
Huff on it. Puff on it.
Please huff on his ass.
You've come this far.
Go all the way.
Blow it. Huff and puff.
-Check it out, ya'll.
-Yo, yo.
Huff onto his anus, endlessly
Yeah, yeah
Huff on his anus
Huffin' on an anus
Yeah
Anus, flowing endlessly
-Something wrong?
-It's "Anus Flowing Endlessly."
What's wrong?
If you're going to blow, go for it.
Turning the pages of old photographs...
Anus flowing endlessly
Yeah, yeah
Anus, flowing endlessly
-Should we all try the Analympics?
-I think so.
Do you have any advice?
You have to be quick.
So... Let me take off the mic.
Take off your pants first,
or you'll be too slow.
-But you can leave your underwear on.
-Okay.
And it's easier to see with your top off.
And then...
Wait for the "Ready, go!"
-Don't touch until you hear "Ready, go!"
-Okay.
-Say it for me.
-Ready, go!
He's quick!
That's fast.
You do it that quickly?
-That was ultra fast.
-Want to try?
You were like a gunslinger.
-You move the cheek out of the way?
-That's right.
Give me a cue.
Ready, go!
Ta-da!
-You're next, Anthony.
-I want to see a worldly butt.
-Like a "World Expo"?
-A "World Anal."
He looks fast.
He does.
-I think he has potential.
-He's in another league.
Wow!
-Wow!
-He's hot.
-I can see it already.
-Are you ready?
-If he sits, we'll see it.
-Don't sit.
-Representing America!
-Ready, go!
What was that "ka-pht" sound?
You're laughing.
Did he take himself out?
You self-destructed?
Did he laugh?
Did Anthony laugh?
It was my "Anus Time" cheer.
Put it back.
We'll do it again.
-Do it with one hand.
-Okay.
Okay? Ready...
Go!
Too slow!
Do it like you're fighting for
the American flag.
And do it exactly when the clock hits
30 seconds.
Start the moment it counts down
to thirty.
Four seconds left.
Three...
Two...
I said, "With one hand."
Look how slow you were!
It's already 28 seconds!
-Maybe you should cheer yourself on.
-Say what you did before.
I think "USA" is better.
Go "USA"!
Drop your pants on "U."
Bend over on "S."
Show it on "A."
Ready, go!
-That was faster, but I want more.
-He's still a little out of sync.
-Good idea.
-USA.
USA...
Let's take a break.
Can I stop now?
Sorry.
Maybe I should tie it.
Will you help me tie this?
-That's scary.
-You're cutting off the blood.
Scary!
I can do "USA" with this!
I think it will work.
-Give me a cue, please.
-Ready, go!
Still not right?
Nice try.
More than two hours have passed.
That was quick.
-I'm getting hungry.
-Me, too.
Shall I cook something?
I want to eat sashimi.
-You want to eat sashimi?
-Yes, I do.
-You're gonna eat sashimi?
-There's some here.
-Sashimi?
-Nope. I can't eat sashimi.
Chopsticks, please.
-Anthony, what do your parents do?
-They own a sushi restaurant.
Sushi, right?
Why don't we get him to make us some?
But he was just touching near his anus.
Not with those fingers.
-You're right.
-Bad idea.
-He was touching around his anus.
-During the "USA" performance.
Wasn't "USA" my thing?
No, it wasn't.
All you've done is drink wine.
-In two hours and 15 minutes.
-And he wore that cheap school uniform.
With that knife stuck in his head.
We should share that properly.
What's wrong with you?
-What was that?
-I thought you didn't want any.
-Behave properly.
-Always looking out for yourself, eh?
Junior members shouldn't act like that.
You're right. That was out of line.
-Come here, Saito!
-Yes?
What's your problem?
That was wrong.
-That wasn't cool.
-I'm sorry.
-Behave properly. Open your mouth.
-What's this?
You know the hierarchy at Yoshimoto.
Seniors eat first, right?
Yes, sir.
-I'm sorry.
-Grit your teeth.
-Okay?
-Yes.
-You're working for Yoshimoto.
-I am.
Don't only serve yourself.
-Okay?
-Yes.
This is the career
you always dreamed of, right?
-Who did you aspire to become?
-That's enough.
Who was your hero?
Shingo Yanagisawa.
He's not with Yoshimoto.
-Sorry.
-Okay, that's enough.
-Is it less funny?
-Things are messy enough already.
-We have lots going on here.
-It's a real mess.
Fujimoto, that's not Scotch tape.
That's called glue.
-Does the uniform make it less funny?
-Are you listening?
The material on that is too thin.
It's too messy.
Can he eat like that?
-Wow!
-He did well.
He must be used to eating like that.
But he chews so loudly.
How vulgar.
-Hey!
-That's dangerous!
Spit it out!
-Spit it out.
-I want to spit, too...
Ptooey!
He said, "ptooey."
-Did you use Scotch tape to hold that up?
-What did you use?
-Glue.
-Oh, you used glue?
Remember his little pouch?
Glue must have been the only thing in it.
-Now it makes sense.
-All he brought was glue.
-Just glue.
-Amazing.
Things have calmed down, haven't they?
Yeah, sort of.
All right.
Where are you going, Kukky?
To the bathroom.
Excuse me.
I don't want to just sit and persevere,
waiting for the others to fail and leave.
I definitely don't want to win like that.
Ideally, I'd like to win the prize
by going on the offensive.
What should we do?
Should we have him make sushi?
-Yes.
-It's easier to eat, right?
-But everyone's been touching their anus.
-You're right.
We don't have any chopsticks.
Daisuke.
Kubota, don't look away.
No way. That was too much.
That one was too much.
-What is that?
-An Egg Tenga.
The masturbator?
That one was Daisuke.
Let's take a look.
He was actually out at this point already.
-Right, Daisuke?
-I knew I'd lost it already.
So, Daisuke gets an orange card!
-Last chance.
-Yep.
-Things could go down pretty fast now.
-I see.
And Jiro's mask is so long,
I can't tell whether he's laughing or not.
-That's not fair!
-You're right!
-What a cheat!
-That's not a nice strategy.
Kukky, stop using that.
The moment I realized what it was...
Just stop it.
-Sure, I'll leave it here.
-Egg Tenga...
-But that is amazing.
-It stretches so much.
That was scary.
You stayed behind me the whole time.
It's so noisy when you breathe.
Saito's on the move.
That's right.
Ow!
-Watch out for your hair.
-It's so sticky.
Your hair will get stuck.
Wow, this is so stretchy.
But be careful with your nails.
It rips easily.
This is amazing.
Breathe in first.
Take a deep breath.
Blow it up.
That's it.
-Awesome!
-Right?
-That's awesome.
-It is.
Lift your head up.
Yes, that's it.
You're really good at it.
He's good.
Watch out, Fujimoto.
You're close.
-Are they brothers?
-He can blow it so big.
That's scary!
-That's awesome.
-They're collaborating.
They're resonating.
Well done.
-You're good.
-Thank you.
Anybody want to try it?
-No, thanks.
-But...
It feels like you're in the ocean.
Or your mother's womb.
You hardly hear anything. Wanna try?
But your face might be too big.
-Don't do it.
-Enough already.
-We've had enough.
-Jiro, don't do it.
-Anthony, stop it.
-You guys look like a comic duo.
Oh, no.
You need to breathe first.
Breathe.
-It looks beautiful on Anthony.
-But I don't fit at all.
This is fun.
He's laughing.
Who laughed?
Who is this for?
I wonder.
Who is it?
-Jiro was laughing.
-He was.
Anthony, when you said, "This is fun,"
you smiled.
It was fun, but I didn't smile.
-He did.
-He was smiling.
He was trying to trick us.
-For real?
-Anthony...
Yellow.
You deserve it.
This is fun.
He's smiling.
You smiled, right?
That's exactly what everyone's trying
not to do.
-I know.
-How many hours have you been doing this?
Kubota keeps turning away.
He's sly.
He always swivels around.
I'm still embarrassed about my ass.
I'm going to have a shower.
My ass...
Want me to wash it?
Want me to remove it?
-No...
-I'll clean it for you.
We've known each other for ages.
We're cool with things like this.
Yeah, but you're still my senior.
How will you remove it?
Will you rip it out?
It's okay.
We've known each other for ages.
You don't have to.
-Want me to lube you up a bit first?
-That's a good idea.
-You don't have to.
-Hand soap will do.
I'll just take a shower.
-You don't have to go that far.
-I'll wash my ass quickly--
-We'll clean around your anus.
-Just like this--
-That won't work.
-Yes it will.
No, it's stuck inside.
Get the soap.
Of course, it'll come off.
-I'll be fine.
-We'll help.
We can't have you
feeling embarrassed anymore.
-You definitely need it done.
-I said I'll be fine.
Hey, don't tickle me.
-Tickling is off-limits.
-You're smiling.
I'm not. You shouldn't tickle.
You took so long, the soap's gone dry.
-You don't have to.
-I'll take care of it.
-Come on.
-But...
You've been depressed ever since
you realized you have toilet paper there.
I was embarrassed. But this is worse.
I'll take a shower.
Don't stare at him.
Put your hands down.
Poke your ass up.
Doing it slowly is embarrassing.
And please don't go silent on me.
We're trying to figure out what this is.
Like I said, I'll just go take a shower.
-You don't have to go that far.
-It's not "that far."
To be honest, I've always dreamed of
removing toilet paper from your anus.
What?
-I think you should let him.
-Why?
-The timing's perfect.
-Make today special.
-"Make today special"?
-I want this.
I've been waiting for a moment like this
for so long.
It's a little embarrassing to tell you,
but it's true.
-He's such a kind man.
-Indeed.
This is so embarrassing.
-Would you? From both sides.
-Sure.
We should make it easier for Fujimoto.
-Need a cue?
-Here goes.
Do it slowly.
Ready, go. Slowly...
-There's so much toilet paper.
-There's a ton.
That's gotta make you squeamish.
Kubota, don't let go.
Don't let go!
Don't let go. I'm not finished!
-Never let go!
-Yes, sir.
Here, sir.
-Hm?
-You're laughing.
No, I'm not.
Both of you are laughing.
No, I'm not!
The two laughing men are at it.
He's removing it now!
He is. It's really working.
Is that a baby sardine?
It's not a baby sardine.
Gone?
All gone.
What was that sound?
Everything's fine.
No way.
Why didn't anybody laugh?
Hey...
What did you use on me?
What was that "phssst"?
That was terrifying.
Wait.
What the hell was that?
If it's me, I'm finished.
Daisuke and Saito!
A double elimination?
You had no more chances.
Wait. Fujimoto was laughing, too.
Everyone was laughing, Mr. Matsumoto.
I couldn't really see Fujimoto.
If he didn't see, that's that.
Others got off the hook for that earlier.
Let's look at Daisuke and Saito.
What was that sound?
Everything's fine.
Daisuke was...
Pretty much the whole time...
Look at that face.
Damn.
-So, that's it?
-That's it.
-Seriously?
-Saito and Daisuke...
You're out!
Well, it's like they all got to me.
But we do have to create
situations like that.
I was actually trying to fart.
But no farts came out.
I tried to pee,
but I couldn't do that, either.
To be honest,
I started to break when Kukky showed up
with that thing on.
I nearly lost it.
I really should have done something then.
But I was too passive. I was...
I let my guard down.
Well...
I knew it...
I shouldn't have actively participated
in a situation like that.
I mean, did you see
that toilet paper thing?
Just watching Fujimoto
trying not to laugh was intolerable.
You can't help but laugh
when someone tries not to.
My fate was sealed
the moment I stood there.
We still have three hours left.
Still only halfway.
Start!
Everyone's used up all their
prepared gags, right?
Our prepared stuff? Yeah.
Fujimoto, have you run out?
I'm not exactly out.
-This place is in such a mess.
-You're right.
-Can't we clean this up?
-Let's do it.
It's our first time in this area together.
-It is.
-You're right.
He has a kid?
I didn't know that.
Wasn't it funny when I did this?
You didn't do that.
-Ohchi did it.
-I made that.
-You didn't make it.
-I did.
You didn't make that.
What was that?
What the hell was that?
You said I didn't make it.
Because you didn't make it.
What else should I say?
You didn't make it.
-That was the simplest straight-man reply.
-Seriously?
But I did make this.
No, you didn't!
-You didn't shape it.
-It just broke.
What happened?
We have no idea.
What happened, Hachimitsu?
I guess I got tired.
-What happened?
-It hit me all at once.
Of course.
I'm gonna watch it again.
He shocked me, too.
That was such a cheerful laugh.
You didn't make that.
Hachimitsu, it's disappointing to see you
go out like this.
This is how it ends?
A little before it happened,
I'd lost my focus.
I couldn't get why Fujimoto was
so persistent about something so trivial.
I thought, "When you think about it,
I made that prop."
But he kept at it.
-He kept insisting.
-You didn't make it.
I wondered why he was so persistent
about something so trivial.
This Documental might be
even more of a mental game than I thought.
Watching Kawahara and Anthony
keeping their faces expressionless,
I have to wonder
what kind of nerves they have.
The fact they don't laugh at something
so funny makes me wonder,
"Is something wrong with these guys?"
-Remember, the prize is 10 million yen.
-It sure is.
It's 10 million yen!
But remembering that puts pressure on me.
-Stop mentioning that.
-What a prize!
-Please, stop that.
-Losing a million yen is a bigger deal.
If I lose it...
You're already thinking of losing.
I borrowed the money.
-From whom?
-Bike Kawasaki-Bike.
What? He had one million?
-No, he gave me 200,000.
-You borrowed here and there?
How about Kawahara?
I just happened to...
-I happened upon it.
-What does that mean?
Fujimoto, how did you get a million yen?
I used my savings.
Excuse me, can I have your autograph?
Your autograph.
Okay.
-As a group?
-What?
Do you want us to write it as a group,
or one from each?
-One from each, so 10.
-That many?
Okay. Thank you.
Got a pen?
-I have one.
-Okay.
-Could everyone gather around?
-Here's your pen.
-That's a thin pen.
-Sorry.
Could you write, "Takeda Tetsuya"?
"Takeda Tetsuya."
-"Dear Takeda Tetsuya..."
-No, sign it as Takeda Tetsuya.
Please sign it as Takeda Tetsuya.
-Like this?
-Yes. As "Takeda Tetsuya."
TAKEDA...
How do you write "Tetsuya" in Kanji?
-Any way you like.
-But...
-Hiragana will do.
-Okay...
I prefer it that way.
-Like an autograph?
-It's fine like that.
Thanks. They'll be overjoyed to receive
Takeda Tetsuya's autograph.
But I'm not Takeda Tetsuya.
It's for a friend back home in Kansai.
-Could you address it to them?
-"Dear Friend Back in Kansai"?
No, "Dear Kansai-ite."
"Kansai..."
-"Kansai-ite."
-"Kansai..."
"Kansai-ite."
Great. Thank you so much.
No problem.
Who is this joke for?
Can I have your autograph?
Sure.
This is bothersome.
Could you just write it here?
Could you write it here?
-On your face?
-Yes, "Good luck."
Could you write, "Good luck"?
GOOD LUCK
Who is this for?
Thanks so much!
I'm a big fan of yours!
-Thanks.
-You know him?
Of course I do.
I've been a fan forever.
I'm not on TV that much.
You're Haruka Igawa, aren't you?
Haruka Igawa.
You're Haruka Igawa, right?
-Okay.
-Thanks.
Lastly, can I get your hand print?
If you don't mind.
-Do you have a print set?
-I'll go get it--
That's usually for sumo wrestlers.
Go find one.
You're not a sumo wrestler?
Can you pull your thing out for me?
I want to slap it here.
-What?
-Can I slap your thing here?
-You want a print of it?
-I do.
-You want a dick print?
-A peni-print.
-Penis?
I don't want to.
Please.
I can't do that.
Pretty please.
Do it for him. Then he'll leave.
-Just get it over and done with.
-I can't miss this opportunity.
You can leave your shirt on.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
I've never made a dick print before.
It's a "peni-print."
He already has three autographs.
Yes. I've got three.
Not many people give peni-prints, right?
So, can I take a print?
I really don't want to.
-Will you use the marker?
-Yes.
-You'll draw the ink onto it?
-Just the underside.
-Seriously...
-It won't take long.
Excuse me.
I won't be long.
-Sorry.
-Don't pull it.
Sorry. I won't be long.
That hurts?
Shall I bring a thicker marker?
Why is he doing it bit by bit,
line by line?
-You could do it yourself.
-Sorry.
How about using some soy sauce?
That'll work.
Dip it in soy sauce,
slap it on and get it done.
Sorry, but...
My parents own a sushi restaurant.
That gives more meaning to the soy sauce.
The gods will punish me.
I'll treasure the peni-print forever.
Sorry.
Let me dip it in.
Stop it, please!
-It'll be over quickly.
-Stop it, please!
Ready?
How is it?
Thanks so much!
Please look at this.
This is the worst!
I'm going home. Thanks so much!
That was scary.
Terrifying.
Kawahara, do you have any gags?
Yes, I do.
I've never seen yours.
Really?
-I do.
-You do?
Show me.
Okay.
-This one's new.
-Sounds good.
It's a greeting joke.
"It's very nice to muscle you."
My body's not quite there yet.
Don't show it, then.
I'm planning on working out.
Will you really work out?
Yes. After all, I have this joke.
The joke came first?
Regardless of which comes first,
isn't the quality of the joke...
a bit too low?
Shall I help you kill some time?
-Shall I do that popular thing?
-What?
The Pikotaro thing.
Pikotaro.
-Pikotaro.
-It's been trending.
He goes, "I have a pen..."
-I'll do an unfunny version of it.
-Huh?
-That sounds even better.
-May I?
Ba...
Nana...
Banana!
-He sure makes it unfunny.
-That's amazing.
He's been trying to spread this.
He makes it unfunny.
Then he says, "That gag's not funny."
B...
Oo...
Boobs!
Seriously, stop being such an idiot!
-Stop being such an idiot!
-You lost to Pikotaro?
What the hell was that?
-That wasn't even remotely funny.
-Not funny at all!
It wasn't funny at all!
I told you.
I'm lucky I've seen this before.
I warned you it's not funny.
-Well, I had no choice, right?
-Yeah.
But that really wasn't funny.
-I know. That's why I did it.
-Okay.
Did you really know it wasn't funny?
Of course. That's why--
-It's funny because it's not funny?
-That's why I did it.
Daikichi laughed so hard
when I showed him, he hit the floor.
I thought, "This will work."
Well, you can't help but laugh.
I had some close calls
from the very start.
I held on to it somehow, but in the end,
I just couldn't pull through.
Sometimes the least funny things
become the funniest.
Kubota hits the spot for me.
I knew I was in trouble the moment I saw
he was one of the members.
I think Kawahara hasn't shown
his true potential yet.
I look forward to seeing what
he does from here on.
NEXT EPISODE
SEASON 1 FINALE
Dodge-bee.
What the hell is that?
It's not dodgeball?
It's dodgeball using a Frisbee.
Dodge-bee is... A moth landed on my arm!
Why?
They're too soft. Isn't that hot?