Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!
Open up, open up, open up!
Stop it, stop it!
Stop it, come on, come on
They stood right up!
Thank you so much!
Thank you very much
Alright
Huh?
There was nothing wrong
Nothing, right?
Nothing at all!
I'm gonna order some food
Let's get sushi!
You can order that?
Here's the list (of menu items)
Calm down! What the fuck man?
What happened?
He's too rough
I really want some soba, let's order some
Soba sounds good
We could also get pizza. You want soba?
We could get the big one.
Is that just for two people?
We can eat this?
We could get Mutsuki
and some soba too
Why soba anyways?
Watch out!
Pull on your chin...
One, two...
He's pulling on his chin!
Ouch!
This is Yoroku Soba!
Ah, Yoroku Soba?
I'd like to order
some soba
Understood.
What's your order?
Also, you guys
have combos, right?
Yes, we do.
We have various different ones.
He's getting closer.
Can we get a tamago bowl combo?
There he is!
An egg bowl combo, right?
I do look the part, huh?
But I've always hated that.
You do?
They think I'm serious
but it's just for fashion.
They really think
I'm a genuine soldier.
Is it the way you walk?
They think I'm serious
but it's just for fashion.
I even look the part
right now, right?
Aren't you actually
happy about that?
No, I wear camouflage
just for fashion.
It's just fashion.
Shut up!
Nadal is so battered.
You shut up, man.
I didn't understand
what he was saying.
You hung up?!
Why?!
You had to wait
not hang up.
You suck man!
You can't hang up on people.
Are you a soldier?
I'm not a soldier. I'm really just
wearing this for fashion.
People think
camouflage is always serious.
They think I'm a soldier.
I want it for the style.
But they always
look at me like that!
I just wear it for fashion!
They think I look the part!
I hate it! I've had enough!
It's always like that
for everything!
Nobody sees it as fashion!
It's always the same!
No matter what I wear
You can't combine those
I just want it
for fashion!
But they think I'm a real soldier!
I just do it for fashion.
I wanna wear camouflage like everyone else.
But maybe it's my body
or my appearance.
They think I'm for real!
I just wanna wear camouflage
like everybody else!
So what about me...?
I'm so jealous!
But when it's this color...
I don't wanna be a real soldier!
A real soldier?
I guess I'll go with
just black then.
Yeah, that'd work.
I'm gonna stop wearing camouflage!
For real!
Nobody told you to, though.
But everybody thinks
I'm a real soldier!
Is there any other fashion
you like?
Nobody's gonna complain now.
You like black...?
No one's complaining now.
No patterns. I'm over that!
I guess so...
Yeah, it's fine.
Looks good.
That works.
You see, I've always
loved camouflage.
I wanted to fit in
with the young kids.
But I guess I'll go
with a simple black then.
Looking completely normal then.
Yeah, looks good.
It doesn't matter what or how...
I always look like
I'm the one in charge.
I just wanted to wear it
for fashion!
I just wanna look trendy.
Well... I don't know about that.
Why don't you show us
how you applaud too...
Like watching something.
I just wear this for fashion.
But I only look normal
with plain black.
So you just
wear that for fun, right?
I just wear it for fun.
You can tell?
-I look like it, right?
-Please clap.
Well, that's just...
Like this, right?
That's not a warm compress, Jimmy-san.
- Huh?
- It's not a warm compress.
That guy loves food, huh?
I have stiff shoulders.
That's cheese, though.
It's not gonna help.
But it cools me, though.
That's insane.
I'm sorry you look the part, though.
I think it's just the general look.
Like the way I move?
The way I look?
Yeah, all of it.
Your gestures too
What about your speech?
Of course not!
-That's it.
-You're wrong!
It's too much.
Look at the cheese.
Private! You don't put cheese
on your shoulders!
This is a warm compress.
That sounded kinda Korean.
Don't put food...
food on your shoulders.
That's not something
you put on your shoulders!
It really sounds kinda
Korean for some reason.
It's not quite right.
I hate it!
What?
What happened?
I also hate... this body!
It's too hard to wear
a damned tank top!
It looks too good!
What's wrong with that?
I look like Bruce Willis!
Bruce Willis?
I look like him in Die Hard!
Bruce Willis was
that ripped?
He was a little jacked, yeah.
Everyone always tells me
that I look like Bruce Willis!
No one says that.
You never change.
They do!
Nope.
It's serious, man!
It is?
It's serious.
What the hell?!
Why did you laugh?
All on his own.
He laughed at himself.
Nadal is too much.
Why did you laugh?
At his face... at his face.
Because he got really mad.
At his sad face.
You thought I really got mad?
You got careless, Soshina.
He made that sad face...
He thought I was angry.
He looked pitiful.
Huh? You did?
I didn't think it was funny
So you laughed at that?
I just felt sorry for him.
It was a strained face.
It's serious, man!
It is?
It's serious!
What the hell?!
No way you did!
Well, I guess so...
I'm fully aware that what I do
isn't funny at all!
I think it was me!
What was with that face? Seriously...
It was emotional
It really got to you
I'm too good, sorry about that.
You got intense
all of a sudden.
Soshina, yellow
Okay, gotta get into it.
That was serious.
For real.
It's serious!
What the hell?!
Koba-san is too harsh.
I'm pissed.
Go home already!
Alright
Get out already!
For real?
I'm serious!
What's with that guy?
Won't you take that off?
Help me!
What's wrong?
Help me
They asked me who I belonged to
I said I'm with Yoshimoto
But they put this on me
Huh?
And then lynched me
And they told me
to bring this to you.
What?
That's scary!
Jimmy-san...
That's bad!
Can you take it out?
That's scary!
Huh?
Whoa! It's a head!
Whoa!!
Huh?
They told me to show this to you.
Whoa!
It has a nametag.
What does it say?
Ryo Tamura. (Editor's Note: 1)
It says Ryo Tamura
It's just one?
There's more
Whoa! Whoa!
That's super scary!
They cut off everything! Eyes, ears!
It still has a nose.
It's got a tag.
Hiroyuki Miyasako.
That's what it says. (EN: 2)
Miyasako-san?
You don't have to...
There's more
Whoa!
What?
This is too much!
Stabbed with a wine opener.
Wait a second!
He was innocent!
Totally innocent!
Who is it?
Nego6-san...
Nadal smiled, right?
Nadal
It was me?
I didn't smile
Who was it?
Come on, stop this.
I know he mentioned Nego6,
but stop it.
I think it's just
psychological at this point.
That's not it, but...
Nadal?
I think I was just
biting too hard and it showed a little.
That's no good, though.
That's what the contest
is all about.
This is too much!
I think this was pretty bad.
Yeah, kinda.
Wait a second!
He was innocent!
Totally innocent!
Who is it?
Nego6-san...
I think that's it!
It counts?
I think it's
mostly because of the timing.
Second one
But I think Koba may be really pissed.
Looking at him in the monitor.
His switch flipped
since Matsumoto-san left
For sure
I think it's kinda common
Come on, focus
Have you seen me get pissed off
on stage?
-Not really...
He laughs the most.
No more chances, Nadal.
You're right, I know.
Calm down for once, Nadal.
It's been a huge bother...
Wait a second, listen to this!
Listen to me!
This is hell.
He looks so bald
when he bows.
This is hell.
A Masso (EN: 3)
A Masso
Their controversy...
They apologized, man!
I asked Anthony
what he thought (EN: 4)
I asked him on Line
About the skin color thing, right?
And then he replied
Give it a break
I'm done playing with little kids.
What does that mean?
When I went to visit my
friend's grandma for summer
she gave shaved ice to my friend.
He came back with it
and spilled it all
That's what he wrote.
He's so mentally strong!
Was it used?
This is serious, Nadal!
It's serious!
What the hell?!
To be honest, I've been
slipping up for a while.
My mental strength is waning.
What's Koba-san's
Nadal Reverse Evolution?
Uh... Sasaki Kensuke (EN: 5)
Change it!
Like earlier
Wait
you think he's serious?
Change it
Try something else.
Koba-san...
Do devolution
Uh...
Devolution...
Maybe...
A devolution for Kenkoba-san...
That's enough!
Everyone's going in
Ouch!!
Are you alright, senpai?!
What's wrong?
-It stabbed me.
-What did?
-This right here.
-You did it yourself.
Don't waste our time.
Why do you do that?
Come out, Nadal
He's still there
The company's driver
really hates you, man.
You called him just to
go buy some porn.
He says you should
stop calling him just for that.
Is that mentsuyu? (EN: 6)
Try some
Why don't you drink it then?
It's just that it's good.
Has a good aftertaste.
It's a good aftertaste!
A good aftertaste?
It's a good aftertaste.
Just gulp it down
Make sure you gulp it down.
Gulp it down.
What international bullshit is this?
What kind of retort is that?
What kind of international bullshit is this?!
Wait, what's with that retort?
Drink up!
Just drink it!
Let's make a toast
Ah, don't get pissy!
If you could see yourselves...
Hey, you.
You've sure been quiet...
You know I've been getting fewer jobs
since I won M-1?
Yeah, that happens.
Wait, the fortune teller's here.
Hello. I'm Getters Iida. (EN: 7)
I'll read anything
in your future.
Alright then...
How will the Olympics go?
The Olympics?
Let's measure.
Measure?
That's a weird word to say now.
UNO?
My fortune telling
reads "Uro's" six stars.
Uro?
The left and right cards are...
going to be turned.
Green, green.
And the ones inside as well
will get turned.
Green, green
No way!
For real?
The center is...
They're all green.
I'm not getting it
The Olympics will succeed
What the hell?!
-It's a bit dark?
-Huh?!
It's a bit dark
Why're you acting all casual?
You're doing it yourself
Like you're one to talk
while fidgeting with your underwear?
Come on, come on
Do something!
I can't do this anymore
What's with that pathetic look?
Huh?
Ina-chan smiled, right?
He did!
Huh?
What?
Ina-san?
Who was it?
Where?
Inada?
Ina-chan just...
So it was him!
He just smiled
like something really good just happened.
Huh?
Like something great happened.
Come on, come on
Do something!
I can't do this anymore
He was smiling!
What's with that?
The whole time!
I just looked at
Nadal's face
He looked so...
it was such a serious face.
I was doing my best you see
This is your first one
Ina-chan
Here we go
He didn't have one?!
I feel like
it was working though
I've been really struggling
I wasn't trying to piss you off, though.
What's with that?
He's kinda scary!
You wouldn't be doing the Uno crap
if you weren't, man!
I think there's comedy
in Uno fortune telling, though.
I think it's just
a solid idea
What're you doing?
I was just about to
get changed when
Are you in disguise like a detective?
He was about to and then
The sushi's here
Sorry for the wait
Excuse me
Thank you so much!
Right here
Read it out loud
Read it?
Someone I'd die to fuck: Zawa-chin (EN: 8)
Don't make the sushi guy
say that, man
Thank you very much
Looks great
Akiyama has also been
struggling, huh?
Kubota, sushi rail
Sushi rail
It's really like
on the level of a little kid.
Huh? What's that?
Huh?
Wh-What?
What happened?
Isn't that what Matsuo used to wear
in his Underground years?
The reggae dance?
I'd like you guys to taste
some cocktail I'm going to prepare.
That's what you're doing?
That's it?
Yeah, that's it.
He wore that for the reggae club?
Those are reggae colors?
I'm kinda used to it.
Like bam bam!
What are you gonna do, Matsuo-san?
Can you clap?
-How?
-Just like
Huh?
He's doing it there?
It's spilling!
He's mixing it there?
That's dirty.
He's soaking wet.
We have to drink that?
The lid is open
It's carbonated.
Ah!
Who's drinking it?
Koumoto-san
It's good
Yeah man!
Bam bam bam bam!
So ridiculous...
There's still some left!
Nadal.
Is it okay, youngsters?
Go ahead.
Isn't it carbonated?
Here I go. Excuse me.
Kubota and Soshina.
I see, yeah...
It feels like diluted
carbonated orange juice.
Huh?
Yeah man!
That's a good voice.
What's your name?
I'm Bob Mario
Bob Mario...
You've heard of him?
Yeah
Um...
He builds something to do with houses...
or something, right? (EN: 9)
What are you on about?
He works in-
he builds household things?
Like furniture?
The man sure liked
his incense.
The one that smells.
Incense?
You know incense?
-You don't even know it!
-I do!
What is it?
When your stomach goes
What's with you?
You're not funny.
I know incense.
Kubota is serious man!
Bob-san
Bob-san...
Delivery!
Huh? The delivery!
Hello there!
I came with a delivery!
He's the guy!
Hello there!
I'm from Yoroku Soba!
Here's the egg soba combo
you ordered.
-Soba?
-Wh-Who are you?
Excuse me! I work for Yoroku Soba
What's with your sunglasses?
BKB! Yay!
It kinda hurts.
Are you Gosuke?!
That's right! Excuse me!
He's Gosuke from the
Nadal army!
My name is Gosuke,
excuse me.
Present yourself.
People call me Gosuke rap.
I'm Gosuke Gosuke Gosuke!
I wanna be popular with girls!
I extend my hand
to girls in trouble
That's the kind of man Gosuke is sank!
Hello, my name is Gosuke
nice to meet you.
-What's your last name?
-Takasawa.
It's not Gosuke?
Ah, sorry. You mind
if I wear my glasses?
Rap it.
Rap it?
I'm Gosuke Gosuke Gosuke
May I wear my glasses?
I get stronger if my eyesight's better.
Way better.
That's the kind of man Gosuke is sank!
What's he saying?
What's that at the end?
That's the kind of man Gosuke is thank you
Gosuke is thank you...
That's right.
It doesn't rhyme.
Ah, excuse me.
You see...
Gosuke rap's strength
is not rhyming.
Nadal, just what...
He can rap,
He can't though.
And he also has
other strengths.
That's right, yes.
Isn't he strong at rapping?
-That's just for the introduction.
That's right.
So he's Nadal's helper?
That's right, yes.
Something's here!
That's right, we have a gag.
For his presentation.
You okay? Isn't it heavy?
Ah! Let me get it down
excuse me.
What's in there?
It's just...
today, you see...
Can you rap it?
I'm Gosuke Gosuke Gosuke
I'm gonna tell you what's inside.
First we have, um... uh...
First we have
this right here...
I'm Gosuke Gosuke
Gosuke has his computer.
And also this cellphone
Watch out!
Ah, right! This, look at-
I'm Gosuke Gosuke
I'm Gosuke Gosuke Gosuke,
my lightbulb broke.
It broke, so I'll have to buy one
on my way back home.
That's the kind of man Gosuke is, thank you!
Wonderful!
It's not wonderful, though.
Nadal? What even is this?
-Gosuke-san...
-Thank you very much!
So that's the real deal.
One, two, three, four!
Wishing for stuff we don't have!
I'm Gosuke
Gosuke dropped out of his graduate program
I failed a hundred interviews and now I'm here!
Please take me already!
Wishing for stuff we don't have!
I'm working at a sushi shop
but I'm also selling soba,
but we don't get any calls.
Why aren't the sound waves reaching us?!
Give me sound waves!
Wishing for stuff we don't have!
Since we don't have waves
I think it's bad, it's bad
that we don't have any waves
but maybe it's my ears that are weird!
Give me more ears!
Wishing for stuff we don't have!
There's a lot
and so now I'm doing this,
but like
it keeps going round and round
and so I wonder what's wrong with me
I don't get it!
Wishing for stuff we don't have!
Wait, wait a second.
Okay
It feels like this is Nadal's fault.
I'm sorry, but...
I haven't heard almost anything.
He's talking about stuff we don't have.
He also said something about waves?
Yes, that's right, that's just...
It's a song about things you want
but don't get.
I see.
It's a little kid gag, kind of
I'm not asking you.
Yes well, let's see
I have a fusion
with the Gosuke rap from earlier.
I wanna see that!
Wishing for stuff we don't have, here!
I'm Gosuke Gosuke Gosuke
I wanna be popular with girls!
I'll lend a hand
to any girls in trouble!
That's the kind of man that Gosuke is!
This is the Gosuke rap!
Wishing for stuff we don't have, here!
I'm Gosuke Gosuke Gosuke,
I dropped out of my graduate program
I studied hard for maths,
but ended up getting it all wrong
That's the kind of man Gosuke is!
I stayed in bed for five whole days
Wishing for stuff we don't have!
Taking it all into account
that's how I got here
Here we go!
Wishing for stuff we don't have!
That's the kind of man Gosuke is!
Thank you very much
Wishing for stuff we don't have
Koumoto-san, what're you doing?
So what changed?
Um...
The rhythm, a little
And you were talking freely?
Like, did the lyrics
get more free?
Yeah... freedom.
Can you rap about Nadal?
Same concept, "wishing for stuff you don't have".
Yes! Excuse me.
Can you wish for something
Nadal doesn't have?
-Can you do that?
-Of course, yes!
That's great.
Wishing for stuff we don't have, now!
You are Nadal, Nadal!
You're a great guy!
You always say awful things
But deep inside, you're a good guy
that's the kind of man Nadal is!
Everyone watch this!
Wishing for stuff we don't have!
You just licked his ass
It was pretty good.
He has like another 50.
Can you say the same?
About myself?
Yeah, of course.
Can you rap it, Nadal?
Do it!
I'm counting on you! Let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Ah, right, right!
Wishing for stuff we don't have!
Everyone plays dumb
acts smart
That's what's great about comedy
and I'm like that too!
Wait, that's not right!
Wishing for stuff we don't have
We have to work hard!
Thank you very much.
That was kinda bad.
Pretty rough.
Go to a school festival with just that
and you'd get murdered by the planning committee!
Do a school festival number.
Can you do it?
A school festival?
I'll be the straight man,
so you start.
Alright, here we go
Wishing for stuff we don't have
I'm Gosuke Gosuke Gosuke
school festivals sure are fun
There are many students
and a lot of shops too!
That's the kind of man that Gosuke is, thank you!
This isn't about you!
Wishing for stuff we don't have!
This is awful.
That's an awful retort
Isn't that
what comedy is all about?
Like in Matsumoto-san's style.
And people get laughs
like that.
Really?
Back in Deluxe's time, yeah.
No way, not at all.
Let's go more mainstream.
Ah, right!
It's still going?
Please, if there's something
you'd like to request, go ahead.
Ah, uh...
Then
Do Chikubo
Chikuwa! Right!
Let's go with Chikuwa! (EN: 10)
Chikuwa?
Here we go
Huh?
Huh?!
Wha-?
What happened?
Chikuwa!
He didn't say chikuwa at all!
He said Chikubo!
Chikubo!
He definitely said chikubo!
I said chikubo
You thought it was chikuwa
but I said chikubo
No way!
I've never heard of "chikubo"!
Didn't you wanna say something else?
Like "Kubota"! or something?
Me?
No, Akiyama-san
Akiyama laughed out loudly!
And Kubota too
I just saw Akiyama-san
Okay, let's look at Akiyama first
What was your helper called?
I'm Gosuke!
Sorry for my manners.
He kept going for hours, huh?
How experienced.
It was too long!
I'm Gosuke Gosuke!
Please, if there's something
you'd like to request, go ahead.
Chikubo!
Chikuwa! Right!
Let's go with Chikuwa!
Chikuwa?
Here we go
No, I think he definitely did.
Even Akiyama
has accepted it
What card is it?
I already have one
Okay, so
orange then
And Kubota too!
Why?
You laughed!
I was just reacting!
Shut up!
He laughed!
But Akiyama did too...
What are you doing?!
Akiyama kinda invited him
But Kubota also stood out!
I didn't!
I don't even know what
he means by that.
Stop it, man!
Okay, I think this is the part
where Amazon said we became
too vulgar
They even said my name, right?
Okay, take a close look then.
We're pretty far into the show
Jimmy-san, you can't be so
hostile with Gosuke
I mean, he had to look
at this stupid face.
Gosuke did.
He had to be kind after all
You were so cold
despite being older than him.
You talk way too much.
Sorry
Well, it's just that
I don't know much about rap.
You've smoked it all, man.
I can keep going
You're far too lax about that
I do it till I feel numb
My tongue gets numb if I keep going.
That's dangerous man
Are you sure about that?
You've all been
playing with girls a little too much, huh?
Yeah
You use your hips?
Hips?
You shaking 'em?
Well, more than before.
I want you to realize
just how you move your hips.
I'll act as a stand in,
so practice your moves on me.
Whoever can do it the fastest.
I want to find someone like that.
What?
Like the manliest guy?
Yeah, yeah, manliest!
We'll challenge you then.
Who's gonna start?
You choose, Kubota
Someone strong-looking...
Alright,
let's go Akiyama-san.
Yeah.
Are we gonna go full?
-Full?
-Full cock.
What do you mean?
I just wanna count.
That's the best way to do it.
Okay, give me a second.
I'm feeling sick.
He's really balding!
I didn't wanna see that.
So Nadal should stand here?
I have to take it out?
Do it
Nadal has to take it out
Take out the red balls
This is the worst
Okay, let's go, one by one.
I'll make sure to let you know
when it's good
Let us know?
With a sound
That's tiny!
You said that?
Stop that!
All ready?
Ready?
Alright! Start!
"Vulgar images not shown on screen"
No way, no way. Come on
No man...
Stop!
Alright, 19 times!
19 times!
Not bad!
Not even 15 seconds.
Who's next?
Koba-san.
Tiny!
Stop it with that!
We could turn it back later.
Alright.
Start!
He's fast!
He's quick!
33 times.
This beats the previous record.
Koba-san beat it?
It was Koyabu-san
with 25 times.
You've practiced?
I just won't lose against
a vegetarian!
Anything more?
Ask the senpais to come over.
Ask us to come over.
Why?
Ask the senpais to come over.
Isn't this rough for me already?
So you're not doing it?
So I should go there?
You probably should.
Ready?
Yeah!
Set, go!
Start!
Wait!
He went all the way!
All the way!
More than anyone else!
That's what Kubota-san is saying, yeah.
But it's also the same
as everybody else.
I'm feeling sick
This is the worst
It sucked!
You're the worst, man!
I take that as a compliment!
Everybody managed to hold on!
So Matsuo
It's his first time
-First time, yeah.
-Huh?! Your first one?!
No way!
He's held on for a long time!
Wait wait wait.
What is it, Kubota?
To be honest I'm feeling
kind of sick at myself.
You did this!
It was far worse for us!
It almost feels like Matsuo
should get more than a yellow!
But, but, well...
Yellow
Come on
Alright, that's it.
Give me a break!
I'm feeling kinda bad as well
Sorry
Here we go!
Let's do it one more time.
It looked good
We can switch
No way
No one will.
This is pretty rough.
What's your problem?!
I don't understand either!
How did it come to this?
-It's serious!
-What the hell?!
I knew he'd say that.
Don't touch me
Here we go!
Ready to start?
Akiyama-san, say the word
Alright. Come here!
Ready? Go!
Alright!
This is awful
That was pathetic! 16 time-
Huh, What's that?!
That was Nadal, right?!
Jimmy-san pisses me off.
Jimmy-san pissed me off.
But you just-!
What was that all of a sudden?
I knew you'd attack me!
What was that?
Why did you have to talk like that
Jimmy-san?
"Jimmy-san pisses me off!"
It was Nadal?!
No, I was gonna hold on, but...
But Jimmy-san went out and...
It's so frustrating!
Why did that go so wrong?!
You're out!
That sucks...
I think you saved Soshina.
He looked about to laugh.
But this guy was
really in trouble.
So two out!
There are still plenty left!
I'm trying my best
Still eight left.
I even practiced holding my laughter.
But there was no way.
It was way too funny.
I think I was in trouble
during the Gosuke rap.
I stayed in bed for five days.
Wishing for stuff we don't have!
Taking things into consideration
Gosuke was supposed to help me out
But he was always
looking right at me
It was like having an enemy
But I guess well...
I felt it again, that...
That I'm just Nishino's puppet.
It felt like that.
None of my gags worked well
It's serious!
What the hell?!
Akiyama-san went all
like this...
It's just the hernia, you know?
You have a hernia?
I thought the energy
and trajectory was pretty good
It was so stable too
Are you going, Matsuo-san?
Ready?
-Okay?
-Yeah!
Ready... Go!
This is actually pretty good...
What does he think he is?
The chief?
23 times. It's a tie.
A tie.
But considering his age
Koba-san did 40...
Seven
I think Koba-san wins
I always move the skin
when I put it in, though.
So like, if you do that...
Ah...
A tattoo?
-A tattoo?
-He has one
-It's too cute.
-It's super cute!
He has a tattoo?
Why d'you have one?
Well, I'm just saying.
I'm curious.
Aren't you curious?
Isn't anyone curious?
You should take a closer look.
Look
Then we can talk
You've been keeping
your distance, huh?
-I haven't, at all.
-You're not participating.
I'm here, I'm here.
When did you get that bra?
Take a closer look
Whoa! No way!
Thank you
It's talking?
I'm feeling sick
Hello
Hello!
Where did you come from?
Me? Yokohama!
You have to say hi.
Come say hello.
Bro
Hello!
Hello
It's nice to meet you!
It's nice to meet you too!
Hello!
Bye!
Um...
Touch me...
Caress me...
Can I touch you?
Yaaay!!
Yaaay!! Yay yay!!
He did it!
I'm really happy right now!
Yay yay yay!
Thank you! Thank you so much!
What's with his urethra?
Looks like a pussy
A cock...
You've never seen one?
His peehole
looks like a pussy.
You haven't even seen a real pussy
Don't get carried away
I'm sure you've also
only seen one online.
I know a good place
to do my own research.
Though I couldn't find
a clitoris until recently.
Where was it?
Right here.
Correct
You guys
You don't know about women,
don't get cocky.
Well... I'm sorry, but...
You come here first
Come on, right here.
Let's check if you're strong.
Come on,
right on my face!
On the face?
I feel like I can do it now
Move it this way
No, that's fine
You should move it
with your fingers
Are you Yanagiba Toshiro? (EN: 11)
On the face?
Yeah, that's what I said...
Really?
Can you count the thrusts?
I'm counting myself too
Okay, ready?
Yeah.
Okay. Start!
That smelled
for like a second!
Don't do that. That stinks!
If you hold it in
it kinda smells like farts.
Sometimes
-How many was that?
-33
He's pretty confident.
33 is tied with the champion.
We're all lined up.
I really don't think
I could do 33, though.
Hey, lend me your cheeks.
I've had enough!
Ina-chan, keep count.
Sorry, sorry. It's okay.
Come on...
Sorry, really sorry.
I know it's not great for you
Come on. Please count.
Here we go. Sorry.
-Who's counting?
-Ina-chan.
How did it get to this?
Ready... Go!
Alright!
The blue one!
It's blue!
This is against the rules!
How many times?
Hey, don't...
Alright, I'll kill myself then!
I'm gonna die!
I did it so much for only 19?
Damn it!
Is he that upset?
It's fine...
It's always 19!
I'm jealous!
You got 30, huh?!
Why?!
Why do I always
get just 19?!
You wanted it so badly?
I did, I did!
I wanted the 30!
That's a man's pride!
Not 19!
It's been three times!
Damn it!
It's not working?
Where's Gosuke?
He's not around.
Time over
It's over.
It's finished!
It felt kinda quick.
It was pretty quick at the end, huh?
Alright, the winner by points is...
Kubota!
Whoa!
No way!
Sorry, no way!
It was great.
You had great defense, too
I'm glad to be alive.
Thank you so much!
Good job
Alright, that was it.
How was it, everyone?
Well, it was, yeah...
Maybe it was all the nudity.
While watching, I was thinking
pissing Amazon off is...
kinda like pissing god off.
Not just working
but like, as a normal person.
I wondered it it was okay
for mere humans to do this.
I'm not gonna say who
screwed up.
But well, leaving that aside...
What bothered Amazon
the most was...
That they were gonna
release it on Christmas
And I guess it just wasn't...
that great as a Christmas present.
Well, as a Christmas present
to the world...
I think this might not be
up to Santa's standards.
So everything before that
was OK?
It was OK until then, yeah.
I think it was when
Soshina touched the dick.
Matsuo-san's?
Yeah, yeah, Matsuo's dick.
But like
He told me to touch it!
And it was really cute, right?!
Hello
Touch me!
I want you to caress me!
Can I touch you?
Yay! Yay!
It was cute.
I know you may not believe me!
No, I think it's fine.
It's fine, but...
But it went in your mouth, right?
Soshina smashed it
against his face.
But when doing it from the front
it went into Kubota's mouth, right?
He did it like ten times here
and a couple times in here.
It didn't go in, though.
You wanted a mosaic there?
It didn't go in, man!
Why a mosaic?
Come on man!
It didn't go in!
We just can't have someone's body parts
going inside someone else's body!
So can you cut it with
the whole entering a body?
Having said that,
Kubota was the winner.
Thank you very much.
Ten million.
Yeah.
You want it?
Of course I do, yeah!
"You want it?"
No, no, I mean... yes.
What do you think?
To be honest, he's a younger guy
so I'd like him to have it.
He worked hard.
But it was pretty heavy, you know...
Come on, don't say that!
Yeah, like he lost it.
Yeah, because this
is the opposite of a happy moment.
Well it's not about happy or sad.
I should go home with the money.
I'm in this world
because I want money.
But you got really mad, right?
No, no. I'm just saying!
I can take all the money with me
even if it takes a few days.
Come on, that's dangerous!
They're not gonna accept that.
Come on, give me the money!
I want the money!
So can you do this to
Amazon's big shots?
I'll do it in their faces, like...
Then it'll all be over.
Okay, Kubota
I'm confiscating the money!
Whoa!
Come on, Matsumoto-san!
Please don't do that, please!
For real! Please don't!
Confiscating?
I wanna give it to you,
but I'm going to take it back.
Come on, you can't, you can't!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
You have no say in this!
I'm sorry! Staff guys,
I'm sorry!
This isn't about Matsumoto Hitoshi!
It's just common sense!
I'm sorry!
Speaking of common sense,
I want to give the money to you.
I really do!
But it can't be helped!
Don't do this! Please!
Please don't!
It's come to this
there's nothing they can do.
Who is in charge?
(Staff)
That would be me...
So? What do you think?
To be honest,
as a project...
as a business,
this is unacceptable.
That's how it is.
Oh wow...
It was a huge deal, Kubota.
They're so mad at me?
He's turning pale!
That's how businesses get mad.
I'm just gonna hold on
to those ten million.
Huh? Hold on to them?
I'll think about it.
I don't wanna say much
but maybe...
it might carry over.
No, wait... come on, please!
We might turn it into 20 million.
Whoa!
We can take these ten million,
and you can participate then!
Just do the same thing again.
I'm not so stupid!
Only Jimmy would do that!
Jimmy, huh?
"Please watch the final hour, from the banned scene onward"
I'm starving.
Let's get along, Matsuo-san.
Sorry,
let's get along.
What happened? What was it?
Wait a second.
You took it?
What happened?
I don't know, maybe...
Maybe it was me?
What happened?
No, this is just...
I really don't know.
Let's wait for Matsumoto-san.
I just saw a normal
grin all of a sudden.
Who was it?
Two people?
Just Soshina.
No way!
He was smiling.
For real?
I guess a lot happened
so he was just giddy.
Wait a second.
Let's take a look.
See?
Let's get along.
He's smiling
When he said "let's get along"!
He did that by himself!
With a face and everything!
Let's get along, then.
I'm just too lonely,
and I wanted company.
Damn it!
Matsuo-san got him.
We do have
some snacks.
I want some!
I want snacks!
I'm _ _ _
I didn't get that.
-_ _ ko!
-We can't hear you.
-_ ko!
-Huh?
-_ _ ko!
-Pyakko?
I'm _ _ ko!
What-ko?
Byakko?
We can't hear you.
Sorry, Soshina.
Huh?
I'm _ _ ko!
Jaako?
_ _ ko!
He gained weight, huh?
Was that a broccoli?
Who are you?
-_ _ ko!
-Ryako?
_ _ ko! _ _ ko!
-What was it?
-I'm _ _ ko!
-Wanko?
-_ _ ko!
I really can't understand it.
He had something right?
He had two broccoli.
Call him, call him.
Yakko-san!
I'm _ _ ko.
What's your line of work?
I'm a delmo. A delmo.
A delmo?
Ah, a model.
What has she done?
What have you done?
I'm sure you've appeared
on mags or something, right?
M and M.
M and M?
M&M's? The chocolates?
How old are you?
A magazine. Magazine.
What?
It's a magazine.
A pageantry?
A magazine.
A magazine?
Yes.
What's with that?
I don't get it at all.
A magazine?
Come on!
There it is!
He's coming here?
Can you see me?
That type of body...
Who are you?
One more time!
_ _ ko!
-Rakko?
-_ _ ko!
-Rakka?
-_ _ ko
-Ouch!
-What-ko?
-Ranko!
-What're you doing?
-I'm Ranko!
-What-ko?
-Ranko!
-What's he doing?
Ranko!
What's that?
Stop it!
I'm gonna kill you!
It's a bazooka.
Kubota
Don't get any closer!
Senpai!
He's your senpai!
I'm gonna kill you
-Kubota
-Don't get closer!
I can do it any time.
Ouch!
Kubota-san. You okay?
That's a fucking heavy broccoli!
Broccoli
Huh?
It wasn't me.
You were smiling, yeah.
Smiling a lot.
Smiling a lot
Me? Me?!
It's a solid broccoli.
You smiled when you said broccoli.
-No way!
-He's smiling!
-Who was it?
-I smiled?
You did.
No way, I- I...
It was definitely Jimmy
He did it himself, right?
He was smiling normally.
He smiled after
saying "broccoli"
All the time.
For real?
For real!
For real
He's your senpai!
I'm gonna kill you
Kubota!
Don't get any closer.
I can do it anytime.
Ouch!
Kubota-san. You okay?
It's a damned heavy broccoli!
Broccoli.
Huh?
Leave.
No way!
For real.
But you did well today.
I smiled?
Of course you were smiling!
All the time!
I was being forgiving, actually.
He can't accept it.
I don't get what
he won't accept.
To be honest, this is
the first time I made it this far.
No, no, no.
Watch out watch out!
It felt like for a second
I might've done it.
But once I got the orange,
I had to watch out.
And I was out
before I realized.
Wanna go on a camping trip,
Maki-kun?
-I guess so, next time!
-Let's think about it!
Let's go with zombie time.
Zombie time!
The zombies are here...
Watch out!
Sit down.
You have to watch it.
Watch out!
What's going on?
That's a tiny face.
It's way too tiny.
He just walked by.
It's like a monster.
He walked by.
That's creepy
The face was way too tiny.
Where did it go?
That's not a performance.
Whoa!
He went to the back!
The back?
The strobe?
Strobe?
Whoa!
Damn it
It's not moving.
What?
Whoa!
"Don Frye" (EN: 12)
Come on!
Don Frye? Really?
Don Frye.
That was bad! Move more!
I was two seconds away
Move more!
That was definitely Soshina!
I did it!
You did.
I knew I was in trouble
from the beginning.
Kubota was struggling too!
I was pretty close
You held it?
I was two seconds away, though.
It's not moving.
What?
Whoa!
"Don Frye"
Come on!
Okay Soshina, you're out!
That was just...
Move more!
Okay, let's go Soshina.
Let's go with Nadal.
Don't come back as a zombie.
Run away!
It was so fun!
I brought a huge bag.
And I was pretty prepared.
But at some point I...
let people around me attack
and that was fun.
That's the sound already.
It's short!
Don't say it's short.
It's long!
There weren't many
straight men here.
So I just adapted to it.
So I watched out
for their attacks.
I think I did that well.
It was fun.
It really felt like a dream.
Alright.
I'll get one.
Sorry. Can you take that off?
This?
It's tight.
Thank you so much.
These are seven bras.
It's made with seven bras.
It's great!
It's so I'm always
thinking about boobs.
Looks warm.
I can put it on easily
with the hooks.
And it's good practice too
Practice...
They're all different.
Yeah, they're all different bras...
I could've used only a couple
But I wouldn't let myself.
What's the criteria?
No criteria,
but the clothes were good
and they had ribbons.
It's cute. Pretty cute.
Try putting it on.
It's soft.
Looks good. Make sure it's
sitting correctly over your ear.
It's really nice.
Right? This part is good too
I'm gonna take it off
and put it again.
I've called it the brahat.
-How is it?
-It's great!
I know!
-Wanna wear it?
-Yeah.
Isn't this expensive?
Buying one by one was like...
60,000 more or less.
60,000?
I wanted big cups.
It's warm!
It's good, huh?
This too!
It's gonna break.
Yeah, yeah.
Give it back.
Huh? I've seen him before.
Seen him before for sure...
-Sushi.
-Is that him?
-Looks like him.
Sorry.
What's your name?
Sushi
Sushi?
The one you eat?
No. Sushi
And your name?
It's Sushi.
He said Sushi, right?
A song? Can you sing?
I sing.
With a band?
We're five.
So he's definitely...
What was it?
Your group?
Hex-hex-hex Hex Japon.
Hex Japon.
Hex Japon?
Hex Japon
Huh?
Hex Japon?
Sing one for us.
I can't sing a song now, but...
This is it for you guys.
I'm gonna kill you all right now!
I'm gonna build a school in Africa!
Is he good or bad?
Why do you have to kill us?
I'm gonna pull out your eyeballs,
and bring water to the Thai people!
He's a good guy
Is he good or bad?
He's really good
He does good
and then bad.
I'm gonna murder your parents
Stop it
And pay for my sister's studies!
He's good
He's super good
He looks bad, though
I'm gonna pull out all your teeth
So please be my friend!
I can't be friends with someone like that.
Now...
Line up in the first row.
You've been here before?
Yes.
Okay.
Keep going.
No, I just
want to buy a ticket.
He's a good guy.
It makes sense.
Feel free to come.
I feel bad for
the fan club guys
Yeah, thank you.
What's with you?
Gaggy! Welcome!
Gaggy!
I came to the village Gaggy
Hello. I came here.
Gaggy village, right?
Long live Gaggy village!
Thank you very much!
I love Gaggy-sama.
That's why I'm here.
I can do a bit more Gaggy-sama.
This is what I am
without Gaggy-sama.
This is someone else.
We're almost the same. We're twins.
I'm a twin.
He shaved it?
I want to be like Gaggy.
I'm almost there!
Kill him.
Huh?
-Kill?
-Please kill him.
Kill him...
You can't just kill him.
Kill him. That's just it.
You can't kill.
Kill him.
You can't kill him. That's no good!
Why did I have this all this time?
For six hours?
Was there a reason?
It's just...
Look at it.
What's the point, then?
Let's go for another zombie time.
Here we go
Zombie time
Here he comes
Huh? Only three people?
I'm Enu from the youth clinic.
Shu!
I'll do a song about
whatever you guys say.
Say whatever you want.
-Sushi.
-Please go with other people.
-People?
-Comedians?
Kubota-san, Inada-san or Matsuo-san.
Ina-chan.
Here I go.
Hey hey, Inada! Hey Inada!
You're close, close, close.
Really close!
You're gonna keep this up?
For real?
-You're gonna keep it up?
-I am.
The broadcast code?
That's what was close?
Sorry.
You really think so?
No, I'm an idiot.
An idiot?
Can you do me? Please.
Hey hey Kubota! Hey Kubota!
Bald fat, bald fat, fat fat
glasses.
Come on...
You're just criticizing.
It depends...
You're just talking about appearance...
You're just criticizing.
Do something serious.
He's just being rough.
Do one more.
Do Kubota.
But for real.
Hey hey Kubota! Hey Kubota!
You're really funny
when you say the truth.
Huh? What was that?
You making fun of me?
No, he did a 180.
Quiet, quiet.
We're not being loud.
Okay, do him now.
Mat-chan...
Hey hey Matsuo! Hey Matsuo!
Your skin is a mess
your haircut is weird!
Stop it, man!
It was more boring than I thought.
I wanted it to be brutal.
Quiet, quiet.
Time's almost up.
What's wrong?
Someone was here?
You talked?
Good morning.
What happened?
Did you talk?
Did you feel strange?
No, no.
Where's Gosuke?
He's not here.
Time over
It's over.
It's over?
It's finished!
That was kinda quick.
It felt quick at the end.
Alright, the winner by points is...
Kubota!
No way!
Whoa!
He won five points.
Here you go
Huh?!
I'm sorry!
No way!
It was incredible.
Your defense was awesome.
Thank you so much.
You did everyone in.
To be honest, I had never
sucked so many cocks before.
Let's hope it doesn't count
as porn money.
He was talking
so much about the money.
I'm glad to be alive.
Thank you very much!
Good job!