Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!
Alright so this is the fifth episode
Of Documental Season 9
But this time
Well, how could I explain it?
We wanted to
Take a look back with everyone
Like an performance review
Why would anyone want to look back
after paying 1 million?!
I don't wanna get mad at myself
It's like revisiting trauma
I really think
that's how it feels at times
We wanted to do this
To talk about how it all felt
And ask each of you
About your experiences and so on
So that's what we had in mind.
It's been a few months after recording,
so you might not remember
That's right!
So we're going to look back
on the whole show.
Let's take a look at the beginning
Alright then
-That was fun
-Documental
Start!
I had forgotten about this
Absolutely
Do you know Mimio's character?!
Do you know the character?
He's smiling!
I wasn't smiling at all!
I made something to drink
Really?
So try drinking it
Ah, this happened!
There's no way...
That's serious!
That was so quick!
It was too soon!
She hated this
There she goes
Everything evil about the sea
in a single place.
You smiled a little!
I was really mad here
There it goes
So annoying
It's wet
I just... I just washed it, so...
You put your ass here
Right!
That was terrible!
And you two have to
have a live conversation
And the popcorn pops
and the moment it hits your ass
Even if you're talking
You have to shout
a fruit's name
Ikesaki is terrible!
It's always so contrived!
You two have to talk
You use someone's topic
and go with it
But once the popcorn
starts to pop
It's gonna hit your ass.
When it does...
What are you talking about?
What step was that?
If it hits you,
you shout a fruit's name
-Once it hits you?
-Right
-A fruit?
-Either a fruit or...
A vegetable's name.
-Which one?
-Whichever's fine
Vegetables too?
That's too broad
Depends on the person
What's he even saying?
Whoa
Right so, Sunshine isn't here
Right
So I have a question
Is he really
That stupid?
Yeah, yeah.
It was very incoherent.
He was speaking for a long time
He really was
Looking back,
you guys really held it in
I really didn't understand
anything he said
Also, Soshina
Wh-what?
This is something
Many people have said
After rewatching the whole thing
Ah, I know!
That I'm too soft with you.
-Not at all!
-He was totally smiling!
He was smiling for sure
Absolutely smiling right there
They say Yoshimoto cheats for you
He's getting favors!
-Hey, come on!
-Like favors, yeah!
I've heard that, yeah!
Come on, you're the worst
-Always defending him.
-I always ignore him.
That's indefensible, right Kubota?
Completely unforgivable!
Having Matsumoto-san say that
is scary
What if I had been out earlier...
There are people with
more ambiguous expressions
That's how it has
always seemed to me
It's not that I'm covering for you, though.
But some other people could also say
That I was too rough with Soshina
And I didn't want anyone
To say that either...
That being said, today...
We're going to look
at your near-death scenes
Her near-death scene,
chosen by Tsubaki Oniyakko
The first time I felt in trouble
Was at the beginning,
with Osada's toothbrush
I had to hold it in for real there
At the very beginning, right?
I didn't realize you were
-Struggling that much
-Yeah, I...
I was really close back then
with Osada
I made a new
electric toothbrush
Electric toothbrush?
They're so compact nowadays, though
What brand is it?
Phillipps?
This one is SunStar (Editor's Note: 1)
SunStar makes
such makeshift products?
Can I go ahead?
Whoa
No way
No way, man
Ah, it's true!
I didn't notice at all!
Is your upper jaw okay?
His face is being dragged around
Stop it man!
You should make it weaker
Well I don't really care what you do
But hearing an old man gag
in the morning isn't great
You're right.
I didn't notice at all
I always think people gagging
is hilarious
You were squirming
Well, in my own case
and this is kind of for me
But I have a TMJ disorder
so it looked like it hurt (EN: 2)
That's all I was thinking, and seeing him
It was like empathy, then?
Seeing him go like,
made me want to laugh from anxiety
Makes me think
I should've kept pressing
But I didn't notice at all
-I think you cut it a little short
-Yeah, it was too soon
Well, so you know...
You can tell this guy
spent an entire day working on that
I know!
So thinking about that
This time it was only four hours, right?
-It was pretty short
-Too short!
So I just had to go
with everything I had
I was even smiling quickly
Right, it was too soon!
And I laughed at Abareru almost immediately
It was really soon as well
So I wanted to use up
everything I had
The pacing was pretty frantic
Okay now,
Kubota's near-death scene
Mine was Goto with
the popcorn in his balls
That one!
Ikesaki's moment, right?
That was pretty serious!
Yeah!
It was really really bad
It burnt me so bad! For real!
Goto-san, talk, talk!
Mandarin!
What?
That was so funny
It's not for me, though.
Is it coming?
Ve-vegetable!
It didn't even hit him there!
Watermelon!
Talk
Watermelon
Pumpkin!
Please sit down, Goto-san
Peach! Cucumber!
Everyone was in trouble
Right, this was pretty bad!
Carrot!
My balls are done for!
Goto-san!
You can do it, Goto-san!
My balls are busting!
My balls are busting
for real!
Whoa!
My balls are gonna pop, man.
He's so upset
They're popping out, actually
Right? My balls are burs-ping
Bursping?
Bursting?
Popping
I think Abareru
was smiling as well!
That was serious
So I chose this.
Goto-san really watched over me
When I first joined Yoshimoto, right?
But thinking about it
This guy hosts a lot of TV shows,
so you have
A TV host with his balls out
being hit by pop corn
So I thought about
other popular hosts
And I couldn't help imagining Miyane-san
doing something like that! (EN: 3)
I found it hilarious
in my own head!
I didn't think
my balls were gonna be hanging out!
You just told me they were out, right?
It's just that
those briefs in particular
Don't fit well, and they were popping out!
It was purely coincidental!
That makes it even worse!
It was hurting
and everyone was kinda laughing
So when I realized
I felt the shame of exposing myself.
Thinking about it
even I almost laughed
"Oh, my balls are out"
You don't frequently
laugh when you see your own balls
The ballsack
was sagging like hell!
They were being pulled
by indescribable strengths!
It sure was stretching
Since they were being
stretched so much
His balls were also
bizarrely dark, right?
It wasn't just the lighting.
That was so weird!
I can't really stand it, Goto
I can't do anything about that!
The color was the funniest part
-Your balls are black?
-I guess so, a little black yeah.
A little black? What does that mean?
They're bizarrely black.
They looked like the floating stone. (EN: 4)
I didn't really get to choose
what color my balls would be, though
Alright then, let's have a look
at the next digest.
Right
Pretty far into it
This was really funny!
That one!
Who was that?
This is pretty bad!
This was really funny!
His pecs are pretty good!
Master Kiyoshi!
He's smiling!
He should've been out!
Why didn't he go out with this one?
He didn't for some reason!
Ah, I remember this
This was a bit moment
It was pure chaos
I'm dying!
I'm gonna die from old age
What kind of performance is that?
Smells like Currypanman
This was really funny
Like that Okumura-san
from Toho or something?
Yakko-san really made me laugh here
It's Okuyama-san, right?
From the film
I said Okumura-san, but
It's Okuyama-san
Was it Okuyama-san?
I have these special
cards for playing Karuta
Do you have "re"?
You see, I really love the "re" one
Throw the shrimp away
He definitely laughed!
He laughed!
I see
Yakko-san's Momoi series
That was pretty good
So happy to hear that
I don't really get to talk much as her
As Momoi-san
But everyone was listening to me!
-I was speaking nonstop
-And you played Karuta
That's right
And also Master Kiyoshi
That was really bad
That was Kubota
I made sure to
properly give him a call
It didn't connect at first
I called his manager
And told him I wanted to make
Kiyoshi-san's face
And he was like
"Um... I don't know..."
It seemed like a no-go
Did you actually
visit Kiyoshi for that?
I gave him a call.
"You see, my reputation is on the line
and I could win 20 million yen"
He wished me luck
and let me do it.
The Master Kiyoshi gag
was hilarious
-It was really bad.
-Kiyoshi was funny
But maybe it was
because of how long ago it was
But I don't remember
anything about the devil's castanets. (EN: 5)
I really don't remember this!
Who's that?
Who was it?
-It's Kubota-san.
-That's Kubota?!
The devil with castanets.
I had to visit an old man
in a bar
to have him teach me
how to use them.
I did all that
for them to barely work
For real
So, Soshina's
near-death scene
It was with Seiya
When he did
the "Suberanai" impression
Ah, right!
And he was just
-So persistent with it.
-He was!
I almost died there
Something's happening
Is that music?
When you slip up with your story!
The best people have gathered together!
We have gathered the specialists today!
It's time to talk!
-That's a pretty nasty impersonation
of Wakamoto Nori
Because of the appearance?
Chihara Junior
Thank you for
always talking with us
Right here
out of the narration!
You're always talking
With these
amazing fellas!
You're not talking!!
You don't talk
when you don't have to!
The man that won't talk
when he doesn't have to!
He can only talk as a presenter.
He won't talk when it's time to.
He doesn't talk when he has to!
And even if you stare at him
he won't talk!
He doesn't talk when it's talk time!
Talk- He won't talk.
He's singing
Talk, he won't talk.
This guy's not talking either
He's not talking!
He's smiling, though!
Not talking!
This took him down
Right, that happened!
I thought you'd
keep going forever!
It was so long!
Not talking
That was the character!
"He won't talk
when it's talking time"
That's what I had in mind!
"He won't talk
when it's talking time"?!
That was pretty serious, yeah
It's the type of gag
that pisses off older people
Depends on the person, but yeah
That's not what I meant!
I just got in character
and went on the offensive!
And I chose Goto-san for that
That was pretty bad
You really didn't know?!
-I really didn't know.
-Among the Shimofuris
I didn't know!
I really didn't
So being with your partner
isn't great?
It really isn't
Because it's lame
if only you laugh at him
It's pretty bad
Yeah, laughing too much
isn't great
That's right
I've never laughed
at my partner though
Of course you have!
A lot of times!
Not even once
Of course you have!
Stop sounding serious
Not since we were in school
How many years ago?!
Two hours left
Alright!
Ouch ouch ouch!
Alright, health fortune
The ice house
You're gonna die!
Leave!
-Leave!
-More!
-Thank you!
I really didn't get this part
Wasn't that a smile?
I haven't smiled at all
No, no, no!!
For real, this part
Ouch!
That hurts!
I think it broke
I find it hilarious that Abareru-san
finds that funny.
The explosive ice duel
You both get topless
and grab ice cubes
And you have to melt them
on each other's nipples
while attacking with your best gags.
What was that?
Huh?
What?
That's too long, man
You lose if you
step away from it.
And you lose if you laugh of course.
They can't laugh
So if you step away...
You lose in Documental
if you laugh.
He's such an idiot.
Aren't those the rules?
Sunshine Ikesaki sure was chaotic
Yakko-san looked really annoyed
by that crow!
The crow definitely hurt
And the sound was
something else as well
That's right,
I tried to protect myself
It was over me
-She was cowering.
-Covering myself
I thought he was pecking me
like a crow would peck at the floor
Like your head was the ground
I got mad
And the sound was something else
It was too long
Like
I never imagined I would be
pecking a random senior's head
Right, that doesn't happen often!
But as time went by
I wanted the crow
to behave like a real one
And in pecking her
I thought she might smile
It was pretty bad
To be honest I got
pretty concerned during the swordfight
Ah, right!
His face started twitching
Right.
I started feeling stressed
It was like
So after around the fifth one
I couldn't do it anymore
That's serious!
You're a great actor!
I wasn't acting!
Not at all.
I'm so jealous!
This happens in manzai sometimes
After getting hit a few times
you go like
Like twitching
Would've been obvious if it were fake
That's serious, man!
Alright so Seiya's
near-death scene
So it was Sunshine
I never understood
what he was doing
He had several games
But the single moment
he stopped the games
I don't know
if you remember
But he was doing shaolin
Something like that...
And he acted like
nothing hurt him
I don't remember
I remember something
about shaolin.
He had a character from Baki
And no matter the attack
he received no damage
No one got that
but I knew that character
So I was the only one in trouble
And then after an attack
His sunglasses fell like that
And his face was super creepy
And I almost laughed back then.
Let's take a look
Ready?
This, right!
This, this happened!
This?
Whoa!
It didn't hurt at all.
Shaolin
That's Shaolin
Ready? Ready?
In the face?
You sure?
Ready? In the face
This happened yeah
Shaolin
It doesn't hurt.
That's what he says
Abareru-kun, you do it
It did look like it hurt, though.
Shaolin
This is shaolin
In the face, Abareru-kun
-It came off!
-Watch out!
That's creepy!
So creepy!
That's creepy, man!
I was in big trouble here!
For real!
That was pretty serious
That was bad
What the hell was he doing?!
For real, what was that?!
I had to hide my smile
What was that?
That's right
And he was talking about shaolin
and then at the end
His face was creepy!
What the hell?
But no one understanding
Is what made it funny!
That's true.
The fact that no one got it
Of course
he wasn't going to smile
That's right
I mean
I got a sudden call
from Ikesaki a few days later
"I couldn't do anything"
But I think he did a lot!
He did a lot of stuff!
He did a lot, but
It did feel
like he did nothing
I think he'd be happy to hear that
I was in serious trouble back then
Alright, Osada's
near-death scene
I struggled when Yakko-san
did that pachinko film
performance thing
It went on for a while
But I was wondering what I was watching
I was wondering
if you had worked hard to do it
With Daisan
And that was pretty funny
But in the end nothing happened
And Yakko-san self destructed
I think I might've laughed
If she hadn't
self destructed.
It was an own goal, right?
I didn't get that at all
It makes you
feel motivated to do things
CR...
A pachinko?
Alright, here we go
CR
Tsubaki Oniyakko
There it is!
That was pretty long
It's hand-made. Pretty cute
You did this yourself, right?
Sound and everything?
A new line
This is pretty funny
I think it's charming
The performance
She looked so thin there
-I'm Gijiren!
-What?
There's a lot of stuff happening!
The yakitori
is completely unrelated as well
The handwriting is thin!
What the hell's this?
Super hot
She said "super hot"
-Freeze!
-There it is!
Freeze?
Something on the screen?
Everyday life
in April 2020
We have some foreshadowing
There it is
That's Chinchirorin
What's going on?
I think he has to pile them up
There we go
There it is
No
What?
But I thought...
What's that?
So he made it?
He's smiling so much
Show us! There it is!
There it is, there it is!
That's good enough
So long
It's too long
That was pretty bad
Pachinko takes time!
What now?
That's enough
Not at all
Oni rush! Break in!
What's that?
There we go
This is serious
That was... seriously
I didn't need
to watch this twice in my life!
That was fun
That was really long
The full thing, yeah
That's enough
We don't need all this
I thought it was
just too good
Horyuuren?
I didn't really get it.
Why was it so long?
We have long shorts lately
The Chinchiro part was too long
Huh?
It stopped
Wait
It's over
I couldn't believe
that was all
There really was nothing at all
I couldn't believe
we had to watch literally nothing
I didn't want the ending
to be so long
But the whole crowd reaction
I mean, I think
it was way too long
I was expecting
some kind of punchline
Looking at it now
it was funny
It's really funny
I remember smiling, yeah
I really wanted it to reach
Pachinko players, actually.
That works, yeah
Alright then, one last hour
Let's look at the digest
I prefer my pork
Roasted
There it is!
Pretend that that's Yoshihide
That was funny
And you want to smell
Yoshihide's farts
You always throw me out!
-I think it's the shape
-I got it
What?
I'm parsley
Weren't you green peas?
Isn't he a pepper?
He's green peas
I thought he was green peas
He's too thick for parsley
Who are you?
I'm green peas
No way
Ouch!
Huh? What was that?
Okay, the last one.
Anyone wants it?
Okayuta-san
I struggled with this one
This one was pretty rough!
And he hit the wall
like Bomberman
He was like Bomberman
One cat, two cats
Madame cat
If only we had song, dance
and a performance!
That's right, but songs
can't change the world!
You know, right?
No, I don't
What?
What? What?
I don't get this at all
Musicals are
What was that, Soshina?
Your weakness, right?
He said it broke him
Do bicycles stop
at the Tokyo Teleport Station?
They don't
Also make sure your wife knows
I saw her take her tit out
on the airplane!
I thought
you left
But you were looking
at my wife's tits, huh?
That's right
and I fucked her later!
You should thank me
What was that?
And it rings with decibels!
It goes like peep beep!
Ouch I'm fainting shaolin
There he goes again
I'm gonna lick
like you've never seen before
Lickity lick boom!
Lickity lick booom!
That's insane
It's completely insane!
Right, right
That was the final self destruction
Why are you
taking up time now?
Everyone made it
pretty alright!
What now?
Is that the most
survivors ever?
Kubota wins!
No way!
He's good
The fire of passion
He was crying
First time I've cried
No, that happened before
Congratulations Kubota!
Nice championship
Great championship
That was pretty good, huh?
It was really good
We had survivors before
but this is the first time
We've had so many at the end
That's just
how fierce it was
And Kubota even cried
Well, we had
the 10 million from last time
So I just
cried without thinking about it
So what were those tears?
You cried from happiness?
Like all of a sudden?
That's right
I just started crying
I was trying to hide
just how happy I was
Well, I was also
so tired, twitching like
Again?
Stress again?
Performing is scary
Winning should've fixed that!
It was 20 million!
No way, really
So I was expecting
To get scolded
since Kubota won again
From all kinds of people
It's fine.
Lately I've seen
Seeing a lot of that on YouTube
And getting rid
of anyone who complains
Unexpected behavior!
You should say something
as well, Matsumoto-san!
Tell all the news articles
and journals online!
Like, here's the video, take it
Is that some kind of revenge?
So anyways, Goto's near-death scene
This is Soshina again
It was with Soshina's comedian chips
And the comedian cards
Right, right
Mine's holographic as well
Lots of holo ones
Narumi-san
Suddenly?
Choice is...
Narumi's holo
Here's where it started
This was pretty bad
Fujii Akira!
What's this?
Lots of funny moments
Sideways Narumi
Another Narumi version!
And it was Junior
Not Sideways Narumi!
A new version! Sideways Narumi!
I was looking this way,
but like
I saw someone running
It was Junior-san
I think that's
when Junior-san realized
And he was running
at a great speed
He realized
He was done for!
I knew it was great
I was done in
Besides,
the pictures were just terrible!
No, no, no
They were awful!
I got permission
from Narumi-san herself
And so, I asked Narumi-san
If I could use a picture of her.
And she asked me which
So she checked the pictures
I sent her about six
And she told me
to use that one
That one in particular
The white one
with the tiara
I had never seen that one!
So Narumi-san chose it herself!
That's right!
I sent her a lot
And she wanted this one!
I think I would've laughed
even harder then
She told you to
not use some of them?
Kind of, yeah
This one was the best
Narumi-san said so?
The one with the tiara, yeah.
You got permission
from Piroki-san?
I think the people at the office
checked it out
I don't think Piroki-san
has an office, though
Of course he does!
He does!
It's a public picture anyway
Alright, so that's Season 9
This is the first time
we've done a rewatch!
And 20 million!
Thank you very much
So last time
We got a scolding
from Amazon
Right
And they told us
to not show genitals
Right, right.
I showed my balls, though
Right
And I had a penis helmet as well
It was very realistic
That's not a good compromise!
He was walking like this!
With it on!
And it was supposed to shoot stuff, right?
It was like glued!
That's right.
I had a spray built in
Inside the urethra
And it was supposed to shoot
But that got destroyed
and it didn't come out
There might not have been
any 20 million if it had
No way! That's scary!