So finally getting started   -Yes
I may overlook some scenes on my own
So I've invited these three members from Documental as witnesses
Thank you for having us
That's the same stage set in Documental right?   -Yes, it is
They must feel nervous for that
I wonder what's their motivation to join   -I hope they'll be fine
There will be 7 contestants this time
-Maybe nothing funny will happen at all right?
-Yeah, that's possible
Well, it's about time to start
Here they come
She must be nervous for being the first one
It's First Summer Uika   -I'm the first one...
Excuse me
(Documental) I watched all of them
Talking about confidence, well, I feel like half-and-half
I'm going to knock down everyone in the room
Wow, this is amazing
It's the real one
It doesn't feel good to be the first one right?
Please, someone come quickly
She brought something so big
She's fully prepared   -Who is she?
Who is she?
Ah, it's Minegishi   -Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you, I'm Minegishi Minami
It gives me a chill
Female Documental?   -Yes
This is the most nervous moment of this year
In a simple yet aggressive manner
Well, these two people are used to variety shows anyway
That's a big bag again, it's fully stuffed
Nice to meet you
It's Asahi Nao
Eh, I have no confidence, to be honest
By the way, they are all idols
Someone's here   -She looks noble
Does she look noble?   -Doesn't look like a comedian
Yahoo   -Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you
Ah, that show right?
I know about it
Seriously?
I'm invited by that show?
I have to join!
Female can win male comedian's Owarai
I want to prove it to those male comedians
Maybe all contestants will be from the same generation
You're right   -This could be a battle with no scruples
She looks like she's going to have a fight too
Who is she?
She must be strong
Too strong   -She must be strong
Is it fine to let me join?
Matsumoto-san nominated you
I'm so happy
I want to let myself go and do want I what to do
I will not laugh today!
Looking at Kyouko-san always reminds me of your father
Yeah, you're right
They look alike
Really?
That's huge!
Hello everybody!
I'm joining! I'm joining! I'm so happy!
Eh? Mental? Joshi...mental?
I have no idea, but I'm going!
I'm a voice actor, so I'm capable of making various sounds
-So I'll try to work on this aspect today
-That sounds so scary
-They're having such a great time
-Yeah, it's like a kitty party
The atmosphere is different from Documental
Hey!
No way! No way!
Someone awful is invited!
Of course I'm going! I'm definitely going!
Matsumoto Hitoshi-san?
I'll work hard
I've always wanted to meet you Matsuno Akemi-san!
I've always wanted to meet you too!
-The combination of contestants is amazing
-Yeah, it's incredible
So it's about time to start, I'll go and meet them now
Okay, got it
You people are really having a good time huh?
No, it's just these two
Please take a seat
We all have some understandings about the rules right?
Yes, we know
If you laugh for the first time, you'll get a yellow card
For the second time, you'll get a red card and you're out
No orange card this time
If you're out, you will be banned from Fuji TV
Eh, really?   -That's too much
But if you win the contest, while there won't be any cash prizes
You win the honorary title of Variety Queen   -I want it so badly
It's not enough to just not laugh
You have to be making others laugh
Winning by simply ignoring other's performance is unworthy of the honor
While it usually lasts for 6 hours
For this time, it will last for 2 and a half hours
The contest will start soon after I left the room
Give me one second...HAHAHA
This looks really scary   -This is terrifying
Matsumoto-san is not impressed at all
When does it start?
Probably after a beep sound
This is really going to start
Oh my god, what should I do
Well, they'll probably quiet down after it starts
I bet they will   -Yeah, you're right
Okay, let's get started
I'm really looking forward to this   -Let's start
This scared me
It started   -Yeah, it started
Let's get started
This scared me
It started   -Yeah, it started
We can't laugh from now on right?   -Yes
I'm really thirsty, may I get a drink first?   -Me too
Ah, there's some fruits in here   -Yeah, that's amazing
Like bananas   -Some snacks too
She's laughing already right?
Hamaguchi-san is laughing already right?
Well, well, well
She noticed it herself and quickly stopped laughing
Don't drink too much
Yes, I know
Eh, did you laughed just now?
No I didn't?
Really?   -Yes, I didn't
Matsuno-san is laughing all the time too
I'll go and warn them about this, if they went too far
I wonder who will be attacking first though
I love those laughing bags
-I have tons of laughing bags at home   -Oh, you like it?
I love laughing bags
Why do you like it?
I use to let those bags laugh one after another, and I'll laugh at last, but I can't show it today though
Can you show it to us, without laughing at the end then?
-Got it, so I won't laugh at the end this time
-Yes, the no laughing version
I won't laugh, but I usually do it like this
And then?
What the heck is this?
This is amazing
What the heck is this, seriously?
I can't hold back on this one, I'm laughing already
Yeah, I'll laugh at this one
-Yeah, if we were there
-I'll definitely laugh if I'm there
I actually had hearing loss because of my own voice
How come?   -Because my voice is too loud
Therefore my ears always hurt because of my own voice
Eh?   -My ears always hurt and...
And when gibbons are in danger, and ask other mem...members...
-Sorry but you're not speaking smoothly despite being a voice actor
-Yes, I'm bad at speaking smoothly
My voice has the same sound wave as gibbons,
when they are in danger and ask other members for help
That's incredible!
Uika tried hard to hold back on this one
Uika was close right? She tried hard to hold back
And whenever I visit the zoo, all of the animals will poo
They all poo because of my voice   -Poo?
They all poo, poop
And since it cures their constipation,
they always invite me to come
What kind of voice is that?
Asahi was very close   -She tried hard to hold back
She should had push it further
-Can I perform a stunt in place of my self introduction?
-Yes, of course
May I?
So I'll perform my stunt of putting a 10 dollars coin to my nose and eyes
That's amazing
Why did you thought about doing this?
I'll continue   -Kyoko-san is staring at it
-Don't push yourself too hard
-Has it been a while since you last did it?
Wow, that's amazing!
It's quite boring to do it myself today, so...
Let's do this together, if you don't mind
All together?   -I never did it before though
These coins are sterilized   -Thank you
Thank you for doing this   -This is amazing
Should I just pass this around?   -I always wanted to try this
You wanted to try it?   -Yes
Start from putting it to the nose right?   -Yes
It's fine if you can't put it in
It's not going in at all   -I don't think it's gonna fit
It's normally impossible to put it in
It's not going in
My nostril is not widening
Your nostril is too small
Wow, that looks painful!
You don't need to force yourself
It went it!   -Ah, it fell out
It almost went it, I almost did it
Not as difficult as it looks
You shouldn't be fainting in order to do this
Ah, is it in?
It's easier to put it in the nose?
Yes, just like that   -Like this?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, this hurts
I really want to put it in even if my nose splits
Ah, Uika is in danger
For your eyes, instead of putting it in, you should just clamp it with your eyelids
Eww, I don't want to do that
Give it a try, these coins are properly sterilized
Hamaguchi were you able to put it in your nose?
I want to try it with my eyes
Both eyes at the same time?
Kyoko-chan isn't even trying to get it done
Well, it's kind of clamped by the eyelids
She laughed   -She definitely laughed
That counts as well? Did someone even laughed?
Kyoko-san, I'll give you a yellow card
You laughed right?
I, Kyoko, is trying to put this 10 dollars coin...
I have to clamp it with the muscles here, therefore...
I have to move my face like this
Or else, it's impossible to clamp it with those muscles
Therefore, I, Kyoko, did not laugh
She laughed right?
Come on, you're not being arrested
I want to try it with my eyes
(I know you're trying hard here)
Both eyes at the same time?
(We all laughed while watching this scene)
Right after here   -I'm not laughing here
But right after here, look, you're clearly laughing
You definitely laughed
You completely laughed here
And your face says "I screwed up" right after
Yes, I agree   -You're honest
Have to be careful at those times
Those are the crucial moments to be aware of   -You're right
Her face was astonishing
Kyoko-san understands how it works now,
she's like "so this is how it will be judged"
Kyoko-san is getting into the swing of it
Let's start
You couldn't put it in right?   -Yeah
But actually, I can do a stunt too
They are all making a move
Can I perform it?
My hand...my fist can fit my mouth
Oh my god, please don't force yourself
No way, your mouth is small
My jaw was dislocated because of doing this
Please be careful
No way, that's just impossible
I'm almost there
Did you try this before? Is this your first time?
Not the first time
There's still plenty of time left, don't force yourself
Don't hurt yourself now
Yukipoyo, hold her elbow, hold her elbow!
That's amazing
Anything else? Only this?
Huh?   -Is this the only stunt that you can do?
What is the timing for us to clap our hands and praise?
I can put it in further   -No please, that's enough
When is the moment that your performance ends and be like "Hooray!"
The moment of "Hooray" right? Got it, I'll tell you
You'll tell us with your fist in your mouth?   -Can you do it?
That looks painful
Matsuno-san was completely laughing
And she didn't even notice it
Why are people not aware of themselves laughing
Eh, who is it?
Matsuno-san, you were completely laughing
Eh? No, I didn't laugh!
That already made you laugh?
You're laughing just because of that?
Matsuno-san was completely laughing   -Sure she did
You'll tell us with your fist in your mouth?   -Can you do it?
Ouch, that looks painful
You clearly laughed   -We can even see your teeth
Let's start
Ah, that's strict
Maybe it's time for me to perform now
Really?   -I want to perform my gags first before I'm out
You prepared some gags?   -Not really gags though
Matsuno Akemi's...where should I face?
The running lesson! Let's start running
Start running?
You shouldn't be just running in a marathon
You should run with your arms
You have to swing your arms while running
Please follow me
Okay, now imagine you're slowly holding up an egg
Hold it up carefully, and your thumbs should...!@#$%...
Excuse me, what did you say just now?   -One, two, one, two
Hold your stomach, stretch your back...!@#$%...
Whaaat?   -Let's start, one, two, one, two
One, two, one, two
Swing your arms
How should this end?
What should they do after this?
I think she don't know either   -I bet so
What the heck is this?
This is hell   -This is awful
Instead of laughing, I feel like "what are they even doing?"
You feel relax now right?
Yeah, my body feel relaxed now
Hamaguchi-san's face looks so relaxed now
My face is softened
No way, your face went numb
Let's soften our faces then
I've brought something that can soften everyone's face in that bag
I've brought something that follows up the scene too
Follow-up?
Let's move together then, one, two, one, two
What the heck were they asked to do just now?
Matsuno-san is amazing   -Yeah, she's incredible
People always say that I'm like Matsuno-san
You mean your character?
Yeah, and like how we speak
Our voice sound similar
When did you start talking in this tone though?
Eh? I wonder when...
That's the monkey scene before
No way, I definitely can't hold on this one
Is it fine to go at this pace though?
Well, she's always like this anyway
Did she drink all of the cold medicine?
Can you speak in a deeper voice, or like in a normal voice?
Yes, I can   -Can you show us, please?
What phrase do you want me to say?
What about some sexy phrases?   -No problem
Let me know what you want me to say, and I'll say it in a sexy way
Then what about "I don't want to leave yet"
I don't want to leave yet...umm...ahh...
How did Minekishi not laugh at that
Minekishi is in danger
Umm~~~
Minekishi is very close, Minekishi is in danger
Well done for holding on that one
Are you able to speak in a deep male voice then?
I've actually spoke in a deep voice, when I'm imitating Oda Yuji-san
Oda Yuji-san? I want to see it
Which scene of Oda Yuji-san did you imitate?
Odoru DaisÅsasen   -Eh?
Moroyi-san, why are there people injured here?
We can't lockdown the rainbow bridge then
How the heck is this Oda Yuji-san?
It's interesting though
Ah, something's happening over there
I'm Matsuno Akemi
Excuse me, please give me a hand
Someone please hold the finish line
This is just...   -This is awful
Is something going to happen?
Hey, this tripped me
This tripped me, help me up
Someone came out, something's happening
Matsuken? Is she acting Matsuken Samba?
Yeah, it's Matsuken Samba
Which means? Is she going to...
Really?
-She went back   -She probably left something
Eh? How can you forget something about that?
And Matsuno-san is not yet finished too
She's back   -Here she comes
What's that costume?   -I think I saw it somewhere before
I feel nostalgic   -What's that?
What, what, what?
She's really gonna dance, this is hilarious
Why is she dancing this now though?
With such a serious face
She's facing the refrigerator
The song ended
Why did you face that way all the time?
That's all?   -Seems like there's another song
That's it for me, I'll go back over there first
It took her so much time, but still...
She turned her back on us for 90% of the time though
I wonder why though
Maybe she'll laugh if she's facing us?
Can I ask something that can only be asked in this situation?
With so many female talents here...
This could be a lame question to ask, but...
Let's have some girl's talk, like did anyone tries to flirt with you?
Like these kinds of gossip
So you mean within the entertainment circle?   -Yes
No one tried to flirt with me yet
I've just started to join TV shows recently, so not at all
Well, I shouldn't be saying these kinds of things as an ex-idol
But I hope you all can listen to me
Eh? What, what, what?
Well, many things happened, and I usually don't talk about this, but...
I've been in AKB for 15 years
Just for once, someone gave me his contact after a singing talent show
That's so nice   -Yeah, that's worth yearning for
So someone gave me his contact
After the show ends, and we're already saying "goodbye"
Just before I leave, he stealthily passed me his contact
Eh?!   -Wow, that's like comics
That's really worth yearning for   -That's so nice
My heart skipped a beat
What was written on it?
His phone number
And his name is Y****
Holy moly, this gal is mad!
She's the worst
She dropped a massive bomb
This gal is unbelievable
That attack was aggressive
I was wondering why is she so quiet all this time
So she was waiting for this
Did you phone him then?
Yes, I phoned him   -Eh? You phoned him?
Well, he is her senior, so I think she just had to phone him
Did you two hangout for dinner then?
We didn't hangout though
So this is the atmosphere when there's only females
I thought someone would have laughed
This is the unique thing about this contest
Are you gals hungry?
I've prepared some snacks for you all   -That's awesome
Let's have some snacks and chat
Do you read books?
Books? No, Yuki don't, I can't read vertically aligned texts
*Japanese novels are written in vertical columns
Vertical texts?   -Yes, vertically aligned texts
You mean those vertical writings?   -Yes
After entering this entertainment circle, I noticed that there's plenty of things to learn
So I started reading some books
To be able to give good comments on shows
Can I recommend some books to you all?
I hope you all will give it a shot
Wow, that's amazing! You sure have been reading it in detail
It's full of notes
Wow, the second season, "Matsumoto"
Are these two the same book?
No, they're different
Ah, it's "Yome!"
Written by Hamada
No notes at all
Not even one
Although it's interesting, but will they understand?
The gag of only Hamada-san's book has no notes at all
It's too high level
This book "Matsumoto" by Matsumoto Hitoshi
What a no-brain title
You're being teased by Yukipoyo
Up until now, you're being teased by a frivolous girl
Let's play Jenga?
Jenga?   -Sure, let's play
"Hey, you're not my friend anymore"
"You're someone more important than friends"
"Keep those tears as a secret"   -She sings so well
"Please stay beside me my friend"
I thought it would be difficult to wear that wig
"Look upon the sunny sky"
*Lunch Pack (sandwich) was endorsed by Ayame Gouriki, the singer of this song, and her dance in the CM was so popular that it's even called the "Gouriki Dance"
She's handing out those Lunch Packs
"The sun~"   -Thank you very much
It's really Lunch Pack
And that propeller dance has been very popular
Although you're dancing professionally...
Asahi is...
Asahi and Uika is in danger
This is incredible
Please enjoy your Lunch Pack
That's amazing   -I really hope it made someone laugh
That was really awesome   -Yeah
If you think about it now, Hamaguchi's Samba dance sucks
The quality is terrible
When have you last wore a wig?
*Minegishi shaved her head and offered a filmed apology after breaking her management firm's rules by spending a night with her boyfriend
9 years ago
You're much more mature now then
I was 19 years old back then   -Eh, 19 years old?
-I thought it happened recently though
-Yukipoyo is doing something
Don't tell me she's finding for that photo   -That's terrible
She's definitely googling for that photo
The photo of her being bald?   -Is she going to show it?
Seriously?
If she really shows that photo here...
But if you keep wearing a wig...
But this hairstyle really suits Minekishi
She's just so mean   -Twisting the knife in the wound
How could these people hold back on that?
Your skin texture looks the same
You didn't change at all
She's even standing beside it
They all held on with that
That's incredible
Nothing changed at all, you look exactly the same
She's really is cute right?
Yeah, she's really cute
This gal is really the worst, she's the meanest person
Yukipoyo   -That's the level of a genius hacker
She took out her phone immediately
Who did this?
Ah, it's me, I'm sorry
You put back the ones that you used right?
I'm so sorry  -Uh-oh
Oh no, she's gonna be scolded
This is no good right?   -Yes, I'm sorry
These should be used to clean dirts
I'm so sorry about this
She's taking advantage of that bald impression
She's being really aggressive
I'll deeply reflect on myself
She's close
Did Yukipoyo laugh?
I'll deeply reflect on myself
But I feel like you're just fooling around
Do it in front of Yukipoyo, come on!
Just one final push   -That's such a waste of chance
Notice it, notice it!
They didn't notice it
That was a good chance
Yukipoyo was very close
"Run forward, run forward, everyone run forward!"
I see where this is going, this is awful
This is just...
The timing that she came out was superb
Is this Sunplaza Nakano-kun?
My husband posted a photo of me in this costume to Instagram
And Sunplaza Nakano-san liked the post
But it feels good to sing that song
Is this skin-tight garment?   -Yes
And it says Nakano   -Very cute
Very cute?
So hot
Ah, she's bald
Who said she's bald
I can't believe there's still people trying to get a laugh with fleeing soldiers nowadays
Fleeing soldier is not interesting at all
Not interesting at all
I'm friends with Zakoshisyoh
And Zakoshisyoh-san said I can do his gag "exaggerated imitation"
I want to watch you do "exaggerated imitation"   -Oh, do you?
Let's say, Hanzawa Naoki-san
Oh, he's popular right now
But he's already quite exaggerated though
No way, his exaggeration is not enough at all, we need more
I'll do it now, are you ready?
That's hilarious
It's so long
Eye for an eye!
Minekishi is in danger
I can do any character that you want me to do, just let me know
Eh? Any character?
Yes, any
What about Hamada-san?
Hamada-san, got it
Why those eyes?   -Facial expression is important
It all starts like this
Is she being possessed?
She should be acting Hamada-san, what's that?
Eh? Did Minekishi laughed just now?
Minekishi is close
Still not done yet?
That's so freaking long
How is that Hamada-san?
When did Hamada-san look like this?
It's the Hamada-san when he looks at me
This is the face when he looks at me   -So that's all?
Yes, that's all
Oh dear, my friend is over there, hello!
That's hilarious
How did they even hold back on that
That scene just now was hilarious   -In an instant
That's invincible
The hellish hairstyle sisters
That's so strong
Their defense is so strong
Here I come
I'm Egashira-chan
I'm Egashira-chan   -This is awesome too
Something amazing came
This is awful
I'm Egashira-chan, who are you?
I'm fleeing soldier
Fleeing soldier?
Why are we the same?
They all look the same
Minekishi was close   -I think Minekishi actually laughed
It's time to take her down though
Hamaguchi-san, why don't you do this with us?
Still lacking a fatal blow
Hamaguchi-san, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
This is absolutely hilarious
She is hilarious
This one is so funny
That was hilarious
Why aren't they laughing?
Hyottoko mask is awful   -That was incredible
It was hell just now   -Sure it is
Hamaguchi took all the attention
How did she come up with this idea
At this rate, Hamaguchi may possibly win the contest
Do you gals do any beauty treatments?
Well, just the normal ones, in routine
I have a machine here that can show your pores
No way, I don't want that   -A machine that shows your pores?
I bet mines are clogged   -But you're young
Nah, it must be clogged
That's so scary   -Let's have a look
But I always go to the beauty salon so...
Yeah, you're skin is beautiful   -It should be fine
What's this? I'm so scared. From my nose?
It's so dirty
It's super dirty
This guy is so mean   -That's just hair
Hair?
What about Uika?
Me?
Huh?
We can see you
What the heck is she doing? Did she miss something?
Why did she opened it?
*Kyoko is imitating her father Animal Hamaguchi
Kyoko!
It all ends in a second
What was that?   -Is it over?
That's amazing
Your hair is so thick
Someone's here   -Who is it?
This room is so dry   -Who are you?
Who are you?
This room is so freaking dry   -Who are you?
Don't tell me she is...
Seriously?
Is she acting Matsumoto-san?
Who is this imitating me though?   -She's Asahi
Ah, she's Asahi
It's so freaking dry
She probably heard that phrase somewhere
I don't care about anything else
Where are you from?
You don't recognize me?
Those nipples are erecting
I never met you before right?
No way, Uika-chan   -Eh? I've met you before?
I'm Matsumoto Hitoshi
It's so dry here right?
Did you say it that frequently?
Your nipples are erecting
Of course, because it's so dry here
Because it's dry?
Matsumoto-san only do chest workouts, no wonder why his chest looks amazing
Yeah I know, but I actually did none of those workouts
Why did you start working out?
Well, since I got married, there's
a lot of things that I need to protect right?
Well, this is just a lie though
It's so dry, are you fine with this?
The intersperse of this line is interesting
That's all she got though   -This intersperse is interesting
Matsumoto-san
Shall we play the Pop-up Pirate?
Then the person who loses need to drink the bitter tea in one breath
In one breath?   -Yeah, that's more interesting
It's gonna make me go to the bathroom
How many times are you going to say that
It's definitely gonna make me go to the bathroom
Nothing we can do about it, please just endure
I'll choose here then
In one breath?
La-la-last person wants to drink the tea
She likes it, she likes it, she can't stop it
Oh, yeah, it sure is tea
(La-la-last person wants to drink the tea)
She likes it, she likes it, she can't stop it
Come on, in one breath
(La-la-last person wants to drink the tea)
It's really concentrated   -Come on, in one breath
It's not about concentrated or not   -Come on, this is a Batsu game
In one breath, come on, in one breath
The flute drinking style
That's old, flute drinking style is old
(She likes it, she likes it, she can't stop it)
Just drink it quickly, my hands really hurt
It's troublesome to shout these slogans   -Really?
She's losing her patience
(Just drink it quickly, my hands really hurt)
Slow, slow, you're so slow   -So many variations
Slow, slow, you're so slow
Is it necessary to drink it in several rounds?
I can't drink it
You drank all of it   -This is my limit, I can't drink anymore
You look down, are you okay?
If you need anything, just let us know   -I want some water
Please drink it then
I see, so she's just thirty   -Yeah, because she did a dance
Thank you very much   -And she's really polite too
On your way, on your way, on your way to hell
She let her guard down
She just let her guard down
Second time?
Second time
What a pity!
I wanted to watch more
And this tastes so bad right?   -It tastes really bad
Isn't this tea?   -It's bitter tea
She drank all of it with a poker face
I bet everyone noticed this...
Kyoko-san
You're out!
Your smile was refreshing
I laughed
Thank you very much   -And she's really polite too
On your way, on your way, on your way to hell
Eh, Kyoko-san is leaving?   -I really had a good time!
She's back to her usual self   -That's great
Let's start
I actually wanted to ask for some advice from you gals
Would you mind listening to me?   -Of course
That's quite rare
What could it be?
It's about the icon for SNS   -Ah, I see
That's quite important
So I need some advice about which photo to choose, from all these front line talents
-Remove your makeup first
-Come on Kaneda, we can't even recognize you now
Beautiful   -So cute
It's Uika
I love this one, it looks so shiny
I thought this one is quite good too
And this one looks good too
Hetake-san from Sharam Q
I'm hesitating between these two photos
This one looks more natural though   -Minekishi...
Did she laugh?   -Minekishi is...
She's in danger   -Is she out already?
Who is this?
Who do you mean?
The one in between
This one?   -This one
This is Hatake-san
Hatake-san? From Sharam Q?
They probably don't know about Hatake-san right?
Yeah, maybe they can't get the gag here
I can't decide which photo to choose   -Hatake from Sharam Q
That was a nice one
You're purposely showing it to me so many times!
This is amazing   -Eh? Hatake-san?
And I thought there's only one photo of Hatake-san, but then there's actually another one
It's really satisfying to get this one
Playing into her hands
Minegishi-san
Yellow card
Yes, I have no excuse   -Well...
Minegishi actually almost laughed all the time   -Yeah, she was
You couldn't hold back right?
Let's take a look
Hatake-san? From Sharam Q?
Uika did a good job here
Yeah, that smooth flip through photos was too perfect
It was perfect   -Yeah, the timing of those flips was perfect
So one more hour left now
Good luck everyone
Zero times?   -Yukipoto is zero times too?
Three of us are zero
Uika-san is zero too?   -Yes, zero
So it's one, one, and one right?
Maybe it's about time for me to do another imitation
Again?   -She's quite aggressive
How many cards do she have in her hand
I watched "E.T." again recently
Ah, that movie "E.T." right?
"E.T."
Very impressive
Her makeup adds to the imitation too   -Yeah, you're right
She probably didn't do it on purpose though
Really well done for them to hold on   -E.T.
Are you okay?
That's not the face of a girl
This is horrible   -You want to be friends with me?
E~T~
Asahi is joining too
It's probably better to join this
They are starting to echo
Uika is in danger
Uika! Uika! Uika!
I don't know what I'm doing, but...
Friends!
Maybe she's actually laughing here
Thank you so much
Here she comes
Someone's coming
What is it?
That's incredible   -Oh my god, that's amazing
The quality is top notch
This is unbelievable
Are you Gachapin-san?
*Gachapin is a popular Japanese television character who appeared in the children's program Hirake! Ponkikki
I'm Gachapin
The costume is really well done
That's amazing, no wonder she disappeared for such a long time
They look alike though
Yeah, she looks like Gachapin
I can do anything
Anything?
What can Gachapin do?
What the heck?
How is this Gachapin?   -That's not it's character setting
Why a cartwheel?
Probably because Gachipin is good at sports, but still...
But still, why did she choose to do a cartwheel
Who is that?   -She's Yukipoyo
*Sento-kun is a yuru-chara mascot created by Nara City Office to commemorate the 1300th anniversary of Nara HeijÅ-kyÅ
Yukipoyo is acting Sento-kun
The music is so loud
She's doing the Para Para dance
Gachapin is dancing together
Is this going to work?
Gachapin is dancing like crazy
They're dancing like KÅji Kikkawa and Ann Lewis
Their minds are in sync   -Good teamwork despite being improvised
What's up with these people? They are amazing!
This would probably get a big laugh even in Documental
Minekishi scored many aggressive points here
But I ruined Yukipoyo's Para para dance
I'm so sorry   -No problem...
I'm so sorry
She's attacking   -This guy is crazy
She's very close   -I'm so sorry
She successfully took her down
This is amazing
Yeah, it's incredible
This is really impressive   -A nice fight
Well done   -She was aggressive
Yukipoyo, yellow card
Nothing I can do about it
That one was cunning
That battle was really impressive
I'm so sorry
She's attacking   -This guy is crazy
She's very close   -I'm so sorry
Minekishi scored many points now
Thank you very much
I'm glad that I did this
Let's start
The last spurt
I would like to sing a song
Judy Ongg-san's "Miserarete (Falling in love with you)"
With no music
Please sing a cappella for us then
I don't know the lyrics though   -You don't?
Is this how you sing that song?   -No, it's not
"Face the south, and open the cur... window"
"Gaze off into the distance, the color of the sea"
"It's too beautiful, it's too terrifying"
"Just like youth"
"The mirage at noon"
Wait, what's next?
Eh...?
I laughed right?
So it's me
I actually warned myself not to laugh though
That was hilarious
That was so funny
It must be me
I know I shouldn't laugh at my own gags, and I'm aware of it
Yes I know   -But then I really enjoyed doing it
Yeah, you enjoyed it
And slowly let your guard down
Matsuno-san, you're out
Nothing I can do about it
Goodbye everyone, wait...
I really didn't want to laugh at my own gags
We will be careful
If she did that for a bit longer, I'll be out
Oh, really?
That first line was ridiculously funny
"Face the south, and open the cur... window"
"Gaze off into the distance..."
Let's continue
Last 30 minutes now
That was amazing
Let's see what Asahi is doing
Here she comes
So cute
What does she want to do?
What is she trying to do?
Shimura-san's...
But Shimura-san didn't do anything like this
Yeah, he didn't
It's just the same costume
What inspired her to do this?
What kind of gag is this?
She went back
She went back...   -I see, so that's it
A beautiful ballerina
She was really cute
By the way, anyone want to battle me?
For what?
Stocking sumo wrestling
Stocking sumo wrestling?
I never did this before though
I never did this before too, how should I do?
I'm not sure, but maybe wear this on your head and do sumo right?
And move in opposite direction
This is quite tough
I'm full of Kaneda's grimace
Yeah, even if she do it again...
She has to add something new   -You're right
How come she knows how to do this
Her face is amazing
Stop it please, stop it
Does it suit me?
It suits, it suits
We're in the same color
The same color
Hey, hey, the same color
The same color, so what
Does it suit me? Do I look pretty?
Both of you are looking gorgeous
Who looks more gorgeous?
Hey, will I be able to get married?
Yeah, sure you can
Her face turns out to be quite funny
It's amazing, oh my god...
I'm so sorry
I'm really sorry
Her face is horrible
This is incredible
I never saw that kind of face
Her face is hilarious
Good boy, good boy...
Why is she giving that thing a stroke?
This is awful
Asahi is in danger, Asahi is in danger
She's the one who brought this item
It feels bad to let others stroke your item
This is just awful
Hotaru...Hotaru...
She keeps saying "Hotaru"
Eh? "Kitano Kuni Kara"?
*"Kitano Kuni Kara (From a North Country)" is a famous Japanese drama, and "Hotaru" is the eldest daughter of the protagonist Gorou
So she's acting Gorou-san
No way, I don't even stand a chance to hold back on that one
It's definitely impossible for me
So last 15 minutes   -Only 15 minutes left
Mom...
That's incredible
She can't find her mom?
You can't find your mommy?
Are you finding your mommy?
Yes, I'm finding my mommy
She laughed
Eh? Uika-san?
What happened? I didn't saw that
Come on, last 15...14 minutes
Uika, you've been doing a good job holding back all the time, why did you laugh at that?
Because she's so pitiful
Are you finding your mommy?
Yes, I'm finding my mommy
But this is the first time for Uika, so yellow card
Oh no
The contest is now nip-and-tuck
Probably now one will be out anymore
So it all comes down to points
Last 15 minutes
Good luck everybody   -Thank you
Damn it
Let's start
So how do we play stocking sumo?
Yeah, I really want to watch stocking sumo
We just move in opposite direction right?   -Yes
They're still continuing with stocking sumo?
She's wearing a stocking, which is even longer than her legs
She did it   -This is fun
Wow, you look like a different person
Eh? Oh my god!
*Senpuki Obasan is a korean famous for having failed cosmetic surgery and her face lost original figure
She looks like Senpuki Obasan
Kanetomo laughed just now right?
Eh? Who?
Kanetomo, she's Kaneda
Did she laugh? I'm not sure
I think so, she laughed slightly
While wearing the stocking...
And laughed out
She laughed for sure
Well, I probably missed it, but...
Kaneda-san laughed right?
Eh? Really?
Really?
They said she clearly laughed even under the socking
Let's take a look
This is amazing
She laughed out a bit
Yeah, she laughed slightly
She's having fun
But it's the first time for Kaneda-san right?   -Yes
Eh, so...
We all received a yellow card
We're all given yellow cards?   -Yes, everyone
So everyone received a yellow card
Let's continue
10 more minutes
They didn't even start pulling
Yeah, the sumo is not started yet
Nice face
Her face changed completely   -This is incredible
What's so "incredible", dude
I'll hold this in the middle
Okay, so start pulling now
OK
Ready, set, go!
So strong
Come on, who are you even trying to make laugh of?
They're heading to the same direction
This is just hurting the neck
Who are you even trying to make laugh of?
Because they don't know how to do this
Yeah, this is ridiculous
They're moving in the same direction
Only 10 more minutes left
Maybe it's better to move on to the next one
What the heck is this
It's amazing
What the heck is this?
This gal is awful
Take a photo, take it, take it
Kaneda-san, only 5 more minutes
Ah, less than 5 minutes now
Let's take a look
If she can show a different photo here
Like the photo of her being bald
Maybe it'll get a laugh
What a face!
Ah, that seems to be it
These faces look amazing
We look like mother and daughter right?
Quite good
We're mother and daughter
If she can show some photos of Hatake-san here
Sadly, no photos of Hatake-san here
It'll probably get a laugh if there is one
Yeah, you're right
These photos are fabulous
This is awful
What the heck is that? So scary
Oh no, oh no, oh no
So cute, you're super cute
Looking good
So cute
This is awful
Yeah, this sure is awful
Who is she acting?
Nice, nice, very nice
Hold on, Minegishi!
I'm sorry
I'm really sorry
They're all attacking at once
Why is everyone attacking her?
They're all attacking!
Why is Minegishi being targeted?
Because she's going to win
Yeah, Minegishi scored more points
So they have to take her down
She's so strong
I'm really sorry
I'm serious, I'm really sorry
Sorry for doing these strange things
Trying to make you laugh with this strange mask
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry
-Despite of belonging to the same generation, I'm so sorry
-Don't tell us your true thoughts
It's terrible for trying to make people laugh with this
I'm really sorry
I'm so sorry!
You don't seem to be reflecting though
I'm really sorry!
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry
I'm really sorry   -Asahi is really doing a good job
I'm so sorry
Minami-san
I'm so sorry for messing around with this
Last one and a half minute, hold on!
Hold on, hold on, hold on!
Please! Hold on!
Can you please forgive me?
Minegishi hold on
Can you forgive me?
They're both working hard
This is amazing
I"m sorry
I'm sorry   -Ah, no way
Why did she leave?
No more time left, it's gonna end
I'm sorry
I'm really sorry
Here she comes, here she comes!
She's in danger, she's in danger!
It's impossible to forgive me right?
Of course, I'm the worst
I'm sorry, I'm the worst, I'm the worst!
I'm the worst! Stupid! Stupid!
I'm the worst! I'm seriously the worst!
How could I do something like this to my senior
I'm the worst
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry
Eh? It ended?
Who wins?
I don't know, maybe no one?
It was so funny, it's too funny
Thank you all
Nice fight
It was amazing, very funny
I've yelled "keep it up!" louder than any sports competition that I've ever watched
So according to everyone's opinion
We've decided a winner
The honorable victory belongs to...
Minegishi!
Thank you very much
Eh? How come?
I'm so happy, thank you everyone
Well, this is just...
The last scene of offense and defense between you and Asahi was just amazing
It really worths watching
But if you think twice, Asahi could actually be laughing under the mask
But this contest was so amazing, that I would really like to watch another season
Thank you everyone for all your hard work
They are all amazing
It was really interesting