Well, they'll probably come up with some strategies
But Documental is where those strategies will not end up as expected
Did I laugh?
I feel like the ability to offense and defense is disproportionate
Funny people are usually easily amused
Remember it, dude
They'll probably prepare some bullets
But it's difficult to determine the timing of using those bullets
Maybe they'll use too much in the beginning, or maybe they'll end without using any
It's not like a machine gun, they won't have infinite bullets
So the timing is crucial
And also who to shoot
And he said "something gummy just came out of me"
Oh, I got some good cards
Tamuken
Eh? No way, definitely not me
Okay, I'll look at it again, is that fine?
Isn't it just a normal egg
Yeah, it's just a normal egg
Out!
Wait a second, wait second, I didn't even...
Let's start
Shall I do the PPAP dance?
The exaggerated PPAP
Shall I do it?   -Sure
Ready?
I have a pen
I have an apple
AHHH
Apple pen
How do you do the normal one again?
I'll do the normal one
I have a pen
I have an urethra
Urethra pen
I have a pen
I have an anal
Anal pen
Urethra pen
Pen-urethra-anal-pen
That's not the normal one at all
Don't put your pen in urethra, that's too painful
Really?
I did it wrong?
You were touching your anal when you said urethra
You tried to act cool when saying it
Like "urethra"   -No, I didn't say it like that
That's really unnecessary   -No, wait...
Like "urethra"
That's not what I did at all
He did, right? Kanoh? Show us how he said it
He's like "It's urethra, dude"
I didn't say "dude"
I never say "dude"
Junior...
What are you looking at?
Eh? He's kind of laughing is he?
Show us Perfect Human
*Perfect Human is a song released by the comedy duo Oriental Radio
Perfect Human?
That's enough
Junior is in danger already
Hey, look at him
Na, ka, ta, Nakata, na, ka, ta, Nakata, na, ka, ta, Nakata
I'm a per---
Per---fect human
Na, ka, ta, Nakata
I'm a per---
Per---fect human
Okay, okay, he endured it
You can imitate anyone?
Yeah, I can imitate Nishimura from Viking too, without exaggeration
*Zakoshi is very good friends with Kotoge and Nishimura from Viking, and he always imitate them on his YouTube channel
Eh? Show us, please
Nishimura from Viking?
Oh, I haven't been here for a long time, I feel so nostalgic
Oh, nothing changed at all, I feel so nostalgic
Kotoge-sensei, it's me, Nishimura
Nothing changed at all
That's it   -It's really well-imitated
You can imitate Kotoge too right?
Yes, I can
Hey, I'm Nishimura, don't you recognize me?
I don't recognize you
I'm Nishimura, don't you recognize me?
I said, I don't recognize you
That's it
You're quite good at imitating right?
Yeah, of course
What about Koume?
Imitation
His another imitation is the best though
Another one?   -Zakoshi is amazing
The one about Fist of the North Star
Oh, the imitation of Fist of the North Star in Famicom, when he enters the cave and leaves
In Famicom
Glad that I don't know about this
You're really into it
Zakoshi is terrible
Huh?
I did over 300 outdoor filming in Kansai last year
Many of them are taken in osteopathy clinics
So I became able to tell whether a person could have bunions
Jinnai-san, please   -Oh, me?
Yes   -Sure, please take a look
He knows about bunions?
With bunion, you may have ingrown toenails, and end up walking in a strange form
And you may even run-down
Ah, showing one leg is enough
Even males can have bunions?
Yes, males as well, you can see many of them in hospitals
Can you please put your right leg over here?
What would you be able to tell?
Whether he could have bunions in the future
Jinnai is having a hard time
He scored many points for this
He's just tickling me
No, this is different from tickling
No way, wait a second, that's just the same as tickling
No, it's not, they're different
That's just the same as tickling
Well, but Yamaguchi scored many points for this
That's just the same as tickling though
Well, but still, you need to endure it
No way, wait a second please, come on
This is inappropriate, of course one will laugh
He was licking like crazy
Eh? Are you joking?
No way, that's a foul, of course one will laugh
No, please, wait a second bro...   -Because you laughed out loud
Not yet, please, wait a second...   -Let's take a look
This is hard to say...   -He's just tickling me
-Should this be a yellow card though?   -Seriously, anyone will laugh when being tickled
Whether he could have bunions in the future
He's already laughing here
Because he's tickling me
Well, he is not tickling here
He kept licking my feet like crazy   -That's not tickling
He kept licking between my toes
That's strict   -He's in danger
You laughed, indeed
No, that shouldn't be called as laughing...
And I don't like how you cover your face after laughing
No, no...   -I don't like how you try to hide your face after laughing
Well, but Yamaguchi scored many points for that
Thank you very much
Let's start
Tamura-san?   -I had a surgery for ingrown toenails already
-Jinnai, let him check your another leg?
-No, no way, I'm fine, I don't mind having it anyway
Takahashi-san, looking at how you stand,
you're probably a potential patient
Just let him check your legs
No way, this is awkward, this needs to be done on two people?
Well, I don't think it's awkward   -Let me check it, just in case
You already know what will happen right? So it must be fine
I didn't know what will happen   -He's right
Takahashi-san just let me do a quick check
(Well yeah, you'll probably laugh if you don't know what will happen)
If you're right-handed, then it's better to let me check your right leg
This is just... Are you okay with this?
I really don't like these kind of things...
It's incredible that no one laughed at that
That was a bit close
I think you'll be fine
Do you need to lick that much to check?   -You were licking it like crazy
I thought something is wrong at first
That's amazing
I somehow feel sorry for you
No problem at all
I somehow feel sorry
Yamaguchi is amazing
What happened?   -My shoulder hurts
It hurts?   -Because he was enduring all the time
Yeah, it somehow hurts
Huh?
-You should check his another leg then
-Yeah, people say it's a diagonal line
Let him check your left leg too
Please, just in case
Well, I don't feel like having any problem though
But I'll check it just in case
He's so kind
How is it?
Doctor, how is it?
Please wait a second
Here comes the last bit
Yamaguchi was incredible
This is inappropriate   -Yeah, it's inappropriate
How did everyone hold back on that one?
Instead of checking my legs, I feel like he's trying to make me cum
That scene was amazing
Taking everything into consideration
Doctor, how is it?
Please wait a second
Here comes the last bit
Well, yeah, a yellow card
That was awful
I feel like Jinnai laughed as well   -No, I didn't laugh
No, I didn't laugh, what are you talking about?
It's awkward to give me a red card like this
Let's start
What's that?
Doctor Yamauchi-sama from Kamaitachi
Take that off, dude
Who are you?
It's so hot, it's so hot...AHHH
So it's his "so hot" gag
You know that?
Zakoshi is so aggressive
Oh, what's that?   -I'm addicted to instagram
You're taking photos with that?   -No way
You can't upload to IG with thtat
Just use smartphones
This increases the charm
So after using the camera, you take the photo again with smartphone?
Yeah, just take it again
Are your photos instagrammable?
Yes, they're instagrammable
What kind of photo?   -I take photos of people too
Can I take a photo of you then, Tamuken?
Can you make a pose, please?
Is "Cha" fine?   -That's good
Cha
Looking good, are you ready?
Say cheese, okay
Can I take one more?
Can you take one step backward, please?
Say cheese, okay
I actually saw him performing this before
Eh? He performed this?   -So it's a gag
You performed this gag before?   -Yeah, I saw him performing
Did that gag get a laugh?
Yeah, it got a laugh
Sorry, I was looking up when I did "cha"   -No problem
He's so short
Eh? Umemiya-san is so short
Why is he so short?
Probably like 136cm
He's so short
Was he this short?
He's so nimble
And he's putting his hands in his pocket
What happened to you Umemiya-san?
He's pissing me off
He's really pissing me off
Junior is quite weak at Zakoshi's performances
He's Satoru Sayama, the original Tiger Mask
The Mask of Tiger
When the Tiger passed over there, he was on high alert
Look, he's on high alert
Because he's a human weapon
Well, but apart from that...try to go near Junior-san
Look, he's on really high alert
What are you doing?
He's really rigid
Although he's not talking at all, he's still wearing the mic
Why are you coming here?
He's here now
He's nose breathing   -Leave me alone
He's nose breathing
Leave me alone
Jinnai wants to do something   -No, I'm fine
Sobat, sobat, I want to watch rolling sobat
Ouch, you hit me
Although it doesn't hurt at all
It's so low, your kick is so low
He's nose breathing all the time
He's nose breathing all the time, he's not opening his mouth
Look, he's nose breathing all the time, despite moving a lot
He's deep nose breathing
He's having a rest   -He must be tired
I don't really know about his character   -Me too
Not familiar with Sayama Satoru-san...
What happens if you take off his mask?
Can I take off your mask?
Take off his mask, Kobayashi
Ouch...
He said "ouch"
Takahashi, Takahashi, Takahashi!
Ouch, it hurts...
Lie down here
Is that what Jimmy said earlier   -No, not about that
Eh? What should I do?   -Lie down and face here
Ok, is this fine?
He's still saying "su-su-su" over there
Oh, I see, he's inhaling oxygen
Just relax, although I don't know what will happen too   -Okay
His head is on the Isodine bottle
It doesn't hurt at all?
A little bit...
Are you relaxing enough?   -Yes
Ah, you shouldn't be prepared for it
You shouldn't know when it will come   -Okay, I'll relax
So it hurts because of this right?
Well, but does it hurt at that distance though
Even my nose hurts...my nose hurts...
Na, ka, ta, Nakata, na, ka, ta, Nakata, na, ka, ta, Nakata
I'm a Per---fect Human
You were recording it all the time?
What happened?
There's an egg   -Eh?
I felt tired and laid my head down, just to find out there's an egg
That's awful
The egg was over there
And it's now here
That's incredible
Is it my fault? My fault?
Wipe it off and deeply reflect on yourself
Eh? It's my fault? My fault?
Let's play Shisho Karuta?
What's that?   -Sounds interesting
Shout out phrases that these comedian masters may say or have said
So the person who put his hand on the card first get to say the phrase
This is Oogiri
Let's try with this card then  -Yeah, sure
I took off my shirt
I can't take it off
No one was inside, so I went in first
Ruiji Yonse, are you free today?
What the heck is that? A shop?
His friend   -The name of his friend?
Ruiji Yonse, are you free today?
Oh, so he's really his friend?   -Yes
Aren't you Ruriko-chan, oh my dear?
That's out
How come?
He doesn't say "oh my dear"
What's this word?   -It's "o"
OH, YES!
Too many cars are parking outside, dude!
I love big cars
Who? Kanoh?
I didn't see that one
That was close   -Sure it was
But then he laughed out first   -That was close
I didn't see that one clearly too
He clearly laughed
Didn't I stopped the laugh like this?   -No, you completely laughed
We can even hear your laughter
Let's watch it again, I didn't see that one too
The color of the card changes, depending on how much he laughed
*Shiroganeze refers to the housewives living in the rich region in Tokyo, Shirogane, who does nothing but shop and dine out
You were laughing like Shiroganeze*
They looked at each other
Well, this one...
Orange!
Wow, that's strict
Good luck everyone   -Thank you
If you're hungry, just call for delivery
I'm starving
Let's eat sushi?
There's sushi here   -Really?
Yeah, it's over here
Do you want sushi too?
Yeah, I want sushi
Let's eat with our hands
There's so many sushi shops
Let's continue
There's many sushi shops to choose from
What about this, the 9000 yen set, Mutsuki?
Shall I call them now?   -Yes, please
Mommy...
Mommy, mommy...
I loved Funakoshi Eiichiro so much
*Kazuyo Matsui is a Japanese actress who divorced her husband Eiichiro Funakoshi, because he cheated on her
I thought I will be with Funakoshi forever
However, Funakoshi Eiichiro cheated on me
He chose another woman over me, he cheated on me
He's Matsui-san   -Yeah, Matsui Kazuyo-san
Matsui-san, we need you help   -Yes?
Can you please order sushi for us?   -Sushi right?
He's really calling them
What should I order?   -The Mutsuki set
Hello, I would like to have the Mutsuki set
Yes, two please   -Okay, two
Two 9000 yen sets, am I right?   -Yes, thank you very much
What is your address?   -What's the address here?
L1 Studio
L1?   -Yes
Can you please tell me your name?
I'm Mommy...mommy...
Mom?   -Mommy...
You are Mr. Mommy?
Yes, Mommy...mommy...
Okay, I got it   -Mommy, mommy...
L1 Studio right? Got it   -Yes, thank you, Mommy...
Okay, thank you very much   -Mommy, mommy...
Zakoshi is terrible
Shall we continue?
Yeah, it's gonna take a while
Starting with "Sa"...   -Sai-shisho helped me a lot
It's really difficult to come up with a phrase for Kanpei-san
It's possible for him to say whatever phrase   -Yes, you're right
Please put it upside down
You said something just now right? What did you say?
What did you say just now?
You said something just now right?
Samba rhythm
Eikoh-chan, say the next phrase straight away   -Immediately?
Okay, got it
Don't put your arm around my waist
You even laughed out loud
That was a good one
I was just thinking "what is this all about"?
Oh, you don't know about him?
Yeah, he don't know about this person
That was unexpected
Akiyama   -Yes, I know
Let's take a look
Don't put your arm around my waist
It took him so much time
And yet, it's not interesting at all
What color should this be?
He laughed out loud   -Yeah, he laughed out loud
We can clearly hear him laughing
It's so strict this time   -Because you laughed out loud
Many people are just one step away from losing
Let's continue
Up till now, Yamauchi is quite amazing for scoring many points, and yet without receiving any cards
And Zakoshi is incredible too
Kenkoba is working hard this time too, he haven't received any cards
You guys wanna play a game?
Game?   -What kind of game?
What game?   -Listen to me...
This is a game invented by Moriya Biyori, a comedian from Osaka
And it's extremely popular among them now
The game is called Hemonica
*Kancho is a prank performed by clasping the hands together in the shape of an imaginary gun and attempting to poke an unsuspecting victim's anus
Put the harmonica in your mouth, and your enemy will Kancho you*
And if the harmonica made a sound then you lose
So you can't blow into the harmonica   -Yes, you can't blow
But it's awful to be Kancho-ed
Yes, but even so, you need to endure and not to blow it here
Do you mean the nose?
Not about the nose
No, he's asking are we supposed to breathe with our nose then
Of course, or else we'll be dead
Yamaue, can you try it then?   -I'm Yamauchi
Why did you call him Yamaue?   -Two hours have passed and still...
He probably mixed it up with my partner's name, Hamaye   -Oh, I see
Oh, I see
Do you always call people the wrong name, even at home?
*Norika Fujiwara is Jinnai's ex-wife
Maybe you'll call someone Norika by accident?*   -No way, I won't
I never said that at home, anyway
Yamauchi, you wanna give it a try?
So I'll get a Kancho? Can I wear my trousers then?   -That's so scary
Maybe I'll show you guys how to do it first, I've played this before
I'll show you guys how to endure though this
Be careful though, don't hurt my bones   -Got it
It's here, over here   -Okay
Are you ready?   -Wait a second...
I'll lose if it made a sound   -Yes
Are you ready?
I'm gonna kill you!
He surprised me
And then, you shouldn't make any sound right?
That's not how you play the game
Sorry, so I did it wrong
It's ridiculous for him to say "kill me" right?
For the sake of argument, let's say it's fine to kick me
He looked into my eyes and said "kill me", that's ridiculous
He probably misunderstood it   -Yeah, it's his first time to play
Let him try this again
(These people are so strong in defense)
I'll do it
I'm gonna freaking kill you!
He's saying it for real
He's really thinking about it
Did something happened between you two?
Let's play Hemonica properly guys
How do you play Hemonica again?
Put this in your mouth, get a Kancho, and hold your breath
You understand me?
Should I do an exaggerated Harumafuji then?
*Harumafuji Kohei is a Mongolian former professional sumo wrestler
Why the heck?
It's not really exaggerated though
Yeah, it's actually without exaggeration
Harumafuji was actually more exaggerated
(That's hilarious, absolutely hilarious)
I'll do it
Let's play Hemonica properly
It's Takahashi and Yamauchi
Who is it?
Both of them laughed
Yamauchi laughed for sure
I'm sure that Yamauchi laughed too
Yes, you're right
This is probably a double kill
That one was just awful, Zakoshi
What's wrong with you?   -It really hurts
Just blow it   -It really hurts badly
He attacked him right in his face
But no joke, it really hurts
Let's take a look at Takahashi first
He's still holding on here
Let's watch Yamauchi next
He's laughing already
Well yeah, but after this...
Yeah, so it's a double kill
Takahashi is already...
For Yamauchi, is this your first time?
Yes, it's my first time
Sorry, but I have to give you this, even it's your first time
Because you laughed out loud
So strict
I scored many points now right?   -Yeah, sure you did
Someone is knocking the door   -It arrived
Ah, mommy is here
Thank you very much   -Mommy, mommy...
Wow, this is amazing   -This looks tasty
Was there anything wrong with our phone call?   -No problem at all
What is your name?   -I'm Tabuchi
-Tabuchi-san   -So you're not Mommy, huh?
Not at all
What's in your waist pouch?
Probably some change right?   -Yes, you're right
Not something dirty, huh?   -Yes, of course
Excuse me...
Wow, this looks so good   -Yeah, it looks delicious
This is really luxurious right?
Shall we play the "Russian Isodine"?   -Eh?
Too dangerous to play with Isodine
You can know which one is Isodine by smell though
Just try to pour some first   -Eh? We're gonna dip in it?
(So basically using it as soy sauce)
As long as the color is the same...   -It's completely the same
Can't tell the difference at all   -Let's try it
Eikoh-chan, try this   -Eh?
Give us a Isodine call
Yeah, he can do this
Isodine
Sounds good, you can do this
Let's dig in
I'm gonna start with Toro
The texture is so tender
It looks so tasty   -It's really good
There's a lot of fat on it, so it should be fine   -Yeah, I think he can do this
It looks so good, I'll eat it
The sauce is even on the rice
What happened?
What's wrong?
Scary, scary, scary
Is it that painful?
This is terrible
Eh, something black is coming out of his mouth
What the heck is that black thing   -Eh?
It reacted with something   -It turned black, that's so scary
How come it's black?
Eh? Show it to us
Chemical reactions   -It's black
That must be poison   -This is terrifying
How does it taste?   -Delicious
So it's delicious?
How could that be delicious
That color was awful
It's completely black
And somehow purple-ish too
-Let's play rock, paper, scissors and the loser will eat this
-Eh, no way, that's impossible, dude
Let's try it with Uni sushi
Every time I breathe, I can taste the isodine and fat
Eh?   -It's reacting?
Maybe it's because of the fat then
What about the taste?   -Delicious
So it's delicious...
Someone, please try this
Let's try it with the egg
Egg should be fine right?   -Easy
Easy? Do it then
You said it's easy   -You can do this?
So only the egg
Yeah, it's isodine, dude
Without rice
No,no,no   -Only egg
Aww, it's red   -Ewww
It's already reacting   -Chemical reactions
It's already reacting, come on
Just eat it, dude
(Who said that just now)
No way, no way   -This is terrible
It's black already
This is terrible   -Seriously inappropriate
It's just egg coming out
Something yellow came out
No chemical reactions at all
How does it taste?   -Super delicious
So it's delicious?
We all know you're gonna say that
And you even tried to make a funny face
That's a dull moment
But there wasn't any chemical reactions
Yeah, it didn't went black
Maybe it's because of Eikoh-chan's mouth?
Oh, so because Eikoh-chan is black
It can't be...
He's probably farting ink or something
Eh? Really?   -POO
Did you fart just now?
You farted again?
Yes
At this timing?
So honest
Do you guys know who's jacket is this?
Eh?   -Is this school uniform?
No, it's suits
It's Hatori-sensei right?   -Yes
The Hatori chef
Why do you have it?
Let's see who suits Hatori's jacket
I think it'll suit me   -Yeah, it'll probably suit Kobayashi
It suits muscular people better
So it's probably me
Yeah, it's Kobayashi
Does this look good on me?
It's the Hatori-sensei during new year
Happy new year   -Happy new year
Congratulations
Yamauchi, try this   -Ok
It probably fits Yamauchi too
Sushi tastes so good
What are you drinking?
Soy milk
So many tattoos...   -Are you Hatori-sensei?
Yes   -You are Hatori-sensei?
He got so many tattoos...
Sensei, you got some tattoos?
Yes
Eh? Aren't you the teacher of a nutrition school?   -And a chef
Were you gangish when you're young?   -Yes, when I'm young
Sensei, what about your back?
Wow, that's amazing
Carp   -Is that a carp?
Because I can cook it   -Oh, I see, carp dishes
But those at the front are irrelevant to cooking
*The Hannya mask is a mask used in Noh theater, representing a jealous female demon
Yeah, it's Hannya*
Your tattoos are separated   -Yeah, I got them separately
I wonder what's the story behind those tattoos
Each tattoo has a story behind
Eh? What story?
I got this one when I knocked down all Osaka chefs
What about the one on your back?
When I opened my cooking school   -In commemoration
What about the one on your right chest?
Only for this one on my right chest...
I was forced to get this tattoo   -Eh?
Who forced you to get it?
Forced by...Kawakoe-kun
The french chef Kawakoe-kun?
Eh?   -What happened?
You had a dispute with him before right?
Yes, and that's when he forced me to get this tattoo
He forced you?   -That's so scary
He forced you?   -Yes, he definitely forced me
A bunch of french chefs came to me   -Eh?
French chefs are all gangish?
Yeah, French chefs are all gangish
No they're not, dude
You're not cooking anymore now?
I'm not cooking at all now
For about 12 years
Eh? You're not cooking now?
This guy is pissing me off
Thank you very much
I didn't eat any
Hey guys
Do you guys shave your pubic hair?   -Eh?
Do you guys shave your pubic hair?
No, nothing to do with it
You guys didn't remove it right?   -Yes
That's actually considered as unsanitary from a global perspective
Yeah, I've heard about that   -And only Asians don't remove it
Only Japanese don't remove it nowadays
What about you then?
I've actually...removed all of it
Since when?   -What the heck?
And you know what? It's so smooth now
You removed it with Brazilian Wax right?
I saw someone use it before, it was so clean and smooth
It's super clean now
Well, I have a bad skin because I removed it recently
What will come up if you connect those dots with straight lines?
Oh, these dots?
Lend me your pen
Eh? Are you going to do this for me, Junior-san?
I bet something will come up
I actually have metal allergy too
Metal, he said metal allergy
Oh, so because of the belt
Wow, this is awful
Yeah, I have metal allergy
Why did you fart, dude?
Control yourself, please
Incredible
Eh? Did something come up?
Yeah, I can see this coming
Eh? Really?
Not doing it on purpose?
No, not on purpose
You've connected the dots?   -Yeah, and that came up
Is that Sneech? (from Doraemon)
So I'm actually Sneech?
Simply by connecting the dots...   -Yeah
Maybe the dots on you guys have something too, so...
I've actually cut my pubic hair too
Oh, really?   -Yeah, but not shaved, just cut
I've brought the Brazilian Wax here
Mine is quite short already
Eh? How do you do this?   -It must be painful
I've already cut my pubic hair   -How come?
Look, look
Yeah, your hair is so short and thin
This can remove your underarms hair too
My pubic hair is short, is it fine?
Yeah, that's perfect, it can't be too long
It looks clean right?
I did this myself, so I can do this for you guys too
Will it grow again after a while?
No, it won't grow again
Eh? No way
The amount that grows become less   -Eh?
That's so scary   -Yeah, so scary
Wow, amazing   -Never seen something like this before
Seriously, after using this
It becomes impressively clean and smooth
It will be removed immediately?   -Yes
So scary
So sticky   -It's quite hard already?
Is it fine to be that hard?
Wow, it's so hard   -What should you do after this?
Wow, it's already...
That's just glue!*
*"That's glue" has the same pronunciation as Norika, which is the name of Jinnai's ex-wife
Norika?   -No, no, that's not what I meant
I mean it's like glue
This reminds you of her?
No, it's awkward to remember her because of this, dude
Do you need to put on that much?   -What the heck is going on...
What a gentle penis
Yeah, he has a smart penis
What was that just now?
I missed that one too
What the heck was that?
I was so happy because he said my penis is gentle
You completely laughed, so happily
I felt so happy for someone to say my penis is gentle
That was a refreshing smile
I was so happy
Is this the first time for Koba?   -Yeah, the first time
That was quite a laugh though   -Yeah, it was
It can't be...
Just kidding...   -This scared me
But still orange?   -Yeah, probably orange
It should be, you were laughing naturally
But apart from this, Jinnai, you said Norika right?
Yeah, that was terrible
-I want to give you a card because of that
-No, no, I just meant it looks like glue
That was surprising   -I feel sorry for this
That was just...I almost laughed too
Do you need to put on that much?   -What the heck is this...
What a gentle penis
What the heck was that?
That was a benign smile
Yeah, I didn't feel bad at all
I even thought he's praising me
Did everyone received an orange card?
Me too   -Me too
Mine is just yellow
Yeah, some are just yellow
And Zakoshi is zero
Received no cards and scored many points
He's so strong   -Yep, zero
Is it fine to take it off now?   -Yeah
Is it dangerous now?  -Quite dangerous
We've waited too long
Let's start
It's dangerous?   -Yeah
Shall we play Hemonica at the same time?   -Yeah, you're right
Let's play Hemonica
Is it fine?   -It must be painful
Wow, is this really going to be fine?
I feel like it's gonna peel off his skin
Is this going to be fine?
Eh? So scary   -Are you ready?
He definitely laughed at that one
That looks so freaking painful
That's awful   -Are you okay?
It hurts so freaking bad, what the heck was that?
I bet it must be painful
Is that the proper way to do this?   -I don't know too
Tamuken said he knows how to do this   -It hurts so bad
That's awful
Eh? What happened?
He's the one who did that and he's laughing
Yeah, depending on the actual situation, I'll give him a red card
You must be kidding me
He already received a yellow card, so let's take a look and decide whether to give him an orange or red card
Wait a second, come on, why did I ever start this?
That's not laughing   -You clearly laughed
You completely laughed   -You were laughing out loud
You definitely laughed at this one
*Takuzo Kawatani was a Japanese film actor, most famous for playing villains
You even looked like Takuzo Kawatani
Chattering his jaw
I was attacked both visually and audibly
Why the heck did I even start this?
OUT!!
You're out!
Eh? Seriously?
*Mizuame is a sweetener from Japan which is translated literally to "water candy"
It's like Mizuame now
Someone, please do this again for Koba
Eh? We have no idea how to do this
Just hold this tight and give a strong pull
Koba lie down and do this again   -No please, I'm so scared
Yeah, better let him lie down first
Someone need to pull this off for him
I actually have many other things to perform
Eh?
Eh? You thought I'm done?
How come you invited me?
That was so fast, am I the second person out?
Yeah, you're right
That was completely a self-destruct, I should have asked others to do it
When Kobayashi's penis, who has been so gentle all the time, went crazy like "uueehh"
That got me and I just can't hold back
I really wanted to stay for a bit longer
Just for a bit longer...