-Let's get started
-Yeah, let's get started
-For today...
-Yes
I personally think that season 3 was fantastic
But surprisingly enough, some people like season 2 instead
So we can see that people are starting to
form their own preferences for Documental
season3 New System
"Zombie System"
We want to create a chaotic situation
This chaos becomes apparent as it comes close to the end
And being active as a zombie is very impressive as well
Some contestants may even want to
become a zombie as soon as possible
Basically aiming for zombie
Although this makes me ask "why are you even here"
The constantly evolving experiment
The ways to enjoy Documental
I understand that you could be focusing on
who will be the winner and even become emotional
However you could enjoy the show in another way
If you try to focus on the fun parts other than the competition
Every episode, every season,
It could give rise to comedy duos like Nyanko Star
Although Nyanko Star never actually won
Many people say that this show
has a lot of inappropriate dirty jokes
But I don't think there's any dirty jokes at all for this show
Those are not dirty jokes
Those are ART
Art?
People need to learn more about art
When I took a walk this morning, some beautiful
hell flowers were blossoming on the edge of the eaves
Have you been visiting your loved ones at the cemetery?
That being said, I would like to offer you an invitation
Could you prepare one million yen
and gather at a designated location?
I shall reinitiate Documental
I have prepared a reward of 10 million yen for the winner
Of course, participation is voluntary
For those of you who wish to participate, I shall inform you of the time and location
Awaiting your reply
During the fruitful autumn,
I hope good things will happen to you as well
Sincerely, Matsumoto Hitoshi
THE PARTICIPATING COMEDIANS ENTER
Someone's coming
The first one?
Yes, you are
-So here comes Nobu
-I'm the first one...
Well, it doesn't feel good to be the first one
Hello, I'm Nobu from Chidori
What's this?
Here it comes!
This shouldn't be for Nobu
Nobu is definitely an all-round player
His responses are fast and interesting
While it's possible to get a laugh out of Nobu
But he's the kind of person
who can turn others into Owarai
The Tsukkomi field's addictive kingpin
However, I don't think he will be an aggressive player
And he probably won't be interesting at all if he becomes a zombie
Since I'm not a Boke
It's not going to be interesting
I don't mean that I've been lazy or weakened
But recently, my jobs are all about
food reviews for cakes at Shibuya or Harajuku
And I even thought that am I really a comedian now?
So I shall become a comedian again right here
and take on this challenge
How could I be the first one?
Who else is coming?
-This is where it all begins
-Who else is coming?
This is such a big suitcase, is he from Spain or somewhere
It's Itoda-san...
I'm Itoda Jun from Speed Wagon
Please let me do this
Excuse me. Hello
In terms of the ability to attack and defense as a comedian
I'm below average for both of them
He's someone who cares nothing about the atmosphere
He has a strong heart and spirit
Did you forget about it? It's me, it's me
Hamburger!!
Having a strong heart could be very threatening
It's fearful to have this kind of person
He's probably aggressive and tries to attack
However, the attacks that Itoda
think is an attack, won't be attacks at all
But the ones that he don't think
is an attack, may possibly be an attack
Jun-san is awful, this is awful
Even if I try to think about it,
it won't turn out the way I thought anyway
So I rather leave everything to chance,
and hope for something good to happen
I want to show a different Itoda, that has never been shown
-You didn't even tell your partner right?
-Yes, I didn't
Because they said not to tell anyone
He never learns his lessons
-It's my third time now
-Third time?
It's already my third time
-I thought Fujimon-san won't be here for the third time
-So it's Nobu-chan and Jun-chan
Hello, I'm Fujimoto from Fujiwara
This time, I really want to win
Haha, come on, I knew it
This always come to me
He is almost like a regular member for this show
Fujimon is really helpful for being the mood maker
Some fans even say that I'm being too nice to Fujimon
No I'm not being nice to him,
but it's always good to have a mood maker
The perpetual motion comedian
In my 29th year as a comedian
This is the first time for me to
find the field or battlefield that suits me
Last time, I almost won for being the last 4 contestants to stay
I even thought I am going to win
The painful regret for having a moment of relaxation
Doing Tsukkomi to every detail could be my way to fight
We're all Tsukkomi right?
-Yeah you're right
-For the three of us
Maybe I should sit on the other side
That's a small bag
-I always use this
-That's a really small one
Because I'm not that type of comedian
Well yeah
It's you again?!
-Why are you coming?
-You're always coming
Fujimon is the one that always comes
You too dude
Hello, I'm Kukky from Yaseibakudan
Here it comes
Again?
She's just my manager
Kukky is actually easily amused
But on top of that, his attacks are even more powerful
The comedian that kills comedian
Who I hated the most was Kukky
That was awful
You have no idea what he will do
The zombie Kukky is just terrifying
Seriously, Yoshimoto has took in someone inconceivable
This may sound boring, but to be honest, for my third time
I want to win this contest for real
I won't hesitate to break my eardrum just to win this contest
I will hang up their cheeks
with fishing gut and make it a smiley face
I want to be greedy and win just once
Hey, our watches match, stop that
Alright, let's get it over with
Yeah, it's dangerous if we found out after the contest starts
How come?
-How could this overlap
-Stop this kind of happenings dude
Damn, here comes a strong player
Even women are joining this?
So even women are joining
-That's a huge one
-That's amazing
Please excuse me for this
I'm Kurosawa Kazuko from Morisantyu, and I'm single
Ah, my hands are shaking
She is the only woman in this contest
Having a women in this contest makes it interesting
For example, Oojima who joined in season 2
Morisantyu is a group with high potential
No one can possibly stop Kurosawa if she freaks out
The meat that sings and dances
If a women eventually wins, then it could possibly be Kurosawa
But Kurosawa has one weakness
What is Kurosawa's weakness?
Kurosawa is on her period
This may also turns out good though
What should I do?
I'm so scared
Seriously, why are you coming?
I didn't win any competitions, not the King of Conte as well
I want to work hard and win Documental
So there's a chance for other female comedians to join again
Are you fine with this?
But I'm nearly forty already,
so I'm not interested in those sex appeal
-Oh I see
-I'm not in my 20s
What do you mean by sex appeal? We're not doing it for you
It's not?
This can't be true
-How come?
-You both are here?
Yeah, this is the main point
Why are you here?
The first time to have a Kombi
No way, Nobu is here
So for this time
We tried something new, like a new gimmick
To have a comedy duo joining together
I'm Daigo from Chidori
I will not laugh
So I'm being invited by Matsumoto-san
We invited both Nobu and Daigo as a comedy duo
This is actually the first time for this show
Which is also an interesting attempt
to know what is going to happen
But Chidori is interesting anyway,
and probably both of them suits this show
Yeah, they are interesting
I am having high expectation for them
But just one thing, they are quite easily amused
The crude and shy bald guy
I'm not good at making others laugh,
while staying calm in the face
I'm the type of comedian that
makes others laugh while laughing
So this may turn out to be an awful day
No one knows what will happen until it starts
If Nobu is here, then we can always
do the usual Boke and Tsukkomi pattern
However, he's not here, so I'm not sure what to do
-This attempt is amazing
-Eh, what should I do
Why is Chidori coming, you guys are being recommended, huh?
Don't say that dude
Someone's coming
-This guy is a strong player
-For real?
You're wearing different glasses today?
I left it at home, and I'm wearing the one for performances
I was too nervous, and left it at my lobby
Hello, I'm Iio Kazuki from Zun
I'm nervous as a cat now
Excuse me
Here it comes
I've been using those gags a long time ago
What kind of gags are effective for Documental?
Can this camera take a shot of my feet please
I was model posing for the last 7~8 minutes
I have many gags
But for those that are interesting,
I can count on the fingers of one hand
Iio will probably attack from somewhere that no one expected
And with weapons that no one is familiar with
The orthodox inheritor of Sekine faction comedy
He's not the type of player who
makes all-out effort in all rounds
But instead attacking in the 5th or 8th round
I don't think I have any explosive power
I'm more like traditional Chinese medicine,
which takes some time for it to work
Sanma-san said I taste like side dishes 15 years ago
Like the curry rice being sold at Sushi restaurants
If I lost the competition, I will walk back home
And praise myself before I sleep,
because I'll be exhausted from walking
It would be hilarious if Yasu-san came instead
*Yasu-san is Kazuki's partner
Don't say that you idiot
This guy is terrible
Yeah, this guy will definitely make me laugh
This guy has a funny face, which is cunning
He looks like he was immersed in formalin right?
I'm Nishizawa Yusuke from Daian
I will try my best
Excuse me
Again?
Oh, it's not for me?
Just shut up for once
-No, it's not for you Tsuda-san
-Eh, really? Not for me?
I quite like Daian's Manzai, and I've always been watching it
It's quite interesting, and it sometimes amazes me
-This is a chance for you to shine bro
-Yeah I know it's a chance
But I have the impression that he never laughs
And he's strong in this sense
Although people use to say that I have a poker face
But I'm actually easily amused
So I have to be careful of this
We're all the same when we are in the wrestling ring
So this chance to beat my seniors as a junior is really exciting
This is what motivates me, and this is what I'm aiming for
He's funny even if he just turns around
Is he an absent-minded character?
No, not absent-minded
Not absent-minded, but people say that I have a poker face
-But I'm actually easily amused
-Yeah he is
Oh, really?
I never saw Nishizawa laughing out loud though
He's really easily amused
Here comes the 9th contestant
Someone's here
Hello everybody
This is terrible
This is freaking me out
You monster
-I know everybody here
-Of course
Of course dude
What is going to happen, seriously
I'm Kurochan from Yasuda Dai Circus
I'm definitely going to get the 10 million
Eh, what's going on?
Letter?
Really?
This man is the unknown
I seriously have no idea what will happen
Maybe everyone will be making fun of him?
And if Fujimon starts making fun of Kurochan,
that's gonna be hilarious
Fujimon x Kurochan
That's enough dude
Just stay calm and act normal
Japan's record holder as prank victim
But depending on how people make fun of him,
something may start to change inside him
People always say that, for me to survive,
I have to become the toy of TV shows
It's impossible for me to attack
I don't quite understand Owarai,
so I won't understand the high level gags anyway
So I believe I have high defense in this sense
This could actually be a chance right?
If people start to think
"Kurochan can actually make people laugh as well"
Then maybe I can have jobs other than Dokkiri
I'm going to change myself here
I really want to change, and move one step forward
I'll try my best
My parents will prepare the money for me
Just one more person
Who's it gonna be
Maybe the last person is the worst
The last contestant must be surprising for them
I won't laugh if it's Watabe-san
Here comes the last person
-This can't be true
-Really?
You're fine with this?
Why is it these members?
He's definitely qualified though
He don't need this money right?
Hello, I'm Miyasako from Ameagari-Kesshitai
Excuse me
Seriously?
Well, many things happened recently
So I'm not mentally ready to join this kind of show
It's impossible for me to laugh, except in the workplace
-Before that kind of thing happens...
-Can you not say "that kind of thing"
What do you mean by "that kind of thing"
If I join the contest with this mental status,
maybe I'll be able to win the 10 million
I never thought Miyasako will accept the invitation
He probably changed right? After that kind of thing happened
The life-and-death off-white comedian
This man is absolutely crazy
He's amazing when he goes nuts
His explosive power is truly terrifying
I'm aggressive even towards seniors or whosoever
If there's someone that I don't feel comfortable with
I'll lay him down right from the beginning
Recently, most of my jobs are about being the host
There wasn't much chance for me to just mess around
So I want to join this
Miyasako-san is joining as well?
We need to be considerate
It's cunning to do things as a Konbi though
We talked about this and it's fine
The rules didn't prohibit this
-That's fast
-He's trotting
He somehow looks like Takeshi-san though
Seriously, having these members to gather is already interesting
Is this even going to take 6 hours?
Yeah, this is definitely going to be awful
I really think so this time
Many of us are easily amused
Did this ever took less than 6 hours before?
-Nope
-No, right
-But for Kuro-chan, while people around him are always laughing
-Yes, exactly
I never saw Kuro-chan laughing
Yeah, I never saw Kuro-chan smile
He always looks embarrassed
That's probably beka...because I'm always in a Dokkiri right?
He said "beka"...
No, some strange words just popped up.
Please forgive me <3
That reaction is no good dude
And Fujimon you're doing too much
brilliant Tsukkomi to those Boke
-That is just making everyone laugh
-Yeah it is
But that just makes me respond spontaneously
Please do it at a different timing then
Yeah all these Tsukkomi, the same applies to Nobu
-Kurochan just sticks in our mind
-Yeah, exactly
He's pouring his soul out to his Boke
No way
It's also a surprise for Miyasako-san to accept this
This is surprising
Well, probably because that kind of thing happened right
My wife said don't let anyone make fun of this today
So you guys can do this, I won't say this anymore
No please
And yesterday, I went to watch you guys Chidori at Lumine
Seriously?
Their manzai performance
From the VIP seats?
No, I'm just sitting at the last row
I wanted to watch these guys at Lumine
Oh my god, that's just terrifying
The support for Chidori is amazing
Well, yeah, not bad
But the Manzai didn't go over very well compared to the support
If you call that didn't go over very well, then how well did you go?
Yeah, it did go over very well, it did
But the support is amazing compared to it
-So the support is too amazing
-Yes, yes
This really surprised me
Have you been immersed in formalin?
No I'm not immersed in formalin, for quite a while
I'm not immersed in anything
Have you been at the bottom of the sea all this time?
No I was at Osaka all this time
Have you been eating rock salt?
Humans become like this for eating rock salt?
Are you the dead body of Murloc?
No, I'm not the dead body of Murloc
-Really?
-Yes
Are you halfway through an experiment?
-Halfway done?
-Not at all
Have you been anesthetized?
No I'm not under anesthesia
Please stop this, these jokes are sticking in my mind
Yeah you're right, I'm sorry
-I think Itoda is a strong player
-He definitely is
-He's gone through a lot
-Yeah, exactly
So Itoda definitely has a strong heart
Yeah I'm sure he has a strong heart, he's gone through a lot
Don't think I've ever seen him laughing out loud
Yeah, he's always the one attacking
No, I always laugh too
Please let me do this
This guy have a lot of characters
This is also a monster right
And he joined for consecutive seasons right?
But I have zero defense, absolutely zero defense
You have a character called Pooh-san, the bear Pooh-san right?
Yeah, the teddy-bear-chan
I bursted into laughter during the hardest time of my life
That saved your life
Owarai saved your life
Yeah it saved my life, but if he does that in front of me...
He's crazy, he's absolutely crazy
So he's definitely qualified to sit here
No, no, no
And Kurosawa is on her period today
-Really?
-Yes, be careful
You may hear some sounds like "pilipili",
because I'm wearing the 40cm menstrual pad
-The overnight pad
-40cm is the largest one isn't it?
-What's about the 40cm
-That's the largest one
So it's like this long?
You can even hide your belly button with that
Well, well
There's nothing we can do about it
So I won't go through the rules in detail
Fujimon should know the rules clearly right?
Yes, it's already my third time
This time, we will be keeping the zombie rule
So you can reborn as a zombie, and try to make everyone laugh
For example, when 2 people stay till the end
And then here comes the zombies
and let's say this person laughs
However, the another person is yet to win the contest
Even though this person is the only one left,
however, if there's still like an hour left
You still need to endure the zombies for another hour
That's impossible
And after that, you win
So the person that endures for 6 hours wins the game
That's just absolutely impossible
And if everyone laughs?
Then it's a draw
As if nothing had happened
But if this is the case, it just means that
the contest was a hilarious and impressive one
And it's also possible for both of you
from Chidori to stay till the end
For our case, Matsumoto-san
Can we do whatever we want to do together as a Konbi?
-When everyone is still here
-Yes
-As a Konbi?
-Yes, as a Konbi
Yeah, it's fine, isn't it?
So we can do anything
So everybody, please hand me your money
This hurts too
I actually thought that maybe
we don't need the orange card this time
There's zombies anyway
So you will be red carded after getting one yellow card
This adds up to 3 million now...
No matter how much you earn...hahaha
What's fun about this?
-It's 3 million dude
-Every time you come, you pay
But there's no reason to decline the invitation
-Kukky is the same too
-Yeah it's 3 million now
Your wife is going to kill you
And you're just earning ¥16000 for each show
-You're earning that much?
-Not much at all dude
But I'm really happy and touched by the fact that,
everyone is able to collect and bring in this one million
-When I watched this series..
-Excuse me
What are you doing dude?
Because I wasn't able to hand this over
-It's filthy dude
-No it's not dirty, it was even washed by the rain
And why is it coming apart?
Why didn't you tie it up first?
Because it took 5 times to withdraw
one million at the convenience stores ATM
Yeah, you can only withdraw ¥200,000 at a time
Then borrow a rubber band
Yeah, there must be some rubber bands
What kind of condom?
*Rubber band and condom have the same pronunciation
Rubber band dude
Why did that become a dirty joke
It's not started yet
It's not started yet dude
So this is mine...
I'm paying for this one million although I'm not even joining
This is really deducted from my wages every time
This is really shocking
-What's going on
-I'm serious
He's saying this every time right?
But I know how much savings he has,
so I just feel like "what is this guy even talking about"
That's not the main point, I'm hosting this show,
yet still being deducted for 1 million, that's just awkward
-Well, some of us can still pay for it, but the others...
-No, no, don't say that
-Having Ku-chan to pay three million just hurts like hell to him
-Yeah it is
We all have the same feeling towards one million
That's just the same, all the same
This is amazing
-Can I touch it?
-This aura is amazing
This is amazing right?
Although it's the same amount of money,
but crisp new bills feel completely different
It's quite strict when it comes to our facial expressions right?
To what extent is a grin forgivable?
I just want you to keep in mind that
you should always keep a straight face
Yamamoto has been laughing slightly all the time in the last season
Oouji is close too right?
Yeah Oouji is close too.
Well, you don't need to be completely straight-faced
But Nobu this face is out
-Nobu has a smirking face
-Yeah you're right
So you have to keep a pouting face
Yeah, that's it
That's a good one
This is awful in another sense
I do think that's a good face though
No way, please don't
But can you keep that face for 6 hours?
I'm gonna make myself laugh
You look like young Babyshambles
Well, although it's important to win the contest
But Owarai fans may actually prefer people like Ku-chan,
who makes the contest much more interesting as a zombie
-Yeah that's true
-So just keep that in mind
It's not always about winning
Is it going to start?
-Yeah, it's starting soon
-Oh dear, give me a second
Wait a moment, give me a moment please
Just one more thing, starting from this time
You can call for food delivery here
Using the outside line, and that is inside line
Use the outside line to call for food delivery
Well, if there's anything else, I'll let you guys know
So that's all for now
And you can play with these things over here
Good luck
It starts as Matsumoto-san leaves?
After I leave, and as the room light changes, the contest starts
-Got it
-This is terrifying
-Good luck guys
-Thank you
Good bye
Should I smoke a cigarette
-We can smoke here?
-Yes it's fine
Should we put our bags over there
We need to laugh now more than ever
What is this atmosphere
Where is my bag, oh I see...
It's about time to start
START!
It just started?
Yeah, it started
-It started
-Got it
-It started guys
-Okay
This atmosphere is abosolutely awful
Yeah, that was unexpected
The last drop of my pee came out at the same time,
as the opening bell's "faaa" sound
That was a nice joke
Yeah, that was a nice "faaa", a nice timing
Daigo was already laughing slightly just now
-What?
-You were laughing slightly right?
-You're laughing right?
-You mean this?
You can't do that, you can't laugh even if you're just asking
Yeah, please warn him about this
Wait a second, which face?
-Do it again
-You laughed half way through
Wait, so this is out?
That counts as out too, do you understand?
You're out if you smile
You can't laugh just because
you're asking "does this count as laugh"
-So I'm out?
-Just be careful
Well, so this is just an explanation
You're seriously out if you get a red card
-Why is there water dripping?
-So then I'll be out?
This is the sound of the toilet
What happened to Nobu's pee again?
What's that dripping sound?
I wasn't listening
You're annoying dude, that guy is annoying
There's even a mic in the toilet
-A mic?
-Yes
Leaving that aside, let's talk about Nobu's pee
You are annoying
Don't bother me
Come on, you guys are childhood friends right?
Please don't argue anymore
Why does he keeps talking about my pee?
The last drop?
Let's stop talking about pee
When his last drop of pee fell to the toilet
-The opening bell went "faaa"
-So Nobu said that?
Yes, yes, that's all I said
-Iio-san can you do an opening gag for us?
-Let's go for it?
Yeah, just to cheer us up
-Like saying that "now it starts"
-Yeah, let's do this
Hey guys...
Hey guys, you can't choose not to watch this
What's going on?
Let's watch the opening gag
Iio-san's opening gag
We have 6 hours right?
That's gonna pass very quickly
Well yeah, just one gag
-Where is Miyasako-san?
-He's in the toilet
-We want Miyasako-san to watch this as well
-Yes of course
Can we start now?
The toilet won't flush
It's automatic
There's no buttons
There's no buttons?
Nobu talked about his pee too right?
That's enough dude, stop talking about my pee
It's smelling sweet here, by the way
-Does anybody have diabetes?
-Who have diabetes?
What about the opening gags?
I got switched on for 2 times
-Opening gag?
-Yes
-We don't need that right?
-Sorry Iio-san...
But I got switched on, for 2 times
Sorry, we will ask you to do it again later, maybe in 4 hours
Isn't that too early?
In 4 hours?
-It's too early for us to be out now
-Yeah, this atmosphere is awful
-I can’t hold it much longer, can I go to the toilet?
-Sure
-The sound, the sound
-Are we going to hear the pissing sounds
She should pee and talk or sing at the same time
-Kurosawa we're gonna hear your pee
-Yeah
-Kurosawa we're gonna hear the sound
-Ok
And it won't flush properly
-Shall we listen to Kurosawa's pissing sound together?
-What the heck? No way
Will it be a thin pee or a thick pee?
What the heck is a thick pee?
Come on, these guys are drinking and smoking,
and trying to muddle through
I'm gonna warn them about this
We don't need to do that dude
He's listening to it right?
-Kuro-chan you're really disgusting
-Eh, what do you mean?
-What are you doing?
-You're listening to the toilet's sound right?
-No, no, no
-You're doing this for real?
-Because the fan
-Why?
-Because I'm hot so I'm using the fan
-It's not hot at all
Stop staring at it while using the fan then
Seriously, you have to stop this
I'm serious, that's disgusting
No it's not disgusting
*Kurochan said sorry with "gomenasobase", which is usually used by gentlewomen only
-I'm so sorry*
-That's too much
-Should I kill this guy
-Why did you say sorry like that?
I'm fine with him saying sorry
But can you not add "That's too much" to it?
-Yeah, Fujimon is always...
-Is always adding sauce to it
Yeah, he's always adding good sauces
Yeah, we don't need that flavor
A.1...
A.1. Sauce, the A.1. Sauce
For steaks? What do you mean?
Because they talked about adding good sauces
What's going on?
What is Kurosawa doing?
Are you talking about Kurochan?
Why are you standing sideways?
He's definitely listening to Kurosawa's pee
-No I'm not
-Seriously, stop it
Wait a second, wait a second
Kurosawa and Kurochan becomes double Kuro-chan.
Let's do this
Why did you hit me?
He's angry because you're seriously trying to make fun of it
Stop messing around
I'm keep hearing an "Ahh" noise
Someone is making the "Ahh" noise
She's probably imitating the Sound Princess
But we can still hear the "choro-choro" sound of peeing
-Yeah I heard some "chiri-chiri" sound, like the sound of masturbation
-No one will masturbate in this toilet
Please don't speak in your dialect, that's making me laugh
Yeah, don't speak in your dialect about pee
You should have changed your accent already
By the way, I acted with Sugawara Bunta before in the movie The Great Yokai War
Yeah, I remember that
He was acting as Kamiki Ryūnosuke's grandpa
We met during the press conference,
and I was the secondary main character
I was the secondary main character and I said "nice to meet you"
Then he replied to me from a very close distance
"Who the heck are you nara?"*
*The phrase "Nara" is added to the end of each sentence for Bunta-san's dialect
I was the secondary main character
Yeah he always do that
Who the heck are you nara?
Eh? He always do that?
For many times?
Who the heck are you nara?
This is hilarious
You bumped into the table?
Yeah I bumped into it
I love that conversation
-Excuse me
-Pay attention when your Senpai is talking
Well, never mind
I'm sorry
The conversation went off-topic,
so I didn't want to talk anyway
He's flipping out
You didn't even listen to Miyasako-san
talking about Sugawara-san right?
-"Who are you nara" right?
-It's "Who the heck are you nara"
This is such a precious chance to listen to Miyasako-san's talk about Bunta-san dude
Yeah, Bunta-san is no longer alive
His hairstyle was freaking cool in his old age
It's like Juza of the Clouds*
*Juza of the Clouds is a character from Hokuto no Ken
Yeah it's really cool
Yeah, and with bangs
Segawa Eiko is cool too right?
Yeah, her hair on the sides are so long
I bet she looks like Eiffel tower with her hair standing up
You're annoying
-If her hair stand up in one direction?
-Yes, yes
You guys are annoying
Are you guys talking about Michizane?
*Michizane is the god of learning, who has the same surname "Sugawara" as Bunta-san
Why are you mentioning Michizane?
It's Bunta-san dude
-He's close, he's close
-It's not Sugawara Michizane
Fujimon is close
Should we stop this?
Yeah, let's stop that
Let's stop making fun of it
Maybe watch some opening gags instead?
No thanks
You don't want that?
But I got switched on already
It doesn't feel good if you don't do it?
I wanted you to do it back then, so the timing is wrong now
Are you the leader?
Well, you can do it if you want to
Yeah, I'm fine with it
I see, then I'm not doing it
-Hey...
-One...
-Why are you breathing like Darth Vader?
-Well, no...
-You're laughing right
-I need some air...
Yeah he laughed for sure
That was a laugh, without doubt
-Why are you breathing like Darth Vader?
-No I didn't
Who is Darth Vader anyway
Who the heck is that nara?
Who the heck is Darth Vader nara?
You're not Sugawara Bunta dude
Having a seat and at the same time Sharon Stone
Did Nobu laugh just now?
You're annoying
Is that safe?
We asked you not to do gags right?
-I can't do it?
-We said no
-We asked you to do it later right?
-And you said you won't do it too
I'll give a "go signal", so please don't do it before that
Yeah, timing is important too
Who is Michizane again?
-Sugawara? The god of learning
(Who's laughing, who's laughing?)
-That's enough
(Nobu right?)
Do you mean Yoshizane?
-Who the heck is Yoshizane?
(Did he laugh?)
Sugawara Yoshizane?
He must be a normal citizen
That's not a usual Boke from you
Well, but...
But that's interesting too though
Yeah Michizane...
Why do I need be scold, just for saying Michizane
We're not angry, but why did you say that
Well, I'm not angry
But I thought that's not a usual Boke from you
And that's interesting to see as well
Can you do Sharon Stone one more time?
You want another one?
Why are you drinking milk?
There's no more water
Stop lying
-There's still a lot dude
-No, there's really no more
There's a lot at the bottom of the fridge
Oh, so it's at the bottom
Yeah, at the lowest shelf
Having a seat and at the same time Sharon Stone
No I'm not worrying about calcium
Your puberty has ended right?
My pu-chu-chu?
You puberty
-What was that chu-chu?
-Nobu is close
Nobu is close all the time
Nobu and Fujimon
Ku-chan is also being lax today
There's cold water here, and warm water over there
Your beard will be stained with milk
No it won't be stained
Try to drink it then
Chug it
That's fast
It's stained dude
You are the one who asked him to do it
That's definitely a laugh
Wait a second, wait a second
-Wait a second...
-It's Daigo
So weak
That deserves a red card right
No, no, wait a second
No, no, wait, listen to me
Because his beard indeed wasn't stained
No, that's not the main point
You just laughed out loud like "poo-hoo"
I said it will be stained and...
Wait a moment, wait a moment...
You guys are all being lax
Nobu as well
-Fujimon too
-Eh, me too?
-And even Ku-chan is being lax this time
-Yes, I'm sorry
Everyone is somehow fluffy
-This atmosphere is just awful
-Yeah, it really is
Yeah, it was awful, I understand that
It's absolutely awful
The Sharon Stone gag almost got me
So happy to hear that from Matsumoto-san
That really encourages me, thank you so mcuh
But anyway...
Daigo right?
Daigo, yellow card
Yes, I know that
Let's watch it again
-That was an easy one
-Yeah, it really is an easy one
Wait, wait, let me explain this
"It will be stained", "No it won't", and then it really didn't
That's none of our business
Your beard will be stained with milk
No it won't be stained
Try to drink it then
Chug it
That's fast
It's stained dude
You are the one who asked him to do it
Nobu laughed as well right?
Wait, please let me explain this, Matsumoto-san
That's because I saw Daigo laughed,
and I was just making a victory pose for that
Well, I agree with that
-That's just a victory pose
-Okay, I see
Yeah, so I'll say that's safe for this time
So anyway, Daigo is yellow carded
If Daigo didn't laugh out loud,
probably three of us are out already
Yeah, that's true
What happened?
She's crying
Eh, what happened?
How come?
What's happening?
Can't understand your emotions
What happened, seriously?
I thought we had a good time
How could this even happen?
What happened, seriously?
It's truly a male‐dominated society
A male‐dominated society...
No way, that's not true
Sorry for being emotional
No worries, don't worry about that
I thought it's because we talked about dirty jokes
I feel like an only child in these conversations, with no siblings
Unable to join the conversation
It's fine even if you're not joining us