THIS PROGRAM IS THE RECORD
OF A "BATTLE" AMONGST COMEDIANS.
IN ORDER TO PRESERVE QUALITY,
IT IS MOSTLY UNEDITED.
AS SUCH, VIEWERS MAY ENCOUNTER
EXPLICIT CONTENT.
Comedians usually take turns at making an
audience laugh within a given time frame.
But on this show,
10 comedians are confined to one room.
They have to make the other nine laugh.
But they have to do it
without laughing themselves.
This might actually be the simplest way
and the best way to decide who truly is
the funniest person.
I must admit,
this is sort of an experiment.
I brought 18 robot model kits.
Another thing is,
I do the TV show You Mustn't Laugh
at the end of each year.
It's become a highly entertaining show
for all ages.
That's great, but it can be limiting.
This sucks!
I wanted to get rid of all the shackles.
There are moments when you laugh,
even though nothing special has happened.
I've been wanting to create something
based on that for several years.
There is a six-hour time limit.
-One man wins.
-We won't need six hours.
No need for six hours, right?
THE ENTRY FEE IS ONE MILLION YEN
THEY MUST MAKE THE OTHERS LAUGH
FOR A 10 MILLION YEN REWARD
Is this for real?
You can do whatever you want.
The funniest person wins.
You have six hours.
-It may seem long, or the time may fly.
-I'm scared.
For the next six hours,
good luck to you all!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Kyojin, from All Hanshin.
-No, you're not.
-I'm Kyojin.
Jimmy?
-You're Kyojin?
-Yes.
Pretty much everyone laughed.
I didn't laugh.
They're mother and child.
Are you hungry?
Yellow card.
-Yellow?
-You only get a yellow card for that?
I'm not sitting next to Daisuke.
He makes me laugh.
-You make me laugh, too.
-That's not fair.
-We're on.
-We are.
They're mother and child.
Are you hungry?
-That's for the parent.
-This one is the mommy.
-I thought so.
-Why is your pinky bent like that?
Mommy has the flu,
so she can't feed the baby.
He's crazy.
He's scary.
-Mommy has the flu--
-What?
Can you please be quiet?
It's tough not to laugh at this.
-He's crazy from the get-go.
-One, two...
Stop it.
Ouch!
What the hell are you doing?
I just wanted you to be quiet.
What did you use?
That hurt!
Did you throw fire at me?
That was really hot.
-He hit him with fire.
-Apparently so.
-It felt like fire.
-Show us your back.
Take a look.
Am I okay?
What's with those muscles?
Your back is gross.
Gross.
-He has old man skin.
-He's full of holes.
-The fire must have done it.
-The fire!
-Fire holes.
-Sorry.
Don't throw fire at me.
It wasn't fire. Sorry.
Anyway...
Look at my cans.
It's too early for that.
-Can I do my can thing first?
-We still have five hours to go.
Please wait.
-One can...
-Five hours?
Two cans.
Three cans.
Four cans.
Five cans.
Six cans.
-Watch him.
-Yeah, watch!
Damn, now I have to recount.
One can, two cans, three cans, four cans,
five cans, six cans, seven cans,
eight cans,
nine cans.
-There is nothing in this bag.
-Okay.
-Nine cans.
The ninth edition of The Shincho Weekly
has been canned.
I don't feel any pressure.
I don't have to worry whether my jokes
work or not, because this time,
nobody's supposed to laugh.
If they laugh, they lose.
With a rule like that,
I can do whatever I want,
with no pressure at all.
I'm going to perform a bunch of new gags.
What was that just now?
They didn't print it. Nine was canned.
Number "nine" went in the "can"?
It was a pun.
It wasn't funny at all.
I thought it was pretty good.
Pretty good? Thanks.
I still don't get it.
-Was it from the radio?
-What?
Was it played on the radio?
-Yeah. Um...
-On the radio? For The Shincho Weekly?
I threw in an impression
of The Shincho Weekly ad.
You can do impressions
of The Shincho Weekly?
Yeah.
The ninth edition of The Shincho Weekly
has been canned.
It should be higher.
The ad was spoken by a kid.
Try doing it at a higher pitch.
-The Shincho Weekly is...
-Pinch your nose.
The Shincho Squeaky is...
You said "Squeaky." It's "Weekly."
-He's good at it.
-You do it.
-The Shincho Weekly...
-It has to be higher.
Pinch your nose!
The Shincho Weekly...
Your voice is too low!
-It's way too low!
-I've never even heard the original.
-Way too low!
-Why are you mad?
-I'm gonna kill him.
-Why?
Snuff him. Seriously.
But I'm scared. I think he knows capoeira.
Don't fight.
-Stop it.
-Know any moves?
Have some candy.
-Do I know any moves?
-Have some candy.
Shall I do one?
Can I do it to you?
Why? No. You're scaring me.
-Don't be violent.
-He's scary.
-I'm scared. Isn't he scary?
-I think you should do it.
-You said--
-Kubota, you do it.
-You said you'd kill me.
You said you were gonna kill me.
I am seriously scared of him.
-That's what you said.
-You're turning this place into a slum.
-Then let me do my move.
-You are scary.
It's scary now.
-Just let me do one move.
-Let him.
-Let him do it.
-It won't hurt much--
-Of course it will!
-No, it won't hurt.
-Let's do it.
-Take it like a man.
No way.
-All you have to do is stand still.
-I said I'm scared.
Just let him do it once.
Let him do it to you!
-Well, that's it. Go for it.
-Why me?
Why me?
You take it!
-I guess you're the one.
-Let's decide by rock-paper-scissors.
-You and Jimmy do rock-paper-scissors.
-Why me?
-With Jimmy?
-It has nothing to do with me.
Jimmy, let's do rock-paper-scissors.
-That's not right.
-I know what you mean.
Do the "look that way" version.
-This isn't right.
-"Look that way."
This isn't right.
You don't need these.
They calm me down.
Who cares?
-No, no, no.
-Uh-oh.
-He's totally laughing.
-He self-destructed.
He's laughing hard.
-He can't stop laughing.
-Okay!
Saito was laughing, too.
Jimmy's out, but Saito is, too.
-You definitely laughed.
-Absolutely.
I want you guys to hide Daisuke's face.
His face makes me laugh.
-That's my line.
-Who's out?
Wait. It should be a yellow card.
Daisuke's face is...
This time,
it's not only one person.
The first person is...
Jimmy.
-No doubt about it.
-I admit it.
-He knows.
And also,
-Saito.
-No way. I wasn't laughing.
-I didn't laugh.
-Saito laughed, too.
-I didn't.
-Saito, too?
I didn't laugh.
-And...
-What? There's more?
Fujimoto!
-These three laughed.
-They definitely laughed.
Let's check to make sure.
But I didn't laugh.
Firstly, we have Jimmy.
-I laughed.
-You know it, right?
Let's watch it.
But I didn't laugh.
But you were kind of smiling.
-Look.
-That's a smile.
-He's laughing.
-He is.
That's not laughing.
He's laughing!
He's laughing, right? Right there.
-And Saito.
-I really wasn't laughing.
Let's watch. Saito was laughing, too.
But it may have been after the buzzer.
No, no. Don't get me wrong!
I thought I could laugh,
because Jimmy had already laughed.
That's not the point.
-I only laughed because Jimmy laughed.
-That doesn't make it okay for you.
But...
Those three get a yellow card.
-But that's not fair.
-You're right.
Then how about Kukky?
I might have missed him.
It was before Jimmy pointed his finger.
If Mr. Matsumoto didn't see it,
then that's that.
Well, I guess so. I am the judge.
I want you to stop attacking me.
-We're not attacking you.
-You're attacking everyone.
Everyone.
He hadn't even finished the set up
to his gag.
-You guys attacked me first.
-No, we didn't.
And Daisuke, I think you're using
the water bottle to hide your laugh.
-No, I'm not.
-Who drinks that much water?
Watch him carefully!
I'm thirsty.
-Seriously.
-Okay. Then drink it all at once.
I can't. It's carbonated.
I won't be able to hold it in.
-He's a cheater.
-That's not good.
-I heard him chuckling.
-I didn't chuckle.
-You were.
-You kept cracking up.
What about him?
He's drinking wine all the time.
His mouth is always on the wine bottle.
-He's setting up a joke with that, right?
-No, I'm not.
You're not?
-Then stop it.
-He really does like wine.
Please watch everyone carefully,
Mr. Matsumoto!
I am, but it's hard to watch
all 10 of you.
But I promise I will keep an eye on Kukky.
-You should've got a yellow card, too.
-Sorry.
-Why don't you pick up where you left off?
-Fujimoto, can I?
-Oh, that's right.
-You should do it.
Fujimoto, don't run from it.
Seriously, no.
-I said no!
-What exactly will you do?
-A move...
-Are you crazy?
We don't need any moves!
He is so annoying.
-Let him do it once.
-That's a good idea.
-Will it hurt?
-It won't.
-Really?
-He said it won't hurt.
Then why do it?
I don't want to pretend it hurts.
How about someone else?
You talk too much. You do it.
I talk...
-I wasn't talking.
-He wasn't.
He hasn't talked
since he got the yellow card.
-You're right.
-That's dirty.
-He's a coward.
-Do it, Ohchi.
-Anthony, try it on Ohchi.
-May I?
-No.
-Do it.
-Will it hurt?
-No, it won't.
Can I have you face the front?
-Put your right hand here.
-On his hip?
Spread your legs and look down.
I mean, stand up straight,
but point your head down.
Look forward...
-Jimmy, stop that.
-Seriously.
Watch them.
Hello.
-He's laughing.
-Anthony, don't let up.
-Go all the way.
-He's laughing.
-Do more, Anthony.
-He's out.
-Attack more.
-I didn't laugh.
I did this. I just clenched my muscles.
-Can I do it to Fujimoto now?
-Fujimoto.
Can I do the same to you?
He is your junior colleague after all.
You do it.
-Poor guy.
-Let's not resort to violence.
-What was that for?
-Stop it.
-He shouldn't tell his senior what to do.
-But he doesn't have any hair.
-That hurt.
-I'll give you my hair.
-Jimmy's giving it to you.
-Thanks.
-This is yours.
-Lucky you.
You dropped your candy.
Oh, my candy, sorry.
-Thank you.
-Don't mention it.
His hair is so wet.
Put it on.
-What's up, Saito?
-Saito?
-Let's see Saito first.
-Okay.
Jimmy, look at Saito.
-Wait.
-Jimmy?
Wait a minute.
Oh, no. He's gone.
That's two players down.
Saito laughed.
But that means Saito is...
-Two of them laughed.
-Yeah, two down.
-He tried to hide in the sink.
-He has a yellow card.
Why did you wet your hair?
He tried to hide his laughter.
-That's not fair.
-I was just washing my eyes.
-Were you hiding your laugh?
-No, my eyes hurt.
Why did Saito laugh? What was it?
-He did it to himself.
-But I've only just started.
-He's gone.
-I'm out.
-That was pretty clear.
-They already have yellow cards.
Let's take a look at Saito.
-He laughed.
-But I was...
He laughed, but why?
Because of Jimmy...
I don't get why Saito laughed there.
Jimmy was making a funny face.
Let's take a look at Saito.
-Why did he wet his hair?
-I don't know.
Because Jimmy made a funny face!
Oh, no. He's gone.
No, I was crying.
I was crying!
And what about Ohchi?
I was just--
He definitely cheated.
-I was just clenching my muscles.
-Never do that again.
Hello.
He's laughing.
-Anthony, don't let up. Go all the way.
-He's laughing.
I didn't laugh.
Everyone could tell
that I held it back, right?
-I clenched it in.
-Well, but...
-In Saito's case...
-Wait a minute.
I could tell he was being aggressive.
-He attempted to initiate something.
-I did.
-Because of that,
-Yes?
you get
an orange card.
Is it better than yellow?
He got a yellow card. Now he has this.
The next one means...
Yellow, orange, red is the way it goes?
-This is truly your last chance.
-Last chance.
-He's got bubbles now.
-What are you doing, Jimmy?
Just because you're not in the hot seat.
It's okay to laugh now?
-What are you doing?
-I'm shampooing my hair.
-He's crazy.
-You are really scaring me!
-Seriously, why are you doing that?
-Because my head started feeling hot.
-He was hiding his laughter.
-Really?
No, I didn't.
My head is so hot.
-Jimmy was totally laughing.
-Good luck, guys.
I only washed my head because
my eyes hurt.
I'll wash it off, then.
-No more shampoo, right?
-Do it in the bathroom.
I'll wash it off now.
-Not now.
-Not now, please.
-Don't wash your head in the kitchen.
-We cook food here.
Okay.
He's so dangerous.
Start.
Scary.
Jimmy, go wash your hair.
Daisuke's always drinking something.
Saito, what were you going to do?
Jimmy really is crazy.
Don't make me explain my jokes.
That wig looks good on everyone.
It's probably a good wig.
Do you look good in it?
That's way too high up.
-Yeah.
-Really?
You're scary.
What a lovely bath!
Lovely bath salts.
That iodine felt great.
What did he say?
-You're sopping wet. Dry yourself.
-I will.
Just a moment.
He can't untie the knot.
-I'm so refreshed.
-Your bald spot is showing again.
-That won't absorb any water.
-Not that material.
Not that thing.
-Use the sheep towel.
-This sheep's name is "Sheep."
-"Sheep."
-You're coming on strong.
Too strong.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I got shampoo in my eyes.
Why do you keep walking around?
Where am I going bald?
-Everywhere.
-This bit is nasty.
It's nasty.
Okay, don't look at my bald spot.
And what's this?
-You have a completely bald patch.
-Actually, it's not a bald patch.
It's where I was electrocuted on my head.
-Electrocuted?
-Electrocuted.
Does electrocution cause baldness?
Does it just fall out?
You'll never understand...
I want a look.
Not the pain of electrocution.
Where is it?
It was electricity.
How scary!
I got electrocuted.
This might fix it.
Maybe this will fix your bald spot.
If he hits the exact same spot.
-Shall we try?
-I guess so.
-Everyone go over there.
-As long as it cures me.
-Over there.
-If it will help, sure.
Are you sure?
Consider it a medical treatment.
Medical treatment.
How nice of him to try and fix
your bald spot.
That was hot!
It was hot?
Did he get burned?
That's hot!
-Is my bald spot gone?
-Are you okay?
It's hot.
That can't be right.
It wasn't me. I just said it was hot.
-I didn't laugh.
-I'm sorry.
-Me, neither.
-Neither did I.
-I didn't laugh.
-What about that rubber band?
-I was just making a funny face.
-To make you guys laugh.
-You twisted your smile.
-That's a yellow card.
-He cheated.
All I did was this.
I thought it would be funny.
I didn't laugh.
Let him decide.
-Daisuke laughed.
-He did.
No, no, no.
-He used that rubber band.
-I didn't.
He used it to stop laughing.
The rubber band said,
"I'm holding back a smile."
No. I made a funny face. Like this.
To be funny.
Yellow card.
-You can't do that.
-That was wrong.
Let's watch it anyway.
That was hot!
He's smiling!
Don't ever try that again!
He was definitely laughing.
Never do that again!
I was trying to be funny.
It was a funny face.
-That should get a red card.
-Red card!
You were totally laughing.
-Never again, okay?
-That wasn't fair, Daisuke.
-It hasn't even been an hour.
-Was it really that funny?
And Ohchi's had a faint smile
the entire time.
Really?
You've had a faint smile the whole time.
-Get outta here.
-Wait.
Are faint smiles out, too?
-Did I have a faint smile?
-The whole time.
-I think we should skip Jimmy for a while.
-Good idea.
-There's sashimi in here.
-What?
-We have sashimi.
-We do.
-Want me to make sushi?
-No, thanks.
-Your hands are dirty.
-Right?
-Why would they be dirty?
Stop it.
I just washed my hair.
-Why would they be dirty?
-That's what we mean.
Your head is dirty.
My head's not dirty.
It's been electrocuted.
The electricity disinfected it.
Please, I want you to be quiet.
Jimmy, stop drinking the water.
-Okay.
-You were hiding a smile with the bottle.
Don't drink that, either.
Stop that.
Of course they want him to stop.
You can't tell him too much.
But he really never stops.
Jimmy? That's a bit fishy...
I'm not doing anything.
Don't be short-tempered either.
Can I ask everyone to write
a message here?
It's for Master Daisuke.
Something short.
DEAR DAISUKE
"UFOS DO EXIST"
Saito was close.
-But he's not retiring.
-Apparently he is.
-Why are we writing this?
-Because he's retiring.
-Who is?
-You're lying.
-This dude.
-Master Daisuke?
Don't call the Master a "dude."
Wait, wait, wait.
-I'm not writing anything.
-Why not?
Because it's wrong.
We shouldn't write him a farewell message.
-But Master Daisuke is--
-He's not.
He's retiring.
Why?
You know Junichi Yaoi, the occult expert?
He's doing a special broadcast with him.
He's going to retire after that.
-About UFOs?
-Exactly.
-On a local TV channel?
-What?
Why would Master Daisuke be on local TV?
-It would be with a major network.
-Does that mean...
Will Hanako go solo?
Let's sit down.
-Will Hanako go solo?
-Sit down.
-Wasn't she arrested?
-We need to discuss this.
-She was, but the charges were false.
-They were dropped?
Pet theft, wasn't it?
What's he doing?
You catch, okay?
It's gonna fly.
Hanako is that serial killer
who dresses as a clown, isn't she?
That's John Wayne Gacy!
It's gonna fly. Catch it.
It's gonna fly--
Excuse me.
You're distracting us.
-Please.
-What?
What is it?
You want my autograph?
No, we're all writing a short message.
-Could you go first?
-One message each?
I already wrote "UFOs do exist,"
so anything other than that will do.
-We're writing a farewell message?
-We are.
Let me write something.
You made my shirt all dirty.
-I got your fuzz balls.
-You gave them to me.
You're just like Master Daisuke.
Master Daisuke isn't dirty.
Look at my sleeve.
It's like I've got ants.
-From the fuzz balls.
-Like Master Daisuke.
Master Daisuke's sleeves aren't dirty.
-Master Daisuke is...
-He has dirty sleeves.
-His sleeves aren't dirty.
-He had a ton of lint.
-His sleeves are clean.
-The lint's on his skin.
He's dirty around here,
but his sleeves are clean.
"Dai-bou."
That's his nickname.
Does the "bou" in "Dai-bou" mean "priest"?
-It means "gang."
-What a scary name!
-Jimmy, did you write your message?
-Yes.
"Everyone's on the boat."
What does that mean?
-Did you get permission to do this?
-You'll get in trouble.
No, I didn't.
I'm sure he'll get upset.
I've heard rumors he's not happy
with you, too.
Well, it doesn't matter. He's old.
He doesn't scare me.
I'm going to tell you off on his behalf.
No, don't do that. It's not your business.
It's not your business!
Master Daisuke is powerless anyway!
-He's just got a big face.
-You should tell him off.
-He's like a loose stool.
-Seniors shouldn't fight.
Cut it out.
Let's stop this.
Shall I do one of my moves on him?
Come back.
He never gives up.
I have some moves...
When we reach a deadlock,
I don't want to get caught up in it.
As time passes, everyone will get
even more used to the situation.
So, I want to take advantage of that,
and be aggressive from the start.
I'll slip in a few light jokes,
and go on the offensive from the start.
You can't blame him.
You're scary.
I saw this on the Amazon commercial.
I had to get it.
-It's what the dog wears.
-Oh, that ad with the baby.
Because the baby cries at the dog.
So that's where it went.
Does this belong to somebody else?
It's mine!
I ordered one of these.
-But they ran out of stock.
-He got it instead?
-What were you thinking?
-Seriously?
Try it on.
You really want to try that on?
-Give me a hand.
-What's that?
I was given a big lucky flag.
I'll put this wig on.
-That's wonderful!
-Look at that!
-Take a look at that.
-Wow!
MASTER DAISUKE
GET WELL SOON
-You were given this?
-Yes, I was.
When he got sick,
his fans made it for him.
-He gave it to me.
-Awesome.
Way to go.
-Want to use it as a tablecloth?
-Sure.
-Move everything off the table, please.
-But I'm...
-Just a moment.
-Okay.
Daisuke, sit down.
-Where are you going?
-What's wrong?
Look. We have Daisuke and Daisuke.
It's not Daisuke and Daisuke.
There's pubic hair around his mouth.
Who put pubic hair on him?
This is not funny. Who did it?
This is beyond a joke.
Who put white pubic hair around
the veteran's mouth?
You can't do that. Anywhere but his mouth.
Where did Kubota go?
He's putting on the wig.
Can I come out?
I'm wearing that Amazon thing.
Is this on right?
Is this correct?
I look like Seiko Matsuda!
I look just like Seiko Matsuda!
Jimmy, right?
What were you trying to do?
-It wasn't that funny.
-What happened?
-What did you do with your eyes?
-You were just squeezing them?
I'm done for.
That wasn't fair.
His eyes were so bloodshot.
-Jimmy.
-You got me.
Let's watch it.
You're definitely out, Jimmy.
You suddenly exploded.
Fujimoto was close, too.
That one is tough to make a verdict on.
You're in danger now.
-This is your final chance.
-Okay.
That's so lenient.
It could've been a red card.
Exactly. I thought about it.
-Sorry.
-This is your last chance.
I know. But they keep on attacking me.
-No, we're not.
-We're all under attack.
I am the type of person
who laughs really easily.
When it hits the right spot,
I can't help but laugh.
When I used to watch
The Drifters' show, Hachijidayo,
I'd laugh a lot.
Start!
Can we play the game
"Who's Really Doing It?"
Let's play "Who's Really Doing It?"
-Was that the name?
-Yes.
No, it's not.
It's "Who's Really Doing It?"
-Really?
-Yeah.
What kind of game is it?
I've never heard of it.
Huh?
Anthony...
One of these sweet buns contains
spicy wasabi.
-It's sitting on the top.
-We can see it.
Guess which one has the wasabi inside.
We can see it!
You're gonna eat it?
You're eating it yourself?
He's cool.
I got the wasabi.
Of course.
You're the only one to choose from.
And we could see it.
There's still one left.
Give us another try. Eat up.
Is he okay?
-You spat it out.
-No, I didn't.
-That's a violation.
-It's still here.
There's one more.
That one looks safe.
It should be okay...
-I'm done for.
-You totally laughed.
That was definitely a laugh.
You laughed so normally.
-He laughed just like normal.
-He totally laughed.
Wait.
-You laughed like normal.
-Completely.
You forgot we're not just chatting.
He's here.
-He put his hand up.
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I don't need to check the video.
-Yellow!
-Just yellow?
Did you know Anthony
had his eyelids flipped?
-I had no idea.
-I noticed, but...
-He was giving a mean stare.
-Like Clint.
Like Clint Eastwood?
Why laugh?
But I can laugh now, right?
That didn't deserve a laugh.
-It wasn't that funny.
-Be quiet!
I can't keep all 10 of you alive
for much longer.
-Somebody will be eliminated soon.
-It's been an hour.
You're Clint Eyelid-wood.
I am.
Start!
Wasabi is dangerous.
-Can you put this flag away?
-What do you think? Should we--
Stop it! It's mine.
Let's pack it up.
Fujimoto, you've been close to laughing.
But he keeps drinking!
You're close again.
Damn it!
Why?
Why can't I drink?
-Damn you!
-Don't blame him, Jimmy.
Damn you!
We all agreed not to hide behind bottles.
Damn!
Jimmy Onishi!
You're out!
Damn you!
What you did was wrong!
-That's wrong.
-Don't blame me.
We all agreed not to hide behind bottles.
I wasn't hiding!
I was only drinking because
the wasabi was still hot.
You are not nice!
You're out.
Leave your million yen and go home!
You make me mad.
What did I do?
You kept tricking me into laughing.
I only tried to stop you from drinking.
That's what we all agreed.
-Where's he going?
-To get his things.
Did he have any props left?
He brought quite a lot.
He had a lot.
I didn't get to use any of these.
-You should have used them.
-He's right.
This will change things.
It makes life easier.
It will be a lot easier now.
This is a big gain for us.
My million yen!
It's not easy to earn one million yen.
Sitting next to Daisuke was
my first big mistake.
Daisuke creates a subtle comic vibe.
You can feel it when you sit next to him.
That vibe was just too much for me.
It got to me.
Another thing was,
I went on the offensive too early.
That was another reason I lost.
I shouldn't have put on
this costume so early.
I had to go on the offensive.
If I just sat still,
they would have ganged up to attack me.
They were so sly.
Only one hour has passed?
-Only one hour?
-Only one-sixth.
Start.
Everyone cracked quite quickly.
Now that Jimmy is gone,
we'll see how things change.
-Pack this up.
-We've seen enough of it.
This is so...
It's like he really died.
He's dead on top of the big lucky flag.
Don't make your final farewells.
Say goodbye.
Ohchi.
Ohchi!
-Ohchi.
-Ohchi, Ohchi!
-He's not really dead.
-Touch him.
Just say goodbye.
-Touch him. He's super cold.
-I don't think we should touch him.
He's unbelievably cold. Touch him.
-Say goodbye.
-Then we can have sushi.
That's not a good idea.
Say goodbye, then have some sushi.
-This is not good.
-Ohchi, say goodbye!
This is your last chance!
Take a good look.
-Raise the cloth.
-Do it yourself.
Look. He's at peace now.
Look at this part, too.
There may be a message. Take a look.
Something may be written there.
Nothing there.
Good. Cover him up.
Next person.
I can't believe he's gone.
He really loved e-cigarettes.
-He loved baseball, too.
-He did.
Why is he smoking a bat?
That's sacrilege.
-You can't do that.
-Seriously.
That's going too far.
He'll become the undead.
-Stop it.
-You can't do that.
Master Daisuke hates the U.S.
-That's not funny.
-Make sure you never do that in America.
Play us a song.
Do, re, mi, fa...
Ohchi, look!
Ohchi, look.
Ohchi, look at him.
-Ohchi?
-Ohchi.
When you think about all the memories
we have...
-Take a look.
-Have some sushi, too.
-He played the melodeon.
-He smoked e-cigarettes.
-He loved smoking e-cigarettes.
-He loved smoking his melodeon, too.
Master Daisuke!
Hanako misses you.
Oh, my goodness.
Come here, shithead.
-War broke out.
-Don't hurt me.
Stop putting the U.S. on him!
This is so sad.
-Kukky!
-Yes?
-Where are you?
-I'm putting on a jacket. I'm cold.
-You ran away from us.
-Is it cold?
-Aren't you guys cold?
-No.
It's not that cold.
Is wearing a jacket too much?
I think you should take it off.
Really?
I'm so cold.
That was a separate piece?
-What's "separate" mean?
-Detachable.
-It's unusual.
-Yeah, that hood.
-Hood? Is "Separate" a car?
-Ohchi.
Look at him.
-Want to wear this?
-Ohchi, look at him.
Ohchi!
Look!
-Look at him properly.
-I did. I looked at him.
What should I do about Ohchi?
-I hate being followed.
-I just want to smoke.
His testicles are twisted.
See, they're all twisted.
Ohchi.
Ohchi's getting close.
Please stop following me.
I'm going to take a shower.
It's hot.
-How about we all sit down?
-Okay.
-Let's sit for now.
-Let's settle down.
-Calm down for once.
This is so tough.
Oh, it's a male and a female.
We're missing someone.
-Where's Anthony?
-Still next to you.
Ohchi and Kawahara aren't here.
Sit down, everyone.
What are you doing?
Oh, no!
Oh, crap!
Does the school uniform make this
less funny?
I don't think that's the issue.
Whatever you wore, it wouldn't be...
Just sit down.
Sit down.
Maybe it's less funny.
I passed a pro wrestling test
for the lucha libre in Mexico.
And today,
I brought a bunch of masks.
Would you mind looking at them?
I have some cool ones,
and some other ones.
-A whole variety.
-They all wear masks in Mexico.
-For pro wrestling?
-Lucha libre.
I want to show how great Mexico is.
That sounds nice.
I'll lighten things up a bit.
Lucha libre.
Lucha libre?
-Lucha libre.
-Lucha.
-Lucha?
I have several hundred masks in my drawer.
Today I brought a dozen of the best.
Just wait and see.
Lucha is going to explode.
This is an old-style mask.
-Mscaras.
-I know that.
I've seen that one.
And?
They'll get funnier.
Should you be saying that?
-You're raising our expectations.
-It's okay.
-The next one's funnier.
-He sounds confident.
He looks fit.
-He's got a nice body.
-He must work out.
-He goes to the gym.
-Is that right?
He did practice some sport, right?
He actually does do pro wrestling.
-Are you ready for the next one?
-Sure.
He has hair now.
It's kind of cute.
That one looks like a clown.
-It's like a clown, right?
-With the nose and all.
When he jumps, the hair flaps up, right?
It makes him look dynamic.
Does your hair flap when you jump?
Maybe his role is to provide comic relief,
rather than big moves.
-Watch out!
-Ouch!
-Are you okay?
-You killed the chair.
-It's dead.
Ow.
This is a serious accident.
Are they okay? Nobody's really injured?
Are you okay?
-That was dangerous.
-It's totally broken.
I've got more masks.
We don't want any injuries.
That was scary.
Is Fujimoto all right?
We have an expert.
Looking good.
-He's in the zone.
-Way to go.
You're pathetic.
Don't hurt yourself.
Ohchi?
-What's wrong?
-Ohchi?
-What's going on?
-Nothing...
Picture in your mind what just happened.
-Are you ready?
-We lost a chair.
-Ready?
-Yes.
He fell down sideways.
One with hair again?
Did you add that yourself?
Did it really come like that?
He looks weak.
He does look weak.
You didn't add hair to look like
the wrestler who uses that mask?
This is how it came.
That was an amazing move you did before.
-Can you believe that?
-It was dangerous. There was a corner.
-I didn't know people fell sideways.
-Apparently they do.
Are you ready?
Okay.
You totally laughed.
It's too late now.
That's totally out.
There aren't many people who laugh
as easily as me.
That's how much I laugh.
I think I'm the only person who laughed
all the way through Forrest Gump.
-He's here.
-You laughed so hard.
I haven't even got a yellow card.
That's worth more than a yellow.
You belted out that laugh.
-It's a yellow card.
-Kukky...
Yellow card.
-Thank you so much.
-You're yellow for now.
-We get one chance each?
-I think so.
And Ohchi.
You're just slipping me an orange card?
I don't get any buzzers?
I'm just casually handed an orange card?
You've been smiling the whole time.
I've been patient with you.
-But I've been...
-You've been terrible.
Everyone keeps saying, "Ohchi, Ohchi!"
Sometimes, I laugh because
I know what they're capable of.
Whenever something happens,
I'll just try to be emotionally dead.
If I think about the person doing it,
I'll laugh in no time.
I can't do this.
When you focus on your offense,
your defense weakens.
-Exactly. I agree.
-Right?
-You become fragile.
-I'm in danger here.
I think I have to go on the offensive.
What color card did I get last time?
Was it orange?
Start!
-Yellow.
-Oh, it was yellow.
Shall we check who has what card?
-I'm orange.
-You're orange.
-I'm yellow.
-I'm yellow, too.
You don't have any.
-Not yet.
-Okay.
Anthony, Kubota,
and Kawahara are fine so far.
Scary.
What was that jacket all about?
-It gets cold and hot.
-No, it doesn't.
The AC has a problem.
You're the one with a problem.
Don't touch it. It's wet.
-Sweat?
-No, it's--
The problem is you.
There's tofu in here.
Wait.
What?
-Why did he laugh?
-What happened?
Damn!
-He was easy.
-What happened?
Damn it!
He totally laughed.
What's so funny about tofu?
It wasn't that funny.
It was a weak jab at best.
It was a super small jab of a joke.
Why did he laugh?
-No idea. He just said, "tofu."
-That's not all--
Show us what happened.
-What was it?
-It wasn't that funny.
-I didn't even realize.
-Reenact it for us.
-It's soaked in sweat.
-Yeah, it's wet.
That's not sweat. There's tofu in here.
He laughed again!
What?
Why?
That's what finished you off?
He let you go so many times.
I still don't get it.
-Was it some old inside joke?
-He uses "tofu" all time.
-He uses tofu as a joke for everything.
-Now I get it.
-It had built up.
-Over the years.
All for today.
And so when he said it today,
I was ready to laugh.
Good job.
Damn it!
-Good job!
-Time to go.
At the 90-minute mark, you're gone.
It's only been an hour and a half?
Damn it!
Why is he acting disappointed?
What is there to regret
after laughing so much?
-How can he be disappointed?
-He laughed the whole time.
He did.
It should be easy
to accept defeat after that.
I was so sure I'd win today.
-No chance.
-You always laugh.
You spent more time smiling than not.
You were cheerful the entire time.
What was in your bag?
Let us see.
What was the best one?
This bathrobe and...
sunglasses.
I wanted to wear these naked.
-I might have laughed.
-Then what?
What?
What were you going to do?
You were going to
say or do something, right?
No, I was just going to come out.
Just come out?
What shallow thinking.
To be honest,
I couldn't do anything at all.
I have so many regrets!
I lost because
I didn't go on the offensive.
Trying to hold back your laughter
is the hardest thing to do.
I laugh easily in everyday life.
But I knew it.
I simply couldn't sit still.
I had to either smoke,
or drink water,
or keep walking around.
And Fujimoto kept talking.
The moment I start to listen
to things like that,
I can't help but laugh.
Just remembering that makes me laugh.
I'm not meant for this show.
That's still only two gone.
Two people out in one hour and a half.
-How's the pace?
-Pretty fast.
-Several of us have no more chances.
-You're right.
They are not allowed to laugh.
But the prohibition of laughter seems
to contradict the creation of comedy.
Why did you introduce that rule
for this show?
It is a contradiction.
Comedy is a contradiction.
It's two different sides of the same coin.
For example,
there was a time in my life when
I wanted to be the funniest man
on the planet.
I put all my effort into it,
and tried my best to become that guy.
But one day I realized,
the least funny man in the world
is probably the funniest.
So, no matter how hard I try,
I can only ever be second place.
It hit me one day.
Comedy is that kind of thing.
Sometimes people laugh at
the worst possible moment.
But when things like that happen,
that moment becomes comedy, too.
-Show us your anus.
-Show us properly.
Show us a bit more.
Ready?