Nice to meet you   -Good evening
It's season 7 now   -Yes
Last time, there were a lot of female comedians
And that season was unique in its own way
The most ever, with 4 female comedians
"Should I go this way?"
"Nope, I'll go this way and turn around"
For this time, I'll change it back to how it used to be again
With many of them making their first appearance
I bet it will be interesting
The Naive M-1 Champion
The Addictive Tsukkomi Dominant
The New Comedy Vader
The Desperate Off-white Comedian
The Grilled Meat Lion Dance
The Regretful Face Weapon
The Resurrection of Golden Pig
The Bird Face Guitar Man
The Incredible Penguin Man
The Citizen of "Hanma Kanma"
Incredible newcomers are joining one after another
And now, the chaotic party begins
The fight between the no-carders
The battle barely coping with rules
The back-and-forth of knock-outs
6 hours later
Looking back at today's contest
Thank you for your hard work   -Thank you very much
It's amazing this time, again   -Yeah...
I'm exhausted from laughing
These comedians were doing interesting things for so many hours nonstop
I'm even worried whether this is appropriate for the work-style reform proposal
It was just as I expected
Or even better than expected
No time wasted until the very last second
The Naive M-1 Champion
The Addictive Tsukkomi Dominant
The New Comedy Vader
The Desperate Off-white Comedian
The Grilled Meat Lion Dance
The Regretful Face Weapon
The Resurrection of Golden Pig
The Bird Face Guitar Man
The Incredible Penguin Man
The citizen of "Hanma Kanma"
Last week, when I had a lesson at teatime
I met someone called Yayoi-san
I asked Yayoi-san, "Were you born in March?"
And Yayoi-san replied, "I was born in July"
I felt a bit disappointed
That being said, I would like to offer you an invitation
Could you prepare one million yen
and gather at a designated location?
I shall reinitiate Documental
I have prepared a reward of 10 million yen for the winner
Of course, participation is voluntary
For those of you who wish to participate, I shall inform you of the time and location
Awaiting your reply
I hope that an innocent Spring will visit all of you in April
Sincerely, Matsumoto Hitoshi
THE PARTICIPATING COMEDIANS ENTER
Here he comes
Very exciting, huh?
Come on!
I'm the first one again
Come on...again?
Hello, I'm Nobu from Chidori
Thanks for having me
Eh?
What?
Wait a second...
This is enough
This is enough!
This guy is very skilled at Owarai
As a side effect, he tends to save every joke that others told
Which in turn, makes himself laugh
He's weak
Very weak
My defense is too weak, I almost laughed at every joke
*The weakest comedian in Documental
So this time, I discovered a face that even Matsumoto-san won't say it's inappropriate
And I've been training myself with that face
Yes, I invented this face
This is it...
The dodging face
"Hey no, listen to me..."
Does this face count as laughing?   -I don't think so...
What did he order?
Last time, he made a desperate attack
Whelk sushi
Whelk sushi?
2000 pieces   -2000 pieces?
Huh? Oops...
A dirty performance that he's not used to
Here comes the pee
That severely damaged the career of the man, Nobu, as a comedian
When other decent shows think about asking Chidori to be the host
They are reluctant to do so because of the "peeing incident"
I really want to rewrite it
I want rewrite everyone's memories
It's not just about the audiences
I want to make Matsumoto Hitoshi-san think that
"Nobu is the best Tsukkomi in the world of Owarai"
That's my aim for today
Who else? Who?!
There're just so many comedians gathering each time
I sincerely hope they're all boring people
Nice to meet you   -Nice to meet you
This is quite unexpected, right?
Hello, I'm Kato from Zabunguru
Today...
I will definitely...
Definitely win!!!
I'm fully prepared
Hello
Whoa! Really?
Whoa!!!
Here it comes!!
This is his first appearance
I bet he has been thinking about this even last night
And I bet he'll find out that none of his plans will work here
The Regretful Face Weapon
But if he can handle and get through this
I believe he can come up with something interesting, and I'm looking forward to it
"That dude is not funny"
"He always cries"
People are looking down on me
They always think that I'm a wimp
Although I'm actually not
I've been perceived like this by the public
However, if I can win this contest, I believe things will change
Therefore, in order to get rid of this "wimp character", I have to win
The best defense is a good offense
I'll be attacking aggressively, even against senior comedians
Seriously, get ready for the fight you people
I'm gonna make you laugh so hard and puke!!
"Wimp character"
Well, the staffs did tell me that he prepared something amazing though
Does it feel different for the 1st and 2nd time?
Well, yeah...
Who is it?
Come on!
Goto-san
Eh?   -Goto-san
I'm Goto from Footballhour
Same as last time, I'm feeling nervous as soon as I enter the studio
This is for you
Here it is
Of course I'll go
I have no reason to refuse this
Tsukkomi Sniper
In terms of Tsukkomi...
I think it's fair to say that Nobu and Goto are the two giants in the world of Owarai
Hamada was said to be the giant at one time
But he's at rock bottom now
All he says now is "why the heck"
Throughout the whole year
Goto is very attentive to details
And his Tsukkomis are always in long sentences
So that's the sweet spot
Amazing!
He's The Ventures
Playing with electricity
I screwed up
Goto was the one I needed to watch out for
When you think about it, he really is an all-round player
It's a place that I never experienced before
But it's also a place full of excitement
Nothing goes as planned, and I believe that's true for everyone else
That's why we're all left frustrated after losing the contest
And if we ever get invited again, we will accept it and take revenge
The most horrible comedians come last
He just went to the convenient store?
Here he comes!
Here he comes
*Soshina and Seiya are partners of the comedy duo "Shimofuri Myojo"
So it's not Soshina but Seiya instead
I know you, you lost the R-1 competition, right?   -Wait...why?
Just say I'm the one who won the M-1 competition
Hello, I'm Seiya from Shimofuri Myojo
In continuation of the M-1 competition, I want to win Documental as well
No way...
What is this?
It's Documental
It's Documental!
I'm looking forward to his performance
And I think he may get into a miserable situation, which is worth looking forward to as well
If he can show his childish and naughty side, then maybe that could be his way out
The Naive M-1 Champion
After winning the M-1 competition...
I thought I don't need to fight anymore, then here comes Documental?
The battles are coming way too quickly
I haven't even received the 10 million cash prize for M-1
Because I'm afraid that people are expecting too much from Soshina
Why isn't Soshina invited to the battle?
Yes, that's true, many say that "Soshina is good, but Seiya should just shut up"
Or like "Seiya is just Soshina's repeater"
After winning the M-1 and Suberanai Hanashi
Everything changed in just one night
Winning Documental will be another life-changing moment
Instead of being clean and neat
I want to fight face to face with Owarai
I want to get dirty and muddy, and show people the soul of a comedian
He has this gag like "I am Se, Se, Seiya..."
It's gonna be awkward if he does that
That's a bit...
Here he comes!
You joined this before already
It's Goto...
It's Tamura-san
You must be kidding me...
I definitely can't hold back on Tamura-san's jokes
What the heck are these members?
Hello, I'm the Owarai triple champion, Tamura Kenji
Ciao
I've said this for many times, but this is my combat uniform
You must be kidding me
So I did really well last time?
He's the type of comedian that can do both Boke and Tsukkomi
I actually praise Tamuken very highly
However...
I remember nothing about what he did last time
But I think he will improve this time
Stop that...   -Everyone will notice it
You're not even trying to hide it
*The words on Tamuken's chest says "Ramen shops are so scary", because around the time of the show, while he was eating at a Ramen shop, one of the staff took a photo with him and posted it on the official Twitter account, saying that "Tamuken is a boring person without mic and camera". The shop was criticized by many comedy fans on Twitter.
They said "Tamuken is a boring person without mic and camera"
We all know about that...
The contestants are pitiful this time
Because Tamura is in serious mode today
*Kansai's side business king
I'm seriously aiming for the 10 million this time
Because I'm seriously in deep trouble now
I'm being cornered now, honestly
If I lose again, this is going to be a 12 million loss
No, no way, it's just 2 million
I already lost 10 million in cryptocurrency
Loss in cryptocurrency + Loss in Documental for twice = -12 million
Oh, I see   -Yes
It's gonna be a 12 million loss for me
This came just in time! This is destiny!
I'm gonna get the money
And I'm gonna buy it again
If I win 10 million, I'm gonna change that 10 million cash into 10 million crypto
Just trust me and strong hold to the moon
In 2020, it will come again
It's impossible for me to hold back on Tamura-san's jokes
I'm easily amused too, I was out so early last time
Yeah, you're right
Goto, you're easily amused too, right?   -Yes, I'm easily amused
I bet they don't want him to be here
His face is just...
His face looks funny already
I'm angry today   -How come? What happened?
You're angry?   -How come?
Why are you angry?
Damn it
Damn it?
What happened?
I'm Hachimitsu Jiro from Tokyo Dynamite
Today, I will definitely win 11 million
Nice to meet you
This is for you
I already know...
This is the third time already, I know what's going on
So it's finally here
I praised him highly since many years ago
He's incredibly talented
The heavyweight whisperer
He did a very good job last time too
So I actually hope that he can win this time
You were hospitalized due to a heart attack last year, right?   -Yes
Many people are worried about that
But I'm actually completely recovered
It's all about my knees and waist
My knees and waist hurt for being a professional wrestler
I'm pretty sure that if my knees don't hurt, I can do better at making people laugh
I need to battle while protecting my knees
And pretending that my knees are fine
In regard to this, I always watch Mutoh Keiji's matches
And learn how to pretend to be moving while actually not moving
Who are you angry at?
All of you
What do you mean? We met just now
The opposite of "Owarai" is "Anger"
So I want to be full of anger throughout the 6 hours of battle
I once talked with Choshu-san (wrestler) before
And he said that he's always angry during his fights
So I'll learn from him and enter the wrestling ring for Owarai with anger
If your car is broken, go find Tamuken-san
No need to mention that, dude
(Yeah, Tamuken is doing car businesses now too)
(Something like a car trading company)
Well yeah, that's true
Just sell me your car if it's broken
Boring person, please!
Seriously?!   -This is gonna be awful!
I can't believe it!
Koyabu-san!
It is indeed quite surprising for Koyabu to join Documental
It's Koyabu-san!
So scary to be with these members
Koyabu-san...   -Whoa!
I'm Koyabu Kazutoyo from Yoshimoto
I'm so frightened that my body can't stop shaking
I've brought you something
What is this? So scary, what is it?
Damn it...
I really hope I was drawn into some scandals
That would help a lot
This is his first appearance
How should I put it...
He's the "auntie comedian", right?
He's just like an auntie
I'm really curious to see how is he going to one-up others as an auntie
The New Comedy Vader
Honestly, I get to work at Tokyo all because of Matsumoto-san
He invited me to many shows like Suberanai
So I'll be damned badly if I dare to refuse this invitation
He's actually quite easily amused
We were on the same show yesterday
And he bursted into laughter because of Huruichi-san's joke
Would a normal person even laugh at Huruichi-san's jokes?
Medaka, Okure and Suuchi, I bet they can do better than me
To be honest, I actually sometimes think that I'm no longer a comedian, because I'm always hosting news shows recently
So being invited to this show makes me think that, I can still call myself a comedian
Which is very honorable
Despite of being surprised, look at that huge bag he brought
Exactly, his bag is fully stuffed
He's fully prepared
I thought he'll only attack with talks, but...
In order to increase my chance of winning
Three more people
Boring person, please!
Please come in
Who is it?
Hello everybody
I like you so much
Michio-san   -It's Michio-chan!
This dude is completely off the wall, no one can predict what he's going to do next
I'm Michio from Tom Brown
Wait a second...nope!
Thank you for having me today
Nice to meet you
Fake TV Show Meeting
This is a special program   -Yes
What is your stunt?
I can pull apart a pineapple with barehands
I brought something else for you though
This is for you   -Yes?
Okay, I know about Documental...
You win if you can pull out others' spinal cord, right?
He's the most terrifying type of contestant
Because you have no idea about what he will do
The first appearance of M-1 Psycho Comedian
What's in that bag?
Maybe others will be disgusted, but I'm willing to do anything
Fusion!
I can thrust my face into vomits
I can wash my hands with pee
I feel sorry for other comedians
But it is possible that the show may even be banned
The Insane Penguin Man
However, I've only seen Tom Brown as a comedy duo
I wonder what he is like on his own
I just have to go for broke
I only have 1,000 yen left in my bank account
And I had to borrow 1 million from my boss
I want to leave a deep impression
and win the cash prize at the same time
That's the ideal situation
I'll make the wind blow
What's in that bag?   -A human head?
It's gonna be a big problem if that's a human head
Well, this is actually...   -A human head, right?
This is actually...
This is a second bag   -Second bag?
(He's already showing it?)
Why don't you show it later?
He's already showing it
I'll definitely laugh if he showed it later
That was quite funny
There's still 6 more hours, dude
It's not even started yet
One more person left?   -Two more people
No way!
Wait a second, this is amazing   -Eh?!
Come on...   -No, no, no way
This is going to be awful   -Come on...
There are people that I know and people that I don't know
Of course, dude, that's usually the case
Yes, I'm the one that you don't know   -Nice to meet you
Hello, I'm Miyasako from Ameagari-Kesshitai
I thought I will never get an offer again
This is for you
Seriously?
It's for you
For the second time?
So he's joining this again for the second time
Last time, he even had an erection for the contest
So this time, it's probably about time for him to ejaculate
All I had was an erection last time
It has been a while since the last contest
So I think I won't have an erection anymore
Because I'm 50 and my body is deteriorating everyday
He's a major comedian, and I would like to witness a major comedian winning
The Desperate Off-white Comedian
Oh gee
9 people now
It's not about the entrance fee, neither the 10 million cash prize
I just don't want to get hurt
Same as last time...
I want to let out the insanity hiding inside of me
Of course, Miyasako is the most senior comedian among them
No girls yet, huh?   -Yeah
You are already not interesting   -Why the heck?
What are you talking about?
What do you mean "already"?
So here comes the last person
And it's him...
Everybody, prepare yourself, it's him
Eh?   -No! No! No way!
The emperor, here comes the emperor
Hello, I'm Hollywood Zakoshisyoh
I am so psyched up to be here!
Two-time champion!
I got to do this
Moved to a new apartment with the cash prize from Documental
Again?
Everyone thinks that Zakoshi is a very strong player for Documental
He's like "The Last Emperor" Fedor at one time
One can totally feel his emperor-ness
The Strongest Man In The World
One in six billion
He's strong in both attack and defense
He's truly an impregnable wall
I personally see him as the emperor
I actually thought winners can't join anymore
But here comes the invitation, and I'm like "Hooray!"
The Super Aggressive Documentalist
To be honest, I can even do this for 24 hours, not just 6 hours
I think it's fair to say I'm a heaven-sent player for Documental
Let's do this
I don't want to do this...
Let's do this again!
The atmosphere is completely irrelevant here
I want to surprise the world again
It's very possible for him to win again
If I'm joining again, then of course I'm aiming to win again
I got to do this!
Why is Miyasako-san coming again...
Come on, you don't need to be even more popular
You don't care about 10 million, right?   -Please quit
I didn't expect Miyasako-san to join again
I didn't expect to come back a second time too
Then please reject the invitation
I already have 10 million anyway   -Hey, dude!
He's pissing me off...
Everyone here wants the 10 million
We are here because we want the 10 million
So scary   -His face looks so scary
What's going on?
His muscles are popping out!
So big!
What happened to you, Matsumoto-san?
His muscles are not balanced
He's so strange today
What was that?
Everybody have a seat
Is he showing off his muscles?   -No, I'm not
Well, this is very interesting
This is horrible   -Yes, it is
These members are horrible
Even for zoo animals, they get to have their own cages
But now, completely different humans are shut in the same cage
I actually thought Koyabu-san will not come
I don't get this too
He's the talking type of comedian
I thought he'll just be attacking with talks too, but then he brought a huge bag with him
Yeah, you're right
This man over here, I call him the emperor, Zakoshi
He's an impregnable wall
Thank you very much   -Who can stop him?
He's a formidable enemy, someone have to stop him
Shall I take it again?
Another 10 million?
No one has ever done that yet
He is very strong indeed
We all know about the rules, right?   -Yes
So there are three cards
And if you get a red card, then you're out
Well, 1 million is nothing to you guys, right?
No, no, no!
No way!   -What are you talking about?
Yeah, it's nothing to me
This man over here...
This man says it's nothing to him again, he's a man of principle
Yeah right, honestly, we all have many millions
We are all equally rich
No we're not   -Not at all
You're exceptionally rich
We are all the same   -You're exceptional
He's the man of exception
Eh?   -The man of exception?
Dude...
Do you even think you can win?
Then why the heck did you invite me?
Wait a second, let me ask this again
Why the heck did you invite me?
No one knows what will happen here
This is like a type of combat sport
Yeah, you're right
I'll seize...I mean collect your 1 million now   -Seize?
One million is a lot...
Well, yes, I know, you're right
But I'm giving out one million too
Yeah, that's true
Hey, Koyabu...
This looks like the money in casino   -Yes, you're right
I'll trust you guys with this. One million, right?
Yes, one million
Wow, so scary!
Amazing!   -That's a lot of money
This is so graphic
It really is!   -This is nothing to Seiya, right?
No, I haven't received the cash prize from M-1 yet, so...
You haven't received it yet?   -No, not yet
Maybe Seiya can get this one too, he's on fire recently
If Seiya can be like how he was during M-1
Yeah right
If he's like how he was during R-1 then that's the worst   -Matsumoto-san...
I got trolled so hard by internet because you said that
And with this, you'll only get 9 millions, so...
I'll add this...   -Matsumoto-san's one million!
This adds up to 10 million
11 million   -Yes
Are you guys ready?
Ready?   -Yes
The contest starts after I leave
Wow! This is terrifying!
I probably shouldn't say this, but...
Those that don't attack and are not interesting...
Will get trolled super hard by internet
Why are you saying that now?
They will be nastily trolled
Ahh, it's about to start
This is my first time   -This is my first time too
Good luck guys   -Thank you very much
Thank you very much
Whao, it's about to start!
Who's taking part for the first time?
4 people
4 people are taking part for the first time
It's not started yet, right?   -Yeah, not yet
I need to go pee
Come on, you're trying to prepare something, right?
No, no, it's not started yet
-Don't rush, there's plenty of time
-No dude, I really need to go pee
Let's start now
Documental
Start!
It started   -Come on!
I'll do this just in case
For what?   -Just in case
Just in case for what?
Ciao
What the heck is that just in case for?
Isn't he laughing?
He's laughing!   -Yeah
I didn't laugh, that's just Ciao
That counts as well   -Yeah, exactly
Hey no, that's Ciao
What do you mean just in case...   -Do it again
He was indeed smiling
You're laughing!   -You're out
That's Ciao!   -You're laughing
This needs further deliberation, honestly
Why the heck?   -You're indeed laughing!
You can't laugh even if you're talking
No way, that's just Ciao
(Well, yeah...)
That's just Ciao!
Do it again
Ciao
You're laughing
Ikko-san
Why the heck?
Why did you do that?
It's not even relevant
Koyabu...Koyabu...Koyabu!
Irrelevant with Ciao
Koyabu is close, Koyabu is very close!
No one will laugh at it, right?
No one will laugh at Ciao, right? I'll go get changed
No, no one will laugh at Ciao
You're the one who's laughing
So no one will laugh, right?
No one will laugh
No will laugh? Not at Ciao?   -Nope
Well, actually, maybe I'll laugh
Eh?   -Laugh at Ciao?
I can't leave if you say that, dude
Please do it again
Ciao
Is he laughing?   -His face is laughing
My heart is not laughing though
What the heck do you mean your heart is not laughing?   -That's cheap
You heart is not laughing?
Well, just let him get away with it   -Exactly
Dude, if I can't even perform gags, then...
Was that even a gag?
He's trying to do something
*Furuhata Ninzaburo is a police detective drama
I'm Furuhata
I am the murderer
This is...
He's the suspect?
Nikaku-san?
*Shouhukutei-Nikaku is one of the most senior comedian in Yoshimoto
Hey, I'm Shouhukutei-Nikaku
The quality of this imitation is very high
Tamuken   -Yes?
Quit comedy now
Not even a single person in Yoshimoto admires you
Why would you say something like that to me?
Stop it, Seiya
Miyasako
Yes, Shisho
For 10 years...
Long time no see
You've always been telling safe jokes that everyone can tell
Seiya...
He's pissing me off
Your jokes are always 50 points
That's not true, stop it
Anyone with a mouth can do that
That's completely untrue
Shisho won't say that   -Nikaku-shisho definitely won't say that
Koyabu
All you got is a loud voice
I don't think so...
Well...
Your voice and your face
That's not true
I've never been told about that though
That attitude is no good to Yoshimoto
Goto   -Yes?
Honestly, you're just simply untalented
You're very lucky to be able to come this far
And yet, you think you've done this with your own effort
That's seriously pathetic, so please stop!
You don't even sound like Shisho for the last bit
Stop it, Seiya!
You're just talking bad about him for the last bit
*Fujimon blew up at his junior, Shiatsuyaro, because Shiatsuyaro imitated Kyojin-shisho and talked bad about Fujimon
By the way, that's exactly why Fujimon blew up at Shiatsuyaro
Yeah, that happened
Eh?   -He let out a "Kee" sound?
That's probably the sound of him laughing, right?
Did you laugh?
Good, take him down
Don't let out sounds as if you're doing Judo
That one just now doesn't count?
He completely laughed
He laughed out loud
I remembered something about Nigaku-shisho
Please tell us about it
We were on the same stage in Nagoya before
*Debayashi is a kind of kabuki music played on a stage by performers.
Nigaku-shisho was going to perform Debayashi
Since Nigaku-shisho got his own room to rest
He walked towards the stage very slowly on his own
And he arrived only after the show ended
Nigaku-shisho...
He's slow paced   -It takes time for him to walk
He probably don't have enough stamina
He was talking with Budan-shisho
Oh, so that's why
Nigaku said to me "your throat is so weak"
"You have to cure your throat if you want to be a comedian"
Then I told him I had vocal cord polyp surgery for twice
And I asked "how many times did you have that surgery?"
And he answered "24 times"   -That's a lot!
Too much
Probably every year
He's a legend
So even him needs to have it for so many times
He doesn't have any polyp left by now, huh?
(Everyone is trying to hold back)
(Very close)
(Everyone is in danger)
I think he almost laughed at that Shiatsuyaro incident
Yeah, talk more about Shiatsuyaro
It's no good to talk bad about others
Fujimon blew up at him
Why? What happened?
What the heck is that?
No, come on, just tell us what happened
Goto-san, you can say it
I don't want to talk bad about Shiatsuyaro-san, honestly
No, we're just asking you what happened?
I think...
He raped someone?
No way...
Am I wrong?
Rape?
Koyabu...
No way, that's not right   -I don't remember
(That's inappropriate)
You're completely wrong
Kyojin-shisho...
Kyojin-shisho?   -Yeah
Well yeah, he imitated Kyojin-shisho and said something inappropriate
Yeah, that's right
He definitely didn't rape anyone   -Exactly
Seiya...
That was completely wrong   -Seiya...
Are you laughing?   -No, I'm not
You were laughing for many times already
That's the same for you, Goto-san!
He's talking so loudly now
No, I didn't laugh at all
Seiya, that's inappropriate, honestly
Do I need to judge myself for this?
Do I need to say like "I laughed"?
No, of course not   -Exactly, so don't blame me
He's about to laugh, huh?
Shall I do the Hazuki imitation now?
*Zakoshi is imitating the Hazuki magnifying glasses CM, which is endorsed by Watanabe Ken. This CM ended up being very popular and got made fun of for Ken's overly exaggerated performance.
*Full CM: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LuVh2zLej3Q
What is that?   -Here it comes
They kind of look alike
Nowadays, the texts are all...
SO DAMN SMALL!!!
But if you wear the Hazuki glasses
The world changes
Everything looks bigger!
Please stop it Seiya, we're being hit by his scattergun too
Something exploded, huh?
I'll go get changed, okay?
What was that Ciao just now?
Just in case someone will laugh at it
So you let out all of your Ciao already, right?   -Yeah
I'll go get changed then   -Yeah, sure
Everyone agrees?   -Yes
Your skin is full of blemishes
What happened to you?
It's full of blemishes
I don't like seniors with blemishes...   -So cold!
So cold...
Yeah, my body gets cold easily
*Miyasako was diagnosed with stomach cancer in 2012 and removed two-thirds of the stomach
Because I had stomach cancer
He laughed?
He let out a "ku" sound   -Yeah, I heard that
Hooray!
It's definitely Tamura-san
He totally laughed
Eh? It's me?
He bursted out laughing   -Yeah, he did
He was like "ku"
Hooray!   -That one was close
That one was so close
He said "ku", right?   -Yes, he did
Yes I did, but please look at my face
My face wasn't laughing at all
Yeah, all I heard was "ku"
The camera did record his face
But there were a lot of monitors in front of me
So I missed that one
Let's take a look   -Yes, let's confirm it
Let's confirm it
So cold
Yeah, my body gets cold easily
Because I had stomach cancer
You were laughing, dude!
You were completely laughing, dude!
What the heck is wrong with this dude?!
He laughed at others' pain
You're the worst!   -That's so mean
But wait, you're the one who tried to make him laugh at your pain
You're even worse
Although you're the sufferer
No! No way! I don't want this!
Anyway, I'll give you this one
Or maybe this one?   -No, no, no...
The yellow one   -Okay, okay
Yellow, yellow
Seiya laughed as well   -No, we're different
He definitely laughed   -Well, well, yeah, I know
It's not good to make those weird faces
Sorry, I won't do it again
But since the length of his career is remarkably longer than me, so please forgive me
No way, dude!
At the moment you won M-1, the difference in career length doesn't matter anymore
You've went through Nichome's times of storm!*
*Shinjuku Nichome was known as the noisiest and most dangerous ward in Tokyo, housing the world's highest concentration of gay bars and nightclubs
Times of storm?
It was already quite peaceful in my days
Oh gee, it's gonna be tough this time
Only ten minutes have passed?!
The tempo is so fast!
We got off to a fast start this time
Maybe it's gonna end earlier?
Come on...seriously, I mean seriously
Let's do this properly
Yeah, you're right
Let's stop camouflaging
Choose your side
Either laugh or hold back
Ok, let's start immediately
It started again
No one will laugh at it
Even I won't laugh at it, of course no one else will!
He's torn between doing or stopping his Ciao
Eh? Just now?
He laughed naturally   -And if the alarm rings...
I knew it!
He totally laughed
So naturally
No, wait a second...
If even that counts as laughing...
You were too relaxed
I didn't see that clearly too, was that you Kato?
Yes, it's Kato-san   -No, no, it's not me
All I said was "Kee"
Which means you laughed
What is a "Kee"?
What made you laugh anyway?
No, no, I didn't laugh
Really?
Let's take a look   -Yeah, we'll see
I'm sure that one of the camera recorded him   -I was just breathing
No one will laugh at it
Even I won't laugh at it, of course no one else will!
He's torn between doing or stopping his Ciao
Eh? Just now?
You totally laughed!
That's definitely out!
Wait a second...
That's completely out!
That one should even be given an orange card
What were you laughing at?   -What's so funny?
Well...
Nothing was funny, but I thought...
"For god's sake, how long is he going to talk about Ciao?"
So I took a deep unsteady breath
So it's my point, I scored one point
I scored one point, right?
Well...
I have to give you a yellow card for this
This one came so fast
I have to pull myself together
This one is probably the fastest one ever
I sat on my chair for just one small moment