Even if no one is laughing
I will not be anxious
I will not doubt myself
I will continue my performance and go my own way
Brigham Young once said...
"I have to save Japan"
"Although this has never been proven in history"
I just love Owarai
I love the excitement and I want to face my fear
I want to move one step forward
"Should I go this way?"
"Nope, I'll go this way and turn around"
Jinnai, you're out!
Come on, really?
"You are trying to escape from here"
"You are trying to escape from the family"
Who are you?
You mean me?
Infinite testicles syndrome
You're out!
Mei-eki?   -Immunity (men-eki)
You mean the Nagoya station?
That's Mei-eki
Someone laughed, huh?
Who laughed?
I'll give her an orange card straight away
So harsh
Who's coming?
Long time no see
I'm glad you guys are having a good time
We look like we're having a good time?
I finished early, so...
Yeah
And I thought I left without doing anything meaningful
Well, yeah
So, although I shouldn't be doing this here, but...
Underwear are very important, right?
Men's underwear are important
Yes, very important
So I think we should check someone's underwear
Check someone's underwear?
Who's?
Mine
Okay, that sounds good
So we will check you underwear?
I'm wearing my favorite underwear today, it's really cute
So please take a look
Men and women have different sense though
So cute
Two colors   -Yes, two colors
TORIO (brand)?   -Yes
There's these designs here too...
Very cute   -That was unexpected
Yeah, it looks good, I like the color
Eh?
There's even a pocket here
No...
That's not the main point
Daigo...
Infected?...
It looks like Kaela now
Kaela Kimura is a Japanese pop rock singer famous for having avant-garde and colorful hairstyles
It looks like a metal ball
Eh? Wild turkey?
You mean here?
No, not there, not about your underwear
It looks like a tropical bird, when it's courting and puff out it's cheek
Underwear, look at my underwear
What do you think?
Eh? Is that just one side of the balls?
No, don't you think the coloring looks great?
The pink color and...
Very cute...
So even his balls are in pink and blue color
Amazing, I can look at it forever
It's artistic
I even thought it's a rock
Thank you
Thank you, too
Thank you for showing us such a precious thing
Thank you
Thank you very much
See you
See you   -Thank you very much
We get to look at it for a long time
Yeah, it was a precious opportunity
It doesn't look disgusting after it's painted, huh?   -Exactly
It really looks like some kind of bird or plant
Huh?
That person...
Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you too
What happened?
Ah, excuse me
I want to make you all to space
Make us to space?
Do you mean take us to space?
Yes, make you all to space
That's neat
Those sunglasses are amazing
She looks like Shiozawa Toki-san
*Shiozawa Toki was a Japanese actress and television personality, and she always wears unique looking sunglasses
Oh, really?
Oh, she's Shiozawa Toki-san
Yes, I'm Shiozawa Toki
What are you doing?
What was that?
I want to make you all into this song
No, we want you to take us to space
Not into this song
Is this a TV show?
She's probably the floor director
She's giving the instructions
*It says "(Kurosawa) One more song"
She's showing the cunning paper
The instructions
I'm doing a great job
*It says "(Fujimon) This has become a memorable song for me"
This will take us to space?
Well...umm...
This has become...
A memorable song for me
Okay, let's stop for a while
Excuse me
(This dude is just absolute chaotic, incredible)
Let's stop for a while
So after this...   -Yes
The recording has been stopped now
And after this...
(Yuriyan is amazing)
I want you guys to...well...
To speak out loud
Whatever you say, remember to speak it out loud
What should we say though?
Well, just say anything that first comes to your mind, that should be fine
Well, how should I put it
Maybe you can make fun of the rustiness of this building
Like "it's super ancient"
Yes, "super ancient" is interesting
In addition...
I want to discuss this further
Should "super ancient" appear for like 4 times?
Once is enough
I want to emphasize this point though   -Once is enough
So please say it once
Is it a must?
Yes, it is
Is it gonna work? "Super ancient" all of a suddent?
Just say what we're thinking, right?   -Yes
And if you stand up from the chair
I believe your feet will be on the ground, so...
Of course it will
And only if you know how to walk
The fabric over there, which is called the curtain   -Yes, we know
If you open the curtain, you can change your clothes inside
We need to get changed?
Yes
And you can take a break inside too
What is this?   -What is this TV show?
Please explain everything to us
What is this TV show and what do you want us to do?
And what is your role?
This is Documental
Huh?
This show is Documental
Documental is not scripted though   -Yeah, it's not
It's freestyle
It's not scripted, so...
How should I put it, well...
This is a fight between comedians...umm...
We know the rules, you don't need to tell us what to do
Please do some Boke and...
We will Boke, we will   -We will do it, no worries
We will do it, there's no need to instruct us
Well, how should I put it...
Please do some greeting gags too
People with a greeting gag will do it, no problem
You mean like Miyasako's greeting gag, right?
*"Ginza Yeah" is the title of Tomochika's famous skit
-I can do "Ginza Yeah" too, right?
-Yes, "Ginza Yeah" is intereting too
Which TV station are you from?
I'm from the Doguyasuji TV
*Yuriyan made up a TV station based on the name of a famous shopping street in Osaka, Doguyasuji
Huh?
Doguyasuji TV?
We are DTV
This show will only be broadcasted at Doguyasuji?
Yes
You mean that shopping street in Osaka?
That street is full of Chinese people
Yes, our target audience is Chinese poeple
However...
I don't think anyone will find it funny with your script though
Well, Watashi have...Boku have...
*Watashi and Boku both means "I", however, for most of the time, only females will use Watashi, and only males will use Boku
Watashi? Boku? What is your gender?
Male or female?
I'm a woman
This person has a lot of gags, please give it a look
Can you do it?
Of course, he has a lot of gags
Recently
I went to the Sennichimae Doguyasuji, at Namba, Osaka
And guess what
There were a lot of Chinese people
About 30 people, and they were walking around
30 people were walking around
Well done
You instructed her to do that?
Yes, I instructed her to do that
Oh, so you asked her to do that
Yes, excuse me
Eh? Isn't it freestyle?
Well, yes it is
But please follow my instructions too
Got it
By the way, there're food and drinks over there...
That's enough, we don't need your instructions   -We don't need it
That's enough
Let's stop recording for a while   -It's stopped already
Umm...
The recording is stopped already
That's enough
You guys are isolating me, huh?
Isolating?
No we're not isolating you
It's already this time
I better go home now
So scary, so scary
Who is it?
Maybe it's just my imagination
Who is it?!
You've been following me from the nursing center, huh?
I told you I'll pay you later!
Can I show you all a short video clip?
Yeah, sure
Nothing fancy, but...
No worries
Okay, it's ready
I'll play it now
Oh, Ms.Chopchop
Ms.Chopchop?   -Ms.Chopchop
What's happening?
Eh? What's happening?
What are you doing?
What happened?
What's this?
Slapstick comedy
What the heck?
That's all you wanted to show us?
We don't need that
Anything else?
That's enough, seriously, that's enough
We don't need this
That's enough, come on
You look like Sakata Shisho
That's enough   -Enough
Who's that?
That's me
So cute   -You're big, huh?
When did you take this photo?
Last year
Last year?!
Stop lying, hum!
Hum!
Very cute
Her feet are so small
And it's squishy
Aren't those shoes from the Heian period?
No, they're not
There're also photos of me growing up
This photo
The girl wearing a red hat?   -So cute!
Red hat?
Nope, not that girl
White hat?
Nope
Which one then?
You didn't change at all
Her feet are so tiny!
That's so tiny
Are those wooden shoes?
No way, those are not
These are wooden shoes...
How is it impossible for kids to wear wooden shoes during sports day?
Maybe it's that kind of school
Wow, it's shaking a lot
We can't see it if you shake it, hum!
Hum! You're right
What the heck is that?
There's not much time left
Only 40 more minutes
Not much time left, so...
We can't waste time on this
We can't waste time on this, hum!
Someone's coming
Oh, Kanmuri-san!
*Kanmuri Jiro is a famous Enka singer, and "Get fired up! Get fired up!" is a line from his most famous song "Honō"
Get fired up! Get fired up!
Seiya!
Shout it together!
He's Kanmuri Jiro-san
Nice to meet you
I'm Kanmuri
I'm Kan-muri Jiro
His name is Kanmuri, and he calls himself Kan-muri
Why do you call yourself Kan-muri?
Just call him Kan-muri-san
Well, please read Kanmuri Jiro as Kan-muri Jiro
*"Pushing myself too hard" is pronounced as "muri", which sounds the same as (Kan-) muri
Because I'm always pushing myself too hard (muri)*
And that's why I call myself Kan-muri Jiro
Instead of Kanmuri Jiro, please call me Kan-muri Jiro
And after he says this, the audience will always say "thank you so much for your lip service"
Oh, it gets a laugh?   -Yes, yes
It gets a laugh?   -Well...
Seiya! That's the spirit! That's the spirit!
You wanna do it? Nope?
Your jacket looks amazing   -It looks fancy
Yes, this is...umm...maybe I'll do it now
Sure, do it now
Maybe I'll get an electric shock though
My body is going numb   -Going numb?
Get fired up! Get fired up!
No, you're gonna set yourself on fire
What are those decorations?
This is called Den-shoku (Electric decorations)
Den-shoku (Electric decorations)
Wa-shoku (Japanese meal), Tei-shoku (Set meal)
*"Den" means electric, and decorations and meal are both pronounced as "Shoku"
Wa-shoku (Japanese meal), Tei-shoku (Set meal), Yo-shoku (Western meal) and Den-shoku (Electric decorations)
Did that ever get a laugh?
Huh?
Did that get a laugh?
Well, this is the first time I said it
But I think you can use this gag in your performances too
Oh, really?
Oh, a mic   -A mic
Mike Maki   -Yes, Mike Maki (Japanese actor)
Kanmuri-san, can you please...
Oh, yes?
What? What's wrong?
What happened?
Please, say it
May I help you?
Question? You have a question?
I just thought it wasn't that funny, to be honest
Oh, I bet so
That wasn't funny, huh?
You bet so?
Yes, I bet so
You bet so? So you knew it?
Yes, whenever possible, I reflect on myself from an objective perspective
That is a Den-ki (light bulb), I am Gen-ki (healthy), and you are Non-ki (relaxed)
No, those kinds of gags are...
What? You have a question?
Eh?   -What's wrong?
Well...
It's okay, males should be silent
What can you do with being silent?
*Being silent (Mu-kuchi) and having six mouths (Mutsu-kuchi) have similar pronunciations
I can have six mouths*
So scary
One, two...
Three, four, five...
That's your nose
What kind of Boke is this?
Because I myself am becoming a Boke (dumb)   -Uh-oh
Do you have a stuffy nose?
Stuffy nose?
That's important
Well, my nose is...
For real?
This thing can clear your nose
Clear my nose?
Yes, I've got something that can clear your nose
Eh?   -Please come over here
Maybe give this a try?
Eh? What? What is it?
Just squeeze it in and it will wash your nose
Very simple, just squeeze this in your nose
No worries
I know, I know this, it's basically salt water and...umm...
No more talking please, just...
Oh, really?
So it will come out from the other side?
Amazing, an amazing amount is coming out
Wow, that's amazing   -Are you okay?
He's putting it all in!
Amazing!!   -It all went in!
So strong
So Strong!   -You're amazing, Kanmuri-san
I'm good, I can put even more in
This is enough   -This amount is enough
Huh? What is your name again?
Many people say we look alike
Shoji-san, please show him your gag
Please look at him, he'll show you his gag
You'll remember his name after watching his gag
Please do it
You've never seen that before? He has been doing it throughout his career
Your eyes are staring into my soul again
Please leave!
Your eyes are canzone
*"Canzone" and "staring into my soul" have similar pronunciations
Canzone!
Yes, they are staring into my soul, canzone
Good
No, please...
What is this?   -Bravo
No, it should be ET
Yeah, ET, it should be ET
Glad that you all know about ET
What's next?
Time to leave
Seiya!
Seiya! Who said it?
Seiya, good!
Ready, set...
Seiya! Hooray!
Bye bye
So powerful
I can't believe he doesn't know about Shoji-san
He probably doesn't watch TV very often, so...
No, it's my fault for not appearing on TV very often
Eh?
It's my fault for not appearing on TV shows
No, no, Shoji-san...
It's simply because he doesn't watch TV, don't let it get you down
No...
I'm only on TV shows in Kansai, so...
Nah, you're not even on TV shows in Kansai, right?
Fujimoto-san...
Our camera team has entered Documental's lodge
*Tomochika is imitating a comedian called Seki Okio, who is well-known for hosting TV shows about urban legends
That's incredible, huh?
There’s no turning back
Seki...
This means that the Pandora's box has been opened
Urban legends...   -That's incredible, huh?
Listen carefully
Seki?...
This is the grand lodge, and it's not allowed to enter here, right?
But everyone here has agreed about this
The losers will give one million yen to the winner
And the winner can take all of the money, which adds up to 10 million
Am I right?
Only the person at the top...
Look at this pyramid
Look at this
Only the person at the top of this pyramid can take all of the money
Listen carefully
That has nothing to do with urban legend though
This is amazon, right?
Amazon, right?
Amazon? Am I spelling it right?
Yes, it's amazon
Amazon, right?
Listen carefully
Cross out the "a", right?
Change it to "s", right?
And that's mason
Therefore, this proves that amazon is in fact freemason
The door to the new world has been opened
But you crossed out and changed the words...
You can change it to anything you want
Do you have a smartphone with you?
Yes, I have it with me
Do you have it with you?   -Yes
Come on, this is just...
You can't just cross it out
Don't cross it out or change it...
These letters undoubtedly proved that it's true
That's incredible, huh?   -No, Seki-san, that's not right
I'll ask Siri about this
You can change it to whatever you want
Is Amazon freemason?
It says nothing
But that's not because it has nothing to say
Instead, there's actually some kind of power that stops it from saying, and that's the truth behind
That's incredible, huh?
The door to the new world has been opened
The Pandora's box has been opened
That's incredible, huh?
You can say whatever you want if you do it this way
This is an undeniable truth
Amazon is freemason
Freemason is Amazon   -No, no...
Believe it or not, it's up to you
I believe you!
Where are you going?
She explained nothing
Maeda, come on...
He's always doing something backstage
I'll go for zombie time then
Oh no...
My nose is stuffy
My nose is so stuffy
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
Ouch! Ouch! So hot!
Ouch! So hot! Ouch!
Ouch!!!
This is terrible
I have to use this
I have to use this thing from Fujimon
And soda water
To clean my nose
It hurts so badly! Only soda water can save me!
Ouch! My nose hurts so much!
I can't take this anymore...
Is it fine to use soda water?
I believe only soda water can save me from this
Seriously...I have to do this...
My nose is hurting so much...
I have to use soda water...
Ouch! This is just...
This is just...
You guys have to try this
Honestly...
I feel like my head is cracking...
This is absolutely awful...
Shoji brother, please try it with soda water...
Try it with soda water, brother
Ouch...my head hurts...
Ouch...
Are you fine?
I'm fine, please try it, brother
(How did they hold back? Incredible)
An old grandpa...
Are you fine?
Brother...
(Yuriyan is close, but...)
Brother...brother...
Brother...
He laughed!
Why the heck...
He's not moving at all...
I can't take this...
That's incredible!
Phew...   -Come on!
That was funny as hell
Are you fine?
Not fine, huh?
Why are you staying still for so long?
Like an old grandpa
Let's take a look
An old grandpa...
(He's actually already laughing...)
It's cunning to do that at this timing...   -Yeah, but it can’t be helped
Fujimon, you've been this far, last 15 minutes, but...
You're out!
Only 13 more minutes...
Please have a good fight in the remaining time
Got it
Come on...
Why are you staying still...   -You're the one who asked me to do it
Well, yes, but...
Okay, Fujimon, let's go
Quite a lot of you received no card today
3 people are intact
Their defense is so damn strong   -Yes, very strong
Their defense is very strong
If you're not laughing at that, what else will you laugh at?
Huh?
You three girls
So last 13 minutes
Good luck everyone   -Thank you
That's a complete defeat
Female comedians are just too strong
Dodosuko-suko-suko, Dodosuko-suko-suko...
My molars are gone and disappeared
They can perform skits at anytime and anywhere
Oh hey, oh hey, oh Jinnai
That dancing scene and the master
I was saved thanks to Jinnai laughing
Or else, I'll probably be laughing in 10 seconds
Well, I'm actually holding back my laughter all the time
Let's start
It hurts so badly
It's so painful if you put it in your nose
If you put soda water inside...
Is it that painful?
Is it really painful?
I wonder how painful it is though
Shall we give it a try?
You people should try it too
This is a precious chance
How do you do this?
Put it inside your nose
Just squeeze it hard
I'll do it now   -Okay
This is soda water
But he's not stopping at all
Amazing   -Very strong
Isn't it incredible?
There's no need to go this far
Don't push yourself too hard
Amazing
Shoji-san only did it once, and yet...
Please...please...
Did anyone see a ball came rolling?
Ball?
No, I don't think so
Shoji-san...
Eh? He laughed?
Please don't...
Shoji-san, Shoji-san...
Please help her find the ball
(Arghh, he laughed, huh?)
(He did laugh, huh?)
(Shoji brother is out then)
You've been holding back for all this time, but...
Shoji brother...
I just have to say you laughed...
Eh?!
I just have to say so
I didn't laugh
You did laugh
And you tried to muddle through
Yes, like picking his nose...
Shoji-san, Shoji-san...
Please help her find the ball
(What was so...)
(But he did indeed laugh)
Eh? I laughed?   -Yes, you did, you laughed
What was so funny? What happened?
You've been working so hard to get here
I was thinking "what the heck is she doing..."
Shoji brother...
Eh?!   -You're out
Eh? Really?   -It can't be helped
He's still not done yet? It's taking him forever
Why are you so slow, Shoji-san?
Thank you very much
That's unacceptable
No, I wanted to do something for you too, but it can't be helped
I know you've been working so hard for me
And you're bringing so many things with you
I can't help but laugh at Tomochika's performance
And Fujimon's tsukkomi as well
It's gonna come out as a bird
You're saying the wrong joke all the time
Tomochika is really good at acting
Did anyone see a ball came rolling?
Her performances are smoothly brought together
So it's really hard to hold back
Let's start
What should we do?
I not a ball
I thought you're a ball, you look alike with it
The children's sumo
(We're done, this dude is the winner)
(This dude has to be the winner)
Come on, what the heck is this dude doing
You look exactly the same (as children's sumo)
Maeda-kun   -Yes
(This dude is wicked)
You wanna do it? Sumo
She looks the same as the souvenir popular among foreigners
But in opposite direction...
Ah, same now...
(She's showing her boobs so naturally)
So scary...
*Tarepanda is a cute panda character, which literally means a droopy panda
She looks like Tarepanda   -That was amazing
Incredible, she's Tarepanda
Excuse me
Your thing is exposed   -Yeah, it's exposed
Yes?
I'm the lowest level creature on this planet
I knew it
We can totally see that   -You can?
Are you finding a ball?
Yes, I'm finding a ball
Well...
I found a ball over there
Where is it?
Can you please say "Seiya" and cheer for me?   -Eh?
Can you please cheer for me?
Cheer for you?   Yes
How to cheer for you?
(She told you "Eh?" already)
Just shout "Seiya"
Shout it together?
Please shout "Seiya" together
Ready, set...
Seiya!
Please shout it a bit louder
Ready, set...Seiya!
Louder, shout it louder
Ready, set...Seiya!!
There it is
That's not the ball I'm finding...
Not this ball?
Not this one
Not this one?
Not this one, dude
Balls?...
You sure is the lowest of the low, you know there's girls here
Excuse me
That's the ball that I'm finding
Oh, you mean these balls?
Oh?
I fulfilled your desire
You're finding these balls?
What have you been doing with these balls?
Playing with balls, of course
Oh dear
May I invite you to play with my balls?
50 odd
The worst has happened
A bit lower please...   -Forty thirty
(Okay, that's the worst)
Deuce
Advantage
Receive
That's the worst
Yuriyan is coming again
What are you people playing? Ladies and gentlemen?
Oh, who are you?
I'm Machiko
My name is Machiko
Machiko-san?
I'm the niece of the owner here
Niece?
Hey, niece, your back...
Ever since I've been working for Panasonic, I've been busy working every single day
But hey, why aren't you wearing any pants?
Well, umm...
Because I'm the lowest level creature
I knew it
I'm an extremely low level creature
I'll make something for you
Huh?
I said I'll make something for you
Don't tell me that you're trying to steal my customer, huh?
Nope
I don't care if you're working for Panasonic or what
But lies are soon found out
This man is my customer
Don't mess around with me
*Yoshiwara was a famous red-light district in Edo
Machiko-san, you're working at Yoshiwara as well?
Yes, I'm working at Yoshiwara
Many girls put on another face and work here at night
(She admitted it)
(Again...)
It hurts!
Not done yet
Almost done
The game is on
Hold it tight
Hold it tight!
It got recorded, it got recorded already
Nishikawa Mineko-san
"Whoever, please! Have sex with me!"
*Yuriyan is acting the famous scene of Nishikawa Mineko in the movie "Yoshiwara Enjo", where she is a physically and mentally ill prostitute being locked up in a bedroom
*Actual scene: https://twitter.com/i/status/1049321589387345920
Nishikawa Mineko-san's scene
"Here, right here! Bite me, bite me!"
Nishikawa Mineko-san is very emotional here
"Bite me, just bite me!"
The scene in the bedroom   -Yes, in the bedroom
"Please, bite me, please!"
She's very emotional
I'll quit working at Yoshiwara
I'll quit Yoshiwara, and...
Who are you?
(Phew...)
I'll quit Yoshiwara
Shin-san?
I quitted Yoshiwara already!
I quitted Yoshiwara, and now...
I came to here
Just to forget about you
Shin-san?!
You're Shin-san, right?
You must be Shin-san!
Hey, you two are not in the same movie
Not in the same scene
Even if you call me Shin-san, Shin-san...
You are Shin-san
If you say that I am Shin-san
Then maybe I am indeed Shin-san
Ever since you started working at Yoshiwara...
Shin-san!
I won't believe you
I won't believe you!
(Why is Maeda touching his dick?)
It's me!
I won't believe you!
(He's definitely trying to get an erection)
No way, no
Keep walking and the street will open for you
*Gosha Hideo is the director of the movie "Yoshiwara Enjo"
I can totally feel that this is in the world of Gosha Hideo's movies
Keep trying and the mountain will move for you
Someday, your cheeks will sunken and you'll get dimples
Then pour some water to your hollow dimples
Don't stop all of a sudden!
I didn't stop
I won't stop!
I will never stop!
Since the day we met, we are...
(Amazing)
Shin-san...
Phew, that was a wonderful battle
That was truly amazing, huh?
That ending was amazing
Maeda, you definitely tried to get an erection, huh?
This is the first time to have so many people remaining
And there's even 3 people intact
Haruna, Kurosawa, Yuriyan
3 people
Because these 3 people are intact
The person scoring the most points will be the winner
That being said
Today's winner is...
Yuriyan Retriever!
Is it me?
It can't be true!
Excuse me
Well, umm...   -Excuse me
Yeah, because she didn't laugh
Yes, she didn't laugh, and more importantly...
I was astonished by her "Children's sumo"
Her breasts were completely exposed
And it indeed looked like "Children's sumo"   -Yes, it did
Tomochika was very close too, but she won by a hair   -Oh, really?
Yeah, because I laughed
Thanks to you, my sister
Shin-san?
If you say that I am Shin-san
Then maybe I am indeed Shin-san
What the heck is that?
She still has energy left over
Incredible
This is your prize, 10 million yen
I'm so happy! Thank you very much!
I'm happy for you   -Yes, very happy for you
Phew, that's a masterpiece
That is a masterpiece, and this is a kettle (similar pronunciation)
She still has plenty of energy left over!
No way, that's not energy
That's the same as Kanmuri-san
That was so close
Yes...
Well, but there's actually quite a lot of scenes where I almost laughed
Seriously, like the scene between Kanmuri-san and Shoji-san
Huh? What's your name again?
Many people say we look alike
You teased Maeda's dick with your foot, right?   -Yes
What were you thinking about at that time?
50 odd
When I ordered that tennis costume
I asked them to make it like those in vintage porn
The staffs from Amazon came to watch the recording too
They are four foreigners
Throughout the 6 hours, they laughed the hardest at that scene
Oh, so that was actually quite good?
It was funny for foreigners too
Oh, really?
Excuse me
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you very much
Congratulations   -Thank you
I'm so happy
This is my first time to hold so cash in real life...
*The pronunciation of "in real life", Nama, can also be interpreted as "sex without condom"
Although it sounds a bit lewd to say "in real life (nama)"
But I'm so happy
It was really like...umm...the world of dream
Everything was so interesting
I always hang out with Tomochika-san
And she taught me a lot of things
If I didn't always hang out and talk with Tomochika-san
I don't think we'll be able to improvise that Shin-san scene
We always do that kind of things and mess around in private
Although no one else is watching, we always do those things on our own
I can strongly feel them saying like "don't make light of female comedians"
Yuriyan was truly mind-blowing
It's actually okay to let Tomochika win as well, but...
Only the person at the top of this pyramid can take all of the money
Listen carefully
That teenager sumo...
I mean that children's sumo
That children's sumo just made me think "this dude is a true idiot"
They're the same
She looks the same as the souvenir popular among foreigners
But in opposite direction...
Ah, same now...
And for Tomochika, she has been rubbing and teasing Maeda's dick in that tennis look, right?
That's just an adult video
50 odd
Tomochika is just insane, right?