Translated by kentranslations
Timed/Edited by blakeo_x
Alright, the losers are back!
Something cute came slinking in...
And it turned out to be a little dog.
But I actually thought it might
be an exploding robot dog.
Seriously?
I was about to burst out laughing.
I was so embarrassed.
I was like, "this can't be real."
What's with that dog? Did
they train him to smell me?
This dog really likes the smell of urine.
That's really embarrassing.
Please cut that.
He peed!
- He peed!
- A little bit.
What's with that dog?
That's so weird.
I mean, he's cute and all.
He was pretty cute.
I kinda feel bad that we
watched him pee. I mean...
I think I've heard this sound before.
Something's coming.
What? What's coming?
I mean, we...
Okay.
That's good.
That's right.
Everyone is even right now.
Alright.
Some people have seen
this before and some haven't.
Some of them will be like, "This again?"
Others will be wondering
what's about to happen.
Non-chan...
They're getting stained.
It's coming from far away right now.
Let's go.
It's grabbing quite a lot.
Here we go.
Don't drop it.
I wouldn't like that.
This must be tough for Fujimon.
Okay, let's continue.
Once the arm is gone, the egg will...
What was that?!
- What? What broke?
- Damn it!
- The dish is broken!
- The dish broke!
- That's dangerous!
- It flew everywhere!
Hot!
- What was that?
- What was it?
- Fujimoto...
- Why me? Why just me?
That thing was super hot.
What was it?
It was super hot.
That robot...
The worst part was it
stayed there the whole time.
I hate loud sounds the most.
And it went like, "Bang!"
I really hate explosions.
Everyone flinched.
No one can get used to sudden explosions.
- That's true.
- For real.
It was super hot, and
it wouldn't move away.
Let's go again.
No, no.
No way...
No way, no, it's too scary.
No way!
No way! No way!
No way! No way! No way!
No way! I can't!
I can't! I can't!
No! No! No! No!
No! No way!
- Non-chan really hates this.
- No way! I can't handle it!
That's so funny.
What about Shizu-chan?
Go to Shizu-chan.
- No way! I really can't!
- Shizu-chan.
Let's go to Kuro-chan.
I can't! No way!
Go to Kuro-chan.
It'll be surprising if
Kuro-chan can handle it.
Wow!
He's good!
This is...
This is amazing!
Kuro-chan is good!
- Kuro-chan is doing great!
- So scary.
Alright, let's get off.
That's enough.
- Let's fly away.
- Scary, scary!
I can't! No way! No way!
I'm so scared! Seriously!
I just moved instinctively.
Wow, Kuro-chan is amazing.
You sure endured it!
It went into my ear!
Into my ear!
I was so scared! Oh my god!
- What the heck?!
- It was so scary! I can't.
- You two were moving way too much.
- I mean, I couldn't help it.
My body just moved on its own.
- It was instinct.
- I get why Suzuki moved...
- Look! She's crying!
- I can't.
A spider this big appeared!
Out of all the creatures in this world,
I hate spiders the most.
I mean, tarantulas are a no-go.
This is amazing!
Kuro-chan is good!
I guess it's because they move
a little and make rustling sounds.
You can't be doing that! It was so scary.
It's dangerous even.
I need a second. I can
still feel the gross-ness.
I'm fine when they're balled
up, but then they reach out.
Suzuki has already lost her cool.
This must be hell for them.
What's going on here?
Just shower him.
Alright, go back.
Go back, go back.
Thank you.
Okay, good job.
Alright.
Enough?
I'm going crazy!
- You didn't move despite all that.
- I just wanna give up!
That's amazing.
How come Bobby sneezed?
All the powder was coming this way!
You sneezed so suddenly,
everyone started laughing.
What was that?
What was the point of that?
That's not something you
should be allowed to do.
At first, I thought I'd
be able to endure it.
But then I was like, "no way."
I started thinking, "I can't keep
getting showered by this stuff."
Instinctively, my body
wanted to get the powder out.
- Here we go.
- What was that?
Non-chan...
Let's get started.
Let's go to Shizu-chan.
Alright, go to the next one.
Let's do a switcheroo here.
Shizu-chan again.
Go!
Alright.
To someone else.
Round and round.
Yes, round and round.
Let's try Bobby.
Go to Bobby.
Wait a little while.
A few more times.
Again.
Let's do it two more times.
Okay, let's move.
Let's go to someone else.
That's too much. Let's move.
Move, move, move.
What to do...
Should we try Fujimon again?
Let's go to Bobby again. Do him again.
Go back to Bobby. Go back, go back.
Back to Bobby.
Alright, hit it.
Let's go back.
If you're gonna do it, just do it!
If you're gonna do it, JUST DO IT!
Bobby, sit down.
Bobby, let's sit down.
- Sit down for now.
- Let's sit.
Let's sit for now.
Let's sit.
Huh? What?
Good job, everyone.
- Good job.
- It's over?
How was it?
- What do you mean?
- "How was it"?
"How was it", you ask?
No way!
No way! No way!
No way! No way! No way!
Wait a little while.
A few more times.
I mean, personally
I'd love to keep going...
- Let's stop.
- No more.
You're the only one having fun.
Right?
A lot happened, but I made a decision!
What?
The revived loser...
and winner is...
Kuro-chan!
I did it! I did it!
I win!
Kuro-chan is good!
Kuro-chan is doing great!
As expected...
He endured that big spider.
Congratulations.
Wait, you're sticky. It's getting on me.
I was clean...I was clean...
I'm here!
Who are you?
It's Kuro-chan!
You know me, don't you?
That hairstyle!
Translated by kentranslations
Timed/Edited by blakeo_x