Translated by Aika
Timed/Edited by blakeo_x
I thought there was nothing...
that could rival or surpass Documental.
It was an idea that just came to
me when we were having a meeting.
If I can expand the
scope of the project a little,
I think we can make
something worthy of it.
The weakest is the strongest, and
I think you'll agree when you see it.
I'd like to see more than
just comedians competing.
Maybe the most interesting
person in the world
is really the second-most interesting,
and the most interesting person
is the one who does nothing.
Is that it? I think I'm getting
to the point where that's true.
The title of the project is "Freeze."
It's made from the idea of doing nothing.
But I'm sure there will be laughter in it.
I think it'll be...
interesting.
It's Nana Suzuki.
She's dressed up nicely, isn't she?
I don't think this is the kind of
project she needs to dress up for.
I don't know which outfit
is suitable for me, though.
Hi, I'm Nana Suzuki.
It's nice to meet you.
They didn't tell me anything about today.
I didn't know what I
was getting myself into.
So I'm really worried.
I'm really anxious.
I haven't really been told anything.
I'm really nervous.
I'm super nervous right now.
I’m entering.
What is this?
Bobby, huh?
I think he's a timid person.
He's a big guy,
but I think he's timid.
OK, I found a good seat.
I'm comfortable here.
I don’t think I'll have any problems.
I mean, even if I wanted to
react, I wouldn't be able to.
It's easier to be told not to do
anything than to be told to react.
I don't want to sit next to you.
Why not?
Well, you scream.
Non-chan is a bit mysterious to me.
As for not moving, I'm not the type of
person who moves around that much.
I generally spend a lot of time
very still when I'm recording a show.
Are they recording from everywhere?
That’s weird.
Are there any safe angles? I'm exposed.
None at all.
I'm sure they'll record it.
It's OK to move, right?
Yes, you can.
Can we move once we've sat down?
I think he’s another timid one.
To be honest, I'm a bit nervous
about the Amazon project.
I'm assuming I'm going to be frozen.
Yeah.
- What are they going to do?
- I'm scared.
It's like a rich man's game.
A bunch of sociopaths.
You're probably right.
But it's not like that.
What? You scared me!
You scared me!
A little change in the type of people.
Hey!
What's with these boring members?
Hello, I'm Kazumi Morohoshi.
I've heard the title.
It's called "Freeze."
It's definitely an adult prank.
I roughly know what it’s going to be.
We're not boring people.
What do they think of this?
I wonder how well they know each other.
Your clothes are kind of dirty.
No, yours are too damaged.
This is expensive.
No, that’s what unfashionable people say.
How much was it?
Oh, Shizu-chan.
Another boring person.
I think she might be a winning candidate.
It's an Amazon project,
and it's with Matsumoto-san.
So I'm really scared.
I don't know what to do.
Isn't this a great line-up?
I love this line-up.
I can't help it.
Oh, it's Kuro-Chan.
A more boring person came.
In a way, he's quite extraordinary.
What?
Why did you hit me?
Morohoshi-san?
What's the matter? Why did you hit me?
It's Kuro-chan from Yasuda Circus.
You know "freeze", where you
hold up your hands and stop.
That's what they say when
you're pointing a pistol at someone?
That's right.
Are we going to be shot?
That's interesting.
The choice of shirt is interesting too.
Feather patterns.
Hello, I'm Diamond Yukai.
Well, I don't know what this is.
But I'll do my best anyway.
They're not just comedians.
They’re a mix of men and women,
and from different walks of life.
- What will happen?
- I don't know what's going to happen.
- Hi, everyone.
- Oh, he appeared.
- Good morning.
- So, how are you all feeling?
What do you mean how are we feeling?
I have no idea what that means.
We don’t even know what's going to happen.
How well are you today, physically?
- What?
- "Physically"?
Will it be something to do
with our physical condition?
It will be related to your condition.
I want you all to aim to win.
- Win?
- Be ready for anything.
By the way, your heart rate...
I'm measuring it.
You are wearing trackers.
Who do you think has the highest?
Who is it?
There's one person
who's really high right now.
It's Morohoshi.
What?!
You're so nervous.
What? Is that so?
- That's so lame!
- It's really unexpected.
- Did you make a joke because you're nervous?
- That's suspicious.
Kuro-chan's heart rate didn’t go
up at all when Morohoshi hit him.
What?
Why did you hit me?
Morohoshi-san?
What's the matter? Why did you hit me?
Does heart rate have
anything to do with it?
I'm just trying to give you an
idea of what I'm talking about.
But still.
We can't freeze our heart rate.
We'd die.
By the way, Kuro-chan's heart rate suddenly
went up when I said it didn't before.
You can't say such things, Matsumoto-san.
- It's funny.
- It's not cool.
I don't really care. Now, everyone,
today I'd like to ask you all to
compete with very simple rules.
When you hear "freeze", don't move.
That's it.
No matter what happens, don't move at all.
Don't move at all. If
you do that, you'll win.
If you don't move, you win. The person
who doesn't do anything is the best.
No reaction.
And keep it that way
until you hear "release."
Just keep your arms folded.
And your face a little tighter.
Actually, it's better to not talk.
Because your mouth would move.
Something's going to happen, isn't it?
Something might happen.
Of course it will.
So we freeze and fold our
arms? And then release.
If it's a release, you can talk.
This is scary.
I'm really scared.
I'm so nervous.
And, ladies and gentlemen,
there will be a prize for the winner.
One million yen!
- Wow!
- I want it!
One million yen for doing nothing.
- Awesome.
- I want it!
What do you think? I
think it's really easy.
Yeah, you just don't react and
you get one million yen. It's so easy.
That's right.
So, first of all, this is the first stage.
Two of you will be eliminated.
Does that sound okay, Shizu-chan?
You know, I feel like I can keep
from moving. But I'm really sensitive.
Sensitive, huh?
The right breast is more
sensitive than the left.
What is that, stop it.
Fujimon, who do you think
is your strongest opponent?
Who do I think? I think Yukai-san.
Me too a bit. I think he's
one of the favorites to win.
Well, then, I'd like to get started.
I'm scared.
I'm looking forward to it!
- Is it starting?
- Don't worry, we haven't been told to freeze yet.
Oh, not yet?
I really can't.
Will it come suddenly?
Starting. It’s starting.
It’s fine now. We can
talk and move normally.
- We aren’t frozen yet.
- It's too dangerous.
Let's just get it all out now.
Freeze, freeze!
- What's going on?
- Stop it!
- Stop that.
Don't say it.
He's the nervous one.
He's trying to
ease his nerves, so he's joking around.
I'm so scared.
- Is it okay?
- Don't you have to cross your arms?
You freeze. Freeze and cross your arms.
That's it. You should just relax, right?
Well, we’d better get started then.
Here we go.
Why do you freeze now?
No, no, no. What did you say?
Isn't this great?
Good, good.
This is hell.
Well, let's do it then, shall we?
They're doing well.
It's tough, isn't it?
How are the heart rates?
They haven't changed that much yet.
Everyone is doing well freezing so far.
They're doing well.
What was that?!
I can still hear it!
- You did pretty good.
- Hang on, my ears...
You're all moving too much.
The thing is still lit.
- No, no, no!
- It's alright.
It’s alright. That’s different.
I’m scared!
Wait a minute!
Nothing happened.
What?!
- Is that the first thing?
- Something that big?
Basically...
you all moved.
No way!
Would you like to see it a little slower?
Look at Diamond Yukai!
There are people like this!
Morohoshi-san too.
Yukai-san and Morohoshi-san are amazing.
I think it's strange
they didn't move at all.
We did move.
I can't do this either.
I tried to hold back,
but it just came out.
I'll give it back to you.
What was that weird
pause before it exploded?
- What are we going to do? This is only the beginning.
- This is bad.
I tried my best to hold
back, but my voice came out.
I know, I was there.
Bang!
There was a huge bang sound.
I didn't expect such
a level from the start.
I was so scared.
I thought, "isn't this dangerous?"
I wondered if it was really safe.
If it explodes, I think I'll die.
I don't know if the people
watching this will get it.
It's really loud.
Of course we'll move, right?
It's so loud.
It's the kind of thing you throw at a
criminal who's holed up in a building.
Are you easily scared?
I'm very timid.
The other day, I was in the dressing
room with Haranishi, and we were alone.
Haranishi suddenly stood up.
I was so surprised.
Like that.
- That smoke was bad.
- My ears hurt.
- It's bad for the eyes.
- Here we go.
Shizu-chan is good. She’s
got a good expression.
Neither a man nor a woman anymore.
It's a good face.
Well, shall we give it a try?
Let's see who we get.
Bobby's smiling the whole time.
I told him to keep a straight face.
His face is annoying.
I've got an idea.
Let's go to Yukai again.
Turn it up to the max.
Awesome, Yukai.
Yukai is amazing.
Stop laughing!
Bobby, you...
Wait a second, it's hilarious.
It hurt!
Why Yukai-san?
- The rhythmic hitting it was doing was hilarious.
- But it hurts!
The most painful part
is when it scrapes you.
If you do something like that right
in front of me, of course I'll laugh.
What was that?
I don't mind my leg being hit like that.
But the hardest part...
is the scraping!
The shin.
That part almost made me scream.
Does it hurt?
Yes, it hurts.
But every time it hits me,
I can hear them laughing.
Bobby was laughing, wasn't he?
Morohoshi was laughing too, I think.
I thought it was rude of them.
Yeah, rude.
Watching Yukai-san...
I thought it was going to break his leg.
It was going round and
round, hitting from the outside.
I couldn't stop laughing.
I want to see the part where
Yukai-san gets hit again.
Okay, it’s starting.
Why is Yukai-san good at...
I don't think I can do this.
Diamond Yukai, so funny.
Diamond Yukai is so funny!
What the hell?
He's almost like a mannequin.
Okay, let's go to someone else.
Bobby.
I like Bobby.
You've got a good face.
Good.
Nice, nice.
Bobby's holding back.
I think that's good.
Enough of the little
bat. Let's try knives.
It hurts, it hurts!
So scary!
What was that?
No, no, no.
Hang on a minute.
Why wouldn't you move?
Of course you'd move!
I didn't think they'd use a drone.
And they attached a knife.
That’s not right.
How could they hit me?
That has to be an accident.
I never thought drones
would be used like that.
What about the drone?
It came at me like this.
Diamond Yukai, so funny.
Diamond Yukai is so funny!
It's like it's moving around my chin, too.
It's so unpredictable!
No seat changes?
I can't do this.
Please don't put me facing Yukai.
I'd like to change seats.
Fujimon thinks Yukai is
so funny. He's hooked.
I hope you get hurt a bit.
People don't find it funny
when comedians get hurt.
That’s not true.
Now, it's time to move on.
Shi-chan's face right now...
She looks like a news anchor, you know?
It's great.
Let's start...
from the middle.
This isn't good.
I would hate it too.
Let's see if Yukai can endure it.
Go to Morohoshi.
Looking good.
Makes me want to shoot him.
Shall we?
Morohoshi is good. Amazing.
Fujimon is so afraid.
Let’s go back to Morohoshi again.
Don't let him rest.
Oh, stop it! I can't do it anymore!
This is impossible!
It's too much.
Impossible.
I seriously can't do it.
No way. I'm going crazy.
You're too scared, Fujimon-san. Just a
little change in angle and you freak out.
Is this possible?
Wait a minute, please.
What?
Please stop it.
Ladies and gentlemen...
The first stage of the
competition has come to an end!
However,
two of you have been eliminated.
The worst was...
Fujimon!
You moved too much.
No, you’re supposed to move!
You need to tolerate it.
It's normal to move!
People who don't move
are crazy, seriously.
This was the most terrifying
moment of my life.
And now, one more person.
It was very close, but...
Kuro-chan is out!
Me?!
That’s unexpected.
- Because of the drone.
- Yes, he moved from it.
The knife hit me between my eyebrows.
Also, Yukai is so good.
He's so strong.
I think Yukai and Morohoshi
are very strong opponents.
Whenever Yukai-san has
something done to him, it's so funny.
It makes me laugh.
Here it is.
Diamond Yukai is so funny.
So, I'll leave you two,
Fujimon and Kuro-chan.
Everyone else, please
move to the second stage.
It's weird. The pistol
aimed at me so many times.
- It pointed at everyone.
- No, it faced me a lot more often.
So we just sit here?
That's right.
We've been eliminated.
Hey, get rid of this too.
Take this back quickly.
You know, when something bangs
in front of you, won’t you move?
Can you really not?
No, it's a big surprise.
No, just take it away quickly!
It was definitely frustrating.
The explosion and the gun
pointing at me were the worst.
I was scared to reach the goal.
The main reason I lost is probably
that the goal was taking so long.
I think I tried really hard.
I did my best.
Too much happened, more than I expected.
Translated by Aika
Timed/Edited by blakeo_x