Subbed by
Mickstar813
(Team Gaki)
&
HouseiGIFs
Gaki no Tsukai's
Legendary Project
Silent Library
Gaki no Tsukai, the legendary game, Silent Library!
They must endure
a variety of punishments
without letting out a sound
------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------
Silent Library
The game where you must receive various punishments without making any noise!
Narrator:
Yamada
Shinichi
After an 8-year absence,
it's revived!!
-----------------------------------------------------
After an 8-year absence,
it's revived!!
Please turn off your mobile phone
Politics
History
Whispering forbidden
Hobbies
Travel
Please be quiet in this room
Lending Reception
Return slot
Azuma Mikihisa
We've got to be quiet, alright?
Yes...
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tsukitei
Housei
Forehead
Flick
From who?
Forehead
Flick
Person who picks the card with the skull gets the punishment written on the card
-----
Azuma
---------
Endo
Hamada
Housei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready, set...
-----
Azuma
Azuma Mikihisa
Flick Forehead
Sh
Be quiet, be quiet.
To make sure you're not being a pain for the people around you, you must be quiet
even when receiving the punishment
From all of us
Be quiet
Ow! What was that?
You really suck at that, you can't do it at all!
The shit ones hurt the most though
The shit ones really do hurt the most
I'm so scared...
His bone hit...
his bone hit just now
I'm scared
It's meant to be a "forehead flick", you know?
Really?
Don't make a sound, shh...
They'll get angry with us
Is it okay?
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
The members get punished! The latest episode of Silent Library!
Strike Ass
With Bat
Person who picks the card with the skull gets the punishment written on the card
---------
Tanaka
-----
---------
Azuma
Endo
Hamada
Housei
Matsumoto
Ready, set
---------
Tanaka
Shh
Strike Ass With Bat
Tanaka
To make sure you're not being a pain for the people around you, you must be quiet
even when receiving the punishment
OWWW!!
Be quiet!
We're in a library, be quiet
You're being too loud
But that was like seriously...
That was like properly serious, right?
That was fantastic
Did it hurt?
Yes it did
Can we see your butt?
You're kidding me...
Okay?
Holy shit
That's so bad
How was it?
It's better you don't see it...
Red as...
Just red
It was so red
Lending Reception
Return slot
Trembling
Earbuds
What? What is that?
---------
Matsumoto
-----
---------
Azuma
Endo
Hamada
Housei
Tanaka
Ready, set
---------
Matsumoto
Shh
Trembling Earbuds
I just knew it was going to be me, just now
What is this though, trembling?..
So you just put it on, right?
------------------------------
Remote Control Switch
Is it connected?
Ow...
Well then, Hamada-san
The switch, if you would
Ow ow ow ow! Stop it, stop it!
Ow ow ow ow! Stop it!
Ow ow ow!
That much?
It hurts so much!
Does it?
It hurts so much
Be quiet
I hate punishments we've never done before
I know
Eyeball
Clothespins
What? Enough man...
Let's just stop with this painful thing...
I'm so tired
So tired...
-----
Azuma
---------
Endo
Hamada
Housei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready, set
-----
Azuma
Yes!
Azuma Mikihisa
Eyeball Clothespins
Shh
OK, OK...
Eyeball
Clothespins
What is this?
Eyeball
Clothespins
What are they going to do to me?
Eyeball
Clothespins
It's the first time?
Yeah
Eyeball
Clothespins
I have no idea
We've never heard of this
First time ever?
Yeah...
Huh?
Where?
There
Here?
Sit still
Ow, ow, ow...
It hurts
Ouch!
That hurt too
We're doing the other one?
It hurts
It really does hurt
Does it hurt?
My eye lid hurts
Are you okay?
Oh, we're meant to do it sideways?
Oh, you're doing it wrong?
Who cares if it's sideways or straight up?
Ow!
Yeah
Can you close your eyes?
Oh you're going like that?
Oww...
Ah, it hurts...
Are you okay?
No no, don't move it, please
Please
Wait, wait. Close your eyes
Oh, this one too?
This one hurts loads too
Are you okay?
The left one is tight
My left eye seriously...
Are you okay?
I said please don't shake me...
When are we going to end this?
My left eye...
Hamada-san...
How much longer?
My left eye hurts so much, seriously.
Shall we take it off?
Can you?
You should look straight ahead...
That must have hurt a lot
All the punishments have been to my face...
Yeah, they're killing your face
It's down to luck...
Kid
Graffiti
What the hell is that?
This is scary too, I have no idea what could happen
Ready, set
---------
Hamada
-----
---------
Azuma
Endo
Housei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
---------
Hamada
Kid Graffiti
Shh
Yes, yes...
No idea what they're going to do to you
This is really scary
Go for it
Unlucky...
That was a good one
It's not even about that anymore...
Vinegar
Facial
Device
Vinegar
Facial
Device
Wait, what the hell is that..?
No no no
-----
Azuma
---------
Endo
Hamada
Housei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready, set
-----
Azuma
Azuma Mikihisa
Shh
Vinegar Facial Device
Everything to his face
His face is literally...
A vinegar facial device...
Put your face here...
Put it here
More, right up against it
Yeah, like that
Yeah, yeah
It's coming, it's coming now
It's a facial device after all...
Fac-...
Put his face closer
Shut the hell up!
Wait, what?
Quiet!
I'm sorry
Be quiet
You okay?
Are you okay?
That was seriously...
All of it
Damn that stinks!
You breathed it all in?
Yeah
You breathed in vinegar?
God, that smell.
You really start to shake like that?
Yes, you do
Oh man, that's tough
Piping Hot
Shumai
Glasses
* Pork Dumplings
Be quiet, guys
Piping Hot
Shumai
Glasses
* Pork Dumplings
Here you go
---------
Hamada
-----
---------
Azuma
Endo
Housei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready, set
---------
Hamada
Get in!
* Pork Dumplings
Hamada
Piping Hot Shumai Glasses
Shh
Alright
Hamada-san
Can you sleep on here like this?
Your head somewhere around here
You're kidding me, right?
Oh come on, I don't want to, what is this?
Maybe a bit more this way...
Yeah, around here
"Piping Hot Shumai Glasses"
* Pork Dumplings
Wait, what is this?
What? Oh my God!
This is bad!
You're kidding me!
Wait, what is it?
This is dangerous, you may want to close your eyes
Wait, what?
It's Shumai
There's shumai on the lenses
Don't take the piss, man!
This is so scary!
Scary, scary, scary!
Shit! It's hot!
Hamada-san!
Hamada-san
We're in a library
It's hot, it's hot!
It's so hot!
It's hot, it's really really hot!
It's hot! It's hot! It's hot!
Hamada-san, please be quiet
As it is a library, please can you be quiet?
It hurts so much...
After This
What punishments await the members!?
This is hot, this is really hot
But this is just the start
The members have been squealing from the punishments thus far
And before we show the continuation
Let's show the punishments the members have
endured in the past
let's look at some past punishments!
-----------------------------
Aired 2001.06.03
Stop RC Car
With Forehead
-------
-------------
Endo
Hamada
Heipo
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Yamasaki
Ready, set
Matsumoto
Shh
Stop RC Car With Forehead
Snake On Back
Just let me mentally prepare myself...
Please be safe
Ready, set
-------
-------------
Endo
Hamada
Heipo
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Yamasaki
Endo
Shh
Snake On Back
Come on...
I can't do it
Yamasaki, you do it
Wait, wait, wait...
Not yet
Wait, wait, wait
---------------------------------
Aired 2002.09.29
Nose Flute
Whistle
--------
Hamada
-------
--------
Endo
Heipo
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Yamasaki
--------
Hamada
Nose Flute Whistle
Shh
Leather Belt Slapping
-------
Yamasaki
--------
Endo
Hamada
Heipo
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready, set
-------
Yamasaki
Leather Belt Slapping
Shh
Yamasaki
It was the same for me before, once you get it, you get it consecutively.
Whoa!!
Damn, it's fast
Even at that speed, it's going to hurt like hell, it's leather after all
Yeah, it's leather
Ready, set
Ow!
---------------------------------
Aired 2004.04.25
Huge balloon..?
Ernesto Hoost (K-1 Fighter)
Ernesto
Huge Balloon
Shh
Ernesto
Huge Balloon
Shh
Stand up, stand up...
OK.
Start.
Oh damn, that's scary, damn
And this silent library game became a huge hit around the world
and has been played in 20 countries!
Bob haircut
Drop a book on hand
Towing vehicle
Like this, the Silent Library game has made its way around the world!
---------------------------
Azuma Mikihisa
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Number of times they've been punished
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Housei
In this episode's Silent Library
The results are as you see on your screen
What will happen to the members!?
Drink Green
Tea Powder
Via Funnel
You guys are really...
I know
You guys, seriously, cut it out already
It really pisses me off
I know
Be quiet, guys
Brazilian
Nose Hair
Wax
Damn, this?
I can't, man...
Brazilian
Nose Hair
Wax
I'm begging you...
-----
Azuma
---------
Endo
Hamada
Housei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready, set
-----
Azuma
You're kidding me?
Azuma Mikihisa
Brazilian Nose Hair Wax
Shh
This is scary
What?
For real?
Nothing you can do about it
Oh, they've got a professional to do it
Oh, a real professional.
Ow, ow...
They actually do this as well...
Damn it's hot
Is it hot?
She's shoved this like right up there but is that okay?
She won't reply or anything
Quiet
Ouch
Ow, ow, it hurts...
Oww.
Until it hardens
We need to wait
You guys, like seriously
No no
Right?
Yeah, it's a problem
We've just been lucky though
Yeah
You have to do one punishment at least...
We can't do anything about it...
since we haven't picked the skull card at all
Matsumoto-san, do you want to pull that one out?
Ready, set
Holy shit!
It's all on there
Yeah
Please don't show it
So embarassing...
Yeah, it is, I guess
There was some weird stuff on it...
It is a bit embarassing
There was weird stuff all over it, huh?
I've had so much weird stuff put in me, so loads of weird stuff came out
Loads of stuff came out from inside
Next Week
Secret
Finale!!
Silent Library
Secret
Will they be able to endure the punishments?
Will they be able to not scream at the even harsher punishments?
Secret
And the man who's been punished the most...
What will be the fate of Azuma Mikihisa?
Stay tuned!