DTR Subs
http://dtr-subs.tumblr.com
Translation by typesoshee
Typesetting by DuckToaster
Proofreading by Oolong
April 6, 2003
Gaki No Tsukai Dressing Room
Hey.
Hello.
Everyone: Hello.
Again?
You know what this is, right?
If I'm dressed like this.
No, I mean...
We've done this a few times before, right?
Yes.
Wait, could it be?
Yeah, the duo partner has asked me again.
Again?
Don’t say “Again?” with that attitude.
But, I mean...
What does he want to do this time?
This time...
it's weightlifting.
Why?
Weightlifting?
Why does he want to do that?
Right?
Weightlifting challenge!!
This time, Matsumoto has set his sights on a world record in weightlifting.
The world record in weightlifting at the time was 212.5 kilograms!!
At the time, the world record in weightlifting was
212.5 kilograms, by Hossein Rezazadeh of Iran.  However...
What he wants to lift is 220 kilograms.
To beat the world?
7.5 kilograms more?
A new world record.
But I will say,
you have to put in your effort.
He’ll get angry again if he doesn’t like your attitudes. Like before, he’ll just quickly leave.
No, we'll give it our best. But if he, himself, doesn't put the effort in,
we'll get pissed off, too.
That’s true.
Yeah.
But we’ll do it, for you, Hamada.
Yes.
Sorry about this. Help me out.
Once again, the four have stepped up for Matsumoto.
Matsumoto Hitoshi - the 220 kilogram weightlifting challenge.
220kg New World Record Challenge!!
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Weightlifting Snatch
Matsumoto Hitoshi - the 220 kilogram weightlifting challenge.
If we could just do it in one shot, and get it done.
Yes.
That's true.
If we could just do it in one shot, and get it done.
And keep him happy.
Right.
That's true.
No point in dragging it out.
Yes.
But this is tough.
This is quite a lot.
The world record really is amazing.
212kg, right?
He's here.
Huh?
Hey.
Hello.
We’ve already talked it over and we’re ready.
Yes.
We’re ready.
Um, well,
To be honest
I don’t feel like being involved with you anymore.
Excuse me?
I don’t intend to be involved with you
on TV anymore.
But for this kind of thing, I don’t mind being involved for your sake.
Since the only ability you have is to lift me up.
Because you’re maggots that can’t turn into flies.
Matsumoto's 1st Attempt!!
Matsumoto's first attempt.
Ok. Let's go.
Come on.
He’s gone limp.
Yes, he's gone really limp.
He’s completely limp.
Come on.
Hold it.  What the hell?
You have to at least hold it.
You can't even freaking hold it?
Fasten it.
Geez.
Hold it. Geez.
Ok, put that on.
Ok.
There’s no way he'll go up like this.
Bring him up. Excuse me. Ok, ok.
Lift the barbell with the buoyancy of a giant balloon
Ok, in one shot.
Even his neck is completely limp.
Ok, start it, please.
Ok.
Lift it up.
All right.
Go up.
In one shot.
Go up, go up.
220, 220.
Lift it up.
Go up, go up.
In one shot.
He tried to lift it a bit.
Yes, a bit.
He tensed up a bit there.
We almost had something.
This is good.
You know what I think? His posture wasn't good.
That's true.
He's gripping it well but he can't go up like this.
He’s got to get around here.
Right, with a better hold.
Right?
Oh, we have that.
Should we do that?
Let’s do these.
Yeah.
Can we put them on while he’s lying down? I don't think so.
In any case, let's stand him up normally.
Ready and go.
You can't stand up normally?
Hamada... Hamada...
Huh?
He’s really staring at me.
He’ll probably jerk up really hard.
Lift him via his reaction to electric stimulation
As a reaction to it.
Yeah.
Ok, this should turn it on.
In one shot.
Good, good.
He's, he's trying to, he's trying to lift it, he's trying to lift it.
I think he's going to lift it. He's going to lift it.
I think he's going to lift it.
Go for it!
Lift it!
It's going up!
Lift it! Lift it! Lift it! Lift it!
Lift it.
What is it?
Wait.
Matsumoto gets angry and goes backstage
Matsumoto.
So he can walk with those.
What was wrong with that?
That went well, didn't it?
It wasn't just one jerk like last time. He was trying to lift it over and over.
He got angry.
Yeah, he got angry.
Yeah, he got angry at the end.
Let's go see him then.
He was really close to lifting it.
Right?
We're working really hard, too.
They go to the dressing room to see how Matsumoto is doing.
Matsumoto was carving a wooden Nandaro*.
*Note: Nandaro is a mascot of Nippon TV, which is the TV network that Gaki No Tsukai airs on.
We had two other things planned that we thought might work, but…
What do you want to do?
The world record…
Yes. 220...
Yes.
What happened back there,
People will think I’m being played around with.
That’s not what we're trying to do.
Yes, we're trying to come up with things.
Yes.
That's our intention.
If you’re just gonna screw around, then get out of here!!
Also,
when you're doing things to me
I’ll be staring at all of you.
So don't say things like,
“He’s really staring.”
Matsumoto's 2nd Attempt!!
Matsumoto's 2nd attempt.
... and he'll try to lift it.
Here he is.
Let's go.
Yes, yes.
Yes, sir.
Prepare the next, that, the set up.
Ok.
You're wearing gloves so
I don't think you need the powder.
Ok.
Really?
Ok. Ok.
This is fine, right?
His head goes on that side. Facing up.
Ok, facing up.
Yeah. No, not like that.
What the hell?
This should work.
There we go.
This will..
Right?
This will be fine.
With this much going on, yeah.
Gloves.
Here.
Here we go. Ready and...
Go.
Good, good. Good, good.
Ok, good, good.
He got it.  Ok, the camera.
He got it.
Flip the camera.
Yes.
Hang Matsumoto and shoot the camera upside-down.
It's a success!
Yay!
A complete success!
His face!
Oh, wow. His face adds realism to it.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
It looks real.
This is really good, right?
Great.
Slowly, slowly.
Ok.
Lowering him.
Yay.
It's a success.
I think it was completely successful.
Let's watch it together.
Yeah, see it again.
Let's rewind it and watch it together.
Let's watch it.
The playback.
Matsumoto gets angry and goes backstage again.
Huh?
Matsumoto?
Didn't that go well?
It was completely good.
It was good, no matter how you look at it.
Why is he angry, then?
Yeah, he was angry.  He kicked this and then left.
It was perfectly done.
They go to the dressing room to see how Matsumoto is doing, again.
It was perfect.
If we showed that to him, it should be fine.
There'll be no reason for him to get angry at us.
Excuse us.
Matsumoto was eating nagashi-somen*.
*Note: Nagashi-somen is a food activity where somen (a type of noodle) flows down water in a bamboo to be caught by diners.  It is usually done outdoors during the summer.
In terms of the visuals, that should have been decent, I think.
It was.
It was, yes.
So... um... what..., what is it that you, um.
So, what... um.
Is it that you want to bully me or something?
No, we don't intend for that, right?
Yes.
When you watch me
you can easily tell that I'm
straining in pain.
From my face.
So when that happens, like
"Oh, Matsumoto is... can someone... he's in pain."
"Is Matsumoto ok?" Nothing like that
happens, right? That's just unbelievable, you know.
That's what I'm saying.
It's dull to talk about this but right at the start
The velcro, the rough side, on my thighs hurt a little.
You put the smooth side on the skin.  That's what I would have done, if I was doing it.
But you guys purposely put the jagged side,
all jagged and all on my skin. It's a dull thing but it hurts.
We have to do that, since you won't really grip it.
You can blame me for not gripping it.
Will you grip it next time, then?
Will you grip it next time properly?
So what I'm talking about is, not whether I'll grip it or not, but
Why was I put into that kind of situation and prepared to that extent and completely trifled with!
You're all responsible!!
I'm the one who
No, that's not it.
I don't want to have a long argument about this, so if you apologize to me and say you'll turn over a new leaf, then anytime,
I'll go back into the ring, back into the dojo.  That's what I intend.
If we become the bigger man and apologize...
What's that, Tanaka?
Should we apologize?
We will apologize.
Then go ahead.
Yes.
We will turn over a new leaf and do our best. We apologize.
We apologize.
This guy didn't apologize.
My bad.
Ok.
Matsumoto's 3rd Attempt!!
Matsumoto's 3rd attempt.
Let's go. Let's do this.
Ok, please.
Yes, please.
All right, let's go.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
Let's go.
Lie down face up.
No, no.
It's the other way.
You can't do that for everything.
Ok.
Face up.
Ok, yes.
His legs, his legs.
Is this wrong?
Like this.
Ok, that's good.
That's good.
Ok, start it, please.
Please.
All right, this will definitely work.
Winch him up on an incline.
Good, good.
That's good.
It's going up.
Wow.
Yes!
A complete success!
Ok!
Let me down.
Ow. Ow, ow. Let me down.
Can you... Let me down. Can you... Let me down.
Can you let me down? Can you let me down? Can you let me down?
Can you lower him a bit? Ok, lower him a bit. Yeah.
Can you... Can you... Can you...
Until his feet touch the ground or so.
Yeah, that's good.
Ok.
How's this? It looks like you're lifting it.
No. No. No.
All right!
Nice!
It looks like you're lifting it.
Huh?
He's walking with the stoppers.
Matsumoto gets angry and goes backstage, yet again.
He's not going to skate with them at all.
It looked clean, right?
It was fine.
Yeah, it looked clean.
It was better than the upside-down one, right?
Much better.
Easier for him, too.
It wasn't good enough?
They go to the dressing room to see how Matsumoto is doing, yet again.
Gee, what is it.
What is the problem?
It's difficult.
Matsumoto was playing mahjong with his buddies.
Wow, all this smoke.
What an old mahjong board.
They're really into it.
Ready hand!
Man, that's fast.
Who are they?
I don't know.
Mahjong buddies.
Mahjong buddies, right?
Mahjong!
Seriously? Seriously?
That was kind of slow.
Ready hand, all simples, no-points hand
One
shot
dora
That's a haneman!*
*Note: These are Japanese Mahjong terms.  Matsumoto won the game with a high score.
You've never played.
I see.
What do you all want?
Was that not good, visually?
What I'm saying is, can you not tell when your duo partner is in pain?
In pain? Well...
The thing is, you all
To be honest, don't have love for me.
Tell me how much
you like me, all of you.
Make an analogy between me and a fruit.
Endo.
Yes.
A strawberry.
Right?
Make an analogy between me and a kitchen equipment.
A sponge?
What?
A sponge.
Ok.
Hey, Hamada.
Yes.
Sing WOW WAR TONIGHT*.
*Note: WOW WAR TONIGHT is a 1995 pop song by Hamada.
Sing it.
Why do I have to sing?
If you feel you were wrong, sing it. Hurry up.
I'd like to sometimes have a drink, side-by-side, like this
And sto-
Sing it with more energy.
Like when you did it for Kohaku*!
*Note: The Kohaku Utagassen is an annual music show (akin to a Grammy Awards concert).
Do it.
I'd like to sometimes have a drink, side-by-side, like this
And have a stop over, just for a bit
That's enough.
Let's go, then.
Yes.
Hold on.
Do an impression as you leave.
Tanaka, do Saigo Takamori*.
*Note: Saigo Takamori is a 19th century historical figure.
A Saigo Takamori impression?
Hurry and do it, hurry. While you're worrying about it, just do it.
How do I?
I am-
That's enough!
Matsumoto's 4th Attempt!!
Matsumoto's 4th attempt.
We've been through a lot so far, but for the end,
Yes.
Let's power through.
I agree.
Shall we do this?
Let's do it.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Like before, put your hands on there.
Mmmn...
His eyes are closed.
What do you mean, "Mmmn?"
Mmmn...
What do you mean, "Mmmn?" Put your hands there.
Sit up. Sit up.
Ok.
Here.
Good, good.
I think we're good.
Let's give him some good posture.
Blow dart
Good posture.
I don't want this...
Ow!
Now's the time!
He got up! He got up! He got up!
All right, let's go. Get underneath. Let's go.
Everyone, come in. Get everyone in.
Ready and
Go.
Using a long bar, lift with everyone.
Go. Go.
Stand up.
Yes.
220kg New World Record Achieved!!
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Weightlifting Snatch
Overcoming many hardships,
Matsumoto amazingly achieved a new world record in weightlifting.
A true congratulations to you.
Yama-chan,
why don't you give him some good posture.
Yes, yes.