Ignore this line
0 0 m -301.25 -66.625 b -311.875 -68.125 -341.125 -66.625 -338 -42.625 b -339.5 -29.125 -310.375 -2 -302.75 -0.625 b -290.5 7.5 -285.875 -2 -278.125 -3.625 b -269 -12.625 -259.75 -15.625 -250.625 -38.125 b -247.5 -59.125 -267.5 -60.625 -269 -62 b -281.25 -68.125 -292 -66.625 -301.25 -66.625 m -293.5 -59.125 b -279.75 -62 -261.25 -53.125 -264.375 -44.125 b -275.125 -56.125 -284.375 -56.125 -293.5 -59.125 m -371.75 -191.125 b -365.625 -191.125 -313.5 -180.625 -321.125 -111.625 b -331.875 -68.125 -361 -47 -370.25 -42.625 b -374.875 -41.125 -399.375 -21.625 -433.125 -53.125 b -440.75 -68.125 -456.125 -84.5 -445.375 -122 b -440.75 -137 -433.125 -165.625 -405.5 -182 b -397.875 -186.625 -385.625 -194.125 -371.75 -191.125 m -233.75 -194.125 b -230.625 -194.125 -193.75 -204.5 -161.625 -149.125 b -157 -135.625 -144.75 -119.125 -152.375 -77 b -161.625 -42.625 -176.875 -41.125 -186.125 -38.125 b -193.75 -38.125 -204.5 -29.125 -241.375 -54.5 b -253.625 -65.125 -272 -71.125 -279.75 -113.125 b -278.125 -113.125 -296.625 -140.125 -258.25 -182 b -250.625 -188.125 -242.875 -194.125 -233.75 -194.125 m -374.875 -144.5 b -417.75 -137 -393.25 -90.625 -373.25 -95.125 b -367.125 -95.125 -353.375 -98.125 -350.25 -119.125 b -354.875 -143.125 -364.125 -141.625 -374.875 -144.5 m -374.875 -131.125 b -365.625 -134.125 -361 -122 -362.5 -119.125 b -362.5 -107 -371.75 -107 -376.375 -107 b -382.5 -108.625 -385.625 -114.5 -384 -122 b -384 -125.125 -381 -131.125 -374.875 -131.125 m -371.75 -125.125 b -376.375 -123.625 -374.875 -117.625 -371.75 -117.625 b -368.75 -117.625 -365.625 -123.625 -371.75 -125.125 m -223 -144.5 b -256.75 -138.625 -241.375 -92 -223 -96.625 b -216.875 -95.125 -201.5 -98.125 -201.5 -125.125 b -206.125 -143.125 -218.375 -144.5 -223 -144.5 m -223 -131.125 b -203 -131.125 -209.125 -107 -219.875 -107 b -223 -105.625 -235.25 -108.625 -232.125 -122 b -232.125 -125.125 -230.625 -131.125 -223 -131.125 m -219.875 -125.125 b -224.5 -122 -221.375 -116.125 -218.375 -117.625 b -213.75 -119.125 -216.875 -125.125 -219.875 -125.125 m -377.875 -117.625 b -381 -117.625 -379.375 -113.125 -377.875 -113.125 b -376.375 -113.125 -374.875 -117.625 -377.875 -117.625 m -224.5 -116.125 b -227.5 -116.125 -226 -111.625 -224.5 -111.625 b -223 -111.625 -221.375 -116.125 -224.5 -116.125 m -456.125 -218.125 l -143.125 -218.125 l -143.125 86.875 l -456.125 86.875 m -146.25 -215.125 l -453.125 -215.125 l -453.125 84 l -146.25 84
TPF
The first challenge of Gaki no Tsukai ya arahende, tiki tiki, risk your life for tasting Green Tea and get hundred thousand yen!
Let's do it!
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
This is the 37th installment.
That's certainly alot
Tsukitei Hosei
Yama-chan, the last time you got it right was 11 years ago
"Miso soup" in 2004 was the last time he got the right answer
It's been more than a decade...
A decade is a way too long time ago
But today we are already promising
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Are we?
Simulation done by staff : 1 out of 3 got the right answer
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
According to the simulation done by staff, 7 out of 21 got the right answer
So 1 out of 3 got it right
What the hell is this? Looks fancy
Its price is 20 thousand yen
20 thousand?!
The cheapest one is 57 yen?
If we mistake take this as that, this fancy one will lose it's face
They have to find the right green tea out of 12 brands
The rule is pretty simple. They have to find the right green tea out of 12 brands
100 thousand yen prize
If they're correct
Who will get it?!
A hundred thousand yen goes to the challenger who gets it right. Who's gonna get it?
The first challenger
Endo Shozo
The first challenger is Endo.
His green tea is "Gyokuro-iri Ocha" by Pokka Sapporo
This tea was steeped with low temperature water to reduce bitterness and promote mildness. Can he remember its flavor?
I don't think it's too strong.
Accuracy Rate: Out of 37 challenges  4 have been correct
Here I go...
You're likely to succeed. 1 out of 3 got it right
Yeah if I get the right answer,
I will keep getting one after another
But the Gaki staff are a bunch liars
No they aren't
If it was a lie...
Usually I drink this one only
Healthier...
So you can recognize the taste of it?
Yes I can recognize the taste of Healthier
You really are eager to burn your fat, eh?*
*(The Green Tea Endo prefers is a diet type)
Yes I really want to burn my fat
But it's not good to drink that kind of tea too much, so sometimes I drink this
He's desperate
Since you have a girlfriend
Endo's challenge
Remaining 12 / 12
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
I'm gonna try my usual one, Healthier, which I had this morning
Kaou
[Healthier Green Tea]
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
He's gonna get it right
He'd recognize it
Undoubtedly he'd recognize that one
This one is totally different
This is not the one
Now tasting
Correct Answer
Fail it!
The one I had was not Healthier
Correct!!
This is obviously different. Now then...
造 He is disposing an empty bottle
I wouldn't mind if he got the buzzer
You will get buzzer eventually
It's a good occasion, so may I try this 20-thousand-yen tea?
Endo's challenge
Remaining 11 / 12
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
20 thousand yen for 750 ml
Royal Blue Tea Japan
[King of Green MASA premium]
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
Seriously?
Now tasting
Correct Answer
It doesn't have any scent at all
The taste though...must be special
He doesn't have any sense of smell...
Here I go
Oh wow, so this is the taste...
I guessed as much
Does it taste like soup?
What the hell...
I guess it tastes like soup, right?
I believe he is younger than me...*
*( Housei is pissed because Endo ignored him even though he's a junior. In Japan people should respect their elders.)
Yes he is. I'm sure he heard you
It's so strong!
It absolutely is
Its color is pretty weak though
Seriously
It can't be it then
What I drank was not "King of Green MASA Premium"!
Correct!!
It was way too easy. Okay, now I'm gonna check the weak ones
Endo's challenge
Remaining 10 / 12
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
I have tried this, and this one too...
I suppose you have
It must be tough if you have never tried it
I think it must be something I have never had before, and it tasted weak
If I pick weak ones, this 93 yen Family Mart's, and 73 yen AEON
Correct Answer
Don Quixote...57 yen. These three are doubtful
He's gonna describe everything so he can be on TV as much as he can
He goes on explaining all of them
Is that what he wants?
He's definitely thinking "I want to be On Air"
By giving all the information?
His girlfriend must have told him
"get more screen time" or something like that
You will see me being cool, honey!
Now tasting
Correct Answer
Endo's challenge
Remaining 7/ 12
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
Pokka Sapporo, Gyokuro-iri Ocha
Correct
Pokka Sapporo
[Gyokuro-iri Ocha]
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
Steeped with low temperature water to reduce bitterness and promote mild flavor
Correct Answer
Now tasting
Weak...
It tastes weak
Though it is weak,I think the one I had had a bit more bitterness. So it's not the one
Oh that's a tough one
The one I drank was not Gyokuro-iri Ocha by Pokka Sapporo!
Incorrect!!
Oh god, is this the one?!
Here he comes. Face that guy
Both your brain and taste are crap!
I clearly heard that
Ouch ouch ouch it hurts
It makes me feel like pooping
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents
Down Town's Gaki no tsukai ya arahende!!
The next challenger is Hamada
Second challenger
Hamada Masatoshi
Hamada san has been getting the right ones so often
He's been connected with staff way too much
He is really a dirty comedian and a dirty TV star
That's nasty!
No way!
I haven't got the right ones for years
He's the first crappy TV star in Japan
Hamada's one is "Takkumiya Umami no Nihon-cha" by Asahi
It was released last April. It has authentic green tea's sweet and rich flavor
The closest one is always Matsumoto-san, right?
Accuracy Rate: Out of 37 challenges  6 have been correct
I am so sensitive about it.
Right hand please...
Pull out your right hand!
Right hand...
It's gonna be so long
Ok you got it
Don't say if you are not holding it!
You said right hand, so I just tried to reach this way
You are talking to Tanaka now
I wasn't there anymore
We've been drinking it too much... right?
It's not bitter at all...
Do you think you have tried it before?
I don't remember
Then...
You have never tried it then
Hamada's challenge
Remaining 12 / 12
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
I have had "Oi Ocha" and "Iemon" before
I'm gonna try Iemon
Suntory
[Iemon]
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
So his first choice is iemon...
I have drunk this before
Try it once and compare
Correct Answer
Now tasting
It's so close...sorry it's the first one though
Oh boy, it's super close!
If I can mention any difference, it would be the after taste
I wonder if that one left that strong of a taste
It's gone so smoothly...
HEY!!!
If I got it wrong, I wouldn't complain. I just got the one by the first attempt
I'm gonna go
I have no choice
What I drank was....
Iemon!!
Incorrect!!
Was it that similar though?
You got it by the first attempt
You gotta be careful
Can you taste nothing but banana flavor!?
You Gorilla Comedian
Say it clearly!
Hey, say it properly
That guy cracked me up
It hurts!!
It's like Thai Kick!
Is this the right one? It was super close
Yes it is
Correct Answer
It was the right one
It might be this one...
It is the correct one
The third challenger
Tanaka Naoki
The next challenger is Tanaka.
Tanaka's one is "AEON Top Value Ichibancha-iri Ryokucha"
It is sold in all AEON stores throughout in Japan. It has smooth, refreshing flavor
Here I go!
Accuracy Rate: Out of 37 challenges  4 have been correct
It's so strong!
Strong?
Yes it is.
I suspected the flavor of the tea to be weaker?
He's started to doubt the tea flavor itself
Each person feels differently
He's suspecting the tea
They have been waiting for us over there
Kobayashi Hiromitsu
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Producer Dancers
Oh really?
They must have told
their bar hostess that they will be on TV
Nakamura san...
Remaining 12 / 12
Tanaka's challenge
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
I'm gonna try this one which nobody has tried so far
Kobayashi-en' s "Cha"
Kobayashi-en
[Cha]
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
Now tasting
Correct Answer
Wrong!
Definitely not it!
To say whether it is weak or not
It's weak
What?
It can be categorized as "Weak" as you guys mentioned
It's not it! What I drank was not "Cha" by Kobayashi-en
Correct!!
造 He is disposing an empty bottle
Remaining 11 / 12
Tanaka's challenge
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
It was so easy
Let me try the Don Quixote's the cheapest, 57 yen one
Don Quixote
[Fuka-mushi Ryokucha]
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
I'm guessing it is weak
Now tasting
Correct Answer
No it's not weak
Whatever
It's strong, but...
Why the hell
do we have to listen to that?
He's talking how he feels in his mind
He's acting like in the theatres
*(A successful playwright)
He's conscious of Mitani*
He's expecting Mitani to watch him act
"Hey Mr. Mitani, I can act like this"
I don't mean it like that
"Isn't it time you choose me for your work?"
So I guess it's not the one
It was a bit different
What I drank was not "Fuka-mushi Ryokucha" !
Correct!!
I can clearly see the difference
Now tasting
Correct Answer
Tanaka said he could clearly see the difference, and he confidently kept on going.
Remaining 7 / 12
Tanaka's challenge
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
He's so vigorous. So steady
I'll try "Oi Ocha"
"Oi Ocha" might be it then
Itou-en
[Oi Ocha Green Tea]
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
He's appealing to someone
He is appealing to someone
associated with theatrical circles
Now tasting
Correct Answer
In the theatrical world?
Like, Miyamoto Amon...(producer)
Ninagawa Yukio...(producer)
Does he want to work in the theatrical world?
If this is not the one
I would probably panic
Don't! Don't be panicking!
You can't be on TV if you do
What should I do if it is not the one I had...here I go
Wrong
It's not it
He's not panicking at all
That's a cool shot
How about starring as a detective?
Nothing is gonna stop Tanaka
Correct Answer
Remaining 3 / 12
Tanaka's challenge
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
3 more to go!
You gotta be getting it!
All right I shall get the right one!
I'm gonna try the AEON!
Aeon
Correct
[Top Value Ichiban-ca iri Ryokucha]
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
Correct Answer
Now tasting
He's promising...
Wrong! It's weak!
The one I drank was not "Ichiban-cha iri Ryokucha" by AEON!
Incorrect!!
Uncool! That's the worst scene ever!
You actually didn't find any difference eh?
Here he comes
Get the right one quickly! You filthy moron!
Of course, you deserve it
It hurts
What's wrong with you?
You pushed your luck too much
But you successfully appealed to the theatrical world enough
**We have facebook and twitter.**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
JoJay Gutz
Karinko
Lei (Team Gaki)
Mike F.
Otviss
Thank you for your wonderful generosity!
Translator:
Typesetter and proofreader:
Xiyu W.
Fourth challenger
Tsukitei Hosei
The next challenger is Hosei
His tea is "Cha" by Kobayashi-en, a tea shop in Shizuoka pref.
This tea is 100% made from tea leaves grown in Shizuoka
Its weight is also an important clue
Tsukitei
Hosei
Ok we have both screwed up now
Good, you guys did it together
If you did it alone, you would have it harder
Accuracy Rate: Out of 37 challenges  3 have been correct
Hey
You got me a lucky one didn't you?
It's super bitter.
What the hell...
I'm not gonna comment on it
As I don't wanna screw up
Hosei's challenge
Remaining 12 / 12
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
Ok it was really bitter. May I try "Iuemon" first?
"Iuemon"?
You mean Iemon, right?
Why do you wish to try it first?
Suntory
[Iemon]
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
Because it is the most unpredictable*
*"Kusemon" (tricky)
You are rhyming with Iemon
Now tasting
Correct Answer
It's not it
Of course it's not
You said it had bitterness
What I drank was not Iuemon....Iemon
Correct!!
He's fooling around...
I'm not! I just can't help saying "Iuemon"
造 He is disposing an empty bottle
Hosei's challenge
Remaining 11 / 12
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
Oh! May I try this one?
Correct
Kobayashi-en
[Cha]
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
Why did you scream like "Ahh!"?
This white label caught my eye suddenly
Correct Answer
Now tasting
It's totally different
The smell is totally different
What the hell is that face? He looks cool
Is he attempting to get something?
Wait a minute...
But that was a bit weaker...
Wait...no, I guess it's not the one
The one didn't taste clearly like this
It's so close, but it feels different in my throat
So dangerous!
What I had was not Kobayashi-en!
Incorrect!!
It's like they're bullying us with that sudden buzzer
That was the perfect timing
He stopped so suddenly too
I thought it was so similar too
Do your job properly! You guaranteed-fee thief!
Guaranteed-fee thief
That makes him feel like pooping
Fifth challenger
Matsumoto Hitoshi
The last challenger is Matsumoto
Set the bottle slightly forward
While Getting Ready
You mean the one picked for you?
Yes and bend it a little bit
Matsumoto's tea is the same one as Tanaka's. Ion Ichiban-cha iri Ryokucha
Tanaka could not detect this. Can Matsumoto do it?
Sounds like they are taking time setting everything up
Is there anything funny?
We picked
You picked? Who picked this?
All of us chose this one
Here i go then
Accuracy Rate: Out of 37 challenges  6 have been correct
It's just average
How about bitterness? Bitterness is an important clue
No particular bitterness
Oh come on guys, the last challenger got a tough one. It sucks
Who are you appealing to?
You are speaking in standard Japanese (not Kansai accent)
It's hard!
I have no idea
Is it right?
I'm sure it's not the right one
Coming Next
Correct Answer
It wasn't bitter
Nobody has succeeded so far. Matsumoto's tea is Ichiban-cha iri Ryokucha by AEON
Correct Answer
Ok I'm eliminating from this side
I actually want to know how this tastes
Now tasting
This is really something
It's super stro-o-o-ong
It remains on my tongue so vividly
It's definitely not it
Completely wrong
What I drank was not King of Green Martha Premium!
Correct!!
I don't even have to try this but I'm gonna do it anyway
造 He is disposing an empty bottle
More or less as sort of an alibi
Now tasting
It's less different than I expected
I thought it would be more different
It is different but much less than I thought
What I drank was not Healthier Green Tea
Correct!!
Ok it's gonna be tough
Matsumoto's challenge
Remaining 10 / 12
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
Can I try this?
Ok let's try Fuka-mushi Ryokucha
Don Quixote
[Fuka-mushi Ryokucha]
m 0 0 l 366.875 0 l 366.875 59 l 0 60
Correct Answer
Now tasting
Huh?
Oh this is the worst...
It's so close!
Calm down, calm down, no this isn't okay
No, It can't end here
No seriously
That's water
To be honest with you,
I guess it's the right one
But the problem is
My screen time on tv
Screen time, that's the problem
I haven't been on much lately
I think I haven't been on TV long enough today
I don't think so
I've heard that this show is on TV at the same time in Osaka now
Yes since last week
Right?
So my mother and sister would say
[Hey, you weren't on TV so much]
No way, you are on TV long enough
Like, "You weren't standing out!" ?
"We were watching but you weren't there so much!"
You guys picked a tricky one. Did you really pick Fuka-mushi at this point?
Yeah it can be possible. I think I was trapped perfectly.
Ok I'm gonna get it right so the show can end happily.
But what if I fail? It would be so miserable
DAMN!!!
I don't think that was quite right
It will be edited
I think it wasn't right
My mom would say "Hey, we watched the show,
but you looked kinda mentally unstable"
In fairness
That's your usual behavior
You often shout suddenly
What should I do? Ok I'm gonna go! Go!
Go!
Ah!!
His normal behavior
That's our Ma-chan
What I drank was Fuka-mushi Ryokucha!!
Incorrect!!
So quick!
Ok I'm gonna poop here!! I mean it!!
It's because you drink nothing but protein!!
Oh it really makes me feeling like pooping...
This video was brought to you by tofu panda fansubs
It really hurts
So nobody got the right one today
So we got zero again
Told ya. They tell us nothing but lies!
All of the staff have had been fired by their former employers because of their lies!