The Third Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende Chiki-Chiki
Fateful showbiz revenge match! Yamazaki vs Moriman - an endless battle!
About that, they're doing that again
How confident today do you think Yamasaki san is?
He is definitely confident today. He already did two times before.
That is so. But you know, how should I say it? He lost in such ways that we can't even talk about them. A complete failure.
Prior to this match, Yamasaki and Moriman had two battles
However, Yamazaki's struggle was in vain, as he was unable to match Moriman's astonishing power. Before your eyes, real men are born.
This time I've thought of all kinds of different ways to fight
And I think there's something wrong with the way Yamasaki fights
That must be it
Our contestant now is 30 years old. Will Yamasaki be able to take his revenge?
Our fighter, Yamasaki san's entrance!
~"Yamasaki is No.1"~
Here comes our good-for-nothing guy
That's right, I'm wearing it.
The first and second time you were completely defeated.
That is so, I did quite bad the second time, but it was unfair!
But we saw it all, how you fought there. We were not unfair to you.
But I will do it today! I will definitely win!
Everything that happened before doesn't mean anything anymore, because Yamasaki san is a Benz owner now.
A Benz owner would never lose.
Are you ready, Yamasaki san?
Champion Moriman's entrance!
There she is
There it is
But nothing can be helped. Next time be prepared.
That was an unarmed attack. That's bad.
Anyway, go ahead.
"Pre-match cheering song "Love" ~hohohoho-i~"
"I don't need friends"
"Because it would be hard to fight back"
Thank you for your performance
The first Yamasaki's round - "Pantyhose" showdown
This round is going to be very interesting
I've already lost Yamazaki-san in comedy
Do your best!
He agreed with that
Let's start
Let's begin the first round
What a scary faces they have
What a frightening faces
That's a good move
He is locked!
Moriman's Victory
You got him now
He was like that
What happened?
I couldn't breeze
But we can't do anything, you have to fight.
Second round - "Slippers" showdown
Moriman's second victory
Yamasaki san
You got your face hit quite tough
For Yamasaki san is too difficult not to be caught
He really was captured
When he was caught, he stopped fighting
That was so weak
That was...
~It hurts~ It was painful?
I wonder if Yamasaki is already done?
He can still do it
Yamasaki san
Yes?
Yamasaki san, can you still fight?
I will do it!
Then please choose from the board
Low kick showdown!
I have a bad expectation about it
Third round - "Low kick" showdown
Moriman's third victory
That was funny
Please win next round
The final showdown! The final one?
The final one?
Piping hot ankake showdown!
Fourth round - "Piping hot ankake" showdown
"If you run away or give up to the hot ankake - you lose"
Let's do it!
"Do not attempt to do this as it is dangerous"
You ran again off the stage
Moriman's fourth victory
Moriman!
It's not over yet!
Don't let him get from the ring
This time, I'm in the lead and this is a vigorous fight
The hell you're talking about, last time you nearly died, you moron!
Shut the hell up!
Alright, let's do the final round
When it'll be hot next time, use water
Let's go with the towel battle? Let's start!
The final round - "Wet towel fight" showdown
That was good!
He's just fighting with himself
Oh that was good
Go, go, go!
Save me!
Moriman's total victory
The only thing that he told was "Help me!"
Yamasaki's defeat!!
That's the only thing you must not say when you fight
He said "Help me!"
He pleaded for his life
He begged for his life
He really said "Help me!"? He did
Let's watch again that part
~Help me!~