Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
-It all started from this day
Hamada, listen,
I bet all the staff have mumbled while sleeping
they wished you were dead
at least once
Get hit and you are IT !!
Big Metal Pot Roulette!
Rule:
Cut a string attached to a pot;
game ends when a pot hits Matsumoto or Hamada
Let's see who the chosen ones are
Endo is the first participant
Yamasaki is the second one
This is his fourth consecutive year
And the last one is...
Hamada, Yamasaki, and Endo will participate in this year's Batsu Game
And this year, it takes place at a...
Police Station
"Gaki No Tsukai"
The Biggest Budget Yet !!
Bizarre Happenings at the Police Station
with Top Celebrities Cameos
Clever Traps
Predicting the Outcome is Impossible
To Make the Matter worse,
Matsumoto and Tanaka Raid the Station !!
They Lure the Three into a Laughing Hell
What Will the Three Have Witnessed
by the End of This Long Day ??
3 Hours of Total Chaos !!
Downtown presents:
Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende!
Do Not Laugh for 24 Hours - The Police Series!!
Cocoriko
Naoki Tanaka
Downtown
Hitoshi Matsumoto
Let me just say this
I'll say it really quick
Let me just say a couple of things
First thing first
You're freakin' tall, aren't you ?
You JUST noticed that ??
After all these years...
I thought I'd get that out of the way
I also have to say
that I appreciate all the applauses here
but please don't be pointing fingers at me as you laugh hysterically
Yeah, you in front, stop doing that
Shall we summon the idiots who
took part in the Batsu Game ??
Come on out !!
3 Batsu Receivers
Cocoriko
Shozo Endo
Downtown
Masatoshi Hamada
Hosei Yamasaki
I'm sure you all have lot to say
Let's just watch the footage
Start...
the...
Video !
Simply amazing
The day of  the Batsu Game
A bus carrying the three losers arrives at the station
Hey
Enough with that already !!
Good morning, guys
This guy used to be my manager
Former Downtown Manager
Hiroshi Fujiwara
How else can I greet you ?
We noticed your dialect
By the way
Do you know who I'm supposed to be ?
You look like "Sukeban Detective"
I see
Endo, why don't you smack me on the head ?
As fate would have it, this is who I am
The Fifth Sukeban Detective
Saki Fujiwara
I'm not letting you get away
That's enough of my introduction
Why don't you follow me ?
Take a look over here
Here's today's stage,
"Shakure Police Department"
They will fight against the enemy, trying to make them laugh,
for the next 24 hours
With that said
Why don't you go get
go get, um, um, changed in there
What's with "um, um" ??
Let me just say
that I'm expecting you to be more professional once this starts
Go ahead and put those uniforms on
Changing into the Police Uniforms
But are they typical police uniforms ?
Let's see officer Endo first
Endo - Courageous Officer
Yamasaki
Yamasaki -Not a "Wuss" anymore
Hamada's uniform is second hand
Hamada san, that's no good
What is that on your left knee
This isn't cool
Not fair at all !
This is cheating !!
What the hell is this ??
You're playing dirty
Very dirty
The production team is using subtle humors to get you guys
I don't see how I'm playing dirty
I wanna look sharp, too, like you guys
I'd love to get changed later
It suits you though, if I may say so
Let me explain how the game goes
Rule:
Work for 24 hours as policeman
After crossing the gate,
you are not to laugh
Rule:
If caught laughing,
a severe punishment is delivered
Wait a sec
Give us a second
Once you cross here,
the game starts
Alright !!
-Let's do this !!
There's no turning back !
Here we go !
Do Not Laugh for 24 Hours: The Police Series
Wait a minute
Don't forget to introduce yourselves
to your senior officers
An honor to meet you all
Look!
Here's our reputable motorcycle team
Motorcycle Police on Duty !!
Pretty cool
Captain
Obachan
(middle aged woman)
Motorcycle Captain
That was a swift first strike
Here comes an American police man !!
You serious ?
Are you serious ?
Are you serious ??
That looked painful
If caught laughing,
you get butt-slapped by American police men
This is how it's going to be ?
Don't be making that face !!
Damn you
This really really hurts
Don't you make that face at me !!
I'm not making a face
Endo, you were laughing, too
No, I don't think so
This is going to be a tough day
We don't need to be looking at things like these
Here's this months' slogan
Let me recite it for you guys
Just repeat after me
Look before you cross
with your big chin
Don't fall for the words of crooks
with their double chin
Let's go
Yamasaki, no more funny faces
Let's try to get along
I didn't do anything wrong
I just ask you not to make that face again
I'm not making any faces
Change in Endo's demeanor
I don't remember why I laughed there
Most-Wanted Criminal Cut-Out Boards
(Gah-Soo)
I was trying to figure out what that was,
and now I know
Take a look
He's one of the most notorious
criminals in the city
His name is Kenji Suga
Round faced, Overweight, and a Dark Complexion
His face is kinda oily, too
That's life-size by the way
Endo Tries not to Look
Here we commemorate our past chiefs
Original Chief
Mr. Suzuki
2nd Chief
Mr. Hashimoto
3rd Chief
Mr. Okamoto
4th Chief
Mr. Kimura
5th Chief
Lopez
That was a tough call
Hamada Tries to Make the Others Laugh
It's so obvious he's trying to make us laugh
You guys needed to stick together, seriously
Here's our receptionist
She knows everything about this station
Receptionist:
Reiko
Nice to meet you all
Let me tell you a little about this police station
Gulp
This station was built in 1967
She would have got to me for sure
We couldn't keep our straight faces
She drinks so much
Gulp
I'm not done yet
Where were we ?
So we've been protecting
citizens for the past 39 years
Gulp
There used to be 213 officers here
Gulp, gulp
She held us there for a while
Will you finish that already ?
Good luck to you all
Gulp
and good luck with the training, too
Here's our Boss's office
Boss, here's your trainees
The Boss
Yutaro
So you've made it
The three new hires
Good luck to you
Don't let me down, huh ?
That "ignoring" routine gets me every time
And where's he looking, anyway ?
What are your "handles" ??
Don't have one yet, I suppose
As policemen,
you need to have a handle or two
Let's take care of that right now
"Gift" from the Boss
He provides Their Handle Names !!
What's your name ?
I'm Hamada
Hamada...
What's your favorite food ?
I like stir fried noodles
Noodles!
They're good, aren't they !?
Alright
I got it
Hamada's Handle
"LIPS"
You, next
What's your name ?
I'm Endo
Are you married ?
Yes
With kids ?
I have a child
How festive !
Endo's Handle
"ENDO"
With that...
Excuse me, Boss but...
I haven't receive my "handle" yet
I couldn't hold myself together there
I see
Sorry about that
Let me have your name then ?
I'm Yamasaki
How many TV shows are you on per week ?
I'm on internet radio
Internet radio...
Respectable occupation
Anything else ?
What else...?
You asked for it
You laughed at the fact
that you have no routine gigs on TV
Mmm...
Not much to work with...
C'mon in
Hi Boss
Detective "Royal Highness"
Akira Onodera
Oh, good timing, "Royal Highness"
Here's our new trainees
They're starting today
I was just giving them their "handles"
To your right is
"LIPS"
To your left is
"ENDO"
And I can't come up with anything
for him in the middle
Maybe you can help me with this
Let me see...
How many TV shows are you on ?
In the Osaka area,
I've got a small gig
And I'm on internet radio in the Tokyo area
I see...
Well, well, well
This is difficult, isn't it ?
How about "D#CKHEAD" ??
"DI#KHEAD"
"Royal Highness" shouldn't have been muttering that word
That sounds good to me
OK, let's go with that then
Yamasaki's Nickname
"D%CKHEAD"
"LIPS"
"ENDO"
"DI%KHEAD"
Protect and serve your community
Good luck to you all
Why don't we go get a drink or two ?
Damn...
I think Hamada should've been slapped then
Should he be saying word like "DI#KHEAD" ??
That caught me off guard
I was shocked
You all got cool handle names for sure
How so ?
Why am I just "ENDO" ??
So what if I'm not on TV so often ?
Hosei san,
will you try not to make us laugh please ?
I'm not !
It was just uncalled for, that's all
What a huge building !
Director Onuma
Janitor Scraping Gum off the Floor
Thanks to these guys,
we can work at a nice clean work place
Oh !
We've been looking for this guy for a long time now
Have a look
Wanted Poster
(Gah-Soo)
He's responsible for the majority of marriage fraud these days
Endo, take a good look at it
--I got it
Burn this image in your head
Man, that's a good drawing of him
Here's where all the veteran detectives are stationed
Visit to the Veteran Detective's Room
to Make Formal Introductions !!
Let me introduce you to everyone
Here's the ex-body builder
"Muscle" Detective
ex-Body builder
He just failed big time
Sexy...um..sexy...
Fujiwara san,
please, no more stuttering !
Get it right, please
Here's an example of a good marriage
Never-Any-Arguments
"Love-birds" Detectives
Nice to meet you all
Next is
a detective who keeps Japanese traditions alive
Preserving the Tradition
"Kabuki" Detective
Goooooooooooood
Mooooooorrrrrrrrninnng
Yama-chan ?
What's up, Yama-chan ??
This "set-up" got to you, Yamasaki
And last but not least
Tomoko Matsushima
HELLO
I AM TOMOKO MATSUSHIMA
GOOD LUCK WITH THE BATSU GAME
I don't like these celebrity cameos
Look, she's not even using that keyboard
I'm afraid I'm getting hit
twice as much as last year
Here's where you'll be stationed
Trainee Department
We're not starting off great this year
Let's put on a game face on
Here's your room
Not bad, huh ?
Seats are assigned to each of you
Endo, you at the end
Yamasaki in the middle
And Hamada, you're at this end
Have a seat
Camera's everywhere, and nowhere to hide
Hamada Gets
the Child's Seat
Hamada, are you vertically challenged ?
I felt for him there
That wasn't fair
I didn't deserve that chair
That hurt
Hamada, aren't you a bit short ?
Were you always this short ?
I'm going to hand you an officer's 3 most important items
Distribution of the Three Important Items !!
Here are your guns
Item No.1: Gun
We can have a gun ?
Handle it with care
Thank you
Should I put this in my holster ?
Please
Yamasaki, here's yours
Yamasaki Gets the Toy Gun
Be careful with it
Item No.2: Billy Club
Endo, here
Thank you
Here's yours, Yamasaki
Yamasaki Receives the GOBO (Burdock Root)
You all got....cough, cough !
Excuse me,
So far, so good ?
Item 3: Police Identification Handbook
Don't turn the page just yet
We'll go through it together
Thank you
Open up the Police ID Handbook...
and You See Your Photo Inside
Could this Photo be Another Set-up ?!
Hamada: First Year in Show Business
Endo: His Debut at 20 Years Old
Yamasaki: Funny Face
Why don't you open to the first page ?
First year in show business
Debut at 20 years old
Funny Face
Those photos are way too much
Um, we don't have the same ones ?
The photo should identify yourself
Don't lose it
Wait a minute
This isn't me
Debut at 20 years old
Your handbooks didn't match the photos, I see
Funny Face
I couldn't help but laugh at Endo's adorable face
The hell is here
It's here
This isn't good
My ass is receiving some serious beat-downs this year
Anyway, I'm pretty sure there's been a mix up here
OK then, make sure to grab your own photo
Here's mine
New to Show Business
Nice face !
Let's turn to page two
I don't get the purpose of that editing
You see three police officer oaths
I'm going to have you read them aloud
Police ID Handbook Trap 2: Police Officer Oaths
Can they read the difficult Kanji (Chinese Characters)
used in the oaths ?
It will surely test their knowledge !!
Hamada, will you read the first one, please ?
Oath 1
I pledge to respect everyone's rights,
Hamada,
What's good about reading it so normally ?
Will you read it as you "Shakure" ??
Oath 1
I pledge to respect everyone's rights
faithfully perform my duties
and strengthen social solidarity
Yamasaki, why don't you read us the second one ?
Pledge 2
I pledge to develop my character
Hey, do the "Shakure"
Oath 2
I pledge to develop my character
You purposely changed your voice just now
You definitely did
Totally uncalled for
Not cool at all
Don't be changing your voice
It was premeditated
He was playing dirty
No sir, I wasn't
Why can't he use his normal voice ?
Please continue, Yamasaki
Oath 2
I pledge to develop my character
by enriching my self-worth and expanding my capacity
to retain a sound attitude
I know I wouldn't have survived this one
Endo, you're up
Pledge 3
As a police man,
That's enough outta you !!
Read it like you normally would
Oath 3
I pledge not to neglect my mission to better myself as a police man
and to refrain from a frivolous attitude
Not good with Kanji
You can do this
so that citizens of all kinds
can be protected
RISSEN
SOSSEN (By any means)
Man, this kept the butt-slappers busy
Endo, continue
And that's ....
And that's...
And that's ...
RYUSEKI
SASUGA (Who I should be as a...)
You messed up on purpose !
No wonder you guys were falling apart
Thank God, it's over
You guys still have a long way to go
Do you really need that ?
Excuse me ?
Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
What ?
Give me a break, guys
Hosei san, you don't need to hang onto that, do you ?
I don't know how much more of this I can take
I bet it's not even close to noon yet
No way to tell what time it is
No Clock in the Room
They didn't give us clocks again this year
They take advantage of being spared from tricks and set-ups for a moment
Time for a brief break
God, I would love to open these drawers
They couldn't have possibly set anything up in the drawers
Do you know how many times I've been through this "Batsu Game" series ?
This is Yamasaki's 4th Consecutive Batsu Game
You deserve a medal for your attendance
Having said that, we should still open these drawers
Just in case ?
I'll go first then
More than enough photos of Chiaki
I was shocked
That's just plain cruel
How can there be so many photos of her ?
She must have provided these to the show
I think you're right
In fact, she told me she once was an honorary policewoman for a day
Chiaki, Chief for a Day
That's from that day then ?
Yes, it is
This must be from one of her CD's ?
Yes
I've seen this one before
Hosei san, could you open your drawers ?
You think you got something in there ?
Why don't you come a little closer ?
Empty
You deserve nothing or what ?
You would have laughed at anything
Anything would've made you laugh
It definitely caught me off guard
I guess I was thinking too much into it
How about this one then ?
Sorry about that
How about you, Hamada san ?
I don't believe I have anything here
Banana Peels
What the hell was that ?
Cut me some slack
The production team must've predicted who would open their drawers first
Who eats that many bananas ?
Could there be more...?
Bananas x 3
Drawer full of bananas
Bananas x2
How many do you want ?
How much is enough ?
You're not really a banana type of guy though
Gong !!
How's it going, Onii (big brother) ?
I am Chiaki
Chiaki
Shozo Endo's wife, Chiaki, announces the 10:00am hour
This is way more Chiaki than I can handle
Will she show up every hour then ?
Once every hour ?
Not sure, but it's 10:00am now
I bet she's announcing every hour
Your wife's getting a crap load of exposure
She's definitely in on this
Why does she call you "Onii" ??
What ?
She started calling me "Onii"
while we were still dating
She didn't call me "Onii" (big brother)
in a literal sense
More like "someone she can look up to" ??
Yes, more or less
What does your wife call you, Hamada san ?
Don't be a moron !
Why the hell do you gotta ask me that ?
There's nothing wrong with that question
It was a very natural conversation
I thought I would ask you now
While Chiaki calls me "Onii" at home
what does your wife call you at home ?
I'm guessing she refers to you differently in public than private
not sure...
What does she call you ?
It isn't anything funny but...
You guys are attacking each other hard this year
We were destroying ourselves
She takes my name and calls me "Mah-chan"
Mah-chan ?
The break time is over
Let's go outside for the monthly meeting
Wow
Shakure Site Wide Meeting
Let us start the monthly meeting
Shakure Police Station
Rally to Eradicate Crime
First, our chief has a few words to share
Greetings from the Shakure Police Chief !!
Shakure Police Chief
Shinji Yamashita
Good morning to all the Shakure officers
I'm your police chief, Yamashita
Today, I will ask you to think about
what it is to be "Shakure"
What the hell ?
A true "Shakure" resides within each one of us
Sadly,
I'm not "Shakure" physically
But emotionally,
I'm more "Shakure" than anybody else !!
What the hell is that supposed to mean ?
So, let's hear it
SHAKURE
That is all
Here's the juvenile divisional manager,
Mr. Mikami, um um...
will address his thoughts on crime eradication month
Juvenile Divisional Manager Speech !!
I'm Mikami from the Juvenile Division
Thick Northeastern Dialect
I've been hearing disturbing news about
drugs and guns
[Indiscernible]
I couldn't tell what the heck he was saying
You can see officers behind you laughing, too
This isn't easy to survive
No, it was not
[indiscernible]
This was a long speech, too
Hey, pay attention
Officers Horsing Around
Zip it
You two in the front !
Don't make me say it again
Shut up and pay attention !
Death to 2 Officers- Execution Style
Who cares about being "OUT" at this point ?!
That manager's pretty funny
Thank you, manager
Next, we're honoring those who helped to make our city safer
Just last week, this group arrested 86 members of a notorious speeding gang
Honoring the outstanding officers !!
Motorcycle team, please come up here
Here's a certificate of recognition
for our superior motorcycle team
whose efforts make our city safer
Nice Ray-Ban sunglasses
Too funny
Why did he have to let me know ?
Endo tries to make Hamada laugh
I spotted him
I didn't mean to but I did
Besides, why doesn't he wanna come outside ?
Why is he staying inside ?
Here's an officer who keeps our ocean safe
by patrolling with his dolphin
"Dolphin" Officer
please, come forward
Who ?
A boy who got to ride a dolphin
"Dolphin" Officer
Michiru Joe
My generation should know him well
On Sale in 1973
You guys don't who this is, huh ?
I didn't know who he was
I remember this guy being a "teen idol" back then
This is awful
They Laughed - No Interruption Until the End of the Song
Why is he singing here anyway ?
Let us conclude this rally with a song
What the hell ?
Shakure Police Station Song
Embracing pride higher than Mt. Fuji
Enables us to capture criminals night and day
There will be some tough days, but don't cry
Dancing on the floor of criminals
I'm alone again
What kinda message is this ?
I know, I don't get this
So don't be
Wait, didn't the chief say he's mentally shakure ??
Shakure emotionally
Let's hear it
Shakure, shakure
Shakure Police Station
This concludes our monthly rally
Dismissed !!
Why don't we head back ?
Only 2 hours have passed
But the three already show signs of fatigue
But the Batsu Game is about to
become even tougher
The day has just begun
There's so much stuff going on already
I'd say too much
You guys have zero team-work
We saw lot of times when you trapped each other
We had such chemistry back when we did
the "Don't laugh at High School"
There was great communication among us
But now, you just care about yourselves
Especially you, Endo
When I see something funny, I naturally want to share that with Hamada san
I don't need it, seriously
What's interesting about watching this
is that it definitely shows everyone's personalities
I can see who is prone to laugh at certain things
What about Yamasaki though ?
Well, he pretty much laughs at anything thrown at him
What's this ?
You know what else ?
Your facial expression isn't fair
The faces you make tend to make everyone laugh
But that is my normal face expression
You're just accusing me of TRYING to make you guys laugh
See ?
What'd you mean "See ?"
I don't get it
Stop making weird awkward pauses
I can't, that's how I am
Start
the
Video
Not very funny, I see
Outside Duty
Means More Terror of Laughter !!
Traffic Officers' Training
Storm of Hysteria
Could there be...
Huge Crash
An Emergency Strikes the Shakure Police Station !!
Bomb Squad Member
Risks his Life !!
Proceed with caution, got it?
Matsumoto and Tanaka Raid  the Station !!
Batsu Game Turns More Sinister !!
At last, the trainees are ready for duty
Let's go train with the Traffic Officers
Shall we ?
Do we really need to join them ?
Endo, sit behind me
Hamada, you're in the middle
and Yamasaki, you're behind the passenger seat
I see, you guys can't just sit around the station all day
Empty Bento Box Trash on the Floor
This set-up is very subtle but apparently effective
As officers, I expect you to use seatbelts
Hamada Uses a Rope for Seatbelt
They're off to traffic training
What will they face there ?
Hey, Hamada
How old is your stupid son ?
Well, the oldest one is ready to start the high school
Even the stupid have to grow up eventually, I guess
Yes, indeed
Hey Yamasaki,
How old is your daughter, Momo-chan ?
She's 5 years old now
How come your answers are so normal and boring ?
Hey, Endo
How old is your daughter, Hoheto ?
Her name is Iroha !
How old is Hoheto ?
She's IROHA !
A girl like Hoheto
IROHA !
Even a girl like Hoheto
Hohe....um..a girl like Hoheto
must have a dream for the future right ?
She's still too young to think like that
She's Iroha, by the way
As long as you're getting along with Hoheto, that's all I ask for
OK...
You gave up, didn't you ?
Man, it's so desolate
Looks like a peaceful town
I need to get some gas
Police car detours into
a gas station
I'd say this was really tough
ZET !!
Hear him ?
Where else can you find this kind of service ?
How may I help you ?
Gas Station Attendant
Ichiro Mizuki
Could you pull up further please ?
They almost got me with that one
That must've sucked having to get out of the car each time
Alright
Alright ZET !!
What's "ZET" have to do with anything ?
Regular or Premium ?
Premium please
Premium ZET !!
We've got to hold ourselves together
ZET !!
Do you have a membership with us ?
No I don't
How would you like to sign up for free ?
Sounds good
Enrollment ZET !!
What does he mean by "Enrollment ZET" ??
Allow me to clean out the ashtray
Thank you
We can do it
zet
Was Mr. Mizuki always like this ?
No, he's never been like this
zet
Mr. Mizuki is clumsy with the equipment
He had no idea how to use that thing
He can't operate it right
zet
Wow ! Gas spill !!
How dangerous ?!
Wait a sec
I'm covered in gasoline !
Not good, not good, not good
Mr. Mizuki, please
Can we go please ?
Let's go
Will you be pulling out to the right or the left
To the right please
Right ZET !!
We can do this, Hosei san
I didn't laugh though
ZET !
ZET !!
I think I can still hear him
Indeed, he's not a quitter
ZET !!
With a full tank of gas,
the three are ready for their next mission
We should be able to join up with
the rest of the traffic officers
I have a feeling their training must be hard
Why are we bothering them during their training anyway ?
Is it imperative that we join their training ?
Yes, of course
We're actually participating ?
Wow
Participation in Traffic Officers' Training
Why don't you line up here ?
The captain should be here any minute
Don't forget to give a formal greeting
I heard he delivers nasty and tough stare-downs
Traffic Dept. Captain
Naomasa Musaka
I'm Captain Musaka and I'm in charge
of the traffic department
I see some new faces here
This was in such a bad taste
That's pretty gross
Did you see how close he put his face up to mine ?
Disgusting
Get back in line
There's definitely some dangerous elements in today's training
If you're not 100% focused, one could lose his life
Chapstick
Just last week
because of my negligence
50 to 60 trainees lost their lives
He should be fired !!
How can he still be the captain then ?
He killed 50 to 60 trainees ?
Line up
You got that ?
I'm letting you smell my breath
This isn't fair
Why his "breath" ?
Salute
What was up with that ?
He's out of control
Why don't we move over this way ?
What ?
You are in "stand by" mode
That captain was terrible
What's wrong with him ?
Rule:
Training begins with one trainee at a time
I don't like this already
Rule:
You're free to laugh at anytime during the training
What ?
Sounds good, doesn't it ?
Well, it sounds good in a scary way
Rule:
Punishment Delivered for SCREAMING at anytime during the training
See, I don't like this one bit
I'm going to hate this
Let's see who goes first
How about Hamada? You're up first
What ?
Extreme Driving Technique Experience !!
Drifting
2-Wheel Driving
The 3 have no idea what they are about to experience
Man, I didn't sign up for this
Hamada
Take it easy, OK ?
We don't need this long one
Stop it
What was that ?
What just happened ?
That was loud
Who cares ?
Hamada
This way
How was that ?
What can I say ?
Sigh
Yamasaki
You're on
Got that ?
Wait a sec
I didn't want to be last
Training for Yamasaki is even more extreme
Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
Trap 1: Door Opens
Trap 2: Door Falls Off
Door Opens
Door Falls Off
Trap 3: Smoke From the Hood
Yamasaki
Yamasaki has no idea what is about to happen
Countdown to Open Door
Hey, it's open !
Open !
Opened ! Opened ! Opened ! Opened !
It's open ! Listen !
It's open !
Open !
Open ! Open !
Ha ha ha ha
Hey ! The door is open !!
Countdown to Door Falling Off
The door is gone !!
It fell off !!
Fell off !
Wow, the door's gone
Hamada san, you were laughing hard just then
Countdown to Smoke
Hey, something stinks !
Hey, it stinks !
No ! I'm scared !
What's with the smoke ?
You failed
You were allowed to laugh, right ?
There's no way...
I'm positive I'll be "OUT"
And you get your ass slapped, too
No reaction from you ?
I could have cared less at this point
Yama-chan ?
Yamasaki
It was so terrifying
The door came off, didn't it ?
Yes
I was really stunned, yeah definitely stunned
What the hell ?
What's with your grammar ??
What's gonna happen to Endo ?
Endo
You're up
"Secret" trap
Saving the Best for the Last ?!
Endo
He got it the worst
God, he's going fast
You were doing well here
Yeah, he's holding himself together so far
That's pretty scary
Scared, scared, scared, scared, scared
Countdown to Secret Trap
This is unacceptable
What the...?
Is this an accident or what ?
Hey !
Aghhhh !!!
I don't blame you for yelling out for him
You guys are friends
Endo, are you OK ?
How was it ?
Is this really OK ?
This is NOT OK
The car flipped over ?
Yeah, look at it
You didn't realize what happened ?
My mind went completely blank
I had my eyes closed, too
And they still called you "OUT"
I'm like "who's OUT" ??
I was clueless
This training was insane
Incredible
You got some great training here
How so?
I was thinking if Endo couldn't get out of that car on his own
then maybe you guys would just let me go home
They return to the station after their rigorous training
But there's more traps and set-ups waiting for them !!
CB Radio
Emergency !!
All officers are to report to the station gate
to apprehend a man causing a commotion at the station
Sounds like a lunatic is out and about
Do we have to...
Oh ! I see him up there
I'm afraid I know this guy
Lunatic Appears at the Police Station
I'll show you what "Funny" really is
What a moron
My wife comes from a wealthy family
Where's the laughing ?
I thought that was freakin' funny myself
"My wife comes from a wealthy family" !!
What's with that "choice" ??
Go ahead and laugh
I'm making an ass out of myself because you don't find me funny
How about this then
Once and for all, let's decide if I'm funny or not
I'll come down only if I'm not funny
Sound good ?
Let me start then
Here's a One-Man-Skit
Titled: Inoki Antonio
One-Man-Skit "Inoki Antonio"
Feeling energized ?
Anything's possible with this energy
Let's hear it
No, I'm staying up here
That's not what I said
I'll only come down if I'm not funny
Get a clue
Do you understand Japanese ?
You need to ask for help from Doraemon
No, I'm not coming down
Absolutely not !
Here's another One-Man-Skit
One-Man-Skit "Concert"
~Let's go find it, Boy
~Take down all the mutants
~I'm flying through the sky
with this cloud machine
into the Mysterious world
`Flying through the sky and over a mountain
all the Adventure
~Let us begin mysterious travels
Get it now !
The world's most awesome drama
This world is full of treasure
Yes, now is the time for the
Adven-Ture~
Way too long
What a moron
I told you I'm not coming down
What a lunie !
A real lunatic !
Let's do a classic comic monologue
I've done many shows at colleges around the nation
But guess how many shows this comic has done ?
48 colleges
Can you believe that, 48 schools?!
All that in one year
Well, guess how many schools I've hit ?
A total of HACHI KOU (8 schools)
Only HACHI KOU (8 schools)
What am I? Some kind of dog ?
*HACHI KOU is also the name of famous dog in Japan
I admit, that HACHI KOU joke was terrible
I don't care if you didn't get it
I see, I'm coming down
Here, catch this one, please
Nice catch
Nice catch-phone
Hello ?
Wow, I'm been apprehended !
Apprehended !
What a freakin' moron !
Oh !
Another Lunatic Appears
How many of these did you have ?
Here comes the big guest
Listen
Who says I'm not funny ?!
Yoshinobu Nakamura
(Producer)
Here's something funny
One-Man-Skit
Inoki Antonio
One-Man-Skit "Inoki Antonio"
Feeling energized ?
I, Yoshinobu, can do anything with that energy
Let's hear it
How's that ?
Pretty funny, isn't it ?
I got it
I'll let you hear one of my monologues
I have booked some shows at various colleges this season
Some of the elite producers have already done 48 schools around the nation
Well, I have some shows booked
I have about 6 schools so far
Only 6
What is this, some kinda tasty water ??
You're left on your own, if you don't get this !
Yeah, he should be apprehended
As a true lunatic, yes
We know we laughed
We know...
We need to be more alert knowing these types of lunatics are around the city
But wait, aren't we in a police station ?
That first guy was a first-class-moron
He's my classmate...
Listen !
I'm getting tired of your poor attitude these days !
Why did you all skip yesterday's training ?
Why did you ?
I'm sorry
but a new game went on sale yesterday
and I had to get it
OK, then
Back to your training !!
And you ?
Riot Squad Trainee
Hitori Gekidan
I went on a day trip with my girlfriend
Back to training !
And you, what's your excuse ?!
I'm sorry but
my mother fell and I took her to the hospital
So what ??
My mother fell and I took her to the hospital
I don't care !!
But my mother fell...
My mother
My
Get up
Out of control !
I seriously feel bad for him
I've seen him in that exact situation before
Stay in here for a while
It's cold
It's cold in here
No kidding
Can I hit the restroom ?
I don't see why not
I'll be right back then
Being out in the cold made me wanna go pee
but if Yamasaki needs to take care of No.2
I feel obligated to stay here until he's back, you know ?
Can I have one, please ?
I thought they were supposed to be "props"
I guess they're yours now
Never seen bananas that small
Are they supposed to look like this ?
I'm not sure
They look too ripe to me
Too ripe ?
Why don't you try one, then ?
Would you like one, too ?
No thanks
Well, I'm not a big fan of bananas to begin with, so...
Put them down, then
But see, I already broke one off
Try a taste then
It'll satisfy your curiosity at least
My guess is
this is a good one
I told YOU to try it
Well, this one is like...
not a bad one
I know the skin looks kinda weird
Why don't YOU EAT IT, THEN ?!!
You're seriously playing dirty
No, I'm just saying I don't like bananas that much
Endo, you're playing unfairly
Why that face ?
As if you were feeling bad for him ??
Feel better ?
(My ass) hurt really bad though
Serious ?
It's from all the slapping, then ?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
I had to really take my time in there
Still working on that ?
Yamasaki Struggles with Looping His Belt
This pissed me off as well
I'm afraid I need some help with this
He's not being fair
Help me !!
I can't do this !
Yama-chan, please get it together
It's been 4 hours since the start
Lunch time for the hungry group
I'll go ahead and pass these around
I'll get some tea for us
Does this mean it's noon ?
Gourmet Lunch Box
This is one luxurious lunch
Can I just go ahead and eat this ?
That's too good of a lunch for you guys
I don't recall getting lunch like that before
Sure ?
We thought there would be some kinda set-up with this lunch, but...
Hamada Carefully Inspects His Lunch
Do you see anything unusual ?
Ramen noodles was all we got when I was involved
Are you serious ?
I'm sure of it
Look at you !
What the hell are you eating ?
Disgusting
Wow, you were hungry
He sure is hungry, eating things he doesn't know
See any paper towels ?
You know, I don't see any around
Don't worry about it, then
Endo's up to no good, isn't he ?
How about this ?
Endo suggests piece of newspaper
You were such a jerk
I didn't know what got into me
I thought I was being nice
Endo's not done yet, wait and see
Hamada san, are you gonna eat that cookie ?
That round one
You done with it ?
Thanks
Why're you trying to bust me ??
He didn't need to specify the shape of cookie
Can I have that piece of cheese, please ?
You guys, I've just about had it up to here
I'm trying not to be wasteful
This cheese is delicious
I don't mind sharing
but don't come at me with that half-smile
and the full intention to bust me
Like "I'm gonna get him"
No more of that, then
Why are we busting each other out anyhow ?
We need something to clean our hands
Oh, thanks
He just leaves them there !
Endo obviously couldn't hold it in
Endo's the Bad Guy !!
I've got some balls treating Hamada-san like that
What is
What is this for ?
This....
I'm not sure
I see, it attaches to the pistol
It goes on here, see ?
Well, I can't get this on
Endo, why don't you hook this thing for me ?
You see this, huh ?
See, got that ?
That was very disrespectful
I'm not seeing a good senior-junior relationship
I'm sorry, Hamada-san
but my mind just went blank
Endo's the Bad Guy !!
And who the hell are you supposed to be, Yamasaki ?!
Is it time for a break after lunch ??
Emergency Order
The station received a Bomb-scare
All officers are to report to the site immediately !!
There's been a bomb-scare, we need to report to the scene immediately
Let's go
An Emergency Surfaces
Report to the Bomb-Scare Scene at Once
The 3 jump in the patrol car and drive out to the scene
So they've set up a bomb way out here ?
What's the point of setting up a bomb this far out ?
It's pointless
Looks like we're here
Let's get out
The bomb is set up in that shack
Could that be...?
The helicopter is here
Is that it ?
What ?
They're here in a helicopter ?
Amazing
This magnitude of an incident calls for an expert from our headquarters
Cool
Pretty amazing
Arrival of the Top Dog from Headquarters
Top-Dog
Haruka Unabara
We have confirmed the bomb scare to be real
I see
What a BOLD(bald) move
They think they can get away with this ?
Any idea when it could go off ?
No idea, sir
Utterly BOLD (bald)!
Damn it !
I know, I know
What a production !
Did he need to show up in a helicopter ?
I see even the top-dog can't resolve this
Wait, he hasn't done anything yet
I don't get why he picked this song
Why this song ?
Oh, here comes our station's renowned bomb squad member
Bomb Squad
Itsuji Itao
It's just one guy ?
The song is still a mystery
I assume that's Itao's sense of humor
You're all in good hands now
I'd better get to work
Good luck
Only a hammer and a pair of scissors
Man, we're losing this battle
Please do not leave this perimeter
I guess he only needs the scissors
Why that song ?
He sure does take his time
He's determined to cut the wire I guess
Shouldn't he be acting with more urgency ?
I'm sure he's a bit nervous
I'm inside the shack, over ?
Confirmed
Take every precaution, over ?
I have just found the suspected object, over ?
Confirmed
Proceed with caution, over ?
I am about to attempt to diffuse the object, over ?
That scared the hell outta me !
The guy from headquarters was flipping out, too
Incredible
Amazing explosion
That was something !
What happened to the bomb squad member ?
Shall we go ?
What ?
Yes, it was quite an incident
But a great lesson has been learned
Let's go
C'mon everyone
What about the bomb guy ?
Indeed, that was something else
Can't you say anything else ?
The 3 return to the station
What the hell are you doing ?
Endo Takes Care of His Dry Skin
It was really dry that day
You must be super sensitive
Does it hurt ?
Yes
You know, my skin is starting to feel dry and itchy, too
One of the day's masterminds, Tanaka, arrives at the scene
I guess I made it
Shakure Police Station...
I must confess
I couldn't wipe the smirk off my face since last night
The other mastermind of the day, Matsumoto, arrives
Operation Headquarters
Good morning
Check out how many cameras they have !
Hamada san seems to have received the most (batsu) so far
He still seems to be in good spirits though
With the arrival of these two men, the game will surely escalate !!
One of the top narcotic officers will be
discussing drug search techniques with you guys
Shall we ?
This way
Endo, you sit at the very end
Hamada,
and Yamasaki
Narcotics Officer
Hosshan
He's starting to look very distinguished
I'm Hosshan, a Narcotics officer
The frequency of drug smuggling has been rampant these days !
And it's only gonna get worse !
So today,
I will be going over things to look for during a drug search
Lecture
Ways to Find Smuggled Drugs
What we've got here is
an ordinary suitcase
Nothing unusual for traveling
Example
Wallet
You can definitely find something here
Don't overlook anything
See this ?!
Package of White Powder
No doubt, it's a drug
No doubt
But this is way too easy
Nobody hides it in their wallets anymore
How about this camera ?
Case 1
Camera
No doubt !
They hide it where the memory card goes
They think we won't look there, I guess
For an unknown reason, he found an Udon noodle
Let me just make sure
This is annoying
He's got full-control of the noodle !
Yes, he does
It's like magic
Go ahead and sit
No doubt, this is a Udon noodle
It's not a drug
It happens sometimes
How about this, then ?
Case 2
Instant Coffee
They've gone to Brazil or somewhere for this ?
It's just instant coffee, isn't it ?
Another package of Udon noodles
See ?
It's well marinated in coffee
Very well marinated in coffee !
I haven't heard anyone use that term in a while
Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
Don't assume this is just a cute stuffed animal
Case 3
Stuffed Bear
Is this for your kids ?
What did I tell you ?!
Once Again, An Udon Noodle
They'll try anything, see ?
It's a desperate attempt !
Where did it (noodle) go ?
I'd laugh at that, too
Where did it go anyway ?
There's just too many noodles !
One third of the day has passed
They have already endured many hard batsu's so far
Signs of fatigue begin to appear
Matsumoto and Tanaka orchestrate the next move from headquarters
luring the 3 men into a laughing hell !!
I'll be playing a video which shows you
how to be an effective officer
Watching these videos is my weakness
Study Time
Learn the be an Effective Police Officer
Hope I can make it through this
Shakure Station Job Descriptions
Let me explain how some of the officers
work to make everyone safe
Motorcycle Team
A group that children admire
A trainer teaches K9 dogs to assist officers
K9 Dog Training
Starting this winter
we have implemented a new department called
The Safe Living Department
Here, citizens can call for help with their financial,
domestic, or juvenile crime issues at their homes
Citizens are free to call our hotline anytime
Let's see how they work
Here's Officer Hirano
And Officer Jimmy Onishi
Hello, this is Shakure Po...
Cough, Cough
My good friend is suffering from D.V.(domestic violence) at home
What ?
Inquiry from a wife
about D.V.
Yes, this is about D.V.
So you've got a case of D.V. ?
This isn't good !
Not good
So far, I'm OK
He has no idea what she's asking
No idea
A bad case of D.V. ?
Oh boy
Well...
Does it involve watching
too many videos with someone ?
Impossible
No, I'm asking about D.V.
So is this a...
Does this involve a camera of some sort ?
You don't know what D.V. is ?
Well
I'm sorry to tell you
that I'm not very educated in that department
So, the answer is no
He gets you guys every time
Of course, he got us !
What's with the way he talks ?
This isn't cool
I can't concentrate !
Well...
I'm sorry to tell you
that I'm not very educated in that department
So, the answer is no
Why do they have to replay that ?
I'm sorry to tell you
that I'm not educated in that department
So, the answer is no
Are you a police officer ?
Well...
I'm sorry to tell you
that I'm totally ignorant when it come to anything new
I can't make it
So you don't know what D.V. is ?
Let me see...
Well...
Is this an Old-Age Pension Plan ?
I don't understand him
Why "old age" ?
Let me see...
Well..
Is this an Old-age pension plan ?
A pension ?
Well...
Is this an employee's pension plan, then ?
I've just about had enough
And so has my ass
Do you know what D.V. stands for ?
Well..
It stands for
"Don't mind"
I can't take this anymore
I'm seriously ready to cry
"Don't mind"
Va...
"Vatican"
Is he serious ?
Why Vatican ?
He took a long time to come up with that ?
This was hard
What the hell is "Don't mind, Vatican" ??
"Don't mind"
Va...
"Vatican"
Oh wait, it's actually
"Don't mind BAKATARE (idiot)"
This guy's really irritating
That hurts
It's utterly meaningless
The night sets in
Just so you know
we have some talented interrogators
at this station
And why not learn some techniques
from these professionals ?
Let's move to the interrogation room
Interrogation techniques...
Learn from the Pros
Interrogation Techniques From A to Z
Come this way
You're looking through a two-way mirror
and obviously, they can't see you
Check this out
There's one suspect
He's been stubborn
and won't budge
Oh good, he's here
He's known to break any criminal's silence
Interrogator
Shoji Murakami
I've got a bad feeling about this
He's got that presence
He radiates an aura
Your hobby is
to travel
You just came back from Izu ??
How is this funny, you idiot ?
Why not talk, huh ?
Larva         Flea    and lice, you moron !
INGROWN NAIL     ingrown nail
SENSITIVE TO COLD     sensitive to cold
Why say it twice ?
Cartilage...Oops, that wasn't it
I see you're disadvantaged already
We both know what you did
The Cartilage, you moron!
RINGING IN AN EAR     ringing in an ear
I don't get this
LONG DISTANT RELATIONSHIP
This really gets to Yamasaki
I couldn't handle this
I don't understand what he means
You can't think too much into it
Wow, look at all those props
I see they edited the hell out of this
Yea, this was easily 30 minutes plus
You know I used be married with kids
This was long
But we're not together anymore
You can leave your family but there are some things you can never part with
And this long coat is exactly that
My favorite coat
He loves that thing
This is indeed...
I see, you decided to escort yourself out at this point
It's been hard
My manager was chatting with a woman at a party one night
And he was asked
"You work for Yoshimoto Entertainment ?"
"Who are you managing ?"
And he said to her, "I manage Shoji Murakami"
She replied, "He has a manager ??"
OK, I've had enough
I'll be back
That was fantastic
What? He didn't get him to talk ?!
He didn't come clean at all
Just wait, there's another one coming in
There he is
Interrogator
Koichi Wajima
PUSH
It clearly says to PUSH !
I'm expecting multiple butt-slaps here
Is he aware this is supposed to be a two-way mirror ?
Um, should I, should I, come back in one more time ?
No ?
What is this guy here for ?
What did you do ?
Why don't you talk ?
I did everything
I'm sorry
Criminal Easily Confesses
How ?
How did this happen ?
How did he get him to talk ?
I don't know
I It happened so fast
What kind of technique did he use ?
Nicely done
Um...
After the interrogation training
they move into another room
What else is waiting for them ?
Here we have an eyewitness of a recent crime
who can possibly identify the suspect
Eyewitness
How to Identify A Suspect
among the line up we have here
Will they be showing us photos to compare or something ?
We have one of the suspects behind this mirror,
Let me know if he's the one you saw
Suspect
Tatsuo Umemiya
You gotta be kiddin' !!
This isn't OK
Was he the one?
I recall he had his hair tied
Is this him ?
Close, but he had big set of teeth
Please stop
No more, please
I think he glanced at us
This is impossible
Absolutely impossible !
Was that him ?
Well, I think his hair was fuller
Seriously, who cares ?
Why bother with full hair or not ?
Is this him ?
He was more like *Gaki Daisho
*Gaki Daisho is the main character of a famous TV series in Japan
What's with that face ?
Is this him ?
I just remembered
He looked more like a Hong Kong movie star
I didn't realize he had such slim legs
Will you please not say anything like that ?
He would just about put on anything they ask him to
It's been already 10 hours
I'm OuYan Fei Fei
OuYang Fei Fei
Announcing the current time
7:00pm
Wow, it's 7pm
Could you guys come with me ?
Just come with me ?
What's going on ?
Just come
We did a lot, didn't we ?
Oh !
Now I remember this !
Let us pay our last respects to Officer Itao, who left us too soon
He lost his life on duty
Funeral for Officer Itao
I would like to begin the funeral for Officer Itao
by asking his friends to speak about him
Itao's Friend
Officer Saito (Heipo)
Dear Officer Itao,
This is officer Saito thanking you for all you did for me
As a fellow member of the Bomb...
You both held your own there
Please pay your final respects to the deceased
He's alive !
How's he alive ?
He's alive ?
He insisted that he's alive
As for the 3 officers in front,
please come forward to pay your final respects
We discovered in Officer Itao's will
a farewell message for Mr. Masatoshi Hamada
Hama-yan...
Do you know who was always willing to help me,
when I was struggling with my life ?
It was none other than you, Hama-yan
You were someone I looked up to
even before I became an officer
And even after I completed my training
I always held you way above
anyone's pedestal, Hama-yan
What's with Hama-yan ?
Then one day you said
Take your time, there's no need to hurry
I see that you're very talented
I couldn't hold my tears back
And you, Hama-yan,
couldn't hold your tears back either
What the...?
The kind words you said to me that day
made it easier to accept whatever fate had in store for me
Because of Hama-yan, I existed
Who the hell is Hama-yan ?
On that note, we will conclude the funeral
with this song,
requested by Officer Itao himself
Itao's wife
She put on some weight
My ass hurts
Thank you for waiting
I've brought your ramen and fried rice
Chinese food delivery
Nobuto Okamoto
What a surprise cameo !
I need to take those dishes back,
so I'm going to stay here until you're all done
I wouldn't like this
I wouldn't like it
Let's finish this really quick
Imagine having to eat so fast
He never changed his face the whole time
Text Message Received
I'll come back for those later
Damn you
Amazing
Kin-chan Family announcing the 8pm hour
Kin-chan Family
If not Chiaki, it's them
Them laughing at the end made me laugh
My back hurts
A Mysterious duo stands-by in the hall
Who exactly are they ?
Our top senior officers are here to greet you
Who comes to mind when you hear "famous detective" ??
What ?
Who could that be ??
Detective Colombo ?
That's right
Yes, yes, yes, yes, NO
The jeans !
We have "W-Jeans" here at the station !
"Bark at the Sun" theme song
Here comes the W-Jeans
What ? What ? What ?
What the hell is that ?
It's nothing more than a green and yellow handkerchief
What the hell are you doing with it ?
WTF !!??
Hey, what the hell is that ?
It's nothing more than a limp rope
WTF ??!!
Click
Where did they rehearse this ?
It's nothing more than a small bag
What're you doing with it ?
Will this be a strong finish?
WTF ??!!
Thank you
Thanks a lot
How ?
Well, since we're already here,
Why don't we hang around for awhile ?
Why the cold shoulder ?
You would be like this if you were in our shoes
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
I'm just saying
When you were in our shoes in a past
you had a very similar reaction
I see...
I'm sorry for not getting that
You gotta understand our situation
We thought you'd appreciate our efforts a little more
You thought your skit would get a better reaction ?
Yeah, I thought it would
But you understand that
we're not in a position to freely laugh, right ?
Well, we thought you'd just laugh regardless
But if we had laughed,
we'd get butt slapped
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
Me ?!
So this is how a batsu is delivered
Amazing
That's some slap !
Incredible
We really don't wanna be bothered
Ouch
That's the worst he's hurt my feelings since we started Downtown
Why ?
I didn't make it ?
Why would you say that ?
A full swing
You know what, guys ?
Since I'm senior to you
you will be spared from a butt-slap
if you greet us with some enthusiasm
I'm sure it will be OK
Say something like, "Good morning !!"
I believe it's acceptable if done that way
But I'd be smiling at the same time
No, it wouldn't count as a laugh
People would see you as an "Upbeat" kid
So when it's a formal greeting, we're spared ?
GOOD MORNING !!
See ?
You're taking us seniors for fools
Fujiwara !
Where's my Fujiwara ?!
Excuse me
Here comes MY Fujiwara !
What do you want to play ?
Well, you're not giving us much of a choice
Let's play
We've played this word game before
Oh, I think we know
Anyway, your Batsu will be the Thai Kick
POP UP PIRATE
*SHIRITORI* Directions:
Players get swords for each syllable of a word.
The swords are then inserted into the barrel
*see
www.shibatabread.com
for SHIRITORI explanation
Are you serious ?
That's a tough rule
POP UP PIRATE
If the player's sword pops the pirate's head, he receives the Batsu
I don't know how much more kicking my butt can take
This isn't anything unusual
We're all playing, right ?
No, just you three
What ?
OK, Fujiwara, you're in, too
Rule:
Four Players including Fujiwara
Why don't we start with Hama-chan ?
Isn't today New Year's Eve ? (OH-MI-SO-KA)
Let's start with KA
I'm picking KA (mosquito)
How dare you ?
Can't you be more adventurous ?
No, I want to stick with KA (mosquito)
Alright, you get one sword then
Hamada Receives Thai Kick !!
This isn't rigged, I swear !
Hamada-san, you got it with just one sword
OK, let's continue, Hama-chan
Please, proceed
How about you start with TSU from word KEI-SA-TSU (policeman) ??
How about TSU-BA-ME (swallows) ??
I'm sensing this head will pop
If you get this again, it'll be something else
Wow, he made it through
Fujiwara, you're up
How about ME-DA-KA (kill fish) ?
Here's your 3 swords
Yamasaki, start the word with KA
I'm going with KA-NI (crab)
What kind of KA-NI ?
If I have to be more specific,
I can't start the word with KA
Don't make me laugh !
What's wrong with just KANI ??
Your butt must be in bad shape
This isn't cool
OK, I'm going with KANI
I'll let you slide this time with KANI
Yamasaki Receives Thai Kick !!
It kills doesn't it ?
It really does hurt bad
I'm not kiddin'
I don't want a Thai Kick
Isn't there anything other than the Thai Kick ?
What would you like ?
How about this, then ?
Let's do some Tongue-Twisters, then
What's the Batsu for this ?
Of course, it's a Thai Kick if you mess up
Tongue-Twister
Stuttering results in
a Thai Kick
I don't wanna another Thai Kick
Spare us from the Kick, please ?
No way
Here's the first one
Say this three times
Say 3 Times: "Bus Gas Bakuhatsu"
(Bus Gas Explosion)
Let's go
Tongue-Twister: "Bus Gas Bakuhatsu"
GASU BAKUHATSU
Hamada Receives his Second Thai Kick !!
What's that on your lip ?
What's the white thingy ??
Wait, listen
I can't stop farting
I'm farting non-stop
Why don't we move on to the next game ?
Let's see some impersonations
How about Keisuke Kuwata ?
Impersonation:
Name one fish as you impersonate Keisuke Kuwata
Yamasaki, you're up
Name a fish while impersonating Keisuke Kuwata
Tuna~~
That was pretty funny
Endo, you're next
Name one fish
Name a fish while impersonating Keisuke Kuwata
Bluegill~~
You two were going at each other
Hamada, you did OK here
Name a fish while impersonating Keisuke Kuwata
Hamada, you're on
Mackerel~~
Will you at least try a little ?
Fujiwara, you're on
Name a fish while impersonating Keisuke Kuwata
Flying fish~~
Who would pick "Flying fish" ??
Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
Let's see Shinichi Mori
Sounds good to me
Impersonation:
Name something "long" while impersonating Shinichi Mori
Yamasaki, you're up first
Carp Streamer~~
Is that considered "Long" ??
What ?
Carps are long, aren't they ?
Bullet Train
Wow
That was an awesome slap
Let's change it up again
Impersonation:
Name a country while impersonating Kenichi Mikawa
Thailand
They're trying to destroy each other
Canada
This turned into a show for you two
You two are just going at each other !
India
Shall we go now ?
I'm still irritated they dissed us
You guys are just gonna let us leave ?
No "Thanks for coming" ??
Oh, thank you for coming
Good job
Thanks
Is music necessary ?
Thank you
See you around
See you soon
That sucked
That Thai kick really hurt me right here
Your left cheek ?
It messed me up
The batsu game is almost half way done
Yoshimoto Entertainment: Vice President
Hiroshi Ohsaki
I'm Hiroshi Ohsaki from Yoshimoto Entertainment
announcing 9:00pm
Hamada-san
How are your hemorrhoids ?
What the hell...?
Mr. Ohsaki announcing 9:00pm...
Indeed
They're holding a welcome party for you guys
Shall we ?
Ah, I remember this now
We're coming with you
Let's go check it out
Show a little more enthusiasm
A Nice Gesture from the Station:
A Welcome Party for the 3 Trainees
This is only for you guys
Unprecedented
Can't you crack a smile or two ?
I'm proud to start the welcome party
for the new trainees
He kinda looks like Fujiwara
Let me introduce you to the legendary duo
who reunited just for this occasion !
Come on out !!
One member of the duo "Alice"
Shinji Tanimura (impersonated by Nobu)
The Other "Alice" member
Takao Horiuchi (impersonated by Fokkie)
The resemblance is uncanny
They look and sing just like the real thing
They look just like them !
Amazing
No way No way
We're fortunate to witness this legendary duo reunite
The duo "Alice" had been broken up for a while
Let's move on to our next act
He's the best folk musician we've ever heard
Let's bring him out !!
Folk Music God:
Yousui Inoue (impersonated by Kannazuki)
Good evening
to you all
What can you do ?
They don't mean any harm
Let's bring out the next act
No adolescents ever missed this imported gem
Here's two actors from that show !
From Beverly Hills 90210
Catherine & Dylan
(Tomochika & Takeshi Nadagi)
Why here ?
Wait a minute
I'll be right there
I'm closer
OK, I'm here
Where were we ?
Why am I always wrong ?
Take it easy
And why're you avoiding me ??
Didn't I tell you to meet me
at the mall in Eastville ?
Why don't you bake me
that cheese cake ?
I tell you what though
What's with raisins in the cheese cake ?
I hate raisins
And how many times do I have to tell you that ?
Wait a minute
You just don't care to remember that
Hold it
What's the matter ?
I don't recall baking
any cheese cake for you
What're you talking about ?
On top of that,
I don't put raisins in my cheese cake
I know what I know
Just calm down
Who are you mixing me up with ?
I know what I remember
Swear on this flag ?
Who knew you had the national flag ?
You got me
Here's the truth
Well.....Kevin is the one
How could you ?
What about all the emails
and all the letters?
Well, um...
I got your emails and letters
Day after day
Listen to me
What about those days you didn't call me ??
I'm afraid you're right
Anyway,
Kevin and I just got together
to have a drink
Don't get upset
Just calm down
How can't I be...
How can't I be upset ?
Dylan, I don't know what to believe anymore
Don't leave
Wait up
You should not have left here
Absolutely not
But I'm coming to get you !
That was a long one
That was funny
That was pretty impressive
That was entertaining
Unfortunately, this will be our last act
From Ishihara group
give it up for this man
Come on out !
From Ishihara Group
Hiroshi Tachi (Producer P)
One left out glass...cigarette
How irritating ?
That's not how that song goes
How can you mess that up ?
You left out "glass"...
What's wrong with him ?
He's not singing loud enough either
Left out "glass" ??
Nobody would mess that up
Everyone would get that right for sure
There's been a lot going on already
So much stuff
Hear me out, Tanaka
We didn't have to be there, you know ?
W-Jeans
We were exempt from this year's event
We had no part in this year's "Batsu Game"
But we thought it'd be a nice gesture on our part
to show some support for you guys
So I was disappointed with your poor receptions
What do you mean ??
We were very welcoming
I thought you guys would erupt with joy
But we get the "Batsu" if we "erupt"
Remember the "Gas Bakuhatsu (explosion)" ??
Honestly, that was a very low point of yours
That's why we don't wanna get old
You also had some weird white stuff coming outta your mouth
What was that you spit out ??
And the shack exploding was something else
I bet Haruka-san had no idea he'd been taped
He jumped, didn't he ?
Elite Detective
Haruka
He had no idea
His face glowed red for a second
Let's get back
to the video !
Good job
As the Game Reaches its Peak,
The Most Notorious Guest Makes Her Cameo !!
Laughter and Screams Fly Around
Sobriety Check Point
Interrogate the Big Star !!
How Do You Deal with A Drunken Celebrity ??
Wait a minute !!
No no no no no no no !!
Legendary Man Revisited...
A Heart-Felt Ceremony
What Do the Three Trainees Witness in the End ??
It's been 13 hours since the start
The non-stop Batsu's have started to take its toll on the 3 trainees
Is this blues music I hear ?
Why don't we continue your training
Come with me
I remember this
This is the first time I've seen this footage
Is that right ?
We had no way of seeing this until tonight
This is it
It's her
Here's Dr. Nishikawa
Medical Examiner
Ayako Nishikawa
She's a medical examiner
This part killed me
Nice to meet you all
You, too
Learn from Dr. Nishikawa
Medical Examining From A to Z
I hope you can learn something from tonight's lesson
First, here are tonight's subjects
Here's a janitor
Subject 1:
Janitor (Mr. Ohnuma)
Here's Mr. Nukumizu
Subject 2:
Yoichi Nukumizu
Nice
Subject 3:
Lunatic (Mr. Nakamura)
Why bother with sunglasses ?
She had me already
Why don't I start the experiment then ?
Experiment 1:
S&M Candles
I'm proving to you that they are corpses
Are you sure ?
I kinda wanted to talk with this guy
See, they're really dead
I saw him move
No, you didn't
Let's move on
Let's aim for his nipples
This isn't good
That looked Ouchy
Are you understanding this ?
They are utterly dead
Let's use 6 candles
I wonder what he's thinking
He's wiggling
I can tell Hamada's really into these types of things
He's loving it
Are you guys OK ?
How about these then ?
Experiment 2:
Paper Strings
I'm going to stick these into their nostrils
But I'm telling you
They won't show any response
God, I wish I could've done this
He's moving
I don't like this
I hate it
Dr. Nishikawa is evil, isn't she ?
Let's see how he does
I'm seriously hating this
We need to get it together
or our butt's are in for a long haul
I can't do this anymore
She's too much into my style (Sadism)
Next, I will use this slipper
Experiment 3:
Slipper
They won't respond to it at all
She's outta control
I hate this
I hate it !
I saw his hand trying to cover his face
No, he's not responding
I'm serious
I can't take this anymore
She wouldn't stop
Incredible
This was nuts
Even dead bodies show red marks
where they were hit
Nonsense
Look, his hair's thinning out from the beatings
No, he's just going bald
Experiment 4:
Electric Pads
Aren't there more sensitive parts ?
Of course, you'd laugh at that
My ass is going numb
Are you still zapping him ?!
That's a long session
Please, no more !
Seriously, no more !
Please stop now !
Lastly, let's see how they do with this
Experiment 5:
Pie Throwing
Amazing
Moving on with the next subject
She has no reservation doing this
See ?
No reaction
What ?
How about if I close both his nostrils and mouth ?
Out of control
She's fearless
I understand this is all for an experiment
But is it really acceptable ??
I'm doing this for your training
Well, I can appreciate your (Sadistic) ways...
What do you mean "your way ?"
Please continue
Why not try a couple more ?
I just saw him sneezing out some pie
Did you see anything funny ?
It was obvious
This was rough for you guys
Hopefully, you got to learn a thing or two ?
I didn't realize how dead they were
This made me not wanna die for sure
It's been 14 hours since the start
That doctor was ruthless
Dr. Nishikawa
The slippers were something else
That type of behavior
makes me laugh really hard
Let's step outside for the sobriety checkpoint
Catch Drunk Drivers
Become Familiar with Sobriety Check-points!
Right now
We have a tough schedule
It was hard
The truth comes out, huh ?
Yes, it came out
The 3 are driven out to the checkpoint
Who awaits them there ?
Checkpoint
*Filmed off public roadways
We're here
I need you guys to learn
how a checkpoint is carried out
Distribute the Breathalyzers
Here's yours, Hamada
For Hamada
Here's yours, Endo
For Endo
Yamasaki, here you go
I'm counting on you
Burdock
Take it
I'll demonstrate once
So watch closely
This shows a person's blood alcohol percentage, right ?
Roll down the window, please
On a "Date"
Mikihisa Azuma
We're conducting a sobriety check tonight
Would you cooperate with us ?
Are you checking for drunk driving ?
Wait
Will you wait, please ?
I'm trying to get to Shibuya
We can help you once your testing is done
I'm Mikihisa Azuma   Haaaa~
How's that ?
No reading
Where's Shibuya ?
Drive straight ahead
And catch the freeway to Shibuya
Go straight here ?
I got it
Thank you very much
Please take this as a token of my appreciation
Statue of Hachiko
in Shibuya
There's a huge crowd at that Hachiko statue
every Sunday ??
It's crazy scary, isn't it ?
Well, I don't think that's "scary" per se
What'd you mean, "crazy scary ?"
Will you just go ?
Shopping Center in Shibuya
There's tons of shoe stores
and fast-food restaurants ?
We know
We've been there
It's crazy scary, isn't it ?
Go on already
Building 109 in Shibuya
We've been there, too
Young and hip girls would call it "Maru-kyu"
Crazy scary, isn't it ?
That's enough already
Why don't you just go ?
Crazy scary
How do you not know Shibuya ?
Here comes another one
This is a busy street
Excuse us
Good evening, I'm Shinichi Mori
Just driving by:
Shinichi Mori ??
We're conducting a sobriety check
will you breathe into this ?
No Reading
Yamasaki, ask him to do it again
If you would, please ?
You didn't find this funny, huh ?
Thank you very much for your cooperation
He's supposed to be Shinichi Mori ?
Well, that's how he introduced himself
Did he ?
But would the real guy do that ?
I see another car
Yes, here it comes
I've noticed a lot of celebrities around here
Will you roll down the window please ?
For the Second Time
Mikihisa Azuma
This isn't fair
Dirty
Weren't you just here ?
And who the hell is this chick ?
It was tough not to laugh at them
And why is she playing with his nipples and stuff ?
I drove straight like you told me but
I couldn't get there
I really need to get to Shibuya or else...
I'm in big trouble
Drive straight up here and get on the freeway
Will that get me to Shibuya for real ?
I'm sure of it
You know Shibuya is where every fad originates ?
We all know where Shibuya is
Just go straight and you'll see
You need to show some respect for us officers
You will be able to get on the freeway
Stop doing that
Ouch
Stop messing around in front of officers
Why is he back again ?
Don't come back
Easy on the gas pedal
Look, he's in neutral
Wait a minute
Are they waiting for us there ?
That car is a little suspicious
Suspicious ?
Let's walk over there
They obviously don't want to be checked
Suspicious Vehicle! Who's Inside ?!
Roll down the window, please ?
What's going on ?
He won't open it
Trashed
Hanako Yamada
Damn, you reek of booze !
She smells like alcohol !
Endo, get her out
Big sis, please
Endo: 15 years in business      Hanako: 19 years in business
Make sure you keep her safe
Carries Her to the Patrol Wagon
So they tell me that
there's plenty of good wines for me
But when I got there,
there was no wine opener
Of course, I couldn't open them without it
They made me wait more than an hour for one
What were you drinking ?
Did I say there was no wine opener ?
What do you do for living ?
I guess I'm an actress
She's an actress
But listen
What the hell are you doing ?!
Hamada san, please watch her
Sit tight
and stay put
There was no wine opener
We gotta watch her
We can watch her now
Please come back when you're done though
Anyway, who are you into these days ?
"Who am I into ?"
Well...
Who do you like these days ?
Well, he's more like...
Don't get up
Go ahead and lay down
Is this good ?
She was so ready to take her clothes off
So who exactly are you into ?
There's someone I admire
I told the Dress Coordinator
"Where's my belt ?"
He hands me this rope
That's no rope, it's a neck-tie
This doesn't do its job, see ?
Stop ! Stop !
Hanako Pulls Down Her Pants
She's outta control
Keep your pants on !
I've seen this on "COPS" before
Let's call for backup
Yes, we need some help here
Hanako Tries to Drag Hamada Back on the Van
No, no, no, no !!
Let him go
Let go
That's a cute ring
What a sloppy drunk she is
Yes, I drank.. but I didn't drive
Good thing you didn't drive
You're OK
Not drunk driving is good but...
Sit tight right here
But you know I..
Listen, listen
Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
So I was
listen,
She had way too much to drink
She's one obnoxious drunk
It's already been 15 hours
After their rigorous training
The 3 prepare for sleep
But...
Here comes...
Hey
We're invited to a monthly get together
held by the prison inmates
These guys look forward to this event
so it'll be.....
a good time...
for sure
Let's show some support
Attend the "Fun"
Monthly Inmate Talent Show
After their bedtime interruption
they are escorted to the recreational room
How will the sleepy and tired trainees respond ??
Good evening !
Inmate# 256
Haranishi
Welcome to our monthly
"Talent Show" !!!!
What the hell is this ?
Without further adieu
Let's get going with the show
He's got one funny face
~ Two words "Oshiri" and "Chinko"
differ by one vowel ~
~ But the two words "Oshiri" and "Megane"
have no vowels in common ~
Makes no sense
Nobody laughed at that
It's kinda funny
I saw you laughing, Yamasaki
Your smile was obvious
Let me introduce our first contestant
They've been here for the past 12 years
for the organized burglary they committed
And they're about to be released in two weeks !
This might be the last we see of them
Let's hear it for them !
Inmate# 56 and 57
Red Yoshida and Golgo Matsumoto
Here's the king of the jungle...
A lion
You know he just woke up
I heard he was asleep up until he was called to do this
I thought this was funny
Next up is
a chimp doing sit-ups
OK, when you're ready
One
Two
Three
Four
Let's go
C'mon
How'd you not laugh at this ?
What's wrong ?
Alright, good job
You're bored ?
OK, then
Why don't we say thank you
to those who showed up tonight
Let's go
Esqueeze us
Thank you very much !!!!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH !!!!
I think all of you guys laughed
These sweat pants don't help
Here's a quick announcement
We unfortunately didn't get enough contestants this month
So why not you
do something for us ?
C'mon up to the stage
Your name ?
I'm Yoshimura
Inmate# 117
Yoshimura
(Heisei Nobushikobushi)
I can see you're ready to go
I can use my body as a musical instrument
Sounds good
Body Slapping Instrument
Let's give it up for him!
Here's a song by Naomi Amuro
Thank you very much !!
Damn...
You got any more for us ?
Of course
I have several more
You mind ?
I'd be happy to
Is that OK ?
Give us one more good one
Here's one of the classics
"If you're happy and you know it"
Anytime you're ready
~ If you're ~
Thank you so much
Not cool
I actually heard the melody
He did a good job
Where has the time gone ?
Here's our last act
She has been one of my mentors
here in prison for a while
She's become a monthly regular here
Inmate# 7
Mother of Haranishi / Tennessee Waltz
This concludes our monthly Talent Show
I'm looking forward to seeing you next month
Thank you so much for coming tonight !
The show ends
and it's already past 1am
Now it's really time for some sleep
But there's another trap set up...
Burdock underneath the comforter
That was creepy
That's a big one
Imagine getting slapped with that
This is the real thing
Let's get to bed
The burdock will come back to haunt them !!
But of course they have no idea
Finally, time for some sleep
Matsumoto and Tanaka plan late night schemes from behind the scenes
Let's make sure they're not awake
The 3 are about to be victims
of a midnight rude awakening
Tonight's crucial
Konyaga Yamada
Tonight's   #$%^
Tonight's crucial
Tonight's crucial...fu
Why's he saying it like that ?!
What the hell is "Tonight's the peak...fu" ??
Tonight's crucial ??
Bookstore's crucial ?
Why "honya" ??
See ?
Bookstore's crucial
It's supposed to be "konya"
Why "Honya" ??
Listen close
Yeah, he's saying "honya" not "konya"
He's saying "honya"
Bookstore's crucial
You mean, "Konaya Ga Yamada" (tonight's crucial)
Give me a break
Hamada-san, you couldn't stop
Yamasaki, you were gone
Say "Tonight's crucial"
How could you guys sleep through that?
Show-hei Hey !!
Showfukutei Show-hei
Calling Showhei
Show-hei Hey !!
Showhei HEY !!!
I was in deep trouble here
We definitely got Endo just then
This isn't good
Yama-chan, you were sleeping ?
I was completely out
Show-hei HEY !
Show-hei HEY !!
We're doomed
We're in serious trouble
I can't fall asleep to this
How can I ?
The second yell gets me every time
Show-hei HEY !
I got past this one
But not the next one
Show-hei HEY !!
It's when he raises his voice that's funny
That got me every time
This sucks
I can't get past that second yell
The second yell was too hard to resist
I can manage the first one but not the second
It's worse because we kept anticipating it
Go ahead, I won't laugh anymore
What's funny is Show-hei has nothing to do with this
Show-hei HEY !
That's just the set up
Show-hei HEY !!
Damn it !!
It was really late and we were tired, too
We couldn't stop laughing
What the hell does Show-hei have to do with this anyhow ??
I see Yamasaki has completely tuned it out
But that's good for now
The only one sleeping
But not for long !
Face to Face Burdock Beatdown !!
That's hilarious you woke up to that!
Lifetime Arch Rival
Mori-man
You're kiddin' me
Wait a sec
How did "Show-hei" not wake you up ??
That looks painful
She doesn't care that I just woke up ?
Out of control
What a nightmare
What was that all about ?
I was hurting
Who ever thought she'd show up ?
She got you really good, Hosei-san
Well, I was in a deep sleep
Sonny Chiba
I'm announcing 2:00am from Los Angeles
I'm Sonny Chiba
What the...?
It is so late
It's past midnight
Analyzing the Mind of an Intelligent Criminal
This footage will show the mind analysis
of a notoriously intelligent criminal
Notoriously Intelligent Criminal
Jimmy Ohnishi
Perform SHIRITORI with only English words
In English ?
Q: SHIRITORI using English words
Damn, I didn't want to end the word that way
Nice, I made it through
Sucks you had to go through this well past midnight
Yes, we weren't expecting it
Describe the smell of the glass jar contents
Q: Open the jar and describe the smell
He's super-sensitive to smells
Man, I can already smell it
Explain what it smells like
What ?
It's like your grandpa's
Grandpa's worn-out sock being rubbed
Rubbed against the inside of a sneaker
and then wiping it on the inside of a toilet like this
So, your grandpa's worn-out sock is wiped
in sneakers
And you rub it and clean the toilet like this...
Just amazing
What's he saying ??
He's just rambling
He just kept speaking nonsense
What's with the sneakers ?
I don't know why he says "sneakers ?"
So your grandpa's worn socks are wiped and
then used to clean the toilet like this
His timing with the dry heave is impeccable
It's not easy watching Jimmy-san around this time of night
It's definitely a challenge
It was a complete surprise
It's been 22 hours since the start
Good morning
I brought you guys breakfast
Rise and shine
He thinks he's being funny ?
C'mon and wake up
Here's your breakfast
Man, it's cold
Being an good officer requires lots of energy
So don't skip your meal
After you're done eating
go ahead and get changed into your uniforms
Man, my ass hurts
My ass is killin'
Yes indeed
I'm actually hurting all over
How does this (belt) go ?
It's a bit tricky
How does it go ?
Yamasaki Tickles Endo
That wasn't cool
Wait a minute
You were obviously trying to make me laugh
What about your belt though ?
What the hell are you two doing at the crack of dawn ?
You're awful
Did you have to do that ?
Seriously
Why did you grab my crotch ?
I didn't, sir
You did, too
No, sir
Let me see your face ?
That's a liar's face
This is disturbing
You've got to bring this one...
What the hell are you doing ?
Give me a break
What'd you do now ?
I didn't do anything
That laugh does deserve a slap though
It's been 23 hours since the start
You guys did a good job over the last 24 hours
This concludes your training
Let's go outside for the commencement ceremony
Patrolling the Area
Officer Heipo
Don't forget to salute him
We gather today to acknowledge
Officer Masatoshi Hamada,
Officer Hosei Yamasaki,
and Officer Shozo Endo
for completing their training
Shakure Police Station
Training Commencement
Mr. Mikawa is here from the Juvenile Division to extend his congratulations
Program 1
Congratulations from the Juvenile Dept. Manager
Good morning to you all
Thick Northeastern Dialect
Congratulations to the three trainees who successfully completed their training
I can never find the right words for this type of occasion
So I thought I'd share some of my personal stories
First, let me tell you that I am the man
who I am because of the environment I grew up in
I actually have three older sisters
And I know that my father really wanted a son of his own...#$$%%
What exactly is he saying ?
What's this about ?
It's his autobiography
Is that so ?
I hope you can take something from this story
as you graduate today
Congratulations
With that we conclude
the graduation ceremony !
Officers
Dismissed !!
Officer Shozo Endo
Congratulations
Officer Hosei Yamasaki
Officer Masatoshi Hamada
Here's to the successful completion of your training
Congratulations
You have become what you always wanted to be as a children
But you haven't fulfilled your hopes or dreams
at this hellish police station
You leave with pain in your buttocks...
Butt-Slapping Counter
Hosei Yamasaki
Masatoshi Hamada
Did I get the most ?
Butt-Slapping Counter
Shozo Endo
Congratulations
You did a great job these past 24 hours
Thank you
Once you cross that gate,
The Batsu Game is officially over
Shall we ?
What a long day
Is this the chief's name written on here ?
Yes, I believe so
He wasn't here for the commencement though
What ?
Don't Cry
Hiroshi Tachi (Producer Nakamura)
One left out cigarette~
..........
He still didn't get it
Why can't he get this song ?
Very irritating
Can you memorize more than just a line ?
Just a couple of more
What's with this editing ?
Thanks for everything
Alright !
We're done
That was a long day
Very long
You just disrespected Hamada-san
Why not just laugh it off ?
We're graduates !!
Laughing is good for our souls
OK, that was amazing
Yama-chan, how could you have slept through that ?
I was really beat that night
You didn't hear the "Show-hei" calls ?
You know what ?
I have no recollection of it
That was hilarious
I feel bad not paying Show-hei san for this
We abused his name way too much
He's not even on the show
You know people will tell him how great he was on this show
and he'll be like, "What show ?"
He'll be puzzled
Lots of excitement
Yes, a lot of it
Watching this whole thing made me remember that day
and it made me exhausted
Are you done ?
It made you exhausted AND ???
That's not fair
Of course, I can't come up with anything !
Don't do that to me
Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com