Subbed and Timed by Outlaws0020.
Outlaws025 on some sites.
Downtown's diary tells about lots of things
One of them is the hard batsu games
Matsumoto and Hamada have both tried it numerous times
It's become a sort of Downtown Trade Mark
The battle between the two keeps on going
Maybe it's because of the pride as man
They are both going after the victory, since that's the only way to avoid the batsu
It might be beautiful to some
Some might even say it's refreshing
But actually..
It's a hard battle for them
Unfortunately for them
A whole new batsu game is about to take place
Um... you're pretty confident in golf, right?
I'm very confident
Yamazaki, me and Cocorico..
us 4 vs you
Doesn't it sound a bit ridicules
No, no. It does sound ridicules,
but it's you after all
Like this
Well then.. let's do it
Do what?
Let's make a showdown
- Showdown?
Why?
Well.. when we are four.
You'll definitely die!
All four of us will have a knife
and go like: "Argh!"
This showdown is being held at the
maple point golf club
At 1:00 pm, precisely on time, Hamada arrives.
Good morning
- Good morning
Is it here?
Keep an eye on it
Huh? Is it the same?
Why's that?
30 minutes later, Matsumoto's team arrives
We are all wearing red jackets
Right?
Yea, it's unbelievable
What this?
Just take it, then I'll take this one
Hey you! What are you doing?
What's this doing here?
Welcome everyone to the Hamada, Matsumoto
and some other persons golf showdown!
Wait a second, what do you mean with
"Matsumoto and other persons"?
Yea, yea, yea
I think it's wrong!
Why do you care?
Well, actually this is only about me
It's still wrong, right?
Yea, yea
He gave up
He really did
It's alright? Peace
- Yea
Now here's the game rules
It's me vs the 4 of you
Every time I do 1 shot,
you guys have 4
We're going to need those 4 huh?
Yea, now we really can't lose!
Since I'm alone, I want Matsumoto
to do the tea shots
That's more fair right?
Yea, yea it is
He thinks I'm retarded
Do your best!
Second is Tanaka, Third is Endo
and last is Yamazaki
The first hole is 354 yards and par 4
It can be bit tricky as it bends to the left
and goes just past a lake
First up is Hamada with his first shot
What?
- He didn't hit it
Here I go
Matsumoto are you okay?
What going on?
You'll get it just as far right?
Yea, yea it'll be alright
But I really need a smoke now
Time for Matsumoto's first shot
I might not do so well today
cause I have a stiff shoulder
Are you okay?
You should have said so earlier!
It's okay
Really?
Okay go!
Make it fly far!
Bad! Bad!
Really bad!
Next is Tanaka. Which club will he pick?
This?
3-Iron... guess it's okay
You look on it as if it's beautiful
Here I go
We rely on you Tanaka!
Where is it going?
Oh, it's there
There's high expectations for Endo.
Can he get it close to the hole?
Yes! Nice shot!
It's okay, it's okay!
Matsumoto's team has used 4 shots
While Hamada just used his second shot
To get it up to here
Hamada's third shot
It's pretty deep
Oh, it is
To the right! Right!
You think it'll go to the right?
You really are stupid
Oh no! This is bad!
Yea it got close!
Can't be true!
- Really?
This is pretty bad for us huh?
We have to be careful from here
Yea, we have to watch out for the bunker
If I just get it over there to the left
then I'll be happy
To the left and you'll be happy?
Just to the left of the edge over there
Left of the edge?
How is Yamazaki's shot going to be?
It's going! It's going!
It's great!
The 2-Iron really worked huh?
I would never have imagined that!
We can still win!
Yea, we can still reach it
Yes, it isn't to late yet
Now it's Matsumoto who have chosen the putter,
but can he pull it off?
Great!
It's going, going, going!
That wasn't bad!
Hamada has used 3 shots
Matsumoto's team has used 5
Hamada is on par if he get's this in.
But it looks pretty hard
Come on, go in!
How is Tanaka going to do?
That's not good , not good, not good!
Good!
Endo it's good!
Good! Okay, okay! Great!
Oh, he's got it!
Hamada made a Bogey
Awesome!
So that'll give you a score on 20, right?
Ok, we'll get no higher than 12
Okay, no higher than 12!
I'll have the pleasure of putting it in
Yea, go ahead
Thank you very much!
After the first hole
Matsumoto's team is in the lead
The second hole is 391 yards and par 4
It's said to be pretty difficult
This looks hard!
Hamada! Get over here!
This looks difficult even for me!
Hamada's tea shot. What's he going to do
at this difficult course
Here's Hamada first shot again
at this very challenging hole
That was all wrong
Now it's Matsumoto's chance to show
what he can do
Matsumoto-san..
You weren't even close at hitting it
Next up it's Hamada again with his second tea shot
Okay?
You used 12 hits at the tea
Matsumoto teams second shot taker is Tanaka
What?
Great!
Wait a sec, that's bad!
Can Yamazaki do it?
Oh, he did it!
Yes! It's there!
But the ball is in a bad position
How?
Wait a sec, I was practicing.
He was just practicing a bit, right?
Matsumoto's last challenge
It's to hard! It's impossible!
After that Tanaka had a shot
and now it's endo
Oh, in the bunker.
But it's good, that doesn't matter at all
After only his tea shot,
Hamada seems to be in trouble
Can he still get back in the game?
This looks pretty good
Matsumoto's team came back on the course
And are still far ahead of Hamada
Yamazaki this bunker looks hard
to get up from huh?
Ah, it does
Endo tells Yamazaki the "rules",
for when he's in a bunker
This is scary
Hey, hey, hey!
Didn't you touch it?
Yamazaki-san did you even listen
to what I said?
You, die!
I rely on you
Okay, okay! We got it out!
This is bad
He got it.
Nice
Have you secretly been practicing?
Yamazaki took his turn and now it's time
for Matsumoto with the 15th hit
I'll try to get it past the bunker
Aim a little bit to the right of the bunker
Is that so?
I'm just doing whatever you tell me to
Great!
What is this?
Super shot!
Matsumoto's miracle shot has forced Hamada
to get on the green
It's going to the right!
Oh, bunker!
My shot early really made me happy!
That's gotta happen more!
Hamada's bunker shot.
Can he chip it?
To long.
Hamada's third try to get on the green
Go further!
Tanaka with a bad 16th shot
Can Endo get it up after Tanaka's failure?
Yamazaki go on!
Me right?
Yea
Don't beam away now,
you have to be in the moment
Come on, home already!
Go home
Here I go
Matsumoto's team is in the lead!
Matsumoto's team has gone inside
for a rest
In the meantime Hamada is out training
for the last hole
Oh, he's outside
Why?
Oh, he got it
Yamazaki maybe you should go out
and tell him to "wait, wait, wait"!
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait ,wait!
Oh, nice shot!
The batsu game is near.
Only one hole left
So last hole
We finally made it to there
It's soon time to
declare the winner
That's right... We'll probably get in a conflict
for first and second place
So Hamada do you think it was
a mistake of you to do this?
Well a little, cause these rules
are really weird
A thing that really surprised me was
that Endo is so good at this
Well I honestly just think I was lucky
to hit the ball that well
Last is this 543 yards par 5 hole
It's breaking to the right
which makes it a difficult hole
Here I go
First up is Hamada's tea shot
Great!
Yards
Wo~ awesome
That was really awesome!
Next it's Matsumoto
Wait a sec
My drive... is like this.
That's why I hit the ground
This time I'll try to raise it higher
I think it's going to work
Okay, let's see
Yards
That was really great!
Hamada had a bad second shot
And Tanaka didn't do much better
Can they make a super shot now?
Matsumoto's team is getting closer
and closer to the batsu game
Then Tanaka 13th shot
Really good Tanaka!
After that Endo made a crooked shot
and Hamada came even closer to the green
Then a chance to get close to the flag
Keep going, keep going!
Matsumoto's team Yamazaki
Bad! This is bad!
Then on the 20th it's Matsumoto's turn
I'll try to get it up this way
The batsu game is approaching
Here I go
Good! Go in, go in!
I'm really good at this!
Then Hamada's put
Hamada missed another put after,
but got it in on his 9th stroke
In the meantime Matsumoto's team
is still on the green
But they don't seem to be able to make
the ball go in
This is it!
What do you say to take
one last hole?
What?
Just one last hole.
Give me a chance
Why did you even have to talk about that
Then no
Wait
We might lose
It's scary
Somehow Hamada got his will,
so they'll play one last round
This hole is 392 yards and par 4
It's straight all the way to the green,
but there's lots of bunkers
It's a difficult hole
Here I go
You surprised me
- Are you okay?
It really surprised me
Matsumoto's team has used 7 shots
while Hamada has used 6
They both in the bunker
Matsumoto teams 8th shooter is Yamazaki
He'll try to take on this difficult bunker shot
No good!
6 shots later Matsumoto's team is still
trying to get up on the green
Oh, that's good
Hamada with a nice out (out of
the bunker shot
Matsumoto's team might regret doing this,
here it's Yamazaki
It went further down
Even further! How are we gonna do this?
You almost can't see it
What is this?
- Wait a second
Go ahead
It's going, going, going!
It went to far now
Shortly after Matsumoto's team
made it to the green
And Hamada took his 8th shot
But even tho Hamada had done everything he could
This happened...
So that'll say that Hamada is up
for a batsu game!
The losing Hamada is to do a batsu game!
In the past Hamada has done many
different batsu games
Such as getting water and skydiving
Getting water in France and later
going to New York to get a pen
Then this time.. what will Hamada have to do