Fifth time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende Chiki Ckihi ~
Asking the top 3 (hotspots) of a town we've never been to!
This is going to be the 5th time already?
Do you remember the towns we've previously been to?
If we don't remember them, is there even a meaning to it?
We're going to a place we've never been
to remember where we've been to right?
Please tell us where we've been to then
I dunno!!
The destination will be decided with drawing lots!!
1 town out of the 6 prefectures in Kanto, roughly 2500 train stations
Which town will they pick this time?
Is this going to be one I...
Whoa.......what's this?
Kazusakubo?
It's read as "Kazusakubo" apparently.
First time I'm hearing that one.
Where even is that?
Everyone is looking it up on their phones right now.
It's read as "Kazusakubo."
This might be the first time it's mentioned on TV.
Kami is another way to read 上
You might even call it Kamisakubo.
Chiba?
Really?!
Kazusakubo should be somewhere around here I think.
Sorry but I'm curious about your head.
I'm more interested in your hair than Kazusakubo.
Play on words 上 and 髪 can both be read as "kami"
(上 means top/above)
You're more interested in this Kamisakubo?
An hour and 30 minutes drive from Tokyo,
Chiba prefecture, Ichihara.
Alright everyone.
Today we're in Chiba prefecture Ichihara -
at the Kominato line, Kazusakubo station.
I'm gonna say this but...
Besides me, the rest of you guys -
are taking the piss out of Kazusakubo right?
Not at all!
You're all like "what kind of place did they brings us to this time..."
We casually got on the platform right?
The train just left and apparently the next one will arrive in an hour.
An hour?
Every day, 25 trains pass through Kazusakubo station.
A station where around 21 people per day get on and off the train.
In that case, the next question is...
So if it only comes every hour -
we have no choice but to start moving.
That's right.
We'll have to ask somebody who's about to get in their car.
Shouldn't we just...
start looking for a UFO instead?
You're taking the piss out of it already!!
I'm not!
Let's start moving.
Let's find some locals, what encounter will be waiting for them?
This tree right here is pretty nice right?
This tree's presence is amazing right?
So Endo is gonna climb this tree at the end?
End it off with Endo climbing the tree.
At least prepare some gloves for me please.
Is anyone from our staff from this town?
Do we know anyone from Kazusakubo?
As Hamada jokes around, they notice something.
Oh look! A car is coming!
Let's go!
Excuse me!
It's someone from Yakult.
Excuse me! Do you perhaps have some time?
They catch a passing car and ask some questions.
This is great, we probably won't find one again.
There's an advertisement on the car though...
That's no problem at all.
Are you filming for TV?
You'll be on TV like this.
Do you want us to censor with mosaic maybe?
You could also stay like that.
This is turning a bit sexual, can we stop that please?
Ishibashi-san, who works at Yakult, has lived in Kazusakubo for 50 years!
What will her top 3 recommendations be?
Do you have any recommendations for us to go to?
Takataki Lake for example.
A lake?!
There is!
There's a lake?
There is, Takataki Lake.
Takataki Lake?
Can you swim there?
You can't swim there!
I'm not in charge of swimming, please stop.
Could we expect some action?
There are swan boats as well.
That's definitely number 3!
If we could maybe get some Yakult...
I've got more than enough!
I'm doing my delivery rounds.
You're buying them.
As a thank you for her recommendation, they buy some Yakult!
~ Random chatter ~
Thank you very much!
It's been a while since I drank Mirumiru S
Delicious
I used to drink this a lot.
Really?
It's pretty good for your colon as well.
We're swimming apparently.
I'm gonna be pissed if we're swimming.
I really don't care.
Let's just stop.
They'll be heading to Takataki Lake by car.
There will probably be some people at the lake as well.
That's right, we could ask them too.
Will there be people?
Will there?
This place doesn't really look like it has a lake.
Wow!! He said it.
I'm just gonna stop talking.
Is that it?
That's a dam right?
The tension isn't really rising...
You just plainly said that.
It only took 7 minutes to arrive at Takataki Lake.
Takataki Lake is the largest water storage area in Chiba prefecture.
The boat and bass fishing leisure activities are very fulfilling.
Excuse me...
Is it possible to get on a swan?
How many people are able to get on?
Only four people can ride in the swan.
Three people in one and two in the other.
We would love to see a 2-shot of Downtown!
Rock, paper, scissors!
That was rather bland.
It would've been great if it was the two of Downtown.
That's right, that would've been nice indeed.
That's just what the results are.
Oh, would you like to join rock paper scissors too?
Unfortunately a Downtown 2 shot didn't get realized.
This one is for two people right? The one over there is for three?
Yes, this one's for two people.
You didn't put a camera on the swan?
Why didn't you put a camera on it?
There was a lot of water in them...
The swan boats were flooded so they got on normal boats instead.
Thank you very much!
We'll be going now!
How long do we have?
30 minutes.
Let's set sail for some sightseeing at Takataki Lake!
I don't think I can pedal for 30 minutes.
I don't think I can either.
How far should be be going?
Where the dragonfly is...
Around where the dragonfly artwork is.
Let's head over to the artwork I guess.
The symbol of Takataki Lake, the Dragonfly artwork.
It's a great dating spot, you can make a 30-minute round trip with the peddling boat. However...
How exactly should we be enjoying this?
Are you having fun?
I'm having fun, yes.
Hmm, yes it's... fun.
The old geezers don't know how to get excited.
Alright let's put this engine in full power!!
Their tension starts to rise a bit.
Yeah so... They won't use this.
The director will definitely cut this out.
They definitely won't use this right.
They can't get excited after all.
I'll ask once more but, are you having fun?
What about you guys?
How is it? It's fun!
It's fun.
I'm having a blast.
When exactly are you having fun?
Please tell us!
When the two of us... go forward like this...
When we're going forward
We're like "Ah, we're going forward" I guess.
*same as Hamada*
Alright.. let's go.
Let's head back.
They return to the port with barely any footage on the boats.
Yeah... This is awful.
I don't think I'll be able to forget about this.
This was...
really fun you know, Takahashi (director).
The most fun thing ever.
Really! Really!
Should we get on these ones next?
Sure thing? We'll wait for you right here.
Never mind!!
That was fast.
The boats are a recommendation for families and couples!
As we continue, what will number 2 be?
Well, there's also something that you could do with animals.
Staff: Do you mean Elephant Kingdom?
Yes Elephant Kingdom!
There's something like that?
It's a five minute car ride.
Elephants, camels, giraffes, you can touch all of them.
That sounds like an amazing place!
If that's gonna be 2nd then...
this one shouldn't even be on 3rd!
It's a 5 minute ride from Takataki Lake, let's start moving!
If you asked that lady to hug somebody, she would definitely pick me.
You're her type maybe? Maybe it's the muscles.
I noticed while you were shaking her hand
that she was saying "so similar..."
She said I looked very similar right?
Maybe you look like her husband?
That would be weird.
Those words flew by after taking a commemoration picture.
Looks very alike!!
She said that right? "So similar..."
I really think she might be wrong.
You'd think so right?
But maybe there is someone who looks a lot like you?
Maybe I look exactly like some YouTuber.
You'll find out more about this in the second half of the show.
And thus, they arrived at Ichihara's Elephant Kingdom.
With roughly 90 different species, there are around 400 animals to be seen.
The biggest elephant performance of the country is a must-see!
They'll be taking a stroll as they head to the elephant hut.
They've got a bit of everything.
This slope is way too steep.
It's an American Beaver.
There's the beaver!
Hey, American Beaver!
He's the worst!
He's thinking "an annoying visitor just came."
Are you an American Beaver?
That's an American Beaver alright.
You're the worst visitor.
They're big!
That tail is pretty amazing right?
Amazing right!
How they use it in water is amazing.
They're really close to us.
Hey! Are you a female?
I'm sorry, beaver!
They already feel at home and they start getting more excited.
It can attack with it's butt.
That scared me!
It got a bit excited
(Matsumoto might be refering to Takarazuka Revue here.)
Are you Takarazuka or something?
There's a pony.
Llamas.
As that is going on...
Yikes!
What the hell!
It's the cameraman!
Wait a minute! That one was way too close!
You should know!!
He was being way too frantic, the way he moved.
We all saw him coming here.
They finally arrive at the elephant hut.
There they are.
They're huge!!
They're riding them.
This one is slightly balding.
It's a bit fluffy.
Staff: Is it possible to enter?
You can hang from an elephant's nose.
Did you hear that?
That's like a dream coming true for you.
Let's all do this?
Hanging from a nose's elephant.
You mean an elephant's nose right?
They get special access to enter the elephant space.
The one hanging from it's nose will of course be...
This is Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende after all.
This is kinda scary though.
Wow - this is amazing!
Its breathing is crazy too!
Thank you.
Hamada, you try it.
Why me though?
Because you'll never be able to do it again.
Ask it to grab your neck.
Next up is Hamada.
Its power is really amazing.
It's a chimpanzee!
Weren't the chimpanzee's over there?
This looks like a scene from the Jungle Book.
That was scary!
That nose though.
It'll win 100%
Thank you for today's experience!
What is Kazusakubo's number 1?
They asked the staff from Elephant's Kingdom.
If you go in the direction of the dam by the tall waterfall...
...there is an Italian pizza place.
The name is BOSSO if I remember correctly.
That should be pretty close from here right?
Do you go there often?
I've been there once...
It's a five minute ride from Elephant's Kingdom.
Does anybody know what "BOSSO" means.
Buono means good.
Good as in "This is pretty good."
Why would you name your restaurant like that?
It's more like in a modest way.
Like you're not overdoing it.
Let's ask them.
You're really gonna ask them?
Kazusakubo's number 1 spot!
A pizzeria located at the shore of Takataki Lake.
We came back here after all.
Such a fancy restaurant like this.
You wouldn't expect that when you arrive at the train station.
They've got a stone oven.
Where should we sit?
Pizzeria BOSSO, Kazusakubo's number 1 spot.
The handmade pizza's are grilled to perfection.
We could totally end it off here.
We already went to three places right?
All that is left is Endo's intentions, right?
With this show Endo usually ends with something unruly.
Separating from the group and doing something on his own.
Doing something he really wants to do.
That's what the staff told me at least.
That guy over that told me to say it.
That guy told me to tell Endo.
You told him to climb the tree!
This is actually the first time I'm seeing you.
Because he said so!!
Yes...
He said "yes."
What I'm also wondering is who I look like, according to the lady from the boats was saying.
She said that indeed.
What was the true meaning behind those words?
Since we're waiting...
Staff: You can go and ask.
Right now?
Right now is better.
You're not really into pizza right?
I'm actually a massive pizza lover.
BOSSO's highly recommended pizza arrives!
A pizza topped with Chiba's local onions and green chilies.
How will the taste be?
Itadakimasu~
The sweetness of the onions!
This is very sweet!
This is way too good!
Whoever decided to put this on a pizza -
is a genius!
Tasty!
It's delicious.
Weren't you supposed to ask about the store's name?
Buono means good/delicous right?
That's right.
In Italian.
What does BOSSO mean?
It means something like an Italian coming in and using ingredients from the Bōsō area.
Right!!
"Right!!" My ass!
It's a coined word.
Alright, I'll be going I guess.
After this, the true meaning behind those words will become clear.
I'm such a pizza lover and yet -
I'm the one not eating pizza.
To find out about those words,
Endo rushes to the boat place
Dessert pizza!
It's dessert time on the other side.
There's was a lot we saw today right?
Right!
There strawberry in there and yet...
Hama-chan didn't get a single strawberry?
You're hogging all the strawberries for yourself!
Nothing for Hama-chan...
While the other guys are having fun at the store, Endo is...
Good afternoon!
Finally, he can ask the true meaning behind those words...
You said with a very small voice...
"He looks so similar" right?
Who does he look like?
Not similar in a way of looking like somebody but...
He was just like he usually is on TV.
So you meant "similar" as in how he usually is on TV right?
I wouldn't really know who he looked similar to.
That's okay, no problem at all.
While we found out the true meaning behind those words...
They decided to wrap it up here.
We have to wrap it up here too.
That's right!
Ending it off with some food feels pretty good.
Usually it's at the start.
It was delicious!
Delicious!
Staff:  That's a wrap.
Let's go home.
He wanted to go alone after all.
He was in such high spirits.
After a five minute delay...
Alright, we got back at BOSSO.
Huh?
You know...
When I crossed that bridge...
Matsumoto's and Hamada's car passed me.
At that point I already knew...