Yanaoka (director) seems to like this theme very much
-Yanaoka is the one who likes it?
-Yeah, Yanaoka loves this
-I see
-Yeah
And Cocorico is on fire with this theme
No, we're not on fire
We're just always getting the joker
No, no, we're not
We wanted to show off our senses to the audiences
But then Cocorico takes all the attention
-Yeah, you're right
-Well, that's true
-I didn't get the joker for even once
-Yeah, not even once
And this is already the third time
Let's welcome the bunny girl
I see, so not even once
I even got it once
Hey, too fast, that's too fast
You didn't even look at her face
At least look at her face first
So better look from above right?
Yeah, that's too fast
Subbed by Appieopie, more episodes at
www.laughseejapan.com/user/18797
The highly praised theme "Gaki Jiji-nuki"
Each card has a different question on it
The rule is the same as Old maid,
you win if you have no more cards left
But if you lose, you'll need to perform
based on the instructions of the last card
Let's decide the dealer first
Let me spin the roulette, alright?
Yeah, go ahead
You haven't spun it before
No no no no...
Not even spun one grid
I thought I would at least spin one grid
That doesn't even count as a Boke
That is unexpected
-Finally spinning the wheel
-That is how it should be
Come on, it's still Tanaka
Always these two
-We can't look at it right?
-Yeah, we can't
Ready?
I hate this...
No one wants to be punished before the 60th birthday
We should be having a celebration instead
Indeed
-All animals...
-Yes you're right
This time, the theme is
To mimic the sound of animals' shouting for real
It is all spread out
All spread out!
-For real?
-Yes, it should be real
Not the kind of fooling around with kids?
Be serious
Be so realistic that the animals may even gather around right?
So real that it may even attract female animals over?
Yes, be serious
Indeed, I was giggling when I see these cards
OK. let's get going!
Got it
Hey, it only took short moment
I didn't know how to do it for this one
Sheep?
Well, well, well...
Yeah, it has to be a serious yell
Yeah, a serious one
The kind of yell which attracts females
Very few cards left for Yama-chan, less likely to lose
So many cards!
I really hope to match this
Yeah, got it!
This one
I actually didn't want to do this one too
Well, yeah
This one is not wanted either
I see
During first half, all members smoothly assembled same two cards
So that's a wolf
Well, what about this?
I would say it is just fine
Yeah, relatively speaking
In comparison to the others
Did you keep peeping at my cards like crazy?
Those cards were picked by me, you have been peeping for a while, right?
Seriously, I didn't peep those cards
Alright
All due to peeping before?
You've peeped, right?
I only got these cards left
-Everybody only got a few cards left
-I still have four cards
Come on, just let Hamada do it
Actually having more or few cards doesn't really matter
-Yeah
-Of course that is how it should be
Why is this card sticking out?
Trying to seduce you
Everyone, good to have this one paired up right?
Which means I'm done!
-That is great
-What? Is that real?
That's amazing
-You're so strong
-Why on earth is that?
Come!
Oh yes, it came
For real?
-It is goat!
-Don't want a goat too
I have to match it this round
Ugh, it is first time seen again!
First time seen this?
I definitely don't want to do this one
Got a couple?
Got it!
Eh?
-No way
-So happy
So happy
This means that...
Yeah, I'll win if this one matches
If not matched...
Just wait a moment
I see
It probably won't match
Yeah, I hope so too...
Probably it takes another round back and forth
Yeah, lion pair
Hamada wins
Then, Tanaka loses for sure
Though certain but which animal?
You need to make us think that this animal is actually in the studio today
I am going to draw the card
Well, the couple is cat
Which means
What?
Tiger!
Be serious
This is quite tough
That's like the High tension theme
And ranked number 10
That is ranked number 10
Not good enough
I have seen this before
That's terrible
The theme is different
Tanaka, cool down, cool down first
This is just awful
It's like watching some boring zombie movie
A really boring one
An exceptionally disappointing zombie movie
I know that feeling. I was like that just now?
That's the worst, that's terrible
-I'll spin it now
-Okay
I'm gonna spin it a lot
Come on, it's Endo!
Seriously what's happening?
It has been these two folks all the time
Matsumoto-san, looking to you!
I won't see it either
-Did you flip it?
-Yes
-I want to do that too, you know?
-Yeah, yeah
I actually wanted to shout as a tiger
The next Jiji-nuki theme is
To improvise and compose something based on the characters on these cards
So it's this pattern again
-Yes, there's various artists
-It's all spread around
This time the theme is to compose an original new song
-Eh?
-That's impossible, seriously
Improvise a new song for these famous musicians on the cards and do Cappella
-This is too hard
-That's just ridiculous
Start the game right away
This time we ask everyone to predict the joker as well
-You only got 3 cards
-Yeah, 3 cards
There is always some comments every time
Ugh! That many cards?
Super many cards, is that real?
Well, based on past experience, people with many cards eventually win
Well, but...
Eh, none?
Eh, really?
How come...
Ah, I'm so sorry
Didn't say this until now...sorry!
Please listen to me...
I have cards in couple
He should really be punished, right?
Yeah
After playing tiger, my brain is full of blank
-You should know when you see it in the beginning
-Yes it is, though it is
Saying your mind went blank and tiger is a pun of white tiger
-You're not allowed to say those puns
-Like the "Kitano-san" you said before
Like your "Kitano-san"
This card came so many times
It came so many times
Don't say "Kitano" dude
I did the same thing last time
Can't escape from my radar
Please excuse me for this
Furthermore, it's Ei-chan
Not exactly understand what it means by "furthermore" though
Alright? I will just draw the card
-Hamada-san's turn
-Really?
I haven't drawn the card yet
Yes you did
I said "no matching cards yet"?
And you said "sorry"
Though I really didn't draw any card, anyway forget it
It is not about "forget it"
Alright, this one
This is it
Who is this?
Nakajima Miyuki-san
-Perhaps it is considered a good one
-Yes, I would think so
After that
This is difficult in another sense
Thank you very much
Yonezu Kenshi-san
-I don't know about him
-I don't know either
This is very tricky
What about this one?
(Matsuda Seiko)
Yes, I feel it is good
Quite difficult
Really?
Well, because it is female
It looks like those difficult ones are avoided one by one
The outcome could be out pretty soon but...
Let me finish it
12 minutes after the game was started
-First time..
-Ugh even until now?
So far no one has won
The person that breaks the balance is
If can't decide, just pick the middle one!!
It is quite loud, these two gentlemen
Yeah, that was so loud
Coming!
*(Card) Mori Shinichi
The first to win
Hamada wins
That's awesome
Endo must had want to do this one
*(Card) Mori Shinichi
Well, on the opposite, it's actually shy to do this one
Opposite?
How far are you away?
15 mintues later
Come on, I'm sick of this
I'm enough of this
This is enough
It is the first time for this person to come
Come on, really? Really?
Please, please
Oh, this again
Matsumoto-san wins if he can match this
I don't want to sing!
Pick one
If not sure, just pick the middle one!!
Is this the tiger just now?
Let's see, is it coming?
Oh no, it's not
This is the first time seen
Here comes the first-time seen
18 minutes after the game starts
Now, the cards at hand for 4 players are as the above
And among those
These three cards are tricky ones
Which one is joker?
Please, please, please!
I really don't want to sing
Enough is enough!
Super difficult!
Yama-chan, Yama-chan, let's game over after your drawing
I will finish the game, please!
-Oh yes!
-Really?
It's Julie
Matsumoto-san if you can get this one
Yeah right, my turn to draw, right?
-Only got this card now
-After drawing this card...
Matsumoto-san if you can get this one
Yeah right, my turn to draw, right?
Only got this card now
It will become the Cocorico battle again though
Please! sincerely, really sincere
Coming, coming
Please, please
Get the right one, get the one
This one right? This one right?
Please, please, really sincere
Feeling good, feeling great!
Bravo!
It is fortunate you got that one
This is really incredible
This card will be granted to Takana-san unconditionally
This card...
If this card matches then game finished
This card was here since the beginning
I was really worried about this card
Let's finish with this card
Yes, let's get it done with this card
Oh please, here comes the card
No, no
-Please!
-No!
Not the right card!!
So weak
What is the matter? You two have been several rounds back and forth
Good, good
-This time Shozo will pick the card
-Yes
Please! please! please! please!
Pick one
Which one could it be?
I'll pick this one
Go, go!
Get it, get it!
Oh yes!!
It's Yosui Inoue-san, and this card will be given to Tanaka-san
Can you show us those 2 cards?
So it's Nagabushi-san or TUBE
Let's turn this card and see which one is this
-Must start right away
-Yeah, you must start singing right away
Think about it now in your mind
-Come up with a plan now
-Yes, yes, yes
-Must start right away
-Yeah
So it's Nagabushi Tsuyoshi's new song
*Nagabuchi Tsuyoshi was sometimes called a "gangster" due to his appearance and the roles he played in dramas
Was called little gangster
Aren't you even mindful with that?
Take a piss, and come up with this weird style?
What do you think about this Japan?
All full of pee
Towards tomorrow, let's run
Wonderful!
Really? Really?
-This is great
-Thanks god
-He lost because he cheated in the beginning right?
-Yeah, God is watching
So that's why I lost
So as a punishment, your singing scene needs to be cut
Because it was funny
Perhaps just mute it?
It will be muted
Only with mouth gestures like "paku-paku"
No way
People will think "What's the matter with Tanaka? Why is he mumbling?"
So strict
Because it was funny
Isn't that great? Is there anything not feasible?
Cut, just cut anything funny
One more round?
Yes, the last one
-The last one is Batsu game
-This one is annoying
The last Jiji-nuki theme will be Batsu game
The punishment for this round, is the classic nose hook
Now the game starts
These four cards are quite subtle
Only got these cards?
Yes, I got 4 cards
This is quite awful...
These punishments are quite lame
*(Card) Stick your tongue to the fan
Hey no, this is absolutely no way
Some are absolutely not possible, right?
Yeah
Like are you joking?
This card
Ah, none
This one right
You got it?
Yes, got the matching card
*(Card) Eating raw meat
And this one is just insane
(Eating raw meat)
Actually this is could be the better ones right?
Eh? Really?
You got it?
Seems to have seen something
-Oh, looks like got something
-Good for you
This one was annoying too, look
Pinch the tongue
-No way
-Dislike this very much
Please, anything else?
*(Card) Freaking hot tofu skin
Eh, what the heck is this?
Don't come to grab dude, not ready
Tidy here
Hurry up dude!!
So difficult
-So difficult
-This is one set
Yeah, I noticed this too, this conversation is becoming a set
The sensor devices for you two have activated
Ah, what is this?
*(Card) Skull bowling
What is this about? Damn
Let's just time it
Yeah
The one with the most cards lose
Last one minute
That's too fast!!
Too fast, one minute left
And I have disadvantage with so many cards at hand
His Tsukommi is also on fire today
Right?
Saying like "Too fast!"
No, please stop mocking me
After that
Oh!
These two cards match
-Bicycle on top of forehead
-This is good news
Tanaka-san with only 3 cards left, everyone got his hands ready
And now, the joker card starts action
*(Two cards) Nose hook bottle and Nose hook floating
No, no, no, no, not this one! Though these two cards look alike
Really, let me win this time!
Wow here it comes again
Here it comes again, comes again
When not able to decide, pick the middle one
Don't know what you are talking about
Yee, it comes back again
(Nose hook bottle)
It's back
Recommending this card
No no no no
-No way dude
-I didn't see this card
-Really?
-Just based on feeling
What difference does this make?
(Nose hook)
*(Two cards) Nose hook bottle and Nose hook floating
What is the difference?
There are such kinds of cards, right?
Feeling like "what's the difference between these two cards?"
I will take care of this
Just let Tanaka do it, I really want Tanaka do it
-Come!
-No way
Don't match please!
Lying right?
He has no understanding of how to be funny
There is slight difference though
-Slight difference
-The same skull bowling
Oh yes!
If it goes that way, we won't be good
But Matsumoto-san never got the joker right?
I don't want to do the Batsu game,
anyone can do it and it'll just be the same
Please
Damn it! Doesn't look good
Put it down, put it down
This sucks
Please, not like that
Oh, I can see this, this one
Really? No way, no way.
It's this one right? The two cards that
make you think "what's the difference"
Like stay home and homestay
Come on, please, let me pick the right card
Let's see
Please don't
*(Card) Sumo wrestler press
Ah, come on, not this one!
Thanks god
When is this going to end?
I want to win, I want to win!
Want to win
End it here
Why? Not this one
It is about time to finish
Otherwise it is not in good shape
About time to end!
Let me win!
I saw this one before!
It's not ending at all
Yeah, it's not ending
Come on
This is a good chance for you
I really think Downtown should just do it
Pick the middle one intentionally!
Hmm, did the same just now
What the heck is this?
Not right, definitely not this card with so many white space
Huh?
It shows up again!
That homestay and stay home thing
Totally different though
The meaning is different
About to draw, put it down
Hurry up
Let's see
Would like to win here
Not even sure if he has my cards though
Yeah, don't know if the card has switched back
Pick the first card on top
Oh, come on, what?
This is a really long offense and defense
Please, enough
Please, please, this is enough
Just let Downtown try once
No way!
That's definitely unforgivable
That's just definitely unforgivable
No no no no, so
That's absolutely no way!
I actually matched it, yet continued playing
Eh, what do you mean?
That's scary
Let's watch replay once more
Hamada should had win for picking Matsumoto-san's nose hook card
What the heck is this?
However, although the cards actually matched
Hamada continued to play the game
Just let Downtown-san do it
No way!
You saw the card after picking it from Matsumoto-san right?
And it matches so you should just put it down
I thought there is no matching so put out 3 cards
This absolutely deserves punishment, right?
Hey, why?
Batsu game!
This has no choice
This is really shocking
I've been doing this so many times
Your favorite
There's still zero bottle though
Eh, zero bottle?
Yes, zero bottle
It's already hooked quite a lot though
The rocket start is awful
He's stretching his legs
-One bottle now
-That's cheating
I would like to eat dinner while watching this
Such dinner show would be nice
Alright, now with second bottles in
With the third bottle
The posture has totally changed
From the third bottle, it is strengthening
Can see inside quite a bit
Yes, not bad, not bad!
-Hold on to it
-It's going to break, it is breaking!
My nose is breaking apart, stop!
Stop!
Scary! Scary! Scary!
It is going to break here!
Very very painful!
-Okay, enough
-Finish
No way, no way
-Oh, fun game!
-That hurts
What had you confirm about after drawing from my cards
Yeah?
Why didn't I notice it?
He must be shocked
The cameraman
He must had wanted to say it
Just tell me then, dude!
He must be thinking "what's happening?"
All he can do is to slowly blur the focus
To be considerate
Yeah, blur the focus to be considerate