Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
So, Matsumoto, we're wearing tuxedos for today, why is that?
Yes, yes
That's right
As for today's episode...
Do you know the old dude card game, right?
Of course we know it
It's kind of different from the old maid
Old Dude:
It's a variation of the game "old maid"
instead of the joker card, there's a single unpaired card
I wanted to try an original Gaki-game based off it
I'm going to hand out several paired cards to you
But there's a single card without a pair in the deck
And that's the old dude, right?
If you end up with it, you have to do the task written on it
If this turns out to be fun, we're scheduling 8 more episodes
8 more?!
Isn't that too much?
Is it really that good?
We're doing this for two months?!
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TYPESET BY MATTEE53
Here's a new project: Gaki Old Dude Game!
There are different topics written on the cards
15 different topic-cards (total: 30)
These are the original Old Dude cards
Discard all the card in your hand, and you win
The cards will be dealt to each member
And you're done as soon as you can discard them all
Lose and you'll have to perform the demand written on it
If you're the last one,
You'll have to do the unreasonable demand written on it
First off, let's see who's going to be the first
Come here, Bunny-chan!
The first one between us?
That's right, we have to decide it
It's important, it can give you an advantage
Maybe, or maybe not
Ah, she actually has a p*ssy
What are you talking about?
It's Bunny-chan
I thought an old dude would show up...
That would have been creepy
Come on, we're Gaki!
This is the first step
Choosing the leader via roulette
The leader is gonna take advantage
Yeah, that's right
He'll have fewer cards
Spin the wheel, Hamada
Huh? Why me?
It has to be him
Looks like it's Endo
I remember Endo playing old maid once
Lifting a single card up to raise suspicion,
it's a game of strategy
But now, you have to take 1 card out of the deck
Right
Right, right
And that's the old dude, right?
Just take one out
Randomly? Ok
Alright, this one
We're not gonna see it, right?
And that's the old dude
Of course we don't know which one is it
But you have to show it to the camera
Which card is the old dude?
Just flip it towards the camera
Alright, here I go
Alright, so we don't know it
Sayuri
Yoshinaga
Tanaka just tried to take a peek
I didn't don't say such things
You just glanced it
Why should I do it?!
You did it again?
I did not!
Come on guys, let's do this
I think that if Tanaka would go to a bank,
they won't lend him any money
What are you talking about?
- They don't trust him
Do you really see me like that?
What is this show trying to turn me in?
We now have 29 total cards in the deck
That's right
We're all getting 6 cards
6 cards for each player (leader gets 5)
But Endo is the leader, so he'll take 5 instead
That's how we start the game
I'm pumped for this round
And that's it
I'd hate first rounds...
We'll follow this order
There's an illustration and a name
Wait a minute
The theme of this round is "my memories with stars"
My memories with stars
I never met any of them
There's a load of people in here
Cool, isn't it?
Me too, I haven't met most of them
That's even better
So, if you lose this round...
You have to come up with a made up memory
I see...
The loser will face the camera by himself
And will start telling his own story
I really hate those
You already have one pair?!
Ah, Tatsuro Yamashita?!
We got a pair out already
Nakajima Miyuki too?
Oh boy
We have two great characters out already...
That's right, we have stars from different worlds
You can talk about their field of activity,
without saying their names
Alright, Endo, you go first
Between the ones I have in my hand...
They're all from different worlds...
I only ever met one of them
I think... two? Maybe?
What about you, Hosei?
I never met any of them
I also have a lot of foreigners...
There are even foreigners?
Foreigners?
I have one woman, all the others
are sportsmen and such
I don't know much about mine
Really?
I think I have met one of them, at least
And you never met the others?
That's right
If Hamada says he never met those, we're screwed
Sorry but I have a pair too
What took you so long?!
Come on man, there's a picture,
you should have noticed it before!
Also, Justin Bieber?!
Endo 5 cards
Hamada 4 cards
Hosei 6 cards
Matsumoto 4 cards
Tanaka 4 cards
If you lose, you have to come up with a fake story with that star
Lose and you'll have to tell a fake story,
It's time for old dude's game - "my memories with stars"
Do you have anything good?
We should show them to the camera
That's right
Let's show them all
Is...
Is this ok?
staff) it's fine
Why do I have these many cards?
But he's about to take one from yours
So many cards
You'd end up having the whole deck
Yeah, probably
It doesn't look good for me
Is that the card you had?
Exactly
So many cards
I'm glad he took it!
Who's gonna lose?
I have no clue which one to pick
The hell is this roster?
They're all different stars!
Of course they are, they have to be unpaired
What should we do?
Alright, let me take one card...
This is strange...
The stake is high, we gotta make up a story...
I'm not familiar with this guy
This guy over there...
It's this guy again!
He's back!
He's wandering around
Who's wandering around?
I don't know
What the hell is going on?
I have no clue
This is going so bad, what the heck?
Really...
- Right
What the fuck?!
At least we took those out
Yeah, at least those
- Ok, but...
Alright, I'll pick this
This is incredible
- Your turn, Endo
Man, I want to draw a pair so bad...
Did you draw it?
- Wow! Are they there too?!
Still new cards?
- Of course
Really, this one...
Do you know them?
I don't know them at all
You thought they weren't even in the deck
I see... so this person was here too
None of them seem to be drawing any pair...
Again
Oh man
This one
It's back again
Really?
That guy is running around in circles
Another important point
But there's another important point in this game
While we're playing this, to be honest
You think about an episode, right?
Right     - Right
And you're like "oh, I should go for this one"
And then someone takes that card from you
And you're like "that's MY card"!
Yeah, you make up this good story
and then someone snatches it away
I totally get you
Come on guys, let's keep going
Here's a pair
He's been doing great
But I'm glad this guy's out
Yeah, Ou-san...
What? I see...
One pair and you're done
'Cause he already drew two pairs
Right
Sorry about that
This is irritating
Here it is!
He's finally out!    - It's Tiger Woods!
This would have been bad
Yeah, totally
Nice one, now we're playing
I still have no clue
Oh man
Now I'm getting scared
This isn't coming to an end
It's time to end this
You really suck at making pairs
I'd love to end this, but...
Come on, Endo
I've never seen this person before
Oh my god...
Really, it's my first time seeing this card
The first of them to clear his cards up...
Let's see if... oh!
I'm clear!
Here, I'm done!
Let's move on
I'm the first one
And not only him...
Matsumoto, please...
What the hell, dude...
I did it!
It's this guy again!
He's back!
And even Maezawa, the card which tormented Hamada...
And that leaves only Cocorico
It's down to the two of us
And if Tanaka makes a pair now...
If he pulls it off...
Let's see...
Wait a second! Wait, wait, wait...
Ready?
- No, give me a sec
Which one is it gonna be?
Yeah, I don't know
What should I do? My memories with them...
As soon as you lose, you gotta start your story
Get your episode ready
Which one is it?
Who is it?
I wonder...
Let's see who's the old dude
It was this lady
So it was miss Sayuri Yoshinaga...
Endo's memory with Sayuri Yoshinaga
If I remember correctly it was... last year? I guess?
At least I think so
Anyway, as you know I like golf and I often play it
And one day Miss Yoshinaga's group played before mine
So I kept on playing while glancing at them
It may sound rude, but I don't think she was a skilled player
Her group's play was really slow
We were about to catch them up, so
We thought we should say them something, but
I was wondering what to do, and then...
I just... hit my ball
And the ball flew so fast and hit
Miss Yoshinaga's head
And she got really angry at me
I apologized as soon as it happened
And it felt like everything was good
Then, I went out to lunch
The hell is he talking about?
Such a long story, huh?
And I played the next course
And when I did, I hit my ball, I shanked
And I hit Miss Yoshinaga again, right above her left eye
And again, she really got mad at me
This isn't going to end
He's stuck
He is
And I... apologized
It's pitch black ahead
There's no escape road inside his head
But then, in the end...
Is that ever going to end?
I told her "it's not like I hate you or anything"
And then we all had dinner together, that's it
Thank you
Were you planning this episode for Tiger Woods?
This episode isn't real, Endo came up with it
It makes sense, with Tiger Woods
You were planning it with someone else, right?
Were, there are lots of sportsmen, so...
To be honest yeah, I was thinking about Tiger Woods
And then he disappeared,
but I couldn't get "golf" out of my mind...
Just as we thought
I didn't expect it would have been Yoshinaga
It's probably the farthest from him...
Yeah, she is
How about we try again with the same cards?
Let's go for another round
With the same cards?
The same as this round?
My memories with stars - 2 -
The old dude changes, right?
Of course
Oh boy...
Alright, let's chose our leader first
Let's roll
I'm not ready for this
You do the honors, Endo
Alright
It barely spun...
But I guess it's ok
I get you, Endo, after telling that story
Sorry, I haven't done this before
You're in a feverish state, I get you
Thanks for your concern
You should go home and think about it
But now you're stuck in here
Spinning the roulette made me nervous
There's no time to not feel tense
You've been dragged here, face it
Yeah
Here's the second round of the game!
The old dude is Bae Yong-joon
Let's be faster this time
Sure, here goes
It's Yumiko Udo!
He's good at this
A story with a woman is harder
I agree
I'd rather come up with a guy
We have more cards this round...
A part of me hopes it's Endo with Yoshinaga again...
Anything but that
You're screwed if you pick her now
Right
You barely even had the strength to spin the roulette
Please, don't
A Quick turn of events
But suddenly, a quick turn of events!
He did it again!
Hamada is the first one to clear
You're good to go, Hamada
I'm good at this
Oh yeah!
Really? Man...
Are you kidding me?
He's done too
Oh man...
Give that to him, not me
Oh yeah!
Really?!
No way...
At this point I swear
I'm fine with Endo's hell
It's fifty-fifty now
Please, give me a break...
I'm panicking
Please... please!
Please don't match!
You're so unlucky, man
Now it's Yamazaki's chance
Give me a minute! Please!
I swear, what the heck!
It's looking bad for you, Shozo!
Something's wrong!
I swear, what the heck!
It's looking bad for you, Shozo!
This is a joke, right? A joke
But look
I have 2 out of 3 chances to win
Right, that's right
What should I do?
As long as you don't draw the old dude
I haven't thought of a story yet...
Why am I always...?
How is it?
And here we go, draw your last card, Endo
Wait, gimme a sec
We don't know which one is it
Right
It's one of them, but who?
Let's see
I have no clue about them both
Endo, come on
You gotta move fast, it's a matter of momentum
Quick, come on!
- Don't think! One, two, and go!
It's Bae Yong-joon
Please, tell us your memory!
Well, I think it was...
Around the time I came here to Tokyo,
I lived in front of this guy
We used to grab lunch together too
It was a time where we both didn't have much job to do
And so we were constantly supporting each other
But then we gained success, right?
I started to sell and I invited him out for lunch
And even today we exchange messages on LINE
That's our relationship, good memories
Thank you
It's a made-up story
That barely felt like a memory
He didn't get ready at all
Nothing at all
I don't know what to say
Are you ok today?
You want me to drive you home?
Are you ok? Can you get back home?
Let's dive into our next theme, shall we?
Bunny-chan, please
She's our Bunny-chan, thank you
How many games are there?!
What's wrong, Bunny-chan?
What's going on? You laughed...
Did he do something to you?
He just...
What's going on?
Come on, tell us
Please
His eyes...
Were around here
You're the shittiest of shits
Was he really looking around there?
He's the king of shit
What can I do about it? I saw her coming!
Of course I'm going to peek at her
But that's not the spot you'd look
It felt that normal to you?
He's a high-quality shit comedian
Yeah, really
That's unbelievable
Sorry about that
I'm sorry
This round's theme is...
Batsu-game!
No way, why that?!
This isn't a fun experience at all!
You thought we were going to have fun?
Of course
If you lose, you'll receive the batsu-game!
Translated Batsu-game list
@ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
This time we won't reveal the old dude,
try to guess it yourself!
Is this what we're doing?
I hate all of them!
Those are really something.
This can't be good!
Really
I have one pair
Oh, already?
"Hot vinegar eyedrops"
This sucks
Eh? What does that mean?
"Electric Spicy Pie"
I don't know what it means
I don't know most of mine myself
I've never seen some of those
Really, they're unknown
I didn't know about them
I agree, some of these are odd
I've never even imagined some of these
They're new, aren't they?
"Leather Belt Slap"
I'd hate to receive this one...
What face is that?!
But I agree, I hate them all
This game sucks
Yeah, it's no fun
What were they thinking when they printed this?
Really...
Please, give me one pair!
"Face crepe"
Hamada would love this one
I still have no clue
- Me neither
Oh, here it is
Please, don't...
This is is, it's my most feared one
I don't know what that means
"Electric Spicy Pie"
I know, right?!
"Electric spicy pie"...
What does that mean?
Sounds like a cake from the future
The old-dude batsu-game no one wants to face...
Can I?
And once again, suspicion is raised upon that man...
This card must be somewhere
It could be
Of course
Maybe someone snatched it from you
I bet it was you
Is it the one I took before?
You're always peeking at my cards
You took my card while peeking at my hand
That's not...
No way I would do it!
How could I've done it?
There's a camera behind me
You've been caught on tape!
Play the tape, I don't mind
Always peeking around, geez...
That's impossible!
Then how is this card still here, huh?!
That's not true
Are you sure?
That's the point of the game
Hey! I had this card before!
Your act sucks!
That can happen
It's looping
Suspicions from Tanaka's peeking haven't lifted
This is getting harsh
Let's see...
Don't peek at me
I'm not, how could I?!
Just don't look over there
He's right Tanaka, you should stop that
Really, he's right
You're better than this, Tanaka
At this point, you should just confess
- Yeah, he's right
Let's just play the game, guys
Are you changing the topic?
Alright, we're good, let's stop for now
Alright then, I'm drawing
The same cards are just spinning around
"Thai-kick on your back"
Is this one here too?
This card, here of all places?
It's a classic, you know
I expected this one to be here
"Thai-kick on your back"
Ah, this one?
What the hell?
I don't think there's such rule in Muay Thai
"Thai-kick on your back"
Yeah, I don't think so
I mean, on your back
Who's going to be the first one to clear his round?
Thanks so much
- Are you clear?
I'm done
"Nipple shock"
Alright, Endo's clear
He's not getting punished for his stories before?
I'm so glad
And then, it's Matsumoto's turn
Alright!
"Face crepe"
Thanks, "face crepe"!
I survived!
And then it's peepy Tanaka's turn
I'm in danger
I've never seen this card before
"Turban shell's guts juice"
"Turban shell's guts juice", ugh...
Is Hamada going to be punished?
Or it'll be Hosei?
The possibilities it could be Hamada are high
Of course there are, no need to tell me
Let's see...
Well, it's not like
We're going to see a loser on the next round
Yeah, but there's a 50% chance to win
So it's pretty high
- Yes, it won't last long
Please, don't take  it
I see, it's Hamada's turn, so Yamazaki's in danger
Please, don't pick it
- He's in a bad position now
70% chance
Right, 75% to be precise
This one!
Here!
"Leather belt slap"
Here's the leather belt!
He escaped it
No way!
So that means...
I hate both of them!
What are...
Let's see... one is "Sumo Wrestler Deep Kiss",
The other one is "Uvula toothbrush"
man! They both suck
Never seen that one before...
Wait a minute
Did you just say "I've never seen it"?
You were talking about the uvula thingy, huh?!
Hamada did it again
Who cares? He's getting it anyway
That's true
"Uvula toothbrush"
It was "uvula toothbrush"
What the hell is that?
Here comes
This is scary
Come on, guys... this is gonna leave scars
Open your mouth wide
Widely, open it
That's not enought, right?
I agree with you
Not enough
More?!
Yeah, I mean... it's a punishment
Alright, take care
What are you doing, man?
He did it three times
Who are you, Mori Shinichi?!
You became Mori Shinichi!
He changed
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TYPESET & REVIEW BY MATTEE53
MORE EPISODES: SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
SOCIAL MEDIA: FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI & TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
WANT TO SUPPORT OUR CONTENT? YOU CAN DONATE ON:
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI OR PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TYPESET & REVIEW BY MATTEE53
MORE EPISODES: SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
SOCIAL MEDIA: FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI & TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
WANT TO SUPPORT OUR CONTENT? YOU CAN DONATE ON:
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI OR PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI