On tonight's Gaki no Tsukai!
The conclusion to places we have never been before top 3 recommendations!!
They gathered up all the train stations in the Kanto area and put them in a raffle draw...
They will go to a place they have never been before
and ask the locals what the top 3 recommendations are
The place Endo chose was...
Where's that?!
- Nagata?
Nagata
Oamishirasato, Chiba prefecture, they arrive at the JR Nagata station
They ask around the station are for recommendation number 3
There isn't anything good around here...
Tell us where you always hang out
There really is nothing huh
Asking the locals is a tough call it seems
Wait a sec, isn't this number 1??
- No!
Then finally...
There is a Nagata Drive in
Drive in?
They found the 3rd best recommendation
In business for 60 years, the Nagata drive in boats a plethora of fresh fish
A wonderful feast from the sea!
Then after asking the customers what a number 2 would be
It's called Arare chan's house
They bake and sell direct
They make way to Arare chan's house!
Endo, haven't you been drinking?
No I haven't!
That took us through last weeks episode
But can they finish the rankings today?!
FunnyJapan/ShinobiSubs
Reddit /r/FunnyJapan
Facebook/ShinobiSubs
Twitter @ShinobiSubs
They arrive at Arare chan's house!
This is Arare chan's house... Right?
- It's a factory
It's completely different to what I imagined
We're here!
You can just buy products as normal here?
- So it seems
Oh! Look
It's a goat!
They have some goats
You took them by surprise with that
They're like, "some weirdos are here"
Good afternoon~
- 'Ello
Don't say 'Ello
(TL;Uncha (Uncha-Baicha Hey-Bye) was a phrase popularized by the
young female character from the Dr.Slump manga Arare-chan,
Matsumoto is word playing the situation and the company name
Arare chan!
There is some story to this train right
But... it's actually quite busy in there
It says factory shop here
There is loads of people here
The factory shop that sells direct, Arare chan's house
They sell over 200 different types of Senbei
rice crackers that are made in the factory
As the producer, they are able to sell at a discount
price, making it a popular spot for all the locals!
Wow that soft cream is cheap!
- 50 yen! (.50c/35p)
50 yen! (.50c/35p)
Wow check this out!
There is so many!
- It's so cheap!
Hm? Hamada-san
I found something great here
- What??
Look look!!!
It says "I'm here~"
- It's Natsumi (Hamada's wife)
She was on Chakkari TV
A TV show you watch in secret when the husband isn't home...
I'm pretty sure you'll get found out like this
They have some tasting samples
"Lucky Mayonnaise"
How is it?
Delicious!
Wow the mayo flavor is great!
And so Yamasaki orders the 50 Yen soft cream
How many? 5?
We don't need 5...
- 2 will be fine thanks
2 for 100 yen!
Thank you
Just 50 Yen
Sure is cheap for something this nice!
How cute!
We should have got one each
Shall I get another 3?
- I really recommend this
He is really into sweet things
It's great!
Wow it's great!
- So milky
Is the milk local?
No.
She was straight out with it!
It's really great tasting
I wonder how many years it's been here
I'm glad we could show it as we came all the way here
- How many years has this been here?
About 13 years now
What's the story with the train?
We made rice cracker for the Izumi train line
And the boss got it as a gift from them
It's the break room, go and check it out!
You use it for breaks?
Do you make all the snacks here?
We make all the rice crackers here
Wow you make them all here!
There is hundreds of varieties
You make and sell direct so that`s why they're cheap huh
Also out the from of the shop...
Free coffee!
- Get me a hot please
Isn't it amazing that it's free?
- Hamada what can I get you?
- I'm fine thank you
Hot coffee please
You started drinking coffee? You always drank tea
My tummy has got stronger recently...
What sort of shit reasoning is that
It got tough when you hit 50 huh
I'm glad you're able to drink coffee now!
Then!
The company president is here
Eh?! You're the president?
Your wife always comes here to buy...
We see her picture in the shop
She always buys these (Kaki no Tani)
We only sell them here
I'd like to give you them as a gift
Natsumi-san always buys them?
You definitely eat them!
- He's eaten them for sure
Thank you so much
He's not going home though.
I AM going home
Thank you
Yeah, you really shouldn't say 'See ya~
(TL;Baicha/Uncha Baicha (Hey-Bye) was a phrase popularized by the
young female character from the 1986 Dr. Slump manga Arare chan,
Matsumoto is wordplaying the situation and the company name)
Baicha!~
- Baicha!
A place where you can buy direct from the maker, Arare chan's house
Popular with the locals, this gets the number 2 official recommendation!
So we ask around to find the number 1 recommendation
Ask the president!
Yeah lets ask
'Ello!
The smallest voice came out
We have been looking around the area since we arrived at the station
We have spoken to lot's of people about
that the best places in this town are
Have you been here? The Nagata Drive in?
- Yes of course
It has a great atmosphere! And delicious
That was number 3
Then we have your company Arare chan's as number 2
So we are pondering over number 1, what would you recommend?
We want to go to somewhere you recommend
Around here?
By the way, why are they goats over there?
They belong to one of our staff...
Really they are one of our staffs pets
The staff keep them...
So we don't have to cut the grass we keep them here
See ya!
You can't say that!
Number 1?
A place with nice scenery or atmosphere
A place with a nice feel or something
We are pretty close to the sea here
It's just down there
Kujukuri beach is probably the best
Probably just in time for the sunset
We might not be able to stay that late...
Well it's kinda nice...
You have been flustered this whole time
Shall we check it out then
A place more hype than Arare
We should go there
I like it there!
Thank you today
Before heading to the beach they check out the break room train
Wow it's so retro
I can faintly hear something...
It's Ootaki Eiichi playing
It really is!
This is the Siberia rail road song
It's sure is nostalgic but... Can't we turn it off
- Let's listen to it
- Why would you want to turn it off
We don't need it playing on the show I thought
(Staff) Are we going to the beach?
Kujukuri huh...
- We should go for a wander there
We should really drop something big for the finale
What's with the youth of today.
Just tell me what is with the youth of today!!
He is sensitive to that kind of thing
He was so quick to look away in disgust
They make the way to Kujukuri beach by car
The 5 of them exchange thoughts over the song in the train
What was that song...
Siberia rail road
Really?
Sorry Matsumoto-san, that is for real
- Really???
I know I have lied a lot up to now...
You're a liar!!
You're making me gag
- Really?
Ootaki Eiichi the Siberian rail road
(Staff in the back) The title is Goodbye, Siberian rail road
Half a lie then
You didn't have the "Goodbye" part
- That's why it's a bit...
I didn't specifically say it...
Ku~ju~kuri~ beach~♪
Who sang that?
What was the name
Mi-Ke?
(Staff in the back) The title was I remember kujukuri beach
And so let's listen to the song
It was quite the seller right?
I have heard this before
Yeah?
Sure takes me back
Was you already grown up then?
Around middle school?
How do you not know that Endo
What era of Kamen Rider was popular when you was that age?
v3 or...
No, no, V3 was my generation
That's mine
I was gen V3
Really?
- Yeah
Was you into Kamen Rider back then Endo?
Not really no
- I thought so much
All I did was play baseball as a school kid
The coach used to scream at ya all the time back then?
They used to chant "The pitcher is scared" and that
That used to really mess me up mentally
2nd base is in a rut!!
It was a real head fuck, it wasn't good for kids
What was it like?
The pitcher is scared~ hey hey hey
The catcher is scared~ hey hey hey
First base is scared too! hey hey hey
They said to every position
But they said the batter is scared too right?
- Yeah
If they said that then the opponent would get scared too
Just stop!
I wanna see the beach
Have you been here before?
I think so!
You're just parroting
It sound familiar to me
The wording and feeling
It's embarrassing to hear that
I think the sand is a little shade of black
Is it a cove like beach?
- It is
'Cove like?
Cove like doesn't just mean individual coves
Yes, it does have a cove
What's with this conversation, it's almost educational
But we don't have any God's with us this time though huh
(Previous episode "Gods")
I wanted to search for a God but...
We just found them last time
Ougon-sama was something else huh
Well, everyone had a full set of teeth this time round
A rare situation for everyone to have teeth
It seems that no teeth means you're a God
Those pieces of high value worth have been pulled out
And so the 5 of them arrive at the beach
We're here
Look at how nice the sand is
Is he surfing?
He's out there alone
Is it Honkon-san?
That would be funny as heck if it was
Imagine if it was him
It would be a miracle if it was Honkon-san
We're finally here
Wow it's great for surfing
- There is no one here!
Wow look at this place
It's vast down here
It's so beautiful
It feels so refreshing
Summer would be great here
- Those houses are right on the seafront
Whenever I'm at the beach with Hamada,
I can't help but think about HamadaJuku
Youtube v=6yQOgK-Uh6E
You can sing it now if you want... Quickly
Instant! HamadaJuku
The switch has been turned
It was nothing but a display of power harassment
It was just pure powerplay. The whole thing
I can see right to the horizon!
Right Tanaka!!
Nobody replied at all
Kujukuri beach, at 66km long it's the second longest sandy beach in Japan
It's very popular beach spot in the summer for all!
It's rare to see a beach this long
It's a shame Honkon wasn't here
Unfortunate
HONKON~~~~~~~~!!
It's worrying when there is on warning like that
What are yu duuing
Today, look, really, I have, everyone in the world has this problem
But I have finally solved it
It's another deep topic?
It's been going on forever now
"What's a vegetable and what's a fruit"
That discussion
Everyone has a different opinion on it
But I have finally got the solution to it
Whad do you think?
What classes a vegetable, what's a fruit
I can just say it now with full confidence
- Seriously
Like, where do you draw the line?
- What line?
People often say...
Fruits grown on a tree
And vegetable grow from the ground
But if that's the case, then what about strawberries and melon?
They're like...
Okay, well sweet things are fruit then
Then if it's not really sweet then it's a vegetable
But then how do you decide the level of how sweet is sweet
But you know what I say to anyone trying to give me that sweet talk?
- You're a fruit too!
That can't be helped, it's just natural
But you don't actually say it right
- No, no
You'd look stupid if you did
- Exactly...
Well what about you?
you just can't decide decisively right?
You can look it up on the internet and
there is all arguments for and against
It goes on and on, round and round, there is no consistency
Can we decide this for good?
- Please do
Right after this break!
After the break
It's still too soon since we began
I have really got the answer
The answer is really so simple
CAN IT GO WITH MAYONNAISE??
Can you or can you not eat it with mayonnaise
- Man you're noisy.
It's decided.
It's my flawless victory. 100% undoubtedly decided.
CAN IT GO WITH MAYONNAISE??
- You're too damn noisy!
IF YOU CAN EAT IT WITH MAYONNAISE THEN IT'S A VEGETABLE
IF YOU CAN'T THEN IT'S A FRUIT
No one has ever said or noticed this before.
Of course no one has ever said that...
Am I the only one that realized
No, because I've never eaten fruits with mayonnaise!
But there is one problem
- What's that?
Hurry up and say it
There is just one damn thing that keeps coming up in this discussion
It`s the fruit tomato paradox
When someone brings it up it`s like... Ah.
What`s with this final boss
But in the end, tomato can go with mayonnaise right
You have to say it doesn't go with it out of spite, so it can go with mayo
I see.
I see?!
You see?!
That's how it's gonna end then! That's your finisher
I know it's an extreme example, but take squid. It can go with mayo right
You can put mayo on squid and eat it right
It's extreme, but I think it's okay to call it a vegetable.
Because fundamentally, if it goes with mayo it's a vegetable. Absolutely
If you ever have a doubt about it,
The only way to decide is if it goes with mayo or not
Ok...
Get it? You understand right?
If you put it like that then
With that, this debate is concluded I believe.
Well, squid isn't a vegetable though.
But on the subject of squid though, I think it's a killing machine
What? What's with this now
You know when you grill squid and then open up the foil
You have that little brown line on top
The brown part of the skin
It's like Romeo reaching out to grab Juliet
But he can't reach
Half of the squid is in you already but
That's the moment it dies
Just then when it's like
Romeo is here but Juliet is already inside
That is just cold blooded murder!
Watch out for the squid, it's fearful
Is that so...