0 0 m -220.25 -65.875 b -228.125 -67.25 -249.5 -65.875 -247.25 -41.625 b -248.375 -28.125 -227 -1.125 -221.375 0 b -212.375 7.625 -209 -1.125 -203.375 -2.875 b -196.625 -11.875 -189.875 -14.625 -183.125 -37.125 b -180.875 -58.25 -195.5 -59.625 -196.625 -61.625 b -205.625 -67.25 -213.5 -65.875 -220.25 -65.875 m -214.625 -58.25 b -204.5 -61.625 -191 -52.625 -193.25 -43.375 b -201.125 -55.125 -207.875 -55.125 -214.625 -58.25 m -272 -190.125 b -267.5 -190.125 -229.25 -179.75 -234.875 -110.875 b -242.75 -67.25 -264.125 -46.125 -270.875 -41.625 b -274.25 -40.25 -292.25 -20.875 -317 -52.625 b -322.625 -67.25 -333.875 -84.125 -326 -121.25 b -322.625 -136.125 -317 -165.125 -296.75 -181.125 b -291.125 -185.625 -282.125 -193.25 -272 -190.125 m -170.75 -193.25 b -168.5 -193.25 -141.5 -203.625 -117.875 -148.25 b -114.5 -134.75 -105.5 -118.125 -111.125 -76.25 b -117.875 -41.625 -129.125 -40.25 -135.875 -37.125 b -141.5 -37.125 -149.375 -28.125 -176.375 -53.75 b -185.375 -64.125 -198.875 -70.375 -204.5 -112.25 b -203.375 -112.25 -216.875 -139.5 -188.75 -181.125 b -183.125 -187.625 -177.5 -193.25 -170.75 -193.25 m -274.25 -143.75 b -305.75 -136.125 -287.75 -89.75 -273.125 -94.5 b -268.625 -94.5 -258.5 -97.625 -256.25 -118.125 b -259.625 -142.625 -266.375 -140.625 -274.25 -143.75 m -274.25 -130.25 b -267.5 -133.375 -264.125 -121.25 -265.25 -118.125 b -265.25 -106.625 -272 -106.625 -275.375 -106.625 b -279.875 -107.75 -282.125 -113.625 -281 -121.25 b -281 -124.375 -278.75 -130.25 -274.25 -130.25 m -272 -124.375 b -275.375 -122.625 -274.25 -117 -272 -117 b -269.75 -117 -267.5 -122.625 -272 -124.375 m -162.875 -143.75 b -187.625 -137.875 -176.375 -91.125 -162.875 -95.625 b -158.375 -94.5 -147.125 -97.625 -147.125 -124.375 b -150.5 -142.625 -159.5 -143.75 -162.875 -143.75 m -162.875 -130.25 b -148.25 -130.25 -152.75 -106.625 -160.625 -106.625 b -162.875 -104.625 -171.875 -107.75 -169.625 -121.25 b -169.625 -124.375 -168.5 -130.25 -162.875 -130.25 m -160.625 -124.375 b -164 -121.25 -161.75 -115.375 -159.5 -117 b -156.125 -118.125 -158.375 -124.375 -160.625 -124.375 m -276.5 -117 b -278.75 -117 -277.625 -112.25 -276.5 -112.25 b -275.375 -112.25 -274.25 -117 -276.5 -117 m -164 -115.375 b -166.25 -115.375 -165.125 -110.875 -164 -110.875 b -162.875 -110.875 -161.75 -115.375 -164 -115.375 m -333.875 -217.125 l -104.375 -217.125 l -104.375 86.875 l -333.875 86.875 m -106.625 -214.375 l -331.625 -214.375 l -331.625 84.125 l -106.625 84.125
TPF
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!! Presents
Please Endo! We Want to See Mori Shinichi Do This!!
Cocorico
Downtown
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
m 0 0 l 0 33.75 l 40.5 33.75 l 40.5 0
These are things that the real Mori Shinichi would...
would probably never do for us.
Say it right
I apologize.
You've been off since you announced the episode.
Your voice was a little too loud and shaky.
So these are things that the real Mori Shinichi would never show us,
Endo will act as Mori Shinichi and
do what the Gaki members want to see
m 0 0 l 0 33.75 l 40.5 33.75 l 40.5 0
and they are requests from the members.
And the plan is that I, Endo Shouzou, will impersonate him and act them out.
But I never thought that Endo
was that good at impersonations or anything
Impersonations aren't really my strong suit, but...
That lip syncing thing was the first time I've seen it.
That was the start, huh
I spent a day and a half recording that segment.
A whole seperate day?
Of course it took so long.
Mori Shinichi does it every second of his life.
A day and a half is nothing
But he's not Mori Shinichi!!
Is that so
Tofu Panda Fan subs presents
Down Town's Gaki no tsukai ya arahende!!
Otviss
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
**We also have facebook and twitter.**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on Youtube, individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own. Please go back and
support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit. You can
download episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching!
Kenny
Translators:
Typesetter:
__________________________________________________
We gathered your requests beforehand
and recorded them, so let's start with Matsumoto-san.
What did you want to see?
Right.
I actually,
Recently I went to his concert
at Nakano Plaza
Mori Shinichi's?
That's right.
I wanted to finally hear his songs live, so
I went to his concert and thought "he really is that good" but
There was something
that I wanted to see that he would never do there.
That one thing is this.
Swimming.
Him swimming.
What he looks like swimming...
It's possible that he actually
Matsumoto's Request
Swimming
m 0 0 l 0 33.75 l 40.5 33.75 l 40.5 0
swims by himself a lot.
Well, I went swimming while impersonating Mori Shinichi,
so please take a look at the tape.
Roll It.
That's just the right amount.
Don't overdo it.
Good evening, I'm Mori Shinichi.
Today,
There was a request to watch me swimming, so
I'd like to start swimming for them.
Was Mori Shinichi
always that tan?
He is very tan.
If Mori Shinichi
were to go swimming...
You have to
keep doing that
face the whole time
Via Sports Avenue
Right, that was
the hard part.
Especially
while swimming...
On your mark, get set...
It's Mori Shinichi...
If Mori Shinichi went
swimming, It might
look something like this.
Does this really need a
song and slow motion?
What is this?!
This is just boring to watch
It's not a great impression...
Right? It's way
more Endo than Mori
It's mostly just Endo.
Especially in slow motion
Ahh
Ah, this might be better
The freestyle
stroke looks better
I tried hard to
keep doing the face
Seriously?
I just saw him
for a split second
Mori Shinichi's...
This song is about
a cold place though, so
It doesn't
really fit here.
But you're still able to swim as him.
That's right.
Oh, but you're kinda
starting to look like him.
Thank you.
I don't know about that...
Here's the butterfly.
Butterfly...
You aren't
even doing it right
He's not doing
the butterfly or the
impression right.
It's bad
A double failure
Yea, I see
The freestyle
part was better
That was better
I see I see
That face, huh
I see
How was it?
There were single moments where it was really good.
Like Mori Shinichi was there for just a moment?
Especially the freestyle.
Especially.
How do you think you did?
After filming for so long, my face started to get numb.
I couldn't tell what face I was making anymore.
And it stays like that.
The Mori Shinichi we think of is the singing version, so
the real Mori might actually swim just like that.
Considering that, it was really realistic.
Next up is Housei-san.
Right
My request, is this.
I've never seen Mori-san get pranked.
Housei's Request
Sleeping Prank
m 0 0 l 0 33.75 l 40.5 33.75 l 40.5 0
And since he's such a star, a sleeping prank would be...
Not to mention, now of all times.
Right, I'd love to see this.
Well, I went and did it.
Please Watch
Roll It
Good evening, I'm Mori Shinichi.
Hey, it's pretty good.
Today,
This is good
It seems that there was a sleeping prank request
for me, so
I'd like to start right away.
Got Pranked
If Mori Shinchi
While Sleeping...
Good morning!
Fujiwara Kazuhiro
Inomoto Takafumi
License
Oh, it's License
They play the
pranksters, huh
That's usually
their role
Right now,
in room 107 here,
So this was definitely
Fixed right?
Exactly
we've heard that it's Mori Shinichi's room.
He's sleeping.
He's sound asleep.
Sleeping Mori Shinichi
Take a look at this.
All of his clothes are here.
Clothes Taken Off All Over the Bed
Surprisingly, he doesn't hang up his clothes.
Mori-san does that?
Perhaps, in the bed he's...
Ah, hold on
Let's take a look at his face.
Won't he wake
up if they do that?
Here we go.
Slowly...
Even slowly
he'll wake up
Sound Asleep Mori Shinichi
He's really sleeping.
What is this
You can't sleep
through this
He's wearing the hotel pajamas.
The hotel pajamas.
His buttons are nicely buttoned as well, as expected from a real entertainer.
That was close, that was close.
He just rubbed his face.
What IS this
There's some power in that thing.
With this bazooka,
Waking Up Mori Shinichi with a Bazooka!
I'd like to try and wake him up with one shot.
Wait wait, that's...
And now,
If they do this...
3, 2, 1...
Good morning!
His face
His face...
Mornin'.
This is a sleeping prank!
It's very realistic
It's very realistic.
Come on, give me a break.
This is the face
It's not
quite right.
I thought you were
doing someone else.
How was it?
When you were sleeping I thought "That's probably what he'd look like" but
When you woke up you became someone else.
By "someone else" you mean...?
It was a bit different.
Maybe a little too much.
Mori Shinichi's gear shift
slips into different gears sometimes.
What does
"Mori Shinichi's gear shift" mean?
If you do the face for a long time
you start to lose control of it.
Like...
First gear looks like this.
But, if...
If you're lying down,
it's hard to get into that gear.
We're never gonna do this, though.
Just in case you guys ever do
We're never gonna ride that machine.
At any rate,
The next request is, Hamada-san.
Ah, yup.
Mine is this.
I'd also like to see this.
How does he get scared?
Hamada's Request
Test of Courage
m 0 0 l 0 33.75 l 40.5 33.75 l 40.5 0
Right.
Like "Does he scream?"
What scares him in the first place?
Exactly.
I completely became Mori Shinichi and did it.
This'll be tough.
Roll it.
To all,
Good evening, I'm Mori Shinichi.
It was requested that I perform a test of courage
for our viewers today.
He's looking
less and less like him.
I'm here at Fuji-Q's Shudder-With-Fear Maze today.
This is straight up Endo
He's just making
his eyes bigger
I've heard it's an extremely scary attraction.
You went all
the way to Fuji-Q?
I'd like to start right away.
This is the second
day of filming
It's getting
hard to believe
It is getting
hard to sell it
If Mori Shinichi
Tested His Courage...
Is this
for real?
It really is
scary, you know?
Here I go.
This is a good angle.
I've heard that
I'd never do this.
the Shudder-With-Fear Maze is seriously scary.
I've heard it's actually scary.
So scary...
I already know, things are gonna pop out.
He's still
making the face.
I tried showing what
Mori Shinichi would do
the whole time.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Stay!
Stay!!
It's clearly you.
But look,
it's Mori Shinichi.
Look!
Seriously,
Seriously, seriously, seriously, seriously.
There's definitely something in here.
Hey
Look, this is
completely Mori Shinichi.
This is good.
Isn't it good?
It's good some
of the time.
This was...
These parts where
you're scared is where...
I think it's the voice.
Stay! Stay! Stay!
Stay! Stay!!
What the hell is "stay"?
They really
come at you.
Like "stay over there"
Mori Shinichi would
never say that.
This hallway can't be good.
Something's gonna...
This can't be good.
The voice is good.
This was a really long hall.
He Prepares Himself and Continues
This was
really hard to do.
This...
You really need some courage for this.
I couldn't
even take a step.
Give me a moment
Ghost From Behind
This one was
persistent.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
He Has to Run For It
Stay!!
You had to start
running away, huh.
Oh, it's kinda good.
It's pretty...
It's Endo again.
So that's where
he came from.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Mori's back.
This part was really good.
That part is great.
I liked that.
This is just Endo.
Then suddenly.
I guess when you get scared
Endo starts to come out.
Right, since I'm being scared there's nothing I can really do.
Your voice starts to go back to normal.
That's what I wanted to see as Mori-san.
So,
I want you to try a little harder, for the next episode.
This episode isn't over yet, though.
We still have more.
Right.
Okay, this here.
Searching for real estate.
I was really surprised by this one.
I thought we could see the closest thing to the real, natural Mori-san with this.
Searching for
Real Estate
Tanaka's Request
m 0 0 l 0 33.75 l 40.5 33.75 l 40.5 0
Something only your partner here could show us.
Take a look, roll it.
Good evening, I'm Mori Shinichi.
There was a request to see me
choosing real estate property at a Realtor,
So I'd like to show this especially for the requester.
Well, here I go.
Only the
end was good.
If Mori Shinichi
Looked for Real Estate...
He Will Visit a Realtor in Yamanashi Prefecture
I'm Mori.
Nice to meet you.
Like he's getting
a holiday house.
What kind of place where you looking for today?
Oh, like a villa.
A place where I can sing would be great.
Where you
can sing.
Right now there's 2 properties.
Places where you could sing.
This here,
There's only 7 of these buildings in Japan.
The insulation is fantastic in these.
You would never get
to see the real Mori
Shinichi doing this.
Mori-san?
This might be the
closest one to the
real thing.
Including everything, it's about 44,000,000 Yen.
Up to now, yea.
True
That's quite a price.
That was Endo
right there.
That was me?
There's also a place with a view of Mt. Fuji and the lake.
That was just you.
This is turning out
just like Fuji-Q.
We can set that property up for a visit right now,
if you'd like to go see it after this.
I see.
It's all over the place.
Are you sick
or something?
They Head to the Resort Apartment Near the Lake.
The resort mansion...
It's this one here.
16065, huh.
This was the best
room in the whole
apartment.
It's huge.
Oh, it's big.
The living room is 329 sq ft, and feels nice and wide.
But the best part is...
The Amazing
View
Yamanaka Lake
That's a great view of Fuji.
Mount Fuji
What a view.
Bravo.
To the right, Yamanaka Lake, and to the left, Mount Fuji.
Taking that all into consideration, 8,000,000 Yen isn't so bad. What do you think?
His face must
hurt by now.
His eyes are
really shining.
He has other
songs, you know?
He had a lot of
other hits, you know?
Why are you only
using this one song?
That's not the
right face.
Sometimes the
wrong face just
happens.
Thank you.
It was very natural.
The most up to this point.
It was the best of all so far.
That place's view was actually really good
so I thought I'd just take it all in and reflect for real.
Do you mean as Endo or as Mori-san?
Mori-san.
As Mori-san?
That's confusing, huh
You have to mean as yourself or else it's too confusing.
Did Mori-san say that?
Mori-san said "I'm gonna reflect" or
something along those lines.
See, that's just weird.
That one word makes it all weird.
I have more request, a prank
This here,
Ah,
I wanna see what will happen.
Housei's Request
Sexy Prank
m 0 0 l 0 33.75 l 40.5 33.75 l 40.5 0
If Mori-san was pranked like that it would probably never be allowed on air,
and we'd never be able to see it, so
I went and did it, take a look. Roll it.
Good evening, I'm Mori Shinichi
watch me get pranked sexually,
There was a request to
So I'd like to show this especially for the requester.
Got Pranked
If Mori Shinichi
Sexually...
So he's pretending to
not know he's gonna
get pranked?
Mori Shinichi's
Sudden
Hole in One
The first lesson is the approach.
1st Lesson
Approach
m 0 0 l 0 33.75 l 40.5 33.75 l 40.5 0
We'll start with around a 35 yard approach, and slight downward slope.
This is a pretty hard approach.
Why is it at a
golf course?
It's getting confusing.
It's too complicated.
I think that was pretty good.
I recommend actually getting it on the green.
Alright, that's good!
We'll prepare for the next shot, so please wait a bit.
This is a tough shot, right?
Mori-san, Good work. Would you like a drink?
Prankster
The Sexy Assistant Approaches Mori Shinichi
Oh, how about some water.
There's lots of different kinds of drinks in here,
Full View of Panties ❤
are you sure you want water?
Ah,
What else do you have?
Suddenly-Squatting Mori Shinichi
Uhm, tea,
coffee, sports drinks, and mineral water.
What would you like?
Pretending-Not-to-See Mori Shinichi
What is this?
Which one would you like?
I don't even know
what I'm watching
anymore.
This is just bad.
I don't know what
this is anymore.
What IS this?
Wow! Nice swing!
It was nothing.
Here you go.
Clueless-and-Lighthearted Mori Shinichi
So stupid.
Recording
2nd Lesson
Putting
m 0 0 l 0 33.75 l 40.5 33.75 l 40.5 0
Anyway, a put shouldn't be swinged
so let's make it roll to the hole.
Just like that.
Alright, we got it.
Please come wait over here.
Alone With the Sexy Assistant...
Uhhh,
Yes?
If you keep standing
you'll get tired, so have a seat.
No, I shouldn't.
It's no problem.
Forcing-the-Assistant-to-Sit-Together Mori Shinichi
Ok, thank you.
You know,
Since we're doing golf today,
could I get a hand massage?
Ah, of course.
Demanding-a-Massage Mori Shinichi
If I may.
What is this?
Does this hurt?
Her Breasts are Right Before His Eyes ❤
Not at all.
Ok, good.
What is he doing?
He's touching her leg.
Hey, where are you touching? Stop it you pervert!
Stop it you pervert!
That was just Endo.
Straight up Endo.
Big Success!
Right?
From the viewer's perspective,
it was hard to watch.
The viewers won't know what to do.
I wonder how they explained it all to that actress, too.
"Because Mori-san is watching."
And now, I received another, final request.
So I'd like to finish the program with this.
Winter's Riviera.
This is funnier than everything else.
I love this.
Not bad.
He's pretty good.
Not bad!
He got way better since last time.
This video was brought to you by Tofu panda Fansubs
He's a little better.
He wasn't great at first, but.
He really drew that out.
Much better than before.
I agree.
I hope to see you all again soon.
Have a good night.
Halfway through he started doing Shimura Ken...
There were a lot of parts like that.