Once again, the 5 Members were told to dress smart.
Downtown
Hitoshi Matsumoto
Masatoshi Hamada
It is really okay to start like this?
I don't know.
I just think we should have started in a better location...
Anyway, today we're going to...
do part 2 of our farting series
Bloody hell, again?
Glad to be here, Sensei
Nice to work with you. Please surprise us again..
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Hosei Yamasaki
Naoki Tanaka
We are just some no gooders...
He is our 'Last Hempera' ('He' is fart in Japanese.)
Yup, he sure is.
Last time at 'Hemachido Paris' (Translation: Waiting for fart in Paris)
We saw a beautiful miracle.
Hamada farted multiple times in quick succession
Showing his superior skills to the others,
And got to eat a delcious French cuisine.
He claimed the name of 'King of farting'
And this time as well, a letter from Suga-chan (Producer)
So cold!
Ma-chan, Hama-chan, Endo, Tanaka and others
I am sorry I couldn't come to the recordings
I know it's a pathetic excuse for not coming but,
For all you guys who tried to hard for the New Year special
I thought I would let you all let a bit out of a gas out and
I have reserved a seat for you in a prestigious sushi restaurant
But you can only have sushi if you fart,
I have reserved the table for 2 hours.
So, please enjoy today
and let as much gas out as you can.
without the Gasu-man.
From Suga Kenji
Well of course.
Yes, you can't blame him for acting like that
So, where is this Sushi restaurant?
Apparently over there.
I see.
This area is really expensive too
Man, it's so cold!
Shall we go then?!
Translated by Mickstar!
www.twitter.com/mickstar813
Oi, it's here.
Sushi 'He'- (Literal: Sushi farts)
I don't remember there being such a restaurant here...
Sounds tasty.
Sounds a bit fishy..
No one would come to a restaurant with this kind of name
Man, the writing is even so neat.
The restaurant today is 'Sushi He-'
First, if you want to fart, you raise your hand up
If you successfully fart, you get to order one type of Sushi.
They have 2 hours.
So, what will happen.
Wow...
Hello.
Wow, this looks really good.
Welcome.
Look at the size of the fishes!
Wow wow wow...
It looks so good.
So we're doing it here today huh
Looks so good!
Last time, we got a course, but
this time, the person who farted can
order directly to the chef
whatever they want
Anything we want?!
Yup! Anything!
Wow wow wow..
Sorry.. Do you have anything you strongly recommend?
Today..
The Tuna is really good.
Tuna huh?!
We're going to have to get stuck into the Tuna first huh?
Tuna sounds good
Look at the size of the prawns!
Looks so nice
This is yellow tail right?
Yes it is
Looks great.
On top of that...
There are Nigiri's
But also Chawanmushi, Miso soup
And tasty side dishes too.
Man, I want to eat so bad.
Me too.
Yes, I want to eat too.
Ok then, we will begin now.
SUSHI TIME START
Ok, next 2 hours are big...
Come on!
I'm going to eat until I'm full
Yes, let's eat until we're full huh?
Hold on everyone.
There's a bit of strange movement over here.
Sorry, hold on a second.
Just as they start, Yamazaki has a fart coming.
Will he be able to open up the farting?
FAIL
Oi, you! You always do that!
No it's weird, it feels like it's just about to come out!
Really?
A strong start. But the time has only just started.
I don't feel anything coming out
It hasn't even be 5 minutes!
COME ON!!!
He got the first fart!
Thank you!
Chu-toro (Mid Fatty Tuna) please
OH MAN!!! SO LUCKY!!!
SO LUCKY!!
Are you serious?!
Man that chu-toro looks good
I always go for Chu-toro first.
I could eat Chu-toro the whole time.
Well of course.
Ye you're right. Wow, it looks so good
Matsumoto-san always gets off to...
I know.
He really starts it off
No no no, me..
This is nothing...
The Sabu chan of the farting world.
I'm just a
piece of ****
Here you go!
Come on!!
It looks so good!
It looks so nice!
The sushi that Matsumoto ordered is the...
A tuna type, Chu-toro
So soft and juicy
it will kick up an appetite
It's so good, I can't get enough of it!
It's good huh?
I bet it is
Of course it is.
There's no way it's not going to be delicious.
IT'S SOO GOOD!!!
You know, the first time
The French Restaurant is amazing too
But I prefer sushi...
Oh of course!
Oh definitely
It is right?
'He Machido Paris' was good too but
But I prefer 'Sushi He-'
Yes, it's better for sure.
As the other members watch and fill up with jealousy
Matsumoto's face is just pure delight
It looks so good!
The other 4 want to follow Matsumoto but
The road to farting is not that easy.
It's definitely there
It's right behind my tail bone
I have no idea what you mean
That was quick
You don't get it?
Because I have never right behind my tail bone
So your farts are behind your tail bone right now?
Ye, it's all just trapped there.
Is he an idiot?
Can that even happen?
What the hell is 'behind the tail bone?'
Why don't you try put some gas in then?
Yep Yep Yep!
It came out
It came out just now right?
Yamazaki gets his first fart out
I'm so sorry.
Hold it in for a second!
You really couldn't wait huh?
Like 'Yep y.. *Buu*'
Well anyway it counted so...
Jeez man!
It was just a little wait more.
I'm so so sorry.
He couldn't wait until the camera came over.
Chu-toro please
Sounds good!
Ye, it's got to be chu-toro.
Yamazaki's first plate is the same as Matsumoto. Chuutoro.
Is it good?
It's always going to be good.
So good.
Obviously.
Yamazaki, we got to try hard and get as much as we can now or
In about 20 or 30 minutes...
All these fishes will be gone.
The poor fish right?
There should be enough.
There's a chance that all the bones might be gone too...
The one to fear is Hamada's ability.
Endo is desperate to fart.
God, so noisy...
You're so noisy too, what the hell are you doing? Where are you hitting!
Where is he hitting?
Now, Matsumoto starts to whip his arse into shape.
When suddenly...
you going for it?
Oh no... Just for a second.
Ugh, it just went past me.
'Went past me?'
Ye, he looked at me as he passed.
Man, that's so annoying.
This is really similiar to bass fishing.
No it's not.
Killed that...
He wouldn't even think about it, would he?
Seriously, it got away, right?
But seriously, just as I tried to grab it, it ran away.
Hang on, I got one I think.
WHAT?!
WHAT!?
Oh god, once it starts..
Please don't.
Why not!?
Oh, just for a second now..
Did he run away?
Ye, he got away.
There's similarities to bass fishing though, right?
NO!
I don't think I said it like that!
Has it come?
King Hamada. Is this the first fart?
I'm sure I got this.
A beautiful fart from Hamada
Thank you very much
Amazing...
He's here! He's here!
Chef, what should I go for?
Start with your favourite one.
But they both got Chutoro, so
O-toro
Let's go for that one!
Just Nigiri? Or grill it on one side?
Oh, please grill it.
Oh that sounds so good!
Ye, then I'll have one too.
Oi oi, why do you get one?
Oh, I don't get one?
It's Oo-toro!
Oo-toro, huh?
This kind of stuff...
When I was a kid, I definitely wouldn't be able to eat this.
He's going to gril it.
WOW WOW WOW.
I mean, come on. This is going to taste awesome.
You can just tell.
Oh, this one already has soy sauce on it.
Oh man...
I should have chosen that one!
There you go
Wow, it's amazing.
The best and tastiest part of a tuna fish.
Delicious with ginger and soy sauce on top.
Should have chosen that one.
Well... you should definitely try this!
it's SO good!
Hamada, absolutely delighted
Oh, I have on coming.
It's coming out for you huh?
Yep! Loads is coming out today.
I don't know what to get after Chu-toro
Oh, but I really want to eat the one Hamada-san got.
Oi! Stop copying everyone else's choices!
What's wrong with that? I love doing that.
Grilled Oo-toro please
Yes I can understand you would want that one.
Here, following Yamazaki, Matsumoto tries...
That's great for you!
What should I get?..
I want Uni... But ANAGO!
Let's eat Anago
Here you go.
Oo-toro no Aburi.
When you see it, you'll probably want to eat it as well.
It's getting busy in here.
I know right?
Seriously, it's getting really busy in here.
You got to keep going.
You have to push yourself.
Ittadakimasu
Excuse me!
Endo has a fart coming here. Will he be able to?
Has it come out?
No... not at all.
Something in my pants moved though, I swear...
You don't usually ask people if a fart came out...
Yes I guess...
Wow, wow wow. That looks so good
Matsumoto's 2nd plate is conger eel.
With lots of volume, you will love the softness in your mouth.
Is that a sandwich or something!?
What a weird way of eating it.
It's so good.
It certainly has loads of volume.
Due to it being so good, Matsumoto finishes it instantly.
On the other hand, Tanaka, who shows no sign of farting
Is starting to show signs he is under heavy pressure.
Tanaka? Seriously?
I'm begging you... come out...
Oh my bum.... Yep!
Yet again, Yamazaki has a fart coming.
Yamazaki's 3rd fart of the day.
You're doing really well huh?
Come on!
What can I get you?
Yamachan's in 1st place.
UNI!
Yamazaki's 3rd plate of the day is Uni from Hokkaido.
Gunkan has soy sauce on it.
The Nigiri has salt on it.
Oh man! He's got 2 different types, 2 different flavours.
This is my first time to eat Uni with salt.
Man, that must taste so good.
He's eating so much today.
Oh? It's a match.
It tastes too good that Yamazaki is speechless.
He's not really pulling it off..
Say something.
The Uni has made him speechless.
We've come here, and the Last Hemperor is a bit...
He's in trouble, no?
But last time was the same though,
Maybe The Last Hemperor's time is coming to an end?
Maybe Yama-chan will take the crown from me?
Ye... Right, I'm going to try my best.
Is Yamazaki actually going to be able to knock The Last Hemperor off his throne and become the king himself?
When, suddenly.
Oh, I have one coming. Yup...
Hamada, 2nd fart of the day.
Will Matsumoto be able to perform a miracle and fart right after his partner?
You got snot hanging out of your nose.
I felt like I was going to die.
I know right? You feel like you're going to die.
Chef! Yellow tail!
Oh man! So nice...
Hamada's second plate is the 'in season' yellow tail.
The flesh is tough but succulent and is from the Japanese sea.
I see Hamada eat Yellow tail all the time...
You love the stuff, don't you?
This is really good chef. Really really good.
Oi guys hold on...
A murder case has occured.
Somebody call the police!
What kind of a way is THAT to die?!
Oi Endo!
I'm so sorry about this...
Ignoring Cocorico, that man once again....
I got one... I got one!
Even though the volume of the fart was small,
Yamazaki extends his lead and heads onto his 4th plate.
Amazing man.
Thank you
Amazing!!
The microphone got it, right?
Right, what can I get you?
Oh man, I'm not sure...
Perhaps the Prawns you mentioned at the beginning?
Ok, the prawns..
What's gotten into you man?
You're doing so well man!
Thank you.
They're really really big.
Yamazaki's 4th item is Giant Sweet Prawns, with two ways of tasting.
Here you go.
Thank you!
This has salt and sudachi and you can put soy sauce on the other one.
2 flavours again.
That's going to be good.
2 TIMES 2 TIMES!! THE TASTE (from an old commercial in Japan)
That's so old..
No one remembers that.
That's got to be good!
What is that..
This is the fried part of the head for you.
I get that too?!
Oh come on!!
Get in there!
No!
Leave us alone!
Wow, it smells so nice...
Yamazaki has had 8 pieces of sushi so far and fried prawn heads and is now a happy bunny.
If it goes on like this, Yama-chan is going to be the champion.
The closing stages of the farting competition.
Will Farting King Hamada be able to make a come back?
There's still gas left in me.
Loads and loads.
Yamazaki is cruising now, and it seems he can still keep farting.
Exucse me, there is another 30 minutes before we close.
For real?!
Oh shit!
Cocorico's still haven't even farted once. Surely it can't finish like this?
When we're done recording... It's all going to come out...
Yep!
That was quick!
That was so cool!
Yamazaki's 5th fart.
Chawanmushi.
He's onto the last stages of his meal...
He looks so cool..
You never know, he might eat the chawanmushi and then go back and eat more sushi...
He's 'HE-nry Ouji' (King Henry)
There it is. A new name.
I really wanted a nickname like that...
I'm KING HE-NRY!
Yamazaki goes into the last stages of his meal and chooses Chawanmushi..
It has a nice and warm citron smell to it.
Oh, it's good
Absolutely nothing.
I'm not even close!
Shall we just replace Cocorico?
I agree... This is just NOT ON!
Please wait a bit more...
Just a bit more time...
I'm sure there are many others who would jump at this opportunity
Oh for sure... Loads and loads
Loads.
I'll fart and show you.
For our spot on the program.
The Cocorico's panic.
But the God of Farts smiles at Matsumoto!
Matsumoto's 3rd fart of the day!
What can I get you?
Prawn Salad Maki!
When you just talk normally, it comes, doesn't it?
Ye, that's what I'm doing now.
Not moving around and all that.
How about singing? Maybe that would work
You can turn anything into a song, right?
Yep, absolutely anything.
That's amazing.
Ok, try this 'If you want to fart, please raise your hand.'
When you're about...
To fart...
Put your hands in the air!!!!
So shit...
Matsumoto's 3rd plate is Ebi Salad Maki
The harmony between the Mayonnaise and the Prawns is perfect.
A little bit of soy and...
Oh man, I could eat these all day long.
That looks so good.
When you're about...
to fart..
No, like this..
When you're about....
to fart...
put your hands up in the air...
I can't remember that melody.
Man they look like they're having so much fun over there...
Ye, we just look like we've come for a nice meal together.
Yup, yup yup!
You serious?
Yamasaki's 6th fart. King Henry, who just doesn't know when to stop, orders fruits.
It's literally dinner for him.
Yup... man that's good.
We just look like idiots waiting for Yama-chan to finish eating his dinner.
He's just relaxing...
He's aiming for another dish...
After this... Yamazaki continues his miracle!
Make 'Care in Softness and Tenderness, Scottie' into a song
Care in Softness and Tenderness, Scottie, ye?
Care in Tendernessssssssssssssssss
Care in Softnessssssss
You're so annoying!
Shut the hell up!
I wish I was like him... I really do.
Right I've decided.. This will be Hamada-san's song.
Why the hell...
You had so much phlegm that I couldn't hear a thing you just said.
Right this will &&*£@&@^$*@& @$*^$*&@
The last 5 minutes. Yamasaki concentrates on a strong finish.
Yamasaki's 7th fart.
And his final dish will be...
What you going to do?
Ice Cream.
One Ice Cream please!
That's amazing.
I've been beaten.
I've been beaten...
Yamasaki just owned today...
I think lastly that we should finish the program with Yamasaki-san's song...
Care in Tendernessssssssssssssss
Care in Softnessssssssssssssss