9th Time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arrahende
"Are their hearts connected?" No Smartphones Meet Up!
Excuse me. I think 4 of us will come to the same conclusion,
4? 4 you say?
There's just that 1 guy who won't
I see
Do you mean me by any chance?
Exactly
C'mon that's not true-
You went to a Yudetaro instead of Fuji Soba!
That was egregious
That is an incident!
It really is, he went to a Yudetaro after all
Which means if it was Yudetaro then he'd go to a Fuji Soba
A guy like that can't do this
I'll be fine, today I'll be fine
The 9th installment of a series testing the bonds between the 5
The rule; They head to a location based on the theme. If everyone ends up together the game is over.
Tanaka use the second idea that comes to mind. Your first idea always takes you far away
That's true
I see
You always end up heading towards Shinobazu Pond
He does, he does
What's with that?
Timed & Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
What will the first theme be? No Smartphone Meetup!!
Let's get to it, time for the first theme
The first theme...is this!
"A car showroom"
"A car showroom"?
I got one already
There's 2 of them I think
This is a good question
So like always they've got taxis ready, let's go!
They depart from NTV at 2PM
I guess not that one
Wouldn't that one be goood?
Aoyama, was it in 1-choume?
That Honda dealership right?
They also have the Cornes there
That one...
Near Shiba Park?
Yes, yes. If this was about foreign cars it'd be that one
Will Matsumoto head towards Aoyama or Shiba Park?
In Aoyama-itchome, was it the Honda?
That one, I think is the best one
You want to head to Aoyama-Itchoume?
Let's head to Aoyama-Itchoume
We might end up fumbling this
We might have 5 people meeting right away for the first time. That's not good is it?
Will Matsumoto's prediction come true? Let's see where the others are going
Before in the opening when I opened the card,
2 of them came to mind
I'd want to head towards Honda's showroom. The one at the corner right?
That one, or in Roppongi, wasn't there like a Ferrari showroom?
Near Iikura
Yes yes yes, yes
Those 2 came to mind right away
Should I go with Honda? Or Ferrari?
As soon as I saw the theme 2 of them came to mind
Near the Iikura intersectionn, I'm certain there's a Ferrari, or some other showroom
At the Aoyama-itchome at the left of the intersection there's a huge place with a car parked. That's a showroom right?
Let's do this
Just like Hamada, Endo is choosing between Aoyama and Iikura
I want to consider what everyone else might think,
If I do that, let's go to [@!#!@#]
Just where is Endo going?
I thought of three, the first one, the showroom near Shinjuku West Gate
That building, also Aoyama, the showroom there
And Ginza
I think, and I did used to live near there,
Aoyama, probably
But I didn't live near Aoyama though, I was trying to look cool
And what about Tanaka, who sucks at this?
There's 1 I thought of, but it seems like a bad idea. It's a showroom you can see from the highway
The highway one is the one I thought of first
Well let's get going for now
What is this showroom Tanaka can see from the highway?
Getting on the highway leaving Shibuya,
Like heading towards Odaiba, around the right side of Shiba Park, there's a showroom you can see from the highway
Oh yeah, there is
That's the first one I thought of,
But in the opening Hamda-san told me "go to your second idea"
He did say that
Yes
Aoyama 246 Intersection, I just thought of one there
I see
Eh, what should I do?
We might have 5 people meeting right away for the first time. That's not good is it?
As Matsumoto said, it's possible everyone could meet up
Will a miraculous meet up with the first theme occur?
I feel like I won't be the only one there
Maybe Hamada...
I think he might not even pass by there
That guy never moved houses right?
He lives in Seijo (Setagaya)
Where in Seijo?
In Seijo?
Which district?
[!@#!@#]-district
What house number?
It's fine really, you can say it on TV it's alright
15 minutes since the start. He arrives at the Honda in Aoyama
Oh yes, there it is. This one.
They used to have a car out front
I guess not anymore
I bet 1 or 2 people will come for sure
Believing everyone will meet from the first hint. He waits for the other 4.
Personally there's a lot of showrooms I see while driving
I think I see quite a few normally
We're almost there right?
He arrives at his showroom. Is he in Aoyama like Matsumoto, or in Iikura Katamachi
In Iikura Katamachi, a Ferrari dealership
What do you think? This is like THE Showroom
Endo chose the Rosso Scuderia in Iikura Katamachi
I am confident about this one,
They'll definitely be there
Let's go meet them
Between Aoyama, Iikura, and Ginzam where did Hosei end up?
Nissan
He chose Ginza's Nissan Crossing
In Ginza...
And then...
Hm?
Who's that?
Can we?
Let's head there
Hold on, look, you can see a camera...
There is a camera crew
There's a camera crew
But that's not Gaki's crew right?
It's a different production
Gaki no Tsukai doesn't have such smartly dressed camera man
And between Aoyama and Shiba Park, where did Tanaka end up?
I think it's in this area
It's that one right? Look! "Cornes"?
Cornes
The main point is whether or not you can see it from the highway
Before going to the showroom, he confirms the highway is there
That there, you can see it from there right? Yeah look
There, there
And then confiriming the Cornes showroom is there
Yeah,
The location, it's that there
Right now it's under construction,
So this is what I always saw from the highway
Just as Tanaka remembered, there was a Cornes dealership, currently under construction
I wonder how many people know about this place from driving by
I messed up
And Hamada who also had to choose between Iikura and Aoyama is close to his destination
Hamada-san, last time you were all by yourself till the end
Yeah
I hope at least one person comes
Who do you hope comes?
Anyone, anyone really, well ...
... If Matsumoto-san comes all of a sudden, then...
Would you dislike that?
20 minutes since he left
Hamada arrives at his showroom
Will it be Aoyama where Matsumoto is? Or Iikura where Endo is?
The first hint "A car showroom" - Hamada had to choose between Aoyama or Iikura Katamachi
Will it be Aoyama where Matsumoto is? Or Iikura Katamachi where Endo is?
They're definitely here, they'll come here
Huh, they're not here!
Not one person!
But then
Nobody!
Oi!
This one right?
Of course, however,
Yes, of course, but, I know what you mean
This is kind of annoying
But it's this one!
But, still...
I don't like DownTown being together by themselves
And whenever we meet up, for some reason we always stand in our manzai position
It's never the other way around
Only 2 people met here, which means,
Time's up
For real?!
They really didn't come?
The 5 go on a group call to confirm their locations
Hello. Why aren't you here?
Matsumoto-san, where are you?
No no Yama-chan where are you?
I'm in Ginza's Nissan Showroom!
Ginza he says
Ginza's Nissan Showroom he said
Nobody would think of that
Eh? And Shozo?
Yes, I'm at the corner of Iikura Katamachi, in front of the Ferrari showroom
Oh yeah, yeah that one, yeah
Tanaka?
Yes, um, I'm at Shiba Park,
It's a showroom you can see from the highway
Oh that one, the Cornes
Yes! The Cornes
I get it, but how the hell were all 5 of us supposed to know that
I thought everyone ... I had a strong impression from the highway
No no no no, hold on
It's GOTTA be the Aoyama-itchoume Honda!
UWAAAHH THAT ONE!
That was my other choice!
Matsumoto-san that was my second choice
That's where you went huh Matsumoto-san
Listen to where Hamada is
Hamda-san, Hamada-san
I'm standing next to Matsutomo-san
DownTown met up!
It's a "A Legendary Day" isn't it!
TN: "A Legendary Day"  is referring to DownTown's recent Manzai performance, their first in 31 years
No this is annoying
In so many ways I want you to COME HERE
For real, next time, for sure
I wanna say, stop messing up on purpose because it's funny to leave DownTown by themselves
It's really obvious
It's obvious, I get it
Enough
Let's meet up
Let's do this
This is a big deal, DownTown-san have already met up
This really is "A Legendary Day"
Well, in the end, I did say between Aoyama and Ginza right?
Well...There's no helping it
I did think of it. I think I can do the next one
Today you wanna meet up
I do, I do
With the first theme, DownTown met up
They want to clear this faster than ever before - Time for the next hint
Damn, so hard!
"A Large Post Office"
We gotta a really tough one here
We just passed by it
That one right?
I don't know what it's called though
Akasaka Post Office?
Oh ok
It's really famous!
It is, and it's huge
Yeah!
It's gonna end now!
It depends on if they come or not!
We can walk there
Yeah let's walk there. Let's go
Oh yeah, let's walk there
Akasaka Post Office, so close by they walk there
If they think about it, they'll go "Oh yeah, there's post office near where DownTown are"
They're not the type of guys to think like that
No way
For real
They gotta take that into consideration!
I'm telling you, their brains don't work that good
Where were the other guys?
Endo was nearby
Endo's in Roppongi right?
Where was Yama-chan?
Ginza's Nissan
Oh yeah
Ginza's Nissan...Well it's not that far away
Walking with Hamada like this...
It feels like the very first episode of Gaki no Tsukai
In Shibuya?
I can't remember if it was Shibuya
You guys were climbing a slope
It was like that yeah
I remember climbing the slope, I can't remember if it was Shibuya
It was the hill near the bottom of Shibuya
Oh really?
Really?
1 minute since they started walking, they arrive at Akasaka Post Office
At least one person will come, 1 person for sure
Meanwhile, Hosei, Endo, & Tanaka were deciding their destinations
Can you think of one?
I can
The first one that came to mind is Meguro Post Office
On Meguro-Dori?
On Meguro-Dori
And the other one I thought of is Setagaya Post Office, with the neon
It has the neon sign, yes
I feel like there was also one near where DownTown are. I can't remember if that was a large one
There are plenty of locations, there's one in Akasaka too-
Nevermind that was a bank. That's a bank
Wait wait! Hold on! I'm counting on my memories right now,
In the past, in Tameike Sanno where Yoshimoto's Tokyo office was,
I think there was a post office behind there. And it was pretty huge.
But, that might be a bank
It might not be that large, if you compare to Shinjuku, Shibuya...
It's not that big
Was there a big one in Shibuya?
Nope, I can only think of [!@@#!#]
[@!!@$] Post Office
Will they meet up with DownTown?
20 minutes since they arrived at Akasaka Post Office
DownTown are pissed off that they still haven't met anybody
You know, it's messed up if Endo doesn't come here
Ah, considering the distance
Considering the distance, the fact that he's not here only makes me worry
So DownTown are probably driving sitting with each other right now huh?
Mr. Driver, did you come up with any ideas for a large post office?
I thought Akasaka Post Office
Akasaka? There's one in Aoyama? - Wait, THERE IS!
It's right across the Aoyama-Itchoume intersection right? UWAH wait a second
Endo forgot about Akasaka Post Office
So, then where is Nedo heading?
Where did Yamasaki go again?
Ginza
Ahh, he's far away
Is there a big one in Ginza? Oh right, Ginza Post Office
Ginza Post Office
It's big?
It is
Oh it's big?
Really?
Alright whatever, even if it is big, we were in Akasaka
We're the senpai...The 2 Big Bosses
The 2 Big Bosses are already in Aoyama-Itchoume!
"What are the 2 Big Bosses gonna do?" - That's how they should think
Of course right?
There's one behind where we passed by right?
They might have gone somewhere totally different
Yamasaki, that guy used to live in Meugro,
But Meguro Post Office is not an option
And that Hosei just arrived at his destination. Just where is he?
Oh! It's huge! That's a big one
Just as Matsumoto predicted, he went to Meguro Post Office
It's huge right?
Yeah, I've never actually been in there
But I have a strong memory of it being huge from all the times I walked past it. Everyone should think that too.
Where the hell did everyone go?
Meanwhile, it's been 50 minutes since DownTown arrived at Akasaka Post Office
This is a loss
The fact that we've waited this long
They need to take into consideration DownTown-san are in Aoyama-Itchoume
Exactly, exactly
Ahh enough
This is is impossible, impossible
TN: Not sure about this line
They're going to get a massive punishment for this
For real, they just didn't listen to us
They didn't listen to us, they don't listen to people
The only thing to do is rip off their ears
Meanwhile, that man appears in front of Hosei at Meguro Post Office
Of course! Hosei-san!
Hosei-san!
SEE! WE DID IT! Hell yeah!
Alright!
Congratulations!\n
Of course right?
For real, it's this one
Thank god!
Also Hosei-san used to live near here. I came here cause I was thinking of him
Thank you. I'm really happy!
Tanaka also arrives at his Post Office
Will he be able to meet anyone?
Nope!
Tanaka chose Setagaya Post Office
Nobody's here huh?
Eh? Isn't it this one?
And then...
Tanaka-san, time's up
Seriously...Not here?
The 5 confirm their locations
What are you doing?
Where did you guys go?
Hold on, we were just at Aoyama right?
So the closest one to us was Shozo. Where the hell are you?
Yes, umm, right now I'm at Meguro Post Office
There it is! Meguro Post Office!
Endo-san is at Meguro Post Office?
No no, GRRR, GRR, I'm pissed off
There it is
Oi! Rakugoka!
Where the hell are you?
I'm at Meguro Post Office!
Of course, Hosei-san went to Meguro, of course
And Tanaka?
Yes, I'm at Setagaya Post Office in Sancha
Goddamn. He went to Sancha
In the end Tanaka is by himself again
It'll be fine, of course I'll meet you guys with the next theme
Because of Tanaka we had to wait for an hour here
No listen, this might sound like an excuse,
In the opening, I partook in Hamada-san's advice to "Go to the second one you think of"
Yes yes, so the second one I partook in was Setagaya Post Office
What was your first one?
Meguro
Oi!
Just go with your first idea!
What the hell do you mean "The 2nd one I partook in"
That's the advice he gave me
What the hell is "The 2nd one I partook in"
Don't, don't make such dumb excuses
Listen. You lot.
If you think about where we started, we obviously walked to the post office
We walked to Akasaka Post Office on foot and have been waiting ever since!
WE'VE BEEN WAITING SO LONG
AND WAITING TOGETHER!
WHAT GENERATION ARE YOU GUYS?!!
TN: Referring to NSC comedy school, DownTown are from the 1st genration
I'm scared, I'm so scared
This ferocious anger in front of Akasak Post Office!
Next Week!
No Smartphones Meetup Finale!
The Theme - "A long tunnel"
I really gotta meet up, that's for certain
Eh? I can't think anywhere right now
I think near [@!#!@]
Ahh, yeah
I think this is a lucky question
Will they be able to meet? Look forward to the answer!
Timed & Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband