DOWNTOWN
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
First ever Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende Chikichiki Episode 4
Chh
Absolutely Tasty : Chawanmushi
Episode 4!
Episode 4
It's Chawanmushi
It's something we always wanted to try right?
That's right
Right?
What is it?
We have tried it
4th time right?
Cooking is about a bride's challenge
But that is delicious, in the end no one complained at all
That's not right
The breakthrough
The prize money too
During the taiyaki challenge i made the wiener taiyaki
And i say "here it go everyone"
Here it go?
Remember?
I've done it, i've done it
First is Tanaka, his first ingredient is ..
First ingredient
Yea
Here it is
What the..
What the heck is this?
Italian style?
That's right
Cheese
Wine
and Wine
The combination between Cheese and Wine is perfect right?
Yeah
That is when being eaten separately
That's right
What are you going to do with the wine?
That's a big piece
That's huge!
Everything will taste like cheese
What's next?
I will put in these shredded cheese too
Into that?
I will put it now
With this dish
You are not mistaken?
This is the normal egg
For chawanmushi right?
The normal mixture
Egg and ..
Taste broth
That's all?
That's all huh?
Wine and cheese makes a good combination
You get the concept wrong
Let's drink the wine now
Firstly the setting must be right
I thought you get the concept wrong
The wine is red wine
Absolutely it's red wine
Why?
Because it's just cheese
This thing have amazing colors
It looks evil
Definitely tasty
Next is the second ingredient
Again with the Italian Style
Cappuccino Chawanmushi
The making process is adding warm milk and coffee.  The cinnamon is for?
You are not putting the cinnamon?
This is for after everything is done
Next is Endo, what ingredients will he use?
Your turn now
You are going with nonsense again right?
It's Frisk
Why do you keep bringing this
Are you waiting for commercial offer?
That's right
It is actually my dream
You are really waiting for the offer?
Well... if they offer me ..
If you do this there will not be any offer!
This is ..
This is not just mine but.. how am i going to say ..
It is also the dream of the staff
What the heck
They want to do this
I've always wanted to try
Of all the things to try, only frisk will fail
That's right
Normally i put 50..
He's right, it's 50 ..
This time, one portion i will put 200
What the heck
That is bad
Why the heck 200
Endo liking Frisk this much is amazing
Second ingredient is Carbonara chawanmushi
Endo did it
That's a lot
You put a lot
Why the comment just now
This looks cool
It's Yamazaki turn and his ingredients are
What's this? Umaibo?
Umaibo and it is corn soup flavor
Umaibo have different flavor
There are different flavors like okonomiyaki but this is the best
Corn soup
It's cheap
It has the dessert's look
I break this into half
Next i pour this in
Simple
Fast
It's simple
Men's cooking
Yamazaki second ingredient is ..
Cream soda
This soda right?
Right, i see, i see , Cream soda
Wait a minute
Just now, that is not polite
That's not right
Ain't it always like this?
It's not like that
Just now?
Mixing up the egg
The whisking process is so fun
While you are whisking put my expression into the scene
This one
100ml of Cream soda
Is it open?
This is not tolerable
How can this guy do it?
Oh, it's open
Here it is
Well it's Yamazaki so i wish to be angry
Yamazaki creation: Cream Soda Chawanmushi
Wondering how it taste like
Next is Hamada turn, what kind of chawanmushi?
I am making something delicious
What is this?
This guy is always cheating
It's luxurious
Hamada is rich
That's right
It's not true
See
Woah, it's luxurious
What's this dish?
This is Tom Yam Soup
Since primary school, this guy has been cheating
Since young?
Since young he is
That prawn is such a waste
Now, this prawn is not a waste
I want to eat it just like this
This soup
Soup
Put this in
This is
This is good
I see
Like this
Hamada next dish is unexpectedly, Natto Kimchi Chawanmushi
This table stink
This table really stink
This is the stock
I see
Last is matsumoto what kind of chawanmushi is he presenting?
This is definitely tasty
OK
It stink!
It stinks here!
It's ... Stink!
The raw one stink
Stink
It's squid ink
I see
Squid ink
This, put in
Just like this
Not open?
This one put inside
I see
It stinks right?
It stink right?
Stink, it really stink
The meat too?
The meat too
Then more
The egg mixture
The egg too
I see
Look at the color
What color is this
What?
Terrible
The color is like Mold bread
Everyone say it stink
Odor removal nuts
I see, i see
This stinkiness is okay
Originally stink is tasty
Who is it?
Kawabadayasi nari crime
You watch those?
In the end everyone die
When they say they die
Stink is tasty
One more
Hai
It's Montblanc
Let's eat this while we wait
That's right
The size is perfect
The size is perfect right?
The nuts looks like something evil
I see
Look at this
Amazing
When you want to bath
You go into the bathtub
It looks like the **** floating
It's good right?
I know the fun reason
I have another version
Show us
After so much trouble
During the pizza series, i used the pig face
That's right, that's right
Now it's not face
The hand ....
This is cute
If it's like this we can't eat it
This is fine right?
You wish for pet like this right?
It looks like shoulder
Disgusting
I'm not joking
You are not Joking?
Joking
Is this what you want?
Of course i want to do it
Cool, it goes like this
Finally is tasting time
Here is Tanaka's
YES!
Ero-Kappa
Who is the ero
First is Tanaka's Wine+Cheese
However, how does it taste?
Open
It doesn't come out well
It stink
It smells like Sake Lees
He is right
The middle one is Tanaka's
No,no this is Hamada's
Why the heck
Why the heck it's me
I heard today is your birthday
Idiot, my birthday has long passed
Treat that as a belated gift
Tanaka-han
Tanaka!
He hate DownTown a lot
Tanaka-han
Itadakimas
Wine+Cheese
Bad
Impossible
Absolutely impossible
This is extremely bad
Top 5 fail
This is horrible
Bad
It feels like..
*I am not sure if I'm right*
*Watching Choju from Warrior 1
It feels like this
This is bad
*Skull and Crossbone*
I am thinking of *Dokuro
Dokuro is fine right?
Betrayal's appearance, Wine+Cheese achieve Dokuro mark
Second is Cappucino chawanmushi, will it turn out nicely?
It looks good
This looks good
Dessert-like
That's right
Then cream
Normally, cream always compliment...
Cappucino right?
Put it on top, a lot
You are first?
Senior must have first
You are the first fast one right?
Then Tanaka, this one
Then put the Cinnamon in it
I see
This is good
Itadakimas
Looks good
Coffee Jelly
What is this?
It taste bland
This doesn't taste horrible
I don't get the energy
The first one, is out-dated
Now it is branded coffee
No impact
Cappucino Chawanmushi, for the betrayal get a 2 point
Next is Endo, before the dangerous Frisk, Carbonara Chawanmushi
First, the appearance
This kind of feeling
I am not sure why the spaghetti still retain it's looks
It looks tough
Itadakimas
Carbonara
Come on, please
Please
What is this?
No taste
It's bland
Among the previous one
It's acceptable
But Tanaka's being horrible
This is still.. edible?
4.. 4 is it?
3 or 4
Okay, 2
It deserves that          Yeah
4 please at the worst
At least he is save from Dokuro mark
Doesn't have the proper taste, Carbonara Chawanmushi scores a mere 4
Finally, the dangerously full mark-minded Frisk Chawanmushi
Ah, the appearance
The appearance is..
It looks normal
It's here
Nostalgic fear
Blinking eye
The feeling is back
Or course, 200 frisk per serving
Each person 200?
Each person 200
Steak?
Itadakimas
It feels like drinking mint
I did not eat anything strange, but why, this "stress"
Everything melted
No remains left
No remains
It goes blub, blub
For real?
When being steamed, the frisk go 'bam'
Try the deeper part here, this
Hot
Now is not the matter of hot or not
It's HOT!!
Looks like the previous one is warm
Cat-Tongue = Sensitive to hot food
Why did i try it with someone who have *cat-tongue
It is hot
We don't need that answer
50 old men entering your mouth
50 warm old men
This cannot make it, Sorry
As expected, the Frisk receive a Dokuro mark
Next is Yamazaki, first impression looks tasty, Umaibo Chawanmushi
It is not expensive
This, here
Looks like Tempura
Looks nice, the smell also nice
The smell is seriously nice
Itadakimas
I think this is success
I did it, see
Tasty
This is good
This can be recommended
This full mark ..
Exceeding full mark 1
Which 1?
Full mark
Definitely not full mark
It is too lenient
Everyone praise it tasty, why i cannot get full mark?
We are just saying
If it come first
Well... 7 then
I think 6
Hm,hm
6 then
Wuah it changed
Everyone say 7 until you say 6 and everyone follow
7,7
5 is also near 6
5 then
What the hell, No way, 7
This round using very cheap ingredient, unexpectedly score 7 mark
Next is cream soda, how does it taste like?
I did it
I did it !
No no, the color
No no, this is not good
No, i did it
Why you say "I did it" when you see this?
I don't know
I did it
I did it this time
Let's do it
Itadakimas
What's this?
It's coming out
What is it?
Taste bad
This is bad
Inside this and that material mixed in
This is evil
The evil Cream soda Chawanmushi obviously receive Dokuro mark
Next is Hamada's first dish, Tom Yam Chawanmushi
Looks tasty!
This looks very good
Is this for real?
Yes yes
The first look
This is a good chawanmushi
Itadakimas
You put into your mouth while it's hot?
It's bad but tasty
The taste in mouth is amazing
Bad
This is the taste of Tom Yam
This can be sold to restaurant
The price of copyright is 500,000 Yen
This can make it
Delicious very delicious
It taste good?
This doesn't taste good?
Not delicious?
This is totally edible
This deserve 8 mark?
If 8 ....
I also think of 4
I think so too
What the heck
What the hell, Then 8 just for this
8.. then 8
If in store, this can sell well
This is good
This is good, edible
Huh? What the hell
You just contradict yourself
I make a huge mistake
Delete the first comment i make
Tom Yam Chawanmushi, scores a splendid 8 mark
The next dish, not much expectation natto+kimchi chawanmushi
What is this!
Scary, this is scary
Sewage water
Knock it off already
Tough
Amazing amount inside
Well, this is Kimchi+Natto
This is good
I think i like this
After tasting, this is not bad
This is not bad
This one too
Most favorite
Extremely the top
For real?
If the one who eat this is animal, that is the strange part.
What mark are you giving?
This is
2~~~~
Effort 2
1 & 2 is close
I don't understand "Effort 2"
This is the score of your favorite?
Then this is 8 and Tom Yam 6
Wh- Why?
Everyone have the same reaction as Tom Yam so surely it's 8
If this get 9 because of Natto, nobody can believe it
Then this is 8
Tom Yam 8 too
Not like that
Seems like 8 is limit
This is 8 too
Reason is B'Q
Idol *********
Natoo+Kimchi achieve a miraculous 8 mark
Last is Matsumoto, his first dish is Squid Ink Chawanmushi
This is bad!
Matsumoto's First dish, Squid Ink Chawanmushi
This is bad
This is not bad
This is definitely defect
It didn't solidify too
Spiritual flow
It definitely like that
This is soup
Itadakimas
It's here
This is
Amazing right? Itadakimas
The inside is still not properly cooked
When you say that
Obviously the first 2 and 3 mouth you can eat
I don't know why
Wait, the wife
The wife!
I think it is well made
It is worth it to put expensive thing in
Salt
Just a little
I understand this one do not deserve 9 mark
Obviously not 9
Not under this circumstances
Carbonara taste is slightly better?
Better than Dokuro
Because it's edible
What? what? The point is 10 full point, i get what point?
On.. 1 point?
Not that
Squid Ink Chawanmushi, because of last minute debate, 1 point
Finally it's Matsumoto's 2nd ingredient Montblanc Chawanmushi
Only the nuts is intact
He is right
There is no change
Here it is
Delicious
Normal
Delicious~~
Taste like Mother's kindness
Similar to picture book
Let's go to sleep
Delicious
Delicious ~~
Like someone rubbing your chest
So kind
If only that happen
It's a new dessert
Kid will be very happy
5 point
Yes
Full mark is okay
Too tasty
Ain't 5 point okay?
Really tasty
I'm sorry, let's stop
This is wrong
5 point is from?
Let's finalize the point
What the hell, it cannot be
Laugh you idiot!
I think full mark is okay
10 is okay, right
Give full mark?
Okay then
Montblance Chawanmushi receives full mark
Last is pig's hand Chawanmushi, how does it taste like?
Open!
Wonderful ain't it?
Last is Matsumoto's pig hand Chawanmushi
Open!
Wonderful ain't it?
Extremely swollen
This cannot be
No way
Whose hand is it?
Wait a while everyone, the spoon put here
It's like this?
I understand
The hand is okay to be big
That hand is not allowed
Then just take a little
Itadakimas
Why nobody is touching it?
Is it  because you don't want to touch another hand?
How is this?~~
Why you keep saying don't touch
Is because there is a hand?
I did it, i did it