A certain library in Tokyo
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
Ozawa Hitoshi
Woah
m 0 0 l -26 0 l -26 13 l 26 13 l 26 0 l 0 0
the person who draws the skull card will
undergo the punishment as displayed
Forehead flick
topic
Ready? One, two and...
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Ozawa
Tanaka
Forehead flick
Matsumoto
Shh
He forcibly took it from me
Really?
Is that so?
All of you?
All of us
One flick per person
Making noise would bother the others
they can't raise their voice no matter what
m 0 0 l -26 0 l -26 13 l 26 13 l 26 0 l 0 0
Wanna go last, Hamada?
First one or last one
Alright, like this
Ouch ouch
Such a strong flick
Go, Tanaka
You heard the sound of his skull?
Sorry
Let's save Ozawa for last
Nice shot
It's a forehead flick, you know...
What the--?
I'm scared
What!?
TYPESETTING & QUALITY CHECK BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
patreon.com/shionnotsukai
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com /fb.com/shionnotsukai /twitter.com/FGRNDNoises /ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Downtown's
Gaki no Tsukai
ya Arahende!
Kid enema
topic
I hate this one
This is the worst one for me
I have anal fistula you know
It'd suck if you'd pick this
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Ozawa
Tanaka
Ready and...
Lucky me
Kid enema
Ozawa
Shh
We made it guys
"Kid enema"...
Who's this kid?
Who is it gonna be?
Over there
Get on all four, please
Like this
All four?
You ready?
Back off
It's ok, it's ok
Don't be afraid of him
Don't worry about him, it's going to be fne
Ready
Holy shi--
My god that hurts
I'm glad it wasn't me
He got my balls
That one hurts
It does
One of the worst ones
Stay quiet
Super spicy mask
Eh?
topic
Sounds scary
This time I have to escape
Ready and...
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Ozawa
Tanaka
Endo
Shh
Super spicy mask
You gotta be kidding me
Uh? What is that?
Is he gonna be fine?
Feels like it's gonna linger for a while
What should I do?
This special sauce is 10 times hotter than tabasco
Woah, woah, woah...
Oh crap
There's so much in there
Are you kidding me?
You're soaking it?
Yes
Oh my
That's too much
This is gonna suck so bad
Man
Wait, isn't that too much?
That's too much, dude
You're gonna have a bad time
Wring it out
More
Gimme a sec--
Woah, I'm scared
Gimme a break
He's holding his breath
It hurts, I accidentally ate some
Ow ow ow
Keep quiet
Quiet
It burns
Silence!
Shut your trap
Come on, man
My throat...
Just shut up
We gotta keep quiet
It hurts so much
I'd hate it
Oh boy
Yoshinobu's electric forehead
The hell is this?!
It's static electricity...
Yoshinobu's electric forehead
topic
Ready and...
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Ozawa
Tanaka
Hosei
Shh
Yoshinobu's electric forehead
Alright!
I'd hate this one
Are we ready?
Eh? Really? This is scary
Your shoes
Take them off
Wow
I'm freaking out
He's getting charged up
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Producer
The voltage is 10 times higher than regular static electricity
Yoshinobu is going to transmit it with his forehead
m 0 0 l -26 0 l -26 13 l 26 13 l 26 0 l 0 0
Draw back, this looks dangerous
Your forehead  Raise your hair
I'm scared
This is frightening
It's making a zappy sound
Look, they're charging him!
Yoshinobu doesn't like this as well
Your forehead
Quiet
He got it too
Of course he's gonna take it too
He got hurt too
It hurts like hell
I swear it hurts so much
From here to here
Wasn't it "forehead"...?
At the same time
Even down there?
Yeah
It's still running
That sucks so much
Do we still have more?
We do, a lot
Old dude garlic breath
Oh, this one
Oh shit
Old dude garlic breath
topic
This one again?
I really don't like this one
One by one
From me?
Ready and...
Endo
Hamada
Ozawa
Why did you flip it too?
He said one by one
They're safe...
Oh, you meant just you
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Hosei
Here we are
It's time
I beg you...
You two, flip it at the same time
Spare me...
Alright
Please...
At the same time
I can't--
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready? One, two...
Matsumoto
Old dude garlic breath
Shh
That's the one I did not  want
Matsumoto's garlic breath agony!!
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready and...
Matsumoto
Old dude garlic breath
Shh
That's the one I did not  want
Holy shit
Making noise would bother the others
they can't raise their voice no matter what
m 0 0 l -26 0 l -26 13 l 26 13 l 26 0 l 0 0
This isn't his first time, right?
I hate the old dude related ones...  Really?
Really?
He's eating them raw
Here he comes
He's gonna breathe through that pipe
Other foods would be bad too
He's looking pale
Yeah
Like, spicy stuff
That's right
Woah
Incredible
Can you smell that?
It's so much
And now he's gonna take it all for himself
Right
I'm done
It came to you as expected?
Shit
It's a knockout for him
Enough with old dudes...
Let's move on
Sea slug innards juice
Eh-!?
No way...
Sea slug innards juice
topic
This makes me feel sick
Is Hamada the only at zero?
Come on...
Ah, Tanaka too?
Yeah, Tanaka too
0 times
1 time
2 times
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Ozawa
Tanaka
current punishments
m 0 0 b -10 0 -20 0 -30 0 b -30 5 -30 10 -30 15 b -10 15 10 15 30 15 b 30 10 30 5 30 0 b 20 0 10 0 0 0
m 0 0 l -26 0 l -26 13 l 26 13 l 26 0 l 0 0
Zero, huh...
I really hate this one  It's disgusting
Is it safe to drink?
m 0 0 l -26 0 l -26 13 l 26 13 l 26 0 l 0 0
the person who draws the skull card will
undergo the punishment as displayed
He's right, maybe it's not  That's real
I really, really hate this
I'm getting nervous
What should we do? One by one again?
Should we?
I'm going first
Matsumoto
Hosei
Tanaka
Sea slug innards juice
Shh
Tanaka
Alright alright alright!
This is the worst one yet
Get it ready, Shozo
Those alone?!
Yeah, just these
Are you kidding me?
They smell
Just looking at them makes me sick
Like this
No way
All of that?
At least a glass
It's more solid than liquid
It's not running down
How much?
That's enough
Try to smell it
Drink it up
You gotta be kidding me
Hurry up and drink
Come on
He's not drinking
Come on, dude
Not even a sip
What the hell...
You haven't drank anything yet
Come on, open your mouth
Open up
Looks like a mole here
Come on
Say "aaah"
It's not even pouring down
This sucks so bad
So noisy!
Shut your trap
Don't jump around, dude
Hey! Don't go next to the old dude, man!!
How is it? Bitter?
Like raw fish?
Yeah, it's like fish
I see
Geez
Probably this one
This is the worst one
Clean your face, it's all there
This sucks
There's still more...?
How many are left?
Enough, really
There's still a lot of them
Yeah, I can see that  Still far from over
Carbonated water from the nose
What the?!
topic
This isn't going to feel good
Enough...
You should do it
He's still at zero?
It's not my fault
Only Hamada has 0 punishments
That's your fault, you pick your cards
Why should I do it if I don't pick the card myself?
Just one time
Think of it as a service
For free
"Service" my ass
Who's going first?
Tanaka
You're still dirty
Sea slug everywhere
Clean up
Matsumoto
Really?
I'm so glad...
Matsumoto
It can't be...
Hosei
Here I go
Carbonated water from the nose
Hosei
Shh
He's so unlucky
How does it work?
Huh?
This one?
So primitive
I'm scared
Sit down please
Do I have to?
You ok?
Here I go, get ready
Yes
Ready and...
What the--
It came out from his other nostril
From left to right
It's connected
But maybe it's good that it flowed
Yeah, maybe
I see
It's nose-gargling, you know
Yeah
With carbonated water...?
Well, usually that's not it, but...
Still, your nose is clean now
Yes
It's going to get worse now, isn't it?
It is
That's how it goes
I have a bad feeling about this
Scalding crêpe
topic
Hosei
What the---
Did you just force his reveal...?
Is this legal?
What the hell are you doing?!
Tanaka
Scalding crêpe
Shh
Tanaka
You can't do this
But you already picked that one
You did, yeah
I know but, flipping my card and getting the punishment...
It was yours
You chose that
He just flipped it, you picked it yourself
I know, but still...
Look at that
Is it gonna be on his face?
That's right
Don't touch that
Oh my
Freshly made?
Yes
It's gonna be freshly made
This is crazy
Tanaka has been so unlucky...
Lie down, man
Do you hear the sound it's making?
It's gonna be fine
It's making noises
What is he gonna do with it?
It's gonna burn like hell
It's done
Here it comes
It looks so hot
Don't move around
On his face?
What?! Are you serious?
It's fine, it's fine
Just don't move
That was quick
Hot!
It's burning
Of course it's hot
Come here
Keep quiet
We have one more for you
He's making another one
Come on
He's already making it, so...
Lie down
They're two
It's two crêpes
For some reason
The punishment consists of two crêpes
Pay one get two, huh
Shhh!
Keep quiet
We still have him with zero
Not even once?
Yeah, only Hamada
It's just luck, nothing you can do about it
Alright
Here
You haven't flipped this yet
Oh, right
Focused
He's desperate
Monkey kick
Ehh?
This is scary
Monkey kick
topic
I have experienced this before
Is it a real monkey?
It is
I see
It's not my fault I'm not getting any
Who's gonna start?
Nice one
Hosei
Tanaka
Alright!
Endo
Ozawa
Monkey kick
Shh
Oh yeah!!
This is a scary one
Are you for real?!
That thing is huge!
It's pretty big
Really
Don't make him mad
Hey, don't set him off
Don't provoke him
Man, monkeys are scary...
I'm freaking out
Woah, terrifying
Ozawa, don't piss him off please
He's gonna destroy you for real
I wonder how fast he's gonna kick him
---'s gonna kick him
Kinda
That was kinda cute
Huh?
Now I'm pissed off
Never been this pissed off before
It's humiliating
To be kicked by a monkey...
Humiliation
You can't even get mad at it
That lil bastard
So humiliating
Can't we just wrap it up?
I wonder how many are left
Only Hamada has 0 punishments
Come on, there are days you're
just lucky and don't get any
Next one is our last one
Last one?
Eh? Really?
It's not my fault, man
Rocket punch
What's this about?
What the-?
Rocket punch
topic
What should we do?
You go first, Ozawa
You've been like this from the start
Ozawa
Just flip it, Endo
Endo
Alright
Hosei
Oh yeah
Really?!
Ok, ok
Tanaka
We did it!
members left: Matsumoto Hamada
We can still make it after all
What a situation
Gimme a break...
Come on
It doesn't change if you just flip it now
I want him to have it
Or if we both do it at the same time
How should we do this?
Are we picking one?
Come on, let's pick a card
You're ok with that?
Let's count to three
Alright
I'll count for you
Ready? One, two and...
Hamada
Matsumoto
Alright!!
Hamada
Rocket punch
Shh
Such a beautiful way to end it
Hamada is gonna get a rocket punch and that thing again!
Perfect
Are you kidding me?
No complaints
Hamada
Matsumoto
Alright!!
Hamada
Rocket punch
Shh
Making noise would bother the others
they can't raise their voice no matter what
m 0 0 l -26 0 l -26 13 l 26 13 l 26 0 l 0 0
Such a beautiful way to end it
Perfect
Are you kidding me?
No complaints
It's just perfect
It's like that one we saw on "No-Laughing"
Geez...
It's scary
This one is pretty scary
It's gonna hurt
It's really powerful
I'm so glad
It's dangerous
He gotta wear those?
You don't need glasses
Of course I do
You don't!
I do
Ichioka Genki
the punishment will be supervised by the Denjirou crew
It's gonna hit you really hard
Woah, scary...
It's gonna hurt
Whaaat?!
This is too much!!
No way
That thing is gonna mess me up
I don't like this at all!!
I mean--
Almost there
I'm freaking out!!!!
Straight on his face
See? I told you so!!
My stomach...
That was so scary
We've finished them all
I only got humiliating punishments
That's right
Kid enema
Monkey kick
Ozawa's punishments
You're right  Only humiliations
The monkey and the slugs were the worst
Monkey kick
Sea slug innards juice
Yeah...
How about the garlic?
Old dude garlic breath
Oh, right, that one too  Yeah...
Wanna try the garlic yourself?
Wait---
We're not gonna air it, it's fine
You're not?
What do you mean you're not going to?
We're not gonna air it
No wait, give me a break
I didn't
I didn't pick any card!
I'm telling you, we're not gonna air this
It's fine, really
Garlic breath explosion right into Hamada!
I didn't pick any card!
We're not gonna air it
Hamada
Old dude garlic breath
Shh
It's fine, really
We're not gonna use it
We won't use it, so it's fine
But---
I mean--
It's not gonna be on air
It stinks!
Already?
Maybe it's from before
Here comes
There was a lot before
Was it this close before?!
Yup
Ugh
Here it comes
Here we go
It's mouth-to-mouth
Straight in his mouth
Look at him
It left a mark
Disgusting
I'm friggin' crying...
Wanna try the nose gargling?
No fucking way
Anything but that
FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FAN TRANSLATION MADE BY FANS FOR OTHER FANS TO ENJOY. NO COPYRIGHT INFRINGMENT INTENDED.
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES
TYPESETTING & QC BY KEDOMAS