Tanaka vs Kojima Yoshio.
So everybody!
So, the first battle will begin now.
Don't lose Tanaka!
Are you ready?
Yes!
So let's start.
First match! Start!
Ohh good!
Do variations!
Good! Good! OK! OK!
Don't lose!
Expression! Expression!
Your face too! Your face!
Excuse me!
Excuse me, let me pass!
Excuse, give way!
Ahh! Good! Good!
Half time passed!
Tanaka!!
You keep doing the same damn thing!!
Show us your youth!
Last 10 secs!
Last spurt!
Finish!!
Tanaka's showed us his moves.
That base movement was Noh right?
That right?
A move that seems like collecting something by Tanaka.
However..
The score, please!
Please!
Kojima Yoshio wins.
3 votes agains 0.
10 points to !Team Junk!.
There was only a few variations in the moves...
It was the same moves only.
I'm saying this only after it ended,
but they were not good at all.
He got disqualified right?
They wanted more expressions.
Kojima did this well.
I did, yes.
And he's totally standing.
What's the matter Tanaka?
We still have the team competition.
Can you give me a hand?
- Seriously!?
- You can't stand up!?
Till the utmost keep moving. Unstoppable moves.
Must see! That man's breakdown!?
Team Gaki lost the first match.
The next match is Housei vs Sagane!
Tell me! Tell me everything!
Even the seconds. The seconds.
Also, say things like "raise your hands", etc.
Yes, yes. We will say.
Listen carefully.
Unstoppable moves, next match!
Start!!
Go lower, go lower!
That's good!
I wanna see the back!
Lower is good!
Hlaf min left.
Use sound as well!
Sagane use the rope as well!
Rope! Rope!
Use the rope!
10 secs left!
Let's use the 3 secs! The 3 secs!
They are not moving at all!
Finish!!
What was that?
That was terrible.
You kept doing only this.
The second half was terrible.
Only the woaahh! In the beginning was good.
The "rocket" in the beginning was good.
Here he goes! I thought, but...
With only the vigor at the beginning.
The rest was a waste of Housei. However.
The score! Go!
Sagane wins.
- I thought you would lose.
- You though he would lose?
I though because he wasn't following
our instructions at all!
Honestly, the second half
was not funny at all!
He won't move.
Senpai!
We still have the team competition.
Give me a hand...
One minute ago he was like "I'm the best!".
So now is the third match! The center fielders!
Gaki team with 2 consecutive losses
have to win now.
Strategy Time
The next who will come out now is...
- We have to seize the opponent..
- My variations are quite powerful..
Wait a sec.
You are bothering us Housei!
- We are making arrangements!
- Go somewhere else!
- Go there!
- Good for nothing...
He accomplished nothing till now.
The third match is Matsumoto vs Uchima.
Can he show the spirit of a regular member?
I definitely don't wanna lose agains Uchima!
I'll go all out.
So keep an eye on my variations!
Because my variations are so sick!! OK?
So! Are you ready?
Unstoppable moves. Main match.
On your mark!
Start!!
Keep it up!
Good! Good! Go! Go!
Good Uchima!
Step in! Step in!
Reach the voice!
Move more, more!
There! We have variation!
We have variation!
Good! This move is good!
It's ok! It's ok!
Voice! The voice!
We got it!
Tanaka was joining together with Matsumoto!
Started with co-acting and finished with co-acting.
Also, what was that?
- Ahh this match we cannot know who won.
- It was a good match.
So let's see how they will judge.
The score..
Please!
Come, come.
Matsumoto wins.
3 votes against 0.
10 points to Team Gaki!
According to our plans right?
What was sometimes that move you did?
That was not moving impression.
You stopped there, didn't you?
It's because on the first time..
..I nailed it.
I nailed on the first time.
That's true.
Wanting to continue the momentum of
Matsumoto's win, Team Gaki..
Forth match Endo vs Shouji.
Well, the relation between Endo and Shouji..
In private too right?
They have this friendly relationship.
But there's a high possibility that
one's moves will cover another.
At this point, I don't know what they are saying..
They are saying something aren't they?
On your mark!
Start!!
We're counting on you!
Go!
Variation! Ohh good!
Good! Good!
He's moving! He's moving!
Nice move!
Very much Endo like.
Good! Good!
Crat a opening!
Once he uses that, he won't stop.
Let's change now!
It's almost 10 secs!
10 secs left!
What is he doing?
Left!
All the same thing!
Finish!!
Wait Endo! Hey!
All the moves were the same.
So let's see the judges.
The score! Please!
Endo wins!
That move made the difference. That diving.
You were amazing!
What's that..
Well it's incredible how they can reconciliate.
- Ah that's true.
- Incredible.
Upcoming, the final match. Hamada vs Nishimura!!
At the moment, both sides still fighting. A tie.
Fighting in the final match Hamada vs Nishimura.
which move is the best...
But you can have anticipations, can't you?
I know, I'm just thinking what kind of move
will make a difference in the points.
- Ah..this is will be..
- Show it to us!
Nishimura also is not that bad.
Looks like he just woke up.
Oh! What is that?
It already started?
You're doing good leader! Keep it up!
So let's begin!
On your marks.
Let's go.
Go leader!
Good!
You can do it! You can do it!
Ouch!
Sorry! Sorry!
Don't relax! Don't relax!
Variation! Variation!
He ran! He ran!
Nishimura ran!
Leader ok!
Good! Good!
This is good! This is good!
Nishimura is not tha bad.
Leader!
This is good!
Let's go!
Good! Good!
Leadger good! Leader good!
Keep up just a little more!
There is no voice! No voice!
Leader, 10 secs!
Leader I love this one! I love this!
5 secs!
That face is the same leader!
Finish!!
- We won! We won!
- Yeah, we won!
That was quite a good match!
- A good final!
- Yeah right!
Nishimura was like a superintendent staff.
This is it.
I feel sick.
So, the score please!
Come!
I feel sick..
Nishimura wins.
Therefore 2 votes agains 1.
10 points to Team Junk!
We won! By a hair's breadth.
What will happen now? Team battle?
- Ah last we have the..
- We can still turn the table.
In the team match...
The winning team, 50 pon..
Point.
50 pon.
We receive 50 pon.