Gaki no tsukai ya arahende!
Let's rendezvous without using your smartphones: Special!!
You're disturbing the neighbors if you talk that loud.
I just announced the name of the segment.
You wanted to brag about how loud you are.
"I can be this loud."
I do this every time.
"And I can take the control."
The rules are simple.
They go to an imagined location based on the theme presented, and if they can meet up with someone there, they can then move on together.
They continue to meet up with more people, and when they are all in the same place, the game is finished.
Let's get this over with!
I always go to the right place.
I'm right.
This game can't be finished if I'm in the right place and you guys don't show up.
The audience will all think that Matsumoto is the only one who is right.
Not really!
This guy is terrible!
- Cocorico is the biggest idiot in the history of Yoshimoto.
- No way!
You are the biggest idiots in Yoshimoto.
- That has a 100 year history, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
Sei Yoshimoto was also saddened by you.
This time, we will challenge this with seven members, including two special guests.
Come on, special guests!
Hi!
First, Alice Hirose.
Where are you from, Hirose-san?
I'm from Shizuoka.
No one here is from Tokyo!
- Are you from Shiga?
- Yes.
- It's the prefecture with the brothel district.
- What the hell!!
Why are you being soo perspicacious?
At least tell me it's a prefecture with Biwa Lake.
- How long are you going to keep talking?
- What the hell!!
Why do I have to be slapped by you?
It's only been 10 seconds since I appeared!!
- You know this segment, don't you?
- Of course!
This segment is about meeting someone or not.
I have been in Tokyo for more than 20 years.
That means next year is the last year of R-1 for you.
R-1!?
Are you going to compete in it?
What do I mean to you?
And if they meet up with the joker, they have to split up.
The joker moves on to see the same theme as them.
Who is the joker?
This person is the joker.
Is it serious?
Oh, really?
She suddenly hit him.
Why did she hit him?
She is hard to get along with.
The joker is Iyo Matsumoto.
Iyo-chan is unpredictable.
You've been in Tokyo for a long time, haven't you, Iyo-san?
I watch this show quite a bit.
Well...I always guess …...pretty well.
What are you talking about?
What is the first theme that will determine their fate?
The first theme is this!
[Big Hospital]
It's in a lot of places.
It's basically big.
It's a matter of what you judge as big.
Iyo-chan, you have to think about it too.
Yeah, I got the general idea.
So fast!
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]
The first theme is Big Hospital.
The game started at 12:10!
I'm glad it wasn't a segment like Strange Town.
That one is tough.
This is a difficult.
I can think of a lot of ideas.
There are a lot of options for this one.
I've been to a lot of big hospitals.
I went to the hospital right after the Moriman Showdown.
I've been to the hospital right after the Gaki recording.
I rarely go to the hospital.
I cure my illness by sleeping.
So I can't think of anything at all.
Where would you like to go?
What would you do?
There are a few common places, but if I go there, I might find Iyo-chan.
The other day, Hosei sang a song of mine.
- Lip Sync Hit Studio?
- Yes.
He was lovely.
Where is the confident Matsumoto going?
After all...
The closest one from here is Juntendo.
He headed for Juntendo Hospital in Ochanomizu.
That place is famous.
I'll go to Juntendo at the end of my life.
I'll think, "I came here for a recording of Gaki a long time ago."
And I'll die.
And Hosei.
I had already thought of a few ideas.
First, I thought of a few hospitals I've been to.
But the one I thought I should go to the most was the one I've never been to.
In other words, I'm not putting my feelings first, I'm being objective.
What hospital is that?
Keio.
- So you would go to Keio?
- Yes, it can only be Keio.
And Hamada.
A while ago, when I caught a cold, I used to go to Kosei Chuo in Ebisu.
I have an image that that place is often used for filming dramas.
That's right.
The entrance there is often used for filming.
Why do they let us use it for filming like that?
Hamada chose Kosei Chuo Hospital, which is often used for filming dramas.
Where would Nishikawa, the guest, choose?
There is a hospital where celebrities often go.
Is it a place with good security?
And it's a hospital that is accustomed to dealing with celebrities.
I think they would come to mind.
I see.
Then I think Sanno Hospital.
- Sanno Hospital?
- Yes.
He headed for Sanno Hospital in Akasaka, where many celebrities go.
I don't think I'll ever meet Tana-yan.
The place Tanaka-san goes is always out of place with the other members.
Yeah, I have watch this segment many times.
He is garbage.
And Tanaka.
Toho...
Toho Hospital?
Where is that located?
it's located in Ikejiri.
- It's Ohashi Hospital.
- Ah, Ohashi Hospital?
There is Seiiku Hospital in Kinuta.
Seiiku Hospital?
There is Tokyo Medical University Hospital in the subcenter of Shinjuku.
Tanaka, who is not good at meeting up, had three hospitals in mind.
I think they know these three.
And where does Alice Hirose, the actress who cures illness with sleep, head?
I think university-affiliated hospitals are big.
***** University Hospital.
There's one called ***** University Hospital.
Let's go there.
- Is it okay?
- Yes.
Are you okay with a decision like that?
Yes, it's fine.
Let's go there.
I can manage if I apologize later.
You can see their destination.
There is a chance to meet up with Endo and Hirose where they are going.
What will happen?
Hosei arrived at the Keio Hospital in Shinanomachi one step ahead of the others.
No one is there now, though.
Well, okay.
Then...
Have you already finished today's class?
Yeah.
- What was your name again?
- You don't know my name?
Remember!
- You appeared in "Don't Laughing."
-  That's right!
What's your name?
Look up my name yourself.
Look, the signal's changed.
What's his name!!?
Stop, I'm embarrassed!
What was Nishikawa doing then?
Thank you.
He was at Sanno Hospital in Akasaka, where famous people go to see him.
First of all, this place is close.
Because there is Hamada-san who wants to finish his work so quickly.
He would not go to such a far place.
There is not enough video taken to broadcast the Downtown DX.
They can't afford the video taken to broadcast that show.
At that time, Hamada arrived at Kosei Chuo Hospital in Meguro.
This place is often used for dramas.
This hospital is often used for dramas.
This hospital is very generous to dramas.
The other members arrived at their destinations one after another.
I never met someone on the first theme.
I hope someone is there.
And...
Time's up.
Where did they go?
They were located on the call.
Hey, you guys, think about it.
We started in Kojimachi.
And the theme is big hospital.
Consider the distance.
For all intents and purposes, you guys should go to Juntendo Hospital.
Juntendo?
Juntendo Hospital?
I'm at Tokyo University Hospital.
Where is that?
- I'm at Tokyo University Hospital.
- Where is that?
See, Alice went to a place we don't understand.
You guys haven't been watching the news lately?
I'm at Nihon University Hospital.
Nihon University Hospital?
If you're in a place like that, you might see former coach Uchida.
Where is Tanaka?
I'm at Tokyo Medical University Hospital in Shinjuku subcenter.
Tokyo Medical University?
Why did you go there?
This place is very famous!
Tanaka, go home now.
Iyo-chan didn't come anywhere?
Where did Iyo-chan go?
Where is the hospital where Iyo Matsumoto, the joker, is headed?
Hello again!
Iyo-chan is here!
But I'm alone, so your coming here is pointless!
No one could meet up with someone at the first theme, "Big Hospital".
No one could meet someone.
We are all idiots.
They did not meet someone, so I would not be offended.
You were not accused of anything by them?
They said, "Where is that?"
They changed their minds and the next theme was announced.
"The first place you go when you come to Tokyo."
What's with this vague theme?
Isn't this different for different generations?
There are so many options.
But I think I'll meet someone on this theme.
The most common is Tokyo Tower.
Now it could be Sky Tree or Asakusa.
By the way, where did you go?
I think...
It was Studio Alta.
But they don't broadcast "Waratte Itomo" anymore.
And where did Matsumoto go?
The orthodox answer is Shinjuku.
Where in Shinjuku, we would say Studio Alta.
It's a bit old.
But I think we can meet.
If no one comes to Studio Alta with this theme, the Japanese entertainment industry is dead.
This is difficult.
This is different for each person.
After much deliberation, where did Hamada choose?
Well, let's go to Tokyo Tower because it's so common.
I'm sure someone will come.
Hamada chose Tokyo Tower.
Downtown cannot meet up at Studio Alta.
Where are the other members destinations?
This theme is an opportunity.
People my age can only think of that place.
This is true.
If I came to Tokyo now, I would want to see Shibuya.
So when I think of meeting people, it would be at the Shibuya *****.
If I think about it simply, it would be there.
Please head to *****.
Where are the places in Tokyo that you wanted to visit, Hirose-san?
Tokyo Tower, Shibuya and Harajuku.
I wanted to see 109 in Shibuya.
But I don't think they will ever come there.
Hey you, are you from Tokyo?
Yes, I'm.
- You are a city girl.
- But I'm from Itabashi Ward in the countryside.
In the real countryside, there are dead raccoon dogs on the side of the road.
There were often dead raccoons hit by cars on the road.
That's insane.
- Where did that happen?
- That's the story of my hometown.
There were often signs saying "Beware of Bears."
The common ones are Omotesando and Takeshita Street in Harajuku.
Oh! I just remembered!
When I asked my nephew where he wanted to go when he came to Tokyo, he answered Takeshita Street.
Nishikawa took his nephew's opinion into consideration and chose Takeshita Street in Harajuku.
A place of memories and a classic tourist spot.
Will they be able to meet up as their thoughts lead them to each other?
Matsumoto is on the move to Studio Alta in Shinjuku.
We came to Tokyo when "Waratteru Baai Desuyo" was on the air.
And we stayed at the Star Hotel near Alta for a week.
We didn't have a week's worth of manzai, so I stayed there and made it up as we went.
But Hamada went somewhere to play.
We bought instant yakisoba noodles at the hotel.
But we forgot to get chopsticks, so we ate it with a comb.
Nishikawa was heading for Takeshita Street in Harajuku.
When I was in the band, I had no money.
But I had to prepare costumes on my own.
I used to go to Takeshita Street clutching 10,000 yen bill and trying to get everything from hats to shoes.
When I think about it, Takeshita Street was the first place they went too.
Did you buy the short pants on Takeshita Street, too?
What the hell.
What are you saying?
Those were made by a very fine stylist.
They are very well designed.
You can make funny jokes like that if you want to edit and use only my footage.
But this time you're using footage of seven people.
Do you know how many minutes of my footage will be used?
Nishikawa's car came near the Shibuya scramble crossing.
Then...
Tana-yan is here!
There he is!
- Whereis he?
- Next to the green train.
See!
What a surprise, Tanaka was there.
See, there he is!
Tana-yan is there!
He is there!
At that time, Tanaka was...
- There's the ZIP staff right there.
- Really?
Oh!
Hi! How are you today?
He had run into the ZIP staffers.
What are you recording?
It's a street interview.
Somehow I'm embarrassed.
Bye-bye, Tana-yan.
I don't want to go over there.
Nishikawa and Tanaka had a near miss.
At that time, Alice Hirose was talking about Downtown in the car.
Why do both Downtown wear sunglasses on the back of their heads?
On the back of their heads?
That's for sure.
I laughed because they do the same thing.
- They both did.
- Yes!
I thought they were kinda cute.
Hamada arrived at Tokyo Tower.
Please! Someone come!
If someone doesn't come here, I'm in trouble!
He waited for five minutes, hoping to meet up with someone.
Come on, someone!
At least come on endo.
This is a common place.
Hamada-san!
I know, right?
Thank goodness!
Hamada and Hirose met up with joy at the Tokyo Tower.
Around that time, Matsumoto arrived at Alta in Shinjuku.
No crowds at all.
If anyone would be waiting here, it would be someone who is not popular.
I'm relieved.
From a distance, I figured there were no stars here.
Because there were no people here at all.
But there you are.
Is it possible that people don't gather here like this?
I was surprised too.
They don't gather at all.
I was over there thinking, "There will never be any celebrities here."
That's enough!!
How many times are you going to say it?
Do you remember?
I thought Downtown would definitely come here.
Downtown used this studio for Gaki.
Yeah, that's right.
After all, Alta is a place of memories for us.
Leaving aside Hosei's unpopularity, they met up at Alta.
He is Tsukitei Hosei.
You wouldn't know what to do if he told you that, would you?
- He is Tsukitei Hosei.
- Hi!
Time's up!
Where are you, Alice-chan?
I'm at Tokyo Tower with Hamada-san.
You are at Tokyo Tower with Hamada?
Yes!
How disgusting!
Where are you, Matsumoto-san?
I'm at Alta in Shinjuku as a matter of course!
Alta?
Thats lame!
Where is Cocorico?
It's Endo.
I'm not at the Tokyo Tower, but at the Sky Tree.
That's too new from my point of view.
Where is Tanaka?
I'm at the scramble crossing in Shibuya.
Are you an idiot?
They're choosing places like a youngster.
Tanaka, really you should go home.
Tanaka, this segment is not for you, so go home.
Please don't say that.
Don't say that.
- Hamada, I'm sad.
- Why?
Downtown started at Alta, right?
I thought so too.
You're gonna leave me for a younger woman?
Two pairs could meet up at "the first place you go when you come to Tokyo."
And where did the Joker go?
Everyone! I have a report!
She came to Takeshita Street in Harajuku, where Nishikawa is.
Did you wait for me?
I have been waiting for you.
Again, the Joker showed up in a place where there was no excitement at all as a show, where there was only one person.
Two and a half hours have passed since the start.
You can see where they are now.
Aim for many successful meetings.
What's the third theme?
[University]
- Hey...
- This is bad.
There are many of these.
I have passed by these many times today.
Come on!
This is another broad theme!!
I came up with a lot, so the important thing is which one I choose.
3, 2, 1...
- Tokyo
- Aoyama Gakuin
There are more than 150 universities in Tokyo.
Which of them would they choose?
Waseda, Keio, Rikkyo, Nihon, Juntendo.
I could only think of Six Universities in Tokyo.
Or Aoyama Gakuin.
A year ago, it would have been Aoyama Gakuin, Tokyo, and Keio.
Nihon is not in there anymore.
- Yeah.
- Now that is no longer in there.
If we did this on TVK, it would be a five-hour special.
What is TVK?
TV Kanagawa, of course!
With all the famous universities that everyone knows listed.
Where will the Hamada and Hirose pair choose?
Tokyo, Keio, Waseda, Aoyama Gakuin...
I have never been to any of them.
- I've been in front of Aoyama Gakuin, though.
- Me too.
Aoyama Gakuin is along Route 246, so it might make a strong impression on people who use cars.
Hey, don't say that.
Alice said Tokyo University first.
Huh?
Why are you surprised?
I thought maybe the young people's opinion would be better.
So what would you do if no one was there?
I would slap you on both cheeks, of course.
They believed in the young people's sense of Hirose and headed for the Tokyo University.
However, they had a touch of anxiety.
Iyo-chan might come.
She will definitely come.
The place Iyo-chan goes to is not bad.
Takeshita Street was not bad either.
I want Iyo-chan to go home.
The meeting rate is 100%.
Iyo Matsumoto, the joker.
Komazawa, Tokyo, Keio.
- Aoyama Gakuin is close.
- Yes.
Aoyama Gakuin, the university of my dreams.
I want her to go home.
Doesn't she have work after this?
I heard she's okay for the whole day.
Damn!
Will the seven of them be able to avoid the joker and meet up?
Let's rendezvous without using your smartphones: Special!!
Two groups could meet up now.
They were all aiming to meet up at the third theme, "University".
The pair of Hamada and Hirose arrived at their destination, the Tokyo University.
Thanks.
My heart is pounding.
It's the Tokyo University that Alice decided to go to.
Please don't say it like that.
Hamada-san!
Hi...who?
I knew it.
They were there.
- I knew it.
- You're nice.
Good.
He probably called out to us because he just found us, but I wish he would have come running when we were waiting over there.
Thanks!
Anyway, Nishikawa met up with the pair of Hamada and Hirose.
Since you guys were going to Tokyo Tower, I was sure you would come here.
- Did you come here for us?
- Of course.
The three of them headed for the red gate of the Tokyo University.
Now I just hope Iyo-chan doesn't come.
Oh, there's someone here!
Who? Hamada and Alice-chan?
And there's Nishikawa-kun too!
Right, this is the only place!
If you guys don't get here, it's over!!
I'm relieved!
You guys are late coming.
They successfully met up with Matsumoto and Housei as well.
Now there are five of them at Tokyo University.
Thank God!
If we don't meet someone here, it will be the end.
I was saying
"Japan must die" here.
The rest were the troublesome Cocorico.
Will they be able to meet up at Tokyo University?
[subbed by RAIDEN1017]
Let's rendezvous without using your smartphones: Special!!
The third theme was "University".
Five of them were able to meet up at the Tokyo University.
The only thing left is the duo of Cocorico.
But they are late.
The usual stuff.
What's going on with Cocorico?
Why are they dragging us down so much?
What kind of ideas do they live with?
What are their jokes like?
Come to think of it, their jokes are not funny at all.
Stop that!
Tana-yan!
I know, right?
It's the only place to be!
Then all that's left is Endo!
If he's heading here from Sky Tree, it'll take him a long time.
If you think about it calmly, this is the only place!
- This is the only place, right?
- Yes, it's!
Sorry, Tanaka.
Before you came I told them that Cocorico's jokes were not funny at all.
Yes, you owe him an apology.
Time's up.
Endo!
Is it serious?
Time's up?
Time's up.
- Endo?
- Yes.
Endo, where are you?
I'm in front of Nihon University.
There you go.
He is at Nihon University.
Why do you like Nihon University so much?
Everyone has joined up except you.
Why are you surprised?
All of you except me?
Tanaka is here too.
Even that Tanaka is here!
Please don't say it that way.
Tanaka who went to Hanayashiki is here too.
I'm here too.
Shozo, do it right next time.
Is this for real?
Sorry, I'm late!
Sorry I'm late.
Is it serious?
- Six of us came here, but Iyo-chan came too.
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6...huh? Only one person didn't come.
Is it serious!?
I really want to scream.
Sorry I'm late.
I feel exactly like screaming.
I want to see the red gate.
- I've never seen it.
- You haven't?
- I can't go there unless it's a good time like this.
- Yes.
Because of the Joker's coming, the six of them have to split up.
This is a dreadful return to the very beginning.
We're splitting up?
This sucks!
Huh? Where's Endo?
Only Endo didn't come.
I'm about to cry.
Hey, I told you guys first!!
I have an appointment at 3:00 PM.
Don't make appointment!
- But I told you guys that.
- What appointment?
Starting from zero.
What is the fourth theme?
This is it.
"Department Stores"?
This is a difficult one.
My gut feeling is that is Mitsukoshi in Ginza.
But my frequency is not in tune with everyone today.
They started to move on, but could not recover from the shock of the split.
This split up is painful.
Come on!
I can't believe this is happening.
Oh crap.
Let's finish while the sky is bright.
This will never end,
unless Iyo-chan gets hit by a motorcycle.
This segment won't be finished until everyone joins the others.
They have to decide where they want to go without being able to get back on track.
Isetan in Shinjuku.
Seibu in Shibuya.
There are many in Ginza.
There is only one that comes to mind for me.
- Only one?
- Yes.
Where is it?
Isetan in Shinjuku.
I think one or two of us might meet up there.
Mitsukoshi.
- Which store?
- In Nihonbashi.
I think old is important.
Yes, Mitsukoshi.
Many choices were raised on this theme.
Hosei chose Mitsukoshi in Nihonbashi and Hirose chose Isetan in Shinjuku.
You and Matsumoto-san have similar places in mind.
Yes.
Come to think of it, I meet him often.
Also, I guess he and I think alike.
- What do you see as the similarities between you and him?
- My wife said me and Matsumoto-san have similar eyes.
- Your face is like his?
- Eyes.
"You have the same eyes as him"
She said I have a keen eye.
What was Hirose doing then?
- I wonder if someone could wait for me first.
- I hope so.
It would be great if someone would wait for me first.
She arrived at Isetan in Shinjuku.
I don't want to be alone!
There he is!
Again?
It's the only place to be, right?
You and I see each other a lot.
Yeah!
I'm so relieved!!
Time's up.
Really!?
Tat was fast.
Time's up
Shozo Endo.
Where are you, Endo?
I'm in front of Mitsukoshi in Ginza.
You're not thinking straight.
Why did you go there and not here?
Where is Tanaka?
I'm at the Mitsukoshi flagship store in Nihonbashi.
I'm with Tanaka!
And Hosei is there too!
Three noble men gathered here!
Nishikawa is at the Takashimaya in Nihonbashi.
This building is registered as a heritage site.
I don't need that kind of information.
The atmosphere is getting a little stiff.
Iyo Matsumoto, the joker, came to Tokyu in Shibuya.
Four hours and twenty minutes had passed since the start.
The key to meet up is held by Nishikawa, who is all alone, and the clunky Endo, who hasn't been able to meet up with someone today.
Those who are alone now, please think about it.
That's right.
I'm not good.
I haven't met someone today.
They want to get this finished soon.
What's the fifth theme?
[Golf Practice Range]
- I have no idea.
This is the worst.
None of us play golf.
Right.
What did Hamada, who loves golf, do?
I immediately thought of a place.
Jingu Gaien.
That's near Jingu Stadium.
Hamada chose Jingu Golf Range with overwhelming confidence.
Please think about where Hamada-san is going.
That is the answer.
I think Hamada will avoid places he goes.
- Is that because he is thinking about the future?
- Yes, that's right.
Then I have no idea.
Suppose the driving range he goes to is broadcast on TV.
Then he would not be able to go there with his mistress.
You right.
- Does he go there with his mistress?
- Yes, he does.
He lectures his mistress, "Hold it like this."
So he doesn't go where he usually goes.
Endo used to go to a driving range in Kasai.
- No way.
- If you go to Kasai, it's the end of the road.
The cab fare will bankrupt TV station.
There are only two places mentioned, Jingu Gaien and Kasai.
This is a big chance for all of them to meet up.
The pair of Hamada and Hirose headed for Jingu Gaien.
Iyo-chan seems to be going to Himonya.
She might say, "I've been here with my husband."
But what if she comes to Jingu Gaien?
If that happens, I want you to slap me on both cheeks.
-It's important what Matsumoto-san, Hosei-san, and Tanaka-san think.
- Yes, it will be up to Yama-chan.
He once went to the tennis court at Jingu Gaien.
He had been to Jingu Gaien last February when the theme was tennis courts.
At that time, he must have seen the adjacent golf range.
He may or may not say that there is a golf range in Jingu Gaien.
What were the three of them doing then?
Matsumoto-san, why do you think Alice-chan and Hamada-san meet so often?
That guy has the power to attract females.
Females don't like that guy, though.
So you mean he chases women's butts?
Yes, he has the ability to chase women's butts.
He's like a anglerfish.
He's always emitting some kind of chakra, and he's always lighting up young women with it.
They were having a lot of fun talking trash about Hamada.
If this keeps up, Alice-chan will be in danger!
She would say to her manager after work today.
"He's too creepy!!"
Is he doing something behind our backs?
"Why does Hamada keep coming to where I'm!?"
"Me and Hamada are supposed to have totally different ways of thinking!"
Hamada and Hirose arrived at Jingu Golf Club one step ahead of the others.
This is where they should come.
We will have to wait for a while.
If they head here from Ginza or Nihonbashi, it will take another 5 or 10 minutes.
Only if they come here.
"Only if they come here"?
- You just don't know when to shut up.
- Yeah.
They come here.
It had already been four and a half hours since the start.
I can't imagine a situation where seven of us are gathered and Iyo-chan doesn't come.
I never go to the golf range in the first place.
If it doesn't work next time, I will quit being a comedian.
Their thoughts were mixed.
What will happen?
Hamada and Hirose were waiting for their comrades to arrive at the Jingu golf club.
They were there!
- Yeah!
- Thank goodness!!
I only knew this place.
And I jog around here, so I knew this place.
- Great.
- I'm  relieved.
Endo definitely needs to come here.
What if he goes to Kasai?
I don't think so.
But he's the guy to go there, though.
Yes!
Nishikawa has met up with them safely, but...
It would be tough if we couldn't meet at this time.
That would be tough.
I hope some more guys will come here.
No one came after Nishikawa.
I don't feel like someone is coming here.
- I was bitten by a mosquito.
- Really?
Are there mosquitoes already?
In this season, they would already be there.
- Is it 5 o'clock?
- I have to go home.
If I were Yujiro, I would have left already.
They waited for 10 minutes.
What?
Isn't that them?
Someone is coming this way on foot.
It's Matsumoto, Yama-chan and Tanaka!
Amazing!
Who's that?
Where's Endo?
Endo's not here!
But it was good.
How did you know about this place?
Hosei-san chose this place.
- He's been here before, apparently on this tennis court.
- That's right!
- It happened just like you said!
I was just talking about that.
Perfect!
Only Endo is left.
The rest is Tanaka's buddie.
He's the problem today, not you.
Yes, it's hard to meet with endo.
I can't remember what Endo-san was wearing today.
I don't remember that.
I can't even remember if he had a single eyelid or double eyelids.
Will Endo really show up?
We have been waiting for him for quite a long time.
There he is!
Now all seven of them have successfully met up at the Jingu golf club.
If the joker is somewhere else, it's clear.
So that means!
Hi!
Are you Iyo-chan, the joker?
Yes, I'm.
Where is Iyo-chan now?
I'm at Himonya Swing.
She is in Himonya!!
All seven of us are at Jingu Golf Range!
- Thank goodness!
- That was close!
I'm usually at Himonya with Hiromi-san (husband).
I have a member card of Himonya Swing.
I met Sanma-san by chance.
Oh, you met Sanma-san?
Huh?
Oh, Sanma-san!
What are you doing?
Welcome!
It's a miracle!
What the hell is that you're wearing?
I'm playing the joker and they're not good to see me.
So I'm not good?
Sanma-san, you're out!
I'm off then.
- You met him at Himonya?
- Apparently, Sanma-san also goes there.
Why do you look so disappointed!?
No, no, no.
If all of us had gone to Himonya, it would have been great.
Don't say that!
[subbed by RAIDEN1017]