Ignore this line
0 0 m -298 -66.5 b -308.625 -68 -337.5 -66.5 -334.5 -42.5 b -336 -29 -307.125 -1.875 -299.5 -0.5 b -287.375 7.375 -282.875 -1.875 -275.25 -3.375 b -266.125 -12.5 -257 -15.5 -247.875 -38 b -244.875 -59.125 -264.625 -60.625 -266.125 -61.875 b -278.25 -68 -288.875 -66.5 -298 -66.5 m -290.375 -59.125 b -276.75 -61.875 -258.5 -53 -261.625 -44 b -272.25 -55.875 -281.25 -55.875 -290.375 -59.125 m -367.875 -190.875 b -361.75 -190.875 -310.125 -180.625 -317.75 -111.5 b -328.375 -68 -357.25 -46.875 -366.375 -42.5 b -370.875 -40.875 -395.25 -21.375 -428.625 -53 b -436.25 -68 -451.375 -84.375 -440.75 -121.875 b -436.25 -136.875 -428.625 -165.5 -401.25 -181.875 b -393.75 -186.5 -381.5 -194.125 -367.875 -190.875 m -231.25 -194.125 b -228.125 -194.125 -191.75 -204.375 -159.75 -149 b -155.25 -135.5 -143.125 -119 -150.75 -77 b -159.75 -42.5 -175 -40.875 -184.125 -38 b -191.75 -38 -202.375 -29 -238.75 -54.375 b -250.875 -65 -269.125 -70.875 -276.75 -113.125 b -275.25 -113.125 -293.5 -139.875 -255.5 -181.875 b -247.875 -188 -240.25 -194.125 -231.25 -194.125 m -370.875 -144.5 b -413.5 -136.875 -389.125 -90.5 -369.375 -95 b -363.375 -95 -349.625 -98 -346.625 -119 b -351.125 -142.875 -360.25 -141.375 -370.875 -144.5 m -370.875 -131 b -361.75 -134 -357.25 -121.875 -358.75 -119 b -358.75 -106.875 -367.875 -106.875 -372.375 -106.875 b -378.5 -108.375 -381.5 -114.375 -380 -121.875 b -380 -124.875 -377 -131 -370.875 -131 m -367.875 -124.875 b -372.375 -123.375 -370.875 -117.5 -367.875 -117.5 b -364.875 -117.5 -361.75 -123.375 -367.875 -124.875 m -220.5 -144.5 b -254 -138.375 -238.75 -91.75 -220.5 -96.5 b -214.5 -95 -199.25 -98 -199.25 -124.875 b -203.875 -142.875 -216 -144.5 -220.5 -144.5 m -220.5 -131 b -200.875 -131 -206.875 -106.875 -217.5 -106.875 b -220.5 -105.5 -232.75 -108.375 -229.625 -121.875 b -229.625 -124.875 -228.125 -131 -220.5 -131 m -217.5 -124.875 b -222.125 -121.875 -219 -115.875 -216 -117.5 b -211.5 -119 -214.5 -124.875 -217.5 -124.875 m -374 -117.5 b -377 -117.5 -375.5 -113.125 -374 -113.125 b -372.375 -113.125 -370.875 -117.5 -374 -117.5 m -222.125 -115.875 b -225.125 -115.875 -223.625 -111.5 -222.125 -111.5 b -220.5 -111.5 -219 -115.875 -222.125 -115.875 m -451.375 -218 l -141.625 -218 l -141.625 86.875 l -451.375 86.875 m -144.625 -215 l -448.375 -215 l -448.375 84 l -144.625 84
TPF
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!! Chiki Chiki, bet your life on this one bite
100,000 yen prize! Kiki Fish Sausage!!
Number 33!
33rd, right?
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Yes, this is the 33rd installment
Last episode was Castella
It's been 7 years for Matsumoto-san
Tsukitei Hosei
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
1 year since correct
7 years since correct
Last episode  Kiki Castella
Ma
Tan
7 years!?
and it's been 1 year for Tanaka
Yes, I was correct
7 years!
More importantly, I was really excited about the fact that we have the chance to win real money
Oh right, you can win money
Yes, I received money
Well, they truly did do &#%!@?!
How nice
What an antiquated way to say it, &#%!@?!
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents
33rd installment: Kiki Fish Sausage!!
GakiFanSub
James
(Team Gaki)
Lei
Otviss
Proofreader:
Translator:
Typesetter:
Will the 100,000 yen prize be claimed?!
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Fish Sausage
Kiki Series #33
Kiki's 33rd installment is a treat that is super popular among children: fish sausage!
Out of 12 sausages, they will identify the
one they ate while they were blindfolded
"Kiki Fish Sausage"
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
If correct,  100,000 yen prize
If incorrect,  harsh punishment
If they're correct, they will receive 100,000 yen! If they're wrong, they will receive harsh punishment!
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Well, with that, let's get right into it
Who shall we start with?
Usually it's me though
Yeah, first up
First up is Endo
His challenge is leading processed food supplier Marudai Food's Fish Sausage
(Marudai Food Co.)
Endo's Challenge
Fish Sausage
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
This is so stiff
How is it?
The texture is firm
You've put a lot of different things in your mouth, right?
Lots of things in your mouth
Out of everyone in Yoshimoto*, you've put the most things in your mouth
Translator's note: Yoshimoto is their production company
If you chew it like that, it feels more stiff
His tongue's surface is the dirtiest in all of Yoshimoto
They're saying you've licked some dirty things
Correct Answer
Fish Sausage
(Marudai Food Co.)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
It didn't seem like it was very high-end
Well it is a fish sausage after all, so
Well, I'm going to try this "Glico Ham Gun-Gun Sausage"
Ahh Glico
Currently Tasting
Gun-Gun Sausage
(Glico Ham)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
"A long selling item with a history of over 50 years..."
Long selling item with a history of over 50 years
About the product on the table
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Not just a kid's snack, it can also be paired with alcohol
"It's not just a kids snack, it can also be paired with alcohol"
By reading it
Correct Answer
Fish Sausage
(Marudai Food Co.)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
he's trying to create appeal
You've exposed him
He can't use it
How uncool
This is completely wrong
It's always like this
It feels like it softly expands in my mouth
He does say it often
It's always "I know
that I'm correct" that is what he's saying
I think I know this, though
Oh the aftertaste is completely different too, this one really comes at me
it's the same
The one I ate was NOT Gun-Gun Sausage
every time the same comment
*He is disposing an empty bag
Unexpectedly not too hard
You sure? It's dangerous if you go through it like that
No, it was surprisingly different
Totally different?
White shrimp sausage...
He's eventually going to forget, since he doesn't know which it is
Currently Tasting
White Shrimp Sausage
(Nakajima Group)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Oh wow, this is completely different
He's desperately thinking "I need to be on screen"
Seriously
When you're right
you're supposed to quickly move on
Can we make the display low quality?
Only when Endo is onscreen
Can we switch the low quality display
at the Tokyo Tower?
Especially for him!
That's rather amazing!
In this high-tech world, we'd revert to analog TV!
Oh, this is so delicious
There's white shrimp in it... Oh but the flavor is very different
It sounds like he's saying "white snake"*
*translator's note: shrimp is "ebi"; snake is "hebi"
Hard to hear
So difficult to hear
The one I ate was NOT White Shrimp Sausage
He's being harshly criticized
He usually doesn't have that sort of character
They're really bad, yeah
(Junior)
If I was the kouhai,
I would definitely be bullied
"You, what the hell!?"
"What the hell kind of response is that?"
Reject, reject everything
What are you going on about..?
You guys can keep that to yourselves
BIG Arabiki
(Maruzen)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Currently Tasting
After that, Endo sucessfully cleared 2 rounds
Too Thick Sausage
(Toyo Suisan)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
4 cleared
Out of 12
He's not going to stall here
Maybe it's about time I go for my target
You've had a target?
Yes, my target is this "Homo Sausage"
Currently Tasting
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
LET'S GO, this homo sausage
For 60 years, right?
Whaaat?
No, it wasn't this stiff
Ahhh, but then
It has the same
"Whoa I'm eating a fish meat sausage" sort of sense I got up there
Ah yeah, you were saying that
But it really wasn't this stiff
Maybe I'll go ahead anyway
maybe I'll take the chance
Oh, that's what you meant
Yes
It's been 60 years (since its announcement), so as a long selling...
When you say 60 years, that's really amazing
about as long as Ke-shi-
Japanese actor
Ke-shi- Takamine*
longer than that
The sausage's history is as long as Ke-shi- Takamine's career
I might do it anyway
I've seen this before too...
I ate it right here, too
Here goes
Ahh, I'm begging you please
The one I ate WAS Maruzen Homo Sausage
Of course not!
You can't fail as the first challenger!
Ahh it's so difficult...
Ah ah he's here he's here
SHALL I TRAIN YOUR BRAIN TOO?
What?
I might not want this
That was very strict, too
This- ah- this is very strict
Well you were first up so it couldnt've been helped
It was dried out, so it was a bit stiff
The humidity is high today
Yes
so I don't know what could have dried it out
Is it dried out?
Are you going to use this footage of me getting scolded?
That's all we're going to use!
Tanaka's challenge Maruha Nichiro's easy on the body, DHA Included Risala Sausage
(Maruha Nichiro)
DHA Included Risala Sausage
Tanaka's Challenge
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
The answer is already there
You can't do that to your senpai
Yeah, you can't do that
Hamada is so annoying
Hamada from Downtown
I'm going to eat it all in one go
Well you're allowed to eat it however you want
Yeah
Oh yeah
It has a good amount of stickiness
Cough
Right now
Hamada is coughing so be quiet
Tanaka has to be quiet
What about you guys be quiet?
Hamada-san is currently in the process of coughing
Correct Answer
DHA Included
Risala Sausage
(Maruha NIchiro)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Is it alright if I start off
with something that's totally different?
You'll gauge it from the difference
Yes, I'll see what I'm dealing with
I want to try Arabiki
BIG Arabiki
(Maruzen)
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
I'll try it
Yes, Arabiki
Nope, wrong
And one is enough?
Yes, one is enough
The one I ate was NOT BIG Arabiki Sausage
Well, if you had gotten it wrong there that would have been...
But you purposely tried the one that was the most different, right?
So you'll get closer now?
Yes, with this I will get closer to it
I'll narrow it down
Yeah, that's right. That's how you get it right.
We didn't ask him
Let's move on!
Glico Ham Gun-Gun Sausage
Currently Tasting
Gun-Gun Sausage
(Glico Ham)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Clearly it has a different vibe from the one I tried
Smell?
More #&%$^
What did you say?
WHAT IS IT?
It came to me stronger
You're not making sense
Are you serious?
I felt like it came stronger
Oh that's it? I had NO idea
NO idea
That's what he wanted to say
It's close, it's actually very close
but the stiffness is different
the flavor is also different
No, this is aimed for children
The one I ate was NOT Gun-Gun Sausage
Well, this is
Fish Sausage
Fish's Sausage
Homo Sausage
Marudai Food Co.
Maruzen
Nissui
After this he piles up his victories and successfully clear 3 rounds!
5 cleared
Out of 12
Correct Answer
DHA Included
Risala Sausage
(Maruha NIchiro)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
You did it
You've passed it
Alright, keep going!
Alright, I will continue
Go go!
Currently Tasting
DHA Included
Risala Sausage
(Maruha Nichiro)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
DHA Included Risala Sausage
Currently Tasting
DHA Included
Risala Sausage
(Maruha Nichiro)
Currently Tasting
DHA Included
Risala Sausage
(Maruha Nichiro)
What does "DHA included" mean?
Currently Tasting
DHA Included
Risala Sausage
(Maruha Nichiro)
DHA...
He is very focused
No, the flavor was stronger
That was dangerous, just now
His articulation today is more...
The one I ate was NOT DHA Included Risala Sausage
Such a shitty presentation!
What a shitty ending!
You had no clue!
The shittiest ending!
Everything you say is a lie
He didn't know at all, right?
Yes
STUDY YOUR FISH FROM THE VERY START!
Shitty
He's the one who said shitty
He's a very formal one
He's very formal
So shitty
Hamada's challenge is the very thick,
(Toyo Suisan)
Hamada's Challenge
Too Thick Sausage
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Toyo Suisan's Too Thick Sausage
He's trying to feel it from many different places
It's not...
He's really sniffing it
Just look at that, how disgusting
So grotesque
Is it "guro"?
"Guro"
Grotesque...
You good?
Yes, it has a sense of "yes, this is a sausage"
Now, I don't want to take too much time
That will help you win, right
These over here have something in them, right?
Fish meat and
white shrimp, and tuna
WHAT!?
If you take out the fish meat, then there's nothing left
We're doing fish meat, you know
He should remain faithful to the title
HE WANTS TO TAKE OUT THE FISH MEAT
NOTHING WILL BE LEFT~
Shut up!
Of course I'll get noisy about it
This is our "tsukkomi". that is what is said, so
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Correct Answer
Too Thick Sausage
(Toyo Suisan)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
That's at the top
He's a "boke", completely
This is definitely "boke" stuff
I'm going to try this one now
Currently Tasting
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Was it this soft?
This has a very light flavor
The one I had was more like, "sausaaage"
Yes but that one is very...
It must be the oldest one here
It is the same as Ke-shi-
Ke-shi- Takamine
It's wrong
Sausage Takamine
The one I ate was NOT Maruzen Homo Sausage
*He is disposing an empty bag
He has the most stars on his chest
Hamada's getting them right
He has 6 stars
He's sleeping around
and it could be with anybody
I HEARD THE RUMOR
With anybody!?
Currently Tasting
DHA Included
Risala Sausage
(Maruha Nichiro)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Yes, with anybody
His pants' zippers are very loose
from what I've heard
"Guro" it's "guro"
If we're talking about the aftertaste, this is very close
No, I'm telling you this is super close
So that means you'll choose that one?
Well I've already eaten it, so I'm wondering which to choose
but the thing is, this was the one that went to Tanaka;
would the same one be used for me?
What happened? What's wrong?
In front of the phone
He's thinking about making a call*
Translator's note: Kakeru (the word they're using) means to risk and to make a call
If you risk it once,
then you have to go all in
Yes
You're right
Oh, he's holding the receiver
Is he going to call?
Here he goes
It's better to call
Ah whatever
I'm gonna do it anyway
it's no use to ponder it
it was so bland
this is the one
The one I ate WAS DHA Included Risala Sausage
No, that's no good
He really put it all on the line
He put it all out
Freeze his face please
I'm scared of this, though
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO BE FAMILIAR WITH KIDS' FOOD!?
Ahh, how scary
Which was it?
It was this "Too Thick Sausage"
Please, try it
No, it's wrong
Whaaat!?
Please decrease the amount of options
Decrease it!
A decreasing rule!
DECREASE IT!
He's calling for a decreasing rule!
The Kiki Fish Sausage has proven to be a struggle for everyone,
(Maruzen)
Homo Sausage
Hosei's Challenge
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Hosei's challenge is Maruzen's Homo Sausage
This is properly cut into a square, right?
Yes, they're diced
Huh?
It's so average!
Softness, average!
Smell, average!
And then, when I
grate it against my teeth,
the smell from the part that was split open!
It has one a scent mhm
What a solidly failed attempt to make us laugh
I mean, I liked it, so
Even though anybody else would say that's wrong
The public, right?
Correct Answer
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
One thing I can say is that,
the surface was very smooth
of the one I ate
Aren't they all like that?
That one is so rough, there are rough ones
You won't know unless you test with your tongue
Ah but wait a minute,
what should I choose with-
I'll base it off of the saltiness
alright
I'm ready to go! I will try Homo Sausage!
Currently Tasting
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Currently Tasting
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
Currently Tasting
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
Currently Tasting
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
I'm ready to go! I will try Homo Sausage!
Currently Tasting
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Currently Tasting
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
Currently Tasting
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
Currently Tasting
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
Oh, this is completely different
the smell is completely different
the hardness is also completely different
this one is not a problem
The one I ate was NOT Maruzen's Homo Sausage!
SO SHITTY!
No more of this!
Nobody will get it right!
There's no chance of getting it right!
You got it on the first try!
I was really struggling not to laugh
It was RIGHT AFTER you ate it
You're kidding right!?
It was so bad,
he was SO CLOSE and then he decided, "Nope, it's totally different"
What the hell!?
EVEN THOUGH YOU CHANGED YOUR NAME, YOU ARE STILL UNSUCCESSFUL
I didn't understand a thing
What did he even say
I have no idea of what he just said
NO idea
You already know, it was the Homo Sausage
Seriously
I had no idea!
Cut down the number!
I had NO idea!
Matsumoto's challenge is
the one that made Hosei eat his tears after one try: Maruzen's Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
Homo Sausage
Matsumoto's Challenge
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
I'VE GOT IT!
I KNOW!
I'VE DISCOVERED A NEW TECHNIQUE TO FIND OUT
This is what I'll do
No biting
No tasting
I'M GOING TO SWALLOW IT WHOLE!
All of it!?
Of course that would happen
It got stuck in your throat
Well the pieces are big, so
You're an idiot
Ah, it came out
He actually tasted it firmly and the results!?
Actually, Matsumoto firmly tasted it. What are the results!?
Correct Answer
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
I'm going to perform a miracle!
Make it happen!
Please do
I know that it's very very difficult to perform miracles though
Too Thick Sausage
Currently Tasting
(Toyo Suisan)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Shappuri Agemasu*
*"Shappuri Agemasu" doesn't actually mean anything, but it resembles a meaning of "I'm confident"
It's very clear, his voice
Your voice is loud and clear, really
Until Shappuri Age, 10 seconds!!
HURRY UP!!
Just eat it already!
He's really on fire
I KNOW this is different!
Surprisingly
If this is wrong
I'm seriously going to quit this program
You don't have to quit over that...
The one I ate was NOT Maruzen's Too Thick Sausage
I knew it was definitely not it
**He's throwing away an empty bag**
Your heart was surely pounding
You were so nervous!
There was the possibility that I was wrong!!
Even though I knew it was definitely wrong...
What about these..?
Got it, I'll go with this
SHAPPURI AGEMA~SU!!
Currently Tasting
Tuna Sausage
(Fujimitsu)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
It would be nice if his voice flew away
Has it flown away before?
No, no, it doesn't fly, but it'd be nice
No.
No...
It's so close...
No!
This is no time to doubt!
Nope! Wrong!
What I ate was NOT Tuna Sausage!
White Shrimp Sausage
(Nakajima Group)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Currently Tasting
Correct Answer
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
The very lucky Matsumoto successfully clears 4 rounds!
Original Fish Sausage
(Seinan Kaihatsu)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
SHAPPURI AGEMASU!
Fish Sausage
(Daiei)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Daiei's Fish Sausage
SHAPPURI AGEMASU!!!
Gun-Gun Sausage
(Glico Ham)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Glico's Gun-Gun Sausage
Shappuri Agema~su
He's getting softer
And then, the last half...
6 cleared
Out of 12
Isn't this amazing?
Only 6 more half of them
From this point, I just have to keep going
This is it, I'm going to go from here
Currently Tasting
Fish Sausage
(Marudai Food Co.)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Watch this! My lifestyle!
MARUDAI FOOD FISH SAUSAGE
SHAPPURI AGEMASU!!
Very nice
It is nice
It's compelling
Genius
Incredible, it's very compelling
Wrong
It's completely wrong
The one I ate was NOT Fish Sausage!
SEE!!
Well I guess I'm gonna go in order now
Alright, got it
I'll go with this one
Nissui Fish Sausage
Currently Tasting
Fish's Sausage
(Nissui)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
FISH'S SAUSAGE
SHAPPURI AGEMA~SU
This is wrong, right?
I wanted to hear the one from earlier
I don't know
After that, he safely clears his 8th sausage
Remaining 4
There are only 4 remaining...
This is it, this is where I will show you the difference between my level and yours
I feel like I've eaten this one before, and this one, ahhh
so I should probably try the ones between
BIG Arabiki
(Maruzen)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Currently Tasting
He successfully takes out his targets, Matsumoto who has no doubts!
Fish Sausage
(Maruha Nichiro)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
FISH SAUSAGE, SHAPPURI AGEMA~SU!!
And finally, he has two left!
10 cleared
Out of 12
Remaining 2
Wow, it's out
He's here
Will he choose the right one!?
He's Michael Jackson
Correct Answer
Homo Sausage
(Maruzen)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
Remaining 2
This means I have to go up there now, right?
Yes, that's right
So, which one is it?
I'm more nervous than I was for my wedding...
Currently Tasting
DHA Included
Risala Sausage
(Maruha Nichiro)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 24.25 15 l 24.25 0
This really makes you nervous...
DHA INCLUDED RISALA SAUSAGE
RISALA SAUSAGE
SHAPPURI AGEMASU!!
PLEASE DO!
This is incredible...
I think it's this one
No, I don't have a doubt anymore
Risala...
HERE I GO!
THE ONE THAT I ATE WAAAAAS
RISAAAAALAAA!!!
YOU'RE KIDDING!!
This video was brought to you by tofu panda fansubs
Poor thing!
This one should be okay!!
Poor Captain!
I am too pitiable!!
Alright, go ahead
I will crush you like fish meat
That was long
Captain
Captain!
Captain, good work