June 10, 2001
Gaki No Tsukai Backstage
Is there something you want to ask him?
Golf. Whether he wants to play.
You're going to play?
Yeah.
How are you?
Hello.
Oh, hello.
I'm fine.  Hold on a second.
Everyone's fine?
We're doing fine, but I mean, we're just doing normally.
Well, well.
It's this again.
What is?
What do you mean "What is?"  Look at what you're wearing, it's obvious what it is.
Seriously? Wow, you saw right through me.
We can tell.  It can be only be that, right?
What do you mean "You saw right through me," come on.
I thought you wouldn't be able to tell.
We can tell.
We can tell this much.
Seriously?
Yes.
What is this?  Why do you look so annoyed?
Because the same thing will happen.
Right?
What?
Because even if we work hard, in the end because that person doesn't work hard
Don't say such a thing.
Ow! Ow!  Ow! Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
No, you said too much there.
That wasn't saying too much.
Don't say the truth so loudly.
I'm saying it because it's the truth.
Come on, as long as we can put him in a good mood, that's good enough.
No, the thing is, and I'm being honest here
If he gets in a good mood then that's fine, but he always gets angry when we're done.
That's true.  That bothers me, too.
Afterwards, right?
What is that, where he leaves right in the middle of things?
Right, right.
He goes into the dressing room and doesn't come out, right? Is he %$#@?
The dream that Matsumoto envisioned this time is!?
The dream that Matsumoto envisioned this time is
Baseball
Baseball.
Like the Japanese players in the Major League, make a beautiful hit against a super fast pitch!!
Like the Japanese players who crossed the ocean to play in the Major League,
make a beautiful hit against a super fast pitch.
The pitches are really fast in the Major League, right, Suga? How fast are they, in the Major League?
About 150 km/h.
Right, right.
He wants to hit a 150 km/h pitch.
No, come on.
That, since I played baseball,
I can tell you, honestly, that's impossible.
But he says he wants to hit a 150.
This is impossible.
Oh my god!
Whoa, geez.
What was that, all of a sudden?
He wants to hit a 150.
I'm on board. I'll do it.  Yes.
Thank you.
I'll do it.
Yeah?
Yes, no problem.
Then yeah, well...
After seeing that?
What? What's your problem?
Like, "Then yeah, well..."
No, I want to do it. Instead.
Please don't do anything.
Ok,
*A kuroko is a traditional Japanese theatre stagehand.  Kurokos wear all black to signify to the theatre audience that they are supposed to be invisible and not part of the onstage action.
The four become kurokos* again to make Matsumoto's dream come true.
Can they create a miracle?
Hitting a 150 km/h pitch!!
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi - Hitting a 150 km/h pitch.
In any case, let's see what the pitch looks like.
Yes.
We're the ones who are actually going to have to do this, anyway.
That's true.
That's true, in the end.
Then, could you please?
Please, thank you.
That is fast.
Ok.
Got it.
Oh, he's coming.
So slow. Right?
He shows less and less effort each time.
Well, he said he'd do it, so it should be fine.
Yes.
He intends to put in effort?
Hey, we're ready.
Hello.
See, he's wearing a uniform.
Yes, right.
That's right.
He's showing effort.
So you'll do it?
Yeah, no problem. We also checked the pitch.
In the past, right? We've done a lot of different things.
Um, looking back, honestly,
They might have been a bit difficult, so I do feel sorry about that.
I see.
But for this time around,
in terms of the difficulty,
I think this is an easy one.
So I want to do this in one shot.
I'd like
to do this with dignity.
Yes, yes.
The only thing you guys are capable of is to support me or so.
Don't be thinking about %$#@ all the time.
Then, let's give it a shot.
Yes.  Let's do it.
Let's go!
Ok.
Let's do it.
Yes.
If we can, in one shot.  If we can do it in one shot, you know?
Here we go.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa.
Watch out.
He suddenly... whoa.
Why are you completely limp? What the hell!
Didn't you just put on your batting shoes by yourself?
Stop it.
Tanaka.
Hold this, ok?
Ok, ok.
Ok.
Stand him up.
Yes.
Stand him up properly.
He won't stand at all.
Come on.
He's limp.
He's completely– geez, he's completely limp.
Argh, come on.
Argh, geez.
Hold on.
Whoa, whoa, come on.
Hey!
Stand him up.
He won't put anything into his muscles.
Stand up, at least, you know?
Here we go.
Ready and go.
Ow.
Whoa, watch out. Are you ok?
Hamada.
There it is.
I don't understand this situation.
Here we go.
Let's just go with this.
We're ready.
Ok then.
Here it comes.
Let's hit this.
Let's hit it.
Ok. Here it is.
Let's hit a 150. Here it comes.
Once more.  Let's go once more.
Whoa, whoa.
Yes.
We're hitting a 150.
Ready and
Now!
Let's put him down.
Right, let's...
It's kind of tough like this.
Let's go to the next one.
Don't cut his fingers.
Yes.
Make him hold it, in any case.
Here we go.
Ok, this is done.
Like this.  The angle is good.
His wrist got red.
You're right.
That can't be helped, though.
Ok.
Yes, that can't be helped.
Sit him on a swivel chair and hit with a long bat
It's secured, right?
Ok.
Here we go.
Like I said, I don't understand this situation.
Ok, here we go.
Ok.  Sit down, sit down.
Ok, this way, this way.
Argh, geez... geez.
Just pick him up all the way.
He's watching, he's watching.
He's watching this way. Hurry up.
Oh, yeah.
It's really heavy.
He's watching, right?
OK!
He's really staring.
Don't meet his eyes.
That's bad, right? Wow, he's really staring.
We're good.
Ok, ok.
Should we go ahead?  We're also...
I really think this will work.
You think so?
Let's get a hit.
The pitch, please.
Here it comes.
That was close.
That was close. Let's go again?
Let's go again.
That was close.
It doesn't work.
It doesn't work.  Doesn't work.
It's so long, you'd think it'd work, right? But in the first pitch...
It was like a foul tip the first time.
It was like a foul tip, right?
Yes?
Matsumoto gets angry and leaves
Can he walk with that?
Why is he angry?
He was angry, right?
Yes, he is angry.
His face looked angry.
He was glaring at you, right?
He glared at me.  Why?
Let's see him.
The group go to Matsumoto's dressing room to apologize
So he got angry again.
I know, right?
Come on, we don't know if he's angry until we see him.
Well, yes, that's true.
And you're already saying he's angry at us.  (??????????????_
Yes.
Excuse us.
...climbed, and ate one.
Yeah, this persimmon tastes good.
Matsumoto was telling a bedtime story to a child
Please pick one for me, too, Mr. Monkey.*
*Note: Matsumoto is reading The Crab and the Monkey, a Japanese folktale.
Who's kid is this?
I don't know.
He's playing a grandpa.
The monkey...
What?
Among the things we did, we almost succeeded with the second one we did, so...
Among the things we did, we almost succeeded with the second one we did, so..
What part of that can you call a success?
Well, it sort of
A foul tip.
Yes, of a 150 km/h pitch.
Let me tell you, I had that thing taken off and peeled off and taken off and peeled off. (?????????????????????????????))__
My hand stings.
And I was cut by the box cutter by you.
I'm sorry.
What do you think this is?
Huh?
Think over what you've been doing.
If I were to make an analogy of this,
..., seriously.
I want to hit a 150 km/h.
The next one will be all right.
I'm sorry.
You piss me off, especially.
Huh?
You.
Me?
Being lazy and all.
I'll tell him.  Don't worry.
I'm sorry.
Let's go. We'll be waiting.
Good night.
I'm sorry.
Matsumoto's 2nd Attempt!!
Matsumoto renews his focus for his second attempt.
Let's do the next one.
We have that, right? A new one? The one without duct tape?
We're ready.  It doesn't hurt as much.
Oh. He's showing more effort.
Oh. He's showing a little effort.
He's running over here.
I heard from the staff. The box cutter was actually extended, it seems.
I heard from the staff. The box cutter was actually extended, it seems.  (?????????????????????)
The razor.
That's not true, right?
Really?
Of course not. Why in the world would I do that?
That's true.
I want to hit a 150 km/h pitch, all right?
Yes.
I don't want my hand cut with duct tape.
It's clear what I want done to me and what I want to do, it's clear, also what I don't want, it's clear, right?
Yeah, that's true.
You get it?
Yes.
All of you.
Yes. We'll give it our best.
We'll give it our best.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Ok.
Ok, please hold this.
This, it'll fly away, so...
Pop a huge balloon and hit the ball with the falling bat
Make sure, before it flies away.
Let's hit a 150.
He's watching Hamada.  Hurry.
Why am I standing here?  (??????????????????)
I'm going to tie these together.
So it's like this.
Ok.
Yes, it's standing up on its own.
It's good, it's good.
The pitch, please.
Please.
It's gonna work. It's gonna work.
If this doesn't work, then this just isn't doable.
That should've worked, right?
It was definitely a good idea.
Let's go to the next one. Let's not pause at all and just go to the next one.
This one is good.
Yamazaki, no, no.
Yamazaki, you have to stand him up.
First, first we have to put him on top.
We have to put him in that.
Here we go. Yes.
Here we go.
Put him in a shopping cart and hit with the power of a sling
Yamasaki, hold him.
The bat, the bat.
Is that fine? Just like that?
That's fine, that's fine.
That's fine, right?
This will work, I'm sure.
Yes.
The pitch, please.
Go.
All right, go.
Ah, that was close.
Watch out, watch out.
Go.
All right, go.
Ah, that was close.
Watch out, watch out.
Yamazaki.
Matsumoto gets angry and leaves again
Are you all right?
The timing was a little bit off. If we let go at the right timing, that would definitely hit, you know.
The group go to the dressing room to apologize again
The timing was a little bit off. If we let go at the right time, that would definitely hit, you know.
And then you said "Watch out" or whatever, making no sense, so he'll also just think, "Oh, I better watch out."
He'll think that.
Right? Realize that. Right?
I'm sorry.  I'm sorry.
Anyway, let's apologize.
Excuse us.
Matsumoto was sorting chicks
Cocorico's timing was a little... right? Since the ball is fast, letting the cart go was late.
Yes, it was a little.
Cocorico's timing was a little... right? Since the ball is fast, they let go of the cart too late.
What the hell was all of that?
Who says something like that?  (?????????????????????????)
Huh?
No, I don't think it's anything like that.
That, sling or whatever, why would you think of using that?
"Mattsun, let's go to Yoshimoto* together," you said.
*Note: Yoshimoto is the agency that represents Downtown.
Your duo partner you entered Yoshimoto with was put onto a shopping cart
And by the time you realized, he was being pulled by a sling
What were you feeling when you saw such a sight?
You're right.
And you. A person you've been following the whole time, watching him on TV
You finally are able to work with him on TV. And before you know it
Some junior that crawled out from a rock cuts his hand a bit.
He's being put in a sorry state.
Sorry, sorry.  We were wrong.
I'm sorry.
I'll tell them, too.
We'll be waiting for you.
Matsumoto's 3rd Attempt!!
Matsumoto, with an indomitable fighting spirit, goes for his third attempt.
Hey.
Hello.
Let's look alive and do this.
Sorry about before.
No, no. I'm fine.
Really, let's do this without getting any injuries.
OK.
Let's go.
Ok, let's do it.
Ok, let's go.
Ok, let's get ready.
Ok, ok.
Ok, let's go.
This way, this way.
Ok, ok.
Hey. Look. He's standing.
Yes.
Oh, whoa.
He's not upset anymore.
When the professionals come in, he behaves.
He behaves when the professionals come in.
Just the bat's left.
Yes.
All right.
This will definitely work, wouldn't you say?
This will work.
This is done.
Use a spinning machine and hit the ball with the centrifugal force
The bat's good.
Firmly, firmly.
Ok, get ready.
Ok.
Let's go.
Here we go.
How many times should we turn him?
1...
15.
2...
Ok, the last time.
Ok, ok.
Let's hit it.  Let's hit it.
Ok, let's go. Then,
Here we go.
Let him go.  The pitch, please!
Please!
All right! Hit it, hit it!
You can hit it!
Another one.
Here it comes.
Let's go again.
We can go again. We can go again.
Now's the chance.
Matsumoto gets angry and leaves, yet again
Huh?
His body language makes him look really sad.
He's really down.
So it becomes like that when you increase it by five turns.
Since we could've kept it to ten turns, honestly.
The group goes to the dressing room to apologize, yet again
Excuse us.
Matsumoto was eavesdropping on the gasps that can be heard from the next room
This is the dressing room, right?
What do you want?
I thought I was going to die.
Just one last chance.
Seriously, we were probably thinking about the timing too much.
We should probably return to the basics again.
Let's give it our best.
We'll be waiting for you.
Matsumoto's 4th Attempt!!
Matsumoto puts his last hope into the fourth attempt.
Here we go. Ok.
Um
You're all thinking about this the wrong way.
Ok.
The scale is getting larger and larger.
Yes.
It's not about machines and things like that.
Yeah, we're going back to the basics.
Ok?
That's completely bullying.
"Man, I am being bullied," was what I felt there.
That's not what we meant.
Look. I'm a bit pale, right?
Honestly, you do.
I think you can see that through the camera, too. "Whoa, Macchan,"
"They got you good."
I don't want that anymore.
All right.
Back to basics.
Back to basics. Right. Endo?
Endo played baseball.
So let's leave it up to Endo.
No problem.
Endo.
Endo will hit the ball as Matsumoto's arms
You got the bat? Ok, move up. Move up.
Ok, ok.  Ok.
It's all you, Endo.
Ok.
You got it?
All right.
Here it comes. Here it comes.
Now.
Here it is!
That was close.
Foul tip! It was a foul tip!
Foul tip!
Go again, go again.
Now.
No, too early, too early.  That's not going to work.
It's not working.
It's getting somewhere.
This is hard.
'Cause Endo can't see.
I can't see anything.
Let's go with the final tactic.
Yes, yes. Ok, I'll get it ready. Hold on.
That was close, though, wasn't it?
That was close.
Endo, just stand up.
Ok, I'll stand up.  Here I go.
Ready and go.
Ok, ok.
Whoa, whoa.  He's completely lying down.
Tanaka!
He's completely lying down.
Hey, we need a ladder.
Endo will hit while Matsumoto sits on his shoulders
This side's in?
Yes, it's in. Everything's good, now?
The zipper's done. How is it?
He's really staring.
Endo, are you all right?
I'm all right.
All right.
Ok.
Go for it!
Endo!
?????????????????????????//
It's all you, Endo!
Ok. Ok, let's go.
It's all you.
Here it comes. Here it comes.
Hitting a 150 km/h pitch!!
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Success!!
After overcoming numerous hardships, Matsumoto finally obtains his great achievement of hitting a 150 km/h pitch.
A true congratulations to you.
There is no such thing as "impossible" for you.
Part 1 Part 2
Great, great.
Endo.
Thank you.
Endo, you did great.
Great job.
I got the hit.
You...
The 150...
No, we hit the 150.
Yes, we hit it.
But, I mean, wasn't it a success?
Yes, it was a great success.
It was a great success.
Right?
Extra Scene
Gaki No Tsukai
???????????????????????
In the studio after shooting
I hate that machine.
You want to try it (the spinning), right?
I don't want to try it.
Fine, Yamasaki, do it.
No, no, no.
(Staff): Ready it, please.
No, no.  Please don't do that.
It's extra. It's extra.
Your senior did it and you're...
After you're done, Heipo will do it.
Heipo
Attempts the Spinning!!
Yamasaki Hosei
I already feel sick at this point.
1...
Whoa, this is bad.
2...
Ready and ok.
Wow, it was going like this.
Wow.
The return spin is also scary.
The ball is coming.
He's not saying anything.
Yamazaki.
Why isn't he saying anything?
What? Nothing?
Attempts the Spinning!!
Heipo
More firmly.
Ah, wait.
No... I mean, you've seen this part.
No, my neck, argh.
What is it? What is it?
Hamada!
It hasn't started yet. Watch out, watch out.
What is it?
Stop it!
Hamada~
Watch out.
Watch out, watch out.
Don't let him hold the bat.
That's dangerous.
Endo, take the bat.
What's the matter?
I'm scared!
He said it very clearly.
Just, the bat...
Just, let's just once...
What's the matter?
You kinda look like a big fly.
What the hell is it, Heipo?
What's the matter?  What are you panicking about?
And why were you screaming "Hamada! Hamada!"
What is it with this guy?