August 14- With the heatwave of 35°C,
one of the show's harshest project was taking place.
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende presents the 1st,
"It doesn't make sense not to live positively!"
Negativity Prohibited Tour!!
DOWNTOWN
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
I don't get any of this.
Hot,
hot!
So hot!
That's what we mean...
We've got complaints
COCORICO
Endō Shōzō
Inomoto Takafumi
Kazuhiro Fujiwara
LICENSE
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hōsei
from various people.
Eh, no way!
I've never even made a complaint before,
idiot.
And he just keeps on going!
Considering their career,
the amount of negative remarks is just amazing.
We've collected some proof
and put together in this short clip,
please take a look!
These are events that happened before the show's recording.
It's slightly cold
in here.
I always feel like
I'm going to catch a cold
by staying in this room.
He's really at it.
Totally~
While he could have stopped at "it's slightly cold",
Matsumoto just keeps on complaining.
Matsumoto keeps on complaining about the temperature during other recordings as well.
Ah, so hot
and humid.
It's so friggin' dry in here.
So dry.
It's the season...
And even about other things too...
Matsumoto-san is really at it.
Got any water-?
Seriously,
speaking of water
you don't really give me any until I ask for it.
I only ask 'cause they don't give em.
I'm only pointing out the truth here.
So cramped in here.
As such, the members' negativity is undeniable!
We four have nothing to do with this!
It's only Matsumoto-san.
I always think about you guys when I ask for the water!
If I don't ask for it...
Take Endo for an example,
I just feel so sad for him.
Endo could ask for himself.
Endo's way too shy for that.
Shy?
Negativity Prohibited Tour is where only positivity is allowed.
While dealing with the various negative traps,
they have to obey to the instructions and visit various places.
At the end of the tour, the person that was the most negative
will undergo a harsh punishment!
So, what about
"So hot!", for example?
"So hot!
but a perfect weather for recording!," for example.
or like, "It's summer time."
Hamada-san, hands in your pocket will be
counted as
negative.
That's quite right.
So this is a negative.
Yes, it's an indication that you're not so positive about today's recording.
Ah alright, so that's a no then.
That was negative too while you were explaining,
Why?
when he was all "Ehhh".
No, no, no.
My apologies.
Yes, that's the way.
That's how you do it!
Well then, for the 1st order...
Here it is.
Change your clothes and get into the car.
Command #1
To take these off so quickly,
wouldn't it be such a waste?
But I'm super happy
about
the change of clothes.
That was great!
Everyone, we'll be starting now.
Here goes!
Negativity prohibited tour!
Whoa, whoa, whoa
No, no, no...
Is this for real?
That's a nice color.
I love em.
This is making me excited.
I don't even
wear these during winter!
Ah, that was good.
That was good?
Yes, it was positive.
So it's ok for us to put these on?
Let's put these on quickly!
That's great.
It's a nice thing to go first!
I'm showing my motivation.
How nice...
Uwaa, this feels nice.
This is quite a first for us...
doing this...
With the down jackets on,
the three winners of rock-paper-scissors
will get to positively wear a hat, gloves and a scarf!
Well then, please get in the car and begin the tour!
Was it 35°C today?
Yes, it's 35°C.
But isn't this
a bit harsh?
We're sitting wherever we want?
Yes.
Whoa!!
What's wrong?
I meant, Whoa~ it's huge
inside.
Isn't it the same as always?
Well, I have an idea...
It's really spacious in there.
That's quite the heat.
Ugh, I'm in the middle...
Everyone, please get in!
I'm pumped for this.
Whoa,
wait a sec...
By the way,
I should probably buckle my seat-belt.
it's 40°C right now.
40°C, huh.
We can
do this, right?
Well...
You sure we can do this, right?
Seriously,
can we?
I'm being real here.
This is friggin'
harsh.
You just clearly said it!
He totally said "harsh".
Edited by J-Hive
Translated by Inkin
http://twitter.com/lkn111
j-hive.weebly.com
Do we have to put on the seat belts?
Yes, please.
Just say it, then.
That was scary, wasn't it?
Scary, right?
"Just say it", he said!
Whoa.
Damn,
that was so natural!
Hold it.
It's not even negative anymore,
he's just being himself.
DAMNNNN!!
This'll haunt me in my dreams,
can't believe they're making middle-aged comedians do this.
The sweat from these two,
can you see it?
Hamada-san...
His face is all shiny.
That's quite the Hamada juice there.
Well, it kinda feels good.
This, this, this... this is the real deal.
The car stops at Yotsuya, while the members take a look at the second command.
Command #2
Walk to Go! Go! Curry and eat lunch there.
I just love Go! Go! Curry.
It's really delicious.
There it is.
We're coming in.
Ugh,
stairs...
You don't like walking up the stairs?
The members obey to the command and eat the shop's recommended curry.
However...
Sorry about the wait,
here's your Katsu Curry.
Looks yummy.
Thank you.
And here is our special offer, the extra-spicy Curry.
Looks great.
Please take your time.
Can I?
Go ahead.
Bon appétit.
I'm so thankful for this, I haven't had anything to eat since morning.
Hmm, it's good.
It's good.
So spicy.
Are you being negative?
I mean, so good!
So it's spicy?
What's so spicy about it?
The sauce.
Is it different from ours?
Totally.
Really?
How different is it, then?
Try a bit of it.
How is it?
So good!~
I know, right.
Bon appétit.
Are you from the New Japan Pro-Wrestling?
You're quite something, aren't you?
Or are you from All Japan Pro-Wrestling?
Moved to another association?
Seriously, what's wrong with you?
I mean, seriously.
Did you put something on?
I haven't put anything on.
The shine is just amazing.
I can't finish this.
Did you apply varnish on yourself?
The members finish eating their lunch and take a look at the next command.
The next command is here! It's the third one.
Command #3
Ride the car and drive to Odaiba. By the way, you may take off your clothes during the trip.
So far...
Did you hear him?
I did, I did.
"So far", he said.
That was totally negative.
It's not far at all.
Odaiba is just close by.
I said "So far".
Kinda like "So far"!
That's just, "So far"...
You just keep on saying it.
Thank you!
We offer you our heat-and-eat curry.
Please eat it with everyone!
Thank you.
Whoa!
There's heaps of em.
Thanks a lot.
The way you just went "Whoa!" was a kinda...
No, I just meant "Whoa, there's heaps of it".
Please be careful with it.
You've gotta hold it tightly.
It's actually quite heavy.
Thanks for giving us so much.
...enough to be this heavy.
Isn't it hot?
It's so hot!
What happened?
He just completely said "it's so hot"!
That's being negative!
Really negative!
You can't be serious.
The florist asked him "Isn't it hot?" and
he just replied with "It's so hot!".
That's a negative.
Just when everyone is all positive...
Couldn't they just park
the damn car here
while we were eating at Go! Go! Curry?
There it is!
No, I meant that there must be people thinking like that around!
There it is.
1 hour and 30 minutes in since the start and Matsumoto has something to say.
I think this project
is really great.
But seriously,
how about something like rest-time,
don't we get any?
Yes, rest-time...
Can we really get it?
Can you give us just 2 minutes
of rest-time?
Is it alright?
Very well, then rest time for 2 minutes.
The hell is with these boxes at my feet, it's so annoying!
It's so fucking hot.
I mean seriously, this is harsh.
Can we really do this?
My curry was freakin' spicy!
Yes, it was.
I couldn't eat it.
Don't they sell it like that usually?
I think so, but the staff went out of the way...
...made you a special one.
Lemme ride on top on top.
We've been down here the whole time.
on the highway...
Let's go on the highway.
...while riding on top.
You always choose the worst time to do these recordings, idiots!
Stop it already!
So hot.
Sorry but your 2 minutes are up.
Well, however...
But really, what a refreshing tour this is!
Feels so nice.
And the car heads towards Odaiba.
Just what sort of command awaits them there.
Command #4
Head to the Ferris wheel.
Let's go.
The members obey to the command and walk to the ferris wheel.
However, that man is waiting for them!
This way, this way.
I'll be filming from here on.
Heipo-san...
Can you really be able to film us properly?!
Yes, no problem.
The members get on with Heipo.
No, no, no!
Get over here already.
It's so cramped.
I'm scared too.
So hot...
125m is crazy.
He totally said it just now.
He said it so casually.
Heipo, can you just record already.
Alright.
I'm filming Hamada now.
Tanaka, I'm sorry but
can you film it instead. I just can't.
I'm scared of looking below.
No, no, I'm
not the one to be filming but....
Since you're especially here for it.
Yes, because you're here for it.
So hot~
I'll just stop filming.
Just now...
He's been complaining this whole time.
Heipo, properly record it.
"So hot.. So hot..."
He's been at it the entire time.
I was wondering what he was on about and
"So hot.. so hot.." is what he's been saying.
You're saying it too, Matsumoto.
You're wrong, idiot!
See, see, see.
This sucks.
Damn, it's scary!
Please take a look below, everyone!
I'm totally fine with looking below.
It's nothing, really.
And the ferris wheel finally reached the top.
Hamada, I can't.
DAMN,
so scary!!
Ah, help me.
Oh shit.
It's really dangerous.
Just stop.
Poot
Ugh, it stinks!
Please stop it!
You shittin' me!
Uwaa, it stinks!
Just stop it, for fucks sake!
You just
suck!
You can't be doing this!
It's unacceptable!
Damn, it stinks.
STOP IT!
Uwaa, it stinks!
No manners!
Yeah, no manners at all.
It stinks
and we're so high up.
Help me!
Just amazing.
Hahahahahahaha,
I can't take it anymore.
Are you crying or laughing?
Stop, it's scaring me.
Quickly...
what the hell are they doing below?
I wanna get off.
Fuckin'
STINKS!
God, that stinks!
Let me off.
We're going down now.
It's 'cause people are getting off one by one.
Can I get down, please?
I'm so scared.
No, no, no...
Watch out.
What're you doing?
I'm scared.
Have a seat.
It's dangerous..
If you don't sit...
Fuckin'
STINKS!
Stinks so bad.
The fuck is this!
It can't be that bad.
God, that stinks.
It stinks and I'm scared. I hate this.
The hell're you doing Heipo?
I can't see below. I'm still scared!
Please stand up.
I can't not stand up.
Can't not stand up?
What d'you mean?
Are you Fujiyama Kanbi or what?
"I can't not stand up."~
I'm scared.
"I'm scared."
Heipo didn't film anything.
That's right.
Please be careful while stepping out.
Please get off.
Please get off!
Matsumoto-san, please!
You bet I'm getting off.
Help! I hate this.
I can't do it.
God,
that was so annoying!
I'm serious!
Open it!
He's really going again.
I can't do this.
The 5 members get in the car again, and take a look at the last command.
Command #5
Eat Chanko-nabe in a restaurant.
Chanko?
My stomach...
Huh?
What d'you mean?
I simply said "my stomach".
That's why I'm asking why you're saying as such.
Sorry, we've got an additiona
command from Liscence.
Additional?
Where did they go?
Additional command!
Play shiritori with only positive words.
Note: Shiritori is a word-chain game. It ends when a player says a word that ends in 'n' character because there are no words that start with 'n'.
Best
sa-i-ko-u
Happy
u-re-shi-i
Nice
i-i-ne
ne?
Taking a long time there.
3,
H-H-Hold on...
2,
With ne?
So long.
Sleepy...
ne-mu...
Sleepy?
So negative.
There's more...
There's more to it.
Sleepy?
'Sleepy' ain't good.
Endo. that's...
I did stop at 'sleepy' but there's more to it.
Really?
What is it?
Not sleepy at all.
ne-mu-ku-na-i
Ugh, that recover sucked.
Hold on...
That was shit.
What the hell was with the recover?
Are there any word that starts with ne?
I hate negativity!
ne-ga-ti-bu-wa-i-ya-da
I can't believe
you used
"negative"
there.
This guy sucks!
But this one is probably on the same level as everyone else.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no...
It was so bad.
Note: ...because Endo used an English word "negative" to start his sentence just earlier.
How about in Japanese?
A cat's ears...
ne-ko-no-mi-mi-ni...
What?
How ironic!
ne-ko-ni-ko-ba-n
How ironic!?
Shit, it ends in n.
Oh shit!
You lost the game.
You ended the game.
If that was me, I'd kill myself.
3 hours since
the start of the tour.
The positive shiritori is still on-going, with Endo, fighting for last place.
They'll be given their last command in this restaurant.
Eat Chanko-Nabe at Saganobori.
Last Command
Thanks for waiting.
Until the nabe is ready,
please enjoy this raw horse-meat from Kumamoto.
That's awesome.
Isn't there any
Soy sauce?
I'm sure there is.
Excuse me!
Yes~
Did you call me?
Ma'am, how to put it... do you have any kind of Soy sauce to eat with this?
Oh, sorry, Soy sauce. I'll bring it right away.
The hell you sayin'.
You can't say things that like, Hamada-san.
This isn't even about being "negative" anymore,
it's about having good manners.
Ah, I see now.
It's the staff's plan,
to make us say stuff like that.
Did you just hear that?
"It's the staff's plan"
I heard it.
"It's the staff's plan"!
Sounded just like a pirate.
You could just imagine him with a hook instead of his hand.
So scary...
Can't be helped.
She's so slow.
He just said it.
He's at it again.
I mean, come on... it's just Soy sauce!
You can't be saying that.
Judge, please take all of this into account.
That was just...
That was just a normal...
I mean...
I'm not even saying anything special.
The waitress finally brings the Soy sauce,
and the crew begin enjoying the horse-meat.
I can't even feel my fingers anymore.
What the... that's so negative, I don't even!
No, no, no, no...
You're just full of complaints.
Hasn't the complaints been increasing since we came here?
Yeah, we should'nt be doing so.
Ah, it's tasty.
Sorry to have made you wait!
And the Chanko-nabe finally makes its appearance!
Ah, thanks.
This is what we do best,
Curry Chanko-nabe!
But we just had curry earlier.
Seriously,
you're non-stop.
It's just repeating.
That was just amazing.
The crew uses their remaining strength and enjoy the Curry Nabe.
It's kinda tepid.
Not really.
Tanaka, please put some more in for him.
I don't know why, but mine was really tepid for some reason.
Give him from the bottom.
It's still
tepid there.
He's going at it like a machine-gun.
Why is he only taking the meat
that looks the worst?
Do your best, Tanaka.
It's alright to put some soup too, for fucks sake!
Why would you take out the soup?!
Do your best!
Hang in there Tanaka.
You were planning on the soup for the last, right?
If that's the case, then why
did you go and separate the soup?
You're freaking slow.
Umm...
I swear...
You're so annoying!
You're really pissing me off!
It's getting scary in here.
You just love that damn horse-meat, don't you?!
What's with you? Right from the start,
you've only been picking on the horse-meat!!
I love them.
Pour him the damn soup already!!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
How long are you gonna take?!
Time to announce the results.
These two have been saying quite a lot of things while cameras weren't recording!
Yes, we have taken everything into account.
Today, the person that was the most negative was...
Matsumoto-san!
Thank you.
What an amazing sight!
First place is Matsumoto!
The other four members couldn't even come close to his negativity.
Ugh,
stairs...
Ride the car and drive to Odaiba.
So far...
That was totally negative.
It's not far at all.
Couldn't they just park
the damn car here
while we were eating at Go! Go! Curry?
There it is!
God,
that was so annoying!
You
just love that horse-meat, don't you?!
What's with you? Right from the start,
you've only picking on the horse-meat!!
And for the most negative person today...
Are you drunk or something?!
No I'm not.
While wearing the same clothes, ride the car with the heater on and drive home!
There's no helping it anymore.
Stop it...
Please go home.
since you were the most negative.
What d'you mean?
Since the time at the restaurant...
It was just amazing.
You've gotta be kiddin' me.
Watch out, we're closing the door.
I've drank quite a bit, is it really alright?
So hot...
Great work~
See ya~
It was really hot in there.
As for the rest of us, let us be more careful from now on,
not to make complaints all the time.
I wasn't even
complaining that much.
I was only playing the traditional comedic role
Note: 'tsukkomi' is the role as the 'straight-man' in Japanese comedy duo as the role usually requires one to retort, criticize, verbally and physically abuse the 'boke', the idiot (the other half of the duo).
as the tsukkomi.
It's not even a complaint or anything.
It's not negative at all.
Actually, tsukkomi is a positive thing.
I'm making people laugh with that tsukkomi after all.
And I believe making people laugh is a positive thing.
And they're making it look negative...
then, is tsukkomi negative?
I guess we're not thinking the same way.
So hot in here...
Edited by J-Hive
Translated by Inkin
http://twitter.com/lkn111
j-hive.weebly.com