Translating and captioning by Colin Burdett
Contact at Colinburdett54@gmail.com
Shibaken's Golf Course
This time's Gaki no Tsukai
Endo is giving the members a golf lesson
Can you two do it?
Today, I really...
Hmm, I wonder
We're doing the whole course you know
That's really big
Yea, so can you two really do it
It's not among the things I can't do
Today, I...
Maybe we should go to the Osaka mini golf course
Good morning
Yes, yes, yes
Mornin
Today we're playing golf, aren't we?
So it seems
Yes, do your best
Yes
Well, then, uhm
There may be a mistake, but I'm not sure
But Matsumoto-San's clothes
Are female
They seem to be young girls'
There's no way that's true
No, it's true
When I asked him if it was OK, well
Matsumoto-San said that
It doesn't matter if I wear girly clothes
Wait, that's bad
Is what he seemed to say
However, he said that
For his underwear
He wished we wouldn't look at them
Underwear?
No, why would we look?
Well, of course we wouldn't do that
It's not really a problem, why would we look
Of course, I wouldn't have a reason to look either
Should we start going then? The weather is a bit iffy
Let's go then
Follow Endo then?
Yes
Despite the happening, by Matsumoto's kindness
As long as they don't look at his underwear
They can continue the shoot
For the first time on Gaki no Tsukai Ya Arehende ChikiChiki!!
Endo's golf lesson
Let's get started then
Well then, I thought that I would
Give everyone a golf lesson
Well then, Tanaka, have you golfed before?
Well...
Have I huh... Well
I haven't heard of you ever playing before
Before the shooting of the golf episode
Matsumoto is troubled with
By having to wear women's clothing
By Matsumoto's kindness
And by not looking at his underwear
They start recording
For the first time on Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arehende ChikiChiki!!
Endo's golf lesson
I wonder, if it's ok to do this for 30 minutes?
Really
Yea, well, from now on I'll be teaching you guys
Hmm
Is it too cold?
Well, well, they've never played before
Well, yes, yes, yes
Today really...
Without the jackets, it's cold
Well, we'll be cold while playing, huh
So it seems
It's pretty cold
it's pretty cold, huh
Well, I'd like to give you guys a golf lesson
Ehh, well how are you at golf, Tanaka?
Goooolllff...
Right, well, well
Well, I've never heard of Tanaka playing golf before
But, as of now, you do a little
For work, we'll go golf now and then
We go to the golf course together
Yes, that's right, but I
But you haven't ever have you?
But I've never actually swung a club
I'm wondering if Yama-Chan can golf
In Yamaguan he played a lot of golf
He plays?
I did, huh
You were pretty terrible, huh
Yea, I was really bad
Yea, but you can still play, like a round at Suishou
That's true
That's right
That's right, everyone could probably play at Shuishou
Although I've never been
That's true
Matsumoto, you also haven't, have you?
No, actually, I played a lot
Really, however many times
I'm not sure where, but we both played a lot in Hokakoma
However times you tried
You really did
You didn't know that the hole had a flag in it
You mean like that one
Right, right, right
You really thought there wasn't a hole
Ahh, I did that
Before the lesson
To prevent injury
They begin by stretching
Let's start with the wrist
Various: Yes
Let's start
Now let's do the ankles
With golf you really use your whole body
Huh
Alright then, let's start
With the inner thighs then
Inner thighs
Yea, well, it's more the hip joint
You happen to use your hip joint a lot
Alright
Now with the left leg then
ow ow ow
One, two
Your hip joint is very important
I see, I see
Don't want to injure yourself after all
Of course, right
Your back too
Back too
Lastly
Ow, ow, ow, this really hurts
Alright
Lastly then, here
If you would stretch your sides then
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Wa-wait a second!!
Yes?
He was totally looking at my underwear
What, me?
I wasn't trying to look at your underwear or anything
Well, sorry, sorry
Well, then, is there some guilty underwear glaring theme going on here?
No, no there's nothing
But you were totally looking!!
Well, today I was hoping to teach you guys some golf
I'm surprised at how fast I lost faith in guys
Yes
Ah, Ahhh, it's become more complicated now
It seems to be one degree more complicated huh?
It's not at all like that
It won't be, will it?
It won't be
It would be best, wouldn't it?
It's not like that right?
It won't be, it won't be!
What are you saying?
You'll stop then?
Right, let's do this like normal then
Well Ok
Alright
Let's finish stretching then
The first thing they'll learn is how to hold the golf club correctly
Before we can start with the correct swing
You must grip it right
With the grip then, well, you have to use five fingers
But you use the last three
And you grip it underneath like this first
Yea
Where, which groove do I grip?
Ahh, well, normally, uhh,
T.N. I don't understand what Endo's saying here
Everyone here's a man
So you get your power from interlocking
With the left hand, then
With your bodies foundation
He hasn't been listening
I'm listening, I'm listening
He's being arrogant because he's golfed before
No, I've been listening
Speaking of listening
you were looking weren't you!!!
I haven't looked
Why did you come to this shoot anyway?
Did you come here to look at your partner's underwear?
No
No, I haven't seen your underwear...
I don't know If I can do this shoot
Well, no, really
Sorry, Sorry
Because you've been looking
Who else has looked?
I don't get Tanaka
He's has such a sincere expression
I can't concentrate at all!!
Really, should we just cut this?
My partner for 30 years is looking at my underwear
We can't possibly use this footage
He's the worst one to be looking
Well
Yes
Hamada, please
Well, yea, not at all, I wouldn't do that
Ehhh, really, can I do this?
Let's then... learn how to hit the ball then
Now that they've learned how to grip the club
It's time to try the drive shot
Do your best
Yes
I've never seen this done before
First Hosei will
Huhhh, really?
Try to swing without instruction
It was a while ago since you've tried, huh
I had a little more hope for you than that
Me too
Next, Matsumoto, if you would
Yes
Please do
I wonder how he'll do
It's over there
I wonder how Matsumoto's swing has changed these years
Me too
Like this?
That was nice, I felt it, nice swing
Yea, nice swing
Ahh, that's very good, yes
Miss
Right there
Right there, you weren't looking at the ball
This is its normal height
But I'll raise it a little bit
Ahh, ok
Haa
It should be easier to hit
That's right
I see, I see
Ok
It should be a little...
Yes
Look at the center of the ball
So, since I changed the ball height
Is it bad to not look at the ball?
Well, the ball, look at the ball a bit more
That's... yeah, you should look
It'd be hard not looking at the ball
It's bad to not look at the ball, but I wasn't looking
Like how it's bad for you guys to look at my underwear but still do
Celebrities that don't look at the ball, and
Celebrities that look at underwear!!
What's with this shoot?
That's the second time
The four, having broken their promises, made Matsumoto very angry
They go to the next lesson location
That's right, the next lesson point is...
When one of the balls is left behind, Hamada goes and gets it...
*Hey, hey, hey*
Yes?
Yeah, well, he's still looking
Still?
Yea
Do you have a moment?
Huh?
Well....
If you were looking
Could you go apologize?
Uhm
I haven't looked
What exactly am I looking at?
Well, uhh, Matsumoto told us....
Well, he's the only one wearing a mini skirt...
It's a bit strange
That's the only reason to look
That's true
Can't you see his whole @#*$?
Huh
It got bigger
It's got way bigger
When was the last time it was that big, huh...
Ah
What's wrong?
Uh, nothing, nothing, uh
We told him
Talking about if I did see it
It's not a problem anymore, really...
Next is the bunker golf lesson
Yes
You totally just looked at my underwear, right?
I'm telling you I didn't
You saw them
That is not so, if I did...
Yes, now you just looked
I did not
You did
How many times after will you look?
I did not look!
If you'd stop looking and just admitted you looked
Let's stop this, let's stop this
I haven't looked
Let's stop this, Let's stop this
If you really saw my pants just say you did
So then I'll know that you can see them, and that this shoot is no good?
I did not look
I have not looked
Let's stop with this fighting
Next is....
The next shoot is here then?
The shoot where I cry myself to sleep?
He definitely looked at my underwear though!
I did not look at your underwear, let's play golf
Let's stop this, let's stop this
Let's play golf, let's play golf
Does anyone want to look at my underwear then?
There's no one, right?
Yes
Then please don't look!
Even you are peeping in the end
I know!
You give the most lewd face, you know
It's ok to look
However
If you see it normally then I won't say anything
It's the obscene part of when you look I hate, the lewd part
Right now you were totally checking it out, right?
You said normally
Since you said we could look normally
But you never look normally
You're the worst here
Endo, tell him
Well, then, uh..., Hamada
Take my example for how you should look, then
Next up is
The bunker shot lesson
T.N. Don't understand
After hitting from the bunker
In good sportsmanship
Rake the sand to be even again
Then Matsumoto
The least experienced
First up is Matsumoto to face the bunker shot challenge
It's so exposed
First off, without looking below
and make sure to look at the ball
Oh, it's really buried
Buried?
That was good
Nice
A quick tip, you could do easier just like this
Ahh, with this being a gentleman's sport
Yes
Make sure to, yea
It's a gentleman's sport so
You guys are not at all gentleman!!
You were totally just looking at my underwear!!
You want to see my underwear as much as you can
on this slope
After all, that's the only reason we came to this bunker, isn't it?
While you guys were behind me
You were totally looking weren't you?
I wasn't looking...
No, I wasn't looking...
I wasn't really looking...
Tanaka's the only one who hasn't said anything
Tanaka please say something
Tanaka, if you did or didn't see say
Well... to say looked at...
Say I saw or didn't see
Well..., to say that...
I saw, I saw
You Saw!!!!
You Saw my underwear
What class rank were you in comedy school?
I was ranked first!
I was the first rank among all the comedians, what about you?
I didn't go to comedy school...
You didn't go to comedy school?
How puzzling
Go to comedy school!!!
The bunker lesson ended after that
In between lessons, they go to a break room
We good?
Yep
Ok
Wowww
Yamachan, you should say it right?
Huh?
Say it
Matsumoto
Hm?
We can see
Let's rest here then
Here?
Break room, huh?
Let's see it then
There are snacks and drinks in the break room
Let's take a small break then
There are things like bread here
Wow, I'm pretty tired huhh
I think if you practice golf you'll get tired
What do you mean by that?
I think that if you practice golf
T.N. Don't understand
Ahhhh
&^*%@
I'm tired
You were all looking!!!!
I was being just a little bit careless
I was always looking out here
You say that but
You're the senior, why didn't you say something?
Matsumoto doesn't like it if you look
So could you cut it out?
You didn't even try to stop them
Why didn't you say something?
You didn't communicate
But I think you did communicate
Since you were always saying how they were looking
I'm not sure I'm happy working with you all yet
If I was with a better group this would be no problem
Like with Matsunosuke Shoufukutei, then it would be no problem
T.N. rakugo comedian
I'm done with you people
It's impossible for me to not be angry
It would be way better if
You made an environment were you'd tell me when you can see my underwear
If you did that, then I wouldn't get angry
If the creative agency asked me about seeing my underwear on T.V.
If that happened, then it would be really bad for me
So please tell me
Ok
On the other end Matsumoto, you need to keep in mind...
You just looked while talking
No, no
We see on accident
Like when Endo
If you just glance, if you just glance it's fine
It's fine if you glance
No, but we haven't been looking at all
Just glance at a good time
That's right, not at all
That's right
We haven't been looking
You're all totally looking
If I just wore different underwear
We haven't been looking
We haven't been looking, we haven't been looking
You're always looking
We haven't been looking
You're even looking now!!
We're not looking
He's crying
Not looking, nobody's looking
We're not looking
Could you just change clothes?
Matsumoto!!
Really, Matsumoto
Can't he change his clothes?
Not looking, no one else is looking
16 Minutes since entering the break room
Huhh, what should I do...
I can't relax at all
Actually, actaully, I have something to say to you guys
I heard something when I was pretending not to listen
Hamada, you said that
It looks like he has an erection
Where in the world
While shooting a golf program
Will someone after looking at someone's underwear and then say he has an erection
Uh, well, Yamachan...
No, no
Said that it got bigger
I didn't do anything like...
Hey
You can totally see my underwear
What are you doing?
I say that but
And the staff says as well that this won't end today
Huh?
I'll be doing this forever
I don't want to change this
You guy's will look back and think it's not your fault,
but you'll regret you didn't change your staring
Would you change your mind if we weren't looking?
It's fine to look!!
How many time's have I said it's ok?!?!
That's not true
I said it was bad to look once
Look in the recordings!!
Should we look once?
Sure, let's look
Let's look? Let's look
Let's look at it then
Wa-wai-wait!!
What are you doing!?!?
What are we doing?
What's with you
What's wrong?
I want you to see accidentally
Accidentally
I hate it if you glance at my pants and then turn away
If you glance around and happen to see them than that's fine
That's what I mean when I say it's fine to look!!
Well then, go ahead and look
Well to bad, that you can't see them!!
What's wrong?
What's wrong here?
You are!!
Who's making this mood
27 minutes since entering the break room
It's been 27 minutes since we've entered this room
Why can't we go out?
I don't feel like going out!!!
Let's get out of here
Why don't you feel like it?
Let's go... Let's go to the green
Green, huh... What color is my underwear?
Yes, Yamasaki-san
White
Yep, you saw
Let's go, we can practice...
Wait a second, I haven't been able to drink a single drop of water
Since you guys have been staring at my underwear
I haven't had time to drink any water
Would you like coffee, or...
When I come home, my wife will ask me what's wrong
Why are you so thirsty
Well, everyone was staring at my underwear
I wasn't able to get a drink
Huhh, what are you doing?
When I'm thirsty I don't drink black coffee
That's bad
Black, huh
Black, and there's the green, and what color is my underwear
White
Yep, you looked
You've been looking this whole time, huh
You've been able to many times, huh
I think I won't wear white underwear from now on
Here's water
Hmmm
This isn't any color, really...
36 minutes since entering the break room
I'm so glad I put on underwear today
If I didn't wear underwear I wouldn't understand why you'd guys would look
My underwear is protecting me
Let's go Endo
If I wasn't wearing underwear, what would you be looking at exactly
Yes
Please wait a second
I'm not done
But
But we're going to the green
There's more?
Really?
We're going to the green
We'll go in five minutes
What with this pattern
T.N. Don't understand
43 Minutes since entering the break room
If you want to look at my underwear, please look during recording
So everyone can know
That you love my underwear
You just agreed, didn't you?
No, I wasn't
I was just saying yes
I'm listening to what you're saying
Then, then you'll stop
Yes, yes, yes
Various: We won't look
Then, you won't after this
Hey
T.N. Don't understand
Yes
Endo let's go
Then, the green
Let's go to the green
We still have to practice
You just looked, huh!
You just looked!!
No one looked
I didn't look, I didn't look
I really didn't
No one is
No one's looking
The last lesson is
How to putt
Before they start the last lesson, while they are on standby
Matsumoto's chest has changed
Then, the last lesson is putting
Yes
Putter
Wellll, then
The driver shot
Is imitated in putting
So if you do that, you'll profit
If you do that much, then...
Have you ever heard that before?
Huhh?
Have you ever heard of that?
Then Matsumoto-San
First Matsumoto will try to putt on his own
In this putting challenge
You know
What will the audience think of this?
What's with you guys?
Huh?
What is this?
Hey, wait a second
Let's go back
You guy's haven't gotten anything
Hey!!!
What is it, jeez?
Bring it here
What's this?
Actually, I expected this in advance
The staff has been counting how many time's you've looked at my underwear
How many time's you've looked
This is how many times
This is actually how many times
Hamada
Tanaka
Endo
Yamasaki
In front of the camera
Say that
I saw Matsumoto's underwear
10 times
Then after that, let's do a one shot
Should we do it with a grain filter?
Yes
Let's start from Yamasaki
Now?
Yes
Ok
Do it alone
I saw Matsumoto's underwear 10 times
This exists now?
Right
I saw it 7 times
I, uhh, saw Matsumoto's underwear 6 times
I saw 12 times
Alright
Then, lastly, let's all get together
I'll be the center
I saw Matsumoto's underwear
And yell at the end
Lastly?
Yes
Ok
Well, then, I'll do this
It's like this?
It's like this then?
Ready, set
I saw Matsumoto's underwear
Alright
Right
I don't want to do that again
Let's go home
Can we go home?