6th time on Gaki no Tsukai CHIKI CHIKI
"Let's ask for the best 3 in a new town"
Very loud isn't he?
The 6th installment after 2 years
Just a bit too loud
So this is the 6th one,
And we've going to mostly Chiba!
That's true
Chiba
Kanagawa
A lot of Chiba
And we hate Chiba, don't we?
No, that's not true
I love Chiba!
You're going too far there
You love a lot of things too much
I was just kidding!
Their destination depends on this lottery
1 out of the approximately 2500 stations in Kanto's 6 prefectures,
What town was chosen this time?
So where is it?
Takezawa
Takezawa...
This is seriously the first time I've heard of that place
Where is Takezawa?
Saitama
Ah, Saitama
Down here? Oh no, up there
There it is!
Takezawa?
And it's the perfect distance from here!
What the hell are you talking about?
subbed by senor_wristband
If you'd like to support my subs,
I've setup these accounts :)
patreon.com/senor_wristband
ko-fi.com/buresurettosan
Their destination is 1.5 hours by car from Tokyo,
In Ogawa, Hiki District, Saitama Prefecture
Takezawa Station
30 trains a day run at this unmanned station, with an average of 31 passengers,
They want to time the start of the shooting with the arrival of the train
Oh there, it's coming it's coming
Here we are, at Takezawa station
That was timed perfectly
Yeah, if we missed this we'd have to wait another hour
However,
Nobody got off the train
What?
Hold on, we can't ask people then
The next train is in 1 hour
1 hour?!
Hold on, we can't do anything here,
We'll just have to wait
But then in front of them,
They found some locals
Hello!
Hello, excuse us
Please, hear us out
Hold on, why are they running away?
I get it though,
It's cause of Hamada, cause he called to them
You need Tanaka for this sort of thing
They just don't like me?
They think you're gonna smack them like "BAN!"
They managed to talk to them
How long have you ladies lived here?
Yes, it's been 50 years now
50 years?
Is this a nice place?
Yes, it's very nice!
None of us feel the same way at all
That's not true
We've only just gotten here, yes
What suggestion does the mother who has been living in Takezawa for 50 years have for number 3?
We were thinking of going to the nice spots in this town,
You might have a top 3 in mind,
Could you give us what #3 is?
And we've got exactly 3 of you here
Who could have known
Somethin like "Oh you should check that place out"
It's towards Arashiyama,
They specialise in making Japanese Paper in that area,
Ah, and are you involved with that?
No, not really
Sorry, it's just we have to stay near the station
Driving to Arashiyama from here would take 20 minutes
Is there anything nearby the station?
I think the Yoshida Family House
I think it has to be the Yoshida Family House then
Yoshida Family?
Yoshida Family House
It's an estate built 300 years ago, and it's been preserved,
They've preserved it?
It's been maintained to be the same way
You're so knowledgeable...
Did you plan this?
I was just passing through
She was so articulate
They jot down Yoshida Family House, but they want to find something a little closer to the station
There's nobody walking outside
Yeah this is amazing,
If we keep messing about, it'll turn dark by 4 you know!
That's true
That's true, we need to finish before 4
I have to go the dentist today...
Today it's the dentist huh?
There's a sake store up ahead,
Oh, there is
Well then,
Let's go inside
Excuse me, hello
Ah, excuse me,
We're looking for recommended places here in Takezawa,
You should go to the Yoshida House
The Yoshida Family House
Woah, the same as before
For example, a nice restaurant
There's lad here who sells ramen,
It's 3 types in 1
Oh it's a special?
Is it close by?
Yup, right next to Yoshida House
Sir, could I get your name?
Yoshida Nobuaki
Yoshida-san?
What a coincidence
Thank you very much
They get a side-suggestion after talking to him,
His name was Yoshida-san
How old was he?
Ah, I didn't ask hi-
Ask that!
I just asked his name, Yoshida-san...
Oh, there's something!
What is that, a convenience store?
It is a convenience store
Hello
Hello, excuse us,
Is there a specialty in this town?
Something in this town that stands out, something you would suggest?
Near here?
What does Yoshida-san suggest, in this convenience store near the station?
There's the Yoshida Family House,
Everyone is saying that huh?
A lot of people have suggested that,
Ogawa Genki Plaza,
Genki Plaza?
In the mountains nearby, there's school facilities and a planetarium,
Anyone can go in though
Is the planetarium open right now?
A planetarium would be nice,
That family house keeps coming,
I think we better go there,
Since everyone said Yoshida Family House, they were gonna go there,
But then that Family House should be #1 then right?
Since everyone is saying it,
But we can't move on until we're done with #3,
Do you have a #3?
Can you go and find out if we can go to the planetarium today?
No no, we'll do it
He's running the store right now
However, we couldn't film inside the Planetarium today,
At Segenyama, there's a roller slide
A roller slide?
Sounds interesting!
Like a park?
You can slide down the mountain
Oh, that sounds nice!
Sir, who are you gonna go down the slide after?
Why the hell?
He's running the store!
Thank you very much
Thank you very much, sorry for the sudden intrusion
We've prepared the car
Now you can go find out that old man's first name
His first name and his age
Yoshida, Yoshitake-san I th-
Just, hurry!
They're always making me run!
If I was Endo, I'd bring the old man with me
I'd give him a piggy back ride
That far?
I want him to go that far
I've come here to ask his first name and his age,
Yoshida Nobuaki
Nobuaki-san? Could I get your age too please
91 years old
Wow, 91 years old. You look very healthy!
Thank you
Yoshida ... Yoshida Nobuaki-san
Now we're waiting on Endo
He said Yoshitake-san
He said something like that
Really?
Ah he's back!
I asked him
I asked him,
What was his name?
Yoshida ... Nobuaki-san
You were way off
His age?
91 years old
His wife, was she there?
... She was ...
Really?
His wife was next to him
What was her name?
I didn't ask her
Isn't Yoshida-san enough?
Isn't that good enough?
After getting in the car,
The 5 head to Segenyama Hill View Park
We said it was his wife, but it might have been his sister,
Ahh ... I think it was his wife though
Endo doesn't really care about people
No that's not ture
You only care about yourself
That's not true, that's not true,
I don't even care about myself that much
Then just die already
I'm glad the weather turned out fine
Ah we're here
This is it
The car arrives at Sengenyama Hill View Park
You can see great views of Ogawa at this park,
And what about the 203 metre roller slide here?
We're here
Wow, the weather is nice
"Roller Slide"
I wanna see DownTown go down together
They do seem love slides
We love slides?
This is amazing!
203 metres...
Yeah it even says it there, 200 yen
So it's 1 yen per metre
They start off with Hosei
This is pretty scary!
If you'd like, you can together, for example the 2 of you
Here I go!
It's pretty fast
Alright Tanaka you go
Here I go!
Next is Tanaka, and then Matsumoto
And then Hosei reaches the end!
How am I supposed to get off?
How are you supposed to get off that?
And Tanaka as well...
That hurt
Oh there's Matsumoto-san!
His hemorrhoids are in danger
Of course that would happen!
Exactly, exactly!
This thing
They never told us about this!
They didn't tell us anything!
Next is Hamada and Endo's turn
Will Hamada-san's hemmoroids be alright?
That's gonna hurt
The end is scary! This is scary!
Oh no!
No way
This is how it ends?
Exactly!
They didn't tell us this right?
Yeah!
Honestly, this "welcome mat" thing is no good!
Exactly
It should be a bit softer
Exactly, we should tell them!
Right around there you go "Hmm?"
"This is impossible isn't it?"
It's just straight up impossible
With that, the number 3 suggestion around Takezawa is Sengenyama Hill View Park
They set off to ask for #2
Ma'am, are you a local?
We're from Funabashi
You're wearing a Tiara and eating Onigiri!
So you don't know too much about this town?
Yes
I guess we can't really ask a non-local. Thank you!
It's my first time here
Oh, your first time? Thank you!
That old man from before
Thank you!
When did you get here?
Did you slide down here just now?
They ask the gentleman from before for his #2
Like a restaurant or such
This used to be a castle town,
There's a very old establishment there called Futaba
What sort of establishment?
Ochazuke
TN: Ochazuke is a rice dish served in tea, broth, or hot water
That sounds nice, an Ochazuke store
Sorry, could I get your name?
Me? My name is Ogino
And your first name?
It's Katsuji
And your age?
I'm 78 years old!
Thank you, sorry for the bother!
Thank you, goodbye!
It's a 5 minute drive from the park to Futaba
They set off right away
The wind was really strong
Wow ... ignored like that ...
I said "yes"
I'm not sure about the people in the back though
I didn't hear your "yes"
I said "yes"
If this was our first time meeting you would be done for
When was the last time you had Ochazuke?
I have it a couple times a year
Oh really? When do you eat it?
Ignored
Wow ... ignored like that ...
Isn't that it?
"Futaba-san", we're here
They arrive at the Futaba Inn
So nice!
It's great
It's amazing!
It's brilliant
Wow! I like this Japanese style
Where should we sit?
Is it OK here?
Thank you very much
Futaba Kappou Inn
A 270 year old establishment preserving the history of Saitama
What do you suggest?
We suggest the Chushichi-meshi Nori Ochazuke, one of Japan's "5 Great Rice dishes"
The Japanese Imperial Household decided on this dish in Showa 4 (1929)
We'll get that
Understood
Thank you
Why does he get to decide?
You guys should try the specialty
That's true
They wait 10 minutes for the food to cook,
This is a dish that uses local ingredients and produce,
It looks so good
And this is the specialty Chushichi-meshi
With seaweed sprinkled over rice,
And served with yuzu, spring onion, and wasabi
Enjoy it like an ochazuke, with hot water poured on top
It's delicious
The seaweed is the great
That's true
Delicious
We can only eat this here right?
Are you done with that?
We can't get this in Tokyo right?
Yes thank you
We can only get this here?
Thank you
Yes
We can't get Chushichi-meshi in the city can we?
Yes. Thank you very much
Just here then
Futaba-san, thank you for the meal!
Only #1 is left in the Takezawa recommendation ranking
Since so many people suggested it, they consider Yoshida Family House
They asked the Futaba-san host
A lot of people have told us about this Family House
The Yoshida Family House, that's right, that's an interesting place
It's interesting?
It's famous?
Yes, it is
Do you remember of that guy from before?
The very first guy
The very first person
The very first person was Yoshida ... Nobuaki-san
The guy from the slide?
The guy from the slide? Honestly I ...
O-Ogiku?
Ogicha?
That's definitely not it
Hagi... Hagi no ...
His name was like "Hagi no Tsuki" or something
TN: Hagi no Tsuki is a sponge cake dessert
If it was "Hagi no Tsuki" I'd definitely remember
It's a 10 minute drive to Yoshida Family House
Oh we came back here
That's where Endo's BFF lives
Yoshida-san thank you very much
That looks like it
It says it right there
It was written there
Hmm? Is that it?
Takezawa station's #1, the Yoshida Family House
Oh, here?
It's amazing
Hamada-san, there's a donation box
There sure is
Hello
Sorry for the intrusion
Ah, it's the smell of that
There's a lot of food here, like Dango
Takezawa Station's #1 - The Yoshida Family House
Turning 300 years old this year,
Preserving the country's national heritage,
The oldest house in Saitama Prefecture
They light the fire with a prayer, and dig in
How many hundreds of years old is this place?
Exactly 300 this year
Exactly
This used to be a house?
They lived here normally until the start of Hesei (1989)
Until the Hesei-era?
Yes, they lived here normally up until then
We can date this house back 300 years,
And the way we do that is using the Munefuda (building tag)
And that tag was placed right there
Do you get it?
Tanaka go look at it, hurry
This thing?
It was placed in that manner
And since the writing is on the reverse, nobody knew how old it was
So when they decided to demolish this place and build a new house,
But then they thought "Wait, I think they did say it was 300 years old or something"
And then after doing some research they found out
That's genuinely what happened
Wow, it was almost demolished
So if that pillar wasn't there in Kyoho 6 (1721), they couldn't have placed the tag there
I see
So it's a good thing that pillar was there
If you look up there, everything has been kept exactly the same
It's rare for things like that to be left so intact
And with that, this place recieved a National Desgination
That looks like it's just right
Thank you very much
There used to be 4 dango, but now there's 3
Why do you think that might be?
Oh, why?
Because "Dango 3-Kyodai" was popular at the time! (3 Dango Brothers)
TN: "Dango 3-Kyodai" is a popular song from 1999
There were 4 dango up until then
You didn't know that?
No, I know Dango 3-kyodai
I think when talking about the 300 year old history, it's best not to bring something like that up
Is that ready?
Thank you for the meal!
Ah, but, it's delicious
It's nice and chewy
How was this episode? It seemed to go smoother than usual
It's not like nothing happened
A lot happened
Yes, we experienced a lot
Endo, you still have that job left,
That old lady's name
You know every time I have some errand to do
Like every time-
Yeah last time we were at that cafe place,
Yes and you all left
When I got back I saw your car pass by
"Hmm?" "It's over?"
You never know, next time we might even visit your town!
Was it always this kind of show?
Was the ending always like this?