First Time Ever on Gaki no Tsukai ... Chi....
Huh?
Sorry, please try again
First Time On Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arrahende CHIKI CHIKI
I Understand Him-
I can't even laugh at this
Even though he might be faking it
It's not funny at all
Did your wife find this act funny?
What is this?
What happened?
I lost my voice 2 days ago
I'm trying my best here
Are you gonna be alright?
I should?
You do it
Tanaka should do it
OK
Tanaka?
First Eve-
Make a joke here! (Do it wrong on purpose)
Prime opportunity!
That was your chance!
I apologise
You took it too seriously
Endo you do it
I didn't realise
First Ever Gaki No Tsukai CHIKI CHIKI
I Understand Him The Most,
Regardless, This Item Will Suit You Competition,
Suzuki Fuku-kun Edition
"In this program, the members will present clothing the guests might like"
You guys uhhh
Tanaka and Hamada should be good at this
Yes
Yes exactly
You two have adolescent sons
Mine's only 4 still
They wear what you buy them right?
Yes exactly
For me it's like,
boy children's clothes, I like,
don't even look at them (he has a daughter)
I've never bought them either
So I think I'm gonna suck at this
But I've already bought them so...
You're good at this segment usually
He is yeah
"With that said, our guest is this charasmatic child actor!"
"Will the members be able to buy clothes that suit this 12 year old?
OK, Fuku-kun, come on out!
He was this tall in that drama right? (Marumo no Okite)
Now he's this tall
I suppose so
You're getting your physicals done right?
He's 12 years old!
You should be getting them done
How old were you during Marumo No Okite?
I was like 6 ... wait no
You were 6!
6 years old right?
He was 6 years old
I was 6, 6 years old
Do you have any fashion preferences?
Do you care about fashion?
If you ask me if I care or not ...
I don't, I guess
You don't?!
Don't care?
Recently,
Well he is a boy,
Recently, I've been choosing what to wear to school
Oh by yourself?
"Before this shooting, the members went to buy a top and a unique item for the guest"
He has the cute-kid look to him right?
But that's not gonna be his image forever right?
Graduate from the cute-kid look,
to the cool-kid look
That's my opinion anyways
This kinda stuff is no good for a middle-schooler
We could wear it though
"Hamada enters this store too find a unique item"
Something like this is good
I wonder if they have a smaller size
I think this would be cute for a kid to wear
Although being cool is better
Staff: If it was a smaller size it would look different
This kind of thing is good, see?
Right?
That's nice, that's good
Staff: What image do you have of him?
Fuku-kun is, umm
not really, how do I say this,
not concerned with fashion
He's more interdedted in his youth
Interested?
Oh, that's nice, this is nice!
This is good
How much is this?
Expensive!
17,000 yen (~$170)
That will hurt if I lose
I really want to win Fuku-kun over
We have smaller ones with this design
You can match the vibe of your model
This kind...
What about this kind?
It's sort of ...
It's not right for Fuku-kun
I think giving high quality sunglasses as a present,
will make a fantastic present
I see, I see
"Will he find the perfect sunglasses for Fuku-kun?"
He's a middle schooler, so something slightly more mature
Suzuki Fuku-kun ....
Will probably suit him
But I need to take a risk here
I can't just play it safe
This is pretty fashionable right?
This is good!
This is good
This is really good
I will get this for him
"Matsumoto walked the most while searching for his gift"
Junior...
"He's having trouble finding an item that suits the image"
This is difficult
"Matsumoto continues to search the mall"
"Did he find a suitable item?"
"Like always, Fuku-kun can take home his favourite item. The person who bought the worst present must pay for it himself!"
Time to present a top that Fuku-kun might like!
Was anyone unsure of their choice?
I think I got something good
Can I go first?
Go ahead Yama-chan
A different order than usual
OK here I go
OK, Fuku-kuuun
You rotting storyteller (Rakugoka)
Who the hell is rotting?
Cause he's balding
Who the hell is balding?
Don't say that with your voice
Here you go Fuku-kun
Thank you very much
You'll definitely like this
Fuku-kun, please take a look inside
Wow it's like, really cute
he said cute right?
This is cute right?
That's really sticking out
It's kinda...
Well for us its,
We're not so sure about this
It's fun!
Fun?
It's fun right?
Is that like a pocket or something on the front?
Maybe it's fashionable?
It's fashionable right?
That's not a pocket or anything
It's just there as the tongue
It feels like something you pick for someone you hate
It doesn't feel like that!
It does
It doesn't, right?
It feels like we started off negatively
Fuku-kun could you try that on?
"Next, the top Tanaka chose"
I asked my children for advice,
My two sons helped me out
Oh really?
They are in 1st and 6th year of school
I think they understand what Fuku-kun would like
And you guys buy clothes normally right?
Yes exactly
That's cheating! I don't know about this!
You're such a goddamn cheater!
That's not cheating!
Biggest cheater in Yoshimoto!
Give it to him already!
Yes of course sorry
This is cool!
The size is kinda big
Did you hear that? He said it's cool
I see, something for Fuku-kun to grow into
Try it on, try it on
It's a bit big
The size is important right?
Yes
I don't like the loose fit
This colour preserves some of the childlike cuteness
Turn around Fuku-kun
Show us the back please
There's nothing on the back
Yeah there's nothing
But ...
It doesn't suit him!
It does! It does
It says "Suit You"
Cause it says that
He looks like a Kansai Electric Railway worker
He does right?
I thought Fuku-kun might need something "wild"
"Third is Hamada? Just what will he present?"
This is similar to Tanaka's
Oh, OK
Cause he's in middle school
A bit of a mature Fuku-kun
In a way,
Yes exactly
Something similiar to my style
Something like your style
What does that mean?
Don't think that would suit him
Woah what's this?
I see
Cool!
I see, it is similar to Tanaka's
Yes, yes
They have those ones that say "Fuku" right?
Oh yeah
I wish he got one of those. This is kinda ...
Yeah but like,
This has that grown up look
There were cuter designs than this
I kinda don't want Fuku-kun to wear this
Why the hell not?
It doesn't suit him
It does!
That's supposed to be today's theme
That's no good, no good
You don't need to wear it so formally, you can like do this
A little looser
That kind of style
That's so Hamada!
You should walk like this, yeah exactly
If you walk like that they'll, steal your lunch money!
If you wear it like this it looks cooler
I guess so
Wear it like this in Summer
"Next up, Matsumoto's top presentation"
I sort of,
That's a childish bag
We had a more mature image right?
Fuku-kun doesn't want that sort of thing-
What is that?
What is that? (x 2)
It's a funny T-shirt
It's funny!
This is honestly,
so lame!
Don't say that sort of thing!
This is embarassing right?
This is embarassing
My 4 year old son has the same thing
It's so good!
So tight!
It's so nice!
Fuku-kun you're allowed to get angry!
C'mon try putting your hands in your pockets, that's the best part
But he doesn't actually have any!
Yeah that's what the funny part is, everyone will laugh
"Yeah I guess - OH SHIT" you will say
This makes you laugh
It's decided then, right?
Yup
He has the worst gift
He actually likes it though
What do you mean he likes it?
We don't know yet
"Finally, Endo's top presentation"
Fuku-kun loves baseball,
The Hiroshima Carps in particular, right?
Using that information is cheating
I knew that already
Red!
Yes
Hell is that?
You're kiddng right?
An entertainer? (TV hosts wear this kind of jacket)
This suits him right?
It's like that show
Scary scary, I'm trembling
Endo this is terrible!
Just try it, try it on
The Hiroshima Carps, right?
This is a bit too...
Yamagami Brothers! (comedy duo)
It's that Tejinani thing! (same duo)
It isn't!
He's an Asakusa person (red light district)
Not at all!
A night club host
It's kinda,
It's something to wear with this kinda shirt
Yeah it's a more formal loo-
But that aside,
look at his sleeves!
Yeah look at his sleeves
You'll get bullied if you stick your arms up!
Those sleeves man...
I guess he'll just be choosing from these ones
No no, just pick the one you like
OK
Your favourite one
He needs a bowtie
"Which of these is his favourite top?"
Fuku-kun, listen,
This is more depressing than you'd think
Exactly, exactly
For us
That can't be helped
Cause we put in genuine effort
With that said, here we go
Which is your favourite?
The one you're taking home
Which one are you taking home?
This one
Of course!
Of course
Black and gold,
I like this black and gold colour
I see, the colour was good
Well I had a feeling I wouldn't be 1st
I kinda had that feeling
Who is in 2nd place?
This one
Obviously!
Yeah, that makes sense
These two both have sons
They're similar in age
Fuku-kun you liked that one?
Yes,
Something to wear when I'm hanging out with friends or family
This is the best for that right?
OK Fuku-kun, there are three left
The 3rd place
Who is 3rd?
That was close!
Last place is...
I really don't wanna be last
"Which is his least favourite top?"
Fuku-kun,
Last place is either one
Do you understand my position in the entertainment industry?
There he goes again
Don't say that!
I'm a pretty important person
With that said, last place is ...
"With that said"?
I really don't wanna be last
Go ahead
That makes sense right?
That is garbage
I don't get it what did I do wrong?
Please tell us why it sucks
I like the Carps, and the colour red, but
It's just,
OK to be honest
It's pretty uncool
The colour and design suck too right?
It's sort of ...
"Endo must pay 4,999 yen of his own money! (~$50)
Time to present a unique item that suits Fuku-kun
"What unique item did Hamada pick out for Fuku-kun?"
OK I guess I'll ...
Please go ahead
That's huge!
That bag is kinda scary
That size is kinda-
It's something illegal
Who cares about the bag!
It's what inside
Woah what's that?
Thank you very much
This guy's such a cheater!
That's cheating man!
Fuku-kun stop that elated smile!
You're such a cheater man!
It's like he saw Santa Claus!
That's no good man, that's cheating
This is great for a middle schooler,
He's an actor after all
If he can buy that then,
I should've bought a PS4!
Exactly!
If you can't fit them now, you will grow into them later
It will be perfect
They're pefect!
They're perfect?
Perfect?
See?
Super cooooool!
"Next up is Tanaka, after the top, will he be able to win him over?"
I got the vibe that Hamada-san was going for
So just like with that jacket?
Yes exactly
So with that in mind, Fuku-kun please take this
He is a father to sons ....
What is it?
What's that?
Ah that sort of thing
Yes they're sunglasses
Not sure about this
Oh that's no good!
What's with that?
I hate this boy!
I tried to get a size for kids of course
But like he said earlier,
Fuku-kun is sort of between the teenage and child look so,
So this colour is a bit cuter
No that's-
That's no good
It's like C-C-B (80's band)
Yeah it looks like CCB
No, no, no
"Next up, Matsumoto's unique item presentation"
Fuku-kun to me is more uhhh
a more fun kid
So I don't want you guys to give him that more mature look
Yeah but he's in middle sch-
You're kidding right?
Amazing!
He's in middle school!
What happened?
Just what is this Matsumoto-san
He's in middle school!
What are you doing to Fuku-kun?!
Hold on, hold on!
Isn't it super adorable?!
No nono no no
Today's Matsumoto is in bad shape!
A shark! It's a shark!
What happened?
It's a shark!
You wanna hurry up and take that off right?
It's OK! Take it off!
Next up is Sadam Hussein's unique item
You guys have just been giving him things to wear on his head
That's not right, what he need most right now is this
I wonder what it is
"I wonder what" he says
Rhino
I'm gonna be sick
It's so realistic
That is sickening!
A decapitated head!
A rhino's decapitated head!
This does not suit him!
No need to vomit
It's rotting isn't it?
A decapitated head?
That looks super good Fuku-kun!
You'll become popular!
Where the hell did you find this?
You'll become so popular!
You seriously think he's gonna take that to school?
It's fun and trendy!
The mouth opens
Yes yes exactly
Well it does open but,
If you forget to close that everything will fall out!
"The guy who bought the worst top, Endo's item is next"
Just like Housei-san, I went for a bag
You're gonna go to middle school so,
I think a fashionable bag is something nice
Thank you
Open it please
A bag is difficult
I think this is good
It might turn out like the last thing
Woah what is this?
"What is this"...
He said "Woah what's this?"
What is that?
It's surprising right?
You just picked that out of the trash right?
The bag it came in is better
The packaging is better!
This one is better!
No this is better!
You just picked that up somewhere!
It's so raggedy!
This one is definitely better
No no no listen this one
It looks like a paper bag, it looks cheap but the inside-
You just said it looks cheap!
At first glance,
but the inside is well made
Isn't that a croquette wrapper?
No it isn't-
Those brown paper bags
For croquettes
That really is a croquette wrapper
It just looks like that!
So funny right Fuku-kun? A croquette wrapper!
A giant jumbo croquette wrapper, right?
So funny right?
"Which of these unqiue items is Fuku-kun's favourite?
Last place is between Matsumoto and Endo again
No no no I-
If you think about it, boys love animals
Boys love rhinos after all
Rhino?
Wait no!
Then it's gotta be Housei-san
OK Fuku-kun please stand behind the table
Which one is 1st place?
This one
Of course it is
So unfair
They're super cool!!
Right? They're so cool
Perfect for middle school
Is he your secret child or something?
Which one wins 2nd place?
Us two again
Another 1 - 2 for us
I guess after all, it's the guys who have raised boys who win
After all
Yes exactly
Our kids ask for this stuff
When they get a little older, right? Stuff like sneakers too
Yes, yes
We were at a disadvantage
So here we go,
Who is 3rd place?
This one
Oh that one?
Exactly Fuku-kun, thank you!
I don't wanna lose to this
It's interesting, and I like the realistic paper look
Well that one looks like a realistic rhino!
And this is a realistic shark!
"Housei's rhino bag, or Matsumoto's shark hat, which is worst?"
(skip to 22:35)
(recap)
I can get you blacklisted from lots of TV shows
Cut that out, Matsumoto-san
That's amazing
Fuku-kun, please select last place
Seroiusly?
Which one do you want the least?
Your least favourite
FUKU-KUUUUN!
You're joking, Fuku-kun!
FUKU KUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUN!
Why is that last place?
It's kinda ...
Try it on again please
Seriously why is that the worst? I think it really suits him
The teeth ...
It looks so good on him!
Why is this last place?
It's too cute, right?
For a middle schooler, right?
It's kinda,
It's warm, which is good but,
It's warm
They'll make fun of you with that on, right?
Exactly
And there's no occasion to wear this
You're right
Maybe I should stab Fuku-kun?