A town the 5 have never been to, Sakura in Chiba Prefecture, around Shizu Station
What are the Best 5 things the locals recommend?
First, number 5
A curry store
A popular curry shop in front of Shizu station, Sathi
Chicken and Shrimp curry, a delicious dish you must try at least once
It's delicious
Yeah, it's not too spicy either huh?
The flavour spreads in your mouth
This one might be better
See!
Next a suggestion from a young mother, South Yukarigaoka Park
They got excited after seeing the lion and giraffe statues
Furthermore,
Aqua
What is Aqua?
An elementary student's #3,
Aqua, a facility with a pool and a bath
Will Aqua be able to take the #3 spot?
And will they be able to get all 5?
Subbed by senor_wristband
Patreon: patreon.com/senor_wristband
Kofi: ko-fi.com/buresurettosan
The 5 leave South Yukarigaoka Park, and head towards the elementary student's suggestion, Aqua
It's totally possible, for example DownTown-san to be the first celebrities these people have seen in real life
Or us, the Gaki cast
That's pretty amazing I think, meeting the Gaki cast,
Tanaka who was the first celebrity you met?
Inagawa Junji-san
Same, same
We saw him together
That's amazing
We met him on a location shoot
Was it something like Kaidan? (one his movies)
It was when he got struck,
Ah back then?
I wonder who it was for me
Who was it?
I think, I didn't run into someone in town,
But honestly, probably at Umeda Theatre I think
The car arrives at Aqua
What kind of facility will Aqua turn out to be?
This is it right? Aqua
Indeed
Well we found Aqua, but we don't know if we can bring the cameras inside
Go inside and check
As there are a lot of guests inside day, bringing the cameras inside would be a bother,
Cocorico went inside by themselves to check things out
Then I guess we have to ask around if there's anything nearby
But this place looks like it could be #1
I think surpassing this will be difficult
Certainly
How'd it go?
The bowling alley had 30 lanes,
30 lanes?!
It was huge
There were billiards, a game centre,
And the first floor was a bathhouse
It's a massive leisure centre right?
Yes
It's a place kids would enjoy
This place, Aqua Yukari, has 30 different types of bathhouse, and an indoor pool. A very varied facility.
Furthermore, there are 30 bowling lanes, and a game corner
A popular leisure centre, that young kids and old people can enjoy
Aqua was selected as Shizu Station's #3 recommendation
Next, to find #2, they ask around in front of Aqua
Let's ask that lady
Ah, excuse me Ma'am
Could you help us out?
Hello!
We're looking for things near Shizu station,
We're asking people for recommendations,
We've asked a bunch of people,
What is this lady's recommendation for #2?
You can also recommend an old man you fancy for #2 if you'd like. We'll go meet him.
Your house could also be #2. We'll head there too.
Maybe a new building that was built recently, a nice place you'd recommend
Ma'am, where do you go usually?
The bank, or the post office
Of course, that makes sense
I don't really know
That's alright Ma'am, thank you very much
Thank you!
I think we've reached the limit
I guess it would be this place
In the end, there's no #1 or #2
We can't decide that yet
Let's try asking some young people
Oh yes
Excuse me young man
Young man, do you have a moment?
Could we talk for a moment?
I'm not good with TV...
You can't?
What about that middle-aged person?
Shall we?
Let's go
Excuse me
Could we talk to you a moment?
Are you a local?
We are locals,
We've come to this area for the first time,
We were thinking of going to Shizu station's Best 5,
A place you recommend more than these
A place for #2
Is a restaurant alright?
Anything is good
A local couple, what is their recommendation for #2?
Was it called Yoen? That place
Ah, Yoen is a good place
Yoen?
On the other side of the station, it's a Chinese restaurant
It's very delicious
Yoen?
Ma'am, do you have a recommendation for there?
I like their Black Vinegar Sweet & Sour Pork
Black Vinegar Sweet & Sour Pork? Sounds great
We all like Black Vinegar Sweet & Sour Pork
And sir, your recommendation?
Cantonese Noodles
Cantonese Noodles?
The Gyoza is good too
The Gyoza is good too?
We got lucky here then
The Gyoza without Soy Sauce
Gyoza without Soy Sauce
Without Soy Sauce?
No sauce
You eat it without Soy Sauce?
Gyoza sounds good
It's good eaten plain
By itself?
Thank you very much!
Thank you
Thank you for #2
I think a food place is great at this point
I think so too
However, now I think finding #1...
It's gonna be pretty hard
Indeed
Not exactly a park, but maybe a place with a good view
Something like that
I see
Perhaps a place to see the sun set
Exactly, exactly
I see
With haste, they head to the recommended Chinese restaurant Yoen
Alright, now Endo...
Was it called Yuen?
You don't remember the name?
I do, Yuen
Wasn't it Yoen?
No it was Yuen
Oi Endo!
Sorry
Endo meant to use the blinkers, but put the wipers on instead
He drives a foreign car, he's used to left-hand drive
Right?
He's trying to say "I drive a foreign car"
He's trying to show off
He put the wipers on after all
What do you mean?
The stalks are reversed on a foreign car
He put the wipers on
"I drive a foreign car" he wants to say
No not at all
"Tanaka, I drive one"
Tanaka has one too
I drive an import too
The used Volvo
TN: Tanaka drives a Volvo 240 wagon (Introduced in 1974)
Eh?! You still drive that?
It's almost 40 years old
You're kidding, Tanaka!
Wait, seriously, why?
You're still driving that Volvo?
Hold on, what's wrong with that?
I'm sorry for this cliche question, but a Volvo?!
No no, it's in great condition
What do you like about it?
I like the shape,
That boxy shape
There's so many other boxy cars out there
I don't understand what's so shocking about it
No no no, I think you should make a lifestyle upgrade
You probably can't replace the engine
Yes, I think it's probably impossible
While they were making fun of Tanaka, they arrive at the Chinese restaurant
Will this store get the #2 spot?
It's the first time I've seen this character
I can't read this
They're not open yet
Ahh I see
They're closed, they open at 5:30
They start at 5:30
Unfortunately it was out of their business hours, they couldn't enter the store
Starting again, they start asking for #2
Ma'am, could you tell us a recommendation near here?
A recommendation near here
What will this lady that has lived here for quite a long time recommend?
I've been here for 15 years
I live there
That's quite a while
Oh my!
Matsumoto-san!
Oh yes hello
Can we go to your house?
What the hell are you saying!
So angry all of a sudden
That's so sudden
She got angry so quickly
I thought your house could be #2
I don't really know any places to recommend
Oh you don't?
Thank you very much!
I guess it can't be helped if there really is nothing
That's true, for real this time there's nothing
Normally people wouldn't have to think so hard about it
There's nothing here then
Hello!
Excuse us
Right now, we're looking for recommendations near the Shizu area
We've been here, these places from #5 to #3,
Do you have a place in mind for #2?
What will this local young man suggest?
Izakaya Hamasen (Izakaya is like a pub)
An Izakaya?
Are they open right now?
Right now? I think probably starting at 5
I see, I see that makes sense
Any other places?
I would've said Izakaya Hamasen
Hamasen and Hamasen?
A location of some sort, some place we should check out
Joza Park
Joza Park?
Is it close by?
It's a short drive
Joza Park
What's over there? A nice view?
A nice view
Is there a hill of some sort there?
Yes
That's great!
We can see the view from up there?
Ok Ok, let's go there
Joza Park
Shall we head there?
Yes
Thank you very much
They drive to Joza Sogo Park, recommended for #2
It's wild, their waving to us this whole time, it's just,
We just don't know what to do
That does happen
I mean I've already waved to them once,
I can't keep waving this whole time
And I guess I'll wave one more time at the end,
But this awkward wait is a lot to endure
Right? This traffic signal won't change at all
The girl in the middle is still waving
I don't think she saw that
Indeed, it seems she didn't
But really, Endo,
You're becoming more selfish each year,
I am?
Well I do get fed up sometimes
There's a lot of rumors flying around
Because of today?
There's a lot of people who say "Next time I meet that guy I'm gonna smack him"
Me?
Eh really?
But that boy definitely hates Matsumoto
I wonder what that was, it was really something
It was really something
He really thought you'd steal it
There's no way!
He's gonna tell his mom about it
He did think that
There's no way I'd do that
His dad bought it for him
Just think about it. That kid was pretty big too
I hope this works out
Right?
A good view would be great
We could take a picture with everyone
Exactly, that would be nice
They arrive at the park. Will this make it to #2?
It's so spacious!
This is pretty big
This is better than the last park we went to
Right? That's good then. That's good then.
There's a statue there
Oh yeah
We gotta check out that statue
I think we should head over there
A statue we should check out
This thing too, what is it?
It's a measurement thing
Forward Reach Measurement
Looks interesting
This a device that measures your forward reach while sitting down
You can measure your body's flexibility by pushing the two pucks forward
The 5 try it out. First off is Matsumoto
I think I can go all the way actually
Matsumoto-san is the most likely to do it
I think so too
I can do this I think
Wow
Oh wow
Damn really?
There's just a bit more left
Oh you can do it
He did it
He went all the way
I see
That's the max
Amazing!
Hamada-san?
Why me?
I can't stretch like that I said
Alright do it
Do it
Ready, steady,
Hamada-san do it for real
No, that's not right
I think you should do it for real
The tips of your fingers
Can I use my fingers like Matsumoto-san?
Yeah totally
Exactly 34
There's a batsu game for this
A batsu game right?
Alright, ready, steady,
He passed 40
That's not right
He was so desperate
No need to be that desperate
What do you think? Well he did do it
Here I go. Ready, steady,
Endo did the same as Hosei, 43cm
Tanaka
Tanaka takes the challenge last
Well you do have the reach
Do as much as you can
Ow!!
What happened Tanaka?
A cramp?
Yes, I cramped up
You didn't say you were gonna start
What happened?
This kind of stuff is scary
Is this your first day?
Next year is your 25th, c'mon do it man
This is scary, this kind of thing
That's what we don't understand
My back, I feel I'm gonna pull it
Is this your first time doing a location shoot?
He's done quite a few
Are you nervous?
Just say "Here I go!" and do it gently
I can't do it gently, I'm scared
That's fine
Just do it slowly then
Can I not do this?
What happened?
I'm scared
I'm scared-
Just do it, we're all having fun
Join in the fun with us
I want to, but I'm scared
Yeah so just say "Here I go!" and do it
Do it slowly so you don't get hurt
Say "Here I go"
I'll say "Here I go"
Just hold on please
I might pull my back
What the hell is this
No really, I-
We're not trying to pad the footage here
Your back hurts right?
Did you pull something?
It's cause your back hurts right?
I'll do it, I'll do it. I'll do it but,
He didn't say anything
What was that, pushing it forward with one hand
You flicked it forward
You really are a goddamn cheater
Such a cheater, really
You can't flick it forward
Tanaka's cheating nature aside, they set out to search for the hill top view,
There's no view point
We can't go up?
We're not going up?
So it's this view, this is the view
It's a nice view though
Well we're already here
There was no view point, but they had fun with the measurement device. Jozo Sogo Park takes the #2 spot.
Finally time for #1
Lets ask around
Let's go there
That's the only place
There's young people after all
Should we ask those young people?
Hello, do you have a moment
Do you have a moment?
Right now we're asking for recommendations near the Shizu area,
And we've gotten up to #2
Up to #2
So for #1,
Yes, finally #1
The #1 recommendation in the Shizu station area
What will this local high school baseball club suggest for #1?
Something that comes to mind?
My house
Do you have a big house?
No not really
We can come over?
Probably yes
Let's go then
Call, call home
This is for #1?
But he's the one who said it, he said his house
What-kun?
So Saito-kun's house is #1?
In the Shizu station area
Alright, alright then
Ask if it's alright
Saito-kun's house is #1 huh?
Have you been there?
I have
It's a normal house
A normal house huh?
It's not like a huge family is it?
It's a normal household
But since Saito suggested it...
He said it himself
Maybe there's something we should ride on
Oh yeah
Maybe there's some famous thing we should ride
Normally what do-
Eh what'd you say?
The monorail
The monorail?
Nobody said anything about the monorail
Nobody said anything
They said "No Good!"
What'd you tell them?
What do you mean?
You suggested it yourself!
Who said NG?
Who? Your mom?
What'd she say?
The reason?
"We can't really do that"
I'm so sorry
How did you explain it? Maybe the explanation was bad
I told them they're looking for stuff around Shizu station,
And I said "They're heading over right now"
And then?
"NG! NG!"
Saito...
Well it can't be helped if she refused
What did you say? Did you tell them who's coming?
I said DownTown-san
Maybe she refused because you said DownTown
Maybe she thought we're gonna mess everything up
You said it before, what should we ride?
Monorail
Monorail?
Well that's it then, it's gotta be the monorail
We'll head to the monorail now, but if that doesn't work out,
Even if we have to break in, we'll go to Saito's house
Indeed
What kind of house is it? A normal one?
It's normal
A normal house?
What's your mom doing? Making dinner?
Probably
She's making dinner right?
That's ....
Saito-kun is losing the will to live each minute!!
They head to the station nearby to ride the train Saito's friend suggested
Well this time,
This was a total failure,
A total failure?
A total failure
Nobody will want to come here
Well it was a nice town, it was real
Well there were some nice moments
The car reaches the station
They looked up the schedule,
It'll arrive in about 4 minutes
Will we make it?
The next one is a 20 minute wait
Really?
It's here, are they getting on? It looks like it
3 more minutes
3 more minutes?
We can make it
Will this train make it to #1?
The 5 have arrived at District Centre Station to ride the Yamaman Yukarigaoka Line
The camera can't be taken into the train, so the 5 will ride by themselves
Here we go
It feels like it's been a while since I've done this
There it is, right on time
Are they filiming from outside? Ah there they are
Their train arrives at the next station, Koen Station
The 5 were giddy with excitement over the Koala's on the side of the train
The #1 recommendation by the locals of the Shizu station area, the Yamaman Yukarigaoka Line
The Yamaman Yukarigaoka line is a new transportation system opened 34 years ago
The train goes around 6 stations in 14 minutes, and is loved by the locals
With this, Shizu station's Best 5 is completed!
How was it? #5 to #1?
#5 to #1,
We've completed it
How was it Matsumoto-san?
Yes, this was a total failure
We're not saying this town is bad, just this episode wasn't very good
It's not that rural either. I think a more rural town would be better.
It was a large town
We wouldn't really get an opportunity to ride a monorail, if it wasn't for this episode
A precious experience
What town will we head to next?
Will we be able to?
This series, right?
Let's do it again
I wanna do this again
You want to do this again?
I do
Tanaka likes this more than I thought
Yeah I wanna do this
You know the view we saw after getting off the monorail was the best one today,
But we couldn't bring the camera with us, that was the worst