The Freeze King Grand Prix!!
- Good evening.
- We have held various King Grand Prix.
The Anger King, the Stomachache King, the Slept with Chris King, and the Takashi Impersonation King.
- This time, we have the Freeze King, the fifth stage.
- Yes!
- Now you were frozen, weren't you?
- Did you know that I was frozen for a moment?
This is what they are going to do today.
What are the rules?
The rule is how to freeze without getting caught!
- This is the ONLY rule this time!!
- I see.
- Do you understand?
- Of course.
- They will compete in this.
- What do they have to do at the end?
When the challenger says the phrase
“That was (their name)!”, the challenge is over.
I would like to shoot 9 episodes with this.
Matsumoto will now explain the judging criteria.
Will to Freeze.
“Hey, you freeze at this point!?”
“That would get you caught!”
- I want them to show that kind of bold spirit.
- If they do that, they'll be caught out.
Also, Not afraid of
having dry eyes.
“Aren't you afraid of dry eyes?”
- Like this?
- I want them to open their eyes.
Basically, no blinking.
They are not allowed to blink when they are frozen.
Time Being Frozen: The time the challenger was frozen
Soulless: To Freeze up as if one's vitality is drained.
unexpectedness: To freeze at an unexpected timing.
Matsumoto will judge these 5 sections.
Come on, first challenger!
I see, so Kinoshita is the first.
Hi!
- They say you are the handsomest man in this tournament.
- Really!?
That's an old standard, isn't it!?
[Subbed by RAIDEN 1017]
The man with the ever-changing face.
TKO’s Kinoshita.
Here we go!
His target is his mother, Sadako.
Will he be able to freeze confidently in front of her, who dotes on him as her son?
It's a good season to freeze.
This is the day it snowed the other day.
This is a nice place.
It’s the season when all living things freeze.
No way!
I hear the shabu-shabu at this restaurant is delicious.
He's a good son to bring his mother to a place like this.
- It's not often you get to be alone with your mom.
- I was nervous.
Cheers!
Does she drink beer first?
She's still drinking.
You've been on TV a lot, do you enjoy it?
I'm having fun. How do you feel about me being on TV?
- I think if you enjoy your life, you should be on TV.
- Is that so?
Does it benefit you that I'm on TV?
- F R E E Z E -
You look like a thumb!
You're caught by her!
- Don't get caught!
- I was just stretching.
- Oh, my back hurts.
- That's not good.
What do you think about TKO?
You guys even hosted one recently.
"Wow! Seriously!?" I thought.
You always send me your work schedule.
That's nice!
So nice!
- I like it!
- Are you listening?
Hey, she's asking you.
It's Ta-chan(his brother) on the phone.
Hi.
That’s nice!
Your mom is frozen, too!
Both of you are frozen!
Come on, speak up!
It's like two cowboys are facing each other!
20 minutes have passed since the start of the game.
Kinoshita, who freezes steadily, launches into a bold attack.
I was told by a junior colleague that you have an aura of back pain.
I was told that auras come in many colors.
The color of Kimoto's aura that the junior saw and the color I felt when I saw him were the same. So I can see the aura, too.
Huh!?
So I can see the aura, too.
- To whom?
- To anyone.
- Then, can you see mine?
- Yeah, want me to take a see?
He's a bad guy!
He can't see that kind of thing!!
This is a mastermind criminal.
Is it not done yet?
He can do this all he wants.
Hey, she is asking you!
He can do this all the time.
This is a bad guy!
Kinoshita, this is good.
He's changing his expression a little.
Are you really seeing at mine?
It's a little hard to see.
- What the hell!
- Nice tsukkomi.
- Also, I think I need to get a qualification.
- A qualification in what?
A massage therapist license.
That sounds good.
I could give you a massage.
It would feel really good. Are you stiff?
I'm always stiff.
I'll do it now.
He's a bad guy.
He's a really bad guy.
Oh, yeah. That feels good.
See?
- He's not doing anything.
- Press harder.
Hey.
Heey!
Are you sleeping?
Did you get caught by her?
That's the problem.
You don't have to do that.
Oh, nice.
Just press with your fingers.
I told you to press.
Press right away.
“Press right away.”
Not bad.
- He has a great strategy.
- Oh, he's doing it.
Press it with your thumb.
Yeah, that's good.
Press harder, please!
He scores a lot.
Press!
You're good.
It hurts! Don't do that!
- Don't bend my neck.
- I won't do that.
Stop right there.
Stop there!
Can you do a little more?
He's disgusting!
Don't overdo it.
That feels good.
Thank you.
It's okay.
That's enough for now.
You're doing it for me.
Gross!
"You're doing it for me."
Are you done?
It was TKO's Kinoshita!!
She's laughing so hard.
What are you doing?!
Kinoshita, your strategy was good.
I went behind her to rub her shoulders, taking advantage of the fact that we are parent and child.
You really thought that through.
I did his evaluation.
Now, Matsumoto-san, please show us his overall evaluation.
Here it is.
This is the first one, so this is the standard.
We have never seen anyone freeze for this long.
- There is no example.
- That's right.
Also, your mom froze as much as you did.
I wonder what that was about.
Come on, next challenger!
Thanks for inviting me.
Is that two Shochiku Entertainments (their office)
in a row?
You're wearing a bow tie.
I'm glad you noticed that!
Audience: Cute!
Yes, I'm a Happy Boy!
Wow!
Your “wow” isn't very sharp today.
That's because my neck is tight.
I borrowed a costume with a tight neck.
Happy Freeze Boy, here we go!
The two targets are juniors in his office.
Kuro-chan and Nasu-Nakanishi's Nakanishi.
Nakanishi's buddy Nasu joins him as his collaborator.
Hi!
The four of them are so close that they usually go out to eat together often.
This time, he called them up for a New Year's party.
I'm here first again.
- Okada-san called me, so I came late.
- Hey!
As soon as it started, Okada made his move.
You had a daughter, didn't you?
Has she become beautiful?
It's creepy when you say things like that.
Kuro-chan, don't you mind if she's your senior's daughter?
Because I might be able to get along with my senior more.
Is this a freeze?
Long! It's long time!
It’s long!
Kuro-chan doesn't know what to do!
You earned a lot of freezing time!
I have a lot of problems, you know.
What month is it now?
January.
It's the end of January.
Nice!
Great. No one noticed.
See, nobody noticed it.
No, they're noticing!
This is crazy!
You were frozen for a really long time!
It's long time!
I've been counting from January 1 to today.
Okada-san, do you have any jokes for us?
Do you have any extra jokes for us, Okada-san?
I have a joke I'm planning to do in 2012.
Please show us that.
The timing is too bad.
I leave my private life to chance too
An hour has passed since the start.
Okada made a request to the juniors.
I asked you guys to come up with a new joke for me.
- Are you going to give me something in return?
- No, I want another new one.
If I get a joke from Kuro-chan, that will finally...
- What would you like to order?
- What shall I order?
Oolong tea, please.
Hey, this will burn if you don't get it fast.
He hasn't been caught!
- He hasn't been caught yet!
- Ouch!
He was hot, but he was trying his best!
Think about it.
Okada-san's jokes always have the same tone of voice.
“Gyu” “Chu” “Wow”
It's all the same.
Okada-san is in danger if you continue like this.
From here you are going to start to get bruised very fast.
How old are you now?
I'm 43.
To be clear, I think your life expectancy as a comedian is up to 46 years old.
So it would be best for Okada-san to retire at about 45 years old.
You did a lot of things though.
Then you can become a legend.
So he has to find his new joke by the age of 45.
Yes, by the time he turns 45 you must find a new Okada.
Kuro-chan, think of a joke that will work for him for a long time.
How about this?
I'll take a picture...
Say, cheese! Bow-wow!
What do you think of this?
Nice!
This is long!
So long!
It’s really long!
Has he been caught by them?
- He still hasn't been caught by them!
- It's long!
So long!
Yeah, he must have hurt his eyes.
I feel sorry for myself.
You should retire at 45.
This year I have to gabve...
What did you say?
It was Keiichi Okada who was deteriorating badly.
Wow!!
I see.
My evaluation of your joke isn't very positive.
Let me see.
Here it is.
His Time Being
Frozen was amazing.
Also, he wasn't afraid of dry eyes in a smoky situation at a barbecue.
- His eyes were pretty open.
- I'm glad he was doing pretty well.
Come on, next challenger!
They're a duo.
Usually only one of you does this, but who did it this time?
This time we did it as a duo.
Doing it as a duo makes the freeze more solid.
A combination of filth and perversity.
Cocorico.
Here we go!
As a meeting for the duo's 20th anniversary show, they called their former manager Tachibana and show writer Horie.
First, Endo waits alone for his targets.
It's been a long time.
- Haven't you gained even more weight?
- Yes!
- How much do you weigh now?
- About 120kg (265lb).
Endo started to move.
Here is an old picture of me.
Oh, you are good!
This isn't Will to Freeze, but it will earn you Time Being
Frozen.
- You have changed a lot.
- Yes.
After this, Tanaka finally appears.
What kind of freeze will they really show us?
Hi!
- What the hell!
- Nice!!
Great!
I was going to do it from the beginning.
- You're already frozen?
- Yes!
- You've gained even more weight.
- I met you a month ago.
- He got fat.
- Yeah.
You've gained more weight since a month ago.
Cheers!
- I'm sorry for calling you guys suddenly.
- Don't worry about it.
We had an idea for our 20th anniversary show.
I'd like to have all of our managers from the past 20 years perform.
Is Endo freezing right now?
I did it while Tanaka had their attention.
- Next April will be your 20th anniversary?
- Yes.
This is crazy!
I'm getting their attention.
It's nice of you two to do it together!
Is this a clothing store mannequin?
- It's nice!
- Is this a United Arrows mannequin?
- Now they only see Endo.
- Yes I’m taking advantage of that.
This is possible because you are a duo.
Yeah, that's in May...
- Great!
- Tanaka, you earn points.
You look like a picture in a magazine!
You do it in a row!
You guys are not getting caught at all!
- Now I’m speaking.
- You have their attention.
It's a duo play.
- D O U B L E    F R E E Z E -
Double!?
This is awesome!
They're freezing too!!
They're all freezing!!
This is fantastic!
Who gets points for this!?
It was like a photograph.
Now that was very nice!
- Akasaka Play BOX is closed.
- Really?
You can earn a score on this one.
And...
It's a double!
This is a video, not a still image.
Don't do that too long or you'll get caught.
Yeah, that's right.
It's a long time!
The manager can wait, after all.
The hall is already closed.
30 minutes have passed since the start.
Cocorico, who is showing an exquisite combination, boldly freeze!
- Who did you take over from?
- It's Maehara-san.
- She smokes.
- Maehara smokes?
He's a good actor.
After all, he is a good actor.
It’s a double!
If one of you doesn't stop, you'll get caught!
That's right!
You guys have to alternate.
It's easy to do when you two do this.
I asked her, "Do you smoke, Maehara-san?".
And what did she say?
She said I've been smoking for a long time.
It's not that surprising!
If one of you doesn't stop, you'll get caught!
They continued to freeze after this.
They kept freezing one after another.
When was the first time you appeared on TV?
- Weeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
- eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeel ...
- He's freezing while speaking out loud!
- This is higher technique!
- That was 18 years ago.
- I see, it is not against the rules to freeze while speaking out loud.
- You ate a lot.
- Sorry.
Should we get the check?
It'll definitely be fun. So...
That would make them worry.
That will be so.
This is not a good freeze.
That's all,  it was Cocorico.
They won't know what Cocorico are talking about.
When one of us is speaking, their attention is on that person, so the other one can act more easily.
There were times when nothing in the room was moving.
- All four of them froze.
- Yes, everything stopped.
Here it is.
It's wonderful.
But when the two of them do it together, there is no more soullessness.
Yes, because one of us is moving.
This Double Freeze is a Extremely Freeze, so to speak.
Next challenger, come on!
Next week.
Freeze King Grand Prix Part 2!
The strongest challenger will freeze in astonishing fashion!
Next week, the Freeze King will be decided!
[Thank you to those who were inconvenienced]
What?!
What the hell is this?!
It's the Gaki's Freeze King GrandPrix.
Huh? What do you mean?
I don't want to meet Downtown like this.
We're here to freeze.
Really?
It was like a skit.
That's why I thought the two Cocorico guys were so close.
Do you hear something?
What?!
The camera was filming the whole thing.
Here's the camera.
Where!?
Here it is.
It's done filming.
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]