2nd time, Gaki no Tsukai Ya Arahende, Mixed rice
It's our 2nd time Matsumoto
Yama-san singing has crossed Japan rule
I understand how it feels
The song is stuck in my head and it's killing me
As we are talking I've forgot about it
Today is Mixed rice
Previous episode where we did Chawanmushi, Matsumoto's Montblanc got 10
I am grateful for that
I wanted to be success one more time, in this mix rice
There are more chances
I think I can do it
There is a lot of divergence because they are raw materials
~There are ways to look at you~
You remember it
First is Tanaka, what is his mix rice?
First is
Is this
Lobster?
Lobster will give seafood flavor
This one make a good Miso soup
Lobster rice will be good
Absolutely tasty
Whote lobster
Whote?
It's Whole
Every time you do this
You didn't say it entirely
Whote or whole
This one is perfect size, see
The whisker is jutting out?
There are 2
Twin
We will trim it
Water
He is taking a bath
This it is
What the heck is this
Champagne and high class grape
It's like Beer + green bean episode 2
That's right
Why are you opening it like that
Heipo caught it
As expected
He is catching with his life on the line
The alcohol of the champagne will be cook away just like before
What kind of Mix rice he is making?
It's kelp flakes, I see
The entire thing
I've tried it many time, it's delicious
Stink
I am putting soy sauce
It will taste like soy sauce rice
It compliment rice
This is ..
This
This might be delicious
Next dish
Next is this
Childhood memory
I don't know if it's still available, Choco stick, a snack
You decided to stop your specialty?
Is it frisk?
I've done my research, in this episode it's entirely bad
It is bad
It's like stop
Will changing the moisture change the outcome?
Next is Yamazaki, what will he put in?
Genius IT boy
Genius IT boy bringing you this
Nandenkanden
This is absolutely delicious
They are good to begin with
Everyone ate this before
Ain't it look delicious?
You tried before right? I really wish the president will be here
I really like the president
Perverted
Are you comedian?
There is not much comedian like that
I am getting a watch
And it will be Rolex
I want to eat this
Yamazaki next dish is Macademia nuts + milk , a snack kind mix rice
Next is Hamada turn
First is easy to make and normal Curry rice
Next is this
What is this?
Gross
What the hell
What the.. this is bad
This is sort of gross
*Grated yam with tuna
Yamakake*
Amazing
No need for that
This is wrong
It must be included
Appearance is important
Come on
The energy is kinda
Rough
At this point, i will add soy sauce
This guy have no sense of volume
But every time you always say delicious
Last is Matsumoto, what is his mix rice?
Well, this is nothing
Duel between ingredient
*Exquisite ham from Aomori
Nama Ham
The texture is amazing
Loin
Running
Keep on running, that is why
Make haste
The producer is laughing
It's frontier splits
It's splits?
Why splits in a japanese dish
Goes in daze
The taste is strong for the Nama ham
I have not seen this
I heard someone saying, this is the first time ever
Scary!!
Scary!!!!!
What is this
Its bear paw
This should not be allowed
It's scary right? The bear's paw
It's big
It's really big
Why does it make me want to touch it
Heavy
It's the first time
It really is bear's paw
The way to eat is first shaving it,
You can't even chew this
Maybe it will hold the rice in the paw
I am putting it
Doesn't fit
The entire thing
It fits way too perfectly
Put in some water
Oh, it's wine
Why?
Wine?
There is smell?
Ah, the smell
This is expensive?
How much?
70000 yen
Please
Expensive ingredient
70000 yen just for paw
*Act of bargaining
That 70000 yen is the result of this*
Put your hand like this
After preparing comes the tasting part
First is Tanaka's
It's different
It has changed
IT changed
Tanaka's lobster rice, how about the taste
It has strong flavor
It's lobster rice
I am opening it
It looks good
Nothing wrong
You don't know anything before eating it
In this case, I will take out the meat
This one does take some time
Looking forward to it
If you put in some soy sauce, it will taste better
With nothing more than a lobster, it will taste bland
Is that so?
Some salt is good
Nice comment
Genius IT boy
Genius IT man
You just stuttered
Gunius?
With miso it will be good
It really is
This one, seriously
Done
This is kinda hard to get
Seriously?
Let's eat
It's not that good
Why?
Tasteless
Why tasteless
Why?
Why like this
I even put lobster
It's like you taste it with the back of your tongue
What do you rate this?
This is bad
2 or 3
Yeah, 2
It is
2?
It's 2
It's 2?
It's just rice
If this is what family eat for once a year, nobody will attend it
Reason is this
For betraying everyone's expectation, 2 point
2nd dish, Champagne and High class grape how will it taste
I think it will look bad at first
It doesn't change much
The beer is cooked completely
It's a strong sour smell
It has such a strong sourness smell
Tanaka, this is bad
It looks like red bean mixed rice though
It really is, without some ingredient though
It has some good feeling to it
Everyone
Let's eat
Not good
I am sorry, but this is not good
BAD
Not good
How many point?
This one
It is still edible
8?
Are you an idiot?
Just by the look of it the taste is not good at all
*Skull and crossbone, dangerous
It's Dokuro*
This is not good
Dokuro
Champagne and high class grape as expected, dokuro
Next is Endo's dish kelp flakes rice
Opening now, open!
What the heck is this? What is this?
This is kind of nice feeling
IT is this
It looks good
Ain't it good?
This is good
I have expectation for this
Let's eat
Please, i beg you
It's not bad
I don't hate this
Delicious
Not bad at all
This is delicious
Tasty
This texture
Hamada, how is it?
I'm not really,.. it's delicious
This is delicious
Yes
It's not bad, but it does not reach the surprising delicious level
I personally think 5
Is it 5?
No,no,no
3?
Not dokuro
The taste is barely there
It is barely 3
Barely 3?
3 then
At worst 4 please
It's 3
It is 3
I am feeling pretty bad now
Based on Hamada feeling, kelp flakes rice 3 point
Next is Chocolate bat rice, how will it taste?
Can you score a homerun?
Let's do this, Open!
Amazing, what the heck is this?
Wait, what is this?
Interesting
Although, it doesn't look that bad at all
It's true
This is irritating
It looks like sausage though
At first glance right?
Let's eat
Why like this?
Bad
It is really bad
I hate this
I am feeling a dangerous vibes coming from you guys
This is not good
This makes me feel sick
The looks and the taste makes people irritated, chocolate bat rice 1 point
Next is Yamazaki's ready-made dish, Nandenkanden rice
Cocorico bring something bad
That's true
Nandenkanden is HERE
Looks good
No good, this will be very good
This smells good, smell of nandenkanden
I've done it
You did it
I've finally made it
Nandenkanden president
The president will be happy
Don't speak of your love here
He can buy rolex now
How good
For my birthday
You can also buy Driver
How i wish for it
Christmas is close too
Seriously?
Let's eat
It's not that delicious at all
Why is it?
Exactly why?
It's a bit spicy
Spicy
This is very spicy
It's the spiciness of the pickle
I kinda like this though a lot of different texture in here
At first bite
Not that bad
The spiciness makes you want more
Even though I am full, i still want more
At first bite I think it's not good, but after that I want more
I hate the pickle because of the spiciness but I like the taste of the rice
Kinda like that though
Because of that I would like a second serving
Edible but didn't bring the taste 100%, 5 point
Next is Macademia nuts rice, how is the taste?
What the heck is this
I've done it
You didn't succeed at all
Let's eat
What kind of flavor is the macademia nuts
Sweet
Truly sweet
Sweet~~
This will bring a bad feeling
Seriously what point does this deserve
Seriously i am thinking 1.5
1.5
I know it does not deserve 2 so the point for this is 1.5!
Sakai Masaaki
1.5
The overly sweet macademia nuts rice, 1.5 point
Next is Hamada with his easy-made curry rice, however
My first dish, Curry rice
At first look it looks bad
I will do this, mix this up
It smells nice
The smell of regular curry
Let's eat
I think I've mixed it up properly
It's not bad
This is not bad at all
*Not enough to stir reaction
However this one does not pack punch* at all
There is none
Hospital food
It's true
The flavor is not that strong
India's hospital
India's hospital will serve this to the patient
Not much flavor curry rice, 2 point
Next is the dish matsumoto afraid of, Yamakake rice
At first I totally hate this thing
This is what?
The bottom part should be the soy sauce
The moment you put this you should know it's bad
What bad, i have not mix it yet
Not good
Why?
Let's eat
Delicious
Very delicious
This is seriously delicious
Delicious
Tasty
Should be around 7 or 8
You decided it so quickly
Frankly speaking the tuna is good
The yam taste very delicious
This is good
This can be made at home
Do you have some sickness
It's amazing
Are you trying to say "Bring the miso soup"
The current best dish, 8 point
Next is matsumoto, his trusted Nama ham rice how will it fare?
It's what you guys are waiting for, nama ham rice, Open!
This is good!
How about the smell? Is it good?
The smell is ..
It's a pile
You can't separate them
Like this
That might be good
This is good right?
This one only have nama ham, no salt or any spice
That's right
Let's eat
Let this be good please
Since no one want to speak, I will comment on it
It taste extremely bland
The lobster rice still have a hint of salty flavor
If this is the lobster taste then I will be confused
There is no hint of ham flavor
The point for being bland is 5 right?
It's certainly not 5
The grated yam is delicious
What point will it be if i am the one who save you
If you are my Saviour?
If you are my Saviour
I wonder..
Don't stop being blur
Not reaching the expectation, nama ham rice 2 point
Final is the exquisite ingredient bear's paw rice
Actually this is what you guys wanted, let's do this
I don't want to look
Don't say that you bastard
Let's stop
I am using polite tone
Matsumoto 2nd dish is the sparkling bear's paw rice
Open!
Please wait
Nothing changed at all
No changed at all
How about the smell?
The smell?
It's the smell of the sake
Smell of sake?
Let's eat it
Are you serious
I can't do it
Let's Janken then
Stick out your paw
Look at it properly
Wait, I am just being blur
First, we need someone to taste it
The bear's paw rice leave a strange feeling in the air
It's not mixed rice at all
There really is no change on the paw at all
We cook it for 10 hours right?
I don't get what the taste will be
HEIPO!
Get a whiff of the smell first
This is good
He can do it
Looks great
Let's eat
That's quite
Mr.Heipo!
He put so much at once