Translated and Subbed by Colin Burdett
Contact at colinburdett54@gmail.com
Editing: euricaeris & Rylix
For the first time on Gaki no Tsukai Ya Ara hen De Chiki Chiki!
Put your life on the line with one bite and win 100,000 yen
Kiki Melon Pan!!!
Alright
Yes
Matsumoto-san
Yes yes
I said that this is the 40th Kiki
Wow
We've eaten that much food, huh
The last one that Matsumoto got correct was 3 years ago
A couple years, huh
Huhhh
My last one was around 4 years ago
So it seems
Endo got one last year
I got one only a year ago
You got one a year ago, huh
Last year
The last time Yama-chan got one
Yes
12 and a half years ago
The stakes have suddenly gotten higher, huh
The rules are simple
Out of the ten different choices
They must find the one that they ate
If they're right, they'll get 100,000 yen
Will anyone get the prize?
Endo might
What happened, are you okay Endo?
I'm fine, it's just that
I haven't had any sugar in 3 months
That's amazing
So, this is...
You haven't had sugar in 3 months?
Then, you haven't seen any of these unwrapped before, have you?
I've only seen commercials
The first challenger
The physically improved Endo
Having not eaten sugar in 3 months
Gunichi's Melon Pan
If you eat it, a sweet taste will spread inside your mouth
He's smelling
A nostalgic smell
It's really sweet
The smell?
The smell
This is really sweet
Melon Pan was this sweet?
That's enough of that
Talk about something else quickly
Aren't you tired of it
Wowwww, it's delicious
3 months since, huh
Delicious
It's really delicious
It's been 3 months, huh
I don't have your experience, but
This is so delicious
This Yamazaki Pan
Melon Pan
Thisss one, I
Wow, it has 11 grams of sugar, that's a lot
That's enough, really
A buttery consistency
It's usually buttery
It certainly was very buttery, I'll try this one
Remember the taste
Remember how it was
It's delicious, huh
It's delicious
That's pretty delicious, huh
It was very delicious, but the
surface was rough
It's wrong?
It was rougher?
How did it taste?
This Yamazaki Melon Pan was a bit more
Well, the butter was a little
Was a bit stronger
That was a hint, huh
Yes
The butter's consistency
The butter, huh
Butter
Mine was weak at first then it got stronger
Melon Pan
The one I ate was not Yamazaki's Melon Pan
Try as a might, I couldn't see myself having eaten that one
The surface had a bit of a rough feeling... This one
Gunichi Pan
KariKari Melon Pan
Here I go
Gunichi Pan
Swee... Sweet , huh
Here I go
Gunichi Pan
Yes
From Gunma Ken
Huh, isn't it the number one bread, Gunichi Pan
This one's delicious too
They are all delicious, huh
You can't just keep saying it's delicious
Really
Sorry
That's, that's true but, ahh
Ahh, it's wrong, ahh
This one's wrong
It was sweeter
This one wasn't as sweet
That time was different
Yeah, the one I ate had a stronger taste
The one I ate
Was not Gunichi Pan
Idiot
What an idiot
What's with that?
You were totally bankrupt
He was
He really was
Right
He's really mad
He's bankrupt
Scary
How scary
Wow, be careful
Your head's more hollow than bread
Gunichi
It was Gunichi, it was Gunichi
Yes
Did you know at all?
I had no clue, the first one I ate was too sweet
Since you haven't eaten sugar in 3 months, you wouldn't be able to tell
Wait a second, are you really....
Thank you very much!
If I said that the one I ate, is and isn't, for example
That's no good
No, no
Get 100,000 yen Kiki Melon Pan
Next up
4 and a half years since his last win
Is Hamada
Hamada's chosen bread
Pasco's
Sakufua Melon Pan
The exterior is soft
The inside is soft and strong
Will he be able to find this taste?
The mood is bad, huh
What are you doing now?
No
Sorry
Melon Pan is, uh...
The surface has different features on each sections
Yes
So what are you doing, then?
I'll eat it now
How does it feel?
Yeah, well, really
Well, it tastes like Melon Pan
It's not terribly sweet
While I was pressing it on my lips, I was thinking
It wasn't like these smooth surfaced ones
I think that its surface was different
Is this the same pattern Endo had?
Do you remember which one was Endo's?
Yes, this one
Ah, Gunichi
Well then, I'll start with Endo's Pan
It's soft
It's sweet
I wonder if Gunichi is sweeter?
Gunichi
I wonder if that's true
Ahh, this one's very sweet
It seems like it's sweeter
So it seems
This is completely different
I know that
This one's too sweet
The one that I ate
Was not Gunichi Melon Pan
It was different?
Yes
Huh, that's good
The one I just ate was way sweeter
I'll go with this one then, Fuji Pan
Fuji Pan
Fuji Pan, huh
The one I ate wasn't that sweet, but
This type of surface that's crisp, I'm not sure about
No
It was a little
less crisp
The one I ate
Was not Fuji Pan Melon Pan
Yes
He's cleared two
I'll do the neighboring Pasco
Yes?
It was softer, so why is this one so crisp
It's because I feel like this is it
Ahh, but then, you don't feel like it's wrong?
Yes
If I feel worried, should I just go for it?
Hmm, I wonder, huh
Hmm
Well, that's the problem here
Huh, so it seems
Right?
It's like choosing between grey, white or black
Right
They're all close
So it seems
Alright, it's been a while so I'll just go
I always throw it out and get it wrong, but today I'll just go for it
Ehhh
You turned right in the middle of it
What's up with that?
What's with that?
Wow, that was surprising, you really got me
Really
What are you expecting when you make a face like that
The one I ate was
Was Pasco Sakufua Melon Pan
Amazing
Seriously
Wow
Hasn't it been a while
Amazing, amazing
Thank you very much
Thank you
This is amazing
Wow, 4 years
Since it's been 4 and a half years since I got it right
Amazing
Amazing, that was amazing
4 years ago
Well, well, well
Wow, that's amazing
Yes
Can he follow up Hamada
Tanaka is the third to face the challenge
His choice is Okinawa Okiko Melon Pan
Will he be able to remember this taste?
Ahh, ahhh
Hmm?
What's up?
Well, it's pretty sweet
Of course it is
Wow, it's pretty sweet
Everyone said so, everyone said so Tanaka
It can't be helped
Everyone has been saying that
Everyone seems to be using their lips
But will he be able to remember it I wonder
Right
If he can, he'd be a master
Ohh, he's eaten it
Huh?
It's not like how it smells
What is it?
It's sweetness
"Sweetness"
It's sweet, it's sweet
Ok, firstly, the one everyone had trouble with
Yes
Gunichi Pan
Ahh
From Gunma
It's completely different
Maybe I can do this
Ehh, the one I ate
Was not Gunichi Melon Pan
How was it completely different?
Well... the one I ate
Was softer
So, Gunichi was more
Zaku Zaku
T.N. "Saku Saku" is soft
Huh?
Wait, wait, wait, how was it?
"Zaku Zaku?"
"Zaku Zaku"
What are you saying?
It was crisper
It was extremely crisp
Which means
The one I ate wasn't crisp
Maybe
Mine was softer
Tanaka, with his heightened confidence, clears two more
Huh, Okiko I wonder, Okiko
I feel like it will be different
It's wrong
No matter how I think about it, the surface was softer
No matter which one I pick, it tastes crisper
This one is wrong
You can tell the softness and crispness, huh
Yes, I can tell
The one I ate
Was not Kokashi Butter Fumi Melon Pan
Whoa, that was quick
Yep, that's too bad
That was so bad
Yep, too bad
I didn't think it was that one at all
That was bad
This is scary
Think with more zip
That looks like it hurt
The right one was this
It was that one
Okiko
It really was Okiko
You didn't know at all?
I had no clue
I'm really counting on you guys, I haven't gotten one in 12 and a half years
Next up, with the biggest drought, is Hosei
Should we go with the same one as Tanaka?
Let's
Huh, wait, what, if you do that...
Let's do it
Thank you very much!!
As they said, the same one as Tanaka
Okiko Melon Pan
The one they said they would choose
Will he get it right?
Yes, Okiko Pan
Did you really choose Okiko Pan for me?
Really?
We really did
I got it!!!
What do you mean by I got it?
"I got it"
I'm so happy!!
I really thought for my turn
That you would pick this one
"Yamazaki"
Ahh, so since Yamasaki Hosei and Yamazaki are similar
Oh, I see
I see
Yes
Uh, actually, I'm "Yamazaki"
Isn't it fine as is?
Huh?
Isn't it fine?
"Yamazaki"
But it really is "Yamazaki" and  not "Yamasaki"
We've always been calling you that though
Yama-saki
Since I'm from the Yamasaki's
Stop calling me Zakisan
I'm a Sakisan
I don't want to say Sakisan
How many years have we been calling him that
Right
Everyone's been calling you Zaki-san
Saki-san, Zaki-san you say
Right!!
Right?
Right
Wait a second, you said Okiko
I said Okiko
You're saying you picked Okiko?
Yes
That's what you said
We said
We did
We did say that
Stop joking around!!!
What's wrong?
He's emotionally unstable,huh
What's wrong with you?
That's wrong, isn't it!?!?
I don't know how he'd know either way
Right
You don't even know yet
Why don't you try eating it?
It's not Okiko is it?
The one you chose
I don't know about that
That's right, why not try eating it
What's with you
I don't know!!
Which one is it?'
From the soft ones
Huh? Okiko is soft isn't it?
Whoa, what do I do?
Wait a second
No, no, whichever one you eat, you'll know if we're lying
That's right
Thank you so much
I was really questioning your service
Whoa, this is my big chance
Which one is it, though?
Really
You really picked Okiko, didn't you?
He's done his weird switch again
He's all over the place
Is he ok?
Right
Is he O.K.?
This is a big problem
You said it was between these two
But did you really choose it for me?
Your head's messed up, it's messed up
It's this again, really
How many personalities are in your head?
How many?
How many do you have now?
How many, it seems like 3
How many are there
Right
But really, which one is it?
After all, there aren't any other soft ones
Did you really choose Okiko for me?
This soft
Did you choose a different type?
This is the only one
But...
I believe people are good
People aren't bad
Right
Okiko!!
Yes
So it seems
Did I pick the wrong one?
Again, yet again, yet again
It's this again
How many are there?
It's a different one, huh
Hey
Ahh, another
It's another one
He's good, huh
He hasn't done this one
It's the most foul mouthed one
The foul mouthed one's here
I picked the wrong one, huh
You almost had me, huh
T.N. Yamazaki's using Yakuza like grammar
You almost had me, huh?
Where did this... What is this?
How horrible
You almost really had me
What is this?
This did
That was close
You said you picked Okiko, but you picked a different one
This one's wrong
I believed, but
But you guys have betrayed me before
Therefore, you picked a different one
You can't betray me now
The one I ate
Okiko Pan
Was not it
Wow, it was Okiko, Okiko
We didn't betray you, it was Okiko
Okiko!!
Even though we really picked Okiko
We said we were picking Okiko
Even though we gave you the prize money
You picked Okiko for me?
Yes
Yes, we did
I'm so sorry
You said some hurtful things
Did I say hurtful things?
You said some bad things
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry
You made some comments
I wasn't being serious
I'm really sorry
You said we betrayed you
I'll receive my punishment now
I'm sorry, huh
What would he have said if we picked a different one
Huh, I wonder
Yeah
Don't have normal expectations!!
Have some more bang!! "Pan Pan"
For us, this is also a sad conclusion
This is kind of sad
That's true, this is pretty upsetting
Well, I'm really sorry
What should we do, he might switch
That's right, what did I even say?
Don't you remember?
That wasn't me, that wasn't me
Really?
I like everyone, after all
I, you know, have my own way of testing
The last challenger
Is Matsumoto
His chosen bread
Let's go with Okiko
Hamada-san?
Hamada-san
For real, Hamada-san?
To the contrary of what Hamada claims
His choice is Yamazaki Melon Pan
With its distinct line surface
Will he be able to find the taste?
We're giving you this, like Yamasaki
Yeah, well...
For real?
So it seems
This, what is this, what is this, I don't understand
You're the last one, huh
I really have no clue
It's kind of
Go ahead, Matsumoto-san
Please
This psychological warfare is cheap
It certainly is
What the hell is this
This has nothing to do with Melon Pan anymore
Wait, give me a second here
We gave you Okiko
Well, I don't know, huh
Wait, I have no clue
This is soft
Uhhhhhhhgh
I have no clue
Why did you pick Okiko again?
Why are you asking me?
This Okiko playing around
Is over
I think I understand...
You have no clue, do you?
Well, you know
Ahh....
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
You were betting that by showing me a soft one like Okiko
That I would think that it was another soft bread that wasn't Okiko
That's why when Hamada was saying it was Okiko
That Tanaka was saying "Ha-Hamada!"
Therefore
It's a soft bread that isn't Okiko
Therefore, the answer is
Is Dai-Ichi Sei Pan's Tezuzumi Melon Pan!!
This one, right?
This is the one
Right?
Ahh, well, wait a second
Wow, this is difficult!
You're so noisy
I'll try one that's completely different
Right, like this one
This one's definitely different
What's with you recently
It's not but it is
I don't know about the taste
Wait a second, is it this one?
Wow
%^&*#$!!
It isn't but it is
It is but isn't
Is it okay to say that this time?
What?
No, no, no
The one I ate
Is but isn't this one
No, you can't do that
That's bad
But it really is and isn't
This is and isn't
If I say it isn't and throw it out
And I end up getting it wrong
I will, absolutely
Start to hate Melon Pan
What's with this
I won't eat it anymore too
I might say that it might be this
The one I ate
Was not Yamazaki Melon Pan
It actually was!
I'm not stupid, I'm not stupid, I'm not stupid
You had it
That was amazing
Why aren't you going to the platform
You guys are dirty!!
That was really amazing though
You had it
The tape is coming off!
It's fine
It's coming off!!
Stop this, stop this!
Your punishment...
Stop this
You have to
You told me the wrong one!!
If you were so sure, why didn't you go for it?
Well, well, well, well
No, no, no
No
Please receive your punishment
It's still not over
It's not over
Please receive your punishment
All of
Melon Pan's
Sweetness
Is it that tiring
The point slid down