Gaki no Tsukai famous section: Shichi-henge
Bob Sapp
Chihara Kyoudai Seiji
Cocorico Tanaka
Cream Stew Arita
Hip-shaking Obachan
Kousei Sakka Ryuusen
Lots of experienced stars faced it before
Chihara Kyoudai Kouji
Cream Stew Arita
Director Ootomo
Fukawa Ryou
Kimura Yuichi
Manager Isomata
Some of them made us laugh and achieved honor
Some of them got mentally hurt and couldn't do it
Ameagari Hotohara
Cocorico Endo
Producer Suga
Shinagawa Shoji Shinagawa
Yamashita Shigenori
Yamazaki Hosei
This pressure, said to be what makes a comedian grow,
Director Tsutsumimoto
Kousei Sakka Takasu
Producer Nakamura
Is hard to imagine
And tonight Komoto from the sharp duo Jichokacho will challenge it
What will his true strenght be like?
First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
DOWNTOWN
MATSUMOTO HITOSHI - HAMADA MASATOSHI
"I won't let you say I'm young!"
Jichokacho Komoto (11 year into comedy business)'s Shichi-Henge!
11 years?
- That's right
And yet the atmosphere feels unusually heavy
Well it's... most times it's like this
How about our past scores?
As you can see, Bob Sapp is still our first one
I see
How will it go today?
- Who knows
Let's call him here, please
Thank you for having us
TODAY'S CONTESTANT: JICHOKACHO - KOMOTO JUN'ICHI - INOUE SATOSHI
Thank you
I often see them on tv
Yeah, that's right
His face feels weird right now
You know, now we're having this sort
of opening talk before it starts
And this whole situation
It kind of
Feels weird, doesn't it?
Come on
You can tell Yamazaki's envy for those
who are younger than him is a real deal
He's right
...or on patreon: patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Want me to bring you more Gaki no Tsukai / J-comedy translations?
read how to help me out here: tinyurl.com/shiontypeset
donations on ko-fi: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
like my FB page: fb.com/shionnotsukai
more Gaki & J-comedy on shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
translation & typeset by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Project meeting
What are we doing?
What should we do?
COCORICO (TANAKA NAOKI & ENDO SHOZO) - YAMAZAKI HOSEI
"Tanaka's premature baldness plan: expedition team for new hair growth"
SHICHI-HENGE RULES: Show yourself in different appearance during the meeting
Those who laugh by seeing it, will pay a 1000 yen fee
Oh, I see
Ever done this before?
Not even once
But feel free to do it anytime
Are you really sure?
When you get them wet they're so bad
Yeah I know
I mean
It's not even funny
Even the wind
SHICHI-HENGE: START
Yeah, that too
Water and wind are your enemies
Here, "Goodbye Yamazaki - This time for real"
No way, that's no good
What if you actually don't come here for like half an year?
No way
They'll think it's a farewell
Or else we could
Leave him here and the rest of us should leave
Is there anything to do?
Welcome to Umeda Kagetsu
PARODY OF RAKUGOKA KATSURA KOBUNSHI
I wonder if that guy is actually fine
I shouldn't have put him in charge
Man, I'm sorry
It didn't go as well as I thought it would
It went bad again?
- I'm sorry
Katsura Kobunshi (the real deal)
It's not my fault
- What the hell are you doing, man?
罰金 = fine (1000￥)
I put you in charge of this rakugo show, man, do it properly
But it's been so long since my last time I got nervous and---
No way...
- It'll go better tomorrow
As if I'm letting you have a tomorrow
- No please, wait
What are you doing?
Learn how to do it properly
Click
Beep
He didn't even say he's sorry, geez
That's unfair, teach
Apologize, man
Even if you say so, I mean...
Bunchin would have never done that
Katsura Bunchin, senior rakugoka
That was so unfair!!
Yeah, man
- That's playing dirty
Oh boy...
Not fair
You can't bring him here, come on
bottom text: All the money will be devolved to charity
Yeah, it was such a dirty move
What the hell, man
It felt like a skit for the finale, didn't it?
Yeah, that's right!
- But it was his first one
I actually met him before recording, in the tea house
Really?
- Yeah, just before
I was like "G--good morning!!"
Is that so?
He was like "stay calm" but I really wasn't
I sort of panicked
So sweet~
Hahahaha
So sweet!
Very sweet
"Sweet"
Come on, toss em in
It was your fault, Heipo
Yeah, your laughter
Just be quieter, man
WORLD FAMOUS HEIPO
Give us a break, please
- I'm sorry
It was so absurd
I think he was using it wrongly too
Everyone's showing an human appearance here so I can't tell...
Parody of famous manga "Gegege no Kitaro - Spooky Kitaro"
If only they would show me their spirit appearance...
Shit...
Kitaro!
Yes?
Listen, Kitaro
Between them there's a spirit which tormented me
Got it, I'll look for him
Yeah
Oh?!
It's him!
Ah! It's him! Go get him!
Take him out!
Beat him up!
PRODUCER - KENJI SUGA
Get him for good!
Come on!
We did it, Kitaro!
Thank you so much, Kitaro!
Let's go now
That kid had nothing to do with it
You're right
This is incredible...
What's going on?
This guy's great
- He choose Suga, we're weak to him
Even his face...
bottom text: All the money will be devolved to charity
You're right
He was right next to me, wasn't expecting it
I saw him so abruptly
Is there something to do?
I wonder...
They're here after all...
Kaori! Akko!
Come here
Unbelievable!
Here's Downtown
Incredible! They're the real deal!
Don't be loud, they always said it's
no good to speak aloud about private stuff
Can we get an autograph or such?
Do you really think it's ok?
I think that's one of the thing Hitosh--- Matsumoto hates the most
Ok but...
You said you slept with him, am I right?
You shoudn't say that aloud
Comedians hate so much girls who can't read the atmosphere
Hitosh--- Matsumoto always said that
But you said...
You got home with Yamazaki and Tanaka last time
But you were with us, Jun
Don't talk about stuff like that here
Hitosh--- Matsumoto said it's not good, really
I also remember last time you said you got home with Endo
For real?
You're wrong! I was just talking to him
Are we? But...
- You said that yourself, Jun
Don't be so mad at me, dude, that's what I hate the most...
He says "ore" (pronoun only used by males)
Come on, Jun-chan!
I told you before
You had sex with him?
- I told you not to talk about this
Hitoshi---- Matsumoto, I'll see you later
Make up your mind, dude
That was hilarious
He normally calls him "Hitoshi"
Even in public
And now it was "Matsumoto"
- Incredible
That's really impressive
This is amazing
- He also said "ore"
This is incredible!
- Amazing, look at this!
If he keeps up this pace, he might beat Bob Sapp
- Yeah, he can
It's Rai Rai Ken
First ramen-house enstablished in Japan (1910)
We have no vegetable noodle soup for ya to eat here!!
It's Rai Rai Ken
We have no sweet-and-sour-pork for ya to eat here!!
It's Rai Rai Ken----
There's none!
It's Rai Rai Ken
No, we're not a bowling
It's not a bowling place
Someone was faintly laughing all the way
It was the staff
Outside this office?
Come on, guys on the back...
It was funny how he gradually pronounced "Rai Ken" better
You noticed that? It was more clear as time passed
He wasn't sure about that character yet
- Must be that
(unrelated small talk)
He looks strong
- Yeah, I think he is
Excuse me
'Morning
I wanna beat Hamada up...
But I can't just do it
What should I do?
Should I ask him?
Oh, hello
Sorry to disturb you, and thanks
It's Komoto
Well, it's that...
I want you to beat someone up again
It's Hamada
From Downtown, yes
Nickname of Takahashi Teruhide, japanese actor
No, not "Shouei", it's Hamada, yes, sorry
Thank you, sorry for this
Oh, thank you
Thanks for coming
Hey, Hamada
Yes?
What have ya done to our Komoto?
What?
Have ya been
Fiddlin' around with his butthole...?
Mmnfff
Dontcha dare
Underestimate us Kansai people!
I'm sorry
Mppffg
Thank you
Sorry for the bother
So irritating...
Man...
He got you good
'Cause he came right at me
bottom text: All the money will be devolved to charity
His denture was moving all the time
It didn't seem attached
- It's like it didn't fit
Yeah, but it's expensive
(unrelated small talk)
I see...
Upsadaisy
This works just fine
The portable CD player is playing "Eccentric Shonen Boy" by Hamada
(from Gottsu Ee Kanji), but it keeps on looping its intro all over
Maybe if I touch it...
Just go away, geez
Woah, look at this
Woah, amazing!
- That's a lot
Incredible
It's really something
Do you think he made it?
Four, five... sixty thousand
It's 63'000 yen
JICHO-KACHO KOUMOTO JUN'ICHI:
TOTAL AMOUNT OF MONEY: 63'000￥
So he scored 63'000 yen
Incredible
And that means
He's now on first position
NUMBER ONE SCORE IN SHICHI-HENGE HISTORY
Oh, Teacher!
- Thanks for coming, teacher!
Translation & typeset by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
This guy... it was so unfair!
For more Gaki / J-comedy: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
I came without knowing what to expect
I have kids at home, you know
Like my FB page for updates: fb.com/shionnotsukai
You're at the top now, even above Bob Sapp
Donate to support this project on: ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
or patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Did I take the first place?
Yeah, it was incredible
I actually paid for all of them
Want to work on new episodes with me? Read here: tinyurl.com/shiontypeset
Really?
Yeah, I paid 7000￥
Also, the way Yamazaki glanced at him as he got inside...
Just quit it, man