This studio...
Isn't every room really cold?
I've had to start wearing long sleeves
This room was super cold!
That scared me!
Good morning!
G'morning!
He's smiling so hard
Such a beautiful smile
C'mon, you can tell what this is from this outfit
Could it be?
What day is it today?
It's September
Right?
What happens in September?
He has the same birthday as my son after all
You get it right?!
This month is Matsumoto's birthday
The date has passed us, however,
The Tokyo Olympics,
there were lots of events,
But there was one thing he thought was super cool
And that's what he wants for his birthday
The black masks have helped Matsumoto 8 times so far,
and helped him achieve his dreams
It started with the world record high jump,
And a 10 tier vault!!
And a miralulous skateboard trick
Batting a 150km/h ball!!
A new world record in weightlifting
50cm limbo dance!
Swimming 25 metres in 10 seconds!
And lastly,
The still rings challenge!
They've broken various records,
And now that he's 58 years old,
What challenge will he take on this time?
For now let's watch this
What is it that we're watching?
This
This (x4 at least)
This!
This super cool this
He wants to do this?
He wants to do an alley oop dunk
No no no no
But you guys will helo him out right
We do have some trust
Right
Let's get it over with quickly
It's his birthday right?
Let's go in these clothes
Let's change and go
Matsumoto's dream...
after 2 years,  a new record!
Matsumoto Hitoshi will do the Alley oop!
The big guys here, make sure,
Help put
It's quiet loud
It's pretty tall yeahhh
It's taller than I thought
GOOD MORNING
Good morning!
Did you tell them?
Yes I did explain,
He told you?
Even though I'm 58,
Don't I seem like a young person?
That feel
Did you explain it properly?
I did I did
What tone did you use?
What kind of tone?
You want us to help you do that trick
Sorry I didn't see the setup part,
But I heard through rumors,
Someone said "Let get this done and over with"
And according to Yanaoka, Hosei-san said this
Then let's begin, let's begin
Don't push me!
For now pick it him up, and go to the end
Alright, excuse me please
His feet
Ready, steady,
He's not putting any effort at all
He's not putting any strength in...
I wish he would try, it would be easier
His hand has gotta move
Let's put him down once
Hold on this won't work
Bring a mat
Yeah, everyone
We'll do it with this, we got this
He's not happy
When we're getting ready,
Why does he stand properly
He won't speak a single word though
Make him jump on the trampoline,
Jump using the trampoline to do the alley oop
And when he reaches the right height I'll pass the ball to him
Time it right please
At the right timing, here we go
This is good, we're in good shape
Bring him up to the bound here
Put his feet on it
His feet are on it
You gotta stand him up
His feet! Oh, isn't this good?
Like that! More!
Keep that up!
It's gonna work!
1! 2! 3!
My armpit hurts...
That was pretty...
That seemed pretty good
Did you hear?
When he stood here and went there
In a silent whisper,
"My armpit hurts"...
It was bright red
For real?
Someone pulled him from there,
Was it you?
Is he angry?
I don't think he would be angry
He just said it hurts
If he was angry he would've gone "AHH" just now
Let's go see, if he doesn't wanna do it anymore then...
That means we can finish this
Maybe he left cause he was satisfied
They head to Matsumoto's dressing room
Excuse me
Does this mean we don't have to do this anymore?
Who held my armpit?
Yes, yes
You took all of my armpit hair with you
You know, what is it, it's, fine,
I finally understand you have no intention of helping me succeed
That's not true
I UNDERSTAND NOW
That's not true at all
You had no motivation from the beginning
I SAID LEND ME YOUR STRENGTH
There aren't any senpais who have to insist so much like this, conversely
There aren't many senpais who ask for your strength, conversely
Grabbed my armpit hair and pulled all of it out
Would it be better without the gloves?
Think about that shit on your own
Why is a grown man like you
asking a grown man like me about gloves
Time for the 2nd attempt!!
Will this be alright?
It does seem like it'll work
This should be more comfortable for him
But either way-Oh, welcome
his mood has improved
Sorry, things got kinda...
I might have gone too far
I was thinking that unless we're all dedicated to this we won't succeed,
We definitely all understand each other
Except for Inomoto
Eh? Really?
He doesn't seem to like you very much
Let's do this, Matsumoto-san please come here
This is something we have to attach,
It would be best if he's on his back?
If you could lay on your back please, alright
Attach it
Here we  go!
Stop thuddign
Don't thud
His flesh is stuck!
He's gonna get blisters!
Yeah for real! This is bad
The shoulder, his shoulder,
Don't force it on
Did you do a simulation?
It's fine it's fine, we did
Inomoto did they do a simulation?
Do it exactly the same as the simulation alright
Once the preparation is done Tanaka and License' you come here
Which young man did the simulation?
The age of the guy
Tell me the age of the guy who did the simulation
Alright attach them
Using the power of balloons to complete the Alley oop
Don't pinch his flesh!
Move him towards the goal
Inomoto why are you under his shoulder?
You need to put the ball in
Yes, put his hands in a catching position
Let's do it on steady,
Ready, steady!
Thank you very much
He can't get out like that
That was, probably,
When we made him jump, immediately,
He fell straight on his face
Yeah that's it
He just can't reach it. I guess balloons are out.
However, he did say "Thank you very much" before leaving
Maybe he means "That's enough"
Well if he wants to quit then that's fine, let's go
We did what we had to do
We can't do much more than that
Once again they visit Matsumoto in his break room
Excuse us
Former DownTown manager Nakamura
Nakamura Dress Up Game
Producer Nakamura
We gave up on the trampoline,
And thought of using the balloons to lift you...
We thought of using them to lift you...
But that didn't work out so...
If you want to quit, then there isn't really anything we can do
"Don't pinch his flesh! Don't pinch his flesh"
you guys kept yelling,
That made me super scared
Cause you did actually pinch it
And when that happened, I don't know who it was,
"KEKA KEKA KEKA" - some guy was cackling like that
It's not something to laugh at
You guys are all over the place
We can't get anything good out of this, that's bad
I asked you guys cause I trusted you!
Except for Inomoto
Why
Right?
For real, can I trust you guys?
Starting over, time for the 3rd attempt
Alright let's go!
I think we can do it with this next one
This mat always gives me concern
Just like last time get on here,
And lay down on your back
Did you do a simulation?
Yes we did
On my back? Where should my head be
Your head over there
Did the kid who did the simulation do the same?
What kid?
You really want to know that
Alright please take it away
Was the kid who did the simulation well educated?
Probably this time...
This will be fine
Did he go to a proper university?
These 3rd parties are super scary
These 3rd parties...did they do the simulation?
Of course
What kid did the simulation? Was it an assistant director?
Don't really know
Was he young and fit?
Yes
If he's too young, you know it'll be too different for me
But we don't have any 58 year old ADs
There aren't many 58 year olds to do the simulation
Oooh you've got a mouth on you!
That's dangerous
Watch out!
Help them out
More carefully
Let him down
Put him down
Try lifting him now please
Attempt to use a wire rope to complete the alley oop
This could work!
There we go
There it is!
He's up there!
Only the pass is left
Yeah!
Stick your hand out!
This side works better
This way, oh right
Fighting!
This could work
Let's go!
So close!
This angle here is good
Matsumoto-san, still,
Just a bit more
Matsumoto-san seems very concerned about his nose
He left again huh
If this doesn't work then...
It would've been better if his hands were like this
It would've been better if they were raised
Yeah raise them like this
Let's go tell him this, we'll tie his arms like this
Right? Let's go
Once again they head to his dressing room
I feel like I've been thoroughly bullied
You were straight up aiming for my face
When you said "So close"
I thought you were talking about the ball almost hitting my face
Matsumoto-san, that's a misunderstanding, the one who hit your face is-
Former Gaki producer - Suga Kenji
Honestly,
I think teamwork is super important
Do you want to do this or not, for real
Seriously
I can't take in what Matsumoto-san is saying
It's too surprising
Did he watch us? He didn't right
His eyes are bloodshot red
Of course he's angry
Anyone would get angry if that happened
It's better if it doesn't hurt right?
No shit!
I'm counting on you! It's the last time!
Yes!
Reflecting on their mistakes, time for the 4th attempt!
We can definitely do this one
Yes it'll be fine!
It'll look like it went in
Fujiwara for real we're counting on you
The idea is perfect
I just need to do my best
And it won't hurt either
There's no danger or anything
No pain for sure
let's do this
Didn't you want to show off your youthfulness?
All's well that ends well
Of course
Let's go
Why is there a mat if this isn't dangerous?
For now just get on the mat
Watch out please
Get up there
Alright Fujiwara, get ready
Place it on properly
There we go
Alright yes!
Just like that! Alright
Pass the ball!
Using perspective tricks to complete the alley oop
Here we go!
Here it coooomes!
This is super cool
The ball...
The ball fell off. Put the ball on
Here it comes
Take it nice and slow
The ball's here!
It went in!
Congratulations!
It went in so nicely
What is he angry about?
Maybe we celebrated at the wrong timing?
We stole the moment?
Maybe we should have celebrated afterwards
Yes that could be it
That's unfortunate, that's my fault
I said "We did it!" right away
Let's go apologise for that
Then we can finish this
It was nice the 2nd time
Yes yes yes
Once once once again they visit Matsumoto's dressing room
Excuse me, If this is the case,
After we succeeded we got too prideful, and before you,
We went "we did it!" and messed up by celebrating
It's not just one thing you did wrong
The thing I want to say most though is that breeze was too strong
It was friggin cold. It was cold in a lot of ways.
TN: Cold is slang for lame/unfunny
Also why the hell were you guys in the frame?
I want to do this by myself
You were totally in the frame
Should we go try again?
We don't have to do it. There's no need to force it to happen.
Sorry but, what,
What is this?
This...
It's a face roller
I get that it's a facial roller,
But why is Suga-chan here?
What happened? Why can't he be here?
His face is red from doing it too much
Will the next attempt succeed?!
Time for the 5th attempt!
It's the last one
Let's nail this
This time for sure
It'll be alright
It would be great to get it right away
If we did this right away...
Yeah we could've finished right away
He's in a great mood again
Sorry about that seriously
I'm not mad at all
I'm not mad AT ALL
Heading towards the ending, everything that happened,
All the hurdles and challenges, twists and turns,
That's just how life is,
Up until the end-
Let's do this
You're right
I didn't really have a punchline for that
It's a mat again...
Put your head here, lying on your back
If you could lay down
A lot of laying on my back...
You won't get hurt at all it's totally fine
Let's go
Be careful
Sorry about this
Alright Shozo. Counting on you
This is perfect
There's gonna be no problems at all
Alright take it way, is here OK?
OK then, please begin!
Matsumoto-san completed the alley oop!
Thank goodness
Maybe he's crying
Why is he crying? He should be happy
He should be happy
One of you pressed on my face
I couldn't breathe for a second
Was it you? Was it you?
Yes