The First Annual Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende, Chiki Chiki
"Absolutely Tasty - I've always wanted to try this": Pressed Senbei championship!
That was close
You almost got it wrong
Pressed...
So now, Matsumoto-san
It's been 7 months since...
Why are you leading us, dude!!
No, no, no
Let me explain this...
Just look at the cue card, it says "Hamada-san"
I was told to stand here 15 seconds before they started filming
Should you really do so just because they asked though?
A normal person should refuse that
This is such a precious chance dude
This is basically a neo-Bully
Pressed Senbei can be found at tourist spots
It presses shrimps or squids directly with the machine
And here comes the absolutely tasty snack Senbei
This time, we will be focusing on the potential of Pressed Senbei
Each member will present 2 original ingredients to be made into Pressed Senbei
While it's important to be tasty
The appearance is crucial as well
To be instagrammable
Ah, we need consider that as well?
Maybe it can even be commercialized
Yes, exactly
Like a new type of Pressed Senbei
So let's start with Tanaka-san
That should be Hamada-san's line though
Yes, Hamada-san should be the one doing this
But they suddenly asked me to do it
Let's start with Tanaka's Pressed Senbei
Here it is
Canned mackerel
Canned mackerel pressed senbei
Tanaka presents #1
Everyone knows that this is very popular right now
Oh, really?
Well, yeah
It's actually good for diet too
Oh, I see
It's affordable and nutrient-rich
Is it really popular now?
It's very popular
To be specific, it's popular 2 and a half years ago
A little bit ago
He's pissing me off
You're treated as a newbie only at this TV studio right?
The staffs at other TV studios are like "Oh, Tanaka-san!"
"Here comes Mr.Tanaka!!"
Wear it quickly dude!
You won't find this kind of TV studio anywhere else
The staffs from Atsuki Pressed Senbei will be guiding the members
Put this at the center
I hope he put the whole can of it directly
You're right
Just go like "Kapu"
The sauce as well...
So you could have put the whole can of it right?
I thought it's because you can't put the sauce
That round shape must be more instagrammable
That must be better, what's wrong with you?
Idiot!!
So press it now
Interesting
Start to turn it slowly now
Turn it slowly
It starts to smell good
Yeah, of course
It smells so freaking good
Let's open it
Okay
It's a bit burnt, but, well...
It's fine
It's quite nice
The members will now try Tanaka's Canned mackerel pressed senbei
It smells really good
Yeah, it smells good
And it's cute too
It's super cute right?
Cute?
It's super cute isn't it?
Is this cute?
It should be instagrammable, of course it's cute
Is this really edible!?
This should be absolutely tasty
Let’s eat
Tasty!!
Ah, this is tasty
This can even be the snacks to go with sake
This tastes freaking good
Yeah, it's just tasty
How many points would everyone give?
The members will discuss and give a score out of ten
Well, two points
So two points
There's nothing we can do
No way
The main cast said so
I was here since the show was first established
I was here since the first meeting
Yeah, but...
Is this instagrammable though?
That's a minus point
5 points
Canned mackerel pressed senbei 5 points
Okay, so Tanaka-san 5 points
The second one that Tanaka presents is a bit adventurous
This is my second item
Doria pressed senbei
Tanaka presents #2
It's Doria
Senbei Doria
Doria itself is already instagrammable
Doria pressed senbei
Tanaka presents #2
Then just eat the Doria
I think this one could go wrong though
No way, it won't
Is this instagrammable?
It will be burnt again anyway
Tanaka, what is your final academic background again?
Osaka design school
Oh, really?
So he should know how to make it instagrammable the most
So that's why his sense is a bit weird?
Lemon Print Shoes
Like those shoes with lemon print
Ah, yes
Normal people won't wear that
No, people wear it
So it's because he went to the design school
I see
He should be familiar with these then
Yes, you're right
So I'll press it now
It's fine right?
Yes, it's fine
But I think I should be good at turning the handle
*"Densha de go!" is a Japanese train simulation game series
I did the same thing in "Densha de go!"*
This is completely different with Densha de go!
Did you play "Densha de go!"?
They said yes
They're not playing it for practice purposes
I'll open it
Let's see
This is Doriya Senbei
It looks tasty
Looks like pizza
Oh, yeah
Tanaka's second dish, Doria Senbei
How does it taste?
This is quite instagrammable
It's instagrammable right?
Yes, it is instagrammable
Those broccolis are so instagrammable
This is well instagrammable
Huh? This is tasty
Eh, really?
It's tasty
This is delicious
Yeah, it has a rich taste
Well, if Uber Eats delivered this to me, I'll be pissed off though
Doria Senbei 7 points
Like what the heck is this?
Hamada will now present his senbei
First item is this
Abalone Senbei
Hamada presents #1
Oh, I see
How far can it be stretched though?
Yeah, that's the point
This is quite thick
But I really want to try this
Yeah, I want to try this
This is luxurious
This is amazing
I'm going to press it
Is this really going to work?
It's crying
Yeah, it's crying
It's groaning
Because it's really thick
Eh, what's this sound?
Is this Hamada-san?
No way!!
I thought so too
Just think about how he always behaved
This is really hard
Scary!!
So this is how it looks like
This is instagrammable!!
This is amazing
Never seen something like this
One more step?
Put some soy sauce
Done!
Hamada's first dish, abalone senbei
Let's try it!
You can add more soy sauce too
So my comment is
It's such a waste
Abalone senbei 3 points
For such a luxurious abalone
And the abalone's groan was awful too
You just made that up yourself
That groan was horrible
Today's theme is for young girls like high school students right?
Fujita Nicole is probably crying right now
Well...
Nicole hate this kind of things
Well, we're not doing this for Fujita Nicole anyway
Of course we are doing this for Fujita Nicole
Are you joking?
Of course it is
Hamada's second dish is a much more affordable senbei
This is the second item
*Peyoung is Hamada's favorite fried noodles brand
Hamada presents #2
Peyoung senbei*
You really like this
It suddenly becomes affordable
I believe this will taste even better after being pressed
Yeah, it must be tasty
Well but...how will Nicole feel about this though
No, no
Then ask her to come!!
Let Nicole watch this contest here
Well this show is on TV, so Nicole will watch it anyway
I think she'll watch this
And see herself being mentioned so many times, although she's not even here
She must be shocked
For being mentioned by these old men
It should be fast this time
Looks good
So it will be pressed now
I'll press it now
It should be pressed into a rectangular shape
Sounds good too
That's just the sound of frying fried noodles
It's fast this time
Yeah
I'll open it now
Never seen something like this
How does the Peyoung senbei looks like!?
Sounds good too
I'll open it now
Never seen something like this
This is different to what I've imagined
It's like the top view of an old lady
How does Hamada's second dish, Peyoung senbei tastes like?
I'll put some mayonnaise on this old lady
I'll put some on this old lady too
Anyone else want to put mayonnaise on this old lady?
I'll put some sauce on this old lady
They're gonna hate you
It tastes good with mayonnaise
Yeah, it's tasty
So what's the score?
The members will discuss and give a score out of ten
Well, four points
Yeah, four points
Are you joking?
This tastes good just because of the Peyoung
Add some points for being instagrammable too
Well, is it instagrammable?
But everyone is calling this an old lady
That's just you guys
Maybe you should put a ribbon and press it
It feels like this old lady gave up being fashionable
Peyoung senbei 4 points
Yeah
Endo will now present his senbei
The first item is this
Endo presents #1
Sushi senbei
Wow
I like your adventurous spirit
Thank you
I want to try making it a senbei
And press it directly
This may possibly be instagrammable too right?
Yeah, it's colorful
Why did you choose so many white ones
Yeah, the ingredients
Put the ones with color to the sides dude
Why are you putting those two in a row?
He's so angry
The power harassment since the Shōwa era
And Endo can't talk back to him right?
But I'm enjoying this so it's fine
I told you to put the salmon on the side dude!!
Do you need to be so angry?
Done
The appearance should look good
Hopefully it will look like a menu
You can press it now
I'll press it
Press it for a bit longer
Okay
You can turn it now
"Hopefully it will look like a menu"
What does that even mean?
Everyone ignored it just now
Like a menu?
Calm down
That sticked in our mind right?
Yeah, it did
Everyone decided to ignore that
We all ignored that like "su-un..."
Something strange went pass
I noticed something passed by
But I thought never mind
But then the exhaust gas stayed here...
So I just felt curious
Just let it go, it passed already right?
You guys are having a good time over there
I was working so hard here and you guys are so pumped over there
I'll open it now
Please open it slowly
Here it is
Wow for what?
It's beautiful
What are you wowing at?
This is so instagrammable
This is just perfect
This is a complete failure
You can't even tell
what sushi it is
The sushi senbei that looks strange
How does it taste like?
What is this?
It should be Hotate
Hotate?
I don't want to eat this
Yeah, I don't want to eat this
Please try this toro salmon
This is?
That's tuna
Oh, this is tuna?
It's tuna
Please try the shrimp Hamada-san
The shrimp should taste good
You can even see it's tail here
I don't like this sour taste
I don't like this salty taste too
This is absolutely tasty
Those two people don't like it at all though
I don't really want to make Endo's part interesting
Sushi senbei 1 point
Can you stop that?
Endo's second dish is a dessert senbei
This is the second item
Decoration cake senbei
Endo presents #2
It's decoration cake senbei
Here comes the bad thing about you
No, please...
Trying to jazz it up in a wrong way
This is awful
Well, young girls like to eat warm fruits right?
Although that's unimaginable to us
Talking about young girls, this is instagrammable too
No, no, no way
No way
Maybe it'll be like crepe
Here it goes
I'll press it
No way, this is awful
This is amazing
Sorry that the cream is flowing down
It's melting
It's flowing down
This just looks awful
I wonder could this even become a senpei
Yeah
The person with the lowest score
Will be camping with Heipo
I’ve never heard of that
This is the first time I’ve heard it
Camping with Heipo-san is like being in hell
Seriously
Heipo always phone me
And say that he's ready
Will it be instagrammable?
This is looking good
Stop lying
But Nicole will probably love this color
No, no, no way
How does decoration cake senbei tastes?
Decoration cake senbei
Well, it smells good
This is so tasty right?
How the heck!!
This is awful
Really?
Why are you lying?
I can eat tons of this though...
Really?
To be honest...
No thanks
Decoration cake senbei
Housei will now present his senbei
My first item is this
Housei presents #1
Shark fin senbei
The luxurious shark fin
That's so expensive
Of course it'll be tasty
It's both instagrammable and tasty
Well yeah, maybe it's instagrammable
This one must be expensive
Yeah
Just look at it
If this is not tasty...
This is just...
That's just sinful
Yeah, exactly
So who will be camping with Heipo
He's putting pressure on me
But for now...
I scored the fewest points for now
Wait a second
You're pressing it now
So saying you're pressured is not appropriate
Yeah, agreed
This is good
This is looking good
Go further dude!!
Why are you just turning it over there
Is it instagrammable
I'll open it
Here it comes
Is it instagrammable?
I'll open it now
Here it comes
Huh!?
Where is it!!
That's enough
That's so old
Stop those old jokes
Just close it first and scrape it off
That's so Shōwa
Here comes the senbei
It looks like croissant
That's true
Housei's first dish is the luxurious shark fin senbei
How does it taste like?
This seems to be double layered
I will eat now
You can really taste the shark fin
This tastes interesting
It's just the same as the previous one right?
It's such a waste
I quite like this though
It has a unique taste
Shark fin senbei 5 points
Yeah, it's good
Housei's second dish is a soul food senbei
Here it is
Housei presents #2
Tonkotsu ramen senbei
Everyone likes this
Pork bone-broth
You're gonna put everything in?
Yes, everything
This must be good
It's unbelievable that the shop allows you do this
Seriously...
So I'll just put everything
The noodles first
I see
You won't put the soup in right?
Of course not the soup dude
Huh!!
What are you doing?
That's enough
Really?
Seriously!?
Are you joking?
Close it quickly dude
Really?
His face is pissing me off
Shall we just give him 2 points?
It changed
That face get even lower scores
I think Nicole already fell asleep now
Stop it, that's enough
Wait for me Nicole
It's gonna be instagrammable
I wonder how it'll look like
I'll open it
Here it comes
Well...
How does the Tonkotsu ramen senbei taste like?
Where is the egg?
Oh, yeah
This looks like the top view of a fashionable old lady
With accessories
With some hairpins
Why are you looking at an old lady from the top
I'll eat it now
This is absolutely tasty
The more you chew it, the more delicious it becomes
Maybe you should have put those Benishoga
So what is the score?
Well, I have no idea why,
But what about a skull
No, no way
I don't know why but anyway
No way, if you don't know why
Just give you a skull without any meaning
You can't give a skull if there's no meaning
Tonkotsu senbei 5 points
Because this has a lot of meaning
So the last one will be Matsumoto-san
Yes
I'm the last, because mine takes a lot of time
And I will bet everything with this one dish
All that I can say is that, this is absolutely instagrammable
Really?
What is the instagrammable senbei that Matsumoto presents?
Aiming to be instagrammable
This is the item
Matsumoto presents
Yellowtail Collar senbei
So I'll be making Yellowtail Collar senbei
It's impossible to make this a senbei
This is so exepnsive too
I actually want to press it vertically
No way...
But that seems to be too difficult
So I'll press it horizontally instead
And this takes about 40 to 50 minutes...
This will never be commercialized
The line will be very long
Which side do you want?
You can choose it
Huh!?
Do you want the left face or the right face?
No one cares about which side
No dude, this is something to enjoy as well!!
Not at all
It looks like this on this side, and like this on that side
It's the same!!
Maybe this side looks more handsome
Is it?
This side then
Looks like Matsudaira Ken from here
This is going to take forever
Yeah
It's impossible
So put it like this
Yeah, the better-looking side
Yep
This is just terrible
How could it be terrible!
I don't want to eat it at this stage already
No, no, no way
People will be fighting for this at Izakaya!!
Izakaya won't have this
You know, like a special menu
Well
I'll close it now
Ah, the crust at the bottom...
This takes 40 minutes...
That's impossible
This gonna take more than an hour
He need to do this for a whole day
Yeah
That's true
It's not letting me to close this at all
It keeps coming this side
It keeps moving right?
That being said
There's actually a completed version
There is?
How does the Yellowtail Collar senbei, which took 40 minutes to press tastes like?
It's instagrammable
Open!!
This is terrifying!!
Where is it?
This is scary
But isn't it amazing to be pressed like this
It looks like those illustration on the folding screens back in the old days
How does the Yellowtail Collar senbei that Matsumoto presents taste like?
Did they press it on the right side?
Well, that doesn't matter
They pressed it on the right side
It's just the same
Let's do it again
There's no need
It won't match on action
No one cares
It smells so good
Wow, this smells fishy
Let's eat it
This is fried fish
Yeah
It's so hard
This thing is so hard
Eat this
No!!
Don't press it on me
Just eat it, it must be tasty
I really don't want this
It's full of DHC though
We want to focus on this part now
We want to focus on Hamada
As he eats the eyeball
What are you doing Tanaka?
There's bone in this
This is so dangerous
This is unacceptable
Too dangerous
No it's not
What have you done?
We have to give this a skull
Seriously
He'll be camping with Heipo-san then
I won't go
I really want to watch that
I won't go for sure