First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende
Chidori Daigo Shichi Henge!
Your voice was amazing
Shichi hengeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
It was dragged out
What the hell?!
I thought it was incredible
It has been 4 months since the last challenger Haruna
This is our 38th challenger
Please come in!
Thank you for having us today
During last year's M-1 contest
*Chidori literally means "thousand birds"
The flying bird Chidori crashed*
No, we're not crashed
Chidori was flying on the right track, but ended up crashing
Well, yes, we lost the contest
After that, my hands go numb whenever I see Hamakan
Well, for today, Daigo is the one who will challenge, right?
Yes, Daigo will be challenging today
Look, Hamada-san
After my manager told me about the offer for Shichi-henge, this thing came out the next day
Yes, exactly
And it's so big
That's strange
So if you can do well, it will probably be healed
That's the main point today
These are the past results
Which position are you aiming for?
If possible, of course I want to aim the best ten
Yes, of course, it's good to dream big
Is he sober now?
Eh? He drank?
Hey dude! How dare you drink on this important day?
Who said I drank on this important day for Shichi Henge?
You look drunk
I told you I didn't! Do you mean I smell like alcohol?
Yes, you smell!
Check it out then
He simply have bad breath
I have an upset stomach
Okay, so let's get started, Daigo's Shichi Henge!
No one is laughing at this gag anymore
It's okay, just do it
So which one should we choose?
Which one should we choose?
There's a whole lot of ideas on there
I'm most curious about the last one though
Heipo's deep-sea documentary!
A miracle two shot with the Giant squid
If we can do this, that gotta be amazing
How deep do you mean "deep-sea"?
Around 600 to 800 meters
It lives at those places
How deep can you dive?
About 10 meters
Really? 10 meters?
I dived in this show before, right?
It's scary to dive even just 5 meters
Yeah, exactly
When you dived during the matchmaking before, it was just about one meter
No way, I thought it was 10 meters
How could that be possible
Why did you matchmake under the water though?
Because you guys asked him to do so!!
Yes, you're right, I remember it now
Oh, come on
Don't stand out to sea when the waves are so high
How dare you sail off when the waves are so high? That's just ridiculous!
I told him not to do so
I told him to take a rest, but he insists to stand out to sea
I really tried to stop him
But then he said to me
"Why the heck, dude!"
"If I say I want to stand out to sea, then it has nothing to do with the weather"
Come on, when the weather is bad, we should just do this instead
We should just pick the Shakos (a species of mantis shrimp)
And stay safe
(No one has laughed after five minutes.)
Maybe you'll earn a lot, but that's bothering others
Just pick the Shakos, when the weather is bad, just pick the Shakos
Oh, it's a girl
Isn't this a girl
This is a girl
This is a girl too
These are all boys
It's all boys
Only a few girls over here
Of course, yes of course, I know
Of course, yes of course
Everything (gags) flew out of my mind
You are dirty!
That's cunning
Just get out of here, dude!
I've been practicing this for a long time
And I've prepared so many Shakos
I'm not paying this penalty.
We don't need to pay for this
He didn't make us laugh
He forgot about his gag
This counts as one of the Shichi Henge
But we don't need to pay for it
He said "everything flew out of his mind"
But that probably relieved his stress
Yeah, you're right, he should feel relaxed now
Isn't the steering wheel reversed?
What the hell!
That's cunning
Hey, yo. Hey, yo.
Thank you for riding with me
I'm the road safety driver, Ika Kawari
Where are you going? Nippon Television?
Thank you very much
Please let me drive safely, I'm the Ika Kawari
By the way, are you always appearing on TV shows?
Yes
I knew it, I saw you on TV before
Thank you
You're that person, right?
You're a wrestler, right?
No I'm not, I'm not
You're Koike Eiko's husband, right?*
*Koike Eiko's husband, Wataru Sakata, is a Japanese professional wrestler and former mixed martial artist
I'm not, no
I saw you on TV before
We don't look alike at all
Oh, really?
But anyway, I bet you met a lot of famous people, right?
I met a famous person recently
Okay
When I was on the Shinkansen
You know, I always smoke
I don't know
So I went to the smoking room
And then, I saw a skinny gangster there
And I thought "Dang, there's a gangster"
And you know, smoking rooms are really small
And I thought "I don't wanna stay here alone with a gangster"
So I didn't smoke
But when I went back, you know, I still want to smoke
So I went to the smoking room again
And that skinny gangster was still there
Although that skinny gangster was still there, but I thought "Anyway! I just want to smoke!", and I entered the room
*Ken Naoko is a Japanese singer and actress, and is well known for her comedy roles featuring idiosyncratic looks
And I found out that the skinny gangster, was actually Ken Naoko-san*
And I thought "Wow, it's Ken Naoko-san!"
She sure looks like a skinny gangster
That really surprised me
Here's another famous person, huh?
What happened? You seem to be in a bad mood?
No, I'm not
*Kawagoe Tatsuya is well known for being the most handsome chef with an arrogant look
You're Kawagoe Chef, right?*
I really like you
I always watch your TV shows
We arrived. It's the Tennoji Zoo
That was quite good
The first one was terrible
But he's getting into the swing of things
If there's another chance...
*Daigo's comedy routines involve made-up words with no meaning
Hene
The point
Red Hene
Yo-noyo-nomoisu (More made-up words)
Hene
Yo-noyo-nomoisu
Red Hene
Tao!
*Yasushi Tao is a Japanese retired Nippon Professional Baseball player
Tao.
Wow, nice, that was nice
That was a perfect timing
I'm curious about the last side though
Yeah, the black side
To be revealed at the end of the show!!
But finally, he's getting us to pay
That one was good
You don't know him? He's Tao
Tao.
Yes. When those things happen, just call this phone number
Yes, I'm the representative, Maya
Iriomote Maya
So how is it going? Is there anymore? There's two more?
Oh, I see.
And you want to bring both of them here?
Then bring both of them
How does it looks like?
One of them was at your home, and you got the other one recently
Oh, I see.
I have seven times two, fourteen now
Adding it all up, there's sixteen now
No problem, no problem at all
You're working in the daytime, so let's meet late at night
How about during lunch time?
Okay, so bring both of them and let's meet at noon
No, it's not embarrassing at all
It's not embarrassing at all for young girls to sell honeycombs
Oh, so you don't trust Maya at all yet, huh?
Okay, I see, because it's the first time we've talked with each other
So you don't know Maya at all
Maya is riding in a tiny Lexus now
A red and tiny Lexus
So you can definitely trust me
See you! Yes, yes, okay
He shouldn't have said it's "honeycombs"
Yeah, Hamada thinks that way
I didn't laugh at all after that
I knew that, when he said "honeycombs", I was like "Ahh, Hamada's gonna hate it"
Hamada don't like gags with a clear conclusion
Hamada's home is too big to visit
Stop! Please!
Help me! Ken!!
This is cunning!
Downtown's coworker
Tomizu Ken
Ken-chan powder
What the heck is that?
If you got sprinkled by this powder, you will become a boring person!
Ma-chan, Hama-chan, here I am!
Ken-chan, here I am!
Ken-san, Ken-san, Ken-san
Don't say things like Ma-chan, Hama-chan
Why did you say those things?
Because we haven't seen each other for a long time
I understand that, but...
Yes, so that's just a little improvisation!!
Don't shout at me!
Why did you say that?
Sorry, you guys can leave
If you say things like "Ma-chan, Hama-chan"
Then everything (gags) after that becomes wasted, am I right?
Oh, is it?
What do you mean "is it?", of course it is
Anyway! There's no need to tell me about this here, right?
I've been working so hard to come up with these gags, what's wrong with you, dude!
Hey! You better not talk to me like this, that's impolite
Who cares if it's impolite, you've ruined all of my gags
Will you talk to Hama-chan and Ma-chan like this, dude!
No, I won't
Of course you won't
Yeah, of course I won't
You're just acting differently with different people
Of course I am!
What are you even capable of?
I can do a whole lot of gags
Do it then
How do you feel? (Gen-ki)
I feel sick (Byou-ki)
That's it
Stop saying that phrase
Stop saying "that's it", it's becoming a habit
King Kong Kang Ken-chan!
What's wrong with you? How should others react to that?
How have you been a comedian for this long?
That's too harsh
You're even living in a decent home, how have you been a comedian for this long?
We're visiting the same dentist in Osaka
What do you expect from us for saying that?
We're visiting the same dentist?
Matsumoto-san probably didn't talk about this shit for decades
That's enough! Come on! Just tell me about this afterwards!
That thing
What do you mean?
"I'm gonna tell Masa about this"
Oh yeah...I'm gonna tell Masa about this
Too late, come on
Anyway, just leave
That's it
That's the only thing
That's the only thing that I've asked you to say
And you never remember that
I'm nervous too, you idiot
No need to add that
Ahh, that really surprised me
Can't believe that Tomizu Ken-san really came here
Downtown's coworker
What was that "Ken-chan powder"?
It's a gag that if you got sprinkled by the Ken-chan powder, then you'll become a boring person too
Like some negative power
Okay, I see
He's always doing that gag in Osaka
His voice was loud and clear though
A moment ago...a moment ago...
He's about to finish
Next one's the last one, right?
Isn't it better to make that gag the last one? Look at his face
Exactly, he need to remove makeup
Maybe he'll bring out the big guns in the end
Again...
Yummy, yummy...
Yummy...
*Paper crane symbolizes hope and unconditional love
The taste of wishes...the taste of wishes...*
The red one tastes the best
The red one tastes good
The red one tastes the best...
The blue one tastes spicy
The red one tastes good
The taste of wishes...the taste of wishes...
The blue one tastes spicy
The red one tastes the best
What's wrong with him
No wonder why he wore that makeup previously
Yeah, you're right, because he need to wear another makeup anyway
It finally ended, please count the money
Quite a lot! Quite a lot!
Good work
So it adds up to 52000 yen
That's high! Just below Bob Sap
So the next thing, is to let Ken-chan take the Shinkansen as soon as possible
Ken-san, thank you very much
Hama-chan, Ma-chan, long time no see
Ken-chan, I heard that you joined the R-1 contest?
But I lost during the second round
Did you perform that gag just now?
Ken-chan powder?
Ken-chan powder
I did the King Kong Kang Ken-chan gag instead
Don't think everyone else knows about it
King Kong Kang Ken-chan
That's it
Who cares
What does this black side means?
Just briefly explain to us, if this side faces up...
Leather
Ken-chan, what is this jacket made of?
Well...I don't know...I borrowed it from someone...
You should definitely say "Leather" here, Ken-san