8th Gaki no tsukai ya arahende!!
Let's go to a town we've never been to and ask for the 3 best places there!!
We will do this again.
- Okay, I'll take this one.
- That was quick!
We don't have to talk, do we?
Even so, that was too quick!
Besides, I know what you guys sound like.
That's not the point.
This is the 8th time.
Chiba, Chiba, Kanagawa, Chiba, Chiba, Saitama, Chiba.
- We went to Chiba a lot.
- Yeah, Chiba has a lot of countryside.
I wanna go to a different place than we've been.
Who draws the lots?
- It doesn't matter who does it.
- Last time it was me.
Really?
Then, Endo draw the lots.
Me again?
- Then I'll draw the lots.
- Draw a good one.
If not, I'll break your hand!
In that case, I apologize very much to you.
I'll take that one!
- I'll open it.
- Please, be a nice place!
- Draw a good place.
- I don't know where the good place is, though.
Is that a town you know?
Higashi-fuchu.
That's where the horse racetrack is.
Ah,  the horse racetrack in Fuchu.
Higashi-fuchu is...
Here.
Right here? Higashi-fuchu station, right?
Higashi-fuchu.
This is where the prison is, right?
I don't think you have to talk that way.
There's a horse racetrack here, too.
I'm sorry.
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]
From the Nippon TV station in Shiodome, it takes about 40 minutes by car to get to Fuchu City in Tokyo.
Now, we are here at Higashi-fuchu station on the Keio line.
Yeah, this is the most urban place we've ever been.
- Yes, this is a city.
- There are many people.
Higashi-fuchu station is served by the Keio line and the Keio Horse Racetrack line, and you can get to Shinjuku in 30 minutes by express train
This station is recommended for commuting to the city center and going to school.
Let's ask the residents here for the best 3 in Higashi-fuchu.
It's going to finish soon today.
- In the first place, there were no people in the previous places.
- Right!
There are a lot of people here.
Well,
I don't want to get wet even if it's just one drop!
Isn't that impossible?
If one single drop lands on me,
I'm going home.
Because I'm a bit cringy.
You are too cringy!
It will rain sooner or later.
They moved toward the station and immediately began asking around.
Let's ask him.
Hello, sir.
May I ask your name?
- My name is Ito.
- Hi, Ito-san.
We are looking for recommendations for a place in Higashi-fuchu.
How about the Sungari Restaurant over there?
Oh, it says Sungari over there.
- Oh, a restaurant?
- Sungari Restaurant?
It's an old and unique Chinese restaurant.
- Sungari Restaurant!
- Thank you!
- Since we're here, let's ask people of various ages, shall we?
- I see. That's a good idea.
So they also interviewed some women who work in the area.
We are looking for recommendations in Higashi-fuchu.
- Food, places, anything!
- Your personal opinions are fine too.
Yeah, do you have any recommendations for places to go?
- Anything at all?
- Of course!
Hey, excuse me!
Sorry, wait a minute.
Please really don't do that kind of thing.
She was trying her best to answer our interview, but he was pushing her from behind.
I didn't push her that hard!
Let's go to the police box together.
- It's right there.
- He was caught red-handed!
I'm really sorry.
So, what's your recommendation?
If you go straight down this street, you'll find an independent general store.
They sell all kinds of things at low prices.
They also sell clothing and school supplies for elementary school children.
By the way, have you ever been to the Sungari Restaurant over there?
It has been there for a long time.
The clerk gave me change for 500 yen, saying,
"Here is 5 million yen."
Hmmm, that's SUPER funny.
If they do that, we all have to overreact.
- That's very good.
- I want to make sure of that.
- Do they always say "5 million yen"?
- I don't know if they always say that.
I want to go there.
They also asked Takagi-san, a resident of Higashi-fuchu, for his recommendation.
As I thought, Okunitama Shrine.
- A shrine?
- Okunitama Shrine?
Is there something famous there?
Something famous?
What's so funny!?
Please don't do that!
You hit harder than before.
Do you know of any more minor places?
Your personal recommendation of a place is fine.
So why are you laughing?
It's fine!
Let's go to the police box together!
This is a Tsukkomi.
Next, they asked the Takanami-san family for their recommendation.
We are looking for recommendations for a place in Higashi-fuchu.
We have to make this guy stop!
This time of year, we go to the playground inside the horse racetrack.
Is it in there?
You can go there when they are not holding horse races.
Can't I get in there if it's being held?
What kind of restaurants do you go to for eating out?
Recently I have been going to VANSAN.
- What kind of restaurant?
- It's a Italian restaurant.
Ah, I see.
The cheesecake is very good.
They roast it in front of you.
Thank you so much.
Furthermore
A cafe with owls.
A famous milk tea cafe.
They interviewed many people in front of the station.
And found out about various recommended places, such as shrines and restaurants.
Where is the 3rd place they are going to?
- Sungari Restaurant.
- That's close.
Do they really say "5 million yen"?
They headed for Sungari Restaurant, where the waiter was unique.
Is he hungry?
He'll keep moving forward.
He'll move on.
Huh? Is it open?
The shutters are closed.
They're not open.
- It sucks.
- Are they closed today?
They're closed today.
Today is a regular holiday.
It was a wasted trip.
Sungari Restaurant.
I'm very curious about this.
What do we do?
Let's go somewhere from this list.
So, would you eat cheesecake in the Italian restaurant?
If that restaurant is closed too, I'm DEFINITELY going home!
To be honest, several drops landed on me already!!
They headed to Italian kitchen VANSAN where cheesecake is recommended.
Maybe that is VANSAN.
We need to cross the crosswalk twice.
We have barely moved from the front of the station.
That's right, we haven't been to a single place yet.
Hey, the light is red!!
Was he that impatient?
Don't be so loud.
It happens.
He's crossing the street.
It's okay that way.
Then let him negotiate permission to shoot.
Matsumoto-san, please negotiate and get permission to shoot.
Matsumoto arrived first and entered the restaurant alone to ask the clerk for permission to shoot.
Suddenly he entered the restaurant alone.
Did he get permission to shoot?
She was someone who had been to a HEY!HEY!HEY recording as an audience.
That's amazing!
She graciously gave me permission.
Is it okay?
She is someone who has been to a HEY!HEY!HEY! recording.
I have been there many times!
Who was your favorite?
Hama-chan!
Oh, you like Hamada?
Is that why this supports Demae-can?
- Oh, great!
- Yeah, it's Demae-can.
- I will go prepare your seat.
- Thank you!
She is preparing our seats.
VANSAN is an Italian restaurant popular for its homemade pasta and pizza.
They went inside for the recommended cheesecake.
It's Iced tea!
We came for the cheesecake.
- Roasted cheesecake?
- Yes!
Is this okay?
Well, do you want pasta first?
You want pasta?
I'd like to try pasta.
Then let's order two kinds.
We'll have the pasta with anchovies and cabbage and  the bolognese.
Sure.
Are you from Mainichi-kou?
I'm presbyopic and have bad eyesight.
They ordered pasta at VANSAN, an Italian restaurant.
Then.
Looks delicious!
- Dish out this.
- Okay.
The noodles are delicious.
This is fresh pasta.
They finished off two kinds of pasta and ordered the cheesecake they wanted.
We'll have the roasted cheesecake, please.
- Just one?
- Two, please.
They asked the clerk, Hasegawa-san, for her recommendation for Higashi-fuchu.
Minor places are also fine.
There is an abandoned U.S. military base.
You can't see it in the summer because of the overgrown trees, but in the winter, when the leaves die down, you can see through the fence the base that was once used by the U.S. military.
- Isn't that place used now?
- It has not been used for decades.
- And you can only see it from the outside?
- Yes. The windows are broken and it looks nostalgic.
It's raining and the derelict building would make a good picture.
And here comes the roasted cheesecake they've been waiting for.
I see!
Now I'm going to roast this.
- Oh, nice!
- It's awesome!
That's quite a roast.
It's like a cheese fondue.
What does roasted cheesecake taste like?
Really tasty.
Delish!
I've never had anything like it.
This is delicious!
It's really good!
I see.
They were all very satisfied with the roasted cheesecake! Thank you!
They headed to the  site of the U.S. military base recommended by Hasegawa-san.
How old are you, Endo?
I am 51 years old.
My career is 30 years.
- Hosei-san's career is 34 years?
- Yeah.
- Come to think of it, you have a disciple, don't you?
- Yes.
Why don't I have any disciples?
Because you are annoying.
A newcomer these days would go to a training school.
Downtown was the first graduates of the training school.
The same goes for High Heel and Tommies.
Huh?
You don't have to say it anymore.
You are not wrong.
Yeah.
Don't say it again, just say it once
Who are the second graduates?
Dango Kibino.
He was in a comedy duo with Katsumi.
- What was the name of the duo?
- Don Quixote.
Yeah, Don Quixote!
Don Quixote.
They said, "Let's meet at the corner of Maru Buil."
"Okay, the corner of Maru Buil.....There's no such place!!"
That's funny.
We all had a good laugh.
Ken of the Tommies was not a first graduate, though.
- Masa-san used to be a solo comedian.
- Masa brought Ken.
Masa-san became popular right away.
He was on a show called Yoru-ha-Kunekune.
He was first in a duo with Hamane.
"I was Surp Surp Surprised"?
He was with "I was Surp Surp Surprised".
I went with Hamada to Hamane's house, and we went somewhere in his car on our own.
You remembered it well!
You took Hamane-san's car without permission?
At that time he didn't say, "I was Surp Surp Surprised"
He said, "This can't be a joke."
Did he say it in a serious way?
They arrived at the site of the U.S. military base.
What a place!
This was a U.S. military base?
This whole forest was it?
Where's the building?
Where's Panama?
Oh, look!
There's a broken window!
- This is it.
- Oh, my gosh.
- We can only see it from here?
- Yeah.
The high school I went to was like this.
-Your high school was pretty wild.
- That was too wild.
There was a time when it was like that.
I want to see this from above.
Site of U.S. Military Base Fuchu
This is the site where the headquarters of the U.S. Forces in Japan was located aft er the war.
Most of the land was returned to Japan in 1975, and although the use of some of the land was reserved after that, it was fully returned to Japan in September 2021.
Therefore, the second recommended place in Higashi-fuchu is the site of the U.S. military base Fuchu.
They went back to the front of the station to ask for more information on their No. 1 recommendation for Higashi-fuchu.
They immediately asked Mera-san, who has lived in Higashi-fuchu for 10 months, for her recommendation.
Do you have any recommendations for places around here?
What places do you recommend that you know of?
- Is it a restaurant I recommend?
- Anything is fine.
Why did you think it was a restaurant?
Cause it says VANSAN, doesn't it?
- Don't talk so familiar.
- Ouch!
That's the seventh time today alone!
Let's go to the police box together.
I watched the whole thing.
You really shouldn't do that!
Restaurant is already ranked, so I thought another place would be a good choice.
I can only think of the udon restaurant.
- Is that place famous?
- Udon restaurant....
They continued to ask around.
There really is nothing in Higashi-fuchu.
There are hardly any good places here.
But they did not get any recommendations.
That's pretty tough.
At that time, they interviewed Yamada-san and his daughter, who live in Higashi-fuchu.
There is only 1st place left.
We can't leave without deciding on this one.
The Kyodo-no-mori Museum.
What is there?
There is a planetarium.
All our members love the stars!
I've never said that.
Have you been there a few times?
How many times have you been there?
Many times.
You've been there many times?
Can you give me a specific number?
That's enough!
This is new information.
Thank you.
- Well, shall we go there then?
- Yes.
They went to the Kyodo-no-mori Museum, which has a planetarium.
We like the stars.
Did someone say that?
I don't remember saying that.
I was surprised that five people who like stars happened to get together.
I don't know much about constellations.
They arrived at the recommended museum.
The Kyodo-no-mori Museum is a field museum that integrates the entire forest, including many buildings.
In addition to the main building, which has a permanent exhibition hall and a planetarium, there are also restored buildings such as an old farmhouse and a town hall.
It is also a place of relaxation where many Fuchu citizens gather to enjoy various plants such as Japanese apricots and hydrangeas.
They immediately checked the planetarium's showing time at the reception desk.
How long is the planetarium?
It is 45 minutes.
Thanks.
It's 45 minutes.
The screening time is 45 minutes.
Would you like to watch it?
I won't watch it!
If it were 15 minutes, I would watch it.
I thought it would be about 30 minutes.
That's pretty long.
Anyway, they checked the planetarium's screening schedule.
What time is it?
It's 15:20.
The time is just right, though.
What else can I see besides the planetarium?
There is an exhibition hall on the second floor.
It seems that there are exhibits about the history of Fuchu City.
How extreme!
Either a small Fuchu City or a vast star-filled sky.
Let's go to the museum.
They went to the permanent exhibition room on the second floor of the main building.
Let's take a look at the history.
It's so big!
In the permanent exhibition room, visitors can learn about the history, culture, and nature of Fuchu through actual materials, models, and videos, making it an enjoyable facility for adults and children alike.
This diorama is amazing.
This is amazing.
I wish I could have seen the U.S. military base like this.
What would you do if "Tanaka Tie Kick" was displayed at the end of this video?
It would really be like that.
Zelkova?
"Which one is Zelkova?"
This is an interactive game where you have to correctly select the flower, leaf, and trunk of a zelkova, the tree of Fuchu City.
- Let's do this.
- I can solve this
Oh, really?
The trunk is this.
Zelkova leaf is this.
And zelkova flower is this.
- You are great!
- No, this is it.
You are awesome.
So what's the answer?
It's coming.
So this is how you know the answer.
This is quite humiliating.
Can you answer this correctly,  curator?
This is a zelkova trunk, right?
I think so.
I didn't know about the leaves.
Oh, the leaves were wrong.
This would be the right answer.
Huh!?
Hey!
When he said "Huh!?", the end roll would be playing.
The 1st place is the Kyodo-no-mori Museum, where you can learn about the history of Fuchu in a fun way.
It's a lot different than the faraway countryside we've been in.
The places we couldn't shoot will be shot by the staff later.
The Chinese restaurant?
A few days later, the staff went to Sungari Restaurant, which was closed on a regular holiday and could not get in.
Among the many dishes on the menu, he ordered ramen, which has been popular since the restaurant opened.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
It's delicious with an old-fashioned taste.
Finally, it was time to pay.
The clerk gave me change for 500 yen, saying, "Here is 5 million yen."
Will she really say it?
It's 510 yen.
Here is 1010 yen.
The change is 500 yen.
Thank you very much.
She did not say, "Five million yen.
He told her the information he heard on the street.
I heard that the clerk here would say "5 million yen.
That is what my father said.
He is old
He is so old that he seldom takes shifts at the restaurant.
If you see him when you come here he might say it to you.
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]