Tonight's Gaki No Tsukai - Bamiyan Marathon Finale!
Ba-ba-ba-ba-baaaaaaaaaaaamiyan!
The rules; From a menu of 49, they pick 2 items at random for each store
They aim to clear all 51 stores across 23 wards
In this battle, whoever gives up has to pay for all the food eaten thus far
Up until the 6th store, they've had 5 ramen dishes, and 0 rice dishes
As well,
The first person to rest?
Hosei-san.
You guys fixed this again
Hosei gets 3 breaks in a row while Matsumoto gets zero!
Nobody expected this!
And tonight again, they will battle against Chinese food!
They head for the 7th store, the Akatsuka-shinmachi location
The menu for this store will be the Balsamic Black Vinegar Pork, and the Soft & Fluffy bread
Speaking of noodles, there's still 13 dishes left
There's still more noodle dishes?
I can't eat noodles anymore
I'll say it explictly, I can't eat noodles
You shouldn't say that so easily
We're only at the 7th store
But still
I haven't gotten to rest once
Yama-chan and Fujiwara...
3 times in a row!
He doesn't work at all
We should be able to buy breaks, using money
He's talking about money again
How much would 1 break cost?
Oh it doesn't matter
I have a lot of money
The dirtiest!
I'm kidding I'm kidding. I said I'm kidding
Let's stop the eating episodes
We're pretty old now
Let's get massages at Temomin instead
Visit every branch of Temomin
"Massaging my feet again?!"
"My neck?!"
"I don't need my neck massaged anymore!"
We'll get so excited!
Like hell we will!
Meanwhile, they arrive at the Akatsuka location
At this store they will enjoy, a splendid mix of black & balsamic vinegar sauce,
Balsamic Black Vinegar Pork, and,
Soft & Fluffy bread, which can be enjoyed with many dishes
Fujiwara meanwhile will dig into Ogio Jelly with fruits
Itadakimasu.
I'll eat this together then
I see, like that
You guys are finishing this quick
It's different from everything before
And in an instant the 7th store is cleared!
That was really quick
Finished!
And the next menu?
Hong Kong Sweet & Sour Pork
But still
Come on, a rice dish!
Uwaahhhh, please forgive me!
Green onion ramen.
Hong Kong
(Complaining about more noodles)
I even said explicitly I can't eat noodles
I said it was impossible
You did say that
Somehow, the 6th ramen dish of the day!
And the person who rests?
This is just in time
You just had a break
You're taking too many breaks
Amazing.
You're kidding.
I'll go with this, this vanilla ice cream
Fried Bread with Vanilla Ice Cream, Hinako and Syrup
This guys has actually rested for half the stores
4 hours since the start
The head towards the 8th store in Iidabashi
No rice dishes yet huh
There's no rice yes, but there's no Matsumoto card either!
Which store is next?
The 8th is next
And you know what else, we even drew 2 cards at one point
My card doesn't show up at all
It's statistically too improbable
Eh? You thought I was talking to myself?
You're not?
All he does is complain
No no,
I haven't complained once today
The 8th store, the Iidabashi-aioi location
At this store, with their homemade spices, Green Onion Ramen with plenty of Green Onion
And notable for its sauce, the Hong Kong Sweet & Sour pork
Is it good?
Their speed has decreased,
but they still finish!
TIme for the 9th store's menu selection
And of course, what they want is...
Let's get 2 rice dishes here
There it is
Gomoku yakisoba.
More noodle!
And the next one,
C'mon, please!
And it is...
Pepper steak
It's pretty much the same as always
The one who rests?
You guys fixed this didn't you?
They're dating
Fujiwara who is resting again decided on Meat Miso Cucumber
The status of their stomachs is of concern
Hamada-san, how is your stomach doing?
Well, well I am feeling it
Now if we get rice it might be risky
If we get rice & rice that will be risky
Fujiwara and Yama-chan, you guys are totally fine right?
You guys aren't eating much
We want to see your perseverance
Honestly,
The time to persevere will come I think
But just for now,
Will you really persevere?
I want to uphold the rules
The fatigue is creeping up on them, they're almost at the limit
Matsumoto proposes a plan
How many dishes are left?
We still have... 41 menu items left.
There's STILL 41 left?
On the contrary, I think if nobody rests,
If we don't eat 3 dishes we won't finish
Otherwise I think this won't end
It won't
Should we try that?
Alright, so after finishing the next store,
No breaks!
No breaks, and 3 dishes
Otherwise,
We won't clear enough stores,
Or eat enough items
For now let's clear all the dishes
How dare YOU say that
What are YOU saying?
Alright let's do this!
(Excited agreement)
Bamiyan Marathon - They've cleared 8 stores so far
Up until now they've eaten 16 items - 6.7kg of food
The 9th store, the Nerima-toyotama location
They arrive during the dinner rush
We'll eat at this type of booth for the first time today
Here they'll eat the 7th noodle dish of the day,
With lots of sauce on top, Gomoku yakisoba.
And notable for its sauce, the Pepper steak
This is really good!
There are a lot of toppings
Isn't this too much?!
It's the same as everyone, really
Look at this!
There's so many goddamn noodles
It's the same
This is scary
This dining table is scary
There's no noodles in there!
There's so many-There's a mountain of them in here
See!
Even as they betray each other,
They manage to finish!
And now to decide their fate with the menu selection
Alright let's go with Matsumoto's plan
Let's go with 3?
Let's make 3 the standard
Lets see what the menu is, and if we think we can do it we'll pick another item
Starting now, there will be no breaks, and they'll eat 3 dishes per store
The total exhaustion strategy
The menu;
Congratulations
Tenshinhan! (Crab Omelette on Rice)
And now a rice dish, you finally got one
Tenshinhan
Well just one is fine
The second dish,
Firm and crispy, Shio Koji Marinade Fried Chicken
(This one is alright, this is good)
The 3rd dish,
Authentically rich, Hakata Tonkutsu Ramen
Hakata Ramen? Now?
Well we gotta do this without breaks
You will do it?
So Matsumoto-san, another dish?
With the fried chicken this will be 4
The 4th one alright
What is this?!
Mountain of fried potatoes.
I feel really depressed now
These 4 dishes will be the menu for the 10th store
I'm kind of starting to feel it now
The Yakisoba?
You didn't have that much Soba in your plate!
I had so much
...Hamada.
Tanaka you didn't put enough in
I tried to make it even
You put the most noodles in my dish!
Even if he did,
With all of those families around, all of those kids
Making such a scary face there...
Yelling in such an angry way...
I thought "You shouldn't do that here"
They were all there to eat out
Exactly exactly
Hold on, that's not what we were talking about
I was saying he didn't have any noodles
And one of the kids there was trembling in fear,
And handed me this crumpled Origami dinosaur
They must've been scared
He handed it to you normally!
No no he was trembling
I felt bad for him,
Hearing you complaining about the noodles
How about we do pairs?
Eat one dish in pairs
I'll do it if it's with Tanaka-san
If we pair up Senpai-Kouhai,
The kouhai will end up disadvantaged
So how should we-
What we have here is the best isn't it?
What we have here
The seating rows here
Like us, them, and you?
We can just decide with rock paper scissors
You really hated that idea just now
Hamada-san, I hate it too
What should we do then
Being with DownTown-san is a disadvantage
Yes it is
Okamoto said it didn't he?
TN: Referring to 2019 Yoshimoto Scandal with Miyasako
We're a family here!
He cried didn't he?!
Bamiyan Marathon, the 10th store is the Senkawa Station location
Starting here, they will finish 4 dishes at a time
The mountain of fried potatoes
The Shio Koji marinade Fried Chicken
The Tenshinhan
Tonkatsu Ramen
First time having rice
Alright, you've finished
Chinese Okowa Lotus Leaf Wrap
Fried Chicken with Tartar Sauce
Ah, Fried Chicken?
Shrimp with mayonnaise salad.
2 varieties of Char Siu with 4 types of Tsukemen
The 11th store - Nakano Sakaue
Thank you for waiting
Here's the shrimp salad.
The Crispy & Juicy Tartar Fried Chicken
I see, very oily
The Char Siu & Tsukemen
This one is great!
Okowa Lotus Leaf Wrap
You've slowed down, so has Hosei-san
This is pretty challenging
Yama-chan you gotta eat more
These dishes are at least different
No more
A fart is torture at this point
With that, they've cleared 11 stores, 26 dishes, and eaten 10kg!
Menu selection for the 12th store
Large Yurinchi Chicken made with 2 types of sauces
Ah Yurinchi? Large piece Yurinchi
Slow Cooked Beef Stewed in Chinese Soy Sauce
Don't fold it!
Fried rice.
There it is!
Kimchee fried rice.
It came!
Double fried rice
Finally, the double fried rice has appeared
My stomach is pretty close to bursting
Will I even be able to eat?
How would you rate your stomach condition out of 10?
I've already gone past that, it's been that way for a while
But if nobody else gives up, I won't either
These people have passed their limits - How will this end?!
7.5 hours since the start
Here we go
The 12th store is Shinjuku West Gate's Large Guard location
I can't go on
You just said it!
Alright, time for 4 dishes
Thank you for the wait, this is the Slow Cooked Beef
Please enjoy
The next one,
Here it comes! The fried rice
Very nice!
This is something you'd order the first time
Well we haven't had fried rice yet
How is it Hamada-san?
It's great. It's a standard dish.
The Yurinchi is very juicy
They started off in high sprits,
But now their chopsticks refuse to move
We might get a 5-person give up for the first time
Never seen before,
Everyone but Fujiwara giving up
You're right
It's no longer a situation where one person breaks
If everyone agrees,
How about whoever has the most grams left loses?
Whoever leaves behind the most loses?
In the end, everyone but Fujiwara couldn't finish
They decide the loser by measuring the leftovers' weights
These 2 are the main issue right?
Alright, starting with Hosei-san
229 grams... Plus
182 grams, for Hosei-san.
I think I've lost this
205 grams,
Plus,
218 grams.
The rest of us have less?
Well the quantity...
Hold on, Hamada's is...
Hamada-san's is suspect
201 grams.
201 and...
215 grams.
Time for the results,
The person with the most loses right?
Yes, it's their loss
This time,
These are the results!
Oh no, hold on
I hate this!
It's not a large difference
Just 7 grams
He lost by 7 grams
I don't wanna lose by 7 grams!
With that, Matusmoto has to pay for everything
What does 7 grams look like?
Yeah, what does it look like
There's five grams.
Six grams... just a little more.
Seven grams.
This is how much he lost by
It's one bite!
It really is just one bite!
Timed & Typset by GakiDave
Translated by senor_wristband