Translation: Mickstar813 ~ Typesetting: YamasakiGIFs
I want to summon up all of my 46 years of living.
For Housei's 46 birthday he's doing a 24 hour long interview!
Narrator:
Yamada
Shinichi
Speaking about his whole life,
he will talk for 24 hours straight, this is a new challenge.
Loads of unknown stuff from his past!
When I was in middle school, I bought like 'eccentric clothing for delinquients'.
For real?
Are you mucking about?
7 HOURS SINCE THE START
I formed the band in 1st year.
What kind of activities did you do?
We performed in a studio.
In front of people?
Well, we didn't perform in front of people but...
The interview continues without rest for 15 hours
Time seems to stop for him...
As he starts to reach his limit, he continues to talk.
An emotional episode about Tsukitei Happo
getting him into the Kyoto Rakugo Association
And then in the middle of his massage,
he talks about how Tsukitei Happo defended him
whilst the other rakugoka's were against him.
He tells us a touching story of how he got to be a rakugoka.
"If Housei does something wrong, I'll quit"
For him to do that much for me...
I've never thought it was possible for someone to do that...
Those are some disgusting tears, eh!?
Damn!
Jesus!!!
What a disgusting picture!
Questions answered from his
childhood to his move to rakugo
Up until now, the amount of questions he has answered is...
1006 Questions
And there's more!
Character count from his childhood to his move to rakugo
There has been a total of 160,242 characters written.
Will Housei be able to beat the 24 Hour Interview!?
2:28AM...
17 hours and 28 minutes since the start
There's 6 and a half hours 'till the finish.
Now that the massage is over, the interview starts back up.
Hmm.. Let's see...
Now we enter into the frank questions.
What did you eat yesterday?
Eh~ What did I eat....?
Eh~ What did I eat!?
First, let's try to remember breakfast.
I didn't eat breakfast.
I just remembered it was Shabu-Shabu.
For breakfast?
Not for breakfast.
I had it in the evening.
Where?
Huh?
In Osaka...
Namba.
How did it taste?
Is there nothing more to ask?
You would
react like that.
I don't care...
18 hours and 1 minute since the start
6 hours remain until the finish.
Now for the next question.
Could you wake up please Housei-san?
The interview continues as he fights
against the temptation to sleep.
Who do you like better, Endo or Tanaka?
Endo.
I really like Endo when he's doing High Tension.
High Tension - A series of Gaki episodes
Alright.
What time is it?
You're lying~
Eh~ Only 2 hours have passed since then?
You've got to be kidding me...
This is bad!
What do you play with your kids?
Right now, jigsaw puzzles.
I bought a 1000 piece puzzle of 'The Seven Deities of Good Luck'
Have you finished it yet?
No~
Right now, just the frame.
Could you show me your piano skills?
♫ Hums "Merry Christmas, Mr. Lawrence" ♫
What the hell is this!!
Are you okay Housei~?
When do you think rock died?
Rock hasn't died.
Rock will continue to live forever.
It's like he's preaching!
Do you ever feel old?
I'm feeling it right now.
My farts just don't stop.
It's not something I can control with my will anymore.
It's getting
brighter!
It's not something I can control with my will anymore.
They've just started running wildly...
Is your hair okay?
It hasn't changed at all.
It has.
Your hair seems black
but you haven't started balding?
No, no I have not.
I get picked on about it.
It's honestly a joke.
We just do it as friends.
What do you love about your wife?
She's just so kind.
Her kindness is just so deep.
The city starts to bustle around once it's daybreak.
22 Hours and 3 minutes
There is now 2 hours remaining.
Amazing huh?
As the interview prepare's for the next question
What sort of question will she throw at him!?
Up until now the interviewer has thrown various questions at him,
what will she throw at him next in the remaining 2 hours!?
Is there anything you want me to ask you?
So this is what
happens, huh?
Damn,
that was funny.
"Is there anything
you want me
to ask you?"
And he's
struggling to
answer that...
Hmm...
I don't think there's anything I want you to ask.
If you were born as a girl
what sort of job would you want to do?
A woman's clothes designer.
I think women understand women's clothes the best...
I think being a designer would be cool.
What would be your brand name?
I'd want to attach "HOUSEI" to it.
But would everyone pronounce it as "HOUSE"?
Oh yeah, that's true.
I think if I did it
「ＨＯＵＳＥ - i 」。
Oh I don't give a shit.
What about the image of it?
Coco Chanel herself said what the best colour was.
Black, this is the best colour.
So...
HOUSE-i would have to have the 'best colour.'
So what colour would that be for you?
I think it's got to be black.
The same!?
So it would look a lot like Chanel clothing...
Yeah but there is no other colour...
Well HOUSE-i is
not Coco Chanel's rebirth or anything,
but I would want to go with black.
Since we are now talking about fashion,
when you look back on your life
there were a few stories about your fashion
choice so I just want to touch on that again...
So in middle school,
you were wearing 'eccentric clothing for delinquents'?
After that, you were a surfer?
Yea, that's right.
A complete surfer.
What was
the fashion?
Trainers of course.
Weren't you too hot wearing trainers on a beach?
What the hell...
A surfer wearing
trainers....
What the
hell is this!
Whenever it gets
bad he goes to
drink something!
Since the start.
It looks like when things are
getting bad you go for a drink huh~
When this interview is over why don't you
phone your wife and tell her how happy you are?
Yea, that's good.
What do you think your wife is going to say?
She'll be like "Oh my god, great work
that must have been so tough!
But seriously, great work.
What time are you coming home today?"
Umm...
Tonight I have my birthday party.
Were you the type of person to always accomplish his goals?
Like 'Once you start, you always accomplish it'?
No, I wasn't.
And that's why for example,
I've never finished a jigsaw puzzle.
So the Fukuwarai you're doing right now...
Fukuwarai - 'Lucky Laugh' a game
similar to Pin The Tail On The Donkey.
Fukuwarai?
Were you not playing Fukuwarai with your daughters...?
Wait I'm wrong... What was that jigsaw puzzle?
What was it again?
'The Seven Deities of Good Luck.'
Yes...
Sorry, when we carried on speaking after this...
I just got really sleepy there...
Yeah, I mean I'm not really surprised...
23 hours and 46 minutes since the start
Finally we visit the moment of fate.
And now, finally we have nearly finished the 24 hours.
Yep.
This really is the last question.
Yes.
What do you feel looking back on this whole experience?
Looking back on it I...
I didn't think I'd talk about my wife so much.
I think, I was saved by my wife.
My wife and I are the protagonists.
My fate is my wife's fate and my wife's fate is my fate.
If my wife is working hard
I'll work just as hard.
The philosophy I just said,
my wife shares the same view.
I consult first with my wife.
Everything is my wife.
There's a saying 'If you're going to die, die on stage'...
Well I've never thought I would die on stage.
When that happens, I want my family...
at least my wife, by my side.
I guess the stage is fine, as long as she is watching.
The thing he learned from this challenge
is his deep love for his wife.
Good morning!
24 hours is up, congratulations!
He calls his wife to convey the emotions he's
feeling after the 24 Hour interview.
For the sake of informing his achievement,
he calls his wife.
I'm gonna call her.
Alright.
You've reached the voicemail service from AU.
When you hear the signal....
Well! Let's go home.
24 Hour Long Interview complete
With this the curtain for the 24 hour long interview
comes to a close.
Maybe she was sleeping?
Yeah, probably...
At 9 AM?
At 9 AM.
If I could, this time... Um...
My interview
was transferred onto paper
Ah, amazing!
Uwa!
There is a character count of 225,037 characters.
Because a normal novel contains 70,000 characters,
this is 4... No 3 times more!
Amazing!
Wait a second Matsumoto.
Please try reading it.
Because of the Baby Boom Age, there were too many for one class~
In 1st year was there 8 classes... Or 9 classes...
Maybe there was 10 classes?
How many were there then...?
Well, this thing...
No, no, please read more!
No, no, no.
I've already watched enough!
Seriously, it's all actually been written here...
Well then, with this,
I'm publishing a book!
Of this!?
Yes.
Oh, right.
So you are asking if someone wants to publish that?
Yeah, that's right.
So you're going to ask them to contact you...
That's completely different to what you said...
It's totally different...
So get this published, huh?
But what are you going to do with this, if no one wants to publish it?
But this, I somehow want to...
As it is now, why don't you stick it in the
drawer beside the bed in hotel rooms?
Instead of the bible?
It'll be a hotel guideline.
They'd be surprised huh? Thinking "What is this?"
To all the publishers who may want to publish this
I will be waiting to hear from you.
Everyone here will do their best promoting the book.
So please, I am counting on you!
5 Minute Free Talk
When did you cry recently?
We've got a postcard!
Alright.
Hello everyone, when I was watching the Olympics,
I saw the various skills and abilities of people like Mao Asada.
It gave me a rush of emotions and I cried a lot.
Lately, I've had the feeling you guys cry at more things,
have you cried at the Olympics or at anything in your daily lives?
This is like serious...
Not like the person who wrote this.
Like properly crying...
Yeah.
I was watching unedited footage of the opening ceremony,
on the television in real time of course.
The Olympics?
Yes, the opening ceremony.
They lit the Olympic torch
and you know they do that thing...
Then finally it was lit but
at that time I sort of leaned forward out of my kotatsu.
That was amazing.
Because of all the tension at that time,
I don't know if I'd call myself easily brought to tears but
I cried!
Actually I want to talk about something a bit different...
I remembered this recently, and during middle school…
Downtown's middle school happening!!
I was with Hamada for ages.
Actually I want to talk about something a bit different...
I remembered this recently, and during middle school…
I was with Hamada for ages,
and we were at someone's house.
We were watching the
closing ceremony of high school baseball.
Closing ceremony, that's what it's called, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Hamada was like "I want to watch the closing ceremony."
Yeah...
And I had no idea at all why he wanted to watch it...
Like why the hell do you want to watch that?
And this program called 'Our Journey' was on at the same time,
something like that anyway...
Like a drama series...
And I really wanted to watch that...
He was like "No no, Mattsun, just no."
We're obviously going to watch the
closing ceremony of the high school baseball.
I was like what the fuck!?
I thought he was kidding at first.
There's no way someone would
want to watch a high schooler...
Like literally...
I was thinking "How could you want to watch that?"
It was like the first time ever we nearly got in a fight...
When I think about it now, I still don't get it.
Like why the hell did you want to watch that...?
Obviously, we should've watched 'Our Journey'...
Yeah, I get you... When I think about it now.
Why the hell did you want to watch it then!?
I wonder what made me want to...
And it was the closing ceremony as well...
It was, yeah... And then
I was like, "Wait, are you serious?"
Like, "What is fun about that?"
But before it, isn't there the actual final?
Yes.
No, the final had already finished.
It finished...
No, so..
So the winners and losers came together and...
No, that finished as well...
The final finished and it was like "Okay, it's finished"...
And to be honest, I don't really care too much
for high school baseball anyway...
And I was like "Okay, great, 'Our Journey'
is about to start on TV so let's switch the channel"...
You were like "Just no... Let's watch the closing ceremony"
I was like, no, no, no, no...
What the hell!?
You were like, "No, just no... Seriously, just no..."
I'm serious...
No, no, no...
Obviously there was a reason he wanted to watch it...
I was like, "What the hell!! He's messing with me!"
Like...
You were like, "Obviously I want to watch it...
Everyone was trying so hard..."
I'm serious, I'm serious!
"Everyone was trying so hard
and the winner has been decided...
Obviously I want to watch the closing ceremony..."
I don't know...
I was like "WHAT...!?"
Maybe I wanted to see the reaction and stuff...
Maybe that was it...
Yeah and he wanted to watch that...
No way would you want to watch that...
Who gives a shit about the aftermath...
To this day, I do not understand the reason...
I don't really remember what actually happened that day...
I just can't shake it off...
You were about to fight...
Yeah...
We were literally so close to a full on fight...
I asked so many times, "But why, just why?"
He would just answer, "'Cause everyone tried so hard."
Tanaka's scary first meeting with Hamada!?
"They tried so hard"?
Oh just cut it out!!
Yesterday, Matsumoto-san
talked to us about when
we first met...
Does everyone here like remember how they felt when meeting each other?
So for example, when Housei-san met Downtown...
Like your first impressions of them...
Of course.
What was it like?
I don't remember at all.
The second chome theatre.
Oh really?
Yes.
You were on that program 'It's 4pm apparently'.
* Broadcast from April 6, 1987
to September 29, 1989
That far back huh?
The time of that program?
Yeah, "It's 4pm apparently" was starting to take off.
So we were like 23, 24 years old...
Yeah, that's right.
Hamada-san was
you met me next to the corridor next to the audience.
And I said "Good morning", you were like "Oh, morning."
You were a bit scary but you said "Oh, morning."
Oh, he didn't run and try and hit you?
What the hell, why would I hit him?
He was just like "Oh, good morning"...
How about Matsumoto?
He was in his dressing room
and was reading a newspaper.
And when I said, "Good morning!"
He was like, "Yeahhh"...
Damn... You wouldn't even look him in the eye...
Damn that's scary...
He wouldn't even look you in the face.
When I first said my greetings to Hamada-san...
We were filming for Gaki at Sanseido...
Oh yeah...
And we finished the opening and we went to say hello...
I mean my part didn't get into the final edit that time...
So we were at the car park, waiting...
And Hamada-san walked in front of us.
We were like, "Good morning"...
He didn't even look at our face and just said "Yeah"...
He does that, right?
Like I remember it so well...
You should definitely look them
in the eyes and say hello at least...
That goes for you too then!!
You'd think that's common sense, right?
I was told that I was going to be on Gaki
and they told me, "From next week."
And the week before,
I went to introduce myself to you two.
But I had already met you right?
Yes, Matsumoto-san, you had.
At Tokyo station, right?
And I was just...
for the first time, I went to introduce myself to you.
Oh, was it?
I said "My name is Cocorico and I will
be working with you from next week."
"My name is Tanaka..." That is what I was going to say.
And as I said "Oh, I am Cocorico's Tanaka...
I will be working with you from next week..."
You had already walked off...
Just as a human being...
Don't take the piss!
I was literally just like this...
I hate people like that...
I really hate people like that.
You've got to be kidding me.
It makes me want to quit Yoshimoto.
Surely you don't feel that strongly about it...
It's important though...
I was probably in a rush...
Yeah probably, I was stuttering a bit...
In my first and second year...
Along with 'All Hanshin Kyojin'
when I was meant to introduce myself
I was just so nervous.
Before I introduced myself to them...
I was thinking in my head,
"You're introducing yourself to All Hanshin Kyojin"...
So I knocked and said "Excuse me..."
I said "Nice to meet you, I am All Hanshin Kyojin"...
This is real.
I just freaked out.
That's so scary!
I really freaked out...
That...
If they had taken that the wrong way they could've
been like "Who does this punk think he is...?"
They hadn't heard what I said...
No no no, that wasn't it...
Was it not?
They reacted to what you said in your favour...
Did they?
They said "That's US!" to him.
That was so good!
No, seriously.
Forget that, your impersonation of him was so good!
What is with that high quality??
Oh, really?
Surely you didn't need to make that impersonation that good...
Was it really that good?
Yeah, it was.
He said "That's US" whilst laughing...
No, the one before was better!
Oh just leave it.
Yeah, he said that to you.
Was it? I was just so nervous...
So he must have thought,
"Oh, this poor kid must be so nervous"
and reacted to make you less nervous...
That was probably it.
Yeah, probably.
Yeah, they could probably
tell you were just nervous.
And Hamada-san as well,
I had just watched you always on TV and
I was to introduce myself to you...
I was like in the same state...
I was like so nervous and seriously...
I was so close to saying,
"Nice to meet you, I'm Hamada."
Seriously, I just held back
and panicked at the time...
Well if you had said it,
he would as usual just have hit you.
Don't you have anything else to ask...?
Gaki no Tsukai #1198 (2014.03.30) - Heipo Review