English Checker
James
Mickstar
Sacro
Team Gaki Presents
Translator
Typesetter
TG
The hell you looking at?
You fools...
Okay, so today...
The losers had to do a Batsu Game,
so that happened...
And this really was something...
So let's get the losers out here
Come in!
Well well well everyone
Yup!
It was a magnificent
Yup...
Batsu Game apparently...
So ummm... Our team morale is really low right now...
You're right
We're so sorry...
Yeah I mean I went to greet you guys a few times during the Batsu Game...
But damn, it was like a nest for old men
Just a nest of old men, right?
And I've heard rumours from a few of the guys and we've done a lot of Batsu Games in the past
But this was the toughest one, according to them anyway...
Oh for sure...
Seriously...
That Batsu was just...
Don't speak, Tanaka...
Damn man, your voice...
Don't worry, you can speak...
He was talking through his nose, right?
You're speaking through your nose so much, so don't speak
It's the effects of the Batsu Game, right?
Yeah seriously, it's down to that Batsu Game!
It was literally that severe a Batsu Game!
30 minutes before the start
7:30 AM
Day of the Batsu Game
The morning of the Batsu Game
The losers come one after another to the Batsu location...
The losers
arrive to the Batsu location one after another...
And their faces show some nerves
Don't film me fucking first thing in the morning!
Don't film me!
I don't even want to be on TV!
5 minutes before the start
7:55 AM
5 minutes before the start of the batsu game
24-hour Endurance Tag (Oni Gokko) Game Venue
Hamada, Cocorico and others: Losers of 100 metres Batsu Game
The members are able to smile about the situation
Where is it?
It's through these doors
Wait, we're going in already?
Wait, does it start as soon as we enter?
Oh man...
Man, I don't want to do this
How is it?
Take a look...
Damn, it's huge...
Wait, what...
It's so big!
It's been layered with vinyl.
It's about 8 o'clock now...
For real?
Are we starting?
We're already starting?
It starts at 8 o'clock
At 8 o'clock?
Who the hell decided that?
Why do we have to start at this time...
Thank you...
Damn this thing is scary
Man it's so huge...
Wait, what are the rules?
24 Hour Tag: The Rules
If a Oni catches you, you get severely punished
Stay 24 hours in the gymnasium
When a Oni comes out, the game of Tag starts
m 0 0 l 1203 0 l 1203 343 l 0 343 l 0 0
Damn...
Man, our voices really echo in here...
You're right...
This is amazing
And like why the hell
Our voices really does echo in here...
are there oxygen cans here?
Will we have to use them?
What the hell?
Come gather around these boobs!
Manager
Fujiwara Hiroshi
Matsumoto's messenger
This guy's an idiot...
Guys, quickly come here a second...
What is it, Fujiwara-san?
For real?
That's his actual way of greeting...
Give us a break...
Good morning
Come gather around these boobs!
Morning
Why the hell, for the likes of you,
did I have to wake up this early...
Well anyway...
We're going to start the 24 hours of horror tag...
Matsumoto-san has passed on any orders he has for you to me...
So make sure you listen to me as if I am Matsumoto-san
Especially you, Hamada
Yep...
Are you an idiot?
No
Oh, sorry...
For real?
He actually apologised as well...
But Hamada, usually you know...
What?
Yep...
You try to show how much of a bad guy you are...
But today, you have to make sure to listen to everything
that Matsumoto-san has to say
Okay...
Okay well, we're going to start, so do your best...
Starting in 3 seconds
24-Hour Tag
m 0 0 l 1222 0 l 1222 308 l 0 308 l 0 0
Starting in 2 seconds
Starting in 1 second
Man, he's annoying
BATSU GAME START!!
Paper Fan (Harisen)
What the hell!
Wait, there's more..?
You got everyone, you got everyone, you got everyone!
He's going to get all of us, everyone?
There's so many of them!
Ladle
Another one came out...
Damn man, this really is scary...
You're still really energetic, as expected I suppose
Yeah, still at this point...
We can still run at this point...
We've just started after all...
Wait wait wait....
This guy...
Thai Kick
This was the scary one
This one scared the shit out of us, right guys?
Shit, shit, shit... Why me?!
What what what?!
What the hell is this?
What's going on?
What what what?!
What... what?!
You got to be kidding me...
This really is something...
And because he's wearing his bloody shoes, it really hurts...
Hamada-san, are you okay?
This is...
This is a bit...
This is much worse than I thought...
Are you okay?
It's only been 3 minutes since we started
Hold on a minute...
We're going to die...
We will...
This is amazing, this early in the morning...
It is...
I...
I received all 3 punishments...
You did as well...
It was so painful...
Do you think they'll let me go home?
It's been about 3 minutes...
Just running is hard enough...
Yeah it is.
I feel physically sick...
Really?
Wait Yamasaki, how old are you?
I'm 32...
And you guys are twenty...
eight
Eight...
And you, Hamada-san?
You're the youngest here...
Hamada-san, how old are you this year?
37...
Damn Hamada-san, you're turning 37 already?
Seriously, I think my ribs have gone
Oh here we go again...
No, seriously
Give us a break...
Yamasaki claims that he has fractured
his ribs
For real?
You said recently that your rib was broken as well...
Yeah, that's right...
No no
It's definitely...
It's not broken, but it's definitely fractured
What, from just before?
You just fell over...
You fractured it just from that?
There's no way it's fractured
No... Seriously, my body is like that
You couldn't have broken it just by that...
No no
It's not broken, but it's fractured
Seriously...
Damn, you really are trying to push the "fracture" thing, huh?
Man I'm so pissed, I'm running away, seriously...
Doing this for 24 hours...
It's going to be so tough on me...
There's no way it's fractured...
No, but like seriously...
It would have to have been something severe for there to be a fracture...
Please don't do that!!!
I was just practicing...
Why?!
I got so scared!
Please don't do that!
Please tell us you're going to practice then!
Oh okay, sorry my bad...
Oh man...
Let's not do this to each other...
See, it's not fractured, is it?
But your movement was totally fine...
There was nothing wrong with you, after all...
Okay fine, show me...
He's definitely lying...
What the hell..?
Wait, where are you going, I'll smack you!
What is it?
Come, gather around these boobies
What the hell..?
I brought you your breakfast
Oh, for real?
Even for the likes of you, Matsumoto-san said
that he would feed you
He really is as kind as the Buddha himself
But before you eat
"Even for the likes of us, you have given food, Matsumoto-san, thank you very much
Even for the likes of us, you have given food, Matsumoto-san, thank you very much
Once you've said that, you may eat
Even for the likes of us
Together now..
you have given us food
I'm so hungry right now...
you have given us food...
Matsumoto-san
Matsumoto-san...
Thank you very much
30 minutes since the start
8:30 AM
Breakfast time
Why the hell do I have to eat breakfast feeling so nervous?
Unsure of when an Oni may appear,
they keep their shoes on...
We couldn't take our shoes off right? Cause we didn't know when they could come
That's right
Yeah...
Cause we didn't know when they could come
What the hell, man...
For crying out loud, please stop that kind of thing!
What's going on?
No, you got it all wrong
This guy...
Come on, man...
You're overreacting way too much...
No, of course I would be shocked...
No, it's not like that
The lighter for my cigarette slipped and hit here
So I was like "Oh shit"...
Please stop that kind of thing...
Like seriously...
Just moving like that once is so tiring...
Sorry man...
That's not cool...
The group even reacts to Hamada's fart
Did you get scared?
Yes! I thought the Oni were coming from over there this time...
If you're going to fart, tell us all, okay?
From here on
Why is my bum going off now..?
One blow
That's amazing though...
I'm begging you
You're finished right, you're finished now right?
You're finished, right?
Are you serious right now..?
He's coming again?
Wait a minute, man...
Hamada-san, what are you doing?!
This is serious, man...
This is... yeah...
This is bad...
Hamada-san, did you try and use me as a shield before?
You're imagining things...
Am I imagining things?..
I could've sworn Hamada-san tried to use me as a shield...
My apologies; I must be imagining things...
No problem...
Hamada-san, what are you doing?!
See?
Dirty Hamada tries to use Endo
as a shield
1 hour since the start
9:00 AM
If everyone ran and one of us just sat here and pretended not to be here,
do you not think we'll be safe?
Oh hell no...
"Hide from the oni using the kotatsu" plan
Planning stages
Why?
Yamasaki, try it.
No way...
Just sit here and don't move...
We actually might be able to get away with it...
Right?
Yes
No...
Because they'll chase the thing that's running away from them
Yeah exactly
I honestly believe
Yeah, when you see something running
Just please, try it once
It might work...
Wait a second, why do I have to do it?
You never know...
Let's do rock-paper-scissors...
What?
Rock-paper-scissors...
Shall we?
Yeah...
No, guys, it's only him!
What the hell is with this noise!?
Come, gather around these boobs!
Enough, man!
What the hell is with that?
He's really getting to us with it...
Here. Matsumoto-san said,
"Your haemorrhoids seem to be bothering you, so take this."
This is the one I brought along with me this morning...
Matsumoto-san said "take it"...
Oh okay... Thank you.
He really is like the Buddha himself
1 hour 50 minutes since the start
9:50 AM
So we're sacrificing the person sitting here to them?
No no.
No, so we will run away.
Oh okay, I get it. So one of you will get caught.
That's...
Why the hell did you move?!
Headbutt
Move, move, move...
Oh come on!!
He's been targeted!
Oh shit this is bad!
Oh damn, he got separated from the pack.
Are you okay?
Hamada-san...
You fuckers left me and ran...
You left me and ran...
I heard a proper sound when he headbutted me...
Hey man...
Yeah...
Why did you run?
You were meant to stay there...
We couldn't see if our experiment would work!
Yeah...
Come on Hosei-san, let's do as agreed...
Wait...
What?
It's not that easy to do...
"Our experiment"...
Hamada-san, are you okay?
I'm so sorry, Hamada-san...
Let's go with teamwork, guys...
No, don't give me that, I saw you guys running as a pack and leaving me behind...
I'm sorry...
10 AM
2 hours since the start
You get shocked first as they come out
And then you react and you get shocked again
And then it hits you properly... I mean how many shocks do I have to have every time?
You'll definitely get nightmares...
You definitely would...
I just see their heads...
Just the head?
Yeah
The head itself
Figure 4 leg-lock
Wait, why?!
Why me!?
You can't drift away from the pack
Wait for me, wait for me
This one's a bad one...
Come on guys, wait for me.
Which way are you going?
Ready, set...
Hold on a minute...
HAMADA-SAN!
No, when I tried to run away...
Hamada-san blocked my path!
No way.
You blocked me, didn't you..?
Really?
Dirty Hamada blocks Tanaka's way...
Is there really no way to escape this?
With the next one, shall I hide in the middle?
Yes please...
Will you?
And if that works, let's keep rotating
Yeah, let's keep rotating.
Yeah...
So we will run as fast as possible.
Distract him...
Yes, we will be the distraction
Wait, hold on, I'm going first? Isn't that a bit strange?
What's wrong all of a sudden?
Um... why?
What's up, all of a sudden?
Well, after thinking about it, at the beginning we told Yamasaki to do it...
So shouldn't he have to do it first?
In the name of teamwork...
Okay then, let's do that...
It was decided on Hosei-san
You chickened out before: that's what went wrong
We haven't tried it once yet.
So when you say hide, like when you hear the noise and
Do you want to practice once?
go like this...
Well yeah, that's good
That's great
You're totally in their blind spot
And we will act as the distraction
Yeah, I was thinking, "We said Yamasaki would do it first so why the hell should I have to do it?"
I understand...
If worst comes to worst and you get captured, it's for everyone's sake.
For everyone's sake...
I understand.
We're counting on you, this next one, seriously
You always say that, but then you just run away again...
I promise I won't this time...
If I run away this time, I will feel the shame I brought upon myself
But then that's it, right?
You're kind of used to that already, no?
But you know, I said Yamasaki had to do it, but if Yamasaki says Tanaka has to do it, then Tanaka has to do it
But you know, I said Yamasaki has to do it, but if Yamasaki says Tanaka has to do it, then Tanaka has to do it
Then Tanaka, you do it.
No no, my body is too large and all...
It's either Yamasaki or Tanaka. Do rock-paper-scissors.
Wait, how has this happened?
No, I'm not backing down here
Whoa whoa whoa...
This isn't right...
Hurry up and do it...
On the count of 3
1 match
"Hide from the oni using the Kotatsu plan":
Tanaka will try first!
We're counting on you.
Okay, okay...
Shall we try it once then?
and even if it doesn't...
Sharpshooter (wrestling move)
What was it?
Sharpshooter...
Tanaka celebration!
Amazing
So that's how onis are...
That hurt so much...
But, thanks to you, I was saved
We found an escape route...
We found a way?
It's so nice...
Next up...
It was so nice
Next up is Hamada-san, right?
Have a break
You'll be fine, if that was fine, you will definitely be fine.
Do you not think it's a bit of a stupid way of thinking?
What?
No, they clearly just don't look here...
Yeah, I mean I ran around this area and he didn't notice you at all...
So please rest up this time, Hamada-san...
Oh man, I should've gone first...
Futon beater
Tanaka's voice...
Hamada-san...
You did it.
This really does
work well, eh?
It really does
Thai Kick
Oh man, he's found you...
He's found you...
Oh man, this is the worst!
Wait, wait, oh shit! It's a Thai Kick!
Wait, wow, no no, please!
It's the worst punishment too...
Hey, ouch, ouch!
That was unprecedented...
Zaki-san...
Wait, what happened?
So the Oni  found you
he saw you
When he came about here
20 hours remaining
Noon
His boobs are moving everywhere, that's disgusting
Come, gather around these boobs!
I still can't tell the difference...
I know...
Yeah...
Even though we were just talking about it...
I've brought you lunch
Yes...
The reason that scum like you
can eat like normal people
is truly down to Matsumoto-san.
So work hard from here on in as well, to ensure you don't become dead weight to Matsumoto-san
Right then, shall we say how grateful we are to Matsumoto-san again and then eat?
Even for the likes of us,
Even for the likes of us...
Hamada... altogether
Right, ready?
Even for the likes of us...
you have given food.
Matsumoto-san,
Matsumoto-san...
from the bottom of my heart,
from the bottom of my heart...
Thank you.
Thank you...
Right then...
Lunch Time
4 hours from the start
The 4 cannot hide their fatigue
All they can do is eat their curry...
The 4 get scared at the smallest of sounds...
Anyone would be like this
Yeah, it was like this the whole time
You guys
So annoying...
That was so annoying...
You were so scared of Fujiwara's "Pon-pon" as well...
That's what happens!
Learn the difference!
Between the sounds, right?
When someone moves, you move...
Picture Story-show
What the hell...
What is it?
I was so tired...
Where are you going?
Where is he taking you?
A picture storyteller arrives!
Something's coming...
Everything's black, that's what makes it creepy...
Yeah, everything is black...
Once upon a time...
There was an old man and an old woman
Momotaro
One day, the old man went to the mountains
and the old woman went to the river to wash laundry
The woman was washing her clothes
when suddenly, a peach
There's absolutely nothing drawn...
came floating down
The old woman got her axe...
He gets angry unless you watch properly...
4 minutes later
and they lived happily ever after...
The End...
Absolutely no point...
He just stole some of your stamina...
Are you okay?
That's so true...
Did you see?
Yes, we stayed around...
That was awful..
Everything was just black
1 PM
19 hours remaining
If this bends, then I'll believe in it...
Yeah, you would...
I mean if that happened
You would have to
Yeah, true.
I would definitely believe it
I would too...
But why is it a spoon? Can you bend forks?
Out of boredom,
the 4 start to try bending spoons
Do you bend forks?
I've never seen that happen
Candle burn
Holy shit, he's fast
He's so fast!
Picture Story-show
Here he comes again...
He saw him walking very slowly...
What story even is this?
The tortoise and the hare
and the hare laughed
at the tortoise
Oh, the tortoise and the hare
Yes.
3 minutes later
He had to watch the whole time!
It's all black...
I'm off ahead then!
He has to watch it all.
...happily ever after...
Nothing he could do
The End
Headbutt
That would be scary
Wait, wait, this isn't right!
Oh damn!
When the "Headbutt" thing came up,
he was like "Wah!"
I did not expect a headbutt to come out of that...
3 PM
Remaining 17 hours
I wonder if there are no snacks...
I want a snack...
I want to eat some snacks too...
I'm tired so something sweet...
Yes, something sweet.
I want to too.
Pie
Gaki no Tsukai Producer
The World's Heipo
What's with this guy? Oh it's Heipo!
He's trying to attack us?
For real?
We can beat this guy!
No no no no...
We can win!
Ow...
Ow, that hurts...
What the hell do you think you're doing!?
Go home!
You're the worst!
He failed so miserably...
As he shot up, he dropped the whole plate...
That was Saito-san, right?
Awful
So awful
He is an awful person
He's trying to kill this project
Even when we're working our asses off running away...
When we see him next time, we'll be able to tell from his feet.
Right at the beginning
Yeah, he ran all over the pie...
When he shot up, he dropped it all...
What the hell, guys?
You reacted first...
Come, gather around these boobs
Oh!
I mean, if you do it for 6 hours,
that's how one would react...
Oh awesome, snacks!
Cookies, huh?
Guys, it's 3 o'clock.
Hamada
Yes
What do we think of when we say 3 o'clock?
Snacking...
Don't say stupid things!
Sorry
I brought you some snacks, as it's 3 o'clock
What the hell...
So it's fine...
And on top of that
Yeah, we don't need the remarks...
I brought you a game to play too.
Whilst you live out your pathetic lives, you should play the Game of Life
You got 20!
The 4 get so
happy playing the Game of Life
You get $250,000!
Here we go
Come on!
Matsumoto Hitoshi arrives at the scene
16 hours remaining
4 PM
Gaki no Tsukai Producer:
The World's Heipo
This guy is amazing...
God, he pisses me off
He's not developed at all...
Go home!
What the hell is this about?
He's the worst...
Go home!
Seriously, go home!
15 hours 30 minutes remaining
4:30 PM
The 4 return to their game
Oh, a boy.
A boy is born
Therefore, receive 5,000 yen... sorry, 1,000 yen from each player
There you go...
You got a baby boy...
Okay, here...
What the hell
Na na na na...
Man, that scared me!
That thing is so scary...
It really is...
How is it?
We're really sensitive to sounds right now, man...
Seriously, the slightest of sounds scares
Just come through the door normally...
the crap out of us...
And how is everything?
We were playing that just now...
Oh, I thought I would confiscate it...
Why?
He just got a baby boy...
Well because I was watching and you looked like you were having fun
"looked like we were having fun"...
so I thought, "Well, I'm not having that..."
Aww man, I just became a professional athlete...
Well alright then, everyone get naked.
Why the hell?
Why? Get naked and do what?
Wow, you're being kind of rude to me, huh?
It's annoying me a bit...
I may be coming back later...
No, you don't need to.
The next time I come,
I won't be anywhere near as nice as I am being now
I just came to tell you lot that...
Please give us a break...
I'm going to kill you all, starting with the tallest...
However you look at it, that's me...
However you look at it...
I mean kill... Really?
You got it?
But in all seriousness, please give that back
Yeah, please give that back
Just this even
No way.
That's my oxygen can...
At least the oxygen cans...
Who the hell do you think you're speaking to?
Tanaka, just take it from him.
Just who the hell do you think you're speaking to?
Tanaka, just take it from him...
Take it, Tanaka!
Please give this back to us...
No, don't, my back is hurting at the moment
Just leave our stuff alone
Seriously, my back is really bad at the moment
Stop that, you fool!
What's he up to now..?
Hey hey hey!
Wow wow, wait!
Come on, man!
Hey man!
Hey!
DIE!
He just said his back was hurting...
I'll be coming back!
No it's fine... Please don't come back
Oh man, he's ridiculous
He really goes too far...
Look at what he's done...
God this is horrible...
He's so pathetic, huh?
Yeah...
We got to get all the pieces for the game...
Yeah we do...
Yeah, we're going to need to find them
Yeah...
Oh man, the tea as well...
15 hours 10 minutes remaining
4:50 PM
By the way, why,
when you hear the sound, do you  instinctively go "Wah!"?
when you hear the sound, do you instinctively go "Wah!"?
Do I?
Yeah when you hear the sound, you always shout "Wah!"
However many times it happens, it scares me...
It really does...
Bum
Wait, why are there two of them?
Wait, hang on a minute!
Hang on a minute!
Wait, wait wait, oh my God I am going to smack you guys so hard!
What did it say?
Bum...
Bum?
Wait, wait, what?
What?
Hey, what are you doing!?
Oh that is just worst form of humiliation...
It was soft...
I see...
The feeling?
But one of them...
his asshole touched my nose...
Seriously?
My shoulder's started to hurt too...
Oh and what happened to your rib?
Oh the ribtotally has a fracture in it
Oh the rib totally has a fracture in it
Like for sure
But you were fine before...
Yeah...
That's true
You were playing the Game of Life totally fine
You were having the time of your life playing it...
That's because I didn't want to dampen the atmosphere by saying it hurt and stuff
while we're playing a game...
Open palm strike
This is bad!
This is really bad
I'm not getting caug-...
"Helper-man" appears
It's Helper-man!
Helper-man!
Oh, he stopped him!
As expected
Awesome
Great work, Helper-man!
Thank you!
Giant swing
Oh man, this is dangerous!
This is really dangerous!
I'm so tired...
I know...
Damn, that guy is huge!
14 hours 40 minutes left
5:20 PM
Bum
What? Again?!
No, please don't!
Wait, why the hell!?
Wait a minute...
That's a bad one...
Wait wait wait...
Thank God...
You did this before...
This is so bad
You literally just did this before to me!
You did this to me before!
Hamada-san, are you okay?
Hamada-san...
Hamada-san?
There he is...
Are you okay?
Are you?
That last one was something else
That was one amazing ass...
The hairs hurt a bit...
It was a proper black ass...
But on top of that...
His balls were just... the whole time...
rubbing up and down?
His balls?
And the hair was like prickly...
For real?
Like lukewarm...
Just lukewarm, huh?
Batsu Game Headquarters
It's not like I enjoyed doing it!
I don't want to stick my ass on my partner's face!
I don't think the nervousness we felt
is really getting across to you guys.
Like literally if we heard anything, we would be on alert
And that was for the whole time...
You just don't get used to it, right?
The sounds, right?
Yeah...
And Hamada-san properly freaks out
so we get dragged along too...
You were the worst out of all of us, you idiot!
But with me it was just the fact I shouted, right?
No no, when we were in the
No, but that's what's scary...
And when we are all sitting in the kotatsu...
He would be the one guy going
Yeah, he did
He did...
Because I was scared...
When the Oni comes up, the noise is like 'Pshuuuu'
When Fujiwara come out, it's "Pon-pon"
Learn!
No no, seriously that is impossible
Every time it went "pon-pon", you guys were freaking out...
Honestly, it's impossible.
14 hours remaining
6 PM
10 hours since the start
Not knowing when the onis could appear
has stolen their smiles away...
From about here, conversations just...
Yeah, from around this point
Yeah...
You must just be defeated by this point...
Just a blank...
A blank...
That's so annoying...
Blanks are not on...
Ladle
This is so dirty!
Are you serious!
Shit
That's not fair...
That's so dirty...
Oh man, this is so scary
We don't even know where they could come from..
Oni sneaking in...
You did well to notice him though...
Who noticed him first? Was it Hamada-san?
Yeah, I was the first one...
That's right
And I thought "Please get Endo" so I didn't say...
Hamada notices the Oni
Oh yeah
Oh yeah, he's keeping quiet about it
Why are you keeping quiet about it? Please tell me!
I didn't care about you
Open palm strike
This guy...
He's a bit too fat...
He's so slow...
Like just hopeless...
He can't run well, can he?
Yeah, he's hopeless...
Yeah, he was
He can't turn well either...
That was quite funny...
I can outrun him...
13 hours 40 minutes remaining
6:20 PM
It's probably better if we all look in different directions
That's true
Right?
I will watch over there...
Then I will watch this area
The 4 start to watch all directions
I will watch this area over here
Then I will watch over here. And you, Yamasaki?
Where should I watch?
You should watch over there, surely?
Over there?
The area that's not covered by the skull...
No, just like
All of it?
This is so annoying...
Just... why?!
So annoying...
I don't know...
Come, gather around these boobs.
Oh...
You know...
Even for people with bodies like yourselves...
Matsumoto seems to be worried about you.
So as of this moment...
He's arranged for someone to give you a massage
I'm sure you all have pathetic excuses of bodies...
but why don't you get one anyway...
Hamada!
Yes?
Do your shoulders feel stiff?
Nope...
Do your shoulder feel stiff?
No...
Great...
He really is like a bodhisattva
Well then, if you would...
Alright, let's start with Hamada
Thanks to Matsumoto, a masseur appears
Starting with me?
Yes, a massage...
Umm, okay...
My whole body is stiff...
This seems safe...
I am so stiff
It should be, right?
Is it okay?
Yes it is.
Is he okay?
It's a bit tough to say...
Bow and Arrow Lock
Wait, what?
We cannot help you...
Oh damn...
Look at all of you, doing your jobs...
Why does he scream "Ahh" himself?
Gaki no Tsukai Producer:
The World's Heipo
Right, this time...
And what?!
He hit his head...
Are you okay?
He didn't say anything...
What a failure...
What is he trying to achieve?
12 hours 50 minutes remaining
7:10 PM
Damn man...
It really does scare you...
Come, gather around these boobs.
Yeah...
Even for the likes of you
Matsumoto said, "Let them eat some good food."
Wow, that looks amazing
It truly is...
Amazing...
There's steak...
He arranged for a first-class chef to prepare your meals...
Awesome...
It's a special dinner.
Great...
His kindness
really can be felt by  your internal organs
really can be felt by your internal organs
Great, let's take this food then...
Dinner time...
What?
You have something to say, right?
Oh, enough of that stuff...
Yeah...
Not until you say your thanks...
Shall we say it together then?
Even for the likes of us,
Even for the likes of us...
you have given us this fantastic meal.
you have given us this fantastic meal...
Matsumoto-san,
Matsumoto-san...
thank you very much.
thank you very much...
Right then...
He's really quick when running away...
Ittadakimasu
Dinner Time
Hoshi Ittetsu (Table Flipping)
God damn it!
I still had over half of my steak remaining...
For real?
I like to eat the most delicious
parts last...
Oh man, what a mess...
This is ridiculous!
My cushion was saved...
God damnit...
At least my cushion was saved...
12 hours 20 minutes remaining
7:40 PM
Come, gather around these boobs
Alright...
We're sorry...
We went a bit too far...
Matsumoto-san said...
"You're probably tired, so eat these sweets" and handed me these
Matsumoto-san's kindness truly knows no bounds
No, I'm fine
Eat it; you must be tired
No, your hands are so sweaty...
Well obviously...
You must be tired...
It's so sticky...
Oh no, no no...
You have to eat it...
I think it fell...
Hold on...
Here...
There's some stuff on it...
That's disgusting...
Just leave it out already...
Oh no, no no no...
What's he doing..?
This is ridiculous...
Tissue sticks...
What are you doing?
You're tired, right?
Alright, just leave it...
Don't spit it out, alright?
Matsumoto-san's kindness truly knows no bounds
He said it twice...
He said the same damn thing twice.
12 hours remaining
8 PM
Oh wow, 8PM, 12 hours in!
We had like an hour-long wait between things happening...
I know...
Until one would come out...
And the whole time, we were terrified...
Matsumoto-san said that you must be bored,
so he said he'd let  you watch a film
so he said he'd let you watch a film
Matsumoto-san's popularity truly rings through the continents
Matsumoto-san's popularity  truly rings through the continent
Right then...
I wonder what film...
I might fall asleep if they dim it this much...
Film Starts
Oh man, this is scary
Yeah...
Why do we have to watch something like this?
Oh, there it is...
A youthful and chivalrous movie
Showa Tetsufutai - Sea of Japan
1991 - Main Character played by Hamada Masatoshi
Blog Recipe Pictures
Everyone from Tetsufutai, led by Hamada goes wild
Is this Hamada-san's "Sea of Japan"?
Seems so...
Hamada Masatoshi (28 years old)
Damn, you're young there...
He really is...
You are here...
I really am, huh?
You truly are
1 hour 40 minutes later
Oh my god, that was scary
Tetsufutai
That is not on...
We were so shocked
Of course we'll be shocked if someone jumps through there...
That was terrifying
I was just getting relaxed...
10 hours 15 minutes remaining
9:45 PM
Another 10 hours...
About 10 and a half hours...
Damn but 10 hours from this point on...
Yeah, that's going to be really tough...
I'm shattered...
Yamasaki!
Yamasaki Slap
He said Yamasaki; just give up man!
Please just hurry up and get caught
He's got him!
Oh no!
Former Downtown Manager
Okamoto Akihiko
His precious cat just ran off somewhere...
It literally ran away as fast as it could...
Hello there...
Hello...
Great work
Great work...
Hosei-san...
Zaki-san...
Are you okay?
This is bad...
My rib is done, man...
My rib is hurting so much...
He did run in shouting "Yamasaki!"
He was going for me from the start
It seems so
Unfortunately...
It said "Yamasaki slap"...
You reacted really quickly there...
You all reacted too...
No no, you were really quick
You all stood up straight away
No, we reacted to you
Oh, piss off...
I just can't get used to it
Come, gather around these boobs
Okay...
Matsumoto-san said that you're probably getting hungry around about now...
So he prepared you a late night snack.
Cup ramen
Present from Matsumoto
So eat up
That's really touch sensitive, huh?
Hey, that one's starting to smell nice
It does...
What?..
What's wrong?
You're kidding...
No way!
Are you serious?
That's so annoying!
You pig!
Oh man, this is so tough!
It's fine, let's eat this one altogether
Shall we do rock-paper-scissors?
Okay
Let's decide an order
Rock-paper-scissors
Okay, I will go first...
Sorry...
Ittadakimasu
Go for it
Oh, he went for the fried tofu
He's gone and eaten half of the 1 piece of fried tofu available...
And he's eaten half of what remains...
The fried tofu is the best part of this kitsune udon
The soup is pretty good...
Yeah, it is
Damn, you eat a lot in one slurp...
You slurp like hell
The noodles all connected...
It really is, eh?
I thought it would be rude to just bite it off
That's a bit weird, no?
I thought it would be rude...
I was trying to make sure it was
I mean...
clean for the next person
That's disgusting, c'mon Hosei-san...
I'm sorry...
Like loads of stuff flew back into the soup...
I saw you spit stuff up...
No, I didn't...
I saw it...
It did...
The spring onion got caught in my throat...
Are you sure?
It's fine...
That's disgusting
What the hell is wrong with you?
You disgusting little fucker...
It flew back into the soup again...
How does that happen?
Yeah...
Seriously, why does that happen?
I can't eat quickly...
And you were pressuring me...
What, I wasn't at all...
Damn, that piece is small...
Oh sorry, you have to stop.
It's one mouthful
Like if you bring your chopsticks away, you're done...
Oh really?
Yeah, you have to do it all in one movement
Yeah...
You got to tell me that kind of stuff
Oh, sorry...
Really?
Yes
Okay, I'm going for my second go.
So I shouldn't have drunk the soup...
Yeah, because you lost out a bit there...
You got to tell me these kind of things from the start, I would have slurped way more...
My God, he's slurping away
Oh I get it, so those are the times you're meant to drink the soup?
Damn this is good...
Wait, this is okay?
This is okay...
His mouth is touching so it's okay.
In this instance, it's okay.
For real?
Yes
Under official rules,
next up is Hamada-san
Sorry, your turn is over
You pulled your chopsticks away
Your movement in general stopped
Why? It didn't stop; I ate it and went to drink
I mean, you know
It's fine and all...
But I mean, yeah
Take it then
You know, I am your senpai and all...
We go in order again...
There's no point getting upset about something like this
It's just drinking now...
Yeah
Yeah, there are no noodles left.
Oh, he's going for it
Wait, what? This isn't right.
He's engulfing it...
Because I am doing that it's safe
I think...
You're good with engulfing...
Engulfing...
He's doing it too
Oh damn, he's engulfing it like hell
This is so called "engulfing"?
Yes it is
When you engulf it,  there's a certain limit to how much you can engulf
When you engulf it, there's a certain limit to how much you can engulf
Oh, I see.
Oh, are you at your limit?
I finished it...
Thank you
Just in case
There is a tiny bit
That was beautiful technique...
Yeah?
Yes, that was great
That was beautifully done
Oh man, I'm full
The fried tofu is so good
Great, I am full
Pitching ball machine
Damn he's fast!
I would hate this one...
If you get caught by this one, you're in serious trouble
This one is going to hurt...
I would hate this one...
Wonton noodles
What the hell is this?
Oh damn
Man, I was scared for a second there
What's this?
Damn, you smell of Wonton...
10:30 PM
9 hours 30 minutes remaining
We enter the night, their physical and mental strength is under strain
And at this point, that man's comment will again
anger the other members
What's wrong with you now?
I have a fever...
You have a fever?
You broke your rib, your rashes broke out, you cut your ear and now you have a fever
Apparently his rashes broke out too...
Not in the slightest...
What the hell is that?
Diploma award tube
Give up already...
You did really well to outrun him...
See, your rib isn't broken, right?
It's too weird that you were moving your arms that well
It's a fracture, after all...
But even so,
however you look at it,
you looked healthy running...
No it's not that
When you're being chased, you have adrenaline going through you
10:53 PM
9 hours 7 minutes remaining
You, I'm going to smack you one, seriously.
You got way too scared just now...
You were the one...
You scared me...
It's because of him
Come, gather around these boobs
Okay!
Share this...
What is it?
Eat it together
Meat bun?
Another gift of food
Meat bun
Yes, it's a pork bun
I mean there are 4 of us
I don't really like splitting these kind of things...
Well we've had cup noodles too...
But you know, we can just split it down the lines on the bun
I think the order from before is fine...
I agree
Wait, why?..
I mean, doing rock-paper-scissors again is a bit...
It's a waste of time
Yeah, I agree
What, we have loads of time...
No listen, just cut it through the lines like this...
But some areas will have more meat than others...
That's true
It's not like the meat is going to be all
in the centre
Okay, well fine then
Alright, sorry about this
Yeah, we don't want to be taking too long
Yeah, it wouldn't be good
It's scary, after all
Okay, I'm going to take my bite...
Watch over there and eat...
Make sure you watch carefully while eating...
You never know when they may come
They could come anytime...
They really could...
There you go
You're all adults so you're probably not full quite yet, are you?
No, I'm pretty full
I'm pretty full
A bit
And so Matsumoto-san gave you another bit of food
Why only 1 all the time?
He said take this...
Thank you!
Split it evenly...
A sausage
Another gift
This one's easy to split
There's only one again...
This is easy to split
Yep...
So far
Just split it into 4 and we're good.
We've had cup noodles and a meat bun...
Wait, wait, if you guys are full...
No, I'm feeling peckish for something small
It's a differentstomach
It's a different stomach
Yeah, a different stomach
A different stomach
to fill
Okay fine, let's just divide this into four...
But...
But if we split this into 4 parts...
The ends...
It's softer in the centre
Oh who gives a shit?
Just man up...
Hang on a second
There's clearly a difference between here and here...
and that's the sticking point...
The edges, right?
Yeah...
What are you on about?
It shrinks at the ends...
It gets thinner
No it's not...
It is
Just open it and check then
The size doesn't change that much...
Keep a look out...
There's basically no difference...
It won't do...
Why not?
Because the edges are rounded
Wait, wait, why? Then you guys take the centre
and I'll take like this much from the edge
Then it's fine, right?
But then you'll be taking too much
Too much...
You guys don't want the ends, right?
Then I will take about this much from the end...
No I don't want it...
But then you'd be taking too much...
I don't think your seniority means anything here...
Alright, let's do this
Yup
We break it in half, and you guys start eating from the centre
Okay...
And then in exchange, just leave me about this much
Just the ends
Okay, yeah
Both ends
Yeah?
That would definitely work
Right?
Yes
That will definitely work
That way, no one has any problems...
Nope
Go for it
Leave some for Hamada-san, okay?
Just the end
Please leave Hamada-san some...
A bit for Hamada-san
Why are you putting it in your mouth once?
You know what, I don't want any
Hold on a second, Hamada-san
We were having trouble because we were doing it your way
Wait a second...
You're putting it in your mouth once though...
Because...
We don't know how much to cut off...
You're holding it in your hand
Can you not just leave a tiny bit hanging out of your mouth and bite?
But it's rounded at the ends so it just slips in...
As we said before...
I'm putting it in my mouth once
No no, don't speak to me with your mouth full
Just hurry up and swallow it!
I'm sorry...
Wait, why the hell are you telling him to swallow it?
So rude
I thought it was rude...
What about my piece?
You have a little bit left, give that to me
Bite down and cut it
Why the hell are you putting it in, dumbass?
Bite it!
No, don't put it in!
There you go...
Why the hell can't you just bite it normally...
Why the hell can't you just bite it normally?
No because it's rounded at the ends...
I mean, why are you twisting it?
I couldn't...
Can you not just bite down? Why are you twisting it and all?!
I'm sorry
It's not your fault...
You've eaten your piece
No I don't want that...
We had a deal, I asked you just to leave me a tiny bit of the ends...
Just bite it and leave me just the ends... I mean he's twisted it off so it looks weird...
Could you not just leave me a tiny bit?
But if you look at it, you've gotten
I was trying to see how much to bite off so I...
a pretty decent piece...
Are you all fucking idiots?
I'm sorry...
We're really sorry
We are really sorry
I will take care next time...
I just don't understand you lot...
We're so sorry
We're very sorry
Damn, I'm full now...
11:10 PM
8 hours 50 minutes remaining
Stick
What the hell is this?
Wow wow wow...
Oh man, that looks bad
No way, you're kidding me!
Again?
No way...
Are you serious?
Wait a minute, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Are you okay?
Where are you going?
To the toilet
Yamasaki heads to the toilet alone
Oh come on!!
Pie
God damn...
Wait a minute!
That is terrifying...
Hey guys!
I heard something...
Huh?
Hey guys!
What happened to you?
They were in the toilet!
What?
The black things?
Yeah!
Are you serious?
3 of them...
No way!
In the stalls...
No way
And did you get to have a piss?
I was having a piss
and then they came out suddenly...
I was so scared...
That is so scary
Are you serious?
Yes!
That is a scary thought...
That's not cool man, this is like...
Oh it's going to fall off...
Oh, watch out...
Your face is properly messed up...
Your face has changed so much from when you went and came back...
3 of them?
I just heard a "Wah!"
Yeah...
I heard this little sound
and then when you turned..?
That is so scary!
They were just there when you turned around?
3 black things?
That is so scary...
I thought I was in serious trouble for a moment...
This is hell, seriously this is hell
There is no such thing as a safe place anymore
There's just so many of them.
Yeah I get you...
Because we're running around loads you probably think we're fine and all...
Yeah, that's true
For 1 of them to come out,
Yeah
we would wait for 30 minutes, sometimes 1 hour...
The whole time, we were like this...
Yeah because we didn't know when...
And we're feeling nervous the whole time...
In the end, I wonder how much you guys ran...
Oh man, I don't know
You must have run loads.
Yeah, we did
Like tens of kilometres, right?
Oh for sure, definitely
Oh man, but seriously
That was something...
The balance between us started drifting...
What do you mean?!
Go on, tell him!
Surely, you know what I mean...
Like the idea even...
I'm sure he will say something again now...
The whole Senpai-Kouhai relationship too...
Oh yeah, that's true
But from here on, we start to get sleepy and it really gets...
That's right!
The strain on us...
That's right
And your muscles I bet start hurting about here...
Honestly, our muscles were already hurting here...
12:30 AM
7 hours 30 minutes remaining
As it goes past midnight, their fatigue starts to reach their limit
16 hours 30 minutes since the start
Their fatigue hits a peak. No one is even talking.
They don't even have the energy to talk to one another.
What is that?
What is it?
What has he brought?
Come, gather around these boobs
What is it?
What is this?
Oh, futons...
I brought it as quick as I could
Time to turn out the lights
Lights out?
So we can carry on with the tag game,
shall we get some good night's sleep?
For real?
We get to sleep?
We're allowed?
I guess it is time to sleep, to be honest...
Let's get some nice sleep...
But lastly,
shall we wish Matsumoto-san goodnight together?
Matsumoto-san,
Matsumoto-san...
good night.
What the hell, man?
Why do I get kicked twice..?
I know
As if it's routine...
Yeah...
There's one futon set each by the looks of it
Damn, that one looks filthy...
The bag is filthy, I mean I'm sure it doesn't matter...
God it's filthy
Well I guess we have no choice...
Yeah, let's do it as the order before
I agree
Where should we put the futons?
The bag of my colour is totally different...
Who cares who gets that bag?
The colour was so different...
Aww man, it's so dirty...
Just my one...
We are doing this because of the order, after all...
Why the hell...
Right then...
It is pretty late; we do need to get some sleep...
After all this...
Oh man, this is a good one.
Oh yeah, Hosei-san, your one is so nice.
Don't you think my one is elegant as well?
Yeah
You're right, your one is so elegant...
It is, right?
I like this one as well to be honest
Have a quick look at mine too!
Oh yeah, that's an awesome one, green and all
It is, right?
Someone change with me...
Wow...
I don't want this...
Hey, switch with me...
Damn, your one is one size smaller, Hamada-san...
It's so small
I know
You'll be okay.
This is fine.
Just switch with me...
Right, let's get some sleep
Right...
Like seriously...
Right then!
Good night!
Damn, that's small!
You not going to put a sheet over?
Oh, no it's okay, this is clean anyway.
Lights out
Damn, it is tough to sleep on something hard like this...
As soon as the lights went out, the 4 fell asleep...
We were shattered by this point...
Oh yeah, we were
We were
And in the dark, approaches
A suspicious shadow approaches them...
a suspicious shadow
Did you eat dinner?
Are you eating well?
Yes, we are...
What time is it even?
Oh man...
You working hard?
You eating?
Am I eating?
Did you eat dinner?
Dinner...no I didn't...
Dinner... no I didn't...
You got to, man...
It's so important...
You guys were totally out, huh?
Right then, I'm off...
Oh, okay.
Good night.
Good night...
Good night
That was so scary...
1:15 AM
6 hours 45 minutes remaining
With no sound, Obachan-Oni appears
It's a ghost!
Deep Kiss
This is ridiculous
It's a ghost...
And then he falls asleep again...
That's a shock...
She stuck her tongue in again...
We were really tired here, man...
Oh man, that was so scary
Thai Kick
What, what, what?
Oh man...
This really is out of control...
Man that was a shock
It was so scary...
Is that allowed? Even when we're sleeping?
It shouldn't be, right?
Regardless of what is done to him, Hamada cannot shake off the sleepiness
You don't even wake up anymore...
Open palm strike
We don't have the willpower to run by this point...
We just let it happen...
So true...
2 AM
6 hours remaining
We had no idea about this
Yeah
Yeah, we were out by this point
What the...
Volleyball Machine
Oh man, this is terrifying!
He got two like right in the face...
There were so many of them!
Yeah, there were...
That was so scary...
I'm telling you
They're breeding and everything...
Yeah...
By the looks of it...
It's not right, there's so many of them
There were like different versions, ones that lit up...
2:30 AM
Remaining 5 hours 30 minutes
Hamada notices a suspicious rope
Rope
What was I doing?
It's a chimpanzee...
Look at this, it's a chimpanzee...
The monkey, the monkey...
He found a banana
There's something hanging there...
What is it?
Slap
What the hell...
I mean...
they didn't have to come from above just to slap us...
What dicks...
There are new species coming out now and all...
There weren't any of those kinds of Oni during the day...
They can move really well
Night species ones...
Which travel through the air...
Nocturnal species...
Yeah...
The night species...
Ones that also light up...
So there are species that appear at night?
I wonder if they're two different species...
Yeah
Like types?
Hamada's face was brilliant, wasn't it?
Batsu Game Headquarters
He made such a funny face
He, like, makes a face like a baby gorilla from time to time..
Yeah, he does!
Right?
Like you know, the huge eyes...
Yeah
Right? What's that about?
He so does do that
Check out Hamada's expression; it's like a baby gorilla's!
2:45 AM
5 hours 15 minutes left
Slap
This is so bad...
I can't do this
What the hell, man...
What the hell...
You guys probably got smacked...
He punched me..
Really?
That's exaggerating it too much...
Ow...
Tanaka, what's wrong?
It hurt so much!
Oh damn...
Come, gather around these boobs.
Gero-Gero, Gero-Gero
Matsumoto-san said
He will allow you to sleep now
Matsumoto-san's kindness truly can deceive a child
Hold on, who are you accusing of that!?
What?
What the hell...
He's obviously just woken up...
But he's saying that he'll let you sleep.
So yeah...
Time to sleep...
I wonder if we'll be able to...
The 4 finally get some peace
3 AM
5 hours remaining
Sleep Time
They were allowed some sleep.
The short period of rest
However, morning will come very soon
And once again, the reality which seems a nightmare...
2 hours 30 minutes remaining
5:30 AM
Wake up
There's no way we could wake up to this...
Chinko Machine
No way at all
Wow wow wow...
Oh man, that's awful
You would not want this first thing in the morning...
It's already morning...
I got my dick slapped first thing in the morning...
For real?
They really do ridiculous things...
Ladle
This is so scary as well...
That's amazing...
You...
When will we get used to it?
Come, gather around these boobs!
God sakes...
Maple buns!
It's time to wake up
Morning
You're all wrecked here...
First of all, shall wesay good morning to Matsumoto-san?
First of all, shall we say good morning to Matsumoto-san?
Come on, guys.
Let's do it...
Matsumoto-san
Hamada
Yeah...
It's morning, so let's start by saying good morning...
If you don't do this, the rest of these guys won't do it
So here we go
Matsumoto-san
Matsumoto-san...
Guys
Hamada's saying it, so why aren't you?
He's so annoying!
Let's try again...
Matsumoto-san
Good morning
Good morning...
Chewing Bon...
Here's your breakfast
Matsumoto-san said
you got to work hard again today,
so he arranged you a meal to give you some strength back
Well then, eat.
So he has nothing to say about this, huh?
2 hours remain
6 AM
Breakfast Time
Hey, it's warm
Oh awesome
This looks pretty tasty
Gang
What the...
What? What is it?
This is ridiculous...
I thought they might take you away for us...
Just water?
Looks it
I'm so cold...
1 hour 18 minutes left
6:42 AM
Thai Kick
No way, no way am I getting caught!
No way in hell!
Oh damn, a Thai Kick...
From 7 in the morning...
This will be tough to take...
Wait, what?
Holy shit...
That's just...
3 in a row is tough...
Oh man, oh man, oh man...
Open palm strike
Damn...
1 hour 1 minute remaining
6:59 AM
Time left
Just over 1 hour
However, the 4 cannot converse
The 4 have lost the will to have a conversation
and there is no joy at the fact the end is so near
Volleyball Machine
Oh man...
This would be...
This is horrible...
This is like so bad..
Oh man, I'm scared...
This really hurts...
Oh damn...
27 minutes remaining
7:33 AM
Again?
Oh man...
Open palm strike
Hey, something's hanging out...
You're right
What is?
Oh, his dick...
This is ridiculous
This is just ridiculous
He gets caught and then that happens...
If this wasn't TV, I would have stabbed him..
7 minutes remaining
7:53 AM
We've finally gotten this far...
Yeah we did...
Finally...
But you can't let your guarddown until we've finished
But you can't let your guard down until we've finished
That's true
So true
Gaki no Tsukai Producer:
The World's Heipo
Let's just get him
This is awful
Get him
He's such a dick...
He really is just a...
There's no way you can win against us from the start...
He must have thought he could do it to us because everyone else was...
That's actually quite shocking; it annoys me
I know, right?
4 minutes remaining
7:56 AM
I have never waited for 8 o'clock like this in my life...
Seriously guys, let's get used to this sound now...
You were as well...
Come, gather around these boobs
Yeah, Hamada-san...
You're right...
Ready, set.
Come, gather around these boobs
Just as I thought
You guys have nearly done your 24 hours
Only 3 and a bit minutes left...
Come on...
Thank you...
How was it?
It was just ridiculous...
Endo?
No seriously, it was ridiculous
Was it?
How about you, Tanaka?
It was so tough
Hamada?
Yeah...
How was it?
I am just defeated
And all of that was truly thanks to Matsumoto-san, right?
That man really is an amazing person
The final 10 seconds, let's do a countdown
Man, this was ridiculous, it was tough.
Seriously...
It was an amazing Batsu...
"Venue"... Ha...
So stupid...
I know, right?..
Where is it?
It's just terrifying
It really is...
Oh man, this is scary, we don't know where they could appear from now...
Your rib broke, your rashes broke out and now you have a fever?
Hold on a minute!
You know what, I don't want it
Wait wait...
Let's countdown...
Right...
From 10...
From 10, here we go
Here we go...
Finish in 10 seconds
24 Hour Endurance Tag Game
m 0 0 l 1223 0 l 1223 307 l 0 307 l 0 0
Finish in 9 seconds
Finish in 8 seconds
Finish in 7 seconds
Finish in 6 seconds
Finish in 5 seconds
Finish in 4 seconds
Finish in 3 seconds
Finish in 2 seconds
Paper Fan
That's so creepy!
That's terrifying!
It really is...
What the hell...
Oba-chan...
Damn...
Hamada-san, they've gone
They have all gone
Wow what, were we all here together?
I was actually over there...
But then they chased me here...
Damn...
We finished though...
How many of them were there?..
Loads, like 200?
Are you serious?
It was just pitch black
24-hour endurance tag game
Complete
Great job, guys
Great job
Thank you...
So what are we going to do now?
I mean...
We'll battle as a team of 4
against Matsumoto-san
and defeat him...
Yeah...
Let's win, whatever happens
I guess that's how it is?
Yeah...
I think our teamwork really came out in there...
Yeah, we have a really strong bond now...
I mean honestly...
Yeah...
I, like, love you guys...
Well, that's how it is
I see.
Please pass on the message
Okay, I will
Okay then, thank you very much
I'm off
Great job!
Thank you!
Thank you
Great job, guys
Great job
Please don't...
The bond...
between us...
What happened to the bond?
I know, what happened to it?
I bet the person who pressed close was Hamada-san...
Well, we did it
We did...
You did indeed...
Oh man..
This must have been very hard...
Oh man...
It really was...
It really was tough
I mean watching it alone was tough... Well anyway, well done
on completing part one of five Batsu games...
What are you on about, of 5?
No no no...
What you mean of 5...
That's what I've heard
I haven't heard that, you fool!
No way
What the hell do you mean, part one of five?
So there's a Part 2, Part 3...
Are you stupid?!
No way...
That was more than enough
That really was
If we're going to do another battle in the future...
Yeah
We could split it like 2 vs 3 or...
Or like this...
No, let's do this
I think this is going to happen for sure...
Let's do it like this
Like this
I mean, that's fine and all but...
In April, Yamasaki-san will...
Really?!
Really?
He's leaving?
Yeah...
I'm leaving?!
No, I'm not leaving!
No way
No because then there's 4 of us so it's easy to match the teams...
Oh yeah, that's true
No no no, it's got to be 4 vs 1...
and if you want a helper, you can have Heipo-san...
See, and you're not funny in the slightest...
No no no!
That was just such an awful joke!
Would you 3 like to go against Downtown?
What, like 3 vs 2?
But I mean Hamada-san, don't you think you should be in our team?
After getting that much done to you?
Well it depends on what the battle will be...
I guess that's true
But on a separate note, let's definitely do Downtown vs Cocorico...
Oh yeah, sure...
Like against each other?
Yeah, please
We will do our best.
We will try and win...
We will...
Cheers for everything, Yamasaki...
Thanks a lot...
Thank you very much...
What are you saying?
We're just messing with you!
We're just kidding... Damn, he's tearing up!
Back then...
Well, that's how it is
Ahh, I see
So we've done the 24 hour endurance tag...
I see
And it's now been made into a DVD
So obviously for everyone it's a bit of thing of a past...
So it must be a bit hard to remember everything
That's true, it was 4, 5 years ago so...
Well, you know in the
very near future, you'll be taking partin a 48-hour endurance tag
very near future, you'll be taking part in a 48-hour endurance tag
Oh hell no!
No way in hell
I'm definitely not doing that
And that's why we need to refresh your memory...
We'll die..
No no no no
The people who watched it may have forgotten
But we remember everything
We really do
We do
Is it burned into your body?
Oh yes, definitely
Oh, really?
Yes
That is a Batsu Game I never want to do again
Out of everything I've done as part of my job, that was the toughest
Yeah seriously...
But seriously
Since all of you are saying it, it seems like it's true
Yeah, this really was
We are serious
Right? We genuinely did 24 hours in there...
Exactly
Yeah, you really did...
We really did and my God, it was tough
This was more mentally tough though, right?
Yeah, it was
Mentally and physically: it was a double whammy
24 hours straight on camera in itself feels like a punishment...
Yeah that's true
And you couldn't really sleep
I mean it says there "Sleep Time"
Ceiling Oni Slap (Yamasaki, Tanaka)
Sleep Time
But we um...
But we didn't get that much sleep...
Did you or not? God sakes...
We only got a bit of sleep
Right?
I see
What is he on about?
Who's the guy next to Yama-chan?
Huh?
Oh wow...
Excuse me...
Come, gather around these boobs
Former Downtown manager
Fujiwara Hiroshi
He wasn't on it that much...
Yeah...
You were hardly on it..
That's right. So what's up, why are you here?
So umm... The 24 hour batsu game
I worked hard during it too...
Your words just literally went...
I couldn't hear a word of what you were saying...
It didn't reach here...
It just rose up...
I couldn't hear at all...
Well anyway...
Right
When we talk about Batsu Games, we think of Fujiwara
That's true
Yup
And according to this board
This is how everything went apparently
I see, our schedule?
I don't remember it to this much detail...
I know
Wait a second...
How many years ago was this?
4 years ago
4 years
4 years...
Us 4 actually took part in it
Yeah
We've been asked to write who pissed you off the most
out of all the people there
Oh yeah
So, please write the answer, you too Yama-chan
Sure
But um...
There were so many...
Well obviously
All of them, really...
I watched it on air and all
And I did go to the shoot as well but I haven't seen all of it...
That's true
So umm... yeah
This is hard...
There are so many for me
For me too
Same
And Yamasaki was saying he hurt himself like really near the beginning...
Yeah, that's true
It was really soon after started
You cut your ear or something, right?
I had a huge cut on my ear
Oh shut up...
Seriously...
But in all seriousness, Yama-chan...
You've said it now so I'm going to bring this out
Yeah...
Yeah
Lies that Yama-chan made
Oh yeah
Wait, what do you mean lies?
Right?
Yes
There are this many?
Yeah, first off
20 minutes in: My rib bone is broken!!
20 minutes in, he said his rib bone was broken
He did
He did say that
It would have been great if your rib bone had not broken though, huh?
Right?
Wait...
It broke, so I can't help that
And the next one,
90 minutes in:  My ear is cut!!
90 minutes in, he said his ear was cut
I remember that
I do remember that as well
He did, right?
He did
Of course I was
That's amazing, his rib broke
and 90 minutes later, now his ear is cut
I told them all
from the paper fan
That's amazing
Yeah, that was awful
But by this point, your rib had already healed?
Yes it had.
It was broken though!
You said it was broken!
No but seriously
It doesn't heal that quickly...
No but my ear was in so much pain
14 hours 15 minutes in: My rashes have broken out!!
14 hours 15 minutes in...
Right
He said his rashes had broken out
I mean yeah
Was this more because of the mental side?
Yeah, I mean you guys even were a bit freaked out
There was some stuff on his skin...
Like there were so many rashes
I don't remember that
I don't remember
It wasn't that bad
Yeah
And when your rashes broke out,  how was your ear?
And when your rashes broke out, how was your ear?
Oh yeah, it was fine!
Amazing...
And lastly, 14 hours 30 minutes in, he said he a fever.
14 hours 30 minutes  I have a fever!!
He said he had a fever and therefore, wants to go home
He said he had a fever and therefore, wants to go ho home
24 hour tag
Yamasaki's 4 lies
20 minutes
Since the start:
Are you serious right now?
No, I'm serious
It's definitely a lie
Are you serious?
You've lied in the past about your rib being broken...
That's true
No no
But it's definitely
It's not broken but it's fractured
No way...
From before?
Just from before?
You fell over, right?
You got a fracture from that?
There's no way in hell...
No but I'm like that, seriously
No way it's broken
No no
It's not broken, it's fractured
Seriously
You're really pushing the fact it's a fracture, huh?
Yeah...
Thai Kick
The footage in question
This is the footage where Yamasaki claims to have broken his rib
Watch Yamasaki on the right
Being chased, he falls, and in this moment...
Being chased, he falls  and in this moment...
Being chased, he falls and in this moment...
His rib bone
supposedly broke here...
Yamasaki's rib bone
broke here apparently...
1 hour 30 minutes
Since the start
Damn, my ear hurts
It's cut...
Is it?
Yes, there's a big cut
There is, right?
Yes
What? Has it been there for a while?
Yes, it has
From just before?
Yes it i-.... Ow ow ow
Oh don't lie, man...
No...
Wow...
You won't forget about that injury, will you..?
No, seriously
Is it cut?
Yes
It is
Oh shit! That's a cut and a half!
Was that from before?
Yeah, it was
Wow, how though?
Damn, that would
From the paper fan
Hey man... That would hurt...
It would, right?
It's about this big...
No way!
It's a bit swollen too
Damn, that would hurt
Someone, please come
Paper fan
The footage in question
This is the footage Yamasaki claims where his ear got a cut.
Watch Yamasaki as he gets hit hard by the paper fan
The moment the fan hits Yamasaki right here...
Apparently his ear
got cut
Yamasaki apparently got a cut on his ear
Fair enough... It looks painful...
14 hours 15 minutes
From the start:
Footage in question
Pitching machine
First, please check this footage out
This is the batsu Tanaka received, pitching machine
Yamasaki, who saw this horrible punishment
Comes up with a
ridiculous lie
After this, comes up with a ridiculous lie
That must have hurt like hell...
Of course...
That hurts so bad...
Oh man, my rashes are breaking out
Really?..
You keep banging on about your rib bone being broken and now your rashes are breaking out
You keep benging on about your rib bone being broken and now your rashes are breaking out
Really?
There's nothing there...
No, nothing there
I'm itchy though...
14 hours 30 minutes
From the start:
Footage in question
Wonton noodles
This is the final one
Endo is getting Wonton noodles poured on him
Yamasaki sees the pain
on Endo's face and
Comes up with
shocking statement
After this, comes up with a shocking statement
What's wrong
What's wrong now?
I have a fever
You have a fever?
So you broke your rib bone, your rashes broke out, you cut your ear and now you have a fever
Your ear is cut but that's it, right?
Seriously...
But
Yeah..
What Yamasaki was saying was to me was
"Hamada was trying too hard"
Yes...
What?
No...
So like honestly...
I thought Hamada-san would snap at around the 8 hour mark
gather all the staff
and say something like "Let's stop here"
But that's not doing it properly!
You were thinking "Why is he actually doing it?"
So because we have good enough footage...
Yeah exactly...
So like what's the point of doing 24 hours
So just get enough footage
Exactly
That's what I was expecting to happen
But you actually did the whole 24 hours
Yeah, he's weird like that
Amazing
I was getting pissed off thinking "Come on, say it!"
But I guess that is true
Like "We are here because of you!"
You guys thought that too though, right?
Yeah I really did, too
No way!
I was thinking like "When are we going to finish?"
No no no.
I thought that too
In my heart I was thinking "Snap, snap, snap, snap, snap!"
"Please get angry!"
"Please just snap!"
I was hoping one of the staff would screw up and set you off
I see
That's how tough it was
Yeah, it really was like that tough
Yes, exactly
Yeah
Oh, really?
Yeah, he's weird, he doesn't snap in times like that
What?
I don't get it either.
He's really professional in those situations for some reason...
Like at the Kouhaku...
Well they did loads of stuff to us
So Tanaka
Yes
Who was the most annoying character?
For me, there were 2
who really annoyed me
Really?
So I wrote both of them down
Who?
The ladle
Ladle (underneath); volleyball
and the volleyball machine
The ladle...
Wasn't that ladle guy really annoying?
The feeling of getting hit by that?
Like the fact you have to run from that
The ladle really hurts as well!
And the guy was really fast
Exactly
Yeah
The ladle guy
It's not that flashy like other batsus but
these ones hurt more usually...
because it's just literally like that...
Exactly. This really hurt
It did
It really did
And they did it so many times
Yeah, they did
And the other one... The volleyball machine
Oh yeah
They were like aiming for my face
I was just glued to a wall
and it hurt so much
That would hurt
I couldn't even give a good reaction...
Well yeah...
It was just so painful
Seriously
Tanaka Naoki
The character who pissed him off most
Ladle
5 minutes from the start
8:05 AM
Damn, there's loads of them
Hamada-san!
Oh crap!
Oh man
This is so tough
Wait, no!
21 hours 35 minutes from the start
5:35 AM
Machine
Volleyball
18 hours since the start
2 AM
Amazing
That is amazing
What happened?
Seriously?
This one
Holy shit
This is really tough
Poor you...
And they were doing it from point blank
Yeah!!
2 of them hit him right in the face
Ow...
How about Endo?
Yes...
For me, the punishment like the ones Tanaka got
were bad as well but
but this was really tough
Heipo
I see
Oh yeah
He comes in from time to time
It says on the board "Heipo: Failure"
Hanging Ten-don (Tempura-don) (Hamada)
Heipo: Pie (Failure)
Ladle (Yamasaki)
Open palm strike (fail)
He was like a failure on all of them
Yeah
But this would really piss me off
When we're like properly down
and we're like "What are you doing to us man?"
Exactly, like "What do you want?"
Like, "no one gives a shit about you"
He's really greedy like that, right?
Character who pissed him off the most
Endo Shozo
Heipo
3 PM
7 hours from the start
What the hell is with this guy?
Oh, it's Heipo!
What the hell are you doing?
What is this?
Hold on a minute
NO!
We can win this!
No, no, no
Go back!
We can win!
No, please
Oh no!
What the hell are you doing!
Go home!
He's the worst
What a failure
He dropped it all as he came out
4 PM
8 hours since the start
This guy!
He's so annoying
Amazing
Go back!
You can't fall like him
That fall was...
just amazing
What is he doing?
God...
He's the worst
He can't walk
God he's so annoying
Go back!
23 hours 53 minutes since the start      (PLEASE RE-TYPESET)
7:53 AM
Like, he just doesn't learn
He really doesn't
This is the ladle
Oh right, he wanted to hit you
But he's just not got it
I mean this even...
At a point when we were all pissed off...
Of course you'll get done
This takes stamina though, doesn't it?
11 hours from the start
7 PM
Oh, it's just Heipo
This time!
He said, "This time!"
Amazing
Why is he telling us!?
Oh man
He's in a state of shock
This is ridiculous
He smacked his head
I thought he might have hurt himself
I do get you
Yeah
That would piss anyone off
It does, right?
And he has a total different effect to everyone else, right?
Yeah
In the haunted hotel I did...
He was saying "I'm scared, I'm scared"
And I'm thinking "You've got nothing to do with this"...
I'd be over here doing something and I could here far off him saying "I'm scared"...
It just really pisses you off
It really does
Yeah
How about you, Yama-chan?
For me, it was the open palm strike
Open palm strike (underneath): The soldiers of the night
Oh yeah
The open palm strike...
The fat guy, right?
Yeah
No, I mean him as well but for me, Okamoto's slap
He came out during the 24 hours
Oh yeah
I forgot about that
His slap was really
I mean
Yama...
It was so bad, wasn't it?
Yeah it was
Yamasaki and Okamoto since the old days...
Right?
Like you got into shit at the airport with him and all...
Yeah
He smacks you  off camera even
He smacks you off camera even
I know, he smacked me so hard off camera...
Wow
I was like "What the hell are you doing, man!?"
That was tough
And the other one?
The soldiers during the night, I wonder if you remember...
When we were sleeping
That rope came down
From above, right?
Yeah, I do
That was just so scary
Yeah, that was scary
If there was a kid there, he would cry
Right?
Character who pissed him off most
Yamasaki Hosei
Okamoto slap
13 hours 45 minutes from the start
9:45 PM
YAMASAKI!
What the hell, what the hell!
He said Yamasaki; stop, man!
Just please hurry up and get caught!
He's got him!
Oh no!
His precious cat just...
It ran away straight away...
Hello
Great job, guys
Oh, thank you very much
The soldiers of the night
18 hours 30 minutes from the start
2:30 AM
Oh yeah, I found the rope here...
Rope
It was hard to see it because it's so dark...
You really look a weak animal
Like a really weak animal
You do...
Like a chimpanzee
Something's hanging down
I had no idea
We couldn't run away
What the hell...
What the hell!
What the hell, man!
He punched me in the face!
For real?
This isn't really a character but
Chinko machine
The Chinko machine
It was because it was when I was sleeping
Oh yeah!
I remember that
I totally remember that
Breakfast
Chinko Machine (Hamada)
Ladle (Hamada, Yamasaki, Endo, Tanaka)
Radio gymnastics
That really hit me hard
I bet
Like, my body was shattered. We had done all that before it.
And that old hag came and properly kissed me and all...
Oh yeah.
I was shattered and then woken up and then suddenly BAM
Yeah that's true
I was like "what the hell" and then I made eye contact with Tanaka
Yes
And his face really pissed me off too
I want to help you but there's nothing I can do at that stage...
My body wouldn't move either...
You were looking at me like "What the fuck are you doing?!"
And the other thing I would write on here would be Tanaka's reaction
Tanaka's reaction?
When it went DON, without fail, he would scream
I was thinking, "Get used to it, man!"
Well I mean, it's impossible to get used to it, right?
Wow
Every single time, you would...
Chinko Machine (underneath says Tanaka)
You would be like "Aaaaaaagh"
I thought if I didn't shout, my brain would just go weird
In that place
Character which pissed him off most
Hamada Masatoshi
Chinko
Machine
21 hours 30 minutes from the start
5:30 AM
My body was just so tired at this point
Oh, make him stop...
Tanaka's face is funny here.
That is funny
That is so funny
Tanaka's
reaction
30 minutes from the start
8:30 AM
Wait, what the hell
Please don't do that!
I just wanted to see if I could move quickly
Please don't shock us like that!
Yeah, please tell us if you're going to do that
Oh, sorry!
Come on, man!
Let's not do that kind of thing to each other
12:55 PM
4 hours 55 minutes from the start
Seriously, man
It was you, you moved
No
Hamada-san, you moved before us
I just got dragged alone to that
It was you!
Your reaction made me react
And the face he makes...
4:50 PM
8 hours 50 minutes from the start
It's not them...
You overreacted so much
Come on, Tanaka
It's the sound you make which freaks us out
You shouting "AGHH!"
Don't shout "AGHH!"
The noise you made freaked me out just now
22 hours from start
6AM (NOTE: GAKI PRODUCERS MADE A MISTAKE HERE AS THIS SEGMENT WAS ACTUALLY FROM THE FIRST BREAKFAST, 30 MINUTES FROM THE START)
1000 questions...
Why?
Sorry
Oh come on, please don't do that
What happened?
This guy
You overreact far too much!
You really do
No, it's not that
Please stop that
Moving like that once is so tiring in itself
You know
amazing
This shows how many times
people got punished in the 24 hours.
As you can see, we had a lot of things done to us
So who got the least?
Tanaka Naoki: 14 times
4th was Tanaka
Oh was I?
But still, 14 times is quite a lot
Yeah it is
In 24 hours, that's how many times
3rd was
Endo Shozo: 15 times
Endo
Me?
There's not much difference though, huh?
Yeah
Between you
And in second place
Yamasaki Hosei: 18 times
Yama-chan
18 times
There's not that much difference still
No, there's not
Yeah
And first was me...
Hamada Masatoshi: 19 times
19 times
You're top, huh?
But when you watch others get hurt, do you not think they have it worse? Like I didn't think I was top.
That's true
Endo Shozo: 15 times
Hamada Masatoshi: 19 times
Tanaka Naoki: 14 times
Yamasaki Hosei: 18 times
But I was first, but anyway, this is how many times.
So what's the total?
Altogether...
60, 70?
around 70 I think
That's amazing
I mean this was something else
It was
If you were there...
It really was hell
It really was amazing
Yeah
Yama-chan got done when he just went to toilet!
Oh yeah!
Toilets should be a safe place, I mean remember the toilet in the haunted hotel?
You shouldn't do stuff in the toilet. Like you know
it's physiological, you have to go.
It's like the most private time too...
11:50 PM
15 hours 50 minutes from the start
Hey guys!
What was that?
What happened?
They were in the toilet!
Those black things?
Yeah
1 night in a haunted hotel
Matsumoto Hitoshi Batsu Game
This is not on! This is not on!
This is just not on!
What's wrong?
No, no way, man!
Please, at least let me piss!
Did we really need Fujiwara here?
He didn't say anything really...
Fujiwara
I'm sure he's come here for a purpose
Oh, really?
I see
Sorry
I worked hard there myself
at the 24-hour tag game
you know so um...
so I made a highlight reel of myself
and I would like you to watch it
if you would, please
He really has tempo, doesn't he?
No!
No, he doesn't!
That?!
It was annoying me so much
Sorry...
Just talk normally!
Sorry
I thought he spoke at a great tempo
Fujiwara Hiroshi
Highlight reel
Come, gather around these boobs
This guy's an idiot
Come over here
Morning
Come, gather around these boobs
This is right at the start
When he's explaining everything
Why the hell for the likes of you
do I have to wake up this early?
I have been given your orders from Matsumoto-san
Why were you dressed like this?
So true...
So think of what I say as what Matsumoto-san is saying
and make sure to listen to me
Especially you, Hamada!
You try to show how much of a bad guy you are
but today, listen to what Matsumoto-san
has to say, okay?
God, that's annoying
Come, gather around these boobs
What do you want?
Even for the likes of you
Matsumoto-san arranged to feed you
Wow, that's amazing
It is
His kindness truly
Oh, it's bread?
can be felt by your organs
I would have preferred rice
Yeah
His kindness truly can be felt by your organs
Okay, well then let's take it
He wouldn't let us take it
Matsumoto-san's kindness can truly by felt by your organs
Matsumoto-san's kindness can truly be felt  by your organs
Matsumoto-san's kindness can truly be felt by your organs
How many times are you going to say that?
You look bored so I brought out some newspapers...
You can look at it whilst making a stupid face or something
Yamasaki
You're an idiot, aren't you?
What the hell?
I don't need you to reply
God that pisses me off
Cocorico
Just because you have a show on Tere-Asa
Acting bossy and all...
What the hell?
No, we haven't...
Don't you have anything to say to Hamada-san?
Guys, it's 3 o'clock
Hamada, what do you think of at 3 o'clock?
Snacks.
Stop being so pathetic
Here's your 3 o'clock snack
What the hell?
And on top of that
I prepared you a game
Whilst living out your pathetic lives, you should play
The Game of Life
Aren't you going to say that was a good one?
You're so annoying
Matsumoto-san said
You look tired
so he said have something sweet and handed me these
Matsumoto-san's kindness truly knows no bounds
You're holding them out of their packets...
Eat up
No no no
Eat it
I said I don't want to
Eat it I said
Why did he bring them on his hand?
You must be so tired
Hamada
Here
You must be tired
Oh no no no
You got to eat it
There's loads of shit on it...
Oh well
No no no
There's stuff on it...
This is such a mess...
Don't use tissue
Tissue will stick
That's disgusting
You must be tired
That's enough, man
Don't take it out
Matsumoto-san's kindness really knows no bounds
Matsumoto-san said
he would let you sleep now
Matsumoto-san's kindness can deceive a child
Who's accusing him of deceiving children!?
He could barely say it
Look, he's kicking us
Come, gather around these boobs
Oh, enough!
We don't need this
His boob wasn't even out there
That's true, he just said it!
Come, gather around these boobs!
Alright...
meat-meat-meat-meat-meat
My meat
Even close by, gather around
Even beside me, gather around
Gero-Gero, Gero-Gero
Chewing Pon
Flashily gather around
I don't really get it
but that was funny
Thank you!
That last part, when it showed him...
He was sniggering so much over here
At your own footage?
Sorry.
But why?
But seriously
We wouldn't be able to do that again
No
I think it's our age
No... That would be tough
A question of age
It'd be too hard
Yeah
Back then, Cocorico and maybe Yamasaki
were still in their 20's, right?
Yes
We were
No, I was 32
and Cocorico were
I see, so Cocorico were still
Yeah, it might be a bit tough now, huh?
It was tough
It was
I mean the leader is already 40 years old...
Leader...
That's true, that would be hard
Yeah
That would be
It would
It'd be difficult
So true
It would be
This is the first one?
What?
It's going to continue
The DVD series
Oh right, the DVD series
Yes
So today, we are just doing the Tag game.
That's right
Well I'm sure there will be more
After this, there is also the Haunted Hotel
Oh I see
and the Do Not Laugh series
That's right
And I'm sure there will be a lot of things
But let's shut up about the money thing
You know?
What?
You know, in regards to the DVD
Let's stop talking so much about the money part
I mean, I will
You really are dirty when it  comes to money
You really are dirty when it comes to money
Seriously
Again, it's come out again
No, it's not like that
Amazing
It came out again! The stingy side!
No, it's not like that!
Well anyway, next up is the Haunted Hotel