Subbed by: Mei.ka~
On tonight's Gaki no Tsukai, a battle will determine
who can stay calm no matter what happens.
The First Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende! Chiki Chiki
The No-Reaction King Tournament~!!
He was pretty loud that time.
Very loud!
He got it together today.
Right?
I bet you could work part-time at a bar!
That'd be nice!
You'd nail that "Welcome!" every time!
So, Matsumoto-san, why are we here?
Yeah yeah yeah!
Today's about reactions.
Right!
Usually, we'd wanna react to things.
Right.
We're told to go above and beyond.
That's right.
People who can do that should be able to not react!!
That's what we're here to see.
No reaction? Huh.
There's no way Tanaka can do this.
No way.
No, but recently,
Backstage, he hasn't even reacted.
That's not true at all!
He's thinking, "I'm a shoe-in for today's challenge!"
I see.
That means that you can't let anything startle you.
The no-reaction king will be determined based on if they
are able to keep calm when faced with various traps.
No matter what happens, we can't react to it.
We want everyone to see how composed we can keep ourselves.
Not even a flinch.
And this time, it won't just be the 5 of us.
We also have some guests today! Here they are!
Who will they be?
Matoba Koji
Owada Shinya
For our celebrity guest players,
we've invited over these three calm and collected men.
I mean, I'm thrilled that I could come on this show,
Right.
But when this "no-reaction" offer came in,
Yeah.
I thought it was to find the person
with the most boring reactions...
Ah, I see.
And then it made me really sad.
So when I came and saw, like, Matoba-san,
I was like, "Oh, so that's what this is."
I see.
But I'm good!
Got it!
Just leave it to me!
You know, in high school,
Matoba was in prison, who knows how many times-
I was never in prison!!
Never!!
Never! Ever!!
I'm just curious,
Yeah?
But did they handcuff you like this or like this?
Well, could I just say this, Matsumoto-san?
I've never been in prison!!
Yup, never been in prison!
Never been in prison!
Well, I think these two were perfect choices,
But for Owada-san,
He can't keep quiet whenever he sees
youngsters with no common sense.
That's right.
Have you given them 3 warnings?
They warned me.
They warned him 3 times!
There's a bit more to it,
But they fought back and uncle-hunted me 3 times.
There're actually people in this world that get hunted 3 times!?
Endo
Hamada
Housei
Matoba
Matsu-
moto
Owada
Tanaka
This is the No-Reaction King Tournament!
The brackets are as shown.
3 traps will be activated for each battle.
The winner will be the one who reacts the least.
Let's get started!
Match one in round one:
Tanaka Naoki vs. Tsukitei Housei
Matsumoto-san, who do you think will win this match?
They'll be checking on the match from a monitor in another room.
Yes?
Well, they're both gonna jump.
So who knows?
Like this is probably gonna be the weakest match, yet.
The weakest!
Well, without further ado,
Let's start the first match!
Battlefield
Enter Challengers
What?
He's balding!!
It's the result of all his failures.
Yeah!
Look at that balloon!
That's just...
Very interesting.
Neither of them know when and what traps will activate.
They don't know what's gonna come to them.
Ah, right!
They don't even know if they're fake traps.
I'm interested to see how this plays out.
So much stuff in there!
Damn, this is amazing.
What's with his face?
The way Tanaka's positioning himself...
Get Into Position
This is where it starts!
They'll be judged on whether or not they can keep their current facial expressions.
Yes, just like that.
Now-
Keep that face.
They just have to stay like that.
Right, they have to keep that face.
The first trap is the giant firecracker.
And they can't hear us anymore.
This would make me jump!
When will it come?
No, this is just...
Neither of them know what's gonna happen.
Their faces are solid.
Really solid.
Very tense.
Are they gonna be okay?
This is taking a while!
This is so long!
The suspense is killing me.
Seconds until the giant firecracker is activated
seconds
second
That was perfect!
Tanaka got a clear reaction from it!!
He jumped up!
But he jumped, too.
Even now, he's scared.
Well, it got both of them!
True!
It got both of them!
Wait
Now they wait.
Ah, now they have to wait.
Maaan, it feels so tense.
I just wanna say that when we watched it,
Owada-san jumped up, too.
It made you jump, are you gonna be okay?
Get Into Position
They can't keep on trying to see what face they're gonna make.
Yeah.
Right.
What's with that face?
He has to keep it.
And since he has to keep it...
Right, that's why I think Yamasaki's face is better.
Me, too.
Well, everyone, the next trap up is flash cotton.
There's cotton candy beside each of them.
Yeah.
After it's lit, a fire will flare up.
I'd hate this.
I wonder how it'll go.
That's one solid face.
That's a really solid face!
Believe it or not,
He might be the dark horse.
There's always a possibility.
But he already reacted to something.
True.
That's also true, but...
They win if they keep their face, right?
Seconds until the flash cotton is activated
Of course!
But they couldn't even keep it up before.
seconds
second
Whoa
They both...!
Holy, that was so bad.
They...!
Wait
Now they wait again.
But Tanaka really had a voice on him!!
He was like,"Whoa!"
1 more trap left
Hold on, this must be so tough!
But I don't think they should get to say anything.
So that already takes away a point.
Like yelping like a dog.
Yelping would already mean that they'd lose.
I see.
Get Into Position
The last one.
It looks like Yama-chan might already lose that face.
Wait, but,
Just a while ago, he wasn't even trying to make a face.
Well, the next trap is the garbage bin jet.
Ah, in the back.
Those bins in the back.
Owada-san would hate those ones in the back.
The ones slanted in the back.
I'd hate not knowing what was gonna happen.
The best part about this is watching it happen.
Definitely!
Yeah!
I mean, the flash cotton was...
They look so cool!
All these camera angles!
Is he wearing that much theater makeup?
Has there been anyone else in variety
whose worn theater makeup?
Seconds until the garbage bin jet is activated
Why does that matter?!
seconds
second
Whoa~
C'mon, that shouldn't be happening!
Look, he's crying!
This is just-!
I have confidence that I won't make the same mistake!!
End of No-Reaction
Please make your way to the monitoring room.
He's crying!
Man, both of them jumped up.
They did.
We got reactions out of both of them.
Yeah, they both moved.
Man, this is hilarious.
Hamada-san,
Your sadist blood must be running wild
It must be!
Right!
Good job out there!
So how'd we do?!
Who do you think won this match?
You probably were too focused on your own selves.
Those were some solid faces.
Oh, thank you!
Well...
You were able to make some tense faces out there.
Alright!
Let's look at their facial expressions in slow motion.
Alright.
This one...
Wait, but...
This one was where they were able to recover fast.
Right. I mean, they did move a little bit, but...
They came back fast.
Tanaka came back fast.
Right.
Oh, now this one...
This one...
You could hear his voice.
Those are reactions, if I've ever seen one.
Tanaka lost this one.
Tanaka definitely lost this one.
It kinda caught me off guard.
Yamasaki's good at getting right back into it.
That was just plain bad.
Man, these gay men are so embarrassing.
"Gay men" ... we weren't being "gay"!
"Aaah~!"
This is the best thing ever!
3 producers will judge based on these
3 reactions to crown the winner.
Let's get to it, then!
Was the winner Yama-chan? Or was it Tanaka?
Please present the verdict!
Yes! Let's go!
Yamasaki Housei!
Oooh!
Awesome!
I will applaud you if you don't react to any of these. Seriously!
Really now?
I wanna watch from over here now.
Your body stiffens up just like that!
Yeah!
You should end it like that but then you just turned into this.
You said it!!
No no no!
You said it!! I heard!
Now that's just-
Like this?
Like this, right?
This is the way to do it.
And then this turns into this?
It does!
Coming up next!
A thrilling match of reactions between Hamada and Zeebra!
Match two in round one:
Hamada Masatoshi vs. Zeebra
Who will this match turn out?
Enter Challengers
Almost there!
They already have their faces on.
Are they gonna be okay with having their faces set right now?
Are they gonna go with those faces?
It's fine for now.
Hm, but I think Hamada-san's a strong contender.
'Cause I've seen Hamada-san spark a
bloodbath many times before.
Is he though?
I think he's a tough one.
Get Into Position
It starts now!
I've never really seen Zeebra flinch before.
It looks like they're going with those faces.
They'll be judged on whether or not they can keep their current facial expressions.
But those are some good faces!
Very solid.
Very solid faces!
Oh, that's a good one!
Oh, nice!
Zeebra's face is solid.
It is.
He's got it in the bag if he can keep it up.
This suspense, though.
So long!
Their minds are going insane.
Probably.
Like the big red one!
Yeah yeah.
They're probably worried about that one.
Definitely.
The first trap to activate will be...
A blow.
I couldn't handle that!
A blow?
A blow to the back of their chairs.
No way, no way will they last!
They're gonna react to this one.
I can't wait to see this!
Their chairs, the back of their chairs will be hit.
They're gonna scream like girls.
This can't be good.
I don't wanna hear that!
I'm begging you!
They need to get ready.
Let's hope they do.
Oh, nice face!
Very solid.
He's keeping it together.
It's Taiga!!
TN: Taiga is a historical fiction drama series that
runs each year throughout the whole year.
This is like the 3rd Taiga.
Oh, nice, Zeebra's solid, too.
Seconds until the blow to the seat is activated
It'd be cool if he could keep it up.
seconds
second
Whoa
Alright, we got a voice out of him!
Yup, we heard that!
We heard his voice!
What a pathetic little voice!
Zeebra's amazing!
Zeebra-san's doing great!
Wasn't he, though?
No movement at all.
Zeebra-san's amazing.
Look at that face just now!
He's great!
It's all over, Hamada-san.
Wait
Waiting for the next one to come is killing me...
Aah, I'm exhausted...
He's already done!
Hamada-san can't take anymore!
Get Into Position
Their backs got hit.
That must be scary.
Can they keep it up?
It's started!
Next up is a shooting from a radio-controlled tank.
Can they keep on not reaction!?
There it is!
They're still fine.
There's just one tank.
Just one.
I see...
What's gonna happen?
And then it turns.
Right, right.
That's cool.
The way it moves is scary.
Very nerve wracking.
He moved before it even shot.
He's already so nervous!
Oh
WOW
Even Zeebra-san!
Zeebra is working up a sweat!
So much sweat!
There's so much sweat on zeebra's face!!
So much!
They're probably nervous!
I see.
They must be nervous not knowing what's gonna happen.
Wait
He did say something.
I know, right?!
He did!
He went W-O-W, like "WOW!".
Zeebra's scared on the inside.
Right.
That's why he has all this sweat pouring out of him.
No no no.
Get Into Position
Alright.
This 3rd one is the last one.
They must be pretty exhausted by now.
Aaah, Zeebra-san's face...
Did he re-strategize?
Although he is still sweating.
Looks like he has a new plan.
Right.
I'm worried about that.
And the last trap will be...
Yeah?
The giant balloon.
There it is!
After all this time...
Hm, but Hamada-san looks like a red ogre.
His Otoko Ume face is kickin'in.
TN: Otoko Ume (Male Plum) is the mascot
character for the hard candy of the same name.
Yeeeah.
True.
Right? It's Otoko Ume.
He really looks like it.
He only looks like Otoko Ume!
He's like the spitting image of Otoko Ume!
He could make it as a mascot!
In a commercial!
Seconds until the giant balloon is activated
seconds
second
Ah, this is...
This was a good match.
No, it was.
It was a good match, but...
This was kinda...
End of No-Reaction
Let's play back the match in slow motion.
The first one.
That's right.
The blow!
This was...
He didn't get hit, but he acted like it.
This was just...
Like he got attacked.
Zeebra's amazing!
He's too good!
You're amazing!
Seriously!
I actually got the hang of it!
And now the tank.
This was so...!
He just got attacked!
He got attacked again!
What a beating!
He really got a beating!
Beating?!
Man, this was...
He's so beaten up!
Why'd you uncross your arms?!
Nah, let's not-!
Don't they tell you to "cross your arms"?
You'd understand if you were there, right!?
Probably.
Really?
I mean, you should cross them, but...
As you can imagine,
Blue, blue, blue.
Zeebra-san!
Zeebra advances to the semifinals.
Match three in round one:
Endo Shozo vs. Matoba Koij
Get Into Position
This art feels so long.
Whoa, look at that stud
A stud, huh?
These are the faces that they have to keep up for now.
Right,
The both of them have such solid faces.
They have to keep those faces.
Well, everyone, the first trap is the rocket punch.
Rocket punch?
Yeah, they're on both sides.
So they did have stuff like this.
It'll fly right past their faces.
That's just...
I'd hate this.
This is...
Especially the punch.
When is it gonna come already?
That face...
Looking' good.
For some reason, if I looked at this face,
I'd end up apologizing to him.
Pretty solid.
You know,
He could use that face in plays, so why doesn't he?
'Cause he sucks at acting.
Seconds until the rocket punch is activated
seconds
second
What?!
They're at a whole other level!
Whoa!
Are you serious?!
This is...!
Holy!
For real?!
This is good stuff!
They didn't react at all!
That's amazing!
Neither of them have shown any kind of reaction.
And even with the flash cotton...
Are you kidding me?!
What is this?!
Man, that's so weird!
Now the third trap will be the dropping of cans.
Now this is where I think they're gonna say something.
Me, too.
Something's up with their nerves.
Something's not right.
Seconds until the cans drop is activated
Seriously, I don't think they'd know what to do in a crisis.
seconds
second
Damn, that's amazing.
Wow, that's crazy.
Endo's and Matoba's match was on a whole other level.
So who won this match?
Blue, blue, red!
The winner is Matoba!
Thank you!
By a narrow margin, Matoba advances to the semifinals.
Last match in round one:
Matsumoto Hitoshi vs. Owada Shinya
Don't uncross your arms!!
I'd never!
I'd never do that!!
Never!
Those two didn't move an inch!
Yeah, no reaction.
Just what kind of battle will unfold between these two!?
Enter Challengers
So this is how they're entering.
Oh boy.
Yeah, not looking good so far.
Owada-senpai's face looks like bad news. Seriously.
They must be scanning the place.
Probably.
Oh, there's one new item in the middle there.
Get Into Position
Well, that was fast.
It's a drone!
A drone?
That drone looks scary.
Oh, nice.
Very solid face.
Very sophisticated!
What kinda face is that!!
Why that face?!
He's narrowing his eyes...
So, the first trap will be...
The giant balloon.
They're doing that one?
That one, eh?
This one is different than the one before.
when this one explodes, cockroaches will come out.
I wouldn't be able o handle that!
No way!
What the-
What the hell is with that face!!
It should be more intense!
Right?!
Now that's an intense face!
Seconds until the giant balloon is activated
Totally.
seconds
Very sharp.
second
He didn't uncross his arms, but...
He did jump up once.
Yup.
Matsumoto-san.
Look at Owada-san! He's holding it back!
For sure.
Next up is the drone.
Can they keep on not reacting!?
Matsumoto-san moved to that one, too.
Drone Operator
Celebrity Tani+1
That was definitely a jump.
This is torture.
He's at two jumps.
Crash
Damn, man!
Even though it hit him, he didn't react!
Even though it hit him!
Man, that's amazing!
That's awesome!
No way, no way!
Whoa, he's so good!
This is amazing!
So good!
No reaction there.
Right!
The wind!
So windy!
Ah, this is amazing!
Ah, now it's Matsumoto's turn.
It's comin'!
Look at him smiling!
That hit him square in the face!
That drone is just hitting him!
seconds
Seconds until the secret joke
second
Matsumoto-san -!
Explosion from the wall
I see!
Of course they'd do that!
At the last stretch!
And he's been trying so hard!
He wasn't prepared for that!
The last one!
He totally uncrossed his arms there.
Yup.
Wait
He let his guard down on the last one!
So long...!
That was so long!
That was so drawn out!
Get Into Position
Damn, that is hilarious.
What a face he's got on him!
Very solid.
Up until now, Owada has been the best bet to win.
What will this last trap be?
But Hamada-san, I'm having so much fun right now!
What are you talking about?!
Seconds until the secret joke
seconds
second
Ijiri Okada Emerges from the Locker
TN: Ijiri Okada is a comedian and impressionist.
Good job.
End of No-Reaction
Please make your way to the monitoring room.
That one got them!
They moved!
Right!
Good work out there!
I told you to keep your arms crossed.
But ours was so long!
Nah.
That's not true at all!
But that drone lasted for ages!!
Look at him!
Look. Did you see him flinch?
That was just...
Now this.
Sure got spooked there!
But now it starts!
Man, this was...
This was amazing!
This one was - !
That wasn't even fair!
That was great!
They broke their promise!!
That shouldn't have been allowed but that was amazing!
The winds looks so nice!
It hit you.
It sure did!
I thought we agreed that you wouldn't hit us!
It shouldn't be allowed!
I heard'em say, "it didn't hit you."
This last part.
Look at Owada-san.
Look, he uncrossed his arms!
What? Owada-san?!
That was a surprise!
Nah.
The verdict!
Of course, the verdict is...
Blue, blue, blue.
Owada-san is the winner!
It was only natural.
But for this kinda thing, actors are strong contenders.
'Cause you just focus, right?
I did, but -
He became one with the drone.
The drone went more to Owada-san than it did to me.
Right, right.
Was it trying to cut his hair?
Get into position.
Next week...
The first no-reaction king will be crowned!
Trap after trap,
Can they keep up on not reacting?
And the weakest king will also be crowned!!
He's so scary,
He's turning into a girl.
Don't miss it!
There should be a theory that if you're hit with CO2 gas,
you turn into Kitaouji Kinya.