Translation by typesoshee
Proofreading by Oolong
Typesetters: Hinnerk (Team Gaki)
DuckToaster
dtr-subs.tumblr.com
December 10, 2000
Backstage before recording the show
Gaki no Tsukai, before shooting
Yamasaki and Cocorico wait for Downtown.
But only one man arrived.
Hel-
Huh?
Hello.
It's Hamada, right?
Who is it?
No, come on, that's hard to smoke, right?
That's hard to smoke, right?
I can see saliva stuck on there.
Since I'm wearing this, you get it, right?
Well, yes, we've already done this - how many times?
I don't even want to say it.
The boss has said he wants to do this.
With another version.
What does he want to do?
Then will you take a look at this?
Yes.
Can you put this in?
What does he want to-
This, this is it.
What?
Hold on.
Look at that.
This is...
What?
Look at that.
Crazy.
Whoa, whoa.
There is no way this is doable.
We can't do this.
Look at that.
That, that jump.
Wow.
Look at that.
He's spinning.
This is, what's that...
at the champion level, you know?
Yes.
This is amazing.
Backside grab
sh... shifty frontside.
Five-four-oh air.
I have no idea what's going on.
Yes.
I don't know what that means at all.
That's the name of that technique.
That, right there, did one-and-a-half turns.
What we saw there?
So – yeah –
He does one-and-a-half turns up there and comes back down.
But the boss says
"That's nothing."
He wants to do two-and-a-half turns.
The technique is called
Backside grab
shifty frontside 900 air.
I have no idea what you're saying.
Again, Matsumoto makes an unreasonable demand
saying he wants to do two-and-a-half turns on a skateboard.
Hamada became a kuroko again
But Hamada became a kuroko* again.
*Kuroko is a traditional Japanese theatre stagehand.  Kurokos wear all black to imply to the theatre audience that they are supposed to be invisible and not part of the onstage action.
To make Matsumoto's dream come true
To make Matsumoto's dream come true.
(Two-and-a-half Turns on a Skateboard in the Air)
Matsumoto Hitoshi
The Backside Grab Shifty Frontside 900 Air Challenge
Matsumoto Hitoshi,
the challenge: two-and-a-half turns on a skateboard in the air.
On Sunday
you have a job in Sapporo as a side act.
Is that true?
Why do you know that?
Yes, why?
He's here.
Hey!
That is some outfit.
Can you scrubs really do this?
He's really pissed.
Yeah, we're fine.
Do you all know what we're trying to do?
Yeah, we do.
Say it, what are we trying to do?
Back-
(The cue card) He's reading it.
He tried to read it.
He tried to read katakana.*
*Katakana are Japanese letters used for foreign loanwords.  It is common for Japanese people to find it awkward to read many foreign loanwords in katakana stringed together as this rarely occurs in Japanese text outside of specialized terminologies.
Say it.
Right, so,
Backside grab
shifty frontside 900 air.
Yeah, that's it.
Say it.
He's reading it.
Backside grab-
Don't read it.
Hammer it into your brains.
It's in yours?
Of course, dumbass.
The person in question?
Yeah.
What is it called?
Ow!
Why?
What was that for?
Let's go.
Please, do this properly.
Because you're the one who's the most lazy about it.
That's true.
Yes.
Do it properly with effort.
I did give that some thought.
I was a bit too lazy about it.
I'm thinking I relied too much on you.
Today, if we don't do things right, I'll get injured.
That's true.
This much, I want to avoid.
Give it your best.
Give it your best as if you have a side part.
Yes, let's go.
Here we go.  I'm gonna get on.
This is annoying.
Get him on.
Shoes, shoes.
Get his legs...
Got him on.
Hold him up by the shoulders.
Straighten his legs.
At least straighten your legs by yourself, damn it.
Good.
That's right.
Watch out.
Watch out, watch out.
One more time.
One more time, one more time.
Ow, ow.
I got it.
It's the-
His legs-
Aren't fixed.
Because his legs aren't fixed.
they're not on the board.
Oh, that's why.
We have to fix his legs.
Good.
Let's change it to this one.
Let's do this one.
A skateboard with shoes fixed on is prepared
Bring him over here.
Here we go.
A rope is then attached and pulled from above
Here we go, here we go.
Ready and
Go
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
A little more.
A little more, a little more.
A little more, watch out.
A little more.
Argh.
Watch out.
He's hanging off of me.
Are we limited by how much we can push him
Matsumoto gets angry and leaves
because we're limited by how much we can pull him, right?
Because, you know
with a thin rope, you can't really get him up by that much.
Isn't that why this didn't work?
Wouldn't it be faster if we just get the people who know
how this all works to do it?
Definitely.
The group go backstage to apologize to Matsumoto
*"Ashita Ga Arusa" was a TV drama that all Gaki members appeared in, with Hamada and Cocorico in starring roles.  The "Sweater Ga Arusa" Coat was a real gift campaign sponsored by Georgia Coffee.  See a TV ad they did here: http://y2u.be/72E6G9eU7CQ
Matsumoto was applying to win a free "Sweater Ga Arusa" Coat
from Georgia Coffee.
Was there something
you were unsatisfied with that made you leave?
You say "something you were unsatisfied with" but
didn't I say at the beginning to make sure to not get hurt?
With the first hit it went "crack" right here.
What the hell are you all doing?
You're like a bunch of hoodlums, aren't you?*
*When Downtown were up and coming comedians, their style was criticized seriously as "[just acting like] hoodlums (chimpira)" by Yokoyama Yasushi, their senior and a hugely influential comedian.  More here: http://goo.gl/OYVmR8
But Matsumoto
we need you to at least straighten your legs
otherwise there's no way we can do that technique.
I wanted to straighten my legs.
I wanted to straighten my legs, too.
But I couldn't do it because of the way
it was said to me.
I don't know what he's talking about.
I couldn't do it because of the way it was said to me.
Did anyone say it in a way like that?
No.
No one said anything like that, right?
What's with this guy?
His nose is running.
You're right.
This guy's an idiot.
Just one more time.
Let's do it just one more time.
Matsumoto's 2nd Attempt!!
Matsumoto couldn't even get on the board.
Now, his 2nd attempt.
Here we go.
Let's go.
Go ahead.
Yes, please.
Ready and
Watch out, watch out.
BANG
Oh, this tilts to the side.
Oh, yes.
I'll bring that over.
Bring that other one over.
Oh, yeah.
This, this one.
Here we go.
This will be ok.
He's staring, he's staring, he's staring,
If you will, please.
Let's go.
Here we go.
Don't letcha hands go. Seriously, don't let go.
If you let go, this'll be bad.
Alright, let's go.
Yay.
Watch out, watch out.
Oh god, oh god.
Matsumoto gets angry and leaves again
That was close, right?
What happened?
He was really angry, huh.
The group go backstage to apologize to Matsumoto, again
*Ogawa Natsumi is Hamada's wife.  "Welcome Home! (Okaeri!)" is a real book by her about life in the Hamada family.  Japanese link here: http://goo.gl/jhbu94
Matsumoto is reading "Welcome Home! (Okaeri)"
by Ogawa Natsumi*.
Give his hat back.
Yes.
Matsumoto, your hat.
*The other two books on the desk are real autobiographical books written by Hamada.  The red one is "Forgery (Gansaku)" and the white and black one is "Read This! (Yome)."
What do you want to do?
"What do we want to do?"  I mean, go up like this, do two-and-a-half turns, and-
Not once did I say "Get a surfboard for this," right?
I was shocked.
What is this?  What's going to happen here?
In fact when I got flipped over
I hurt my ribs.
You know,
You all saw the tape, right?
They had that cool-sounding rock music playing
so there's this stylishness in doing it in that kind of atmosphere.
What's with you all?
With that Kansai dialect. Like, "Don't letcha hands go."
In the standard dialect, then.
Ok.
He's seriously saying don't speak in an Osaka dialect?*
*All five cast members virtually always speak with a Kansai dialect on the show.  The term "Osaka dialect" is sometimes used interchangeably with "Kansai dialect."
We can't speak in a Kansai dialect...?
Once Matsumoto comes, let's all speak in the standard dialect.
Yes, we'll do that.
Yes.
Matsumoto's 3rd Attempt!!
Emphasizing stylishness this time, his 3rd attempt.
Here it is.
Yes, good.
This will work.
This is a sports equipment called a "Rhönrad."
Definitely, this will work.
Should we move it on?
What is this?
Should we do the feet as well?
The feet.  The feet as well?
The feet are fine.  They're fixed on by that.
Ok.
Ok, it's good.
Ok, let's go.
So, we will go from this side.
Ok.
Let's go.
No, no, this is bad.
This is bad, this is bad.
This is bad, this is bad, this-
Wait, wait.
Matsumoto gets angry and leaves, yet again
Wow.
He is going wild.
The group goes backstage to apologize to Matsumoto, yet again
I had found a job to start after graduation.
Matsumoto is being interviewed by a magazine reporter
So,
Hamada took a boat racing test...
A foreigner?
They're doing an interview.
It's an interview.
I wasn't that interested in Yoshimoto* but Hamada really wanted me to join, so that's how it happened.
*Yoshimoto is Downtown's talent agency.
*She is speaking with a Kansai dialect.
I understand ya.*
She's got an Osaka dialect.
If you could tell us what caused what happened earlier, otherwise we don't know-
I'm doubting whether or not you really care about me.
What is that, that round thing?
A Rhönrad.
I was taped while I couldn't even grip it.
I was fixed while I couldn't even grip it, fixed with two fingers.
What do you all think about how scared I was there?
I understand ya.
That's not for the interview.
That was part of our conversation.
I actually feel like quitting.
But if I quit, I'd feel sorry for you guys more than for me.
You'd end up going home with a sense of failure, so for you all, I'll try one more time.
I understand ya.
That was part of our conversation.
Matsumoto's 4th Attempt!!
Will the two-and-a-half turns succeed? The 4th attempt.
Let's do it.
Yes.
Audio crew person
Ok.
Here we go, here we go.
Here we go.
He jumps here once, then he goes to the other side.
Jumps here.
Ok, he goes to the other side.
There he goes.
It's working.  It's working.
He gets to the other side and now he's coming back.
Ok, he's back.
Ok.
1 turn.
1 Turns
2 Turns
2 turns.
3 turns.
3 Turns
That should be enough.
Ok, go back.  He's going back.
Yes!
There we go!
We did it!
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Backside Grab
Shifty Frontside 900 Air
Success!!
Translation by typesoshee
Proofreading by Oolong
Typesetters: Hinnerk (Team Gaki)
DuckToaster
dtr-subs.tumblr.com
Congratulations.
See, you all tried and you succeeded.
Next, we'll do synchronized swimming.