Seen last week:
A series of shocking truths unveiled.
Yamasaki Hosei Sneaky Thief Trial!
The first one...
Even though he lost the quiz,
Yamasaki ignored the rules and asked Umezu for an autograph!
Excuse me, your autograph?
A rule violating sneaky thief!
Like an autograph,
It's fine isn't it, to get one?
No it isn't!
- That's what we're telling you!
When Tanaka did that thing with Ikko, you didn't even approach her!
Well I couljn't joo anything then-
"Couljn't joo" he says.
And the second one...
When Yamasaki tried an image change, he stole the entire outfit!
Oh this is kinda scary!
No way...
This is straight up theft!
You can't do this!
There's a limit to how much you can steal!
This is horrible.
What did I do wrong here?
And the third one...
An incident where Yamasaki stole gags from two young comedians!
"Cause it doesn't matter, cause it doesn't matter!"
"That don't matter, oh that don't matter!"
"Cause that's no problem, cause that's no problem!"
A shameless gag theft!
But just let me say this,
I used that gag I remembered, the "doesn't matter" gag.
And I remembered his rhythym, and all I did was combine them!
That's what we're saying is wrong!
We're telling you that's bad!
Why are you calling this theft, you're making me look bad!
You can't copy and combine them!
And tonight, another victim makes an appearance.
A shocking revelation awaits.
What will Yamasaki's fate be?
subbed by senor_wristband
If you'd like to support my subs, I've set up these accounts :)
patreon.com/senor_wristband
ko-fi.com/buresurettosan
By the way,
all of the gags Yamasaki has done, his material ... it looks like this.
It's not really that special.
In November 1992, he came up with this:
This, "Yey yey yey."
This is the one I most...
I wish I could remember them.
There's also "Yosha-Ko", "MA" ... "Chopsticks"?
"Face Paku Paku", "Doi Takako", and "Chucky."
What was this "Face Paku Paku" one?
So it's like this:
Paku Paku, Face Paku Paku
What's with the hands...
When do you use this...
When do you pull that out?
When do you use that?
If someone doesn't tell you-
It's for times like this.
Meaning?
If someone says "do that one."
If they tell you to do it?
TN: Doi Takako was a prominent Japanese politician
And this "Doi Takako"?
"Murayama Tomiichi has been appointed as Prime Minister."
It was that age.
Well, that's how it is.
So Yamasaki-san, would you say these are you original creations?
Indeed.
You thought up all of these?
Yes.
I see. Your Honour,
We have another victim in regards to his gags.
Can we call in this victim?
Understood.
Witness, enter.
Haranishi!
You all know him already, this is Haranishi from FUJIWARA.
Yes, that's right
Now, Yamasaki invented everything on this board.
According to him.
As he says.
You know, honestly, up until now he's been changing things other people did.
He straight up stole from me though.
He blatantly stole from me, he didn't change anything.
Really? Exactly the same?
Exactly the same.
This is shocking news isn't it?
Do you have any proof?
Yes, let's watch the VTR.
How he stole "Doi Takako."
September 1999 - 9 years ago
This was material he came up with for Matsumoto's 36th birthday.
So, Yamasaki-san?
Using an impression of Doi Takako, I will wi-wish you Happy Birthday.
"Matsumoto-san"
"Murayama Tomiichi has been appointed as Prime Min-"
What does that have to do with him?
You didn't say "Happy Birthday" at all!
On this occasion Yamasaki finally came up with a great new gag.
This became one of his signature acts, and there are many scenes of him doing it.
However, there is one thing that sticks out about this gag...
This happened 1 year before that performance...
This was an Osaka TV show that FUJIWARA were regulars on.
This is the scene that sticks out:
An imitation that a comedian shouldn't do.
An impression a comedian shouldn't do? Alright then, do it.
Former speaker of the house, Doi Takako.
Please begin.
"Murayama Tomiichi has been appointed as Prime Minister."
You straight up copied him!
"Murayama Tomiichi"
"has been appointed as Prime Minister."
The exact same performance.
Is Yamasaki a serial gag thief?
You ... you went this far?
It's just one after another!
I guess coincidences do happen.
What'd you say?
Is he laughing?
So you didn't know Haranishi did that a month ago?
Well I've never watched that show before.
I don't mean the show.
In private,
I did it in front of other comedians,
and Yamasaki was there too, no doubt.
He said you were there.
First off, the choice of Murayama Tomiichi is outdated.
It was something happened a long time ago.
It doesn't match his generation.
That phrase is from Haranishi's generation.
You know, I....
I feel really sick all of a sudden.
That's unacceptable.
No way, we're only just starting.
Can I be excused?
No no no.
No way.
Incidentally Haranishi-kun, do you have more to add? Other than that one?
Nothing else?
Actually, can I say it?
There's more?
Can I see that board from before?
Those are supposed to be Yamasaki-san's original creations.
This, "Face Paku Paku"...
He got some laughs with that before.
The discussion before of "When do you use that?"
"What's the setup?"
It does have a setup, because it's my gag!
It's unfortunate.
Really?
What kind of face is that?
Stop your cheap acting!
The origin of how he knows this...
On that TV show, there was a weekly skit corner.
I see.
Miyagawa Daisuke and I were supposed to have a conversation.
I thought it would be boring if I did it normally, so I thought up a character.
And it was this, exactly this.
I thought talking like this would be funny.
"Hey dad, dad, listen."
So I was gonna talk with that face, I thought that up.
So I showed that to Yamasaki in the train, since I was scared.
I thought it might not work
You tried it out on Yamasaki.
And he found it really hilarious.
I thought it would work then.
But I never got to do that skit.
I see.
So I never showed that gag to anybody.
But after a while, that person...
He was getting big laughs using that "Face Paku Paku."
What is the meaning of this?
There's no footage bu-
Don't just listen to him.
Look carefully, they're totally different!
Then Yamasaki-san, how did you come up with that?
Yes, why that gag?
Well, certainly, in Osaka we worked on the same TV show...
I might've seen a little bit.
So that was just seared into my memories.
So in regards to him,
Um, can you stop that? Looking at me with those dirty eyes.
You guys are all so dirty.
You should apologize-
Apologize! Why do I need to apologize?
Can I say something?
Back when we worked together in Osaka on a TV show, there were many times when I went to him for advice.
Oh really?
It was along the lines of
"We wanna leave for Tokyo soon,"
I see.
So I asked him, and he said "It's the time for you yet."
"I know best about these things. Don't leave yet.
"I'll tell you when you should come to Tokyo."
So he said he'll have your back?
But that's messed up isn't it?
It is.
The only reason he said that,
If I use that gag he wants to steal before he does...
...everyone will know he stole it.
Exactly.
So because of that, he told me to stay.
That's awful!
For that reason.
And in the end, he never told me to come to Tokyo!
"I know best about these things?"
You're the one who knows the least!
This one is terrible.
It's not terrible.
I need some advice.
Advice?
What do you mean?
For example, if a criminal admits his crime, the punishment is lessened right?
Slightly right? It's only slightly.
How much will it be lessened?
I'm not really sure about that.
Will we still be able to smile together and be friends after this?
If you're found guilty, you'll be banned from using the stuff you stole.
This is a trial after all. You can't use them anymore.
But that "Doesn't Matter" one...
...they were chanting it in the bar.
That made you really happy didn't it.
You keep bringing it up.
And that's never happened to me, in my 20+ years of comedy.
So that made me really happy.
So then shouldn't you make one up yourself?
Yeah, make your own original gag.
It's not my fault I can't think of anything.
You might come up with something right now.
Right now? Maybe, that could happen.
Naits..
I can't think of a thing.
What was that "Naits"?
I heard that "Naits" somewhere.
It's a bad habit of mine.
Finally, it's time for Yamasaki to be sentenced.
Alright, please announce his sentence.
There is no end to the defendant Yamasaki's sneaky thievery.
Since he has caused trouble so many people, we had to take that into account.
His sentence is...
...to be slapped by Chono!
WHAT?! HOLD ON!
You're kidding!
You have to be slapped by him, there's no escaping it.
Now come here.
What do you mean "Mouuuu?"
I don't like Chono-san.
I seriously don't wanna!
What the hell?
Also, after this, you can't do those gags anymore.
You're banned from those gags
Hold on...
C'mon, you gotta get past this.
I did, didn't I? I said sorry at the end.
No you didn't say that.
I did say that! I said it at the end didn't I?
You didn't.
I said "I have a bad habit. Everyone please help me fix it!"
However, the strength of the slap...
...if you really ask Chono-san to make it weaker, he just might do it.
Do I absolutely need to take this?
If I have to...let's do it.
I'll take it. I will take the slap, but,
Chono-san, I am genuinely...
...a nice guy.
I'm really a nice guy! So, just...
Chono-san, which is your dominant hand?
Just tell me that.
I'm really sorry!
Check this out!
I'm really sorry! But, this hand, could he use this hand?
I'm not sure about that.
This is supposed to be your sentence after all.
In fact, because it's this hand,
But in the past...
I got slapped on New Years right?
Because of that, three months later...
What happened 3 months later?
I was hospitalized.
That's a lie!
You weren't!
Why?
But I seriously can't do that. For real, and this is true:
...the doctor looked at me...
...and got on the phone immediately...
"WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?!" he said.
Enough of that lie now.
No really!
It's true!
Idiot! Let's move on.
Wait wait wait wait!
What the hell is it man?
No really, the doctor really did get mad.
Why'd he get angry?
He told me to say "Stop messing around!"
To who?
Chono-san
Chono-san?
Yes, exactly.
Why do you have to tell him?
Well he didn't know Chono-san's phone number!
No seriously, because what if...
The hospital might shut down!
The hospital will shut down?
That doctor might get fired! Who will treat me next time?
What kind of worry is that?
Let's move on!
Then you get slapped first please!
You get slapped first!
If Hamada-san takes it I'll do it!
Just let Hamada-san do it!
I'll do it if he does!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
ENDO!
I'M GONNA GET MAD FOR REAL!
Zaki-san, Zaki-san please!
I'M GONNA SNAP FOR REAL!
What happened?
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU! YOU STOLE FROM ME!
Enough idiot!
Enough already!
Wait wait wait wait! Hold on, wait!
What happened?
You've become a frantic miserable man.
That's true.
Put your mic on.
I went a bit frantic there...
You just stole that line from Ryu-chan!
Wow, just now!
He just stole that from Ryu-chan didn't he?
That is his phrase.
And he copied the whole thing!
I'll take it.
I, too...
...am a man after all.
Of course.
So I will take this slap,
...but with your left hand please.
No, you can't do that.
That's not allowed, otherwi-
Then, then!
Then I won't do it!
What the hell!
Where should he stand?
He's so uncool.
Are you gonna do this bit again?!
He's doing this shit again!
Enough already!
I got it.
Come stand here already!
I got it! I got it.
Do it when I say please. When I'm ready.
I'm sorry.
You're making the guy who has to slap you wait.
Yeah if you keep wasting time...
Yes, exactly.
I'm sorry everyone, really, but...
...I'm scared.
Well that makes sense.
Even after all I've been through in life,
I'm scared.
That was funny just now!
Very funny!
It doesn't matter that I'm a fully grown man,
I'm scared.
Hurry up!
I said I got it!
Did I really do something that bad?
You did!
It's because you did!
I have to get smacked by a Pro-Wrestler?
Did I do something that bad?
Yes, you did.
Sorry, it's just...
...can you not spread your stance like that?
How else would you stand?
Sorry, it's just...
Have you seen a wrestler slap like this before?
HEY ENDO!
I'M GONNA HOLD A GRUDGE AGAINST YOU!
Why? Why me?
I'll never forgive you!
What do you even mean?
You know, it's more dangerous if you try to dodge it.
So let's do this.
Wait!
The punishment slap!
That's dangerous!
Put your hands down, your hands.
The punishment please!
Dirty! So dirty!
His shoe!
How did it come off?
That was amazing as expected.
That went like "BACHIKYON!"
So the trial has been decided. Yamsaki-san, never again can you use those gags.
You must promise that.
Do you understand, Yamasaki-san?
Yes.
Hello!
Quiet down!
Shut up!
Go ahead.
How does it feel to see a star in the flesh?
You've been saying that a lot recently!
Recently? I don't know about that, I've always been a star.
You weren't famous.
Some of the guests here might have come again, after last week.
Oh poor things.
Last week we were supposed to have this talk segment right?
But then they told you to come again today.
Do you know the reason why?
For real, last week Hamada said "Let's not do the talk, man."
Because of that, we didn't do it.
It was you.
Hold on, my memories of being hit,
I've been hit 2 times.
I've been hit twice, OK now three times.
And alright alright, FOUR times.
You wanted to skip too didn't you?
What do you mean?
You were feeling sick and said you couldn't do it.
Ah yes, I was feeling a bit sick in the opening.
So we had to stop cause of that, and you had to come again, and we have this bad weather again.
Well, that's-
So I was standing outside with an umbrella. I wanted the staff to bring out a stove.
Did you really?
I did want to.
Well sometimes there's trouble on set when people come to watch.
But you know it was cold.
I was thinking two stoves per person.
Well, I'm sorry, really.
I really did think that.
Things like that happen sometime.
Excuse me sorry, I've been feeling ill lately.
Well yes, last time you were.
I noticed something after getting sick.
I think, if you timed me...
...you'll find I'm really fast at inserting suppositories.
I won't lose to anyone.
Inserting suppositories?
You know, in Japan, uhhhhhh...
I'm the 80th-
Spit it out already!
That pause is unnecessary.
You can stick them right in?
I'm probably the 80th fastest.
For example, have you ever used suppositories?
I have.
Oh really?
They're like these...
These white things.
So if you put a bunch of unwa-unwrapped ones on a table, a table like this...
...and I have my hands to the side...
Start the stopwatch and...
That's...
And my fingers will be completely clean.
Are you inserting all the way?
All the way, it's amazing.
If you hold them for too long they dissolve.
Yeah exactly, so I'll just be like this. "Ready, start" ...
Slides right in.
My fingers won't be sticky at all.
They'll be strai-
Enough already.
I can do it with anything.
Why are you eating sushi?
You know, it's not that impressive to be quick at that...
I do want to do that for an episode.
It's amazing you get it in right away, usually you need to look for it a bit.
"Here? Oh here!"
That is just plainly stupid.
It's impossible to be good at it!
You're dumb, you're dumb.
You have a messed up asshole!
Your asshole is all loose is why!
Are you saying you don't know where your anus is?
It's cause your asshole is always wide open!
Are you saying I need to put a cork in it?