1st Gaki- no-tsukai-ya -arahende!!
Duo Competition! Comedian Quiz Grand Prix!
This time, we've got some great prizes for the winners!
So please do your best!
Here are the participating comedians!
And we have special guests!
Downtown!
Hi.
This time you guys are special guests.
- All I have to do is answer the quiz, right?
- Yes.
Please take a look here.
On the back of the numbers in this panel, there are quizzes about each duo.
The higher the point, the more difficult the quiz.
- If I win, will you give me something?
- Of course!
We have prepared that.
We will present a Hawaii trip to the winning duo!
- Are you serious!?
- That's amazing!
You mean the winning duo and us get to go to Hawaii?
Sorry, your explanation wasn't clear.
If Downtown wins, you guys can go to Hawaii.
- So if Cocorico wins, we can't go?
- Of course.
This is the prize.
Good luck everyone!
- However, you cannot answer questions about yourselves.
- Well, that's obvious!
Is there something wrong?
Nothing.
- However, you cannot answer questions about yourselves.
- That's obvious!
It's natural that you know the question.
[subbed by RAIDEN1017]
There is an answer button in front of each duo.
The correct and incorrect answer buttons are for you guys to press.
If it's correct, press the correct answer button.
- We can just press this when it's about us, right?
- Yes.
So, Downtown, pick a question.
- Are we first?
- Yes!
- Which one do you wanna go with?
- I'm good with either one.
Then, Cocorico's 10.
Q. What was the name of the duo when Cocorico debuted?
Well, do you know the answer?
Of course I know that.
Downtown!
Cocorico Bombers, right?
Excellent!
You're quite knowledgeable.
Next is Cocorico.
And how many points do we get?
It was 10 points.
It was a question of 10.
Is the number on there the point?
- Yes, it was Cocorico's 10.
- Is that what it means?
So, because we chose 10, we get a 10 points?
You should have said that first.
The rules are a bit unclear.
I said that first. This is the points you get for each correct answer, with different points depending on the difficulty level.
So, do we get to go to Hawaii?
Only if you guys win.
If only you had won at the end.
You can't go to Hawaii every time you answer correctly.
Huh?
What?
You can't go to Hawaii every time you answer correctly.
I thought I could go to Hawaii every time I answered correctly.
That's not doable.
Isn't that number the number of times you can go to Hawaii?
All right, that's enough.
Sorry, anyway, Downtown gets 10 points!
Now, Cocorico, please pick a panel.
Downtown's 10!
Q. What was the most popular show in Osaka that began broadcasting in 1987 and was hosted by Downtown?
I know this!!
I know this!
This is too easy a question!
Jikacho!
"It's 4 o'clock"!
That's wrong?
Isn't "It's 4 o'clock"?
Is this wrong?
Not "It's 4 o'clock"?
It's not.
No, it's actually "Rush! It's 4 o'clock".
Huh, why did you already give the answer?
- There are duos who haven't answered yet.
- Please wait until you get the correct answer.
- You should have said that first!
- It's hard to understand!
Did it have the word "Rush" in its name?
I watched the show every day, but ...
We left that out from the first show because it was too complicated for the broadcast.
Then, the answer is "it's 4 o'clock".
It might have been "it's 4 o'clock Rush!".
In any case, " Rush" is in the title.
- But there was no "Rush" from the first episode, was there?
- Yeah.
But at the meeting stage, it was "It's 4 o'clock Rushï¼".
Then we don't know.
But the producer told me to do it with that in mind.
But we were watching the broadcast from the very first episode, so...
Cut it out with the endless gripes!
This is incorrect!
So we get 10 points?
No, Jicho-Kacho just doesn't get the points.
That is nonsense.
We should get 10 tons.
10 tons!?
That's not possible. The units are different.
Because no one could answer.
Hey, nobody's laughing.
Let's do it properly.
Nobody's laughing.
But this is just a quiz.
So which one shall we try next?
I would like to challenge the high scoring question.
Downtown's 20!
Q. What is Hamada's favorite animal with a long nose?
Football Hour.
Elephant!
- No?
- There are many other things besides elephants.
Cocorico!
Anteater!
Jicho-Kacho!
Tapir.
Got it!
The animal with the long nose is...
I haven't answered yet.
Dog.
Time is up.
I got various answers, but...
This one was a little difficult.
It was a difficult for 20 points.
Now tell us the correct answer.
Shall I give the answer?
Yeah....yeah....okay.
Hamada said that an animal with a long nose is an elephant.
I answered that!
But Hamada doesn't like elephants.
- So...
- But the question says "his favorite animal".
Yeah, so...
The animal with the long nose is definitely an elephant.
Do you like that?
No...
Oh, it can't be helped.
It says so in the question.
This is a quiz made by Downtown.
It's not a quiz made by the staff.
This is a quiz made by you guys.
I think this must be a question made with reference to Hamada's much older profile, surely?
Now Hamada says he doesn't like elephants.
You have to understand that.
Did Hamada-san write in his old profile that his favorite animal was an elephant?
- I don't know about that either.
- It's a cute profile.
You can decide what to do.
I don't like that, though.
See, Hamada is getting like this!
That's enough!
Okay, let's start over and raise the energy!
Downtown, please pick a panel!
You can pick.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Let's do it together.
The game is just beginning.
Downtown, please pick any one you like.
Everyone has made their questions.
Jicho-Kacho's 20.
Q. JIcho-Kacho used to be a trio called Jicho-Kacho-Shacho.
So, what is the occupation that the former member is currently doing in Shinjuku?
Male host.
Okonomiyaki restaurant.
Bar?
Udon restaurant?
Time is up!
Hey, this is up!
This was UP-P before the time's up sounded.
What's wrong today?
What the hell.
This was up before the time's up sounded.
- And it's a disgusting atmosphere.
- "Up-p"?
He's been stuttering a lot today.
So what is the correct answer?
The correct answer is a hairdresser.
By the way, what were you going to answer?
Hairdresser.
- But...
- His answer was correct.
But the time was up.
-I was correct.
- But it can't be helped.
- What was Hamada's answer?
- Bar.
I think the bar is close to the answer too.
In terms of approximate values, yes.
Approximate values?
Jicho-Kacho won the game match and became the top.
This is rigged!
- This is ridiculous!
- It can't be because there are so many holes.
- But if we were the first, we would have put it in this hole.
- Yeah, I said so.
- I said, "This one, I guess".
- "This one"?
- I said so.
- He said he would put it in this hole.
But Inoue was first in the order.
Earlier, when he had the sword, he said, "This one".
But you guys were not first.
Is this not good?
But the turn was theirs first, you guys were close.
Whatever!!
Q. Hamada invited Matsumoto to join Yoshimoto and he was quite torn. But...?
The 40 points question is quite difficult.
"But..."?
Is this a valid question?
Time is up.
Please tell us the correct answer.
After all, no one could answer and I don't have to tell you that, do I?
We want to know the correct answer.
There is no answer to this question.
What does that mean?
There is no answer.
Then it's not a question.
Huh, why are you looking surprised?
That's actually the expression we make.
Why are you looking so surprised?
"There is no answer"?
If the answer is your private information and you can't answer, is there even the right one?
Of course there is.
There is that.
I wouldn't be saying this if that wasn't there.
Would you tell us that?
There is that.
I don't like today's Endo.
He is very quarrelsome.
I'm not like that.
I really want to compete with people from my own generation after all.
But when Tommies hears that, he's going to say, "What do you mean?"
High-heels would say the same thing.
No, Ken-chan(Tommies) will answer in a better way.
Then, Downtown, please choose the next panel.
Okay, Endo's.
My dislike of Cocorico Endo's 40.
Q. What was the first legend they achieved when Cocorico Golden Legend was still airing late at night?
- Downtown.
- Ate all the conveyor belt sushi?
Eating eel pie for 7 days.
Climbing the chimney of a public bathhouse.
We did that too, but different.
- This is difficult.
- Time is up.
Hey, is this the button that makes the time is up sound?
- No, this is the button to up this.
- Are you sure about that?
- This is like the time is up button.
- The timing of the sound of Time is up was the same.
Oh, this is up again.
Then please answer.
What's the answer?
Guys, can I give him the right to answer?
I won't listen, so go ahead and give the answer!
This has already timed out, hasn't it?
But I gave him one chance to answer.
He's covering his ears now, so just tell me the answer.
He's covering his ears.
Matsumoto-san, what are you doing?
Matsumoto-san?
Matsumoto-san.
Please go ahead and answer.
- I won't listen, so go ahead and give the answer.
- Yeah, don't worry.
Why don't you tell me the answer?
It doesn't make sense to me.
I really don't make any sense.
I told him I would give him the right to answer.
- So I don't make any sense at all why he is covering his own ears.
- You must never say the answer.
If he really can't hear, should I go ahead and give the answer?
It's better to speak in a low voice.
We made a leaf rake using real bear paws.
Wow, you were doing that!
Well, Matsumoto-san, please answer.
Matsumoto-san.
Ummm, could it be that one?
Maybe it's the one about the bear?
Did you hear the answer I said?
"The one about bear"?
Maybe it's the one about bear?
Close! Close! Close! Close! Close!
Making a leaf rake using real bear paws?
Yeah!
Excellent.
It's weird to answer, "The one about bears".
This is quite a difficult question to answer.
So, Downtown gets 40 points.
We have no choice but to play a big game.
Downtown's 50.
Serious match!
Washtub Stopper Challenge!
Please come forward.
This is a game where your guts count.
Whoever blindfolds themselves and stops the falling washtub closest to their head wins.
- Wow, that's scary.
- Who wants to be the first to do this?
Iwao, you do it.
Okay, I'll do it.
It's a big washtub.
It's disadvantageous to be the first to do this.
That might be true.
Wouldn't it have been better if you had seen someone else do it first before you did it?
He suddenly said, "I'll do it."
- Please start at your timing.
- Okay.
Here I go.
Don't let go of the rope.
Do you understand how to do this?
If you let go of the rope, it's absolutely impossible
Why did you do this in the first?
You should have points deducted.
Why did you let go of the rope?
I was going to let go of the rope and then grab it.
That's impossible because you're blindfolded.
Get a hold of yourself!
- Now it's Jicho-Kacho's turn, which one of you will do this?
- I will do it.
- If you've done this before, you're good at it.
- Koumoto-san seems to be good at this kind of thing.
Shouldn't he be out?
Isn't this a game where you shouldn't let the washtub hit your head?
Alright, you may begin!
I'm counting on you!
Here I go!
Stop! I'll measure!
You were too scared.
That's pretty high.
70 cm!
I thought I could get it under 50 cm.
Your record is 70 cm.
Next please.
Those with a higher sitting height may have an advantage.
- Are you alright?
- I'm okay.
You have to grab the red tape.
- You were grabbing the red tape, weren't you?
- Yes.
He didn't.
Are you okay?
He's out, isn't he?
He hasn't tried yet.
- That sounded terrible.
- It hurt like hell.
The corner of the washtub hit him in the head.
Are you okay?
It's pretty dented.
That must have hurt him a lot.
His face is turning red.
Endo challenged in place of the injured Tanaka.
However, he could not match Koumoto's record.
85 cm!
Now, Matsumoto-san will take the next challenge.
Matsumoto-san, you have done something like this several times, haven't you?
Maybe so.
Alright, you may begin!
Here I go.
Wait a second.
The ruler isn't long enough to measure the length.
- Wait a second.
- What's wrong?
I'm kind of so scared.
This is that kind of game.
This is a game of chicken.
I'm having heart palpitations.
Really?
I have a little heart palpitations.
Are you okay?
However, your record is already out.
It's over 100 cm.
Okay, I'll do it.
I'll do it again.
Let's have him do it again.
But he has already done this.
I cannot end with such a record.
I feel bad for everyone.
No, you don't have to do it anymore.
He feels bad but says he'll do it again.
Please grab the red tape.
Let's go.
Matsumoto-san, you may begin!
This isn't good, I still feel sick.
-  I feel sick.
- Let's measure his record.
No, no, no, he is feeling unwell.
I feel sick. I feel palpitations.
You'll be okay. It's okay.
Let's measure now.
He didn't do this yet.
- I feel like throwing up.
- Hang in there a little longer!
Hang in there! Just a bit more!
- Oh, I feel sick.
- Just a bit more!
- I feel sick. I feel like throwing up.
- Just a bit more! Almost!
Oh, great!
Very nice!
That's great!!
You did it!!
Okay...
Here!!
What the hell are you doing?
You did it!
Measure it quickly, Yama-chan!
8 cm.
You did it well.
You did well even though you weren't feeling well.
It was close.
Look, it's only this much.
It's because you were giving instructions.
I didn't do that.
You did.
I'm kind of sorry.
but...
I see, so my record was 8cm.
It's not your record.
You didn't stop the falling washtab by yourself.
He did it slowly.
He didn't do it slowly. Can't I see the video recording?
Can we watch the recorded video?
He didn't do it slowly.
Let's watch the video recording.
[VCR Verification]
This is very slow
See, I'm just cheering him on.
He is not wearing an eye mask.
His eye mask is completely off.
Here!!
He said "Here".
As you can see, Hamada-san was giving instructions.
No, I was just cheering him on!
And Matsumoto-san's eye mask was completely off.
So Koumoto wins!
You guys totaled 70 points.
That was the last game.
So the winner is Jicho-Kacho!
Congratulations!
We are giving away a trip to Hawaii to you guys.
Yeah! Hawaii!
Have fun!
I don't think he can easily accept something like that.
Yeah, I feel sorry for them.
Thay hasn't shown his good side at all
I could see how athletic he is.
That's not good.
Shall we receive it on your behalf?
Why?
Could you lend it to us for a little while?
Do you want to borrow this?
Do you want to borrow this board?
It would be okay to just lend it to them, right?
I can lend you this board.
But, we have the rights to the trip to Hawaii.
Show us on camera.
What are you doing?
Play the sound, hey!
What are you guys doing?
What are they doing?
I don't mind lending it to you guys, but what are you guys doing with it?
The winner is Jicho-Kacho.
You guys wanted to feel like a winner?
I see.
But I don't think the sound will play even if you have this.
It's the same for anyone who has this.
See?
Please don't push the button.
Then lend it to us.
Staff should also not play that.
Why did they play the sound?
- They are not winners.
- That's the staff's fault.
What are they doing?
Let's go then.
See you.
Yama-chan, you should think more about what you're doing.
Because the quiz is all about the content.