DTR Subs
http://dtr-subs.tumblr.com
July 17, 2005
Translation by typesoshee
Typesetting by DuckToaster
Proofreading by Oolong
In the green room before shooting
In the green room before shooting,
Yamasaki and Cocorico wait for Downtown's arrival.
However, only this man arrived.
Hey.
Who is this?
"Who is this"? It's me.
Hello.
Oh, hello.
Hold on a second.
You're dressed up like a pervert.
I'm dressed as a kuroko*.  If you see me wearing this,
Note*: A kuroko is a traditional Japanese theater stagehand. Kurokos dress in all black to imply to the theater audience that they are supposed to be invisible and not part of the onstage action.
you should be able to tell what I've come for.
Could it be that thing that we've done a few times before?
What is the dream that Matsumoto envisioned!?
The event that Matsumoto set his sights on this time is...
Swimming
swimming.
The 100 meters freestyle world record at the time was 47.84 seconds
The 100 meters freestyle men's world record at the time was 47.84 seconds.
What is Matsumoto's challenge!?
And Matsumoto's challenge is...
This time he wants to swim 25 meters and go under 10 seconds.
Impossible, that's gotta be impossible.
That has to be an impossible time.
Matsumoto is saying he wants to do it.  So help him.
But...
What's your problem?
Are you going to do it or not?  Be clear about it.
I will do it.  After that
He's waiting at the hall!
No, no, I'll do it.
Then, why don't we
Yes.
get ready.
You guys get changed, too.
Oh...
This, this thing here - they've been prepared for you.
Ok.
The four kurokos have risen again.
Freestyle Swimming
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Swim 25 meters in 10 seconds!!
Matsumoto Hitoshi: Swim 25 meters in 10 seconds!
For now,
Yes.
let's just do what we can.
Yes, yes.
That's always what it comes down to, anyway.
Yes.
Understood.
Huh?
He almost slipped there.
Yes, he almost slipped.
Hey.
Hello.
Everyone
pretty much agreed
and showed up.
Whoa.  Pecs?
He's moving his pecs!
But it's not that much.
Why is he moving them?
I feel like
you all are thinking that I don't want
to break a record.
But I do want to break a record.
Which is why,
I ask that you help me out here.
*Note: Matsumoto is doing an impression of Takada Nobuhiko, a former pro-wrestler, MMA fighter, and PRIDE (an MMA organization) executive.  See video: http://bit.ly/1O9wt1C
Come on out!*
He might be a little scared.
That's true.  The goggles are also really...
Frankly,
I have no idea what's going to be done to me.
But, I mean... right?
You'll be fine!
Matsumoto's 1st Attempt!!
Matsumoto's first attempt!
Please, thank you.
Let's make it happen in one shot.
That'd be nice.
Set him up, first.
Whoa.
He's already gone limp.
Just do it.
Let's make it happen in one shot.
Yup.
Here we go.
There we go.
Let's make it happen in one shot.
10 seconds, all right?
Let's go!
Yes, let's go!
Ready, start!
All right!
Let's go!  Hurry!
Hamada, Hamada, please hurry!
Ok, flutter kick!
All right, it's good, it's good!
There we go, there we go!
It's deep!
Forget it! Forget it!
It's too dangerous!
My feet can't reach the bottom anymore.
Get out of here!
That was dangerous.
Yeah, that was.
That was deep!
This pool becomes gradually deeper towards the goal area.
Didn't know that was the deal.
Are you even trying?
It's just...
If you're gonna abandon me when it gets deep...
Matsumoto's 2nd Attempt!!
With caution for the depth of the pool, the second attempt.
Tanaka.
Here we go. Yes.
Endo, too.
Yes.
Here.
Yes, got it.
Yes. We got it.
Ready... Go!
No way, this is impossible
Let's go.
Time's running.
Time's passing.
Ok, here.
Ok. Ok.
Keep going, keep going.
Come on, Hamada!
Come on!
After he gets on, all right?
Set him on a shopping cart and use the force of a rubber cord to swim
Don't pull! Don't pull yet!
It won't attach!
All right? Go!
Ok, go!
Go!
What?
That's strange.
He gets separated from the shopping cart and the plan unfortunately fails
Wait, what?
Come on, you gotta do a better job pulling it.
Can we, one more time...
Hey.
Huh?
One more time.
Let's try it one more time.
You know, he was drowning the whole time when we were setting up.
That's why...
He was drowning?
Let's go and tell them we want to try it again.
Yes.
The result wasn't so good, but if we can get that belt attached firmly to you,
Yes. Yes.
it should be able to make it to this side
It would've made it.
at a pretty good speed.
Yes.
600.
600?
What do you mean?
The amount of water I swallowed.
*Note: Matsumoto means in milliliters.
It seems I straight up swallowed 600 water.*
Yeah.
What's that?
Tajima?
The thing is,
Assistant
Tajima Yuichi
to be honest, um
the velcro
really hurts.
But if only that would stay firm, then
Huh?
That sort of, oh
Tajima, this piece is done cooking.
Yes. Thank you.
That sort of consideration from you is completely lacking.
The male side of the velcro is right on my skin,
not the smooth side, the really jagged side,
is completely locked on to me.
Matsumoto's 3rd Attempt!!
Building on top of the past failed result, the third attempt.
Thank you.
Got it, thank you.
Use the power of radio-controlled boats to swim
Ok.
Let's go.
Ready, go!
Let's go!
Ok, thank you.
Put him on top.
Put him on.
Ok.
Ready, and
Steady. Ok.
There.
Ok.  The other way.
Argh!
What the hell are you doing?
It's supposed to be the other way.
Oh, just do it from that side.
Let's go.
Ok.
Wait, stop, stop.
Good.
Whoa.
Ok, still ok.
Pull Tanaka, just pull more.
Ok.
He's fallling, he's falling.
What the hell.
Here.
There you go.
Ok.
We got it.
The other way?
The other way.
This is for the feet.
Ok.
All right.
Make this straight.
Go there.
Yes.
All right!
Go!
Yes, go!
Yes, go, go!
It's going.
It's going, it's going.
It's going, it's going!
It's going!
Keep it up!
Fast forwarding
Almost there!
A little more.
Hey, almost there, almost there.
Go. Go. Go.
Goal!
Goal
He's probably full with emotion.
Yeah, you're right.
Yes.
We're good.
He's coming now.
Watch out for the boats.
Make way.
How many minutes was that?
Someone smacked my inner thigh.
Someone did that, right? Who was that?
It was you?
You smacked my inner thigh, didn't you?
That kind of stuff really hurts.
Sorry.
Saying things like "This guy,"
"Do it right, dumbass."
No more verbal abuse at me.
Matsumoto's 4th Attempt!!
They pull themselves together for the fourth attempt.
Let's make this one work.
Let's make it work.
Please!
Use the power of wrestlers to swim
Shall we?
Ready...
Here we go.
Here we go!
Ok, go!
Swim fast!
Here we go!
It's fast! It's fast!
It's fast!
Here we go!
Whoa!
Let's go!
Let's go now!
Keep it up!
It's good!
Go!
Good, good!
Keep it up!
Let's go!
It's fast!
Keep going!
You can do it!
Keep it up!
You can do it.
That was close.
That took a lot of time.
Right.
Wasn't this faster?
Would it have been better if we had more people?
That might be right.
Should we go see him?
Yes.
Yes. Yes.
Let's go, again.
The group go to Matsumoto's dressing room to apologize
Excuse us.
*Note: A reference to the manga and anime Dokonjo Gaeru.
You probably get it
without me having to say anything.
Well, uh,
in the one before the previous one, talking about the velcro, I mentioned it right?
That I can't stand that jagged sensation.
Oh, yes.
Right?
There was a guy in there who had a stubble
that was crazy.
At first I thought someone was wearing a fake beard.
Those jagged sharp edges.
It's tedious just having to mention this.
So, what I'm saying, you see,
is that none of you think about those sort of things for me,
*Note: A reference to the manga and anime Dokonjo Gaeru.
so I'm scared as hell when I'm going through it.
Yes.
All right?
It's ridiculous.
Hello.
Sorry, Hiroshi is giving a scolding right now.*
*Note: A reference to the manga and anime Dokonjo Gaeru.  Hiroshi is the character in the manga that Matsumoto dressed as.
Yes, Hiroshi is.
He's attempting to achieve a new record.
But Hamada's directing is awful.
Will you give us another chance?
Let's finish this on a strong note.
Yes, let's do that.
Let's go.
Matsumoto's 5th Attempt!!
Will they finally succeed? The fifth attempt!
If this here works out, it'll be really fast.
Yes, that's right.
Yeah.
It might go under 10 seconds.
Yes, it should.
I think this will.
It'd be really nice if it did go under 10 seconds, after how far we've come.
Let's do this.
He's really making sure not to slip.
Walking very cautiously
Walking very firmly.
Yeah, he's walking very firmly.
Won't his eyes hurt?
I really want to make this the last one.
Yes.
Yes. Apologies for that.
Of course.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
Ok, get it ready.
Please, thank you.
All right.
All right, let's bring it out.
Let's seriously make it with this one.
Thank you.
This equipment is called a "Zorb"
Ok, it's good.
Please, thank you.
Here we go.
All right.
Use the Zorb and the power of the wrestlers to swim
This will go fast.
Yeah, this will.
Ok.
Let's go all out on this on.
Ok, let's do it.
Let's go!
Ready...
Good, good.
All right.
Yeah!
Go!
Turn it, turn it!
We ran out of time
Ah yes, we did
It was turning really fast.
Yes, it really was.
Matsumoto?
Matsumoto!
Matsumoto.
He left again.
Yes, he did.
That's all we can prepare, though.
The group go to Matsumoto's dressing room to apologize, again
It can't be helped. Well, we did what we could.
*Note: "ZEEBRA - Big Big Money ft. Hiro" is the original hip hop track.
My name is Tajima Yuichi,
*Note: Yoshimoto is the talent agency that represents Downtown.
number one bad boy of Yoshimoto.*
Gonna make you hear
my awesome rap, listen.
Matsumoto is pretty furious.
Your (mumbled) is being considered thus.
You 4 as entertainers are worthless.
Hamada's lips: hilarious.
Matsumoto is amazing with his kindness.
The last chance he's giving you is this.
You 4 as entertainers are B-list.
Besides that, Hamada's lips: hilarious.
This is the last one, so
Yes.
All right?
I'm really counting on you for this last one.
Yes. That's totally... right?
Yes.
This is the last one, all right?
Why the hell are my lips hilarious?
I have no idea.
Matsumoto's 6th Attempt!!
This is the last chance. The sixth attempt!
He really is making sure not to slip.
We've overcome some issues we had,
and the program is getting near to the end.
Yes.
If we don't make it work here
We understand.  We do understand that.
people will think we're idiots.
Yes.
Let's go! All right!
All right!
Let's go!
Ok.
Velcro
This will definitely hurt. This will definitely hurt.
This will definitely hurt.
The rope already has a dangerous color.
Is everything good?
Make him swim by pulling on a rope from the goal area
We're good.
We're counting on you.
All right.
Ok. Ready...
Here we go.
It's fast! This is good.
We can make it!
Goal
There it is!
9.80.
A Great Success!?
Swim 25 Meters in 10 Seconds!!
After overcoming many trials and tribulations,
finally, success
in swimming 25 meters in an amazing record of 9.80 seconds.
A new legend was born today in the world of swimming.
Matsumoto Hitoshi,
you are a true gold medalist.