It's time for the Murakami Shoji's class series no one asked for
On his latest episode, the feudal lord class,
he set a new record with his low 5.5% ratings
Not only that...
Huh? What's that?
Another feudal lord?
Real feudal lord - Tokuma Nishioka
What are you doing here? Why don't you come to my class instead?
It ended up with the real feudal lord
Nishioka taking over his entire class
I'm a feudal lord and I'm feud up with all of this!
Which will be today's class about?
Downtown (Matsumoto Hitoshi & Hamada Masatoshi)
Cocorico (Endo Shozo & Tanaka Naoki)     Yamazaki Hosei
We came after all
Are you a granny?
Is this "granny classroom"?
If so, you'll get a full score on it
Are you in charge of this?
You seem to be our master
That's not it
We already have one
Actually
I heard that he disappeared without explanations
But really, I wonder what is this?
I want to know
Same costumes
Today will be...
"Michael Jackson classroom", it seems
I think it will be better than learning from Michael himself
Is it okay to say this?
I wouldn't want him to abuse me, you know
It's our senior but I guess you can say it
Anyway, during our meetings he always says
"I want to do this and this and this..."
And that's amazing
Yeah
But when we're actually filming, everything becomes half-assed
Such a waste of spirit
Or donate @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai   /  patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Want to support? Like my FB page: facebook.com/shionnotsukai
translation & subs by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Murakami Shoji's Classroom Series!
Nothing will ever happen today!
On their way to the park where they'll meet
To be honest I don't know much about Michael
Unfortunately
But you do, right Yamazaki?
Yeah I actually like him a lot
Really?
- Yeah
Why is he making us join him?
There's a sign
We don't even know much
"Michael Jackson Classroom - wait here"
"koko de wait"
Is there really no one else besides us?
Right, now that you mention it
Someone should do this
Yeah, like some young comedians
- That's right
I think Fruit Punch or such would do this
That's undoubtedly him
He's here
Murakami Shoji
That's the real deal
No doubts
That's him from back then
I don't know much about him but I heard about this earlier
He moved while staying so stiff
That was unexpectedly quick
So fast
Please, do not expect much from today's episode
nothing in particular is going to happen overall.
Is that it?
I wonder
You can tell he practiced
He laughed at himself
No good, I made one mistake in a dance move
If Michael was
avil
liv...
still alive to this day
He would have been so mad right now!
Eh? What?
What was that?
But now he's peacefully resting
I can tell you're surprised
Like, "weren't you dead?!"
I'm the second generation
Janet called me and told me the next Michael should be me or such
His little sister?
- Yes, Janet Jackson
Yes, his daught--
little sister
"Daughter"
He said it
You know
This is exhausting for me too
I'm traveling nonstop by myself
I see
Few days ago
I had this double booking for Singapore and Wakayama
I only went to Wakayama in the end, though...
I'm already 57, man
My legs hurt, my back hurts
Lately the only
thing I've been doing since morning is eating fried rice
Why fried rice?
Hey!
The hell are you doing?
Learn how to dance
Michael Jackson Classroom - First Lesson:
First off, they'll have to learn
Some easy dance moves, indispensable for Michael
Do you know what's Michael most peculiar dance move?
Can I say it?
It's the moonwalk
What's up with you getting it right so easily?
Whatever
We don't need gags for today
Ok
- Oh, really?
Matsumoto, try to do the moonwalk
Here?
Yeah, try it
Hey, are you bullshitting me, you dick?
Sorry but I have no idea how to dance
Your turn, Endo
I never tried it before...
That's the right posture!
Really?
That was so good! I'm shocked!
Was that your first time?
Yes
Whaaat?!
Did you see that?!
We did, yeah
That was really good
But I think Endo is not accustomed to it yet
Yes
- That's obvious
Here
We'll use this
That's what Michael used when he was learning the moonwalk
Come on, Endo & Tanaka
Alright
He really likes drawers, doesn't him?
Endo & Tanaka are challenged!
Hey! Watch this!
Yes
This is how you learn how to moonwalk
Move it until the sign with "until here"
Sure
Until there
I see
sign: "until here!!"
Move it in a moonwalk-like style
"Like"?
Alright
Oh, that's good!
Just like that!
Try to go a little faster
Raise your feet up, just like that
Looking good, well done
Now, opposite direction
Turnabout
- It's reverse now
Tanaka!
That's not how you do it
You're not moonwalking at all
Have you seen Endo's?
I did not
Did--- oh, you couldn't see him
- Yes
Alright, whatever
Put it down
So it's just Endo...
Endo is good at it
Ok, Matsumoto & Yamazaki
Yes
You're next
- Ok
Yamazaki & Matsumoto are challenged!
Counting on you
Alright, ready, set, go!
It's like shuffling
You have to slide better
Raise your feet more or else you can't do it
Reverse!
Got it
Matsumoto
Your axis is way too tilted, what are you doing you idiot?!
What a sharp tongue
Raise em up, low em down!
He's so rude
I had enough
Watch out!
Dangerous
And so rude
- That was scary as hell
Let's have Endo do it
You're not suited for this
Isn't Endo enough for you?
You want me to do it?
Michael!
Be sure to watch this
His name is Michael too?
So confusing
He's my relative
Oh I see, it's so clear
He's more related to my sister actually
Alright
Here we go
Michael, let's go
He's running
Change!
Can he do it?
- He's too fast
I mean, he's teaching us
He's good
- He's really good
The best one
He's the best one!
Your sister's relative is so good
Look how good he is
Put it down!
Your sister's relative has talent
Just read the mood
You idiot!
I'm always saying that
Geez...
You got it? More or less?
Shall we head to our next training while the weather is still nice?
Are... we done here?
Learn the way he sings
Michael Jackson Classroom - Second Lesson:
Next up they'll learn Michael's singing technique
Which bewitched the entire world
Listen up
When we talk about Michael, we talk about his shafts
"Shouts"
It's "shouts", actually
Shafts
The "shout" is that thing on boats
What do you w-- I mean, come on, feel it
Alright
Each time he made those screams
The audience would completely go insane
How about we try it?
Try it out, Hamada
That "PPOOH!" thing, ok?
Ok
Do your best
Like this, try it
I must say, it was impressive
Go for it
That was really good!
Now you try, Matsumoto
Maybe a bit higher pitch?
Ok, Endo
Sure
Yours...
Your shout was like... you know, like that thing...
Oh well, whatever
Like what...?
Are you trying to worsen my headache?
Ok, Yamazaki
Good, very good
But you were all no good
Let's practice
We'll practice it while listening to a song we all know
We're ready
POH! POH! POH! The pigeon goes POH! POH!
This is horrible
Hey, we're gonna do it
Get ready, we're all doing it
[music] let's all eat em together~♪
Get ready!
Almost there
Go!
POH! POH! POH! The pigeon goes POH! POH!
Not even close
Stop it!
But teacher...
That was so bad
You know
Once you'll become Michael you can live in Neverland Ranch
Yes I get how you feel
Me too, I can finally live here in Neverland Ranch thanks to this
In here...?
I've talked to the original owner of Neverland
He said he wouldn't listen to me though
Who cares
Here we go
Don't be shy
Huh?
I thought it felt strange
I thought "maybe he forgot to rewind the tape"
Ok, enough with this
But we haven't learned anything yet!
Listen
More than Michael Jackson...
You should
Know more about his life, or else you won't understand this
He's right
Let's start from Jackson Five!
Jackson Five, ok
Jackie
Yes?
I said let's start from Jackson Five and I said "Jackie", ok?
Yes
You're the older brother!
I see, Jackie, the older brother
Tito
Yes---
Too slow
Yes, sorry
It's you, isn't it?
- Tito, yes, sorry
Enough,
you can't do it
You can't even do "Jackson Five"
Oh come on, let's do it
Don't you think you're cutting everything too short, teacher?
Too quick!
Let us do it
You can't quit climbing halfway
What's wrong?
Pros like me know it
Only by that?
- Yeah
Jackson Five was too much for you now
Should we go for Finger Five instead?
note: Japanese pop band from the 60s
Finger five...    - Isn't that unrelated?
No, Michael used to listen to them
That's a news
Oh, this one?
He went "WOOOW" here
song playing: Finger Five - Koi No Daiaru 6700
She just said "wow"
So late
Take notes!
Tomorrow is our graduation ceremony ♪
[music] And it will be my last chance ♪
[music] So as my fingers are trembling ♪
[music] I slowly turned the dial ♪
[music] And your phone number ♪---
Number!!
Is 090 [censor] 28 [censor] 1
Telephone numbers sure became long since mobiles were made
I can only remember my phone in Osaka
It was 06 [censor] 34 [censor] 5 or such
Wanna quit this?
I have no idea, really
I have no idea what you want to show us
Learn his attitude
Michael Jackson Classroom - Third Lesson:
Next up is a training to become like Michael on a mental side
Please, do not expect much from today's episode
nothing in particular is going to happen overall.
Listen, let's just stop moving around for now
We're all tired, let's set it aside
Let's do a Michael training using our head, shall we?
Yes
I'm now going to show you some of Michael's famous pictures
Let's make it like a quiz
I'll give a prize to whoever gets it right
Alright?
So
Do you know this picture?
That's his signature pose
Yeah
Isn't that the "POH" we just did?
Oh right, that
It's the "POH"!
Not even close
I'll give you a hint, he was in Korea
It's like he's saying "so spicy!", right?
Maybe he was eating Jjigae?
Something spicy...
No, it's not Jjigae!
Kimchi?
That's it!
But
It was a home-made Kimchi made by a korean mom
He's saying something
Something like "WOOOOOOW!"
And that means "it's spicy"?
Tanaka
You won something
You're weak, so I'm giving you this
Take it
Try to hold this
Hold it tight
It was that banana
Nice, right?
I got this from Mah-kun
note: Masahiro Tanaka, baseball player
You mean Masahiro Tanaka?
A guy who works in a yakitori shop
Not our Mah-kun
Alright, next one
He liked kids, right?
That's right
That's true, but this dude is not a kid
He's not a kid
It's an old dude
Yes
It's from an exhibition in Japan
An exhibition in Japan...?
Is it?
Yes, it's from the backstage
That's a picture from when he met Minoru Shiraki
note: a very short japanese actor (1,40m)
Such a shame none of you got it
What about this one?
Is he spotting someone from the audience?
Damn, you were so close!
Think about something he puts on
Come on
Something...
Sunglasses?
That's it!
He forgot his sunglasses, these are impromptu hand-sunglasses
You're amazing, Endo
I'll give you this
That's a hat I got from a hostess in Ebisu 2 years ago
Alright, Matsumoto try harder ok?
You're right, I will
This one
That's the picture from when he met Minoru Shiraki
Oh, my mistake
Here, Matsumoto, this...
You got it right, so here
This is...?
- A bag for you
Alright
One more thing
As an extra prize, I'll have you hold this, Matsumoto
You had that too?!
That's huge
This is
What's this?
It's a movie
"Crow's thumb" by Tadafumi Ito, 2012
Coming out this fall
Is this really coming out?
Yes, it is
Is it a prop or is it real?
No, this is real
I have more if you want to see them
Like this one
It seems so fake somehow...
- What's with this pose?!
- You sure it's not a prop?
I mean look at it, it looks so fake
What's this?
I swear it's true
What's with this expression?
Well, I'm sort of the main character
"Crow's thumb"...?
Yeah
I also have this
Looks so fake though
Is this true?     - You gotta be kidding me
- It feels weird
I don't know what to say about this
But it looks true
I'll bring this up again later
I'll go get em
Alright
Next training
Learn his steps
Michael Jackson Classroom - Fourth Lesson:
Here's their final training
It's time to learn Michael's incredible steps
I think it become clear
What to do with the third generation
Is that so?
- Yes
But let me say this
You're not ready to be Michael Jackson yet, it's impossible
That's why I think I should show you Michael's greatness
Some more
Alright?
Take these
Huh? What's that?
He really likes those too...
- True
These are ash bombs
Back then when I used to live on the countryside
I used to put ash inside bags and throw em
To old dudes on the fields
Ash bombs?
- That's their name?
Yeah we called em like that
If they hit you, they cause some damage
Of course they do
- If they hit
But now I'm going to avoid em all while dancing
If he manages to do it he's even better than Michael, isn't him?
Wanna try it?
Sure
Woah, ash bombs...
Throw em as they are
Impressive
Let us know when you're ready
It's ok, throw em
What are we gonna do after this?
I think that's it
Are we going?
Well, I think we...
Come on, let's go
Don't worry, I'll pay for everything
If it's money---
Huh?
Hmm?
I'm sure I...
Huh?
Translation / typesetting / subs by  Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
This is my wallet!
Oh my!
I have no idea how it got there
THRILLER!!
Thriller!
Websites:  shionnotsukai.wordpress.com  /  fb.com/shionnotsukai  ← like it!
Isn't this--
Isn't this just horrible?
Support my works on :  ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai  or  patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Let's go home      - It's so bad
Macchan it's just like we said during the meeting
He even shouted "thriller"!
You were laughing so much during our meeting!
Endo! Come here and apologize!
Enough