First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai!
"This ain't ecological, right?"
"Scorching heat bare-hand hell:
no-chopsticks battle!"
Matsumoto-san...
Yes?
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
I don't get it
Oh, don't you? We can't use chopsticks
Today we're gonna see if we can eat all the food bare handed
That's why it's a "no-chopsticks battle"
We all got fired up talking about this in the meeting
But thinking about it, there's nothing to be excited about
We're not even betting on anything
Right, we do have the right atmosphere though
No-chopsticks battle!!
Scorching heat bare-hand hell!
Welcome to the no-chopstick hellfire battle
Starting tonight for all to see!
No-chopsticks fight
You have 90 seconds to eat up all the hot food without chopsticks
rules
Waiting for our members is a full-course of hot food
Their challenge will be to eat everything bare handed within 90 seconds
Charm
Each member's performance will be rated following these parameters
Finger technique
Madness
No-chopsticks fight
Smartness
Speed
rules
The best eater will be decided by the rest of them, following these 5 parameters
"Madness"?
Yeah, madness
By this I mean "being majestic, manly, aggressive"
"Being majestic, manly, aggressive"
Madness
"Aggressive"?
"Majestic"...?
It's hot food, so it's about how aggressive you can be despite that
Oh, it's basically the attack stat
That's why I called it "madness"
We also have "charm" here
"Charm"?!
What does charm mean here?
What's that?
It's "the power to prevent our viewers from zapping"
Avoid having the audience change channel
Charm
The power to make the audience feel the urge to watch it again
It's how you leave a mark
It's also "the power to make the audience want to see it again"
I see
This is so hard!
Is that "charm"?
Some may think "then why aren't you all comedians?"
That's right
We're seven
He's here to tell 'em "don't underestimate me"
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Producer
That's why he's joining us?
He volunteered
What do you think of his exhausted look?
You can tell he went through a lot
That's a feature
In a way, I'd store this view in my hard-disk so I can
see him again and again...
Typesetted and QC'd by KEDOMAS
Translated by SHION
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com | twitter.com/FGRNDNoises
fb.com/shionnotsukai | ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
| patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
They'll show us their ultimate bare-handed madness
Get ready for the hellish bare-handed no-chopstick battle!
Typesetted and QC'd by KEDOMAS
Translated by SHION
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com | twitter.com/FGRNDNoises
fb.com/shionnotsukai | ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
| patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Eat scorching hot food within 90 seconds without using chopsticks
No-chopsticks battle:
rules
Welcome to the no-chopsticks food battle
Our challengers will try to eat just made hot food with bare hands
Charm
Finger
technique
Madness
Smartness
Speed
No-chopsticks battle:
The best performance will be rated by the following parameters
rules
The best performance is going to be rated by the other 7 contestants
Let's dive into it, here's our first dish:
Our first one
What is it gonna be?
What is it..?
Bare handed hell! No-chopsticks battle!!
Chuuka-don
Second dish
Third dish
Woah!
Holy shit, it's a chuuka-don
There will be a finger-bowl for each contestant to use
You can use the provided finger-bowl filled with water
Oh, so you can cool off?
It would be impossible without it, wouldn't it?
It depends on how much you're gonna rely on it, I don't think I will
Are you kidding me?
Really?
That would be incredible
Who's gonna go first?
Usually it's Endo
So how about this time you go first, Tanaka?
I see, should I go first?
Sure? You'll be in charge of setting the
overall course of action for this show
It's all up to you
That's right
Just bring it!
Alright, Tanaka
Yeah
Please go to the challenge room
Huzzah!
He flipped the excitement switch on
All the way up to 11
I'm gonna show y'all my madness!
Walking down the infernal road to prove his worth
Chuuka-don
Tanaka
Naoki
challenge dish
Show us your madness, Tanaka!
Let's try to call him: Tanaka?
Yeah?
In order to release my madness...
I don't feel like
using the finger bowl at all
Woah, already?!
Are you kidding us?
Of course you all know about this, but...
The food is really scorching hot and
you have nothing to pick it up with
I'm aware of that
But as you said before,
it's up to me to set the starting point
That's right
I'm gonna become a good ol' guidepost for ya
What the f-?
A guidepost?
That sucked
You can start as soon as the chef
places the bowl on the table
I'm ready!
Woah!
Are you serious?!
That's too hot!
They cook it right beside you?
This can't be real!
I guess it's gonna be hotter than at a normal chinese restaurant
It's boiling
Alright!
Chuuka isn't really easy
It's gonna be hard
Let's get ready for this
We're going
Tanaka's no-chopstick battle
Starts from now!
How is he gonna conquer those quail eggs?
Now the rice is hot too...
Oh, it started!
Here we go
I'm ready
Let's go!
Go for it!
Bon appetit!
Don't waste your time around
It's time to strike
Here I go
Just go
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on, dude
Don't hesitate
He won't do it
This won't go well
What the hell are you doin'?
What's that?
Time is running out, man
No way, no way, no way
This sucks so bad
He's not doing good at all
He sucks
He can't even touch it
Come on...
He didn't even take a single bite
You're doing really bad, man
We can't give points to this
Not good at all
What a filthy mess
No way, no way, I'm done, he's so weak
There's no smartness in him
Surely there's no charm in this
No charm, no speed, nothing
That much?
Now I'm scared of this
Look at all the rice flying around, this sucks
Oh my
He's barely doing anything
That was his worst one yet
You're running out of time
This guy is seriously the worst
Four
Three, two...
And it's over!
That sucked
That was bad, wasn't it?
The end
It couldn't have gone worse than this
Alright, let's vote
What a lady
Eh? Gimme a break...
What should we...?
Acting like a little girl
Maybe we expected too much from him
No doubt about it, his score is gonna be so low
I don't think anyone is going to praise him
Yeah, me too
Are you all done?
All done here
Alright, three, four and...
Here
Ok, let's flip this
Well, it figures
Really? So generous of them
Oh, I see...
Makes sense, yeah
Hamada's choice is a bit extreme
How about you, Hamada?
It's just a dot for me
A single dot, huh
But I guess it's not wrong
Yeah, it's something like this
Nothing to complain about it
What the hell were you doin'?
That's what we all thought of you
Nothing to be surprised about
What, did you expect something different?
Yeah, you shouldn't be surprised
We had high hopes for you
Let me say something, the thing I hated the most
Yeah
Is that you said no finger-bowl
but you tried to reach out to it once
For a second yeah, he did
As soon as I saw that I thought "hah!"
"That fucker did it!"
No doubt about it:
You should definitely use the finger bowl
Seriously, you have to use it
Would you have made it if you'd have used it?
No way
Eh? What do you mean?
Not even
Not even if I would have used it
Not even with it?
Yeah, it's impossible
Even with it?
Second dish
Bare handed hell! No-chopsticks battle!!
Chuuka-don
Third dish
Their second dish is going to be...
Grilled squid
"Grilled squid"...
I think this is way easier than chuuka-don
You think so?
Yeah
License? Are you ink?
Sure
I'm squiddin' ready
Just quit it with this bullshit, please
Let me do it!
Don't ever make puns again
I'm ready for the no-chopstick cuttle!
So lame...
His spirit is seething as if shrouded in flames
Fujiwara
Kazuhiro
Grilled squid
challenge dish
Blaze up, Fujiwara!
Fujiwara!
I can hear you
How about the finger bowl?
It's here, make sure to see how I use it
Oooh...
It's beside him
Yes
Alright, get ready
Yeah
Eh? Still cooking it?
What the hell?
Holy shit!
I didn't picture it to be like this
This is not okay
It's crazy
I underestimated it
It's boiling
Alright, let's see Fujiwara's no-chopstick battle!
I didn't think so
I wouldn't know how to handle this myself
What do you do?
How about that broth?
They're pouring it in!
It's even worse than chuuka-don
I bet he's so angry
This is not ok
It's so hard
He thought he could do this
I wonder if he can
Huh? What is he doing?
What's this for?
...Fujiwara?
Huh? What the--?
That wasn't funny at all
I'm sure it felt better inside his head
Not only didn't he make us laugh
What a waste
He also wasted all his water, what now?
Alright!!
He's not starting at all
Madness!
He went full madness on that
The madman!
He transformed
That was outstanding
Really
It's all starting from here now
He got no water left
Look! He's spreading it!
Right over his body
That's what he did
This guy is seriously amazing
Madman! Madman! Madman!
Look at him go
Incredible
He's striving like crazy
I can smell his madness
This guy is pure madness
Go! Finish up that last bit!
Eat up!
He gotta spread it
How exactly does this work?
He got no other choice
How can it benefit you?
Five seconds left
Four...
Three, two, one...
You're doing great, Fujiwara
That was incredible
Time's up!
He really did it, amazing
I'm speechless
Look, his personality changed
He's not the same as before
Scary!
Let's reveal our scores
It's close to full marks to me
I think that's good
Yeah, he did really good
I think it's ok
Both his madness and speed were outstanding
Thank you so much
No complaints here
Good job, really
You were incredible
Maybe it lacks "charm"...?
And look
It's so unexpected how Nakamura's score is so harsh
He could have been kinder
Are you kidding me?
He deserved more
He even volunteered
So strict, woah
So cool
I'm expecting a lot from the rest of us
Third dish
Chuuka-don
Fifth dish
Fourth dish
Grilled Squid
The third dish
Is combini spaghetti
Combini spaghetti
Fourth dish
Grilled Squid
I don't get it
It's time for his dormant wild nature to rise
Combini spaghetti
Endo
Shozo
challenge dish
Go for it, Endo!
It starts as soon as the spaghetti is fully
microwaved, just like in convenience stores
It's gonna swell with hot air
Yes, yes
C'mere, spaghetti!
It's a balloon
Look, it's a hot air balloon
Just look at it
Isn't that a bit too much...?
Yeah, probably
Three seconds left
This is dangerous
It really is
It's dangerous
Are you all ready for this?
Let's go
Here I go
Start!!
Is he gonna be ok?
He's going for it
The vinyl---
Go!
Release your madness!
Alright alright!
Use you madness!
Here it is
You're just scattering food around
Dig into it!
Aye aye
What the heck...
Come on!
You can tell he's burning his mouth
He lost it
Just grab 'em all
He's talking so much
But he's not eating at all
But he's really aggressive
Can't deny that
His madness is on point too
He's just making a show, that's all
Combini spaghetti
Fujiwara
Hamada
Inomoto
Matsumoto
Nakamura
Tanaka
Yamasaki
challenge dish
charm
finger
technique
madness
smartness
speed
He mostly pretended to eat, and because of that his score is low
Here's the next dish
Combini Spaghetti
Fifth dish
Fourth dish
Grilled Squid
Sixth dish
The fourth dish...
Is boil-in-bag hamburg steak
Boil-in-bag hamburg steak
Combini spaghetti
Fifth dish
This isn't an easy one
The challenger is our most ferocious man
Hamada
Masatoshi
boil-in-bag hamburg steak
challenge dish
Hamada, the mad dog!
Is it immersed? Oh, it is
It is
Woah...
This is gonna be hot
Yeah, he gotta pull that out from here too
Can he do it?
Alright, get ready
No-chopstick battle: begin!
Here we are
How can he...?
Come on
How is it possible?
Time is ticking away, man
Why are you dropping it?
Don't let it go
Take it out from there
Why dropping it?
Just grab it
Get it out quick
That hurts!
He got it out
It's so hot
It is
He's really making an effort
That should do
We're almost at 30 seconds
Come on
What a waste of time
You're wasting time, man!
He's still not done yet
It won't come out!
So fuckin' hot!!
That gap isn't enough
It's smaller than the hamburg steak
He opened a cut smaller than the hamburg itself
All right, moving on
Take a bite!
How is he supposed to eat that?
Yeah, how?
Just take a nice bite out of it
Oh, he's gonna use his fingers
He's trying to cut it
He became his own knife!
He's respecting manners
Just go for it
Go, go, go! Show us what you can do!
I bet it's hot as hell inside
You can do it
Show us what you got
Shit, that's really hot
He's taking so much damage from its insides
His technique isn't bad at all
This is freaking me out
Giving up now?!
He's done for
There's no time left! Only 15 seconds
This is freaky
I can't watch this anymore, why is he doing this?
Come on!
You're running out of time!
Just eat it
Time's--- man, he sucks
Come on, just go
He barely ate anything
And it's over
Such a pussy
Look, he's finally eating
Is it me or did he get thinner?
I'm done here
He looks pissed off
What's wrong?
Woah, he's pissed
He's mad 'cause he did awfully
First off...
That happens
First of all, it took you way too much time to open it up
Yep, a bit too much
You fucking try then
He kinda became Mori Shinichi for a sec
We'll do our own, we will
That cut was smaller than the whole thing, wasn't it?
The gap wasn't enough
It does happen sometimes
Combini spaghetti
boil-in-bag hamburg steak
fifth dish
seventh dish
sixth dish
Their fifth dish is... tanmen
Tanmen
boil-in-bag hamburg steak
sixth dish
It's tanmen
A though one
Definitely
The challenger is our most composed
yet passionate man: Inomoto!
Inomoto
Takafumi
Tanmen
challenge dish
Are you for real?
How can one possibly eat this?
Unbelievable
Isn't this a bit too much?
How many degrees is that?
It doesn't matter, just look at that
Too much...
Woah
So goddamn hot
How are you supposed to...?
This one's impossible
I mean, your hands...?
Hot!!
Fuck!!
You gotta praise his efforts
He's already trying his best
Look at him go
Holy shit!
Woah!!
Grab the noodles!
How can he put his fingers inside that?!
He's incredible
He's been trembling no stop
He's shaking like crazy
He really is
Amazing
Bravo, bravo!
Outstanding
He's really good at this
Awesome!!
Hot!
He's an expert
This is insane
You're doing great!
This guy is incredible
And he keeps on eating
That was incredible
Unbelievable
Thank you
But your right hand has been shaking the entire time
At one point...
I thought about using it
As a ladle to scoop up the broth and drink it
I see
But it's just impossible by nature
Of course it is
Don't say it, then
Here's our next dish
sixth dish
Tanmen
boil-in-bag hamburg steak
eight dish
seventh dish
Seafood paella
Tanmen
seventh dish
It's a paella
Seafood paella?!
Can I just
Can I have few words with my manager, please?
What the hell!
Why?!
Need his permission?
Why can't you do it?
I really can't, I just can't
But we all already did it
That's right
No point in wasting time here, how about you go, Yoshinobu?
Me?
Counting on you
And then only those two are left
That's right
Alright then, I'll go
He's really strict, he's gonna get mad at us
He kinda is
Let me prove you wrong, then
Really?
You heard him?
So cool!
Madman!
Whatever, you're not a comedian, who cares
We're not gonna put you on air
Come to think of it
He's the only one not getting his appearance fee
And yet he's so confident
After this, we'll see the overly confident no-fee man
Who's gonna show us the ultimate madness
He's the bare-handed master!
Have you seen his face?!
I've seen it...
Have you seen that?!
How couldn't we?
That's the face you make when you drink poison!
Enough of it
Gimme a break
We've seen enough, haven't we?
Let's call it a day, guys
Thanks for the meal
His miraculous madness shocked everyone
We'll get to see his performance soon!
But before that, Yamazaki the king of sloppy
eaters gets ready for his challenge
Boiled udon
Yamazaki
Housei
challenge dish
Are you ready?
Yama-chan's no-chopstick battle: start!
This isn't safe at all
He's dead
Woah...
Here it is
Look at all that vapor
The bowl is hot too
Come on
Come on, come on
Hoz!!
Did he mean "hot"?
Hoz!
That's all he's sayin'
Can't blame him
The way he shouts is always the same
He's not gonna make it
He hasn't touched a single udon yet
That's not the finger bowl!
Holy shi---- so hot!!
He just wants to get hurt
Wait a minute guys
Are you using that?
That's not it
That's broth
It's broth, not water
Wait--- gimme a sec--
The finger bowl is over there
This guy fucking sucks
That's not the right bowl
He might be the worst one yet
Wait--
Just grab one, soak it and eat it
That's against the rules!
That noodle you just ate was outside the pot
You can't eat that one
Well, it's gone now
That one cooled off, right?
Yeah
Sduck nma troh....
What?
I have an udon stuck in my throat
*cough* *cough*
He just coughed at you
Just a regular cough for you
Dude, you've been coughed at by Yoshinobu
Staking his pride as a man,
Matsumoto ventures to challenge UFO yakisoba
Matsumoto
Hitoshi
Yakisoba
challenge dish
I also want you to witness
The three minutes it takes for the hot water to cook it
I see
So you'll see I'm not cheating
Makes sense
Woah
I'm telling you guys, you shouldn't underestimate me
I'm not here to play around
Shit, that's hot
He already said it's hot
Running out of madness already?
Alright, cover it up, place it down and start the timer
Ok, ok
Let's have it rest for 3 minutes
That's how much it takes
Look, I'm even warming up the sauce so I can't possibly escape
Alright, alright
That's nice
Oh, I see...
See? Can you sense my madness?
The madness is starting to show up
In few seconds you can open it up
And start, three, two, one...
Let's begin: here's Matsumoto's no-chopsticks battle
The sauce fell down
He dropped it?
It's inside the boiling water!
Hey!
I'm gonna get burned
I didn't plan this!
No way!
And start, three, two, one...
Let's begin: here's Matsumoto's no-chopsticks battle
The sauce fell down
He dropped it?
It's inside the boiling water!
Hey!
I'm gonna get burned
I didn't plan this!
No way!
I didn't expect this!
He had no reason to get in this situation...
Look how scared he looks
He made the whole thing way harder
This is pathetic
He's a lady
Look at her!
He's not even using the finger bowl!
Does he even know he can use it?
It's hard to watch
What the hell is he doing?!
He hasn't done anything so far
All of this just for the sauce...
Hurry up and pick em up!
What are you doin'?!
Finally, finger bowl
Come on!
He used it way too much
All he's doing is saying "it's hot"
He dropped the pot!
Dude...
Where the hell did it go?
This is fucked up
Open up the sauce, quick
There's no time
Mix em up
Like this, go
Now you have to mix them
Eat it!
Hurry up and eat!
Mix them up, quick
What am I looking at...?
What is this?
You barely even touched 'em!
What was that for?
Mix 'em up, come on!
He spilled his finger bowl all over, look at him
Look at that finger bowl
Hurry up and mix it up!
Eat! Eat!
Please eat something
Quick!
Eat up!
Time's up!
Did he eat it?
Nope, he didn't
Well... how should I put it...
Everything I wanted to do has been
done by Nakamura before, so...
Everything?
What do you mean?
I wanted to do the exact same moves he did and stuff
Huh? What do you mean?
Seen how he gulped down his bowl?
Ultimate Way Of Eating Madness Revealed
coming up
I wanted to quickly change character like he did
But I ended up becoming gay instead
The time has come
Nakamura
Yoshinobu
Seafood paella
challenge dish
Here's Yoshinobu's performance,
a perfect example of madness
Holy crap
How are you supposed to eat this one?!
Are you kidding me?
This isn't humanly possible
It's impossible
How can a human being survive this?
Maybe the toppings?
But there's rice
Huh? Really?
You gotta be kidd---
Holy shit, he has a plan
No way!
Unbelievable!
He's gonna shove his face inside it
His heart is too strong for us
So cool
Here comes Yoshinobu's no-chopstick battle
I think the stuff on top of it is too hot to eat
Shellfish?
He went for that
He ate it
No way!
Is he fireproof?
Look at him!
Bare hands master!
My stomach hurts
Incredible
He's the MVP
Are you kidding me?
He's a monster!
Monster!
The monster appeared!
I'm dying
Gimme a break
My stomach hurts so bad
The shrimp!
He's peeling it
He's doing it
He's even peeling the shrimp
Even the shrimp?!
He did it and ate it!
He ate it!
Enough, please...
He's the maddest of all
His fingers too
His finger technique is great
Look, the shellfish
Look at his face
I want to see him go for the rice
There's still time for that
Go!
Really?!
For real?!
Man
He's scooping it up with both his hands!
I can't believe what I'm watching
Look at his face!!
He did it!
Outstanding
I can't
This is too much
Incredible, really
Incredible
My stomach...
Time's up!
I'm speechless
That was simply incredible
Have you seen his face?
I've seen it
Seen his face?
I'm glad I did
That's the face you make when you drink poison
That's the face you'd do if you got poisoned
Pure agony
It makes me wanna watch the whole thing again
I agree
I'm ready for a full rewatch
I really want to
Incredible, this guy is incredible
The given time wasn't enough
I think I'm gonna ask for his autograph later
One for me too, please
TYPESET BY KEDOMAS | TRANSLATION BY SHION
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
SPECIAL THANKS TO KEDOMAS FOR TYPESETTING THIS EPISODE!!
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FAN-TRANSLATION MADE BY A FAN FOR OTHER FANS. ALL COPYRIGHT ARE RESERVED TO THEIR RESPECTIVE OWNERS.
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES