Classroom Series
Murakami Shoji
It's time for Shoji Murakami's
Classroom Series, which always drops the ratings
And Girolamo hosted his own Ninja Classroom!
Shoji was left outside last episode
Last time, Girolamo took his place
as they decided it was time for Shoji to leave
Missed this episode? You can find it on shionnotsukai.wordpress.com:
Shoji Murakami’s Ninja Class ft. Girolamo Panzetta
Amico!
We thought he parted ways with this show, but...
"Thanks for everything" my ass!
They thought this was enough to cut ties with Shoji, but...
I'm not quitting this yet!
Tonight, the series resurrects after 1 year and 3 months!!
Tonight, his series resurrects after
a 1 year and 3 months hiatus!
Cocorico
Downtown
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Hosei
No one wants to do this, huh?   - I guess not
It's the wigs
I mean, I'm not the only one, right?  - We're in the same boat
I'm not really invested
We're not dressed like this 'cause we want to
That's right
But don't you think that "Feudal Lord Classroom" sucks?
Doesn't it feel like a parody? I mean,
We had "ninja" and lots of other stuff before
Can't we, like, meet him in Shimbashi, get his signature and cancel this shit?
Alright, alright...
Heading to the meeting spot
Even in this dire situation, Yamazaki
is trying to make us laugh with his erected topknot
Thanks for noticing
- "I thank thee", I'd say
So...
- There's a sign
It's the same as always...
- There it is
Gather here for the
Feudal Lord Classroom!
Is he here already?
Yeah, he's here
I can see him
I ended up seeing him
- I didn't mean to, but our eyes met
It's that shenanigan
I think I've seen it before
- I don't remember what it's called
The hell is this?
Oh! It's been a while, hasn't it?
Good morning
'Morning
Are you doing well?
Murakami Shoji
Murakami Shoji showed up early,
in spite of everyone's desire
You know, I'm just back from a Feudal Lord Meeting
Don't expect much from today's episode
Nothing relevant is going to happen.
T'was fun!
There were tons of Feudal Lords...
Yeah?
It was really fun, we ate a whole lot
Like, boiled ainame and stuff
T'was... t'was outrageously delicious!
I bet it was, huh
The fuck is wrong with you, Hamada?!
What have I done now?
What have you done? I'll tell you what!
- What the...
Don't you wanna become a Feudal Lord and eat good stuff?!
Of course I want to eat
Not sure about the Feudal Lord thing...
- Everything was delicious!
Isn't he shouting too much?
Yeah, even more than usual
I've caught a cold today, I don't have much voice
Huh? Really?
- And you're still so loud?
His volume doesn't reflect that
Anyway, today I'm really going to make you all
some fine Feudal Lords, I swear
All the other things we've done... I wouldn't recommend becoming any of those
But today you'll become Feudal Lords!
So goddamn loud
My eardrums hurt
- Just shut up
How about we play a little game?
- Oh, are we going to?
Tell me something a Feudal Lord would say
It's a sort of quiz show
I bet you know some words a Feudal Lord would use, huh?
I see
- Let me go first
Something a Feudal Lord would say! Hey, hey!
This pleases me!
Hey, hey!
That is indeed foul
Yeah, it works
- Nice! Hey, hey!
Come closer, would you?
- Oh, nice one
Hey, hey!
Disband!
Nice one!
Hey, hey!
You shall be beheaded!
- This works!
Hey, hey!
Heads high, don't succumb to pain!
What the hell are you... "Heads high"?
You're copying his "come closer" but... it's ok!
Ah, is it good?!
It's fine, yes
I've changed my mind, it's good!
You did? Thank you
Someone!
Hey, hey!
Was that... it?
- "Someone", you know...
I thought the game changed for a sec
You mean as "someone, help me"?
- That's right
Hey, hey!
And now, this issue is settled
That's a good one!
Hey, hey!
I order you to commit seppuku
Nice one!
Hey, hey!
Who art thou?
I like this one! Hey, hey!
Bring me a horse!
Nice! Hey, hey!
You shall be beheaded!
Nice one! Hey, he--
Huh? Didn't you just copy him?
He did
- He did
- He did it so nonchalantly
Did you notice?
FOLL
LOW
MY S
OCIALS
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SUP-
PORT /
DONA-
TIONS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
WEB
SITE
Let's start with something essential
to a Feudal Lord: a training for military arts
Feudal Lord Classroom - Lesson 1
Military Arts Training
First off, do you know what these are?
Don't expect much from today's episode
Nothing relevant is going to happen.
These over here
Targets?
Tsk
You're ok with that normal answer?
How about "is this a doll stand?"
Or "Is this for the Hina Matsuri?"
That's right, it's the five court-musician dolls!
Don't you need jokes like that at all?
Not really...
Of course you do!
Alright Yamazaki, who's this?
This is Saverio, right?
Yep, that's him
Are you ok with that answer?
Do you want to give up on this world?
I don't...
- Do you mean showbiz with that?
What are we...?
You're a feudal lord, aren't you?
Of course I am
I was asking about the other world (showbiz)
I thought he was talking about being a feudal lord
We have to become one, first
So, if you ask me what's crucial
when it comes to becoming a feudal lord...
I'd say it's horseback archery
Do feudal lords do that?
Of course they do, lots of daimyos used to
This gesture is strange too, right?
Why is he letting go?
Yamazaki...
- Yes, sorry.
Are you ok with that?
Here comes the tilted neck
You sure?
So, as our first training,
we'll learn how to perform horseback archery
Here!
Whoa... I've never done it before
You really like those things...
What is this?
It's a wheelbarrow
That's what I see
The hell are you saying?
And why are you speaking so softly?!
You said it
- I mean, that's it
I'm saying, you really like those, right?
I always see one of these around you
But you can't ride a horse, right?
- Right, right
We can't, actually
That's why we're relying on this
- I see, I'm sorry
You know what this is, right?
- Yep
Yamazaki?
It's a bow
You really gave up, didn't you?
How about answering "it's a fire tool used by cavemen" or such?
I'm sorry
Unbelievable...
Alright Tanaka, let's start from you!
Oh, sure!
You're brave, you can become a feudal lord
Oh, is that so?
- Amazing!
Come here, Hamada
- Thank you
Yes?
Have this
Sure...
- Place it around your neck
What should I do with it?
- Like this
Here
- Huh?
What is...
Like this
- Careful, ok?   - Sure
I'm coming from this way, get ready
What the hell are you doing there?!
What the hell am I supposed to...
Are you here to stop us from working or what?!
What should I do with these?!
- You gotta make some noise, like this!
Oh! I see!
Of course
- I see...    - That's the horse running, right?
Let's see how you do it
The sound is...
A horse is faster than that!
Do you want to...
You wanna screw this over or what?
This is something precious I've warmed up for ya!
Don't say it like that
He surely warmed it up for us
Come on, do it properly!
- Show me how
Like this!
- I see
Now you try
Here we go
- Good luck!
Good luck!
- Go for it, Tanaka!
What the hell?!
- Careful!
I'm not really good at this
- For crying out loud...
Just do it!
He's pretty good at it!
- That sounds nice!
Alright, let's go!
- He's good at it
Here I go
Oh no
- I'm sorry
Oh, is that so? I'm sorry
You gotta follow me, come on!
It's weird if the horse is over here
but the sound is over there, right?!
Next up, Yamazaki rides the horse
while Matsumoto is in charge of its sounds
Horseback archery
Matsumoto
Sound making
Yamazaki
Alright, let's go
Maybe he can strike two arrows before getting here?
You're right, he could do it
Good luck!
- Give it your best
Here we go. Say "go" when you're ready!
Can I?
- Yes
Go!
You're the one who should say "go", idiot!
Ouch!
It's your job!
- I guess he's right
He's scary...   - Really
- Sorry, I forgot to say it
Go!
- Go!
Oh, no! He lost an arrow!
This is scary! Stop! I'm scared!
Goddamn...
Wait a sec--- stop it!
- Watch out, it's dangerous!
I'm scared! I'm scared!
Stop it, please!
- Be brave! Man up!
This is so scary!
- Shoot it now!
Please! Stop!
You're no good
This is impossible
The sound was pretty crappy too
Hey
I had enough, I'm exhausted
- Sure
We don't have time to waste on this crap
Celebration Training
Feudal Lord Classroom - Lesson 2
A true Feudal Lord, must be able
to reduce the distance from his people
Don't expect much from today's episode
Nothing relevant is going to happen.
When there's some sort of battle
You can win or lose, but there's a big difference
When you win, it's the best feeling ever, right?
- Yes
So it's time to practice how to celebrate when you'll win
Do you know how to properly do it?
- Is there a proper way?
Well, it's a sort of ceremony itself, right?
Use the provided tools to liven up the celebrations!
They'll use the tools Lord Shoji provided them
To liven up the victory celebrations
Matsumoto's challenge!
Matsumoto will be the first challenger
Make sure to liven it up for good, ok?
Hoorayyyyy!!
- Oh yeah!
You're making fun of this, aren't you?
I'm not, I swear
Move away, geez
I knew I had to do this in the end
Show us how it's done
- I agree
That thing wasn't there before...
He got that thing for himself
Ah, you're right...
Thanks to all of you guys,
today we defeated our enemies!
You surely gave your best!
I'm so glad and happy I just can't---
That's how happy I am!
On August 28th, in the shopping district, a new pachinko parlor will open
Boss, use this to make some fried rice
What's wrong?
Huh?
Is everything ok?
Well...
We... we're fine
- Yes, we are
You're doing your best
Are you sure you---
I thought it was good
Even if you say so,
Are you sure you want to become Feudal Lords?
I'd like to try, if possible
I know, right?
- Yes
Alright, let's move on to our next train---
Ouch
Gimme a break
Coming up
Shoji will give them all a prize!!
A present from the Feudal Lord
Feudal Lord Classroom - Lesson 3
Feudal Lord Shoji will give a prize to the
5 men undergoing his harsh training
In the end we only move
Don't expect much from today's episode
Nothing relevant is going to happen.
If we're given money
Or material goods, am I right?
I know that's everything people ever want
I know that Tokugawa too
had a buried treasure, if you try to look for it
That's why
Today I'll have you search for the buried treasure of Murakami
Turn around for a sec
- Sure
You're doing it now?
- Don't look back!
Count to 10!
Alright, here we go
- Sure
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven, eight...
Nine, ten!
- Good! You're done
Now...
Where's the treasure?
Can we take as much as we want?
- Sure you can
Oh, here's another!
- I got it
Here's two
- There's a bunch over here
Hey, hey
What do you think your countdown was for?
Now that I think about it...
I toss them and you go like
"can we take as much as we want?"
This isn't the right answer!!
It's like eating a pizza soaked in water, who would eat it like that?!
Well, whatever
Eh?
- Whatever?
Whatever
Alright, Matsumoto
- Yes
I got number 2
- Oh! Wait a sec...
You did it!
- Huh? What?
Here
Terracotta figures?
But these aren't your regular figures
- Really?
Yep
- What are they?
President Osaki (from Yoshimoto) gav--- gave this to me 13 years ago
He told me they'd bring me luck
After 1-2 years since I received them
My job offers crumbled down faster than usual
Now they're yours
I don't think I...
- Whatever, let's move on
I've got number five
- Number five!
You picked a good one!
- Thank you
Here, Yama-chan...
So nostalgic!
Nostalgic, isn't it?
It was something, back in the days
- This used to be so popular
High-heel Momoko used to wear this a lot
High-heel Momoko
She said "bro! When you won't wear that thing anymore, give it to me!"
Is that how it went?
- I swear, she always said that
Also, this one...
I got this from president Kanai, from the steel mill
This is real, check it out
- What's with that pair?
It's a Versace!
That's right!
- This isn't cheap stuff
He told me "wear this when you'll visit Korea"
It doesn't feel like a real conversation
You can wear them together?
- That's correct
That's really nice
- Congratulations!
Your turn, Hama-chan
- I got number 10
Here
Hama-chan...
- Yes?
Watch this and learn again what comedy is
- What's that?
It's my DVD
Its title is "I did my best"
I was forced to personally sell 1200 copies of this
Oh my
I almost went bankrupt
"Personally"?
Next up, they'll learn the right
love techniques to conquer every girl
Feudal Lord Classroom - Lesson 4
Love techniques
It's crucial for a Feudal Lord
Don't expect much from today's episode
Nothing relevant is going to happen.
To have lots of children so you have more heirs
I see...
That's really important   - That's right
You need to know some techniques
Alright, I'll pretend to be a woman
Tanaka!
- Yes?
Come right here
- Sure
Come here and try to casually touch my nipples
Like, nonchalantly. I'm a woman, you know!
Does he really have to?
- I guess so
What is he singing?
You suck!
What's that song?
You really suck!
Sounded like a folk dance...
Yeah, kind of
You gotta go for it, quick and determined!
- I see, quicker
Determined?
- You're not good at all
Matsumoto, you try
- Sure
Alright
- Please
He's not going for it
Kind of...
He's attacking from the outside
Maybe that's where he's starting
That hurts!
Wasn't that good enough?
It hurts!
I'm sorry
Sit down
- Yes
Listen, you gotta do it nonchalantly
Pretend you're walking past behind her...
And then?
So, you're walking behind her...
The fuck are you doing?!
H-Hey, stop it
What the hell are you doing?
This has nothing to do with it!
- That's weird!    - Hey, Lord!
This has nothing to do with my nipples!
What are you doing?
Can you just go and aim down there?!
Why not?!
Of course you can!
Ah, I see...
When a lady gets... you know, in that mood...
That's how it ends!
And then
You're ready to take her to the bedroom
I see
You know?
You take her to the bedroom...
Yes...
What's that?
It's her kimono sash
Ah, I see
Makes sense
I'm going to...
I'm going to strip it all away from ya!
I can see all your embarrassing parts!
Wanna go home?
Should we go?
- Yeah...
Oh, he used it all
Excuse me!
Can I have another one?
Let's go home
Yep
W-Wait...
Oh, God!
I call upon thee!
Bang!
Don't you hear something?
I definitely heard something
What's that?
Is this still going on?
What?
What's that?
What's going on?
Wait, what's that?
Is it part of this bit?
Whaaaat?!
What's this?!
It's a Feudal Lord...
Eh? Is that a Feudal Lord too?
Nishioka Tokuma
What are you doing here?
Nishioka Tokuma's
Feudal Lord Classroom
"Classroom"?
What do you think?
Why don't you come to my class instead?
Oh, definitely!
By the way
Your teacher hasn't any approval to do so, right?
Have you?    - Really?
My Classroom has been approved by the shogunate!
Let's go to his Classroom, then!
- That sounds way better!
What do you think? Wanna join me?
- I think it's good, let's go!
Alright then, follow my lead
- Yes! Alright, let's go
- Good
- Thanks, you saved us!
- Thank you so much!
Come on, follow me
- So he's not a Feudal Lord...
Tokuma's got everything arranged
- Yeah
True, such a lifesaver!
You got involved in his schemes, didn't you?
I'm a Feudal Lord, and I'm feud up with all of this!
You got me? I'm a Feudal Lord!
What are you? A Feudal Frog?
I can hear him spitting puns
The hell is he talking about?
After the recording
That really surprised me!
I'm like--- what?!
Thanks for today!
I'm shocked!
- I bet you are
I thought I was going to be arrested again or something!
Ninja Classroom Prank
I was really scared!
You had no idea, right?
- I get you, you had no clue
That was frightening!
Coming up
Unseen talk footage from the Music Memory Drive!
Coming up, some unseen talk footage
from the Music Memory Drive episode!
This is a song we released in a CD back then when we started Downtown
It's time to reveal an unaired talk segment
Footage from last week's episode, "Music Memory Drive"
Unaired talk segment big reveal!
From last week's episode, "Music Memory Drive"!
Alright, my turn
- Sure
Is it ever gonna stop raining?
- I don't think so
That's why I'm picking a rainy-weather song
Oh, please do
Nice!
This is from when I joined Yoshimoto
And I had no job offers whatsoever
I see
I see...
I see!
(Matsumoto was 19)
Released: december 1982
♪ Hisame (cold rain) - Mika Hino
- I know this one
Ah, this song?
- I see...
Everyone knows this song
- This was really popular back then
Yeah, it was really famous
- Yeah...
Really...
This song...
Back then, me and Hamada worked part-time at "Petit"
"Petit"?
A snack shop, Tommy helped us making our way in it
You know, as a big guy from Yoshimoto
- I see
And so, we had this part-time job at Petit
♪ Let me stay here and drink some more...
So, this song was really popular
And there were no karaoke boxes at the time...
- Yeah...
♪ I don't want to go home, not tonight...
And I clearly remember this song,
all the old dudes were singing this
Right, everyone used to sing it
♪ You know who's waiting me inside that room?
But it's such a good song
- Yep
So, you know...
♪ That's right, there's no one in there...
Me and Hamada used to go back home from Nanba to Amagasaki by foot...
Whoa, that's long!   - That's a lot!
♪ Please, don't sing me that song...
That's what we did after our part-time job
I actually got a taxi fare from my mom
♪ Because it reminds me of that person I've lost...
But I didn't want to use it, so I told him "let's walk our way home"
How much is it from Nanba to Amagasaki?
♪ The more I drink, the more I want to cry...
It's pretty long, I'd say 10 kilometers...
- It takes a lot
- I think even more...
More than that, right?
- Maybe yes
♪ Please forgive me for who I am...
I'd say around 20 kilometers
- Around 20, right?
So, it was pretty cold outside...
♪ The winter rain outside still pours down...
And we were walking...
♪ It feels like it's leaking from my heart...
And this song was really popular, at that time
You two didn't drink alcohol, right?
♪ I have an umbrella, that's not the issue...
We didn't, actually
But sometimes they made us drink a bit during our part-time
- I see, you couldn't refuse
♪ It's just that I don't want to go home...
- Exactly
One time he gave us money and said "pay a taxi with this"
And so we went back home to Amagasaki by taxi...
♪ I want to stay here and drink until I'm drunk
You wanna talk about my trauma, huh?
What happened?
♪ So I'll forget about him...
They made us drink, and we got drunk really easily
I'm still traumatized by this
- So I was feeling a bit sick, you know?
- I see
By the time I opened the cab door
I puked and made a fuss
I just couldn't help it
- I know
The taxi driver stormed out of his cab
- That's right
Matsumoto stroked my back all night
- I see
I was feeling awful
- But the second time he puked...
He even let out a fart
Yeah, while puking!
But you know, just to be clear...
It doesn't feel good at all
- Yeah, I wasn't having fun
It's not a fun situation to be involved in
But even so, I saw him laughing like crazy
together with the taxi driver we didn't even know
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
Maybe that was for the best
- That must have sucked
- I was like "the hell are you laughing, you two?!"
I mean, given the situation...