Second time on Gaki no Tsukai Ya Arahende!
Let's play with table games from around the world!!
For the 2nd time
Yeah
Second round
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
At the end I'm glad we're doing this
The one I don't want to do anymore
Is Yoshimoto's New Comedy
Never again on that
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Come on, we had fun
Even the ratings for it were terribly bad
Really?   - Is that so?
Tsukitei Housei
Yes   - Oh
That's our second time
It is
This time too, Tanaka-kun will...
Tanaka is really good at explaining them
That's because I got there 1 hour before you
Tanaka understood and learned the rules beforehand from an expert
So I make sure to spend my time learning the rules
He's still feeling down about his divorce
It still hits him hard
By now it's been a year
One year?   - Has passed, yes
He's carrying the wound
I bet he's saying to his younger colleagues "I'll get over it in 3 years"
I'm saying I'm ok!   - His wounds are deep
Translation & Subtitles by Shion
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Let's play with table games from around the world~!!
Play with the game which caught your attention between
note: voice = same as black text
the selected ones from around the world!!
I was thinking that uhm...
Giving that Hamada is here with us
I think we can't really play the brainy ones
Easy ones?
He's a simpleton
Is he?
He is
Deja V첫 - Germany
Get the piece when the same picture appears twice!
The first game Tanaka chose
Is "Deja-v첫", from Germany
So, the first one is this
We'll start with the made-in-Germany game "Deja-v첫"
Yes
Deja-v첫
Long story short
Yes?
When you think the same picture appears for a second time
You have to take its illustration, It's a memory game
Ahh, that kind of game
Yes, as you can see there are several items here
For example, I flip the card and got this
Yes
You can see this one has a compass and a lipstick
Alright, I see
If these appear for a second time
For example if another lipstick appear, you grab its piece
Ok
New items appear one after the other
I see...
So you have to remember them
You see there's a duck here, right?
So if another one appears like this, you must take it
I see, I see, I see    - Alright
Got it
This is pretty hard
Whoever fails this will be banned from entering Nippon TV
Really?
Is it that serious?
As a bet?
Who takes the wrong one will be disqualified
If that happens, he can't play the next rounds anymore
He can't join?   - He's out
That's pretty harsh
Are you ok with the rules?    - Yes
It's kinda like Concentration
Shall we go then?   - Ok Tanaka
Alright
Suddenly three items
Endo-san
Ok
Here I go, they may appear right now
W-wait I'm already...
What the hell? I have no idea
- They're all different
And this one
Did they really appear before?
This one I'm sure...    - Yeah it did
We can't look at them now, right?
At the moment
We can't, we can look at them later
We can't?
We can't look at them now!?
So we can check if we got them right later...
Been drawn a second time
If the lipstick hasn't
The lipstick is somewhere in the deck
Then it means
That's right
Is drawn again from the deck
So if the lipstick
You already took it, so you're disqualified
I see
You took this thinking it appeared twice?
Yeah, it did
Ok, so we'll know it later    - Yes, later
What!? For real!?
note: the kanji over the boxes are their names. Just keep the usual colors in mind: Housei, Matsumoto, Hamada, Endo, Tanaka
Housei-san   - Flip it
These are new
Stack them up properly    - Ok
I'm 100% sure on this
This is new
Maybe you should stand up
This one is reappearing
Alright
That was it
Or maybe I'm wrong
You have no idea yourself?
We don't know if that came out or not
That's right
Huh?
Who took it first?    - Yama-chan
He's fast
Lipstick
The lipstick!    - Alright!
See? The lipstick hasn't been drawn before
Yes, this is its debut
You're out
Alright!
Even though I got that many?!    - Yeah
Housei: Disqualified
You're out
Nippon TV isn't enough, you're banned from Kojimachi now
note: Nippon TV headquarters used to be in Kojimachi until 2004
The area is widening!
The area suddenly got wider
It didn't appear before!
Yeah it didn't
You know why I took it?
'Cause I've memorized it when you were explaining the game!
You know what pisses me off?
This guy who mistook the lipstick
Got in my way so many friggin' times!
If he wasn't here!
He got them from you?
If he wasn't even born in this world!
I could have got tons of those!!
I think you're taking it too far
If only his parent weren't born!
Come on, man
It would have been better not to meet him at all !!
You're exaggerating
Such an asshole
Anyway, he's out and can't take part in it anymore
At this point I don't remember anything
Yeah me neither...
Let's try to move on a bit
This was took    - This too
This too   - He took the axe too
He's really getting in our way!!
Even though only one was drawn
That can't be!
He just took a non-existing lipstick
And made sure to always get in our friggin' way!
He's right, he's right
I bet if he didn't do rakugo at all
Everyone would enjoy rakugo so much!
Are you for real?
He's the root of all evil
Really? Really!?
Why?
Line them up good
Alright, I'm going
This...
Oh, right
No doubts, right?
I think so
This--- ah!
This one too!
Oh that one    - Could be...
Was it so?
Huh?   - Wha-?
Woah! That's embarrassing!
The root of evil showed up!
What the hell!
This was at the very beginning!
You're wrong
We got this first, right?!
No, it's here    - It can't be, there are two here
Matsumoto: Disqualified
That's right
This   - That one
Keep in mind there are two of them
That's cause I have one of these at home
There he goes
Come on, Tanaka
There are way too many by now
These are all new
Geez...   - Three?   - Yes, there are three of us
That's how it's going
Looks like it
Only those who tried have lost
You're right, you're right
Only the idiots are left
That's true!
Idiot leftovers!
That's a bit---
Shut your trap!!
Can you please be silent?
Can you please shut up?
The dumbest ones have it best    - We can't concentrate
Right, right
This is reappearing
Are you sure?!
This one too
You didn't take a single one
You sure?
Hamada-san didn't take any
That one    - This
No way!    - This one for sure
This one too, right?
For real?
I remember it...
Wha-?    - It's there!
The guitar too!
Talking about getting in the way!
Matsumoto-san surely did get in our way
This one was there, it was, it was
We all
We all suck at this
We're all screwing this up
It won't last long
Banana
This one too
Hamada-san is not taking anything
Hamada?
I'm afraid he'll...
If Hamada-san wins this game is a fraud
Yeah it would suck so bad
The guy who did nothing would win
Oh, this one--!
It was there
That's right, ok, Endo
Endo disqualified!
Alright! It's me and Hamada-san
Alright
This--- Wait a moment
This--
Why is this guy a victory candidate, huh!?
He didn't do anything at all !!
What the hell!
He managed to get to the last round
That's messed up!
All he did was flippin' cards!
I've been waiting
At least I didn't get wrong ones
Is that the type of country Germany is?
Wasn't it supposed to be a more aggressive country...?
You rushed too much!
If you don't take your time you may be out
So it's ok to wait according to rules
Is that so?
Ok, here I go
Here
That one
I already saw this, yes
The key... oh right
See?
This too
Yeah, it was there
Sure?
There are no words for this
That one is reappearing, I remember it
Hamada-san?
Hamada-san are you
ok empty-handed?
Hamada-san?
What's wrong?
I think that one's wrong
Are you ok?
There aren't many cards left
The cards are going to finish soon
I already saw this!
I think so too
He finally got his first one
The mask, yes
Is it reappearing?     - It is
Last one
This too    - That too?
So
They all came out, only three cards are left
With the 3 remaning cards they'll check if they make mistakes
We'll verify our guesses now
That's why you left these three?    - Yes
Oh
So you check them?    - We'll check them
You're screwed if (the pieces you took) are on these 3 cards
That's right
Tanaka's position is more unfavorable    - Right
I'm still on it
You took a load of them
Yeah but I'm probably sure about them
A hat...    - These are the 3 cards
Huh?
Tanaka...      - Huh?
The glasses    - Glasses
The glasses...
They didn't appear before    - Yeah...
This one too
The clock too
The clock
So it means that...?
Who won?
Hamada-san
Hamada Wins
What the hell is this?
Yeah what the hell?
This wasn't fun at all
The person who didn't take part in just won !!
But in the end the few I took match, so...
What the hell!
I took it slow
Everyone got at least two pieces!
The guy who did nothing was the winner after all
Quickly line up the cups and let the bell ring!!
Speed Cups - Germany
The next game Tanaka chose
Is "Speed Cups", from Germany
Ok, this one's called "Speed Cups"
This too is from Germany
Germany  - Speed Cup
Line up your cups in the color order the card is showing
The fastest to do it and ring the bell, wins
The rules are extremely simple
Quickly line up your cups as displayed on the card
The first one to do so and ring the bell, wins!
I ha
ga
is
me
te th
My lower back hurts too
I can't
Let's do it, let's do it
He's surrounded
Come on
This is really something
Seriously, look
Even my finger is a bit cut and hurts
We're doing this
You can't run
I finally took that hangnail off
These are third grader excuses
Come on I just took it off
Here we go
Nope nope nope
Alright alright alright
Hamada-san did it
Thanks
Ok, they match!
Good good
He didn't stack em up
Isn't this awful?
Huh? Why?
I can't see it (the card)
If you couldn't see it
You wouldn't line em up this way
You got the right
order 'cause you could see it
He's right!
Are you ready?
Geez     - Ok
Here goes
How frustrating
Here
For real!
Who was it?
Hamada-san
Hamada-san?
Hamada-san is so fast!!
What's going on?
What's with this sudden ability?
I have no idea what you're talking about
This is hard, I don't think I can win
We're going!
Yeah me neither...
Woah Hamada-san!
He's friggin' fast, what is him?!
Just what is him?!     - Hamada-san is amazing!
So accurate too
He is
Yes...
This ability?
What is this now?
Since when do you have it, Hamada-san?
I think you
Have you considered taking part in Inter-High?
note: Inter-High School Championships is an annual sports competition for highschoolers
Inter-High in Speed Cups...
Which Inter-High?!
Why don't you take part in a world tournament?
Speed Cups?
A Speed Cups game?
Seriously, he's freaking fast
He's so fast, I wonder how
He's something
His head is emptied of worldly thoughts
What the hell!
I wanna try to win at least one time
Here we go
Here    - Gotta try
Oh, this is-
I can do this
Watch out!
What happened?
I was thrusted away !!
I got thrusted away!
Just when I thought I've pressed it
That was scary    - Yeah
He used his                  !!
muscles
You can't use your                   for that!!
Let's have it played in slow motion
Hamada-san is on a rampage      - It was Hamada
Yes, last one was Hamada-san's
What!?
This is our last one
Alright
Let's go
The hell is this?
So fast!
He got it right
So quick!
Hamada-san got this one right too
This is really ridiculous
Amazing!
5 points
So fast...
Hamada Wins
What was that?
His abilty...
He destroyed us
Must be some power
Between the 5 of us he's the idiot number one for sure
His score
Was so pure!!
He was so dedicate to it
Coming up
Hamada's serious struggle with a rhythm game!?
We'll see Hamada's struggle with a rhythm game!
Strike a pose while following the rhythm!!
We Will Rock You - France
The next table game Tanaka chose
Is "We Will Rock You" from France!
First of all I'll give a random card for each one of you
So, this is mine
This is Endo's
Hamada-san
Matsumoto-san
The pose drawn in the card will
Become your own personal pose!!
I see
So Endo-san will go like this
Hamada-san this-- So, these have become
Your poses    - Ok
With them...
Giving that the game is called "We Will Rock You"
You know
Using the rhythm from Queen's "We Will Rock You"
Exactly
Like this, let's start from me
On your turn you go like that
Then you strike your pose and choose one of another player
For example, if I happen to choose Housei's pose
First of all
I strike my pose
And then his
So, because I chose Housei-san's pose as my second one
Now it's Housei-san's turn to strike two poses
Then, first of all
He must do his own pose first
And again, he randomly selects his second pose
Oh, got it
I see, I see, I see
So...     - Let's try
Are we trying this?
We'll start from me
Alright
Here I go      - Go
What the hell
Endo-san
Goin' for eternity!!
Come on dude
This is har--- huh?     - Endo-san
Was I pointed at?    - No no no
Your pose...      - He did this
The fact I did your pose meant you've been chosen
He chose your pose
So it's your turn to strike it
Oh, is that how it is?
So he should have done his own first?     - Yes
You have to do your own first     - My own, ok
The second one is up to you
Before choosing the other, right?
So you always have to strike your own pose
Right     - Yes
Ok, I'm going      - Ok
Get ready
One, two...
Hamada-san !!
Hamada-san?
Was it me?
He can't keep up with this at all !!
I'm not following
You weren't looking at me, Hamada-san?
He wasn't looking
After I did this
I did yours
There's a chance your own pose is coming as the 2nd one
Hamada hasn't looked at me at all, that's why
He looked away
I was focusing on the others     - Oh I see
This is hard
We have to stay focused     - Yes
Also
He went full cat pose while looking towards my direction
While smiling
(The rhythm was) maybe too fast
(staff)
Let's try to do it considerably slower than this
Let's take it slowly
Yes please      - It was too fast
Let's take it easy
I mean what do you think is the average age in here?
Housei-san
Come on, Yama-chan     - Can I?
Ok
That thing you're doing is bothering me
Seriously I can't withstand it
He keeps on bouncing it to me! This shouldn't be allowed!
Right but
Unrelated to that, you kept on raising your hands so annoyingly
He's right
That's not it
I think this guy is totally throwing down the gauntlet at me
In a one-to-one
Yes, it's a duel
They will change all their current cards and face a new challenge!
note: voice = same as text
I see     - What's this?      - This one's hard!
Ok, Endo      - I'm going
No no no
You're one beat off!!
He's completely off!
You're tempo is really slow!!
Yeah, the way he gets into it
He reflects before posing
I have no idea what to do next
I don't know where should I pass my baton!!
Man this is freaky
It's making my heart race
It's a really fun game
Don't say I'm slow!
note: voice = same as text
Coming up: Matsumoto's unexpected talent!?
Dancing Egg - Germany
Let's grip the eggs with every part of the body!!
The next table game
Is "Dancing Egg", from Germany!
This is a game called "Dancing Egg"     - Ok
Here
There are lots of eggs as you can see
You roll the dice and do what the face you got indicates you to
Then you have to hold the eggs with the displayed body part
There are these two types of dice, a red one and a white one
You throw the red one first
You can see there are various images on it
Those are various directions
The person who takes the egg, must throw the white dice
For example, in this case
You use your thighs
You follow the directions which tells you to hold it in various ways
The eggs you're holding gradually becomes more and more
Doesn't it become difficult for the one who takes them?
It does
But getting the eggs is the point of this game
So by doing so you're stacking up points
It surely becomes difficult
But in the end the one who stacks up
More eggs without making them fall, wins
"Cock-a-doodle-doo"
Any noise
As fast as possible
Catch it as it falls
Drop the egg and
Grab the dice
No one must make
Run around the table
The dice gets the egg
The one who threw
On the red dice, the one you throw first
There are lots of directions, such as running around the table
Or shouting "cock-a-doodle-doo"
The one who clears it first
Gets the right to acquire one egg!
Question, sorry      - Yes?
Drop the egg and catch it
What's that "drop the egg" about?
The one who gets it
Takes the egg and
Lets it fall down like this
We encircle it and the first one to get it as it bounces, wins it
So we're acting as if we want to insert them on us
Right, right, right
"Insert them on us"?
So we're holding them between our body parts?
Yeah you hold them
And the point is how long you can keep them
Alright
If you're ready, let's start
We have to drop one egg
Drop the egg and catch it
Ok let's do it, I'll drop it here
You have to catch it, here goes
Ok, I took it
What the hell
You're playing alone
You're doing everything by yourself
What is this?
So now you roll the white one?
Yeah this
To know where to place it, right?
It's an armpit
This can get in your next movements' way
Armpit
Ok, I got this
Endo's turn     - Alright
Run around the table
Around!
Of course he took it!!
It's not like we can run any faster
It's right this way
Yama-chan could have take it easily
Alright alright alright
Do I have to roll it?      - Yes please
I got uhh...
Chin
Woah!
This suddenly became bothersome
This is tough     - It is
Make a chicken noise
COCK-A-DOODLE-DOO!
I think Matsumoto-san was the fastest
Good
Take that
Anywhere = OK
Oh, you can place it anywhere you want
What?
You're plotting against yourself
I think that
I can keep a better balance this way
Oh, I see it makes sense this way
Still looks cornered to me
Make a chicken noise
COCK-A-DOODLE-DOO!
Ok, Matsumoto-san
This is so strange
Arm
Arm?
Like this?      - Yes
Ok
Yama-chan      - Ok
Drop the egg and catch it
Oh, this one again
That was so good
He's really good at this game
He is
Again?
It's the chin
Chin
The chin again?
He's so good at this, his chin again
He's doing great
Impressive
He's holding so many eggs!
He already got four of them!
Drop the egg and catch it
Yama-chan     - This one again
So good!
That's impressive
He's killing it!    - Amazing!
You gotta see where to place it
Arm
The other one
He's holding so many eggs!
Run around the table
We gotta run!
Here Matsumoto-san
Matsumoto-san is so good
Incredible
Anywhere = OK
Anywhere's fine     - Anywhere again!
The armpit!
Only one left
I'm throwing it
Run around the table
We gotta run!
Let's run!
Hurry up
Let's take it
Come on
Ok he took it
Now throw this
Armpit
Where is this?
He's so strong
Who won?      - The winner is...
Who is it?      - It's Matsumoto-san
Matsumoto Wins
His victory was overwhelming
I haven't had fun at all !!
I'm never playing this again !!
He tossed it away
A shocking electric game full of tension!!
Coming up
Is a shocking game full of suspense!
Alright
I've mentioned this before
If your reaction is slow, you'll get an electric shock!!
Lightning Reaction Reloaded - U.S.A.
Do we really have to do this?
I don't want to      - Me neither, I don't want this
This was the electric thingy, right?
This too is from U.S.A.
Reflexes, right?
Yeah, it's about reflexes
Music will start playing
Each one of you has to hold a handle
And as soon as the music stops
On your own handle
You have to press the button
The slowest one to press it will be electrocuted
Ok, I got it
Each of you grab one
This...
Is only for 4 people, right?
Four people, yes
You're not doing this, Tanaka?
I'm not doing this
If I press it before?
You get electrocuted even if you press it before the music stops
Got it
Ok so
I'm going to press the button and let the music start
So as soon as it stops
This is like a Batsu Game
Be ready to press the button as fast as you can!
Alright
Here goes
THAT HURT!!
Translation & Subtitles by Shion
You just...
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
You just scared the shit out of me!
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
This hurts so bad!
This is incredibly terrifying
It hurts a lot!
What the hell!
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Sorry but
One more time please
Wha-?       - Come on...
Come on, we're done Endo
Want to support my translations? Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Then let's have a deciding round with Endo and Hamada alone
Why should we!?
What do we "decide" with it?!
'Cause he just shouted when Endo got hit
I didn't shout!
What are we deciding?
He did      - It's pointless
We already got our scores
Let's have you dual-wield them, lik- AAAAH!
There was still something left on that!
Two....      - They were still charged
He took two of them and shouted like crazy!
Matsumoto's rage on Housei's scheme!?
Next week on the second half of Table Games from Around the World - Second Round
Second part coming soon on www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Stay updated on future updates' status on www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai