Tonight's Gaki No Tsukai, a revival of the Classroom series after 8 years,
In Murakami's place, a new teacher will conduct the lesson
and also,
Suda Masaki will take part!
To leave with a smile, that's it
Ahh this is the worst
It's so hot
Is this, that thing?
Cookie, will be leading the classroom,
Up until now,
we've had so many
What classroom, well we can already guess
Cookie's Woman Diver (Ama-san) Classroom
I won't say it though
Shoji-san isn't doing the classroom anymore?
It does feel like Cookie stole this idea
Well he stole it, and also Shoji-san passed away,
No, no he's still alive
Shoji-san is dead right?
No he's still around
He's rotaing his shoulders like crazy
There's no ocean here at all
It's a mountain
It is a mountain
Found him
He's so high up
Who?
Ama-san Classroom
C'mere!
Why the hell's he so far away for?
Over there would've been fine!
Where?
You should be over there!
Right?
Come here!
Why is he there
YOU come here!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
He's so angry
We couldn't hear that!
Come to the marked spot!
I'm telling you, we can't really hear you
The marked spot?
Marked spot?
It's somewhere here
OK, well done
Who the hell's that?
He's back. He always tags along.
A great morning today,
Everyone ... Thank you for coming,
Why is he laughing
He's like a Chief Executive in SHOCKER
TN: SHOCKER is a fictional evil organisation from Kamen Rider
He really is
There's no ocean here
We're in the mountains
And I never said I wanted to be a woman diver!
There's no sea?
There's no sea!
Ji Ji Ji!
That's so Ji Ji Ji bro!
I'm gonna come down now, wait for me
I'm gonna smack each one of you
Why? Why why?
That's scary man
Emotional Unstability
And he has to come down at the end
Exactly
There, there right?
So slow!
That's a grandfather's pace
Cause it's steep
What the hell
So very cautious
Good work
Today's class will be led by Cookie,
and the old man from the Fishing Association, Adachi
Excuse me, this is a diving class right?
Yeah women diver
Why those clothes?
In my class, the Ama-san don't wear such old clothes
This is a wetsuit
But this is a ZOZO-suit, not a wetsuit!
It's making me laugh
You made a mistake?
I made a mistake
Hey Macchan, can I go on Suberanai Hanashi with this story?
No way idiot!
It'll all be cut!
All cut?
The only unfunny story?
Why? Right Hosei-chan?
It's hot, and hard to hear!
Yeah this is annoying
Oh really? Sorry
Alright then, I'll lend you this,
It's just right,
Probably something useless
I went to Sakata Toshio's house for a shoot, and he gave me this
Sakata Toshio's hat
That definitely is his real hat
He would buy that
It's really his
That's real!
It's the real thing
You stole it?
He gave it to me
"You're fashionable, so have this"
Who the hell would wear this
This weird fabric
Take care of that please
Can you wear it? I'm embarassed
Hama-chan, put this on
Why do I gotta wear it?
It'll look good on you I think
You...
It's cute
It's Sakata's right?
TN: Sakata Toshio is a very senior and respected comedian
Hamada is referring to him without any honorifics
Sakata? It's Sakata-shishou
Put his hat on please
Put it on
Why are you smelling it?
You would smell it too
"would smell it too"
So lame
The Shishou's hat is so small
Yeah he has a small head
SO lame
It's fashionable
And somehow, everyone,
Some good news,
There's a part 2 of this episode
2 weeks of this?
Eh? Really?
No way
However, you guys aren't entertaining enough for 2 episodes,
Too weak
You're really saying that
You don't have the charisma,
But we have some quality charisma available to us,
Really?
There is 1 extra person joining,
Let's show them all a refreshed, brand new Gaki No Tsukai!
Why do you care for Gaki No Tsukai?
Of course I'm caring for it, look at us here now
You just happen to be doing an episode
You say that but I'm doing a lot!
On that, No Laughing special,
You guys didn't call me back on!
It's so hilarious
Cookie's specialty is short explosive skits,
There is a worry he can't sustain 2 episodes
I'm gonna call in the new guy, okay?
It's a real guy right?
Why is he calling him like that?
If he's in the same clothes as us he might not hear
He's here, he's here
Oh he's here
Same clothes
Seriously?
I look forward to working with you
For real?
Why did you come for this ocassion?
This ocassion is no good
There will be no happy ending
There will be at least 3 misfortunes
Bringing charisma to the Ama-san class  -  Suda Masaki's unexpected appearance
I'm not really sure,
I'm not aware of the plan
I'll just have to go along with them
Suda-kun?
I heard I can promote myself here
Konto Ga Hajimaru
Promote your show?
I'm not at all surprised
See, exactly
Is it related to Ama-san?
It's unrelated
Cut it out then, let's stop this
Why women divers?
This is Murakami Shoji-san's thing right?
You know about that
It's the Classroom Series
Then I'm not looking forward to this
Yeah this series sucks
We have to make 2 episodes using your charisma
Eh? My charimsa?
Exactly
These comedians are too old
And this guy can't be managed by Yoshimoto
Unmanage-Yoshimoto can't manage him?
Yes
He's a pain in the ass
Before the training, they will recieve items that woman divers need
First, clearly you need ear plugs
A woman diver definitely needs these
Oh really?
Then, Endo,
OK, Oh, I have to get it?
No shit, am I supposed to go there?
I thought you might-
The teacher coming to you?
Oh I'm sorry
You, listen, you
OK OK sorry, I'm sorry
Why woul-
Enough, enough, that's too much
Now I can see, you have so many wrinkles
We don't get any?
Everyone, everyone gets one
Thank you
Next, uhhh, Tanaka
Why's he the second batter?
A Sukeban Yo-Yo
Sukeban Yo-Yo...
Is it related to woman divers?
Of course it is!
When you run out of oxygen, suck in from this crevice
The crevice...
Oh, it's started
The unfunny streak has started
It's your fault!
Look closely, after his joke bombed, his face turned red
It's red! It's turning red!
Oh! It's turning red!
No it isn't
It's not
When you bomb it's a signal
Someone of your class can't bully me!
Why does that matter?
I can bully you
So next, uhhh, Matsumoto
What is it?
White glasses, they're Fu-kun's glasses
Why do I gotta look like Fu-kun from when he divorced Tsuchiya Kaori
From when he was in that thing
TN: I can't make out what Yama-chan said
Oh yeah, from that thing
I'm fine like this?
Yeah you're fine .You're wearing that for the rest of the day
Rest of the day
I didn't get anything that special
Umm, Suda,
Suda, you, you take, take this
You're so stylish, those clothes are a pity. This should be good.
The hell's that?
That's too warm
I have to wear this on top of everything?
It's Fu-kun's aloha shirt
Fu-kun's back
Fu-kun again
Give that to me then,
Finish my outfit then
As a set
So hot
Yeah it's too hot
So Hamada,
Hamada already got something
Hamada, come here
He already has something
Hamada, here,
There's something else
Really?
Hamada already got the hat
The hat is just for fun,
Should we stay here?
YEAH DAS FINE
Why that tone?
Why's he taking Hamada by himself
Why do I have to go so far? Just leave it
Do it someone else, why me?
Is it always like this?
Well, yeah. Speaking of always...
A weird atmosphere
We just have to leave it to him
What is this?
Sidecar, a sidecar
It's only the side car
What's the point of just the sidecar
It won't move
Great, aint it?
This part looks like a rocket
Put your legs in
Great yeah
You're filming from here today, okay?
The whole time, you there,
Wait, wait, I'll come back
I said you're staying there
Hamada should just sit in the side car!
You chimapnzee  bastard!
He's talking so much shit
The hell are you doing?!
He's so angry, he's talking so much shit
Hamada is,
You guys find Hamada annoying right?
No we don't
I got him stuck in the sidecar
That's not right,
Can't Hamada-san be with us?
San? Hamda-san? What do you mean -san?
Is that guy important?
He's our senpai
More than Macchan?
The same, the same position in the industry
He's very important then
Yeah it's not good. Hurry u-
He didn't know who he is?
The way he runs!
What's with that running?
He has to do something each time
He doesn't watch much TV maybe
Yeah
Hamada from DownTown
I thought you were a super low rank person. Sorry!
Eh? What?
Why should I be a low rank person?
Good, good, good
He deserved that much
I wish he hit harder
Exactly
A good one now
Can't be helped
You're a pain in the ass!
Just do the class!
He said "I thought you were a super low rank person"
It seems he didn't know
Somehow, it seems he didn't know you
His clothes are so dirty
So dirty now
I think that's enough for one episode
Hell no!
Not yet
Not at all
Don't underestimate Terrestial Broadcasting!
I wanna finish this soon
I want to finish this soon, actually
"Finish this soon, actually"
My chest hurts a bit
Can't be helped
Was Igor Vovchanchyn here?
You kicked me like Igor Vovchanchyn
Let's continue the training,
When you enter the sea,
The scariest thing in there, is fish, right?
Fish?
And the scariest one of all, is Tuna
Tuna?
You aren't aware of a Tuna's ferociousness
But why would tuna attack an Ama-san?
There's tuna that seeks out Ama
Don't say "Ama" like it's Amagasaki
TN: Amagasaki is DownTown's hometown
Oh, Ama, uh, Amagasaki, huh
What the hell!
What happened?
Get a grip, Teacher
This guy is our teacher?
He's really terrible today huh?
Also, that guy, Suda-kun's manager, didn't laugh at all
Pay attention to them sometimes
You have to look over sometimes
Not laughing, at all
Oh! Long time no see!
You know him?!
Liar
You were the guy in that Roppongi club,
holding your Zima going like this
Stop it,
Cut it out
Don't involve him
He's got a great manager
This guy is messed up
I didn't want to picture that
Back to training, time to fight Tuna
I'll be the guinea pig, you guys come at me like a Tuna
Really?
What is it?
I thought I could film your faces as you hit me
I don't like that somehow
It's unwanted
He's like some college student
It's unnecessary
I don't want that to go viral
Matsumoto,
Matsumoto-san, if you will,
How hard should I hit?
Yeah
How hard?
However hard a Tuna hits, according to you
Oh yeah like that, yeah
Ah, no good, no good
That shit, your footwork is no good for a Tuna
Why?
Why? Uhh, yeah, umm,
Like how a Kei-Truck, in a small-
If you can't say it clearly then who cares
He was just mumbling
I ended too early?
You didn't end it properly
Then, next, Hama-chan you go
Harder than before is better right?
Yup, harder
Looks the same as the last one to me
It's something like that
Absolute rubbish
That was like, you know, ...
Uhh,
Just forget it
Like Concorde,
Concorde?
It's like, when Concorde has its nose down while taxiing,
and the tip slightly grazes you
That won't hit you
So weak
Next, Suda takes the challenge
I think I gotta hit harder
Harder would be better
I got it, Teacher, let's do this
Suda, for you,
So cute
High Heel's Ringo (Apple) Dakimakura
Why?
Yoshimoto is really taking the piss recently
Yup,
This is the Ama, you are the Tuna
We can do it the other way around too
This can be the Tuna
It's better for Suda-kun to hit
Harder than last time right?
Of course
Amazing
Is that what Tuna is like?
Ringo was embraced
Don't be an Orca!
That was an Orca
You said to hit hard
So let's move on, to defeating the Tuna underwater
What do you mean
Underwater?
Underwater fight training
Next, fighting the real Tuna
I'll be the Tuna
Macchan, let's do this
This thing, watch out it's a knife
It's supposed to be real now
We fight using this?
In real life, imagine this is a giant blue dragon
Then prepare that,
I think killing a dragon with this will be too difficult
Think of it as the real thing
Sorry, there were budget concerns
The hell does that mean
Matsumoto fight - Cookie-sensei's plan?
Try to stab the Tuna
Try to defeat the Tuna
What is this...
This guy is annoying. I seriously want to hit him once this is over.
Be our guest,
When my face changes, the battle starts
Oh, it changed
It did indeed
Here he go-
Not yet, not yet
Cookie in the flesh, trying to find the best moment
It changed though
It did look like it changed
Taking so long, seriously
Step back please,
STEP BACK!
STEP BACK CAMERA!
GET BACK, CAMERA!
Did it change yet?
It did look like it changed just now
Oh! It changed, it changed!
It hasn't changed yet, ok?
Still?
IT CHANGED NOW!
So easy, I'm dodging
Dodging so much, super easy
Totally, totally dodging you
Totally dodging you
This is the best moment?
This is hell
Hell indeed
Messing with Macchan like this is no joke!
Oh no
He's Yoshimoto's treasure
He's Yoshimoto's treasure!
Exactly!
I have no idea what to do
Cookie-sensei chooses Hosei next
This is the scary part. Normally it would be over with that.
Yama-chan, this is gonna be hell
I'm motivated to do this
Really?
This thing, this way is-
It's like,
Like Jackie
Cookie-sensei told us to add Kung-Fu sounds here
How is this gonna end?
What the hell is this?!
Who would laugh at this?!
I'm not laughing,
or you!
Nobody's laughing!!
Next uhh -  These territorial disputes are nasty huh?
Who's?
Between Ama's
Also, the fishermen don't take Ama's seriously
You need to be good at scolding,
So let's try that, OK?
Dealing with territorial disputes - Necessary for this, is training to yell
Ready, steady,
Seriously,
Kay?
Asashoryu~
TN: Asashoryu is a sumo wrestler
And finally,
Maino-umi~
TN: Mainoumi is a sumo wrestler
Yeah! Skill Department Store!
If you say that, you win
You won?
If you say "Skill Department Store" you win
I'm so confused
Ah, really?
Over there,
There's a bike, go over there
There
So far away!
Pain in the ass!
Pain in the as!
The cameraman won't come with you either
That's quite a distance
For the "Mainoumi"?
For the "Mainoumi"
Oh sweet! He looks just like Fu-kun from the back
That's not good
What do you mean "not good"?
Not bad, not bad
Why the sidecar?
Yeah
Okay! Head Crown Restoration!
Don't say stuff like that
Okay!
Suda OK!
What training was that
Voice training
Suda, your agency didn't approve this, so run over
He is running
Why are you running so slowly?
I ran quite a bi-
You run like that while everyone's waiting?
It's supposed to be like this right? Like this!
This is how you should run!
Definitely like this!
Next, Hamada and Suda reply from the top of a hill
So now I'm gonna ask both of you questions, in turn. Reply in a loud voice.
Questions?
First is Suda
What's another good name for Suda Masaki
If Suda Masaki wasn't your name, what would another good name be? A cool name
Micheal
Micheal J Fox
That's already taken!
He's a huge star!
So, still you Suda
What is Yamasaki Hosei-san lacking?
Go ahead!
Hatred, I think
Such a nice guy
No maliciousness you mean
A good answer
So next, Suda
Still me?
This is hell, hold on
What is this?
A new name that Cocorico should adopt
Your answer?
Turtle & Rabbit
What is that? What does that mean?
Turtle...
Turtle & Rabbit?
Not Rabbit & Turtle then
Exactly
I got it wrong...
C'mon man
Hamada, I'll give you one question
1 good thing about Dorians?
Dorians is a comedy duo that Hamada is friends with
He does take care of them a lot
1 good thing about Dorians?
They come whenver I call them!
He's being serious
That's not a good reason to like them