0 0 m -300 -65.625 b -310.75 -67 -339.875 -65.625 -336.875 -41.25 b -338.375 -27.75 -309.25 -1 -301.5 0 b -289.25 7.625 -284.625 -1 -277 -2.5 b -267.75 -11.625 -258.625 -14.625 -249.375 -37.125 b -246.25 -58 -266.25 -59.625 -267.75 -61.375 b -280 -67 -290.75 -65.625 -300 -65.625 m -292.375 -58 b -278.5 -61.375 -260.125 -52.375 -263.125 -43.125 b -273.875 -54.875 -283.125 -54.875 -292.375 -58 m -370.625 -189.875 b -364.375 -189.875 -312.25 -179.5 -320 -110.625 b -330.625 -67 -359.875 -46 -369 -41.25 b -373.625 -39.875 -398.125 -20.625 -431.875 -52.375 b -439.625 -67 -455 -83.875 -444.25 -121 b -439.625 -136 -431.875 -164.875 -404.375 -181 b -396.625 -185.25 -384.375 -193 -370.625 -189.875 m -232.5 -193 b -229.375 -193 -192.625 -203.5 -160.375 -148 b -155.75 -134.5 -143.5 -117.75 -151.25 -76 b -160.375 -41.25 -175.75 -39.875 -185 -37.125 b -192.625 -37.125 -203.375 -27.75 -240.125 -53.5 b -252.5 -63.75 -270.875 -70 -278.5 -112 b -277 -112 -295.375 -139.25 -257 -181 b -249.375 -187.375 -241.75 -193 -232.5 -193 m -373.625 -143.5 b -416.625 -136 -392 -89.5 -372.125 -94.25 b -366 -94.25 -352.125 -97.375 -349.125 -117.75 b -353.75 -142.375 -362.875 -140.25 -373.625 -143.5 m -373.625 -129.875 b -364.375 -133.125 -359.875 -121 -361.375 -117.75 b -361.375 -106.375 -370.625 -106.375 -375.125 -106.375 b -381.25 -107.375 -384.375 -113.5 -382.875 -121 b -382.875 -124.125 -379.75 -129.875 -373.625 -129.875 m -370.625 -124.125 b -375.125 -122.375 -373.625 -116.75 -370.625 -116.75 b -367.5 -116.75 -364.375 -122.375 -370.625 -124.125 m -221.75 -143.5 b -255.5 -137.5 -240.125 -91 -221.75 -95.25 b -215.625 -94.25 -200.25 -97.375 -200.25 -124.125 b -204.875 -142.375 -217.125 -143.5 -221.75 -143.5 m -221.75 -129.875 b -201.875 -129.875 -208 -106.375 -218.75 -106.375 b -221.75 -104.625 -234 -107.375 -231 -121 b -231 -124.125 -229.375 -129.875 -221.75 -129.875 m -218.75 -124.125 b -223.25 -121 -220.25 -115 -217.125 -116.75 b -212.5 -117.75 -215.625 -124.125 -218.75 -124.125 m -376.75 -116.75 b -379.75 -116.75 -378.25 -112 -376.75 -112 b -375.125 -112 -373.625 -116.75 -376.75 -116.75 m -223.25 -115 b -226.375 -115 -224.875 -110.625 -223.25 -110.625 b -221.75 -110.625 -220.25 -115 -223.25 -115
0 0 m -455 -217.125 l -142 -217.125 l -142 86.875 l -455 86.875 m -145 -214.125 l -451.875 -214.125 l -451.875 84.25 l -145 84.25
TPF
Are their minds connected!?
Are the minds of the Gaki members connected!?
They're not coming, are they? 'Cause they're idiots.
"Make them think as one" Test Segment
Tonight, we're continuing last week's test segment where we test if their five minds think alike.
Ichigaya
Nippon TV Kojimachi
Yotsuya
Rectangle
Test Rules
☛ Head to the place that comes to mind according to a theme
☛ The test won't end until everyone gets back together
Speaking of a large parking lot?
Theme 1
The first theme was "a large parking lot".
Test Rules
Text
☛ All 5 members will begin in different places
☛ Transportation is by taxi
All five members will begin in different places to add difficulty.
They took off in a taxi to head for the place they'd thought of.
Where is everyone gonna go?
Look, this place is huge, isn't it?
About
Akasaka
Cars
Komazawa
Yoyogi
Cars
Odaiba
Daikanyama
As expected, no one came together,
And they all spread far from each other.
Akasaka
Daikanyama
Komazawa
Odaiba
Yoyogi
They check their location with a group call.
If there's a parking lot that can
fit 150 cars in Akasaka
That'd be it💢
I came to Daikanyama.
The facade looks like a Japanese house.
That's gotta be small, right?
It's not small, it fits 44 cars!
That's small!
Speaking of a big billboard?
Theme 2
The next theme was "a big billboard".
Yotsuya
Matsumoto headed to the Onishi Lion billboard in Yotsuya.
And there...
Ah!!
Ahhhh~!!
Alright!
That's Tsukitei, right?
Matsumoto and Hosei were able to join up!
Matsumoto and Hosei were able to join up successfully.
Yotsuya
Akasaka
South Aoyama
Omotesando
It's been 1 hour and 50 minutes since the start. Only two people have gotten back together.
Will they all do it? Tonight, the conclusion.
Will they all be able to get back together? Tonight, the conclusion.
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Christian
Derek
!!
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
**tofupandas.tumblr.com**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on YouTube
individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own. Please go back and
support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit. You can
download episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching!
J-Lan
Proofreader:
Translator:
Typesetter:
____________________________________________________________________
Akasaka
Harajuku
Omotesando
Shibuya
Shinbashi
Shinjuku
South Aoyama
Tokyo
Yotsuya
Time since start: 1 hr 57 min
It's been about 2 hours since the start.
In the second theme, only Matsumoto and Hosei got together.
Yotsuya
You know, this kind of segment
makes you start hating the other members.
Well...
It makes you think that they're idiots.
Theme 3 Announced
Now, we announce the third theme.
Akasaka
This one is just...
It's a difficult one.
Theme 3
I have no idea about places where we record frequently.
Frequent Gaki recording location.
We always go all over the place.
This one's actually really hard.
Omotesando
Because there's actually a lot.
Since there's many, the impression it left them is key.
Indeed. So far, Gaki no Tsukai has been recorded in all kinds of places.
So naturally, there are many options to choose from.
Yotsuya
In Yotsuya, Matsumoto and Hosei will...
Let's think about this one.
Because now we can both think about it.
A strategy meeting at MOS Burger
The pair take their time for a strategy meeting at MOS Burger.
I'll have the fish.
Conversation
inside
I'll have the fish.
Cashier
Would you like it with the lettuce wrap?
Yes!!
Something unexpected happens...
This is when something unexpected happens to Matsumoto.
Like badminton...
and "Itao is watching",
the first episode.
There's no bun...
You're kidding, right?
There's no bun but...
There's no bun?
No way.
Is this what the lady said? Something about only lettuce.
I mean...
I though it would still have the bun!
Eh?
Really?
Which one is it?
How stoic do they think I am?
I'm really hungry...
A stoic
meal
Stoic Matsumoto,
filled his belly with lettuce.
South Aoyama
I think we've been in that place more than once.
Playing badminton in that place, that's what comes to mind.
Alright, I'll go there.
What place did he decide to go to!?
What frequent location did Endo choose as his destination?
Omotesando
Wait a minute.
What should I do?
There's one place that comes to mind.
Incidentally, where would that be?
Staff
Can I say it?
The first place that I though of was
It's *Beep*.
For Downtown's opening segment before the talk,
I remember recording there quite often.
I want to see them there!
Believing his hunch, he heads to his destination!
Tanaka decides to trust his hunch and head to his destination!
After eating, they discuss their destination
With their bellies full, the pair discuss their destination.
"Itao is watching" was
on that field in front of Yoyogi Park.
Haru no Ogawa Community Park
Matsumoto is thinking about a park in Yoyogi.
The park where "Itao is watching" and other segments were born.
This is the park where "Itao is watching" and other famous segments were born.
They chose it as their destination.
Akasaka
At the same time, in Akasaka, Hamada looks like he's still wavering.
The park where Itao watched from his apartment, we went
there at least once, right?
And other things.
But the closest place would be Shiba Park, right?
Shiba Park
Hamada thought of Shiba Park.
"Heipo stops a giant boulder" and other memorable segments.
Many memorable segments were recorded there too.
I'll try going to Shiba Park!
There's even two of these ladies.
I thought this was the perfect place.
Rides a taxi to Shiba Park
Hamada has chosen his destination and gets on a taxi.
Matsumoto and Hosei head toward Yoyogi
Matsumoto and Hosei begin moving toward Yoyogi.
That was LOSS Burger.
LOSS Burger.
Rectangle
Test Rules
☛ The traveling time limit is 30 minutes
Akasaka
Omotesando
Shiba Park
Shibuya
Shinjuku
South Aoyama
Tokyo
With their destination in mind, everyone begins moving.
Yotsuya
Yoyogi
With their destination in mind, everyone begins moving.
Okay, wait a minute.
I should think about this one.
There's one more place.
There is.
There is, but
In terms of distance, I wouldn't consider it.
Where?
Sagamiko Picnic Land.
But this
It's not an option, considering the distance.
I told you.
You told me.
Don't you think this is it?
From being separated,
Us five will get together and it'll feel good.
I really hope they come.
Absolute
Confidence
Endo is very confident on the place he thought of.
Arrival at Shiba Park
Around the same time, Hamada arrived at Shiba Park.
Shiba Park
We came here a few times but
I want to know where the others
decided to go.
Hamada surprised me, he went to the place where you were.
I said that I was in Akasaka,
Akasaka
Matsumoto
Theme 1
and then he goes to Akasaka.
Akasaka
Hamada
Theme 2
That's why
I think he's an idiot.
The zipper is completely broken...
It's like he thought
that I wouldn't move away from Akasaka.
There's no way that would happen.
Yeah.
No way.
That's why he needs to study more.
Now it got stuck.
We used to take this road
all the time when we went to Sanseido.
There's also this park!
In an apartment here Itao would...
That apartment.
He would watch us from there.
I think we did it at least one time.
In the end, what's his destination!?
Where exactly is Tanaka heading?
(Tanaka's) parking lot for 44 cars really startled me.
Tanaka is starting to scare me.
He's scary.
There are times when you can't really understand him.
There are.
I Think You Like This
Like with his sense of style.
Right.
When that happens.
If he hadn't entered Yoshimoto, he might have not made it.
Yoyogi Park is getting closer!
The two get closer to their destination, Yoyogi Park.
What will happen...
What will happen?
Alright!
I did it!
Of course you did.
Yeah!!!
This was the only answer.
Endo has joined up!
This was it.
Yeah.
You're right.
I'm so glad.
They're still not here.
I'm the only one here.
It had to be this place.
Yeah, this place.
That's were Itao would...
That's right.
Itao was watching.
There was also the Cream Stew episode and Tanaka fight.
We did those, it was here, right?
Right.
And Housei's "God of Laughing"
It was over there.
Yeah.
This is the only possible place!
This place for sure.
Their feelings prove useless, as their time is up.
Nobody came!
It's over!
Staff
No, it's not over yet.
It's still not over.
But seriously,
Tanaka has a problem.
Yeah, I think it's really showing now.
I wonder what's wrong.
Is he doing it on purpose?
It makes you think...
If he's really doing it on purpose, then it's getting old now!!
Is he doing it to get a reaction from us?
Yeah, it feels that way.
He's not that type of person though...
"No way!"
They confirm Hamada's location
First, they confirm Hamada's location.
Hello?
Shiba Park
Yoyogi
Where are you?
Me?
I'm at Shiba Park.
Shiba Park?
I knew it.
You went there!!
Over here, there's three of us now!
Another correct place.
One more person joined up?
Yamasaki and
Endo here.
This place was the correct answer!
Shiba Park
Yoyogi
The correct answer? Where are you?
Obviously, the park where Itao watched us.
That's right.
I thought of that place but
"Itao is watching" was only one time, wasn't it?
What else did we do there?
I mean,
You're by yourself, right?
Shiba Park
Yoyogi
What if I am?
This was the correct answer.
This was it.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
The real problem is Tanaka.
Please call that monster.
Staff
Time's up.
Speak with everyone.
You're kidding...
Shiba Park
Yoyogi
Where are you?
I'm near Sanseido,
Shinjuku Central Park
No.
That's where we caught bugs.
You thought about the time we were catching bugs, didn't you?
It's a park that we used plenty of times before.
Rectangle
Shinjuku Central Park.
Tanaka's own "Bug Hunt Segment" was recorded.
Shinkuku Central Park, where Tanaka is,
was where he produced the "Heatwave Bug Hunting" segment
and there's no mistake that it has been used before.
That's old, that's really old!
It really is.
Wait a minute,
Did I get it wrong?
Matsumoto, Yamasaki, Endo. Us three are together at the park where Itao watched us.
Shiba Park
Shinjuku
Yoyogi
"Itao is watching"?
Shiba Park
Shinjuku
Yoyogi
Hamada, where are you?
Shiba Park.
Shiba Park?
Who cares about Hamada.
There's no use talking.
This conversation is useless.
You both got it wrong, your conversation
won't do any good.
I'm at Shiba Park!!
At Shiba Park, have we even recorded there?
Shiba Park...
Well then...
You're just loitering now.
We're still...
We're still continuing...
The number of times doesn't matter to them.
They're saying their choice was right,
because "Us three came here", thinking about "Itao is watching".
I thought about it too but I only remembered going there once.
I've really been trying to make the right choice...
Akasaka
Harajuku
Omotesando
Shiba Park
Shinbashi
Shinjuku
Time since start: 2 hrs 34 min
Tokyo
Yotsuya
Yoyogi
It's been two and a half hours since the start.
Three people have come together. Only Hamada and Tanaka are left.
Theme 4   Announcement
Next, the fourth theme is announced.
Tsutaya
Theme 4
Speaking of Tsutaya?
I don't go to Tsutaya very often.
Possible Tsutaya locations: About 42 stores
Considering the time limit, they have
about 42 different stores to choose from.
Aired on 10/08/2014
Let's continue strolling until we meet Celebs ! in Daikanyama
In Gaki no Tsukai, they recorded the "Strolling to meet celebs" segment,
and they should remember their visit to the Tsutaya in Daikanyama.
Shinjuku
I already have two in mind.
I have two.
The first one that came to mind was
The Tsutaya in Sancha.
Sangenjaya
The one in Carrot Tower.
And the other one was the Tsutaya in Daikanyama.
Daikanyama Tsutaya Bookstore
Is that one a Tsutaya?
Yes, it is.
I wish I could have seen it better, Daikanyama's Tsutaya.
I didn't really see it...
Yoyogi
Ah, Matsumoto, we got this.
We got this one.
There's a lot of them, but it's gotta be that one, right?
Let's say it all together.
1, 2...
Daikanyama!!
TV Asahi!
The one in front of TV Asahi.
It's gotta be one in Daikanyama.
No, the one in the corner in front of TV Asahi.
I'm telling you it's the one in Daikanyama.
Daikanyama...
If you think about it, they're gonna go to Daikanyama.
If they're thinking straight.
However,
there's also a Tsutaya near the yakiniku place
where Hamada sometimes goes to eat.
The one near the Equestrian Park.
Equestrian Park
Ah, that's...
But the one that comes to mind
has to be the one in Daikanyama
Right.
Let's go there.
They'll go there.
Right now, I'd go to the one in Roppongi.
Shiba Park
The one near TV Asahi...
The one near the intersection.
If I had to choose a Tsutaya...
Personally, I'd go to the one in front of the Equestrian park.
Equestrian Park
But I wouldn't go all the way over there.
It'll take more than 30 minutes.
There's also the one where we recorded recently,
whether we could meet celebrities, the Tsutaya in Daikanyama.
Daikanyama Tsutaya Bookstore
Which one is closer? From Yoyogi.
Daikanyama?
Daikanyama.
It's Daikanyama...
Let's go to *Beep*
Which Tsutaya did he choose!?
After pondering an answer,
which Tsutaya did Hamada choose as his destination?
What will Tanaka do?
Right now, we're in Shinjuku...
I think it has to be that place.
Akasaka
Harajuku
Omotesando
Shiba Park
Shibuya
Shinbashi
Shinjuku
Tokyo
With their destination in mind, everyone begins moving.
Yotsuya
Yoyogi
Now that they've chosen their destination,
they begin moving.
A frequent recording location,
Staff
the one with the most (people) became the right answer.
The number of people.
Yeah.
That's the rule they made up.
It said "frequent" in the theme,
but they ignored that part.
They don't even bother reading the sentence.
They're all idiots!
On the road to Daikanyama
Those three are on the road,
heading towards the Tsutaya in Daikanyama.
Tanaka thinks very differently.
What's going on with Tanaka, Endo?
He's always like that.
I wonder what's wrong.
He's starting to stop thinking like a Japanese person.
Stop thinking like a Japanese person?
Tanaka is...
He's the type of person who destroys himself.
A self-destructive person!
Yeah, he's destroying this.
Samantha Thavasa, was it?
It was just a normal billboard.
Tanaka's  "Big Billboard"
What was he thinking?
It's not even big.
There's no way five old guys would get together at a Samantha Thavasa billboard!!
Were they complaining about you? On the phone?
Staff
I don't know who said it but
when I said, "I'm at Shinjuku Central Park"
I heard a voice say, "That's old!"
It made me feel embarrassed, for a moment.
I don't know...
That's old, that's really old!
It really is.
Knowing who said it...
Staff
Yeah,
I think it's gonna make me feel worse so...
I'm thinking of not watching this one when it airs.
Arrival at Daikanyama's Tsutaya Book Store
At around that time, Matsumoto, Hosei and Endo
arrived at the Tsutaya in Daikanyama.
No, there's no one here.
There is, over there.
No, there's no one.
You're kidding.
If they're still not here, then...
They'll never...
Not good news.
Isn't this too hard?
But,
there was a bit of traffic so...
Tanaka, please...
You can't stand up for Tanaka.
He's off somewhere else.
What happened, Tanaka?
If we're unlucky, he went to Sangenjaya.
It's this one, it's gotta be this Tsutaya.
But, yeah...
I want to meet them.
It would make me very happy, if I could meet them.
Where are they?
Worst-case scenario, Tanaka went to Sancha and Hamada went to Roppongi.
And we're still separated.
Still separated.
And we do it one more time.
One more time.
There's two choices, but which one do I choose?
At Daikanyama,
will they
come together!?
Will the five be able to come together at Daikanyama's Tsutaya?
My stomach hurts.
Matsumoto.
There.
Dahama-senpai!!
Senpai!
Of course.
I'm so glad.
You're here.
Alright!
Hamada is able to join up!!
This was it, wasn't it?
This was it.
Right?
We recorded here.
What about Tanaka?
He's still not here.
I don't know where Tanaka went but
There's no way it's anywhere but here.
It's really strange for him not to be here.
Yeah, considering the distance.
Tanaka was nowhere to be seen and time ran out.
Mulling over two choices, he went to Sangenjaya.
After mulling over his two choices,
he decided to go to Sangenjaya.
They're late...
Scolding him over the phone
They're going to scold Tanaka over the phone.
Staff
Time's up.
No way.
This is just ridiculous!!
Hello?
Daikanyama
Sangenjaya
Where are you?
I'm in Sancha.
T/N: 'Sancha' is how they shorten Sangenjaya.
Sancha?
He went to the Tsutaya in Sancha.
Why did you go to Sancha?
Daikanyama
Sangenjaya
There's four of us over here.
There it is.
You four are together.
We're in Daikanyama.
There it is! Daikanyama!!
If it's Tsutaya written in alphabet letters,
wouldn't it be the Tsutaya in Sangenjaya?
What are you talking about?
He's desperate.
He's really desperate.
This is his weird, serious attitude.
He's displaying it.
He's desperate, not good.
Daikanyama
Sangenjaya
But, in the strolling around the city segments...
The most recent one...
Right now, suddenly, *Beeeeeeeeeeeeeep* has shown up.
Encounter with a celebrity
What the hell...
It's the wrong
segment.
Wrong segment.
Daikanyama
Ebisu
Nakameguro
Sangenjaya
Shibuya
Tanaka went to Sangenjaya, and was unable to join the others.
For the fourth theme, Tsutaya, Tanaka headed to Sangenjaya
and was unable to join the others.
Right now, suddenly, Pierre Taki has shown up.
Right now?
What the hell...
It's the wrong segment!
Wrong segment.
This time we don't have to meet celebs.
What are you doing?
Happened to pass by
Pierre Taki
Recording for Gaki.
Taki is right in front of me.
I met a celebrity.
Then...
Daikanyama
Sangenjaya
Alright, last one.
Yes, last one.
Let's do this.
We have to get together with this one.
Of course, this is it.
Bring Pierre along too!
Ah, together with Taki!
Why?
I'm here with my kids, shopping.
Ah, of course.
Taki is shopping with his kids.
Daikanyama
Ebisu
Nakameguro
Sangenjaya
Shibuya
Time since start: 3 hr 24 min
It's been 3 hours and 20 minutes.
Four have come together, only Tanaka is left.
Theme 5   Announced
They want to end it with the next one, the fifth theme.
Next is...
It can only be that place.
If it's Donki, it has to be that one.
Theme 5
Speaking of Don Quijote?
Only that one.
That one.
Let's say it all at once.
Wait.
I'm ready.
1, 2...
Nakameguro!
Shibuya!
It's Shibuya, right?
We went Nakame, Nakame, Shibuya, Nakame.
(Nakameguro)'s closer, isn't it?
Yeah, it's close.
We could even walk there!
We can.
Are you walking there?
Staff
We're not walking there though.
Nakameguro is fine, yes?
Yeah, it's fine.
Yeah.
There's one in Roppongi, isn't there?
Uh... yeah, in Roppongi.
Yes, in Roppongi.
Taki, speaking of Donki?
Speaking of Donki... I guess...
Nakameguro
It'd be Nakame. First one is Nakame.
Nakame, right.
Kanpachi Setagaya
Also, Kanpachi,
the Honancho store,
Kannana Honancho
and there's also the new big one
Shinjuku East Exit
in Shinjuku's Kabukicho.
You know a lot about Donki!
Yeah.
Well, I just got a hint from Taki so...
all that's left
use it to make my own choice...
Yeah.
I'll be going now.
He parts ways with Pierre Taki...
After receiving help during his private time,
we part ways with Pierre Taki...
Having chosen a destination, Tanaka heads to Don Quijote!
After choosing his destination, Tanaka heads to Don Quijote!
How should I feel about this?
There are people waiting for me in that place...
I want to feel it,
what everyone else already felt.
Arrival at Nakameguro Main Store
At the same time, the other four
are already at Nakameguro's Don Quijote.
Why do we have to wait for Tanaka?
Sorry.
Only one wish
Tanaka only has one wish.
I wish I could meet them. I want to meet them!!
At last, will they be able to meet!?
At last, will Tanaka be able to meet with the others?
Stand-by at the Nakameguro Main Store
The four wait for Tanaka at the Don Quijote in Nakameguro.
Why do we have to wait for Tanaka?
Tanaka has arrived near a Don Quijote.
Arrival at his chosen Don Quijote
This is the only place I could think of.
And now...
I want to meet him, in the end, it'll feel nice.
I bet Tanaka wants to meet us too.
Oh?
There's a lot of people over there.
He's here!
It was this one.
Look, they're here!
Look, there!
Hey, this is...
There they are!
Yeah, we're here.
Here you are.
At last, the 5 come together!
Time since start: 3 hr 43 min
Don't be saying "look, look".
Don't say that. What the hell is up with you?
Why are you like that? You're not excited at all.
It's not like we're happy.
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
This one was really a no-brainer.
You're the only one that thought differently.
Look who's talking! You just met them in the last one.
Seriously.
Isn't it true?
What's wrong, Tanaka?
Are you doing it on purpose?
He's doing it on purpose.
I would never...
It was...
On purpose.
If you were...
If you were actually doing it on purpose...
You would really be a despicable person.
He called you that again.
Stop saying that.
Matsumoto, please stop calling me that.