[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
A usual day in the meeting room before the recording of "Gaki No Tsukai".
They are all looking and getting excited over the girls in the magazine.
But that 'man' is nowhere to be seen.
She's cute.
I mean, I get it...
You're returning it, right?
Excuse me.
Sorry...
Sorry for interrupting...
May I have some of your time?
I have another letter from our guy, Matsumoto.
-Our guy?
-Everyone knows Matsumoto!
I have come to deliver it.
I bet he drew a tiny map again.
In the letter...
I got this from 'our guy' Matsumoto.
Again...
Again with this...
-It's the usual pattern.
-Right, right.
"You lot are a bunch of begging lowly celebs who are no better than chickens."
"It is so painful to see how the lot of you fly around the big sky of showbiz like a bunch of sexual vultures."
Here he goes...
He wrote the same thing before.
"So let us see who is the real technician, the sexual dynamite, the human crimson viper."
"That is the purpose of this letter."
"Hitoshi Matsumoto".
He drew a map again.
He included "Safari Park".
There's the "Fuji Safari Park" and then "Here".
This is too broad.
He also included a pet shop at the side.
This is pretty bad.
He included the zoo as well.
-But you know he always does this even though he never gets first place.
-You're right.
That's just how it goes.
He was so desperate last time.
Did you see?
He went like this with the mannequin.
And his reaction after barely winning over me.
Wasn't that so lame?
Yeah, isn't it so lame whenever he's happy?
Anyways, 'our guy' Matsumoto is waiting so please go ahead.
Are you guys coming too?
Yes, of course.
We also wanna see what it's like.
Yes.
You'll be shocked.
The guys have put their prides on the line to see who's the sexiest.
Matsumoto came out victorious the first time around.
But it has been a close race.
Alright!!
With two losses for Tanaka and one loss for Endo, everything is on the line.
What kind of contest will they face?
And what punishment will the loser endure?
We're closeby every time.
-We don't need that map.
-Right, right.
-That map is so useless..
-Yeah.
We're at the "Safari Park".
He's always sitting like that.
-Good morning
-Morning!
Good morning!
You always have this nice setup going on.
You sure took your sweet time getting here, you $@#% celebs!
$@#% celebs?!
$@#%?!
Right, I don't think any of us are $@#%...
Today is all about kissing.
Kissing!
-Yes.
-Right.
-Kissing?
Lift your hand up if you've kissed before!
Of course we have...
Then let me hear your first kiss stories!!
How about it?
-I think it must have been in my 2nd or 3rd year of middle school.
-Oh, that's pretty fast.
-Quite fast.
-That was back then.
Tell us her full name.
Huh?!
The other person's name?
-Yes.
-What?!
-Say it, quickly.
Who did I kiss back then...?
What do you mean?!
We're talking about your first kiss!!
Say it, come on.
You guys, are you serious?!
How shameless can you be?
It's your first kiss!
You don't remember her name?!
-Do you remember yours?
-Of course.
Who is it?
It was Mieko Ishida.
Mieko Ishida?
Why am I the only one spilling the beans?!
We don't really remember...
It must have been pretty humiliating for you guys then...
Right?
Saying the full name is embarrassing...
It's all about kissing today!
Kissing!!
Kissing, right...
We're seeing who's better at kissing!!
Oh right...
We have the stage all ready to go!
-Yeah.
-Sure.
It's over there!!
Let's get over there.
You're just embarrassed.
Let's go.
Open it.
Oh, this way.
Alright.
What's this?
-What is this?
-I see...
What is it?
Alright, it's the Kiss Machine!!
We have more people this time around.
So deciding who goes first will be hard.
Listen up guys!!
Today we'll be seeing who is the fastest kisser!!
The rules are simple.
Players will ride a moving platform.
And they will try to kiss as many lips as possible from the 80 slots.
This time around, 6 people will be taking up the challenge excluding Matsumoto.
Of course, the worst one will have to take a punishment!!
-I see...
-Right...
Understood?
Are you confident?
Are you confident in your kisses?
This is not about confidence, I would bite off every single one of those lips apart.
That's not good.
You can't be biting them off.
I guess I'm just "wild".
It's my "wildness".
My "wildness"!!
That's how they say it in Okinawa.
Hurry up and decide who's first!!
Here he goes.
-The order...
-Should I go?
Shall I go?
- Vacuum are you going?
-Vacuum are you going first?
I mean you normally don't want to go first.
Sure, you can wait and see what the deal is.
Alright then, let's have Vacuum go first.
-Alright.
-You going?
Are you guys just gonna call me Vacuum from now on?
Are you?
Aren't you Vacuum for License?
I'm totally okay with it.
Alright.
Our first batter is Vacuum Fujiwara.
How good a kisser is he?
Let's start.
Here comes Vacuum!
Go ahead!
Ready...
Set!
That's so creepy.
So creepy.
Amazing! Amazing!
Alright!
He's missing quite a few.
-Right, on the right side.
-He missed one.
-The platform's speed is fixed.
-I see.
So it's all skill.
But look at these ones, they are moving.
Oh, right.
It's getting harder.
By the way, it takes about 50 seconds to get to the finish line.
50 seconds?
He's missing a lot of them.
You're right.
You know...
I would also like it if you could keep in mind your expressions.
-They're running away from him.
-They move a lot.
-You can do it!
And you might even bite them while they run away.
They are running away.
-They really get away.
-This is hard.
It looks so hard.
Alright, that's it!
-I see...
-I don't get it.
Vacuum, how was it?
I felt it in my legs.
-What? For real?
-Really?
That's crazy.
Even a 29 year old guy like me ended up like this.
No way!
-You even seem like you work out.
-That's true!
For real?
It hurts a lot over here.
I see.
Let's look at Fujiwara's score!
Go ahead!
54!
-Is that good?
-How is that?
But out of how many is this?
So it takes around 54 seconds to get to the finish line.
-Right.
-It's around 50 seconds.
So he got 1 for every second.
It might be good.
Yeah, it might be.
Let's see who's our next challenger!!
This persona comes and goes.
So annoying.
Maybe I should go next.
For real?
-I should...
-Hold on, did you say you were 29?
-I'm 29.
I'm 39.
So we're gonna see who's better?
You'll feel it right in your thighs.
But you know, he has had surprisingly good results on this series.
You're trying hard, right?
-I'm quite confident.
-Right.
He's pretty confident.
Alright then, you should go.
Okay then, here I go.
-Alright.
-Go on.
Yes.
Ready...
Set!
Whoa, that's scary.
How will he fare?
He already missed one.
That was pretty fast.
This is pretty bad, no?
By the way, kissing the same one twice doesn't count.
Yes.
-You have no choice but to ignore the ones that pop up in your peripheral vision.
-You're right.
He did that for nothing.
Alright!
He's not hitting them.
However...
-He's not doing too bad...
-He's going.
-I feel like he's doing better than Vacuum.
-No way, no way.
He's not?
I don't think so, he's missed a lot.
-Is that so?
-Yeah.
Isn't he backing up a bit too much?
He's bumping against all those obstacles after all.
And it is quite fast.
-What do you think?
-He looks flabbergasted.
He looks exhausted.
Was it hard?
This hurts.
Huh?
My jaw is all stiff now.
Because of all the kissing...
Because of all the kisses?
Alright let's look at Yamazaki's score!
Whoa, amazing!
Awesome!
This is amazing.
-Awesome!
-Amazing!
This is amazing!
I didn't think the gap would be this big while I was watching you.
-I think where I differed from Vacuum, was that he went for the ones at the bottom.
-Right.
-Oh, you're right.
-That's so true.
-He got all the bottom ones.
-Yes.
He went down...
-But you can't do that unless you're a big masochist.
-Right, you have to go down...
You have to dive down.
Right, dive down.
So in that sense, masochists have an advantage in this challenge.
Then Hamada is at a real disadvantage.
Let's go to the next contestant!!
Honestly, I wanna see how this turns out.
We had a guy in his 20s and a guy in his 30s.
Now we have to do a guy in his 40s.
-How is the 40 year old guy gonna do?
-That's right.
-Alright then, I don't mind.
-I really wanna see how it turns out.
Hamada, the representative of the 40s.
How many kisses will he steal with his octopus lips?
Alright, let's go!
Please start!
How will he do?
Ready...
Set...
-Scary!
-That's scary.
He looks pretty good.
He's very good.
You're right.
-He got them all so far.
-He did.
-He's really getting them all.
Oh, he just missed one.
He missed one.
You should always ignore them if you mess up the timing.
Oh no, oh no, oh no!!
-This is bad!
-That's bad!
He missed a ton of them!
This is terrible!
He looked a bit dizzy there!
He's struggling!
Oh! He went for the bottom!
He's gonna fall!
-Look he's gonna fall.
-He missed about half of those.
Look at that face!
That expression!
-That was bad!
-The end!
That was so bad.
I'm very interested in these results.
-This is bad.
-It's terrible.
I can really feel it in my back.
It was really bad.
In the middle there you looked like Akira Shimizu.
This could be the lowest score yet!
What is Hamada's score?!
-Alright!!
-Yes!
Hamada, this is bad.
-I figured as much.
-Me too.
-I never thought there would be such a big gap between scores.
-For real...
Can I go next?
Endo?
Okay then.
You're going?
I'm going.
-Endo won't do good, I'm sure of it.
-Right...
-He's the kind of guy that just pokes the $@#% around.
-Right.
-He doesn't know what to do.
-That's so true.
That's why he was startled when he called us $@#% celebs.
He's the only one that reacted.
He looked at everyone with that "who?" face.
He straightened up right away.
And we didn't say anything.
Endo, the butt of the joke.
How will he do at the kissing machine?
Alright, let's go.
Please start!
Ready...
he must be excited.
Set...
This thing is so exhausting.
This one is actually harder than the ones we did before.
In terms of stamina as well.
-He's missing a few.
-He is, he is.
That must hurt!
He must be...
Look, he's not getting any!
-This is bad.
-This is really bad.
-It's bad!
-What's he doing?
You are done for if you fail there.
But he's coming back.
He's run out of steam.
But he didn't get that many, did he?
It's over!
I also got sprayed with that stuff, rigth?
-Yes, you did.
-Yeah.
I was like, "What the hell is that?".
Shozo! Shozo, did that break your heart?
-Honestly... Remember how we were getting hyped up back there?
-Yes.
I knew I was done for at that moment.
-Let's look at Endo's score!
-52... 52...
Show us!
52! 52!
I knew it!
It's because he fell.
You shouldn't fall.
Of course I was better!!
40...?
That's right.
Falling off the platform was really bad.
These guys have no clue.
Yeah, they are clueless.
It's pretty hard.
Right?
I have zero confidence now.
I shall go!
But I'm not confident at all.
Inomoto is feeling the pressure after seeing Endo's blunder up close.
How will he do at the kissing machine?
Alright, please start!
Ready...
Set...
The first part is the easiest.
This part...
Oh, he's missing a few.
Everyone does fine at this stage.
-This guy is ignoring a lot of them.
-He is, he is.
He might be ignoring them on purpose.
Maybe...
But he's doing much better than Endo.
He's pretty good.
-Endo was crumbling at this stage.
-You're right.
He was all wobbly around here.
-He came close to falling off.
-He's fine, he's fine.
Endo is in trouble.
Oh this is...
I don't know...
This part is so annoying.
You can't get anything.
Doesn't he look tired already?
-But he's definitely done more than Endo.
-You think so?
-This is good.
-The end!
-Endo really messed up by skipping the bottom ones.
-He really did.
I was panicking.
How do you think you did?
I was in full panic mode!
You look pretty exhausted.
I feel sick.
I might throw up.
Besides that...
Your movements were a bit...
You also briefly fell off the platform.
I was just rushing.
I just had to go faster.
I wonder how he did...
Alright, let's see his score!
-Alright!!
-Whoa, 49.
-He even beat me.
-True!
He beat Hamada...
Yeah.
Honestly, I don't think I'll lose to Tanaka.
Right.
At the very least I have to beat Endo's score of 40.
That's right.
Rather, why is it always a battle between these two?
Alright!!
-Hurry up and go.
You're so loud.
-Alright! Here I go!
Tanaka has already lost twice in this series.
Will he clear his name this time around?
-Tanaka.
-Yes?
-Are you ready?
I'm ready!
Please start!
-I don't think he'll get to 40.
-Ready...
Set...
I don't think he's gonna do it.
From these three, Tanaka...
He's no good!
Good! Good! Good!
That's great!
He fell off!
He fell off again!
Why is he falling?
He's missing everything!
Whoa, he's getting left behind!
It left him behind!
Tanaka, you can do it!
That's super bad!
This is such a failure.
-He's picking back up.
-No, he's no good.
But you know he's not scoring any points.
He's going like this.
How many times are you falling off?!
Oh, this!
It's over!!
How'd he do?
-How'd he do?
-This is bad.
-How many times did he fall?
-Tanaka...
-Tanaka.
He's the most exhausted.
-I must thank you.
His face is pale white.
-Your face is pale white.
-You're right.
That was something...
What happened to you?
What went wrong?
He looks like one of the people in "The 8-Tomb Village".
(Japanese mystery movie)
I hate this contest the most.
He's afraid of the running away faces.
He's afraid his bride will run away from him.
Alright, Tanaka!
-Shall we see?
-Yes.
What is the score?!
Come one!
Alright!!
I knew it!!
Is this for real?
33?!
-It's almost half of Hosei!
-Half!
What the heck...
33 is so bad.
Are you serious?
With that being said...
Tanaka is the loser!!
Tanaka's punishment is: "Poster Kissing Pervert at the Shopping District".
You'll know what it is once you get there.
-Have a nice trip!
-Good luck!
Seriously?!
This project should just end already!
This series too!
I really hate this.
I can't win...
I really can't win...
This is a punishment and I won't quit until I get it done...
So let's get going.
I will kiss every single poster hanging in this shopping district.
I will try my best.
Here we go!
Damn it.
I'm really getting that Asakusa vibe.
Alright.
Where are they?
Over here?
Alright.
Looking for them is such a pain in the ass...
This is a poster, right?
This one...
Alright.
Let's go.
What am I doing...?
Okay.
Alright, okay.
Isn't this Eiko Segawa?
Alright, let's go.
Shall we do it?
Ehm... Mr. Tanaka?
Yes?
Is that you?
Yes... Yes...
Are you filming?
Yes...
Right!
This is Asakusa!!
I kinda hate this.
Excuse me.
Alright, let's keep going.
The king...
Impulse...
True...
There's a ton of these.
Let's go.
Whoa, I can't reach this one.
I see... "Nude T heather Rockza".
Whoa, Asakusa 21st Century...
There's another one.
Another Asakusa 21st Century...
I've never seen this Monchhichi.
(Stuffed monkey toys similar to beanie babies)
There's a ton of them here...
Let's get it done...
I have to do it.
Alright!
Oh, Eiko Segawa!
We meet again!
Let's do it.
Is this a poster?
I don't know...