0 0 m -220 -48.125 b -227.875 -49.125 -249.25 -48.125 -247 -30.25 b -248.125 -20.375 -226.75 -0.75 -221.125 0 b -212.125 5.625 -208.75 -0.75 -203.125 -1.875 b -196.375 -8.5 -189.625 -10.75 -182.875 -27.25 b -180.625 -42.5 -195.25 -43.75 -196.375 -45 b -205.375 -49.125 -213.25 -48.125 -220 -48.125 m -214.375 -42.5 b -204.25 -45 -190.75 -38.375 -193 -31.625 b -200.875 -40.25 -207.625 -40.25 -214.375 -42.5 m -271.75 -139.25 b -267.25 -139.25 -229 -131.625 -234.625 -81.125 b -242.5 -49.125 -263.875 -33.75 -270.625 -30.25 b -274 -29.25 -292 -15.125 -316.75 -38.375 b -322.375 -49.125 -333.625 -61.5 -325.75 -88.75 b -322.375 -99.75 -316.75 -120.875 -296.5 -132.75 b -290.875 -135.875 -281.875 -141.5 -271.75 -139.25 m -170.5 -141.5 b -168.25 -141.5 -141.25 -149.25 -117.625 -108.5 b -114.25 -98.625 -105.25 -86.375 -110.875 -55.75 b -117.625 -30.25 -128.875 -29.25 -135.625 -27.25 b -141.25 -27.25 -149.125 -20.375 -176.125 -39.25 b -185.125 -46.75 -198.625 -51.375 -204.25 -82.125 b -203.125 -82.125 -216.625 -102.125 -188.5 -132.75 b -182.875 -137.375 -177.25 -141.5 -170.5 -141.5 m -274 -105.25 b -305.5 -99.75 -287.5 -65.625 -272.875 -69.125 b -268.375 -69.125 -258.25 -71.375 -256 -86.375 b -259.375 -104.375 -266.125 -102.875 -274 -105.25 m -274 -95.25 b -267.25 -97.625 -263.875 -88.75 -265 -86.375 b -265 -78 -271.75 -78 -275.125 -78 b -279.625 -78.75 -281.875 -83.25 -280.75 -88.75 b -280.75 -91 -278.5 -95.25 -274 -95.25 m -271.75 -91 b -275.125 -89.75 -274 -85.625 -271.75 -85.625 b -269.5 -85.625 -267.25 -89.75 -271.75 -91 m -162.625 -105.25 b -187.375 -100.875 -176.125 -66.75 -162.625 -69.875 b -158.125 -69.125 -146.875 -71.375 -146.875 -91 b -150.25 -104.375 -159.25 -105.25 -162.625 -105.25 m -162.625 -95.25 b -148 -95.25 -152.5 -78 -160.375 -78 b -162.625 -76.75 -171.625 -78.75 -169.375 -88.75 b -169.375 -91 -168.25 -95.25 -162.625 -95.25 m -160.375 -91 b -163.75 -88.75 -161.5 -84.375 -159.25 -85.625 b -155.875 -86.375 -158.125 -91 -160.375 -91 m -276.25 -85.625 b -278.5 -85.625 -277.375 -82.125 -276.25 -82.125 b -275.125 -82.125 -274 -85.625 -276.25 -85.625 m -163.75 -84.375 b -166 -84.375 -164.875 -81.125 -163.75 -81.125 b -162.625 -81.125 -161.5 -84.375 -163.75 -84.375 m -333.625 -159.25 l -104.125 -159.25 l -104.125 63.75 l -333.625 63.75 m -106.375 -157 l -331.375 -157 l -331.375 61.75 l -106.375 61.75
Can you take videos on this?
No, you can't take videos
Oh, you cant
Yeah
Huh, I didn't know
Good morning
What's wrong?
Do you have a toothache?
I was punched
What?
By whom?
Heipo!
what!?
No way!
There's no way he would do that
He seems so gentle
Right
He dragged me around by my hair
You don't have any
Heipo's super angry today
Why?
If I think about it,
I think I can partially be blamed
How many years have we been running this show?
Fifteen years
How many episodes?
Dunno
You can't even tell anymore
And...
Of those times...
Has there been a time where Heipo looked cool?
Well, if you think about it, you're right
Has there been a time where Heipo looked 180 cm?
Nope, never
But hold on
We've had a lot of episodes
centered around him
Yeah
Like having him be a baby
Right?
And he's unhappy with that?
In just this year, he's already had
six prospective marriages destroyed
Yeah but isn't that Heipo-san's own...
He's only had 5 meetings, but 6 were destroyed
So whose fault is it?
So what are we supposed to do?
so...
He's saying to show his cool parts on the show.
He says he wants people to go,
"Wow, there are cool parts about Heipo-san"
That's hard...
But...
He gets scared at
even the slightest things
Yeah, that's why
So even if we do it...
There's nothing we can do for him, right?
I don't think so either
Right?
He's actually getting worse
I don't know, I can't tell
What do you mean you don't know?
No, I have to go back him up
It's all the time now
I have to go suck up to him now
So...
Just think of some ways
I really have to go
But even then..
Heipo, whose lameness has been getting worse every year
It's a currrrse!
which has been continuously shown on TV
for fifteen years now
Will they really be able
to make this man look cool?
To grant the chief director Heipo's wish,
four men stood up!
Make Heipo look cool!
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Otviss
Pencillover12
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
Ayumi
Proofreader:
Translator:
Typesetter:
____________________________________________________________________
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on Youtube individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own. Please go back and support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit. You can download episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching!
It's okay, right?
They all head to Heipo's green room
Let's make his mood better
Excuse me
Good morning
Well, so...
Saitou-san is cool...*
*Saitou is Heipo's real name
Of course
Obviously he is very cool normally
So,
I think the idea is that
we just need to show him
as his regular self
Well, we talked it over
between ourselves and decided
Still, what's cool have always been cowboys
Visually
And with that in mind
we prepared a costume and everything
So specifically, what do you...
Yeah, since he's a cool cowboy, we thought...
Rodeo!
Rodeo, huh
It is manly
What do you think, Heipo-san?
Heipo whispering to Matsumoto's ear
So what is it?
"Is it definitely gonna be cool?"
Yeah, it's cool, right?
I think there's no doubt about it
I think it's definitely gonna be cool
Say it yourself!
It's bothersome, again and again
What?
You all and I have been friends
for 10 years, no 20 years
So as such long friends,
it this something that must be done, or not?
Was he really speaking to him for that long?
We think, after giving it that much thought,
that it should be done, but...
This is definitely going to be cool!
Yeah
Let's do this, Heipo-san! Heipo-san let's do this!
So since he thinks the same...
Okay so we'll be waiting here
please do it for us
Let's Show a Cool Heipo Using Rodeo!!
this is gonna be perfect
Yeah this is good
We've spent a lot of money for Heipo
A Rodeo Machine
Going through the trouble of preparing this
Oh, he's coming
Ok, so pretty much...
we've been allowed to set this up so
Ok, I see, you meant like this
And just in case you fall
you'll be totally okay
"You've done pretty good!"
Oh, thank you very much
And, since it's very easy, anyone can do it
Yeah anyone can do it
"Oh no! I'm getting super hyped!"
So are we doing this?
It seems good
So let's go
Yeah, let's go
Yeah we can do this whenever you're ready
Yes, please do
Yeah
Let's put this on just in case
Just in case, ok?
He'll probably be fine though
Just in case
You're still plenty cool after this
You're right, he's still very cool
Usually if you put that on you wouldn't
Heipo-san, let's try striking a pose
It's very good
Super cool!
No matter how you look at it, he's a cowboy
Cameras, make sure he's properly captured
Ok, please
So...
Heipo-san it's up to you!
Yes!
All yours!
Don't wanna!
He's talking
It's only spinning around!
No... I don't wanna
Wait! Wait, sorry!
Scary....
Heipo-san, um...
It was only turning around
It's after this we wanna see..
And, Heipo-san, um...
Can you go like "Yee-haw" or...
He was like "Don't wanna, don't wanna"
But you know
He was actually saying "Yee-haw"
It kinda sounded like "Don't wanna", right?
Yes
But that's it
He's misunderstood
If he could say it a little more clearly
"Yee-haw", please
Show us your cool side!
Your cool side!
Show it to us!
"Yee haw!"
Say it!
Yee...
Ha- no! Don't wanna!
I'm getting off! I'm getting off!
Heipo-san
Heipo leaves in anger
Heipo-san!
You all better remember this!
Heipo-saan!
What does he want us to do..?
After we grudgingly...
He got scared
It only rotated...
It's nothing, right?
It's almost just fun
Maybe he was tired?
Ok, then, we should just go apologize
Everyone goes to see how Heipo's doing
It would be dumb if he says something later
What's wrong?
I was punched!!
again?
He was very agitated
and finally, just now
he got his calm back
I guess it means there's room for improvement
So can you let us talk to him about...
Improvement?
Let's do that, we can't continue like that
So we want to explain that to him
Can you ask him?
If we can go in or not
Ok, ok, then
Excuse us
pardon us...
Heipo elegantly enjoying a book
Heipo-san...
Can we have a moment of your time?
So us four talked it over
and decided that
the mechanical way it looked
may have contributed to the fear
and we made a small adjustment
Changing the Appearance to Erase the Fear
Point of Improvement
aayyyyayay
ayyy
to the machine itself
to change the appearance
What do you think?
He says "I will believe you"
"just once more"
Seriously!?
Thank you very much
"If something were to happen again..."
"A revelation from the gods will come down"
I think it's weird he said "revelation"
What did you mean, Heipo-san?
He says, "But, you know..."
"It's a very good thing"
Huh?
"Friends, I mean."
Oh, it's very gratifying that he thinks so
It is
He's reading a really old book...
Tanaka Yasuo's...
"Vaguely Crystal"...
Let's Show a Cool Heipo Using Rodeo!
Let's Show a Cool Heipo Using Rodeo!!
This is really great, right?
Wow, it is really good
It's so cute...
Not scary at all
It's a field of flowers
Yes
It's great
The colors are very good
Oh, he's coming
He's here
We've been waiting for you
What do you think of this
fun-looking...?
"I like it because it's cute!"
Oh, his opinion changed...
The first one was too mechanical, right?
This way the mood changes a little
And this isn't the only thing
To help with the fear,
we've arranged for this person to come
She's cute
She's laughing a lot, though...
It's very nice
"This is irresistible"
He even tried to speak himself just now
Maybe, you know
See? He's forgotten
if he shows her his cool side, something might...
Something romantic
Maybe it will happen
See? Something rewarding might...
Well, well, um...
What'd he say?
Something dirty, you know!
He totally said it as it is!
He used language!
So, Heipo-san, are you ready?
We're counting on you!
Please watch right in front of him
Yes, please see him
Are you good, camera-people?
Catch his cool moment perfectly, please
Catch him being cool!
Ok, then, please!
Then let's go!!
He looks very cool
No! I'm falling!
Why is he leaving?
Wait, why is he leaving?
Heipo leaves again
Heipo-san
You all have done too much!
Heipo-saan!
We haven't done anything too much!
Right?
This is a little too hard...
She's gone through the trouble of coming
I'm sorry
We're very sorry
Everyone goes to see how he's doing again
We're gonna go... Thank you
Go home!
Wait, hold on
He's very very angry!
So he says
I've been saying, not to embarrass him in front of women!
That is the root cause behind this!
And yet you again, bring a woman
And embarrass him in front of her
This isn't right!
Then... Can we at least explain ourselves...?
I don't think you can see him!
Definitely not...
Well, that's that
I guess it can't be helped
He says it's okay!
Oh, it's okay?
That was fast
Excuse us!
Heipo getting measurements for a new suit
Heipo-san...
Um... They say they want to talk to you...
We all talked together afterwards
about other possible improvements
and thought... maybe a machine isn't right
So basically, instead of machines, using ourselves
Point for Improvement
Using Manpower Instead of Machinery
aayyyyayay
ayyy
Using the power of man
I understand that, but...
"I want to hit someone!"
Wait, please, we've been doing this seriously...
Heipo-san has been saying
he can't go on to the next step
without hitting someone
but next...
Who are you angry at, Heipo-san?
Who makes you most angry?
It's okay...
I'm very sorry.
To be honest....
After this
Heipo's slaps get worse!!
I'm much less excited now
Let's Show a Cool Heipo Using Rodeo!!
I saw that slap and I thought, "Wow, he's really mad"
Yeah, I thought so too
Yeah, but it wasn't all Endo's...
I guess he...
Oh, he's ready already
So...
this is set up so
it's not a machine anymore
You get it if you see it, right?
Mikoshi Rodeo
Yeah, we can imagine
This does seem more gentle
Ok, then...
Great
Yes
Let's do this
This should be okay
Ok, Heipo-san
If you'd please get on...
Yes
This is really heavy
Heipo-san's pretty heavy
Wow, this is pretty tough
Hahahaha
He looks really pleased
Wait wait wait
Wait
He's not ready...
Ah, he's okay
Ok, let's go!!
We're ready!
No, ahh, ah
Ow ow ow ow
Wait
What the hell?
What is it?
What's wrong?
Uhyahahaha!
Heipo leaves for the second time
You!
You're all devils wearing people's faces-masks!!
Devils, I say!!
Why the hell...?
Yama-chan are you okay?
My hand got caught
Oh, that's painful...
between the gun-thingy
Yama-chan it's all messed up!
Yup, it is
I was about to go, "POW"
For the last try, there's only *that*
Everyone goes to see how Heipo's doing again
Yeah, there's only *that*
Yeah, it's already...
Please leave.
Wait,
you can't just...
Please, just leave!
But since we've come this far, and
we finally got something...
He's very very angry!
The thing we're about to explain will definitely do it
I think there's definitely no way
Please, you have to
Yes
We have nothing to lose
He says it's fine!
That's a relief
Yup, that was fast
He might even
go along with it
Excuse us
Excuse us!
Heipo is waxing a surfboard
Does he even know why he's doing that
Heipo-san
You dare come here now?
We're very sorry
We really are
As proof that we've worked hard for you
look at Yama-chan's hand
it has a welt
How do you feel about this Heipo-san?
"Well, before any of that..."
"I..."
"Want to hit someone"
Who do you want to hit, Heipo-san!?
Endo, wait wait, I get it, but...
I get it, but!
Fine
I'm sorry
We know this is our last chance
so this will definitely be
very safe,
Point for Improvement
Using a safe and reliable method
aayyyyayay
ayyy
without anything to fear
and without danger
While still being cool
Of course
that's why...
Can you really do it?
I think
it really is safe this time
What do you say?
For real?
"I want to hit another person!!"
Who is it? Heipo-saaaan!!
Are you okay?
He got my ear
He's okay
I'm counting on you!
Yes
I'll make Heipo-san
go as soon as possible
Let's Show a Cool Heipo Using Rodeo!!
If he's got a problem after this...
He wouldn't
It wouldn't be fair to Tanaka
That's true
Why do you have to do such a thing?
For real
Tanaka Rodeo
To be honest it's embarrassing
I'm sorry, dude
It's okay, I'll do it
Why don't you have that nose ring...
I'll do it
It does suit you though
Does it...?
Oh he's running here
Oh, wow
His spirit's changed
wow
Heipo-san, it's as you see it
this has no danger
undeniably safe
What do you think?
"Well, despite all of the"
"ill-feelings and such"
"All's well that ends well"
Of course
So, um...
He is greatly regretting
his choice to hit Hamada
Oh, really?
As for Endo, nothing at all!
He's not even finished yet!
I see... did I do anything to him?
It's okay with this, right?
Are you good?
He says it's absolutely no problem
He's really depending on you
Yes
If you'd just do it with love
We've been together for years, and I'll do it
You can only wear this out of love
Exactly. I can do it
Ok, let's go
Yes!
You will look very cool
Ah, wait
I promise I'll make you look cool
Very cool
Yes, very cool
Ok, steady, ok
Ow ow ow
Augh
Ah! Ow ow!
Wow, very cool
Please do your best, Heipo-san
Just a little more...
Heipo leaves for the third time
You don't have to go?
I don't care about that guy
This week we are releasing an unreleased Talk
"What is in Antonio Inoki's chin?"
Wow, this is a direct confrontation
Yes it is
Before that, his chin is actually paper-mache
He's actually just putting it on
It's fake?
Yup
And if you take it off,
There's like a caster inside
Just like the wheels on this
That comes out
And?
So if you hold Inoki's legs,
You go like this first, then like this
And when you can't just go like this
You have to go further first, then like this, then this
You can't just turn
because then Inoki will be like "Scary, no, no!"
My shoulder's gonna get scraped! It's gonna get scraped!
Well, of course,
the mental image is funny
but why the hell would there be a caster there?
If you get to Inoki's level, you don't just wanna walk anymore!
I think that way is more tiring though...
Why? Fujita holds him and stuff
It doesn't matter who holds him, but...
you're saying since he puts it there to hide it?
It's easier to go like this for Fujita when the road is wide,
If he goes in a narrow one, it goes like this
And since Inoki was like "anything but that",
Fujita now goes forward a little, before backing up.
And Inoki's all...
"Hey, Fujita, you're not so bad at this"
Ok, I get that
Once, when he was resting his chin, his hand slipped like this
"Y'know, in that case-" "SHKOW!"
and the wheel turns like this
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
It was so hard to keep from laughing
Because you can't laugh too much, right?
Yeah
It was like "RRRROOOOLLLLLLLL"
Wow, his hand really slipped huh?
Something would've got caught in it
Shut up already
It was all
and he says, "I'm leaving now"
and it was like