Ooooh.....delicious!
Continuing from last week, with special guest Umemiya Tatsuo,
Sushzanmai challenge finale.
Delicious!
The rule: They can advance if they finish the Tuna Set.
They win 100,000 yen if they make it past all 31 stores.
But it ends if one person gives up,
and they must pay for all food eaten so far.
I want to eat so much!
I'll make it to 31 today.
Fired up by Yamasaki's passion for winning,
the five have no problem advancing.
But at the 10th store, Yamasaki's confession:
I'm already feeling full.
Just let me take a little break.
Break?
I'll still take part of course, but,
What the hell are you saying?!
Will they be able to finish?!
Finally, the finale!
Typeset by GakiDave
Translation by senor_wristband
After Yamasaki's confession, the bus heads to the 11th store.
Nishikicho
Tsukishima
Can you show the total?
After the 10th store, this is how you all are doing.
Hmm?
Hosei-san and I
I'm eating so much!
20 is the highest.
After all that talk, you guys are stuffing me!
It doesn't change.
Yeah.
What do you mean by "Stuffing" you?
Everyone is eating at the same rate,
you're not being stuffed.
Who, what are you talking about
Yama-chan, being dead serious, how are you feeling right now?
Dead serious?
Probably,
Five
Five?
Everyone, Yama-chan can only do five more stores.
Yama-chan, excuse me, let's put that aside a second,
What if at this store, we said "Yama-chan can have the Akami?"
Seven.
You're not eating at all!
Seven, he says.
While Yamasaki confesses his weakness,
they reach the 11th store in Tsukishima.
So please go ahead and decide.
Since nobody wants to choose the fatty Sushi, a new rule is introduced.
Everyone chooses one Sushi from the five available here,
and if nobody matches, they eat what they chose.
But, if there is a match, there is an extra piece of that sushi.
I'll go for this.
I see, going for that at this point.
Everyone have you chosen? Here we go.
Alright!
2nd time Cocorico-san have matched.
Don't choose chu-toro!
Hosei-san, unexpectedly, Aburi-toro.
Exactly! Yeah!
Extra Chu-toro.
Fatty specialty Aburi-toro, Sushizanmai's Tuna Set is ready.
OK, thank you let's do this.
So everyone eat what you need to.
Our choice right?
The Chu-toro.
Itadakimasu!
So, the Otoro is left,
I'll get both of those.
And Tanaka-san?
The Otoro for Yama-chan-
I'll go for this.
TN: Hosei cheats and eats the smaller roll instead.
He ate it quickly.
Already in his mouth.
Tanaka-san gets left with the heavy stuff
OK, finished!
We're going so fast!
OK everyone, we're heading to Tsukiji.
Finally Tsukiji.
How's everyone's stomachs doing?
Mine, like, became alright.
You can help out now?
You're feeling better?
Yup.
If you got your excitement back, how far can you go?
Currently it's limitless.
The guy who said it was 5 stores earlier, now it's limitless?
Yes.
I guess, it was building up.
Cause you guys were stuffing me.
We're eating the same.
Everyone, we've arrived.
So everyone,
we're finally at Tsukji.
Everyone, look at that billboard
Right under the billboard, there's a map,
Those are stores right?
Those stores, we're gonna go to all of those
Amazing!
So everyone let's head this way.
There are nine stores nearby in this area.
If they can make it past here, the prize money will be in reach!
First off, the 12th store, Sushizanmai Honjin.
So everyone, first off,
make your choices.
Going for this.
This one, if I go for this one,
OK, here we go!
Ready, set.....go!
The Chu-toro matched!
What are you doing?!
Cocorico-san's third match.
Up until now, the duo Cocorico has matched three times.
And Yamasaki has matched Umemiya an unexpected five times.
This right?
Otoro for Hamada-san right?
Ah, tasty!
Hamada-san ... oh he got the Tekka-maki.
What about the last two?
You're having the Aburi?
Amazing!
Tatsuo-nii is having the Aburi, look Yama-chan.
Let's take a break.
No, we gotta keep going.
Everyone had theirs.
I can help you out
Let him do it himself.
Thank you so much.
You're supposed to tell him, "no, I can handle it myself."
But the Senpai wants to eat.
Finished!
You said you were hungry!
Still in the Tsukiji area,
close to the head store, Okunoin.
This is it here?
A good distance.
OK, I gotta decide between these.
Yeah you have to think about the other's choices.
Yeah.
Balance is important.
It is.
Place them in the middle, have you decided?
Here we go - ready, set...flip!
Otoro and Akami matches!
You idiots!
This is the third time Hamada-san and Hosei-san have matched on Akami
Please!
Again you chose that.
Why did you pick Akami now?
That's my line!
Sorry for the wait.
(Excited Crosstalk)
Uwahh there's so many.
It's delicious!
Tekka, Tekka, Tekka,
Endo-san and Hamada-san, oh and Hosei-san.
Yama-chan, take the negitoro.
If anyone can eat another one.
I've got such a big one here
Yes we can see-
Ahhhhhhh!
Wait someone, take this!
C'mon, you can handle that tiny Tekka.
Seriously?
Yamasaki somehow manages his three pieces.
They head for the next store.
Right now.
Everyone, we've arrived.
It's this Shinkan store here.
Eh? Next door?
Are they attached?
Shinkan is here.
Is this attached?
Just 10 metres away, they reach the 14th store, Shinkan.
That last meal packed a punch, I'm just saying.
Everyone's feeling it, everyone is.
Endo is barely eating.
I'm at the top of the scoreboard!
Nah you haven't eaten.
I ate so much.
Right? Endo hasn't eaten.
Then fine I'll eat here.
Okay do that.
Are you ready? Have you chosen?
Here we go.  Ready, set... flip!
Three aburi-toro!
You guys are idiots.
YOU GOT THE AKAMI AGAIN!
You have to eat two extra again, as a penalty.
Please wait.
This and those.
Please, you will make your junior cry with such a request.
Please dig in!
The Aburi...
This is the Otoro right.
There's so much volume.
I'm going for the rolls again.
Please, allow me a roll as well.
Tatsu-nii, you can have the roll too.
Only Hosei-san left.
Hamada-san, I promise, for now,
I won't chose Akami again in the future.
This time, can I just eat ginger?
Are you an idiot?
Just take it, and hurry up eat the Otoro too,
No time for breaks.
Then, promise me something please.
What the hell?
If I eat this, the next two times, help me out.
Can I just eat the Tekka?
A single Tekka each time.
But everyone-
Then screw it! It's impossible!
Stuffing me.
Hurry up and eat it man!
But, please help me out.
Help? I'll have to consider the situation.
C'mon, someone please say they'll save me.
Just that will put my mind at ease.
Then, I'll save you.
For real?
I'll help you.
Hurry up.
For real right?
OKAY.
Finished!
And finally, the Sushizanmai Head Store, the 15th one today.
Yama-chan, the next store is the headquarters.
If you drink a lot of Sake here, you'll be in good shape.
How about some Head Store commerative sake?
If you guys will rescue me, I'll think about it.
What do you mean rescue?
There it is!
The president?
The president was waiting for us.
Wow!
What do you guys think?
Butcher Show
It's huge!
It's very big indeed.
The guy cutting is Sushizanmai's president, Kimura-shachou.
Kiyoshi Kimura - President
Probaly 200kg.
Ah that's how it is.
They're sawing this way.
We chose the best Tuna the vendor had.
There's a lot of fat, especially here there's a lot.
Shall we go?
The president came out for us.
Welcome!
Thank you very much!
Sushizanmai Head Store.
We're here!
We finally made it here.
We're here.
Everyone, choose please.
Have you chosen? Hosei-san?
OK, then let's go
1 ... 2 GO
Akami, Chutoro, both matched.
Why do I gotta match with Hamada-san?
Look at the fresh Akami.
Going into the Sushi is of course, the Tuna the president just butchered.
So everyone, to mark this occasion...
Well done! Kampai!
Here everyone refreshes themselves with some alcohol.
So quick.
Tekka right away.
Shozo?
The head store's Otoro, it doesn't get better.
Exactly, it's a luxury.
As Endo enjoys his rich Otoro, the 15th store is cleared!
But then!
Alright everyone, a special treat,
A special service for you!
The president's special service!
TN:  From the Tuna's jaw, Kamatoro is exceptionally fatty
It's kamatoro!
Wait...
Wait-hold on-
Does the president understand what we're doing here?
If we can't finish, the next store is cut.
We can't do that!
You can have one each
Thank you very much, president.
We don't get to eat this often.
Yes, very rare.
Hmmpg MMm yum
Everyone manages to finish the president's kamatoro.
Next the 16th store, Sushizanmai Tsukiji Rotary Sushi.
And there's another store just 10 metres away.
You've got to be kidding me.
Let's go.
Not stopping to catch a breath,
The cards they chose?
Akami, ootoro, aburi, negitoro...
...akami!
How many times?!
Damn it, Yama-chan!
Can't you think of anything else?
Hosei-san and Hamda-san matched.
With everyone struggling, they eat their chosen Sushi.
Only one left, Yamasaki.
Hosei-san still hasn't eaten his Akami.
In fact, he hasn't poured his soy sauce yet.
Shozo, make him hurry up, we gotta get to the next store.
There's not much time.
Sorry, but we're all trying our best.
If we don't get past this, No listen,
You didn't help me out.
I will help you.
I'll save you next time.
You will definitely help me next time?
I wil definitely help you
Did you hear that?
It depends on whether or not you can believe him.
At the next place, I will give Hosei-san one thing I cannot finish.
Please actually help me.
I will definitely do that, definitely.
For sure?
Then I'll eat this.
The things this man does are so different from what he says.
Finshed! Thank you very much! Next store!
This store here.
Hosei-san, we're going!
The 17th store, Sushizanmi Chuoko Bekkan.
It's Bekkan!
Let's go!
Everyone has heavy steps.
Hosei-san!
Yama-chan, what's your status?
Just impossible now.
What do you mean?
Do you give up?
Not a give up, but,
Here, Vacuum
Cause this is the halfway point, right?
A chance of two seperate cards, if you get the Vaccum, Fujiwara will eat all the tuna.
However, the other card,
A loss.
Loss -> Everyone Eats Together
It's not unconditional?
Who said it's not?
That is not on.
Cause there's a chance to win here.
Yama-chan, do you want to take it?
Yama-chan will try the vacuum challenge.
Choose well.
Shall I go?
Sorry,
This is the most important part.
The performance.
Just slam the card on the table.
A failure!
No vacuum chance for you!
So everyone, choose your card.
No retries?
Look at Hosei-san.
He looks like Hanagata from "Kyojin no Hoshi."
The Tuna on his head...
The bangs.
The tuna is like his bangs.
Yama-chan, choose.
How many did I eat?
Everyone ate a lot!
Housei-san-
I ate THIRTY ONE!
31 pieces is the same as 31 stores.
11 stores.
Everyone's amount is around the same.
It's the same.
Here we go..........ready, flip.
Akami matched!
Hosei-san this is unacceptable.
How many times is this?
I'm eating so much.
Everyone is eating.
Endo didn't eat.
I just saved you Hosei-san, one store back.
You did.
I believed he was gonna help me here.
He said he definitely would.
I mean next episode.
During the next series.
I'm still fine with that.
Alright, here we go.
Hosei-san, could you take your Akami?
You see it right there, right?
Everyone is finished.
Oh, he's going for it!  That was speedy.
Good, keep up that tempo.
Yama-chan, finish this, and use the vacuum chance again.
I'm in agony.
We're also suffering.
We really are.
Well done, finished!
Next store!
Your footsteps are heavy!
This is really tough.
With heavier footsteps than the other four, Yamasaki....
"I'm so hungry!"
"I'll make it to the 31st store"
A different Yamasaki,
is present now.
I don't wanna see the store.
The next store, Rotary Sushizanmai Tsukiji 2nd Store.
Time for Sushi again.
Let's go.
Yama-chan, use the card again.
Yes again.
Should I?
It's up to you, Yama-chan.
So Hosei-san?
Yama-chan, please pull the "vacuum" card.
Grab it please.
Please, the vacuum.
Ready, Hosei-san?
Go ahead!
How unfortunate!
I give up.
It's over!  He said it!
Yamasaki pays everyone's bill!
So the total is: 33,989 yen, Hosei-san.
Unfortunatley, whoever gives up must pay.
He isn't speaking a single word.
He understands the situation.
You can pay right?