The First Gaki no Tsukai Arahende Chiki Chiki!! 1 Million Yen Octopus Ball Eating Challenge! Covering 37 Stores over 23 Districts in Tokyo~!!
0 0 m -330 -72.25 b -341.875 -73.75 -373.875 -72.25 -370.5 -45.375 b -372.25 -30.625 -340.125 -1.125 -331.75 0 b -318.25 8.5 -313.125 -1.125 -304.75 -2.875 b -294.625 -12.75 -284.5 -16.125 -274.375 -40.875 b -271 -63.75 -292.875 -65.625 -294.625 -67.5 b -308.125 -73.75 -319.875 -72.25 -330 -72.25 m -321.625 -63.75 b -306.375 -67.5 -286.125 -57.625 -289.5 -47.5 b -301.375 -60.375 -311.5 -60.375 -321.625 -63.75 m -407.625 -208.875 b -400.875 -208.875 -343.5 -197.5 -352 -121.75 b -363.75 -73.75 -395.875 -50.625 -406 -45.375 b -411 -43.875 -438 -22.75 -475.125 -57.625 b -483.625 -73.75 -500.5 -92.25 -488.625 -133.125 b -483.625 -149.625 -475.125 -181.375 -444.75 -199.125 b -436.375 -203.875 -422.875 -212.25 -407.625 -208.875 m -255.75 -212.25 b -252.375 -212.25 -211.875 -223.875 -176.5 -162.75 b -171.375 -148 -157.875 -129.625 -166.375 -83.625 b -176.5 -45.375 -193.375 -43.875 -203.5 -40.875 b -211.875 -40.875 -223.75 -30.625 -264.25 -58.875 b -277.75 -70.125 -298 -77.125 -306.375 -123.25 b -304.75 -123.25 -325 -153.25 -282.75 -199.125 b -274.375 -206.125 -265.875 -212.25 -255.75 -212.25 m -411 -157.875 b -458.25 -149.625 -431.25 -98.5 -409.375 -103.75 b -402.625 -103.75 -387.375 -107.125 -384 -129.625 b -389.125 -156.625 -399.25 -154.375 -411 -157.875 m -411 -142.875 b -400.875 -146.5 -395.875 -133.125 -397.5 -129.625 b -397.5 -117 -407.625 -117 -412.75 -117 b -419.5 -118.125 -422.875 -124.875 -421.125 -133.125 b -421.125 -136.5 -417.75 -142.875 -411 -142.875 m -407.625 -136.5 b -412.75 -134.625 -411 -128.5 -407.625 -128.5 b -404.25 -128.5 -400.875 -134.625 -407.625 -136.5 m -244 -157.875 b -281.125 -151.375 -264.25 -100.125 -244 -104.875 b -237.25 -103.75 -220.375 -107.125 -220.375 -136.5 b -225.375 -156.625 -238.875 -157.875 -244 -157.875 m -244 -142.875 b -222 -142.875 -228.75 -117 -240.625 -117 b -244 -115.125 -257.5 -118.125 -254.125 -133.125 b -254.125 -136.5 -252.375 -142.875 -244 -142.875 m -240.625 -136.5 b -245.625 -133.125 -242.25 -126.625 -238.875 -128.5 b -233.875 -129.625 -237.25 -136.5 -240.625 -136.5 m -414.375 -128.5 b -417.75 -128.5 -416.125 -123.25 -414.375 -123.25 b -412.75 -123.25 -411 -128.5 -414.375 -128.5 m -245.625 -126.625 b -249 -126.625 -247.375 -121.75 -245.625 -121.75 b -244 -121.75 -242.25 -126.625 -245.625 -126.625 m -500.5 -238.875 l -156.25 -238.875 l -156.25 95.625 l -500.5 95.625 m -159.625 -235.5 l -497.125 -235.5 l -497.125 92.625 l -159.625 92.625
TPF
Woo~
Thank you very much!
Cocorico
Downtown
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Hosei
6 months ago we did one on dumplings, right?
Kazuhiro Fujiwara
License
Takafumi Inomoto
What's with that smile?
Can you wait until the train passes?
For some reason, there's always a train at the start of our recordings
There's no helping it then
Sorry, there's nothing we can do
27 stores is a hell of a challenge...
Awesome!
There's no way we could have finished all those dumplings
Delicious~
Challenge: To eat at 32 Stores over 23 Districts in Tokyo
Gyoza King food marathon
They each ate one piece of dumpling at each store, and they were about to reach the goal of 32 stores, however
Oh shit
It's not open
When they reached the 29th store, it was already closed. All they could do was retire from the challenge
Although close to finishing, the challenge ended abruptly
This time, they will take on the challenge of eating at Gindako's stores in 23 Districts of Tokyo
37 Stores over 23 Districts in Tokyo
Total Domination Challenge
At each of the 37 stores, the 5 of them will aim to eat up an 8 pack of Octopus balls
The 5 of them will eat up an 8 pack of Octopus balls at each store
Each person must eat at least one, the remaining 3 can be split either way
Each person must eat one,
The remaining 3 are free to be eaten by anyone
If they complete the challenge, there will be a million yen prize
The prize for completing all 37 stores is 1 million yen!
However, in the event that someone retires, the challenge ends there,
And the person who retired has to pay for all of the accumulated bill
If any one of them retires, the challenge is over!
and the person who retired will have to pay for all of the accumulated bill by himself
What's up?
You barely ate any dumplings
I ate so many dumplings
No you didn't
The guys from the shop were all shocked I ate so much
You barely ate any at all
They edited that part, to maintain my image...
They were shocked at how little you ate!
If I remember correctly
I fucking love  takoyaki though!
I fucking love takoyaki though!
He's said it! You better eat loads then!
Because my own grandfather
used to run an octopus ball store
It's true, I'm telling you all
You know this, right? My father used to sell octopus balls
Octopus ball store?
This is the first time I've heard of this
He died so hard though!
I'm a little confused
with this costume we're wearing
When I asked the staff
"What's with the get-up?"
They said "We're mocking Osaka"
This is taking the piss out of Osaka?
This is their image of taking the piss out of Osaka?..
They said it right to my face "We're taking the piss out of Osaka"
That's messed up
That's really nasty
Yeah, what's that all about?
Because the stores are opening
Let's start right now. Ready?
Start!
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Elliot &
Otviss
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
Hans (ind)
Mickstar
(Team Gaki)
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on Youtube individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own. Please go back and support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit. You can download episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching!
Proofreader:
Translator:
Typesetter:
____________________________________________________________________
I've only eaten one rice ball
You already ate?
Why the hell did you eat rice balls!
It was only one
Why'd you have to go and eat something?
Haven't you guys eaten anything?
It's no good starting on an empty stomach, so I thought that if I had a rice ball, I'll feel better
1st Store Shinbashi Store
Here we are
Welcome to our store. We've got customers
Store no. 1 Shinbashi Store
Are we the first customers today?
Looks like it
There are many flavors to choose from
Cheese w/ Fish Roe
Octopus ball
Spring Onion
Teriyaki w/ Egg
You guys can pick any one you want
Let's just go with the Original flavor then?
This one?
Yea, just the standard one
First up, of the 4 choices, the first flavor chosen is the Original
1 Pack 500 Yen
Original
You all must be starving
I'm so hungry
If you're that hungry, you probably want 2 or 3 pieces, right?
I would...
You've been saying that for ages
Excuse me, the food's arrived
Can we decide who will eat how many?
Yes, that's fine
So who's gonna eat how many?
Just start eating first
Anyway, we each have to have one piece
It's really is huge. Let's eat.
Ittadakimasu!
Wow, you can eat it in one go, huh?
This is really good
That's because this is the first store
It's real good
Soooo good
It's delicious
It's very delicious
Is it really?
Really feels like we can win this one
You all probably feel like eating more because you are all starving
For now at least
Matsumoto
I mean, I can do it...
We're starting with tricks already
It's not
that kind of game, right!?
We know that but everyone is finding it easy at this point
Sure, then I'll have 2 pieces but, how about the rest?
We're at the first place, how did it suddenly
become this situation?
I know, that was quick
Fine fine fine
I'll eat one then
It's the Downtown Duo
Oh both of Downtown...
Someone else can have the last one
You look like you want it
You look terrified, why are you so scared?
What are you afraid of?
I would but,
It was bigger than I thought
Just eat it, Yama-chan
I'll take it because it's the first place.
The youngest should stay hungry for later on
You say 'young' but, he's 38 years old
Relative to me, of course
Complete
Okay, all done
Easy...
We've got a schedule to keep, so let's move on to the next store
We're just going to overlook the fact
That he swept bonito onto the floor
So this is what having 2 pieces feels like
1st Store
2nd Store
Ginza HQ
Shinbashi Store
Well, since this challenge will take a while
There will be time to digest
I see
My father
made smaller octopus balls
Yea, they're usually smaller in Osaka, also the fried style is uncommon
Yea, no fried ones
During my time
It was 10 Yen per piece
Yea, it was
It's the headquarters, right?
Yea, Gindako's headquarters
GINdako?
Oh that's why it's called
The "gin" in Ginza, you mean
It could be
Ask them later, Tanaka
Sure thing
Why can't you just ask them yourself
It's probably not so embarrassing for him
I don't think that question will anger them
We're here, let's go
Store no. 2 Ginza HQ
Ginza headquarters
This is my first time here
Wow, it's huge, isn't it?
It really has a headquarters feel to it
It's really well built
This is so cool
It's awesome
Let's have this one here
Spring Onion Ball
Thank you very much
We're going up to the 2nd floor
We must strive to achieve the goal, guys
Didn't you have something you wanted to ask?
That's right
Oh right, about the headquarters
The "Gin" in Gindako
Why didn't you ask them? What the hell!
Is it good?
similar to the one in Ginza
The Origin of Tsukiji Gindako
Tsukiji Gindako hopes to have a store
Let's have one each first
With this flavour, the last piece is probably the best tasting one
Spring Onion Ball
That's because it doesn't sit heavily
It's quite easy to get it down
What about these 3 pieces?
If we go in order
then Tanaka and myself haven't eaten yet
Yea, we haven't had our share
So we'll each have one
Yamazaki have one
I can still go for sure
Have you
been planning for that?
That's no good, stop that
Complete
Thanks for the meal
Okay, let's move on to the next store
2nd Store
3rd Store
Ginza HQ
Ningyocho Store
We finish so quickly
Since we finish so fast wouldn't it better to bring the octopus balls to us instead?
Yea, I agree
(Menu) Want to pick the next one first?
Okay, let's have a look then
We're having Teriyaki w/ Egg Ball next, aren't we?
Teriyaki w/ Egg Ball
Shall we try Teriyaki w/ Egg Ball next?
40 pieces means... 1 pack each
Johnny Depp?
AD Tsuruta (Age 25)
Gaki no Tsukai's
Johnny Depp
He gave up after 10 pieces
(During the simulation)
10 is quite a lot, isn't it
He's so bad, giving up after eating only 10 pieces
10 is quite little, isn't it
He's not good at eating
Because he's old
What, he's still so young
We're like the same age...
Gaki no Tsukai's
We're talking about Johnny Depp
Oh, you guys were talking about Johnny Depp
Huh? Wait, what
aren't we the same age?
What is?
He's like 40 something, right?
Yes, the real Johnny Depp is...
We're not talking about that Johnny Depp
Oh, aren't you?
You had no idea?
You think Johnny Depp
ate Gindako octopus balls?
When he came to Japan
He could have tried some
You're senility is really starting to be scary
He's been saying that a lot recently
Last time he said something similar as well
It was a quiz
But he went and gave out the answer
Whilst saying the question?..
We've arrived! Let's go
3rd Store Ningyocho Store
Again? It's too soon
We're only up to the 3rd store
3rd Store Ningyocho Store
Come on. This will be easy
This one's made of wood too
Hello, good afternoon
Can we get it to go?
Teriyaki w/ Egg please
Thank you very much~
1 Pack 600 Yen
Teriyaki Sauce w/ Egg & Mayonnaise
They've put too much teriyaki sauce
The youngest person should have the one with the most toppings
Yea, I'd say so too
That one over there
As the youngest I'll have it
Is it good?
Have another
Okay, I will
There are still 3 pieces
He's going for it
He's seriously going for it
Downtown Duo, could you stop
putting down your chopsticks so quickly?
It's not over yet
Yea, could you stop putting them down so fast?
At least hold on to them
Hold on to them please
I want to eat it too much
You can have another
I'm holding back. I don't want to seem selfish.
Please please, here Hamada have one
Well if Yama-chan says so
Enjoy, Downtown Duo
Oh, what?
Don't transfer your topping over
Did you guys see that? He's trying to put more on mine
It doesn't matter
He dumped his all onto Hamada's
All done. We've finished up here
Complete
On to the next store. Thank you very much
3rd Store
4th Store
LaQua Store
Ningyocho Store
We've just barely started
Tanaka's not even trying
Wait wait, hold on. Don't say that
But it's written down right here
I'll be depressed if you say that
It's only Tanaka
Just like a Gravure Idol
Only 4 pieces is no good
I don't think having 5 pieces
Come on! It's just 1 piece
would make you a man
We're here! Let's go!
Store no. 4 LaQua Store
Good afternoon~
Excuse us
It's not what we had in mind
Store no. 4 LaQua Store
Yea, this store's different
Cheese Mentaiko
The cheese one
It was surprising
Yes, Cheese Mentaiko
Thanks
The octopus bits are quite huge
They're huge, aren't they?
Food's ready
Please have a seat
Let's dig in
One piece each
Bon appetit
Time to try Cheese Mentaiko
It's hot
How is it? Is the flavor good?
A little hot though
It's quite hot
Tanaka, have another
That's trying the least
You're the one
If you say that to me, I will go for it then
It was so bloody hot
Endo's going for a second piece
The youngest person should have the last piece
Yama-chan
Oh right right
Here, I'm just going to rest...
I think it's better
if I allow Yama-chan to get on TV a bit
Even though it's the tastiest one...
But he's dropping it all
Are you guys all done?
Complete
This one was quite easy
Okay, let's move on to the next one
Shall we go for the Original or the spring Onion one next?
4th Store
5th Store
LaQua Store
Yoshiike Okachimachi Store
Have we gone through the list already?
Look at Endo and I
Well, it's because we're the youngest
We can eat as much as we want
None of you have even eaten 1 pack's worth
Up till now...
No one's gone
"I'll have the other 3 pieces"
I guess so
Yea, that's true
It's fine if someone wants to
But if someone does
It's not out of the question since
I see, it'll help
It helps the digestion process
Right, I get it
We wouldn't know but, each of our bodies digest at its own pace
So you're saying that
Tanaka should eat 4 pieces next
You really haven't eaten enough
"It's Tanaka's turn to eat 4 pieces"
Hold on a bit
With that Tanaka will be up to 10 pieces
That's quite true
That's right, you should give it a try
Then we'll see how he feels after
Tanaka goes first, then Endo goes
I wonder then,
during that, will you guys have time to digest?
One person slowly eats one by one
It's worth to try that to see how effective it'll be
While the other 4 of us wait around
While the rest of you wait around
I get it now
What number store are we up to now?
It's the 4th
We only up to the 4th store
That's so bad...
It's still a long way away
It's only the 4th store, but you're already frustrated
37 (stores)
is rather many isn't it
Frankly speaking, with 23 districts
eating at 1 store for each district should be fine
What do you mean "should be fine"?
He's spouting out some
business strategies now
That's Gindako's job so...
Octopus balls~~~
5th Store Yoshiike Okachimachi Store
There it is, I see it
This one here
Is there really?
I guess you're right
5th Store Yoshiike Okachimachi Store
Don't forget your strategy
This is where we'll try out Tanaka's tactic
Spring Onion Ball please
Spring Onion Ball
Please have a seat, guys
No no, Tanaka should be the one sitting
Tanaka's the important one here, the rest of us are just extras
We will just follow his lead
Anyway, you guys have to eat one piece each
Firstly, you guys have your one piece each
As usual, first, we have one piece each
Maybe I should have brought my own chopsticks?
What?
My own chopsticks
It's good
Really? Well, I guess for now it is
Tanaka, are you sure you can take 4 pieces?
Yea, first I'll just, you know
If I do this here, we can start rotating...
Shut up and eat
Go on!
Hamada, could you please
That's a sign of affection
refrain from violent behavior?
He's sacrificing himself, so you shouldn't be treating him like that...
Yeah exactly
I'm sacrificing myself here
During my turn, make sure you don't try that
Woah, he's eaten 3 pieces already
He's finished them all
Complete
Finally, he's actually trying
We're going on foot now
5th Store
6th Store
Ueno Ameyoko Store
Yoshiike Okachimachi Store
It's not far away
It's close by
Let's have a look at the scoreboard. With the 4 pieces that Tanaka just ate, he's up to 10 pieces now
I'm on the top of the leaderboard now
We have 7, 7, 8, 8, and 10 pieces
So, for the 6th store... Endo?
I'll have a go
If Endo does finish them, he'll be up to 12 pieces
Are we in Amemura?
Yea, from here all the way to the Ueno station
Don't you mean Ameyoko?
But you were saying Amemura
Right, Amemura's in Osaka
We've arrived at the store
Store no. 6 Ueno Ameyoko Store
We can eat inside this time
Oh, you're right
Cheese Mentaiko
Cheese Mentaiko please
Are you serious?
Wow, this is unexpected
The cold is our biggest obstacle
This one will take a bit of your energy away..
Yea, the cold's not helping, is it
SO, WHEN IT'S COLD OUT
DOES IT SELL BETTER?
I guess so
You're so bloody loud
Lower your voice a little
You're being too loud
Like you're back at school...
Thanks. Here we go
Shozo, you're up
Yup
Are we eating outside?
Yea, we're eating it outside
You can have the whole pack
Wait, the rule says we've got to eat one each
But I ate one piece just now
First, one piece each
Here I go
I just noticed, you guys always take chopsticks over toothpicks, huh?
Bon appetit
It's hot, ow
Tanaka has taken his turn, now Endo is up
Taking on the challenge to eat 4 pieces of Cheese Mentaiko
Tanaka, you did it too, right?
He's almost finished, well done
All done
Complete
6th Store
7th Store
Kinshicho Station Terminal Store
Ueno Ameyoko Store
As expected, eating 4 pieces makes me quite full. I'm not sure I can go on
What the hell is this whispering! You two
Sorry
These two here are planning something sinister
No no, we're not
A SINISTER PLOT!?
It's because we both had to eat 4 pieces
Calm down calm down
AT THE NEXT STORE 4 PIECES FOR YOU!
That's the punishment for your evil plotting!
No no, there's no way
I can still keep going
I was just thinking
I don't think it's a very efficient strategy
While one person is eating
the rest are just standing around watching
I did think of that too
The audience won't be
entertained enough
I felt so very bored
But that was quite obvious from the plan
Was that not what you were expecting?
I'm sure I can do the next one
So, I'll be
having 4 pieces
You want to try?
Okay, Matsumoto's having 4
Lastly, I will
eat 4 pieces
Wait, what do you mean by "lastly"?
Actually, I don't see why Hamada can't be next
Would you be okay?
If you don't have 4 pieces now
are you really going to be okay?
What do you mean?
I don't quite understand
what you meant by "okay"
It's because he's so worried for you
Well, it's about lunchtime now
If you're fine,
then I'll go now
I still don't get what
your "okay" means
Ask him
Hamada doesn't quite understand
what you mean by "okay"
I'm just wondering if
he doesn't go now, will he be okay later...
I worry that he won't be
if he doesn't go now...
Store no. 7 Kinshicho Station Terminal Store
Okay, we've arrived
Let's go
So cold~
Over here
It's so cold~
I'm freezing
Store no. 7 Kinshicho Station Terminal Store
We're counting on you
YOSSSSHHHHHHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!!!
Takoyaki, this one!
Original please
Original
Sorry, I didn't quite order properly
So we'll have one piece each
Only one piece each
I'm going to have my one piece first
Should I put on the mayonnaise
As you like
Excuse me, coming through
It looks hot
There's 4 pieces for you
It's good
I see
Pick up
the next piece
If you could pick up the pace
Matsumoto, since we've got a schedule to keep to
If you could increase your pace a little
It'd be great if you could hurry up
That would be really great
What are you rolling it about for?
Just go one after another...
makes it easier to eat
Yea, probably
Are you guys serious? Should I eat them all?
Ah I see
*Matsumoto hits his mic
He just admitted it
He really did...
Last piece
He's done it. Good job
Complete
All finished
YAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
7th Store
8th Store
Kinshicho Station Terminal Store
Shinkoiwa Store
We're running short on time, we have to get to the next store now
Hey, umm......
Since I already ate
a rice ball before we started
That's your own problem
Why'd you go and eat it?
Store no. 8 Shinkoiwa Store
It's up to you this time
At the Shinkoiwa Store coming up, Yamasaki will take up the challenge
Store no. 8 Shinkoiwa Store
Here it is
Spring Onion Ball please
Spring Onion Ball
One Spring Onion Ball coming up. Here you go, thanks
We're each going to have one piece first
Could you guys please take more of the spring onion?
You all are barely getting any
Yes yes, please have more
It's good
You've only had one, and already look full
It shouldn't be a problem, right?
You just look
like an old geezer...
He's taking his time to chew
He's only moving his mouth
Here I go!
Nicely done
All finished
Complete
8th Store
9th Store
Koiwa Popo Store
Shinkoiwa Store
So, Hamada, you're having 4 pieces of
Teriyaki w/ Egg,
is that okay?
Yea, Teriyaki w/ Egg
Teriyaki w/ Egg?
He already agreed to it earlier
He's really going senile
9th Store Koiwa popo Store
It's still far from the halfway mark
At this store, Hamada will take up the 4 piece challenge
9th Store Koiwa popo Store
Teritama please
Teritama
Yes acknowledged
Teritama or  is back again
Thank you
Let's have a seat over that way
It looks really dense
Yea, it does, doesn't it
This one's not going to be easy
We should continue with this strategy
and just switch the flavors
I agree, we should change the flavors
What do you mean?
We should decide one flavor
For each person, agree?
Hey wait wait
"Teritama" will be
Hamada's
No way no way
I see
"Hamada's Teritama"
Shall we do that then?
so each person eats their own one...
Yes, he's done
Complete
All done
How well will the 4 piece strategy work?
I need someone to help me
Will they be able to make it through all 37 stores in 23 districts?
Will they be drinking to celebrate or drown their sorrows?
I do not want to eat anymore
Next week, the exciting conclusion unfolds!
Mmm~ That was good