Episode Aired: 2004.12.05
Subbed by: Mickstar813 & HouseiGIFs
You know how I am really talented with music?
2 years ago, he made original
songs for the Gaki members
Narrator:
Noda Keiichi
I made you all songs...
to try and live off royalties
for the rest of his life.
Am I actually going to sing?
Yeah.
We were all shocked by his talent.
Why?
To sell...
It explodes in the middle of the town
♫ Machi no man'naka de haretsusuru ♫
The desire that I cannot suppress anymore
♫ Osae kirenai yokubō to ♫
It seems
♫ Mou ♫
That we've come
♫ Modorenai ♫
To a point where we can't return anymore
♫ Tokoro made kita mitaida ♫
The theme of this song makes you look so lame...
However, no one from
the music industry called...
So tonight, in order to save
his reputation, Yamasaki will try again.
Yamasaki Produce
It's been 2 years since the last one,
this is the 2nd installment of Yamasaki Produce.
Yamasaki Housei
Cocorico
Downtown
Endo Shozo
I totally forgot about it.
It's been that long?
Matsumoto
Hitoshi
We've all done the filming
this time already, right?
Yes we have.
I am just done...
But seriously,
we've actually done three songs
Downtown
Hamada
Masatoshi
this time.
Right.
A solo for Endo-san.
Yeah.
Then a duet for
Matsumoto-san and Tanaka-san.
Wow awesome, that'll be incredible.
Yeah, what the hell was that about?
Cocorico
Tanaka Naoki
And lastly, all 5 of us,
with Hamada-san being the main lead.
Well, we did it together...
Yamasaki made the song and lyrics
And they're all really good songs this time.
Last time, unfortunately...
none of them became CDs
You say unfortunately but we had no plans to make it into a CD anyway.
No, but seriously Matsumoto-san,
your song last time...
It seems...
was good--
♫ Mou ♫
That we've come
♫ Modorenai ♫
To a point--
♫ Tokoro made-- ♫
You're going to continue singing!?
There was a bit of a laugh
from the staff so just leave it.
Man, that's lame.
It really is...
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todokanai ♫
The music this time is also awesome.
Oh?
First up, Endo.
Endo up first.
It's a solo, right?
Oh this one, I've not
got a clue about it.
Me neither.
This will be the first time we see it.
So I'm looking forward to seeing it.
During Rehearsal
When I think of your song,
my creativity just goes crazy.
Oh, well I'm very thankful to hear that.
Yeah, right?
So, can you listen to this once?
Um... wait, just before that,
last time...
it was death metal right?
Right.
Wow...
This is...
Last time, you were awful.
Yeah, honestly...
You were like the Endo who I hate the most...
I hate that kind of Endo...
So this time,
it's totally different, seriously.
Really?
I want you to sing this seriously
and to hear your beautiful voice.
Ah, OK.
So let's take a listen first.
That unforgettable Summer
♫ Wasurerarenai Summer ♫
It's actually Japanese this time.
Like properly...
Yeah.
Huh?
There was a girl who had just split up,
alone at Enoshima, by the sea
♫ Enoshima no umi ja wakareta onna ga hitori ♫
Without showing tears
♫ Namida misezu ni ♫
So listen and make sure you understand
it's about summer--
Wait a second...
It's a medley?
Yep.
But I've only just listened to
this song for the first time ever...
and I have to do a medley suddenly?
Yeah, so...
In my head
you've already released loads of hit songs.
Wait a minute...
I don't get the meaning of this.
Seriously, in my head I just
started imagining loads of things
and I got loads of good ideas for songs.
So I got the best part of each song,
so instead of one song
I combined all of them together.
Look at it like this,
I'm betting all this on you
Seriously...?
Endo's Solo Medley
Yamasaki Produce
Endo will sing: The Summer Medley.
Lyrics & Composition by
Yamasaki Housei
Summer Man 2006 Medley
Sung by Endo Shozo
That outfit...
That Unforgettable Summer
I have definitely listened to something similar to this...
That unforgettable Summer
♫ Wasurerarenai Summer ♫
What the hell is with that?
I was just doing as I was told.
That Girl of Enoshima
There was a girl who had just split up,
alone at Enoshima, by the sea
♫ Enoshima no umi ja wakareta onna ga hitori  ♫
Without showing tears
♫ Namida misezu ni ♫
This is...
You've definitely heard similar,right?
At the Yokohama district,
there was a girl who had just been dumped
♫ Yokohama no machi ja furareta onna ga hitori ♫
She didn't have her umbrella up
♫ Kasa mo sasazu ni ♫
And she kept walking
♫ Aruiteru ♫
Oh, so he sings a number of songs.
Awesome, right?
Truly.
It's going to change here again?
What's going on?
The Sea '06
How do you do a medley when it's new to you?
The blue sea is calling out to me
♫ Aoi umi ga yonde iru ♫
Like, no one knows these songs in the first place!
Tonight, it moves me like the waves
♫ Koyoi nami no you ni tsuredasu ♫
My burnt skin shines bright
♫ Yaketa suhada mabushiku ♫
It starts a fire in my heart
♫ Ore no mune o kogasu ♫
Summer day
♫ Summer day ♫
To You Who I Love
The road which I was
used to seeing after rainfall
♫ Ameagari ni minareta michi o ♫
The way he sings is hilarious.
This is so screwed up!
Oh yeah
♫ Oh yeah ♫
You're just impersonating that person...
With you who has not
♫ Nanimo kawaranai ♫
No, this is Endo.
Really?
Yeah.
This is something you do like 10 years down the line!
Changed at all
♫ Kimi to ♫
I can say finally for
the first time with all my heart
♫ Sutekina omoi o mune ni ♫
Oh yeah
♫ Oh yeah ♫
With all my heart
♫ Hajimete ieru ♫
That I love you
♫ Sukidayo ♫
That Unforgettable Summer
That once in a lifetime Summer
♫ Ichido kagiri no Summer ♫
Once in a lifetime Summer...
This is hilarious
Just this part, I like...
4 songs...
That Unforgettable Summer,
The Girl of Enoshima,
What's this? Sea '06
Sea '06.
To You Who I Love,
And lastly--
The very last thing he said...
the, "Once in a lifetime summer,"
that's a bit depressing...
No, not at all, it's to encourage people to
enjoy their summer and Endo
got his message across.
And, as everyone was saying before
I was just suddenly given a medley.
The lyrics are fine, right?
You didn't rip it off from someone, right?
No, of course not.
I'm sure I've listened to something similar.
Yeah, me too.
Well yeah,
you've heard of Enoshima right?
You've heard of the place
Enoshima, that's all.
Really?
That's what you're confusing...
Even the way he sang...
Um--
Half way through, it became
a bit like Sen Masao...
Right, shall we go to the next one?
Tanaka and Matsumoto's duet.
We did...
This is something
you wouldn't normally see too.
That's true.
Yeah.
This is really pop-like.
During Rehearsal
Pop?
It's really pop, watch, from here...
This is pop?
The prelude is really long.
So as a present,
I'm allowing you to do what you want.
I don't want a present like that...
Not yet, not yet, see?
Oh, really?
Damn, this is gonna be difficult.
It really is long.
It's so long...
It's great for him
♫ Kare ni wa saikou ♫
But I feel lonely
♫ Dakedo oreni wa kodoku dake ♫
Now is the time
♫ Imanara zekkou ♫
This is the last chance
♫ Kore ga saigo no chansu da ze ♫
Umm....
Maybe you should ask Kinki Kids to do this...
* Popular pop music duo (1997 - Present)
I think...
I don't think we can do this...
No, no.
You can.
This is awful.
Is it?
My face is gonna go so red.
This is a song for someone in their teens.
Like someone young.
That's right, young...
He's in his 30's, I'm in my 40's...
But it's great that you understand this song
is meant to be sung by someone in their teens.
That's exactly how I made it.
Tanaka, when you sang last time
Yeah.
that was a 16 year old girl.
I always think
♫ Itsumo omou no ♫
It's Noppo-san.
When I feel you next to me
♫ Anata o soba de kanjita toki ♫
I know...
He's gay?
But this time, you get to sing as a boy.
I guess you're right.
So even that, he's closer to being himself.
Yeah, you are.
I guess so.
Oh man, this is tough.
Honestly,
I want to see a Matsumoto-san
we've never seen before.
Like really pop.
It's great for hi....
♫ Kare ni wa sai... ♫
I do want to see that too.
It's so funny.
Damn, this is tough.
I really do.
This is hard...
Just do it like facing forward.
OK.
No seriously,
I will just make you do it all day...
No we are trying our best.
Seriously, we are.
More like this!
Wait, how?
Like this.
This looks awful.
Stop trying to make it sound like this is cool...
And then what?
Like this, you know...
Youngsters do this all the time.
There, yeah, yeah.
Oh like this?
Right, right.
That's it, yeah, yeah!
Is it really like this...?
It's so different to what you said before...
Just do it like that.
After this
Matsumoto & Tanaka's song!!
Matsumoto and Tanaka perform their duet,
Matstumoto & Tanaka's Duet
Yamasaki Produce
a hot tune to reach your heart.
Lyrics & Composition by
Yamasaki Housei
Sung by
Matsumoto Hitoshi
& Tanaka Naoki
Woah, incredible...
This was really hard.
This is something else.
It was so hard.
This is awful.
This is something else.
There was 30 seconds of this.
30 seconds!
Just the prelude?
It's great for him
♫  Kare ni wa saikou ♫
But I just feel lonely
♫ Dakedo oreni wa kodoku dake ♫
Now is the time
♫ Imanara zekkou ♫
This is the last chance
♫ Kore ga saigo no chansu da ze ♫
With my dancing that will make you tremble
♫ Kurueru youna dancing de ♫
I'm going to drop it tonight
♫ Otosu ze konya wa ♫
And with my steely gaze
♫ Itetsuku youna hitomi de ♫
I'm going to score tonight
♫ Kimeru ze konya wa ♫
You can do it
♫ Kitto kiminara ♫
Let's fly away together
♫ Tobou ze futari de fly away ♫
Until our eyes open
♫ Megasameru made ♫
Far away
♫ Touku ♫
Let's go, the two of us, just run away
♫ Ikouze futari de run away ♫
Wow, this is something else.
I know.
Until we forget
♫ Wasureru made ♫
This is so lame.
It really is...
More and more
♫ Motto motto♫
Let's fly away together
♫ Tobou ze futari de fly away ♫
Until our eyes open
♫ Megasameru made ♫
Far away
♫ Touku ♫
Let's go, the two of us, just run away
♫ Ikouze futari de run away ♫
Until we make
♫ Yume ♫
Our dreams come true
♫ Kanau made ♫
Holy shit...
This is so lame.
This really is.
Incredible!
Sure is.
You moved a lot...
Actually, we did it 3 times because
we screwed up a couple of times...
Ah, I get it.
Right.
My body is so tired...
The prelude was 30 seconds...?
Yes.
And you had to do that dance the whole time?
Right.
I thought whilst doing it,
"Someone has done this kind of dance before."
* Comedian Sakata Toshio (1967 - Present)
Sakata Toshio, right?
No, I don't think so.
It looked similar.
I saw him doing it backstage.
The reason why the song
is written is ridiculous too.
So, if we like have an example...
For example, if we have
Endo and Chiaki, married
and then,
Matsumoto falls in love with Chiaki.
Yeah.
So he falls in love, and this isn't a song
between Endo and Matsumoto as rivals
it's a song about me and Matsumoto-san
where I am supporting him to win...
That's so complicated.
It is complicated, there's 4 people in this story.
What the hell is that...?
And when you include
Sakata Toshio, there's 5 of us.
Yeah, and it becomes complicated.
There's no reason to
include him anyway, but...
"I'm going to score tonight,"
and you reply, "You can do it."
Yeah.
Until our eyes open,
Away and away, More and more.
That's the point.
We tried our best.
And I can't believe that
the producer of that song watches it and
says, "Damn, that's lame."
I can't believe that either.
No...
I couldn't tell when I was watching it live--
I feel so betrayed.
Yeah...
That shouldn't be aired on TV...
I'm really sorry about that.
Yeah...
That was shit!
You're going to admit it?
I mean, that will happen,
but the last one...
This is the one you really like, right?
I do, this song
Yeah, he loves it.
really got good reviews...
From who?
I listen to it in my car,
my daughter remembered
this song and she sings it.
I genuinely cried...
listening to her singing it
Well,
I'm sure your wife was
crying about you crying...
I was really touched.
For a different reason...
The final one
has Hamada in it.
Well, we did it all together
and Yama-chan was part of it too.
I wonder how this one turned out.
Anyway, let's watch it.
OK.
If you would.
Seriously, I want us to go on Kouhaku.
During Rehearsal
No, before that,
it's not even going to be made into a CD.
Wait, does it have to be sold as a CD
for Kouhaku to consider us...?
Well, yeah...
It's about the sales.
But anyway, sing it
and they might really love it.
This song is really awesome.
The song?
Yup.
Oh stars that shine so brightly
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todokanai ♫
So embarassing...
That our hands cannot reach
♫ Hikari kagayaku hoshi-tachi yo ♫
It is...
Somehow, always, please envelop
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
Us who are too weak
♫ Yowa sugiru bokutachi o ♫
Damn, we are really weak, huh?
Somehow, always, please envelop
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
This is tough.
Re~~~
Us who are discouraged
♫ Kujike souna bokutachi o ♫
You go into the next line so quick.
Yeah...
I think that will be impossible.
The last part, right?
So Hamada-san will go...
Somehow, always, envelop
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
Oh, so it goes up.
Us who are
♫ Kujike souna ♫
Discouraged
♫ Bokutachi ♫
♫ o ♫
What was that?
Oi, oi!
You go up again?
It's Hamasho...
* Popular music artist Hamada Shogo (1975 – present)
It goes up?
That was a bit...
Hamada-san does
♫ Bokutachi o ♫
So they go...
♫ Bokutachi o, bokutachi o ♫
Right, right.
Yup.
But seriously,
how weak are we...?
Yeah, we seem so weak...
We are though, when we are alone,
we are a 5 and we are good.
And then this is the first part.
So, "masen," that one
that Tanaka cannot forget
And then...
Oh stars that shine so brightly
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todokanai ♫
That our hands cannot reach
♫ Hikari kagayaku hoshi-tachi yo ♫
We're like drifting
Somehow, always, envelop
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
I know right?
Don't raise your hands.
Us who are too weak
♫ Yowa sugiru bokutachi o ♫
Oh stars that shine so bright--
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todo... ♫
I'm in the center?
That can't be right.
This is seriously messed up!
This is weird!
I can't be in the middle surely?
My position changes so much.
So Tanaka finishes in the middle?
And this last part,
Can we change it?
before, I was singing it with everyone
but it then suddenly
becomes a Hamada solo...
That's really annoying to remember.
OK then here, if all of us sing
then it should be fine, right?
And then Hamada says
the, "Somehow, always..."
Exactly, let's just sing this altogether.
Then why do we have to do this here?
So, just the part it goes slow
at the end, I will sing by myself.
Oh, the final part?
Shall we do that then?
That way...
it might be better...
Well, if that's the case,
the "somehow" part--
Stop complaining!
No, seriously, it's disgusting.
Let's just make the "somehow, always"
part just Hamada's thing here...
Oh, from the start?
Then the "Oh stars..." we sing altogether.
Shall we do that?
Well, put bluntly...
I don't give a shit how we do it...
Umm... he just told you straight out.
No, this is great.
You can't say that.
It's fine.
I just realised, I am getting
so into singing this song!
Yeah, I know!
I was thinking,
"Damn, he's getting into this."
Damn, I just realised, you guys
must be thinking I'm so up for this...
That's good!
No, it's just the planning is crap.
After this
The ultimate song is born!?
"Not an Errand Boy" Theme Song
Gaki no Tsukai
Yamasaki Produce
Lyrics & Composition by
Yamasaki Housei
Sung by
Gaki no Tsukai All Stars
Please watch Tanaka at the end, by the way.
Ah, Yamazaki-san
♫ Ah Yamazaki-san ♫
The star filled sky that we gazed upon
♫ Futari miageta hoshizora ga ♫
That's the kind of face you were making...?
Still rings in my heart as if
♫ Kinou no you ni kono mune ni ♫
That's funny.
It were yesterday
♫ Utsushidasa rete imasu ♫
That's a hilarious face.
Ah, Matsumoto-san
♫ Ah Matsumoto-san ♫
That promise we made that day
♫ Ano hi chikatta yakusoku wa ♫
You are as well!
This is funny
You are so into this!!
Has been shut in the
♫ Kokoro no hikidashi ni ♫
He looks so happy
Right?
I thought I would
do this part properly
Look at you,
you're so into it!
Drawer of my heart
♫ Shimatte imasu ♫
Of course...
Because it's important to me
♫ Taisetsu dakara ♫
I am so sad
♫ Sabishi sugite ♫
I cannot walk alone
♫ Hitori ja arukenai ♫
I shake all lonely
♫ Kodoku ni obieru boku o ♫
Please do not let me go
♫ Hanasanaide ♫
Please hold me tight
♫ Dakishimete ite ♫
Ah, Tanaka-san
♫ Ah Tanaka-san ♫
Did you find the thing you were looking for?
♫ Sagashi mono wa arimashitaka ♫
Me too...
You just don't know what kind of face to make there, right?
You probably know the way to
♫ Kokoro no sukima umeru no wa ♫
Make your heart whole
♫ Kitto wakatte iru hazu ♫
Look at him, only guy wearing a hat.
Ah,Endo-san
♫ Ah Endo-san ♫
Here comes Endo...
That dream that you told me in your room
♫ Kimi no heya de katatta yume ♫
You smiled whilst you nodded
♫ Hohoemi nagara unazuite ita ♫
That kindness
♫ Sono yasashi sa o ♫
I cannot forget
♫ Wasure raremasen ♫
Oh stars that shine so brightly
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todokanai ♫
That our hands cannot reach
♫ Hikari kagayaku hoshi-tachi yo ♫
Somehow, always, please envelop
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
Us, who are too weak
♫ Yowa sugiru bokutachi o ♫
Ah, Hamada-san
♫ Ah Hamada-san ♫
Please take care of your body
♫ Karada ni wa ki o tsukete ♫
That's hilarious.
Even though you always try to act tough
♫ Itsumo tsuyo gatte bakari iru kedo ♫
It is.
We know, we know
♫ Wakatte imasu wakatte imasu ♫
Oh stars that shine so brightly
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todokanai ♫
That our hands cannot reach
♫ Hikari kagayaku hoshi-tachi yo ♫
Somehow, always, please envelop
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
Us, who are too weak
♫ Yowa sugiru bokutachi o ♫
Oh stars that shine so brightly,
♫ Bokura no te ni wa todokanai ♫
That our hands cannot reach
♫ Hikari kagayaku hoshi-tachi yo ♫
Somehow, always, please envelop
♫ Dou ka zutto tsutsunde kure ♫
Us, who are too weak
♫ Yowa sugiru bokutachi o ♫
He's so into it...
He is.
Somehow, always
♫ Dou ka zutto ♫
Please envelop
♫ Tsutsunde kure ♫
Us who are feeling discouraged
♫ Kujike souna bokutachi o ♫
Watch Tanaka...
Does he do something?
Yeah, he does.
Eh...?
Woah...
What are you doing...?
What the hell were you doing?
We said "hands up."
What happened?
What were you doing?
Well, um...
I got a bit carried away...
You do get touched really easily
by these kind of things...
Yeah...
In Yoshimoto, you get touched the most.
How is this, you all sang your feelings and...
isn't it great?
We don't usually sing and have to move about.
Yeah
I don't know...
It was great, it's a fantastic song.
This was your favourite song, right?
Yeah, I want to get onto,
I want to get onto Kouhaku.
You all went on?
Right!
Yeah, we did.
Except you.
We've all been on it...
Right.
Right?
I can't accept that.
But even if we get
onto Kouhaku as a 5...
Uh-huh, yeah.
It will be like, "Ah, Ezure-san..."
What?
He's got nothing to do with this though!
Assistant Director
Ezure
He's not wearing a belt today...
Oh yeah...
* Mochi placed one on top of another
That's right.. He looks like a Kagamimochi.
Amazing...
We can do it.
They won't be interested...
Music producers who are watching this,
we WILL release a CD!
We WILL?
No we won't.
Anyone who really wants us to release it with you,
we will await your call.
Everyone, bow your heads.
Please consider us!
What if Tanaka and my song gathers interest?
The duet?
Yeah.
Yours and Tanaka's one?
Well yeah, let's just release it.
Release it and see how lame it is...
Producer...
Let's watch it once more.