First time on Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende CHIKI CHIKI
TN: The guest for this episode (ぺえ) is someone that describes themselves as a "genderless man".
"I'm the one who understands them the best..."
"Anyways, you'd look great in this thing" - Peey edition!
He was so loud I couldn't tell what he said. His voice broke.
His voice broke.
It was quite loud, quite loud indeed.
He couldn't control it.
That's a bit too far.
I feel bad for Hamada now.
I'm surpri-
Ow owowowow
He's trying so hard to do his best.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't talk to him like that.
We've done nine people so far...
...so he will be the tenth.
Wow, we've done that many?
A special series on Gaki, where the members buy gifts for guests based on their interests.
I don't think this one was that difficult.
Eh, really?
Cause, basically, if it's colorful or furry it's good enough.
That's a bit too simple.
Let's introduce the guest, come on out!
Hello, nice to meet you all!
Today you came in a sort of plain style today on purpose? Relatively, relatively.
Since I will be dressed by you.
It's not really that plain. But your normal style is even more flashy than this.
But I didn't think your fashion was that hard to understand.
I've never even bought clothes recommended by someone else before.
I see.
So today, if one of you gets a strike...
...I want to take you home along with the clothes.
You know, about the state of your body...
I'm not really sure I understand it.
You don't have boobs right?
Ahn~ ♥
That was your real voice just now.
Timed & Typeset by RIDDELL and GakiDave
Translated by senor_wristband
Before the filming, the five think of different shops to buy a top and an accessory for Peey.
That guy wears a lot of decorations.
For this sort of thing I could just close my eyes and grab one.
All of these work. All of em.
What's with that guy?
But, this type...
...it's alright to have this part uncovered, right?
You can have it uncovered right?
Yes, you can, yes.
I think this would be a good accessory.
Other ones ... well not these ones, these decorations don't work.
He's so flashy, so conversely maybe something to remind him he's a man.
Something that says ,"you're a man, right?"
Peey-kun doesn't ever wear Japanese style.
So I took a challenge, because I think Japanese style would work.
A flashy one would be good.
What is this?
This is a coat.
Incidentally...  Looks expensive.
But, but, it's 15,800 yen.
You know this, but if you're last place...
That's true.
If you come last, you pay with your own money...
Honestly...There's just something about paying for Peey, I'm sorry...
His fashion is quite flashy right?
A strong impression of pink.
The impression of pink is really strong.
This seems like something he would wear too.
Damn this is hard.
What is this?
It's a thing kids in America ride on.
Ah! They play like this?
Like this?
This kind of thing? Oh, this could make a good gift too.
So, we're here, Village Vanguard.
I think this store is a challenge.
This is great too.
Peey-kun probably likes this kinda thing right?
Wow, this is awesome.
This could be good too.
Is that for sale too?
Is this for sale? How much is it?
30K.
30K huh...
It's gonna hurt if he says he doesn't want it.
Like, something fluffly and colorful should be good right?
Something like this?
Right?
What is this?
Is this not good?
No of course, I wouldn't wear it.
Unless I'm in an incredibly good mood.
This is good too.
The feel-
This is so heavy, of course, as if to bully you,
They put chains in there.
This is so malicious, because this is so heavy.
Peey will take the item he likes most home with him.
Whomever comes in last must pay for their item with their own money.
First off a top that would look good on Peey.
I think I went on the offensive here.
If you don't do that, it's like, the surface tension is just barely holding you back.
You can't fall back.
First off, Tanaka presents his top.
I think I really took a risk here.
You gotta take a risk.
And I chose the one which I think will make him the most happy.
Of course of course.
I have a lot of confidence in this!!
Thank you very much.
'cause if you think about it, buying plain stuff is a waste.
Well the first facial impressions...
Uwah, what is that?
Well, you know, I...
...I can understand the fluffy part.
Yes, yes, yes...
It's a jacket.
Yes, yes it is.
He's not into it at all!
See!
He's not into it
Of course, Peey-san wears pink and other vivid colors.
So I thought instead he wouldn't be happy if he got the same thing again.
And he's in the middle of an image change...
...and I thought Peey hasn't bought anything monotone before.
And this fluffiness keeps the body lines.
No no no...
He has no confidence so he keeps talking.
Someone who goes to the park and listens to the radio all the time would wear that coat.
No no...
Next, the top Endo chose.
This bag is cute!
It starts from the bag of course, thank you very much.
If he thinks that cute then I have no idea what cute means.
What's that?
The brightness on his face.
Ah, spread it out.
Yes.
What is that?
You can wear it if you want.
You don't really wear Japanese style clothes right?
But there's a lot of stuff with Japanese style...
I think this one will actually look good on Peey-san.
It's not even funny.
That's the worst.
What do you mean "it's not funny"?
I genuinely think it suits him.
What? What is that thing called?
This is from a Kyoto shop, they have one in Tokyo too.
It's like a kimono.
It has nothing to do with Peey.
So you think something like this would also look good?
Yes, yes.
Here, this here.
Interesting.
It's interesting, right?
Interesting really means "I don't like it."
When you don't have something to say you call it interesting.
Next is Hosei's presentation.
Ameli?
The brand is already drawing him in.
That's a cute name.
It really is.
The bag is cute!
Do you know it? Ameli?
Of course it's Ameli!
I have no idea what that is.
I don't know Ameli.
Go ahead.
Hmm?!
This is, right?
It's sleeveless.
Yes indeed.
You can wear it without getting hot.
No no, there's no point in that.
It looks so good on you Peey-chan!
What happened?
I'm amazed!
Wow! This Peey-chan you see from the front...
And the Peey-chan you see from the back is totally different!
What's the point of that?
Is that uneven on purpose?
No, this is actually...
...it's detachable.
This um-
It won't come off.
It comes off, it comes off, for real.
His aging eyes, his eyes...
He just can't see.
Is there a young person here? A young person?
You can tell by looking there isn't a single young person here.
Yeah.
Next, the very confident Matsumoto.
For Peey...
...all the ideas I've had...
..I have to unleash them.
See, you can already see how happy is face is.
See, I've got the colors down.
Wow!
What is that?
It's got an extra pair?
It's like an octopus.
Cute!
See! He's calling it cute!
See!
On purpose these are useless.
What is this?!
You don't put your legs in here.
It's a Nininbaori thing!
TN: Nininbaori is when two people wear one coat.
It's for two people!
It's this kinda thing, isn't it cool? The colors too!
It's so exciting!
He said it's exciting!!!!
Like this?
Yes. See?
It's good right?
What is this?
Wasn't it better before?
I think either this side, or this side works.
This is a defective product right?
No no no!
Try wearing the lower one, that could be another style.
Put it in the lower one.
Yes yes yes.
This one?
How will it turn out?
Crazy!
Like this.
That's strange.
Put this in the front.
Ehh!? What is this!?
Hold on.
Wow!
You could tie it like this.
So cute!!
It's hella cute!
It's hella cute ain't it?!
You can't move properly.
Hamada is the last to present his top.
Everyone else appealed to the feminine style...
...but I, on purpose, did the opposite.
That bag...
It's for old men.
Maybe you should try dressing like this instead?
If you don't mix things up, you can't blend in.
This is scary. What is that?
Oh dear, he's gone and done it.
Yes, thank you very much.
That belongs to Onigawara Gonzo!! (Beat Takeshi)
He's messed it all up.
He thought too much and ended up with a bad idea.
No no no...
I thought on the contrary a masculine style would be good.
That face.
I want the smile I inspired in him to come back.
It's so different from before.
Which of these tops does Peey like best?
Have you decided on #1?
Yes, I have.
Alright, let's go.
Which one of these, is number one?
The one you can wear.
This!
YEAHHHH!!
I don't get it.
This one!
I really think the colors, and the innovative style of the arms...
...and how this feels worn and loose.
Oh yes yes yes.
It's on purpose.
Really advanced fashion.
Understood
And which is #2?
YEAHHH!!!
No way...
It's exciting to think about how I can wear this.
Thank you very much.
Fine, what about how mine can be worn?
Only someone with advanced fashion can wear it!!
All you can wear with that are work gloves and work pants!
That's the only outfit.
Work gloves, work pants, and cheap cigarettes, that's it!!
Peey you should show your skills!
All you can hold in your hand is BOSS Coffee.
TN: BOSS is sold from vending machines.
Let's see third place, have you decided?
Yes, I've decided.
Let's continue...Which one is number three?
Please, please.
It's between two.
This!
YEAHHHH!!
No, no - this is messed up.
No, no way, Peey.
C'mon.
Good work today!
Stop it! Stop it! He's the one who decided!
That's number three.
That's you guessing their feelings.
Peey tell em, tell em why.
If I put some patches on this and make it colorful...
...I want to try decorating it.
It's actually quite appropriate if you think about it.
I want to make this fashionable.
Which top did Peey like least?
Please think this through.
Seriously think about it.
Ignore their standing in the comedy world.
Ignore anything about them as comedians.
Cause in that case this guy is right out.
HEY!
I'm not out!! I'm a rakugoka now!!
So, who will pay for their purchase?
I don't want this.
Which one?!
The worst one.
How many times have I come last?!
For real, so many times.
It's like it's me everytime!
The reason please.
As soon as I saw this, I knew anything else would be better.
Right away? Even without seeing the others?
I kinda disliked how you tried too hard to pander to me.
In my head I was going on the offensive.
It's like he was saying
"Besides, you like this crap right?"
Like "Let's just serve the kids hamburgers."
That's not true.
Tanaka has to pay 32,184 yen from his own pocket!!
Next, an accessory for Peey. Endo is the first to present.
So, I just simply want to hand this over.
It's a cheesecake.
A cheesecake.
Again...
Peey-chan's face...
Well...
They are just sunglasses.
Yes, they're Ray Bans, the standard ones.
I wonder how this will turn out...
See? It just straight up looks good. It suits him so well.
It works only if you have those stars in the background.
I really think it suits him!
There's no way he's taking that home.
It's too out there.
How about upside down? It totally works!
Next, an accessory from Hamada.
I'm not sure if he already has this.
This is a cheap store.
Like, "maybe let's just try it on."
I'm scared.
What?
Yup, he did it again.
Hamada-san is in a slump today.
I'm not in a slump!
What happened?
It's a spiky bra!
Cause he doesn't need a bra right?
But it's something that he can wear as a top, above a t-shirt or something.
Please try that on.
What're you smiling for?
He looks happy.
Well, it's...
It's not totally unflattering.
It's good!
He can coordinate it with different outfits.
Interesting, this might not be bad.
Right?
But how is it really?
Even if you do that...
What are you doing?!
C'mon, touch it touch it.
Alright alright.
What is this interaction?
Next, will Tanaka make a comeback?
Something like this, it transcends imagination.
What is that?!
It's a bag.
This, yes! Like that.
This is a bag!
You can wear it on your shoulder, or just carry it.
You can wear it too.
Give him a bag to hide that bag in.
Give him something to hide that bag in.
Where do you put stuff in?
Here?
It has a zipper.
It looks too small.
It's way too small.
It's fine if nothing fits!
Who the hell is speaking too?
Everyone here is your senior, what are you doing man?
Matsumoto presents his accessory.
Interesting bag.
Yes the bag is interesting.
What the...
It's super cute!
Finally!
What the hell is that?!
It's a flamingo cap.
Flamingo cap?
It's just a flamingo.
The pink and pink clash....
Those legs are a pain!
No no, they're super cute. They're like, like piercings.
Like earrings, exactly.
It's the first time I've seen a hat like this.
It's for those times when you feel like wearing a flamingo.
You've never wanted to do that right Peey-chan?
Nobody feels like doing that.
AH! Backwards is good too!
BACKWARDS IS GOOD!!
It's like a topknot.
Wow!
I never thought of doing that.
It works! It works!
Last is Hosei's accessory.
Please, bring it out.
I told you this is not that type of segment!
Take this seriously, do your best!
What happened Peey-chan?
What the hell is this?
It's a body pillow.
That's a salmon.
A pillow.
C'mon try hugging it. It feels awesome.
His face, look at his face please.
It suits Peey-chan so well!
You got it wrong, it's supposed to be an accessory.
Something you wear or bring with you everyday.
Well we've got three creatures, try all of them on.
Wear the flamingo hat.
So cool!
So stylish!
"Besides, You Look Good in this Kinda Thing" Contest!
Which accessory did Peey like most?
So starting with #1.
Yes.
Once you've decided, announce it.
The number one item is...
Thank you!
No no, he likes it!
You wanna appear on his show "Hama-chan Ga!" right?
That's not why he picked it!
When I wore it I thought it was really stylish.
And it would be great to use in bed.
What the hell are your interests?!
Just what the hell do you like?
Number two, please decide number two.
I've decided.
You've decided?
Which one is number two?
Flamingos are really trendy right now.
Exactly.
Did you really know that?
Flamingos are just everywhere in Japan right now. They're all flying here.
It's that kind of trend?
That's not what he meant surely, flamingos flying to Japan.
OK, which one is your third favorite?
What should I do?
It must be hard for him to decide.
Can I actually choose the last one?
So one that's way worse than the others?
Not really.
They're equally bad?
Basically.
What do we do here?  He's already picked the worst one.
Yeah, let's do the worst one now.
So which accessory did Peey like the least?
Here we go!
Which one is the worst?
Please not mine!
Please!
Thank you for having bad taste.
I did think it kind of had a Harajuku vibe...
...but it's just wrong.
Wrong?
You don't understand Harajuku at all.
I'd rather pick something else.
You'd pick THIS?!
Knock that off!
This is good!
You can take that to Hokkaido!
Hokkaido?!