TRANSLATED, TIMED AND TYPESETTED BY KAIZEN SUBS.
The first edition of "I understand you the best, I think you like this kind of thing don't you?" competition! (Stuttering)
Don't look at me like that.
Are you a bit tired?
I can't really tell.
What happened?
Nothing happened.
Please tell us. You're Gaki no Tsukai's leader!
What happened?
I'm not tired!
(TL note: Matsumoto is referring to the news about Hamada's affair.)
You know, when Hamada was on Yahoo! news, at the same time Tanaka was on for finding a new species of bugs.
Why are you so happy with your life!?
Why are you doing this!?
No one wants to know your story!
Really?
Yes, the new species...
Also, no one probably wanted to read it because it was taken down straight away.
Because of this, I apologize like Chage.
(TL note: Chage and Aska are a famous Japanese pop duo. Aska was caught for drug use and Chage apologized on his behalf.)
I'm sorry.
But you know, even though Aska stopped doing drugs, Hamada wont stop drinking.
Are you alright?
Please stop.
Are you sure we should be shopping for girl's items?
The shop assistants will think we're creepy and desperate.
Yeah, you're right.
So everyone, before we did this with Kimura Yuuichi.
Last time, we had Kimura Yuuichi in the "I think you like this the best" competition.
This is a segment where gaki members buy items for Kimura that they think he'll like.
And tonight the special guest is?
Today's guest, welcome!
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
You look a bit different today.
It's a tight look.
Oh I see.
I am very sorry for your loss.
Our first ever female guest is the single celebrity, Tomochika.
Today the five will present a top, a bottom and a personal item to her.
Can the five pick the right presents for her?
Before the shooting, the members hit the stores to shop.
Matsumoto went to Ginza to find bottomwear that he thinks Tomochika likes.
Well...
So something like this would be good right?
Nah, this can't be the one.
Not these ones right? Nah, these definitely aren't the ones.
I know the ones she wont wear.
But I don't know the ones that she'll want to wear.
Ah, not this.
Matsumoto struggles, choosing for a female guest.
Meanwhile, Tanaka was in Shibuya to look for a personal item.
Personal items are difficult to choose because there are so many variations.
Oh I see, I see. I can choose bags as well?
Tanaka has difficulty with choosing a personal item. But...
Oh? I see, I see, I see.
This is a bit different. Isn't this good?
Oh I found it!
Are you going with this?
Yeah I'll be going with this.
But there are so many.
Hosei, goes to a shopping mall in Koyosu.
She is forty years old so,
that means that she is usually a calm and relaxed person.
Oh she usually wears these types of clothes.
Ah, these sorts are summer bags.
Those flowers, I mean dried flowers.
You can put those in these bags and Tomochika could walk around with it often.
And Endo, for some reason goes to a city for young people, Harajuku.
I'm going to a place that I go to quite often.
Endo is going to a place that he knows quite well.
Excuse me.
Is it ok for us to film?
Yes it's ok.
Actually, I'm not here privately today.
You're serious about this right? You think Tomochika-san will like these?
I'm serious.
Hamada is off to Ginza to choose a top.
I have a bit of information and I have an idea of what to choose.
Really? What is it?
I can't say that.
I can't say it here.
This probably wont fit you Tomochika-san.
I have never seen her wear this type of clothing.
This is hard... Tomochika, or women in general are difficult.
This time as well, Tomochika will be able to take home the item that she likes the most.
As for the one rated last, the gaki member who chose the item will have to pay for it themselves.
What type of style do you like Tomochika-san?
For me, I don't really care about the design but more the material.
The material?
I never thought about the material.
And also colors. I like vitamin colors (vegetables/fruits)
I have no idea what that is.
I didn't even know that existed!
All I can think of is a pizza delivery boy.
With the red jumper?
First to present the top that he thought Tomochika would like, Tanaka.
Since I do work with Tomochika often, I recalled a bit of the past and thought "Ah this is it."
Do you see her often in her own clothes?
From time to time at work.
Yes, but I'm pretty sure you don't really remember.
Yes that's true. I don't really remember.
What? That doesn't make sense!
You're just following Tomochika's pace!
Also, I think Tomochika has absolutely no interest in Tanaka.
Actually, I really like Tanaka
Really?
Don't you get the feeling?
No I don't get the feeling.
I say it often.
What the hell is this conversation?
Out of all of us, do you like Tanaka the most?
Yes I do.
Really?!
I'm actually happy right now. Because of this, I really want her to choose my present.
It's a top.
Ah it's quite simple.
When I see Tomochika in TV,
No no no.
This is bad.
She doesn't suit tight clothing. I've never seen her wear any tight clothes.
Just look.
You could see what she thinks from her face.
No no no.
That shirt should be for Lioness Asuka!
Her training shirt!
Next up, Endo with a top he thinks Tomochika likes.
Is that a famous store?
It's called 'merci beaucoup.'
Oh it has vitamin color.
The color is good.
It's kind of playful and um, the material...
Show it to us!
Just show it to us!
Will she wear that sort of cardigan?
Isn't is big?
You're meant to wear it loosely.
It's not meant to be tight.
Girls are all about first impressions.
That looks terrible.
That's horrible.
It's huge!
It's too big right?
It's like this.
You look fatter.
I do right?
You look a bit like Hashida Sugako
Third up is Hosei, who has a special connection with Tomochika.
Tomochika and I are diet partners.
Oh yes.
Oh right, you guys did that TV commercial together.
That's a very good brand.
Yes it is.
Oh I like this place.
It;s from Burberry, Blue Label.
Ah, this feels really good.
The material is good.
The way it feels...
It feels really good and it only has two sizes.
No no no no.
This doesn't suit her.
Doesn't it look like something a grandma would wear?
That's not the true. Look at the stripes at the back, they're so nice.
Endo, your one is too big. The boobs are hanging out of the cardigan.
It's freaking gross!
This is disturbing.
It's too big!
The different designs on the front and the back is quite nice.
Oh, thank you.
Next is Hamada who's got special information.
Mine is very simple.
I tried to go for her likes and interests.
That's no good.
Ah, no.
No no.
Ah, you're for real.
It's an animal design?
I heard that Tomochika-san likes animals.
Yes I do.
Who did you hear it from?
That's dirty!
It's a nude colour.
Isn't that a bit small?
It's pretty small.
From behind she looks naked.
Looking at her from behind she does look naked.
She's naked.
She ain't naked!
Why was Tomochika smacked?
Last up, Matsumoto.
I think she fits this type of clothing.
That doesn't matter.
It's up to her to decide.
She'll like this for sure.
You want to see me happy don't you?
See!
What the hell is that?
That's for grandmothers!
This is definitely Tomochika or something!
No this is horrible!
Isn't this Tomochika?
This is the worst!
She wouldn't wear that!
This is a tribal outfit right?
I think its good for you.
It suits you!
I don't think so.
It really suits her!
I said that isn't good.
I look a lot older.
Yes yes.
This is not good.
Seriously?
I saw you wearing this in my head.
It was either you or Itami Juzo.
Which one is Tomochika's favorite top?
First place is...
this one.
YESSSSSSSSSS!
Now, which one is the worst?
Last place is...
this one.
Are you serious?
I was a bit sad when I saw this.
Really?
What would you rate it out of a hundred?
I would rate it 0.
I didn't expect this!
Matsumoto has to pay for his present.
This looks so good.
That's for women that go to theaters.
That's true!
"I think you like this" competition! Now it's Endo with bottomwear he thinks Tomochika will like.
I really want you to wear this.
Ah that makes me really happy.
Really?
Can you open it please?
I think she suits shorts.
Her face!
Do you wear shorts?
No no no no.
I often wear it.
I just heard her whisper "Uwaa."
You did right?
Yes I did.
What were you thinking Endo?
The ribbon...
This has a ribbon.
I'm not sure about this string though. It might make an awkward shape around here.
Don't worry. The material is thin so it wont.
Don't lie!
No since the material is thin...
Is this something you wear at the circus?
Next is Hamada's chosen item.
I think this will fit Tomochika.
Thank you very much.
Although, I haven't really seen Tomochika in casual clothes.
I see.
Oh I can see it.
Wait it has a top part?
I think it would have been better as a skirt.
No no no no.
It would have been better as a skirt!
It's completely fine right?
It's not too bad right?
Is it an apron?
It's an apron.
It isn't an apron!
Just put it on the mannequin and see.
The design looks nice though.
What is that?
This is bottomwear right?
Yeah I think so.
The breasts on the mannequin are amazing.
Are you supposed to wear this without anything underneath?
No no no.
Since it's summer you can just wear a shirt underneath.
What material is it made out of?
It's like the material you use for curtains.
Curtains?
That's awful.
It's an apron made out of curtains.
It's not an apron!
Next, Tanaka's turn to present his chosen item.
I tried to be a bit creative.
This is no good.
Her ass will stick out of it.
You'll see her ass!
It's too young for her.
It'll make you look thin.
Thin?
You can show your body off.
She doesn't seem that happy.
It isn't really creative.
Really?
She doesn't seem that happy.
This'll suit you for sure.
Next is Matsumoto. Can he redeem himself?
I got her something that's sort of something like the vitamin color she mentioned before.
It's a bit hard.
Hard?
It's hard! That looks so hard.
It has pineapples.
It doesn't look that different to mine.
It's similar to Hamada-san's.
They have the same feeling.
Yes.
That's a child's apron!
I thought it looked good.
This is amazing.
You're right.
I think it will be nice if it was a bag.
Oh for the summer time?
A bag to put your stuff in.
Are you Maezono-san?
It's just my fashion today. I'm not Maezono-san.
Lastly, Hosei who is trying to get first place again.
Where is that from?
(TL note: Hosei says Rirandotooruu instead of Rirandochuuru)
This is from Rirandtoore.
Is that even correct?
Her facial expression doesn't look good.
She's looking pretty dull.
It's a long type.
Isn't that for grannies?
It's good isn't it?
It's so good right? This is so good.
That's for women who go to theaters.
That's true!
The type that makes dinner early then leaves so she can go to a performance at the theater,
and then leaves a note saying "just heat this up."
It looks like a joke.
No no, this looks so good.
What's the design?
Flower... Pressed flowers?
Yes, it's a pressed flower pattern.
Not just flowers?
Yes, it's pressed flowers.
What will be Tomochika's favorite bottomwear?
Come on, come on.
Hamada-san's one.
YESSSSSS!
Of course it was mine!
Really?
Just out of these 5 right?
No actually, if a shop assistant showed me this I would have probably bought it.
Really?
Thank you very much.
What's so good about it?
Truthfully, I was hesistating between this and Matsumoto-san's.
See?
I knew she liked it.
That means you like those kind of patterns?
Yes I do.
I don't understand. I don't understand you.
He is so hyped up.
Don't get too ahead of yourself!
She hasn't announced last place yet!
Which one is the worst?
Endo!
Seriously?
I agree with this.
This is what homeless girls wear.
That's a hopeless homeless.
This means Endo has to pay for his item.
Lastly, a personal item. Starting from Hamada.
I think you can even use this in the summer. At times when it's slightly cold.
It's not a scarf, it's a shawl.
I thought it would be weird if there were animal patterns on this.
Yeah. Look at her face though.
Do I look older?
No I don't think so.
The design looks like it was a drawing by my toddler.
Is that even relevant?
Don't you feel younger?
Next is Tanaka, who chose an item perfect for summer.
Please open this.
I think this one is perfect.
They said I didn't go for it enough last time, but this time I did.
Did you become adventurous?
Yes.
like Uemura Naomi?
Yes, of course.
We don't need that.
I'm going to climb this mountain!
And coincidentally, when Hamada-san gave her the T-shirt,
she said she liked animal designs.
Firstly, a fan!
You honestly have no sense.
(TL note: This was a pun. Sensu - sense, sensuu - fan)
I know you want this! This is good!
So it's like, oh this fan actually has an animal design when you open it.
Yes that's right.
I don't really need this.
Yeah she doesn't need it.
Next is the personal item that Hosei chose.
This is for the upcoming season.
Is the personal item you chose that big?
It doesn't look that good.
Is the color a vitamin color?
The color is good.
Yes, this'll fit with anything.
Nah... It's a bit wrong.
I think it goes well with Hamada-san's gift.
I don't think so.
Yeah maybe not.
Next is Endo. Can he avoid paying twice in a row?
Please open this.
The brand is called "6% DOKIDOKI."
It has a style similar to things like Kyary Pamyu Pamyu.
That type of style is too young for her.
So it's a unique shop?
It's quite adjustable.
That is horrible!
Stop freaking messing around!
Is that a party prop?
No not at all!
It looks like 'Mr. Okure.'
No that isn't right.
It is Okure-san.
You can put it on your hair.
Ah I see...
Endo, I really hate this.
For example, wearing it on your hair like this.
You made these girls over there laugh the most out of all of us!
The teens are laughing.
They're laughing the most!
"I think you like this kind of thing" competition! Matsumoto's chosen personal item is?
If you can I'd like you to try it on and show us.
Wait are there snacks in here?
No way!
When I saw this, I was pretty sure that you wore this sort of style.
Really?
Seriously?
Underwear?
That's so weird.
You just made me wonder what she would look like in those.
Don't you think she would wear this?
Will she wear that?
It doesn't give an erotic vibe.
Tomochika, do you have similar underwear to this?
Yes I do.
She definitely has it!
It's a very nice color.
Wait do you mean it's a bit erotic?
No, what I'm saying is are the panties meant to be that big?
Isn't it too big?
It's the big type.
Look at her putting it on casually.
But doesn't it look like Tomochika?
I'm bad with g-strings, so I like this.
I understand that.
I don't think she dislikes it.
Without any hesitation she just started trying it on.
Yeah I just started wearing it on my own.
Just which one is Tomochika's favorite item?
The best is...
this one.
YESSSSSSS!
I knew it!
I really like this.
Wear it straight away!
I will wear it after.
I can just imagine her wearing just that at home.
So you bought this right?
No I didn't because I thought it'd be weird. So I got my junior Onigiri to buy it for me.
Won't it be scary if some random dude over 2 meters tall came in and bought this?
And now for the worst item...
Last place is...
this one.
That saved me.
Again, Endo has to pay for his item.
Overall, how was it today?
I was expecting someone to push me to choose their items but no one did.
Wait there was someone!
There was? Who?
It's there! I wanted you to wear that!
It's our first female guest, so I think it was a bit difficult to choose today.
Well next time I see Matsumoto-san I'll wear this underwear.
So you can thank him right?
This is so embarrassing.
For more subs, go to kaizensubs.blogspot.com
You can also find information regarding the people mentioned in the show.