First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai! Mess around and you're out!
Serious and accurate animal acting contest!
How was his shouting?
It was somehow muffled
Mess around and you're out
Serious and accurate animal acting contest!
Each one of them will choose an animal and they'll study their way of living
f
They'll have to play that animal seriously in a dark jungle set
Who will be the most realistic animal actor between them?
Comedians usually react fast, sometimes too much
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
I think that's what I don't like about comedians
It's kind of lame, isn't it?
- It is, yes
But this is realistic, isn't it?
Yes, it is
They have to act like real animals without messing around
Cocorico
Tanaka Naoki
We're gonna think they're real?
We'll have them act like
real animals without exaggerations
Tanaka will explain the distinctive point of each animal
To decide how much they'll be realistic
Is up to Tanaka, who is so well-informed on animals
To the point he even published a book!
Is there going to be a winner?
Yes, when we're done we'll talk about them and decide the winner
Actually, me and Hamada want to set a prize money
I think 9000 yen (81 USD) is enough
I agree
Prize money of 9000 yen
The winner will receive a prize from Downtown:
That will be 4500 yen each
At least raise it up to 10'000 yen!
At least 10'000, come on
No way we're gonna do that at the end of the year
It's time for our first contestant's appearance!
Tsukitei Hosei, please come in!
Tsukitei Hosei
I think it kind of... feels like he's messing around
That's not it, just wait and see until I'm done
Can I say which animal am I?
Yes, which animal are you?
I'm a meerkat
It's a small animal, isn't it?
Yeah, it's really small
He chose this between others?
Why did you choose it?
Please tell us
I once heard that it's one of the strangest animals there is
That's what made me choose it
Is this an act or...?
When the contest starts it's no good but
You can mess around with us now, it's fine
You're not being funny at all!
Follow Shion No Tsukai:
・Website: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com/
・Twitter: @FGRNDNoises
・ Facebook: fb.com/shionnotsukai
Follow Tofu Panda Fansubs:
・Website: tofupandas.tumblr.com/
・Twitter: @TofuPandaFansub
・ Facebook: fb.com/TofuPandaFansubs
This episode was brought to you by
Tofu Panda Fansubs & Shion No Tsukai
Timing by Patrick
Translation & edit (lousy one) by Shion
Typeset (good one) by Otviss
Mess around and you're out
Serious and accurate animal acting contest!
Meerkat
Entry no. 1
Tsukitei Hosei
Our first challenger is Hosei
How will he play the not-so-known meerkat's behavior?
Serious and accurate animal: start!
filmed with a night vision camera
Meerkat
Is the set completely dark?
I think it's almost pitch black
We're watching this with a night vision camera
Oh, I see
So we can just barely see what's going on
Where will the meerkat pop out from?
He's not showing up
Where is he?
Maybe it's so realistic it won't come out at all
He can hear us, can't he?
Meerkat
Yes he can
We're connected
So what's this about?
Here it is
That's where he was...
He's into this
Yeah he is
It isn't really blinking that much
That's right
What's going on?
Looks like he's moving
It's actually realistic
Is it? It's fine?
Yeah, it feels real
He's quick
He is, yes
So irritating
I bet he just wanted to do this!
These moves?
Meerkat
Did he shout?
What's happening?
Woah, that's impressive
It's a wild animal after all
There's something
It's a scorpion
A scorpion! A scorpion came out
He missed it
He did
He's eating the scorpion!
Is it going to be fine by eating them?
Meerkats are immune to the poison of scorpions
They're immune to scorpion's poison, that makes it their st
They're immune to scorpion's poison, that makes it their staple food
Meerkat
That must be a watering hole
Like a puddle?
There's something here
Did he take something?
There was something
He must be really hungry
It's a frog!
It eats frogs too?
Yes, it does
He really looks like an animal in this light
He's going for it
He's eating it
He's not using his hands
Isn't that enough?
He ate it all!
He ate it for real! Is he gonna be ok?
Is he ok? He really ate it!
Meerkat are surely cute, but they can also be fierce
I think I actually got what a meerkat is like by this point
You did? I mean, this scene is so realistic
His reactions are so accurate
It just cried
Alright, it's over!
It was really good, and it was way more legit than expected
When you ate that frog...
Yeah, that frog scene felt really wild
After all we're talking about a wild animal
So that's why, I mean---
What do you think about it?
We just said that
That's all we've been saying
Our next challenger is Goto from Jaru Jaru
Goto Junpei
Jaru Jaru
It does look like he's messing around
No way, I swear I'm not
Are you a japanese language teacher?
If so I would be messing around a lot
What is that?
This is a Bonobo
So it's not a gorilla?
No, it's not
It's neither a gorilla nor a chimpanzee
This is said to be the closest living being to humans
Is that so?
This is my first time on Gaki no Tsukai
Is this your debut?
Yes it is
To be honest it was my dream to appear on Gaki someday
But I never thought I was going to appear on it as a bonobo
(Jaru Jaru)
Bonobo
Entry no. 2
Goto Junpei
Next up is Goto Junpei from Jaru Jaru
Will he be able to become a bonobo
Which is said to be our closest relative?
Serious and accurate animal: start!
Bonobo
Which moves is he going to do?
I wonder
It's even closer than chimpanzees to us humans
Oh, here it is
He just normally entered from the curtain
The way he's moving on two legs is really...
Impressive
Yeah but anyone could do that
They love to play around and climb up trees like that
I see
How can this not be labeled as messing around?
No but it's true, they actually play with trees like that
And now... he's eating something?
Yes, he's eating
Really
Some berries maybe
Yes, they're omnivorous
So they eat lots of things
That was so good
His cry was really accurate!
Ok but his first scene when he entered through the curtain...
Was straight out from a red light district
There's not so much space to move around
He's finally moving again
This is really...
Maybe it's a young one...?
Yeah it kind of seems that way
I mean, rolling on the ground and playing around...
He really doesn't seem to be on guard
That's true
They're really carefree
Chimpanzees or such are often fighting
But bonobos don't like conflicts at all
They usually solve problems peacefully
They have a calm personality and don't like fights
They're immune to scorpion's poison,
And that's why they're so calm and carefree
And that atmosphere is really clear in here
Bonobo
Well that's... I see
Oh, it's moving
It went there again
One more time
He really likes that spot
I was thinking...
What we've been shown is a cutback footage
But there's barely any editing
I mean, nothing's happening but it's onscreen
It's off again, what will he do?
That's a yet unexplored zone
Behind the rock
He found something
He's humping something
He's copulating! This is a valid point too
Look: as you can see that's a missionary position
It seems so
Almost every other animal does it from behind
You all should have noticed that
But the bonobo is said to be one of the few animals that prefers missionary
It uses missionary position, which is rare in animals
They're immune to scorpi
That's also why it is said to be close to us
And I think this scene really made it clear
Bonobo
He cried
END
THE
And it's over!
So, how was it?
I think I've reached my limit after 5 minutes since the start
By the time I was done with copulation, I had no more energy
The thing about losing energy after copulation you just said...
Sounded like a dirty joke
That was just by chance
By chance, huh...
Says the dirty jokes machine
It was a coincidence
Alright, he's messing around
Yep, definitely
Endo Shozo
Entry no. 3
Panda
Our next challenger is Endo
He'll act as zoo's most popular animal: the panda
Panda's movements are really slow
Panda
They surely are
Yes, they move very slowly
I've seen them doing this
That's bamboo grass, yes
That's really like that, they love it
He's eating a lot
All he's doing is eating
Hamada, you just said all he does is eating, right?
Their feeding habit is pretty much that of a herbivorous
But they're actually carnivorous, so they don't digest it so much
Their principal food, bamboo grass, is hard to digest, and
its nutritious values are also low, so they have to eat nonstop
They're immune to scorpion's poison Woooo
They can only digest 20% of it
So in order to get a proper nourishment, they must keep on eating
That's why they're always eating
And he's showing this feature to us?
Most likely, yes
What if he just can't come up with anything good?
Our next challenger is Kotohge from Viking, please come in!
Kotohge Eiji
Viking
It's a pleasure
COMPLETE BODY PAINTING
s
That's wonderfully done!
And which animal is this?
I'm a cheetah
A cheetah, of course
That's a wonderful cheetah
Why did you choose it?
First off, I thought it suited my physique
I see
Also, the cheetah is really fast
I think all of you know it can run really fast
But it has lots of other features and I want to show them to you
(Viking)
Cheetah
Entry no. 4
Kotohge Eiji
Our fourth contestant is Kotohge from Viking
How will he act as the cheetah, the fastest running animal in the world?
Serious and accurate animal: start!
Cheetah
From where will he pop out?
He's there already
As you can see he's here
He's here
Woah, it's a cheetah
This is really a cheetah
Really, this
It's a real cheetah!
The balance of his body is incredible
This is wonderful!
But if kids would see it, they couldn't sleep at night
That's a nice angle
That was...
He let out a cry
It was...
Unexpectedly loud
Yeah he went for it
He's raising up his voice
That was quite powerful
The way he's walking around...
Yeah
Is really good
Yes, it's magnificent
It must be tiring
The way he moves around without staying still is very cheetah-ish
Is it?
They don't usually stay still?
That's right
They move around a lot--- oh?
What is he doing?
Looks like he's drinking water
Yes, he must be drinking water
The way he's intimidating is so real, so good!
Cheetahs show their teeth and hiss to threaten the enemy, that's so realistic
They intimidate the enemies by showing them their teeth
They're immune to scorpi
Cheetah
Just like this
That was so good
That's a nice expression
He's doing such a great face
Huh?
Is this Osamu Niisan?
If so, that would count as messing around
Oh, nice threatening
Oh boy
That's such a good face
Yeah, it's perfect
That's a great face, can't deny it
You can feel his force, he's intimidating after all
I wonder if it's a male or a female?
That part is not clear
That's a cub!
So that means...?
Yes
It's a female, this one's a female
Female cheetahs carry their cubs around with their teeth
They're immune to sc2
When they sense danger, they carry their cub with their mouth
They carry them around when they sense danger or such
I wonder which situation is going to unfold?
That's a cheetah...
Cheetah
Yes
What now? Is something going to happen?
He's aiming at something
That was disgusting
That scene was sickening
They actually do it, they hide in grassy places and leap out
Is he trying to attack his cub?
No
I think he's showing it to him
Oh I see, he's teaching the cub
Yes, I think so
It's pedagogy
Yes
That's so realistic
They actually teach it to the cubs
It's really amazing
It is
Painting aside, his face is the same as always
He cried
He made a sound
END
THE
And it's over
Let's call him here
His posture has always been bent
I wonder if his back is gonna be ok
That must have been tiring
I'm dead tired
That was really...
Worth 9000 yen
I agree
Was his act the closest to 9000 yen?
Yes, it was
Our next challenger
Is Iwao from Football Hour, please come in!
Iwao too?
Looks like he did something
Football Hour
Iwao Nozomu
Look how elegant he is!
I have a sort of bad feeling about this
That was such a bold choice
What is this?
I'm a shoebill, it's a bird
Why did you choose this?
You see, the shoebill
Has a certain major feature to it
And I felt a sort of sympathy to that
Don't tell us now what it is
That's what I want to show you
I see, I see
Makes sense
(Football Hour)
Entry no. 5
Iwao Nozomu
Shoebill
Next up is Iwao, from Football Hour
He felt something close to this bird
But what will it be?
Serious and accurate animal: start!
filmed with a night vision camera
Shoebill
From where will he pop out?
He's standing up like normal
He's standing...
That's a person
It's more a human than a bird
But the way he's slowing moving its feet
It's so realistic
They walk slowly and calmly
They're
Isn't it kinda creepy?
Shoebill
It's frightening
I mean, if I'd saw this on a security camera I would freak out
It's not moving at all
Is it a calm animal?
Yes, the shoebills...
Are a type of bird which barely even moves
It doesn't move much
They're
But it doesn't look like a bird at all
You're right
What the hell
Seriously, what is this?
He's just standing there!
But they really can stay still for several hours
I want to see the real ones now
I swear they're like this!
If they move around
Their shadow on the water would move too, and fishes would swim away
Oh, I see
That's why they barely move around
They just try to stay still
And they're quick when it comes to catch them?
Yes, they quickly jump for it
So it's aiming at something
It's looking at them
So he can catch them
We may be able to see
A scene where he'll attack
Maybe he's full
He's enduring it
But it seems to be aiming at something
To me it looks like it
Is it?
But really, they can stay like this
For such a long time
Yeah but... what's this?
It spread its wings
That's unusual
Yeah it is
These movements
He flapped its wings
He moved, the fishes went away
Yes
What is he doing now?
This movement
He's making sounds by hitting stuff with its beak
This is clattering
Clattering
Making sounds with your own beak in order to threat
or communicate with the others
im gonna have nightmares about this guy i'm soooooooooooooooooooooooooo sure of itttttttt you wont believvvvvvvvvvvvvvvv meeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
smol guy
Clattering...?
Yes, yes, yes
What the heck is this
With this
They can threat enemies or even
Shoebill
Communicate with others through sounds
That was clattering just now
He went too hard on it and placed his beak back with his hands
That's all he could do, even the rubber band...
Right
It fell down
Because he did that
He couldn't do much
That's all he could have done
It cried
Yes, it cried
END
THE
And it's over
I must say, you really put a lot of effort during the first half
Where you had to stay still for so long
That was so good
It was incredible
But there's a problem
Yeah
The clattering
Clattering
After you did it you moved your hands like this, why?
He couldn't use his fingers!
Right?
Here's our last challenger
Oh, the last one?
Haranishi from FUJIWARA
Please come in
Takayuki Haranishi
And here he is...
Again...
Please do your best
It's easy to get this
That's right, please tell us
I'm a sea lion
A sea lion
I actually want to become a sea lion, someday
Is this a bombshell announcement?
Sea Lion
Entry no. 6
Takayuki Haranishi
Haranishi from FUJIWARA is our last one
He chose the well-known sea lion
The star of aquariums!
Serious and accurate animal: start!
Sea lion
l
How will he...?
How will he enter the stage?
Here he comes!
Of course he went for that!
That's amazing!
So natural
Incredible
He's pulling out a great sea lion
He really can do it
And he's not even wet
That's incredible
It's really amazing
He's doing something
You can't do it without physical ability
I thought he would have gone "ou ou" first
Sea lions do smile, actually
They can show a smiling expression
here comes the sea lion | a smile on his face | just look at him smilin' | with his nightmare gaze
They really do it
They make that face?
Their expressions are great, that was really on-point
Sea lion
l
Why is it shouting now?
They usually shout to mark their territory
You sure it didn't get involved in an accident?
That's impressive!
Do they cry so much?
That's an amazing cry
He's still going
That's really something
Incredible
Is he done?
Maybe he'll roll around now
Was that... his final cry?
Was that his last one?
He cried so much he's completely done
He wanted it to end
That's how much he shouted
You think so?
Must be it
Was that your final cry?
Alright then, it's over!
END
THE
He cried too much
So it was an ending cry...
He was too tired
Everyone did their best
They really did, didn't they?
Yup!
But we're not actually done yet...
For our grand finale we'll have them all on stage together
All of them?
All of them will be present
Coming next
Will their final appeal time result in trouble!?
So get ready everyone!
Skip to 21:47
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
tofupandas.tumblr.com
Here we are, it's time for our final show
Amazing, huh?
This is incredible
That's unlikely
Yeah, very improbable
It's a miracle they're not brawling
You're right
Not even the cheetah is attacking
That's right
Huh?
Oh
Something came
Danson!
Fiizaki!
Tooza teesaza konsa!
What the hell?
Danson!
Bambino
Fujita Yuuki
Ishiyama Daisuke
Fiizaki!
Tooza teesaza konsa!
What's going on?
Nibura!
Danson!
Fiizaki!
Tooza tee-- nibura!
Is he going to...?
What the hell!
Danson! Fiizaki!
He's getting them one after another
Tooza-- nibura!
He's going really fast
He quickly gets to "nibura"!
He's quick
That's a double!
He's getting em all one by one
Danson!
What's going on...?
Tiisaki!
It's the cheetah
I wonder if it's gonna get caught too
Toosa tee-- nibura!
Ok everyone, come back he~re
The winner is going to be revealed!
And so, who acted the best as an animal between them?
Have you made up your mind, Matsumoto?
Yes
So, can you tell us
Who is today's winner?
Yes of course, the winner is...
Please!
Bambino
Winner: Bambino
W-wait...
Bambino is our winner
In the end they won
That last bit was really something
I think it was the best part
You got em all good
All of them
Let me count them just a sec
Oh, ok
3, 4, 5...
You're giving those now...?
Right in front of us?
I really liked you on King of Conto too
That worked way better than you're probably thinking
(I also made this robot)
FACEBOOK: /TOFUPANDAFANSUBS & /SHIONNOTSUKAI
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FAN TRANSLATION MADE BY
FANS FOR OTHER FANS TO ENJOY. NO COPYRIGHT
INFRINGMENT INTENDED. ALL THE RIGHTS BELONG
TO THEIR RESPECTIVE OWNERS. ENJOY YOU GAKI!
TIMING BY PATRICK | TYPESETTING BY OTVISS
TOFUPANDAS.TUMBLR.COM
TRANSLATIONS & NOTES BY SHION
TWITTER: @TOFUPANDAFANSUB & @FGRNDNOISES
YOU CAN SUPPORT TOFUPANDA & SHIONNOTSUKAI BY FOLLOWING THEM BOTH ON SOCIAL MEDIAS OR BY MAKING SMALL DONATIONS, VISIT EACH WEBSITE FOR MORE INFO
→
▀
・