TRANSLATED, TIMED AND TYPSETTED BY KAIZEN SUBS
The first edition of "I understand you the best, I think you like this kind of thing don't you?" competition!
Matsumoto-san.
Yes?
The last time we did this as a five.
Yes, that's right.
I think this segment is a good idea, but this sign sucks.
"I understand you the best," it says.
It's a bit disgusting.
This is the sequel to the one aired earlier this year, "I think you like this kind of thing" competition.
This is a project where the gaki members buy items that suits the guests interests.
This time, we have a special guest.
This guy is quite old. He's one year older than us.
Yeah.
By the way, fairly recently he's become a grandfather.
He's become a grandfather.
That's amazing.
Today's grandpa guest.
Well then, let's begin. Welcome!
You were knocking from behind the curtain.
I'm just saying, we're the same age.
Wrong!
We're all born in Showa 38 (1963)
I'm so freaking sick of this talk.
You know, I really like this corner.
It makes me happy how you guys care and try to understand things about me.
But you know, you were honestly the only one we thought about.
We didn't want to, but we couldn't help it.
A celebrity who is known for his fashion sense, Kimura Yuuichi.
The gaki members will each pick out a hat, a top and a book which will be presented to him.
Before the recording, the gaki members went shopping.
To search for a hat that Kimura might like, Endo went to Omotesandou. (A place in Tokyo)
In my opinion, Kimura-san is very fashionable,
so I think this'll be good for him.
If this was just sitting somewhere, I'd be like "Woah, Kimi-nii what's that you're wearing today?"
Meanwhile, Matsumoto went to a bookstore near Tokyo Station.
A book about flowers... He's probably not interested in things like this.
I've never heard Kimura talk about flowers before.
When talking about Kimura-san, I've thought of the ideal hat for him.
Tanaka, who is full of confidence goes to a specialist hat store to find a hat.
Umm...
When I think of the ideal hat for Kimura-san, I think of Borsalino (Italian-style) hats.
I'm not really sure which one.
Hamada goes to a select shop in Ueno.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
I think everyone else will choose these types of hats.
See? Those are the hats he wears nowadays, though I'm not sure if he'll like this.
That's something he'll decide.
Do you have an image in mind?
Yeah I do, I think a baseball cap would be good.
Hamada's decided to go with a baseball cap, but just what did he choose?
How's this?
This hat has kind of an angry feel to it.
The place that Hosei went to was in Shibuya.
This is the place, it's perfect.
It's perfect, so perfect.
Oh man, this is the one for Kimura.
Is this a bathrobe?
For the boxing ring?
In the same store, Housei also looks for caps.
Ah I've found it! This is it, oh sorry, this, it's this definitely.
I really like this man, I've decided, excuse me.
Everyone is completely serious about choosing their items.
That's because...
Kimura will be able to take the item he likes the most home.
As for the item that Kimura ranks last, the gaki member who chose that item will have to pay for it himself.
This is for real. You really have to pay and that's why I don't have the receipt.
That's enough of that.
I've seen this too many times.
First up, Endo with a hat that he thinks Kimura likes.
This is the item that I chose.
It took about one hour to pick this.
That long!?
The truth is I quite like hats as well.
I don't think a lot of people have seen me wearing a hat.
Oh this is leather?
Yes. My understanding of Kimura-san's fashion is it has a unique look.
It is a bit unique.
Yes that's right.
Leather huh? I don't really have anything leather right now. The shape is...
The shape, I think it's
Look at his reaction!
Kimura sweats a lot, and the leather might make him hot and sweaty due to the material.
I don't really want Kimura to wear this hat.
Oh, it really suits him though.
I look a bit older.
Wear it a bit higher to show off your forehead.
Oh higher?
Show a little bit of your hair at the front.
He looks like Toshio Sakata.
No no, not at all.
Next up Hamada. What is his pick for the hat he thinks Kimura likes?
You guys went for what Kimura is wearing recently, but I've gone for something he doesn't really wear anymore.
I haven't seen him in this style for a quite a while now.
Oh I see, I don't really wear caps.
Recently I haven't worn caps.
The colors are black and white.
Since you haven't worn this type of hat recently, why not take a trip back to the past?
Are you asking him to?
Yeah like a request.
Ah I can see it, it looks good.
The shape is not bad.
But then again... nah it's kinda wrong.
I don't understand what the image is here at the front.
Wait Sakata was wearing it as well.
Why him again!?
When I asked the person at the store, they said it was a snake.
A cobra.
Oh it's a cobra.
Ah I see.
You know, Kimura is scared of cobras.
That doesn't matter!
He can't handle reptiles.
Next is Tanaka, but there is some worry.
Uhm I....
Tanaka and Kimura are like water and oil.
What are you saying?
I don't think he understands me.
Don't worry, I have confidence in this.
This is huge! Oh, it's a CA4IA. (TL note: A high end store)
I'm confident.
Is that a Playstation?
Oh it's a Borsalino!
Yes!
That's famous.
Will he even wear it?
It's an Italian brand.
Oh it's because Kimura like the godfather.
Yes! Yes! That's right.
If you come last you have to pay for it though.
Every year, this...
This is supposed to be for private use you know?
Is it made out of straw?
Yes. That's right.
It's a summer hat.
It's huge! 61 cm?
Why the hell is it 61cm?
Please wear it.
61cm is too loose.
You don't know anything.
The colors, I see.
It shows the design.
The curtains behind are the same color.
You can't really see it.
He looks like he doesn't have hair.
Next is Hosei. But, there is one problem.
Last time you were ranked last.
I'm sorry
Wait isn't this bag a bit weird?
Did you buy a sex toy?
Like lotion or something?
That's not fair! I haven't even shown him what I chose yet.
It starts from the bag itself.
No it's about the fashion sense, the actual present itself.
The price doesn't matter.
I think none of you understand what Kimura-san really likes. What he likes is rock.
He likes music.
You like the 80's right, Kimura-san?
This is something amazing.
You can see the rock in it.
See!? This is the one!
I want you to feel the rock in this.
I see. Well... I see.
It's hard to decide what to wear with this.
He can wear what he's wearing now.
I don't really like hats where the wings are small.
Yeah it's a bit small.
A bit. Yeah.
If you fold it out, it can be any size you want.
Next is Matsumoto who knows Kimura the best.
From my view, Kimura is a Daikanyama (Tokyo) type of person.
I see.
So that's where I looked for things.
See?
How is this?
Wait does Kimura-san like skull designs though?
Not really.
Right?! You don't like them!
Not really an image I have of Kimura-san.
IS THERE A PERSON THAT DOESN'T LIKE SKULL DESIGNS!?
Kimura-san doesn't like it.
WE'RE ALL SKULLS!
Wait, from the way it fits... The leopard design from before looked better.
Yes!
I'm not really sure,
but I have known him for a while now and I can tell you that he's not that happy.
Which one is the favourtie for Kimura san?
The best one is...
I knew it was going to be that one!
I told you this was good!
Recently, I don't have anymore caps.
For second place, he chose Tanaka's. And for third, Matsumoto's.
That's gotta be a lie Kimura-san!
So then, who will be chosen worst?
To be honest with you, when I first saw this hat I wanted to punch him in the ribs.
It was that bad?!
Which was the one that made you want to do that?
This one.
Really?
It looks ugly and it has bad color.
Use your freaking brain!
This is a joke right?
You're a freaking joke!
When you showed me the item, I knew that no matter how bad the rest were you were still going to be last.
Endo has to pay for his chosen item.
Next, tops that Kimura might like. First up, Tanaka.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Thank You. Oh!
It's all about the first reactions!
This is...
That's something Kimura of the past would wear.
I see, I see.
Different to his past, but something a bit playful.
The recent trend?
Yes! The recent trend.
Yes, something a bit playful...
He would wear this!
A unique type of fashion!
Ah! Kimura would definitely wear this!
Oh look at him taking his jacket off. He looks so freaking happy.
He wants to wear it so bad, look at his face!
It's too obvious.
He is so pumped!
Those tiny eyes!
Ahh I see, A swing top
The swing top fits tightly.
How is it Kimura-san?
Do you play golf?
No, apparently a swing top is like something you can do a golf swing with while wearing.
Really?
You can swing with the top on, hence the name.
Oh really?
Yes.
His face looks so pumped.
Next is Endo, can he rebound from before?
Well...
That's a good face.
He is getting pumped up.
He was wearing this type of shirt during an Okinawa movie shoot.
That kind of style.
You can wear it outside of Okinawa.
He was wearing this when we shot Downtown DX (TL Note: Another Downtown program) in Okinawa
With a star pattern.
What's the pattern?
It's maps of Africa.
This brand shows us Bhutan.
I really like maps.
Oh you like maps?
This isn't too tight on your body.
Ah I see, I see.
He isn't too bothered or annoyed.
I see.
Ah this looks good!
He said it was good.
He just said it was good!
Next is Hamada, presenting Kimura with a top he thinks he likes.
Sorry, I think I went a bit far with the modern look.
That's not good.
I think we see this a lot from Kimura.
This is a vest!
He likes to wear this type.
Yeah, I can imagine it.
I really like vests.
Ah it's denim with tuxedo buttons.
It's not Hamada like at all.
Yeah he likes this type.
You got your buttons in the wrong place.
It looks good.
He's so pumped!
He gets pumped so easily.
So far, Kimura seems to be happy about his gifts.
Now Hosei's turn, can he continue the trend?
I though of exploring...
Look at his bag again!
Oi you! Stop messing around!
What is this!?
Did you buy adult toys!? Is there lotion inside that!?
I bought it at the same place.
But that same place had a lot of stuff that you really like.
I think it's a bit too young for me though. It's more for people in their 20's.
Yeah, you don't understand.
But you haven't aged.
Woah, what the hell is this? This is a joke right!?
Pajamas?
It's not pajamas.
It looks hot and like it'll generate heaps of static shock.
Looks too hot to wear.
It's so good though.
I swear I've seen this in disney before.
The sleeves are out of place!
What the hell is this?
The length of the sleeves are perfect for Tsukitei Happou.
It's the kind that he likes.
Last up is Matsumoto.
I got this at Daikanyama. When I first saw it I thought it was the one,
but I still went to look for more. However I just had to come back for this one.
This is so swag!
That's for the younger Kimura.
Look at how swag this is.
This is really swag.
I see, I see.
He likes this type of colors the best.
See? Doesn't it look good?
I see.
I see. This one...
Isn't this good?
It looks like he has to go to the hospital.
Just what is his favorite top?
Thank you so much everyone.
This one.
Hell yeah!
Thank you.
I like the pattern and the color.
Don't you have one like this already?
I didnt have this blue type.
Second place was Matsumoto's Jacket. And third the Jacket Hamada brought.
And now, which one is the worst?
This one.
It wasn't surprising at all.
With an obvious result, Hosei has to pay.
The last item is a book. First up Hamada.
Well I had a pretty hard time looking for a book, but I did know that recently Kimura had moved houses.
I thought if Kimura was at home with some time to spare, and if he wants to do something. Like growing vegetables or something.
Because he had just moved houses, Hamada had bought a book on gardening.
Well his wife makes a lot of things.
No no that's wrong. The wife hates you.
That's not good.
Hosei bought a book for the Kyoto local Kimura.
Again?
Doesn't it piss you off? He carries the same freaking bag.
It's the same bag.
No no no.
Wait what, why would you even buy that for a local?
Look at Kimura-san. He's blushing.
You mean he's pumped up.
(TL note: Hosei said Kouchyou (blushing) instead of Kouyou (pumped up))
Don't use my lines and make mistakes!
Next is the book that Endo thinks Kimura likes.
Well before Kimura-san said "I really like maps" and I was surprised about it.
Oh,"Tokyo in the Edo period"
You can see how modern Tokyo and Tokyo in the Edo period compare to each other.
You can compare them!?
I'm also kind of interested as well.
That face!
Your so into it!
Endo's book contains a comparison between the old and new Tokyo maps.
For a person that enjoys maps and geography it's an absolute sensation.
It looks fun to read.
He says "it looks fun."
He said it.
How's Tanaka's book, who's done mediocre so far.
I don't think he likes unnecessary things so...
Ehhhh?!
He's surprised.
Wait is it good or bad?
Ah no no no no.
I've been saved!
Wait really? Is it bad?
I don't do this type of shopping.
(TL note: The book Tanaka got is a book about shopping online, over the phone and through TV)
Come back, there's no point continuing.
What really!?
Last Is Matsumoto's chosen book.
Before the final shooting, Matsumoto is...
Isn't this it? A photobook of OOOO
I don't think Kimura will hate this. He'll read this often.
In the end, what kind of book did Matsumoto choose?
Lastly, Matsumoto's book. What did he choose for Kimura?
I knew that Kimura-san likes maps and Geography. So I thought Endo did a really good job.
So I thought about that fact, and that's why I went with this.
Well, it's a photobook.
This is a book which shows many photos taken from a helicopter bird's eye view. It enables the reader to see photos that aren't usually able to be seen often.
It's from a bird's eye view.
Woah this feels good.
How is it Endo? what do you mean it feels good?
Well it made me feel good when I looked at it.
Look the airplane's flying! It's from the top of the airplane.
Isn't this good?
It's good.
Isn't this good already?
If you want it this badly just rank it first and read it later.
Oh look its Universal Studios!
That's enough!
Even Haneda is here. Ginza too.
Hurry up you two.
Sakuragi-chou!
Stop making that face!
Hurry up!
Now the announcement! But...
Can I announce the last place first please? I want 2 people to pay for their books.
There are two last places?
Last are...
Kimura-san, there was another book called "Encyclopedia of Kyoto." If I had bought that what would have happened?
Well the point is I'm not interested in Kyoto.
He's not interested in Kyoto.
Look he's struggling. Everyone is struggling.
Even the cameraman is struggling.
Stop trying to make yourself look better.
It's difficult.
What will be Kimura's favorite book?
My favorite is...
this one.
Congratulations! So it was that one huh?
It was really interesting Endo, but I'm not that interested in history.
Yeah Kimura, doesn't really look at his past.
That's why he is Batsu 5.
I'm Batsu 4. (TL note: This is a reference to how many times Kimura has married.)
Hosei and Tanaka had to pay for their own items.
Who can you guess correctly then?
I can guess anyone.
I think you know too little.
Maybe Ohnuma-san?
(TL note: One of Gaki's producers)
I don't even want to guess Ohnuma-san's likes.
At least make it a celebrity.