Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
More clips? Subscribe to this channel: Shion (ガキの使い用)!
For other gaki clips visit www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!
Show business world man vs man home cooking showdown!
Yeaaahhh!!
So, guys
This is going to be good!
Today we'll have a home cooking showdown, it seems  - Yeah!
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi___Hamada Masatoshi
And that's why you're all wearing an apron
Yeah!
Right! Exactly!
Yours will be the Team Gaki
Yeah!
And this time we'll also have a guest with us
Eeeh...
So it'll basically be Team Gaki vs the guest
Cocorico
Endo Shouzo______Tanaka Naoki
I'll have you prepare something to eat
Yamazaki Housei
To be honest I don't think we're really that good at this
Cooking showdown! Team Gaki vs the guest!
But we can gather our forces being 4 people!     - Yeah, that's it!
So we can actually do something
Yeah, we can manage it      We can do it, right?
We may win
Hamada will eat both teams' dishes and judge them
I'll be eating what you've cooked in the end
And the best dish
Yes?
Will earn the prize
100'000 Yen!
＊Winning team will get the 100'000 Yen prize!
That's awesome!
Now we're talking!
Is it really okay for it to be this way?
Well
I mean, the prize and everything
The fact there's no punishment...
Things like those
It's just for fun
Lightheartedly
It's not like you're doing something bad, you don't deserve punishments
Right   Absolutely right!
Ok, so
Combine your abilities all together
Yeah!
To face the challenger, which is this person!
Who?
Kishibe Shiro-san!
＊A japanese movie / drama actor from Kyoto
Home Cooking Showdown Guest
Kishibe Shiro
Please!
Thanks for coming!
It's a pleasure!
Wha-!
What?!
Kishibe-san!
Wha-
Kishibe-san!!
What just happened to Kishibe's body?!
Suddenly, Kishibe falls down in a deep hole under the ground
Just what happened to him?
(this is a no-profit fansub made by a fan for other fans. All copyrights belong to the original creators)
If you enjoyed my clips, follow/subscribe to this channel/my wordpress/twitter/ etc. to show support!
New clips will be uploaded on this channel,
subscribe so you won't miss any of them!
All my Gaki Clips are always available at www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Also, visit www.foregroundnoises.wordpress.com
Twitter: @FGRNDNoises
Facebook: /sanzunokawa
Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
More clips? Subscribe to this channel: Shion (ガキの使い用)!
Kishibe-san?
What the hell!
I wouldn't say "what the hell"...
Why is there a boobie trap in here?
We don't...
Uhh...
We have no idea, really
Wait, what's this all about...?
A-are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine...
But what the hell are you planning?
Well, today there's a cooking showdown...
Yeah...
Well, I'm just glad I'm unharmed
Yes, you're right
Maybe this was something from a previous recording or such...
Something they left behind?
Yeah, exactly
Yeah, must be it
Yeah but still today it'll be impossible to me
Please don't say such things...
We're sorry
Do you have any idea who did this?
We have no idea...
I used to be filthy rich, you know that?
Yeah we're really...
Are you really ok?
Yeah I'm fine but I'm done with this today
Come on, don't say so!
Come on!
Please reconsider it...
With his mood down, Kishibe says he want to have a talk with the producer
Kishibe, in a completely heavy mood due the unexpected happening
Returns for a moment in the recording bus to have a talk with the producers
I'm going to have a talk with the producer
Uh...
You know...
About what they've been doing
Huh?
Okay but be sure to settle this down so...
Kishibe-san?
Kishibe-san!
What?
Settle this down and let's start this all anew!
For now I just have to
Calm down my spirits
So it would be better to give it some time
Because right now it's really impossible to me
Just let me relax a bit
Sorry about this
Ok but
Please be sure t-
KISHIBE-SAN!!
Kishibe-san!
Kishibe-san!!
Why are there so many boobie traps in such place?!
There was a hole even on that spot
Kishibe is yet again absorbed by the abyss
Could this be the definition of "It never rains but it pours?"
Kishibe-san!
What's happening?
Come on!
Woah, what the-!
For real?!
Hey!
Aaah, I'm sorry! Sorry for this!
Sorry for this!
Who the fuck dug holes in here?!
This is really...
Who is the executive producer?
The executive producer...?
Uhm... it's Suga
I mean, the one beyond the whole thing
Should be Suga-san...
I'd like to have a talk with him in the bus
A moment please, for now
This is just messed up
It's just horrible, didn't expect this from my beloved Downtown...
With bitternes all over his face, Kishibe parts from them and gets on the bus
The guest Kishibe Shiro ends up secluding himself
together with the producer inside the recording bus
The crew faces him once more in order
to discuss about doing the cooking showdown
Shortly thereafter, the crew tries to persuade the embittered Kishibe
But by which conditions will Kishibe grant them to resume the shooting?
Excuse us...
Uhm...
We...
We're here for the filming
You know, me too
I went through lots of things
Even pitiable ones I must say
Still, I could actually enjoy all these things
Of course, I understand...
But I never fell down a hole before
Yes...
That was my first time falling down a hole
I understan-
Truth is, I enjoyed falling too
Yes...
But by now I can't enjoy this all anymore
A thing as crazy as this
Was something new even for me
Y-yes...
I have no idea whose idea was this, but it was already there filled with rubber, right?
I wonder...
I don't know who worked for that
I guess we can settle all of this talking about money
This thing can become a bit of a trouble for you
I don't want to make a fuss out of this though
A moment, we're not going to use cameras for now but...
Of course you're not
How... much...?
Well...
Well, today I came here for 50'000 Yen, so...
I guess that's what we call "luxury"...
Pay me at least 8 times this amount!
8 times?!
Eightfold!
Eightfold he says...
I'm not asking for ten times the price!
Yeah, eight times...
Yes
Eightfold...
That will make 400'000 Yen
Indeed
Can you manage to compensate me with these 400'000 Yen, producer?
I will, I will...
Kobayashi Hiromichi
Producer
Be sure to provide them to me as fast as possible
Sure, just...
Just look how muddy my induments got, I'm not waiting 2-3 months for my refund
Uhm...
We'll be sure to include the laundry charge...
If that's the case, then make it 8.5 times the original amount
Eh? Which is--
Wha-
Oh, for the laundry charge...
Yeah, the laundry charge
Ok, thanks! We'll wait you!
Our guest Kishibe Shirou has someway agreed to have a 8.5x times payback including the laundry charge
With an amount of 8.5x times the price plus laundry charge, Kishibe agreed on resuming the show
Thinking about the incidents happened until now
We can easily state this one was the most expensive
As expected from our guest of honour Kishibe Shiro
Ok so, let's get Kishibe out the bus and bring him there...
Yeah
So we can start this thing as soon as possible
Ok, got it
Are we doing this?
Yes!
So, Kishibe-san let's move together towards the set...
This way please!
Once you get here we'll start this
Huh?
This way please, let's just do this
Please
Wait this
This is a bit dirty, it's bad
You're right
Oh I understand
We'll deal with this once you're here
We'll pay for that, so...
Yeah
It's fine
We're counting on you
Let's go
Let's move towards the set
WHAT?!
Kishibe-san!!
Kishibe-san!
Kishibe-san...
Just who dug up all these boobie traps?
There are boobie traps even right in front of the bus
Kishibe Shiro, 53 years old: A man with no luck whatsoever
Kishibe-san!
Gimme a break!
Are you okay Kishibe-san?
This is bad, this is sooo bad
With this I can't an-
Please ask the staff to come here and lend me a hand
Right, but yeah, uh...
I can't move my legs at all like this
Ah, got it
We're sorry
He's right, he's right
I'm actually 20 years older than my actual age, you know
I-is a hand going to help?
Sorry
Careful careful careful!
Watch out!
Come on, come on, almost there
Okay, he came out
Good, good
Thanks
How did these holes happen?
Well, I'm going home
No!
Nononono!
No, please wait!
Wait just a momen-
Uhhh...
Thanks
Keep up the good work
Cooking...
What?
We still haven't cooked yet
The cooking showdown
Yeah, the "man vs man cooking showdown"
You were planning to film it in here?
Yes
And I was meant to be part of it?
As a guest
Yeah we invited you as a guest
A guest?  Exactly
You're saying I'm today's guest?!
Our guest Kishibe Shiro is gradually dismantling
That's right   ....Kishibe-san?
And what are we going to do from now on?
A cooking showdown
Thanks
Where are we going to have it?
Over there
On the other side
Okay
Let's do this
Everyone's walking before Kishibe Shiro
To avoid having him falling again in a boobie trap
Matsumoto leads the way so his senpai Kishibe won't fall again in a hole
But even by this, his looks doesn't appear to be the best
It's okay, it's okay
Everything's normal
We're finally here, let's get through this
Right!
Let's do this
We're ready!
Starting in 5... 4... 3... 2...
Remaining seconds before the settled anew show: 5
Remaining seconds before the settled anew show: 4
Remaining seconds before the settled anew show: 3
Remaining seconds before the settled anew show: 2
First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!
Show business world man vs man home cooking showdown!
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi___Matsumoto Hitoshi
YEEEEEAHH!!
Ok, with that being said...
Yeah
We welcome Mr. Kishibe Shiro as our guest for today!
Yeeeahh!
Welcome!         A man-vs-man match?      Yeah, a cooking showdown
home-cooking showdown guest
Kishibe Shiro
It will be Team Gaki no Tsukai vs Kishibe Shiro
Yes
Well, to be honest I don't think we're that good,
But there are 4 of us together, so we won't lose!
Cocorico
Endo Shouzo_____Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Housei
Am i right?!         You bet it!       We won't lose!        Bring it!
Cooking showdown! Team Gaki vs today's guest
And Hamada will judge our dishes     That's right!
I'll be eating both your dishes
Hamada will judge and compare both dishes by tasting them
And the most delicious one will be rewarded with a prize of 100'000 Yen!
The winning team will earn the 100'000 Yen money prize
Thanks a lot!       Thank you!
So, I'll have both your teams go to the kitchen corner
We have a time limit for this right?
Yes, that's the point of the showdown
Okay, let's start!
Please!
KISHIBE-SAN!
COME ON!!
Why was there a boobie trap even in that place!?
A boobie trap was even before the kitchen corner
Without a doubt, this will leave Kishibe shocked by surprise
Kishibe-san!
Come on!
Kishibe-san...
Kishibe-san!
We're so sorry
Even now it-
This is crazy
We're so sorry
Sorry
Sorry for this
What is a "sorry" good for, I mean-
YOU CAN ONLY PAY ME FOR THIS!
Sorry...
GO GET ME THE MONEY!
Translation, subtitles & encoding by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
More clips? Subscribe to this channel: Shion (ガキの使い用)!
For other gaki clips visit www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
I'll buy me a house with those
Because of the boobie traps
Today's shooting has ended
Way before we planned
TL note: ain't happening lol
We'll now broadcast
An unreleased collection
of previous Gaki no Tsukai talk