Downtown no
Gaki no Tsukai
Ya Arahende
Translator: Staccato
Back again, Gaki's Jiji-Nuki!
Gaki Jiji-nuki (Old Man)
The cards being used will have various different original subjects on them.
Like the game Old Maid, match the cards to deplete your hand.
Whoever's left with the one unmatchable card must follow its orders.
Let's get going.
Matsumoto Hitoshi      Hamada Masatoshi
Tsukitei Hosei        Endo Shozo       Tanaka Naoki
Bun-chan's here today.
No he's not.
He is this time.
Here in his prime.
Picking the dealer, right?
Dealer decided by roulette.
Endo popping up a lot.
Feels like it.
Endo-san
Yes
You are now the dealer.
The theme for this game is
"Vicious Fight with Big Game"
Vicious Fight with Big Game.
Written on these cards are various big game animals.
But what is the vicious fight?
The loser will, with all their strength, fight a stuffed animal.
Got it.
Fight a stuffed big game animal with all your strength
Whatever happens we have to lose.
Let's fight a stuffed animal with all we got.
Yes
Let's do it. Yes.
Picking the "Old Man" (players cannot look)
The 'Old Man" (Joker) card is...
Shark
This card.
Players have 6 cards. (Dealer has 5)
Please, please, I'm begging.
Alright, is it a bust?
It's all over the place.
Oh, there's lots written on these.
Ohh.
God was with me. If I may...
Eagle
It would suck to fight an eagle.
And then there's...
Eh?
Oh no, what.
Two pairs?
Seriously?
Lion
I'm honestly glad the lion is gone.
One card left
Eh?
Once he pulls my card I'm safe right?
HOLY
He's right!
I guess that can happen.
Because he's the dealer.
Yes
To have only 1 card at this point in the game.
Endo
has won!
Haah ha ha ha
I am sooo glad.
That's crazy.
I got a pair.
Ok ok.
Kangaroo
I had kangaroos.
This might end quickly.
Seriously though, it's going fast.
Everyone else got nothing.
Let's move on.
No, I have nothing.
Yama-chan takes...
"Old Man" starts
Takes the card, then Endo is done.
Shark
Joker
Thank you!
Uwa, fastest one hunh?
Fastest.
Fastest so far
The fact that there's nothing is amazing.
Even with an opening like that.
Well, a match is out there somewhere.
Yes, there was.
Elephant
C'mon, give me something.
I said give me something...
There's nothin'.
A vicious fight with big game...
A vicious fight with big game alright.
I really don't want to do it.
No, nothing
This is getting crazy.
It is crazy, seriously.
Endo
Endo was too fast
I think thats how it is.
Thats what it is.
Thank you so much for this.
Bear
Oh! A match!
A bear???
Getting a read on Hamada, Housei makes a pair.
Got it!
Rhino
Rhino!
Gradually the cards start matching up.
It came.
Alligator
This is something that our  children will do.
The children of the FUTURE.
Can't argue with that.
They will play this game.
The next generation
of comedians who won't even know us, will play.
The "Vicious fight with big game"
Although the game is going smoothly
Tanaka won't do well.
Once again, my new card is...
Damn thing came back again.
Old man shark starts making its rounds.
This card is back again.
You just mentioned it.
Came back?
What's your recommendation?
This one maybe?
And your most "not recommended" is?
I wouldn't suggest this one I think.
Which which which?
THAT ONE?!!?!
HELL YEAH!!!
Hell yeah...?
Sorry about that.
No match.
He didn't get a match!
Pick this one.
That's fine?
I extremely suggest it.
What is that! Damn it to hell.
You're... a snake.
Snake
It was the snake.
Bam!
And then...
Yes!
Octopus
Tanaka won!?
Giant Octopus!
Tanaka
has won!
Thank you giant octopus.
Why does Tanaka get to win?
Cards remaining
Down to just 3 players.
I hate this already.
Matsumoto-san, Matsumoto-san, big game.
Toneruzu
Ucchan Nannchann
Would never do this.
A vicious fight with big game
You just like that title!
No, no, no, no, no!
I ain't doing the vicious fight with big game.
Please do it.
I won't do it, therefore
I will leave it to you guys.
UWAAHHH!!!!
Come on!
AAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!
YES! YEEESSSSS!!!!!
YES!
YES!!
The place is heating up.
What is going on?
Enough Enough
The chances are high.
That's the thing.
Which one???
Your turn will decide it.
Not good! Not good!
Don't!
Gorilla
Hamada
has won!
Match!
Take it.
This is a big moment.
This is yours now.
Had enough? Seriously?
Come on, help me out.
Would you really be thankful?
Alright, this is big.
If you have that then...
It's pretty much a given.
Since I was 18 years old,
Since I was 18 years old, I've been doing this shit.
A vicious fight with big game?
Not for me.
No match. This game is screwed.
There's another chance.
Insane. This is Insane.
Matsumoto vs Housei. Where is this headed?
Now at Matsumoto.
Cards remaining
Yep.
The vicious big game fight.
He's attempting to limit any hint giving.
If I survive this I'm fine.
When in doubt, pick the middle.
A true student of the game.
Should I just throw them face up?
We're going.
The "I really don't want to do it"
Vicious fight with big game
Come on!
SAFE! SAFE! SAFE! SAFE!
SAFE! SAFE!
Monitor Lizard
Matsumoto
has won!
Let's see the rest.
Shark!
Stage is over there!
Go right ahead.
Vicious Fight: Shark
Oh I'm waiting.
It's the middle of the ocean.
He's drowning!
Pretty strong.
Stab it!
He's underwater now.
He's been bitten!!
You gonna lose?
A revenge bite!
How's that!
Nobody is laughing!!
Not even once.
And now he goes straight to dirty!
Not even one laugh.
Not even.
Wrapping up the shark.
Going down? A one shot down?
It got your mic, you're done.
I can't even...
You didn't get a single laugh.
I thought it would end if
someone just laughed once.
You got a lot of energy.
Next up, the second battle.
The theme for this game is "Strong one-liners"
Famous one line jokes are on these cards. If you lose, you must become the comedian and perform the joke.
Joker
That don't matter!
The joker for this round is Kojima Yoshio's "That don't matter!"
Jokes this time. What kinds will we see?
"Whoah! It's out!"
This pair has saved me a bit.
I'm Osamu-Chan!
This pair is also a blessing isn't it?
Panty Techs
Shimada Tamayo
I'm pretty weak at those.
It's long.
Game Starts!
You've got 3.
Hunh?
No, nothing.
Alright, I'm going.
Yes, thank you.
Stiiiiink
No one asked you to come
Ueki Hitoshi-San
This one's tough so thank god.
You gunna start goofing?
Goof? You bastard.
That was a textbook goof.
You wanna fight some big game?
Endo breaks open the first treasure of the game.
I love Lassen!
I'm fine with it ending that way.
With 2 pairs in a row, Endo is the first one out.
Endo
has won!
Thank you.
You looked like Ogata just now. That's not a good thing.
I guess, well its a joke so...
Nah, when you are doing that,
and say thank you,
and say thank you, it's a goof.
I see Ogata more like this.
Like this.
Oh ok.
I'm barely safe though.
Many people have said it before.
Thank you.
Things are moving!
The next play comes from Housei.
Revolution
Hosei
has won!
I want to see one of these.
Finally, Matsumoto moves forward.
YES!!
Empty head
Matsumoto
has won!
What are you going to get?
Cards remaining
Gotta go with this.
Wrong!
If Hamada ends up losing.
And if you don't know the joke
You could viciously
You could viciously fight big game.
After finishing the joke performance.
If you don't know it, that is.
IF I didn't.
We could do that.
Ramen, Tsukemen, I'm Ikemen (Handsome)
See, that's great.
This is it!
Hamada vs Tanaka!! How will it go?!
Tanaka do you know those jokes?
Cards remaining
Yes... They are jokes that I do know.
Getting Pissed while Smiling
Hamada
has won!
Getting pissed while smiling.
Takenaka Naoto-San
Takenaka-San
Tanaka is the loser!
Now, what is the joke?
Was it the "Hot Hot" one?
"That don't matter!" is the one you will do!
Kojima Yoshio's "That Don't Matter"
But but but but!
That don't matter!
Yeah! Oh Pa-pi~
You don't seem to know the joke.
Did you really not know it?
I knew it, and I felt a response to my performance.
Not in the slightest!
You disrespected the joke.
No I am not!
I did it with all my strength.
It goes "But But But But"
You trailed off.
I would never trail off in a game of punishment.
You couldn't capture the original spirit.
Let's just do the other thing.
You have deep hatred towards animals.
The viewers couldn't grasp it.
No screwing up this time.
Is that how it is?
Careful!
It's soo big!!!
Fight with Giraffe
Amazing!
Get away!
The neck is long, it is a Giraffe.
Oh! The neck!
Wow, crazy.
You're making weird sounds.
I got you now!
Amazing, get away!
Blam, blam, blam, blam.
We will think about which one gets broadcast.
I'm back.
Mix the two and you've got one good punishment.
To sum it up.
Yeah.
Uh, yes.
I can't stop sweating.
3rd Round: Punishment
Last up are the punishment games.
This time we will not reveal the joker, enjoy it!
Let the game begin!
I don't like the pain-inducing ones.
I hate them.
Most of these hurt pretty bad.
Most?
Adams Apple Pachinko
What the hell?
Did some dumb ass write this?
You saw something pretty dumb?
Seriously stupid...
Whoa, hey hey hey.
I thought you took two.
The two of you.
You two gonna vicious fight?
I thought he took two.
Comedian vicious fight?
Tanaka would absolutely lose that.
I would. I would.
Did you think you had one more?
Got one!
Bowling with a nose hook.
Bowling nose hook
Oh yessir.
You did that one.
Sun dried fish to the nose
Nothing at all!
Hand it over already.
Give me a minute to process.
Suggestion?
My recommendation is, this one.
This ONE!!!
HELL YEAH!!
You said it again.
"Hell yeah"
It doesn't seem to be funny.
Completely worthless.
"Hell yeah" is a no go.
Come on.
The middle!
Wait nothing. No, there's a match.
Paper fan the troublemaker
Paper fan the troublemaker.
A paper fanning from Hamada would suck.
But! Hamada won't be stopped.
Hell yea...
Saying that before you even pull the card...
Sun dried fish to the nose
Hamada
has won!
And riding Hamada's wave, Tanaka as well!
I'm out!
Struck with an exploding bolt
Good riddance to that.
Tanaka
has won!
Finally, Housei also has?
Fermented Tofu BOX
HELL YEAH!!
Flower Frog Stomach Drop
Hosei
has won!
This one's pretty "Hell Yeah"
That's the only one so I'll take it.
Alright!
Cards remaining
Are we really going to do these punishments?
I'm putting these three down face up.
YEAH!
FIRST!
THIS!
SHOCK MASK
SHOCK MASK!
There! Uhh, what is this?
Phf... erm... Fermented Tofu.
Fermented
Tofu
BOX
Shock
Mask
COME ON! COME ON!
Fermented
Tofu
BOX
Raw
Wasabi
in
Mouth
Shock
Mask
YES!
Endo's got a chance!
This is absolutely nuts.
Big chance for me.
Give me a sec...
They all perfectly DONT MATCH.
You are in trouble.
How you want to do it?
Lay them right there.
Seriously though pick a good one.
The middle!
You copied me.
At a time like this you pick middle.
No dice?
FUCK YES!!
You've got to be shitting me.
Nothing.
Put them down.
This gonna be the last one?
I've got nothing from however many pulls.
HELL YEAH!!
He didn't pick middle this time.
He said "Hail Yeah" so its bad luck.
"Hail Yeah"
You said "Hail Yeah" Matsumoto-San.
Shock Mask
Fermented Tofu BOX...
Fermented
Tofu
BOX
Shock
Mask
Raw
Wasabi
in
Mouth
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
WHAT THE HELL!!
You traded into the
You traded into the exact same hand?
Matsumoto in trouble! What will happen?
Who will take the punishment? Matsumoto or Endo!?
Cards remaining
Line them up.
What is this battle?
It's really not looking good for me.
It should be mostly decided by now.
Middle!
Endo come on.
Raw Wasabi
in the Mouth
Endo
has won!
This is...
So the punishment is?
Fermented Tofu BOX
Joker
Stink-type punishment.
I'm getting away.
You put your head in the box?... You can sit if you want.
It's that fermented SHIT
Yea, it's shitty.
It stinks.
Take a seat.
This is more than I expected.
Yes.
How do you put it in?
Put it in the front corner.
Shut the lid.
STINKS!
That's it! LET ME OUT!
It's INSANE.
It's INSANE!
IT STINKS!
He always says that on these punishments.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
I'm stiff today.