This is a recap, skip to 6:24 for new stuff or download the hardsub version.
The game continues
Will they succeed?
This is a non-profit sub by a fan for fans
This sub is provided as is with all errors
It ended like this, huh
This is okay right?
No this is not okay
I thought he had the 100 card
But this is still pretty high
Or maybe the 99 card
See if Matsumoto only had one card left,
then I might've played my card
But he still had two
Sorry but, just one more time!
Any objections? None right?
Well for the 2 card version
I want to end on a good note
Well it was pretty fun so
It's fine if just end here
One final round, will they succeed?
That was fast wasn't it
It was fast
I see
But that's how it is
So it's like this huh
Let's begin
Ready, Start
Let's finish this
I want us to win
Are you serious
No, definitely some of you are
Overthinking this
What is that face?
What does that face mean?
Well yeah, that makes sense
Well
It's scary isn't it
This is good, this is good
Remaining Cards
Housei  Matsumoto  Hamada    Endo     Tanaka
He's not even being the master
He's probably like
Putting on a comedian vibe
Such a subtle point
He's just making funny faces
Probably
I had to point that out
You're done?
I'm all out
I'm counting on you
It's become precarious
Indeed
Done!
Remaining Cards
Housei  Matsumoto  Hamada    Endo     Tanaka
How many cards are left? Three?
Only three, definitely doable
Each of them has one, we can do this
I don't understand their faces at all
I see
It's the last 2 cards
Seriously, please
Eh? Seriously?
It's Tamura Masakazu
He's pretty master-like now
But he's also kind of...
You're right
Please, it's the last card
It's the last one
He's checking your master level
He really is pretty master-like
He's pretty master-like
He's performing at a high level
Whether his audience is big or small
He properly does the same bit
He's unwavering
Once he's decided he's completely set on it
Exactly on time!
Please be it
It would have been better if he was more master-like
But he was making such a face
But you had a 90
That was great
That felt good
This is pretty fun
Up Next: A French Strategy Game!
Let's Play World Tabletop Games!
The next tabletop game is-
This one
Is called "Quoridor"
Each of us will pick a piece
France: "Quoridor"
Each piece starts on one side of the board
The first one to reach the other side wins
But also
Each of us gets 5 blocks we can place
I see, we can't go through them
On your turn, you can move your piece or
Or you can place a block between the tiles
And it blocks two tiles
And if this happens then
You have to go around it
Exactly
You use the blocks to force paths
It's that kind of game
This time the four will play the game without Tanaka
Then let's start from Endo
I see
No big moves, just a slow advance
I place it on its side?
Yes on its side
It blocks two tiles?
Yes
It blocks two tiles...
If you use a block, you must block two tiles
So you have to block two
I wish I knew that earlier
That's huge
You can't block just one
You might obstruct yourself too
I see, I see
Right in front of Endo
Now it's Hosei's turn
To the side right, since you couldn't go forward
This is bad isn't it
Your own wall has come back to bite you
What do you think you're doing
What are you doing, this is terrible
It's become like this?
This guy is so unreasonable
Endo and Matsumoto both blocked, a big play!
But we only have five blocks
If we only have five...
Not much you can do
So I can't move forward?
Right, you can't move into another piece's space
Nice
Oh, nice
Hosei's path is blocked!
Nice, Endo
Ah I see, you're blocking Hosei
Matsumoto and Endo both blocked!
What are you doing?
You're not even a part of this
I'm just planning ahead
This is bullying!
Quite a barricade has formed
Quite a detour now
Hosei is boxed in!
Hosei is seriously...
Matsumoto and Endo both blocked!
Now wait a minute this isn't funny
Me and Endo
only have one tile to use!
Only path
Seriously this is impossible for me
Me and Endo are in the worst position
What do we do?
Even if I move down there
That makes sense
Hamada's path is blocked!
If you put it there it's hard for me
Matsumoto
The blocks have slowed the game down
Eh!?
Is he allowed to do that!?
Their only path is even more blocked
Matsumoto this is impossible
Why would you do that?
I've never even blocked you before
A Super Spartan State!
No it's just that kind of game
Why are you going after me so hard
This became incredibly Spartan
It continues! The crushing battle
"Quoridor"
The French Strategy Game
Who will be the first to reach the goal?
Eh, hang on
Yeah he needs to be stopped
Hamada's path's path is blocked!
But Hosei needs to be blocked too
Hosei is just 1 tile away
I can block Hosei but...
Hosei's path is blocked!
Then I'll stop him here
Yeah, right there
Hosei's path is blocked!
So here, this is the end
Right, that's the end
Hosei can reach the end in 3 moves
If I do this we'll be good right?
Hosei's path is blocked!
Just now I
Used my last piece for everyone's sake
You're really angry aren't you
Matsumoto's path is blocked!
So blatant
He's incredibly angry
We need to stop him too
Only two more tiles
Endo's path is blocked!
I expected as much
So hostile!
There's no more blocks
We're in the endgame now
What do I do?
Well of course
This isn't blocked
Hosei isn't blocked
My goal is over here?
No it's here
Eh, hang on, seriously?
Matsumoto's path is blocked!
This has nothing to do with you!
Me and you are aiming for different schools
You can just go to whatever school you like
This is weird
It's not weird
You're out of walls now right?
Yeah I'm all out
Eh, hang on
Now that it's like this, I'm in a pretty bad spot
Endo's path is blocked!
Of course
But now Hosei is out of walls too
Yeah and I'm all out too
My turn right?
What's up with this? Shouldn't it be like this?
Each of them blocks two so
This makes a huge difference
I wish their size was correct
Such a narrow passage
It's my dream school, why is everyone getting in my way?
I didn't choose such hard place
Finally, the battle reaches its conclusion!
"Quoridor"
The French Strategy Game
It's finally settled, who is the winner?
It looks like
The only thing I can do
Is this
Hamada's path is blocked!
I have two blocks left...
Wait you still have two blocks!?
Yeah I do
Incredible
But still
This is bad, he's only two away
I'm already
unstoppable
He's right, we can't put block him
Before this we must've screwed up
Aah, we've lost
You guys ****** me way too much
Well it can't be helped
You absolutely would not let me go to my school
No we weren't doing that
You just can't help but get in my way
Matsumoto's path is blocked!
Sorry this was the only play left
Wait wait wait
Translation - Tekno, Typesetting - Teknova, Timing - Teknonavi, QA - TeknoProasheck
It was the only move left
You keep increasing it
An amazing road has formed
This is so stupid
What the hell is this!
This one is Hosei's too
And now I win
Hosei's Victory!
That took quite some time
Yes, surprisingly so
That was fun wasn't it?
Yeah it was