Matsumoto-san,
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
Yes, yes?
We're back with the highly rated Jiji-Nuki
No no, not so sure about that
*TN: Gaki no Tsukai Production Supervisor
The person that likes this the most is Yanaoka*
He can keep the production costs low for this
Especially since we're put in this jail of a room...
It's only us five in here, too
You can't play this game sober
Gotta drink some tequila
I'd like to do this game while drunk
(Saying something about this game being impossible)
You've got some terrible memories from this Hamada-san
You got owned
*TN: Konbu is a seaweed heavily used in Japanese food
by that giant konbu* once
Konbu Slap
Past Batsu Game
The Konbu Slap punishment was crazy
The BPO* probably saw that and made their decision
TN: the BPO, an ethics watchdog group,
made recommendations against pain for comedy
Probably
Comedy based on pain, right?
That probably it, the BPO decided after that punishment
Typesetting: u/this_guys_a_t***
Translation: u/classicalover
Downtown no
Gaki no Tsukai
Ya Arahende
Presenting: Gaki Jiji-Nuki
The cards being used will have various different original subjects on them
Like the game Old Maid, match the cards to deplete your hand
Whoever is left with the one unmatchable card must follow its orders
First let's use the roulette to pick the dealer
Dealer decided by roulette
Can I spin?
Every goddamn time you do this
And every time you're first right?
Spin it more!
Something is up with the bearings
Before I announce the first topic,
Draw one card from the pile
and show it to the camera
Old Maid Card Reveal
Here I go!
ytivaC a
toG ohW
rotagillA ehT
Excuse me, the card is upside down
It's upside down.
What's "upsighdown?"
How can you not understand
Come on man
If you think about the word in kanji you'd understand
I processed it in katakana
The Alligator
Who Got
a Cavity
The word is everywhere on cardboard boxes
Please deal the cards
6 cards per person (5 for the dealer)
Before you look at your cards...
It pisses me off that you're a know-it-all
Why does it piss you off?
You could do whatever you want with the game
Ah! No way, you think I would cheat? I would never
You do it all the time
All the time!?
Excuse me, I can't play this game with that kind of attitude
It's been like that
for several years already
No it hasn't!
You're going too far into his weird side
Too far
This round's theme is...
Create a Nursery Rhyme
This is the second time right?
Yes, we had this theme previously
A fictional nursery rhyme's title is written on each card
Create and sing the fictional nursery rhyme
The loser must sing a nursery rhyme from the remaining card
I had the punishment last time,
it's actually really hard
Pretty challenging
I'll do ANYTHING to avoid this one
We're all trying to avoid this
First round: Nursery Rhyme
Here are the cards. Can Matsumoto get his revenge?
"Old Man" starts
Joker
The Alligator
Who Got
a Cavity
Nothing matches
I've got nothing too
I'll just take a card from the top
"The Ant Progresses"
Pair
The Ant
Progresses
My turn to draw right? Okay
I've gotta check carefully for pairs
'Cause you missed pairs before
Well, I think it's fine not to notice
That's why he got konbu slapped
I'd hate to get slapped by konbu from that...
Damn, I got slapped by konbu because of that?
That was the worst
You probably have konbu minerals left on your body
Ah, this should match
Here's a pair
Pair
Pikarin
of
Mt. Gorogoro
Nice
Joker
The Alligator
Who Got
a Cavity
After that, the pairs keep coming
A match!
I got "Liar Tanuki"
Liar
Tanuki
Pair
I've got "Whimpering Bear"
Whimpering Bear
While other cards are being matched...
NOTHING
I'm checking properly
If this keeps going
let's just say Hamada gets the punishment
4th Round Cards Left
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING
5th Round Cards Left
Give me something
Gimme a damn break
Joker
The Alligator
Who Got
a Cavity
You have NOTHING good!
He's missing the pairs in his deck again isn't he?
No I'm not, I'm not, really I don't have any
Only Hamada doesn't have a single match
Cards Remaining
The first one to win is...
Joker
The Alligator
Who Got
a Cavity
I'll choose this one.
This is hard.
Card: Kichintosan
I matched!
Endo
has won!
Kichintosan
Pair
Kichintosan?
Kichintosan, what the hell?
Don't wanna do that one
Joker
The Alligator
Who Got
a Cavity
Next up to win is...
Card: Bye-Bye Sacchan
What, for real?
Excuse me, I'm second
Tanaka
has won!
Bye-Bye
Sacchan
Pair
Thank you, "Bye-Bye Sacchan"
Nothing we can do about that.
I still haven't got ONE pair!
I guess even that happens too
You won't get a pair for the rest of your life
No way I won't get one
Holy sh*t, finally got one
"Belly Button Sticking Out"
Belly Button
Sticking Out
Pair
After eight rounds, Hamada finally gets a pair
Cards Remaining
Hosei draws for the win
However, Hosei only has two cards left
Man I hate this!
Joker
The Alligator
Who Got
a Cavity
Monster's
Meal
Pair
Hosei
has won!
"The Monster's Meal"
Nice one!
It's a battle between Downtown!
So it has become
Who will sing the fictional nursery rhyme?
Only Downtown remain!
If I don't get a pair here I'm screwed
Cards Remaining
This is bad
especially if you don't get a pair
Joker
The Alligator
Who Got
a Cavity
I hate this
This isn't a game to play sober
Pair
The Thieving King
"The Thieving King"
Isn't this the last draw?
Cards Remaining
Matsumoto draws for the win
If he matches, yeah
You have a 2/3 chance of winning
Joker
The Alligator
Who Got
a Cavity
I'm thinking soon that
I'm gonna get the punishment
You shouldn't do that
Just take a breath
I hate this,
I F*CKING HATE THIS
This isn't a game you play sober!
I choose the middle one!
What did he draw?
Maybe I should cover the one I drew...
Ehh--wh-what, it's wrong
It doesn't match!
Hamada you have a big chance!
Cards Remaining
Hamada draws for the win
This is judgement time
You'll want to make it this time
Gosh this is exhausting
Now I have a 2/3 chance
Whatever, here you go
Joker
The Alligator
Who Got
a Cavity
You sure?
He drew, here we go
Which is it?
It's down to this card, 2/3 chance
Pair
The Girl Who Turned Into a Frog
Hamada
has won!
Which means...?
It's one or the other
I Hate Green Bell Peppers
Pair
This matched, so
WTF, this is the first time I've seen this card
"The Alligator Who Got a Cavity"
Matsumoto's Nursery Rhyme
The Alligator
Who Got
a Cavity
The alligator~ The alligator~
got a cavity, a cavity~
He's just repeating the title
When it got the cavity~
it also got an autograph~
WAO!
The f*ck?
THAT WAS THE WORST!!
The f*ck was that?
THIS SUCKS SO BAD
I so flustered that I used Okada's* gag
*TN: Keisuke Okada
WAO!!
Getting someone to sightread and sing this,
that's messed up!
Even with 40 years
as a veteran comedian!!
This round's theme is...
Go all out! Animal Imitation.
Imitate Animal Sounds
Show off an all-out animal sound imitation
Next is an all-out animal sound imitation
Try to guess what the punishment might be!
"Old Man" starts
Without further ado, let's start!
Joker
Horse
Pair
Horse, huh?
Would suck to do a horse imitation
You got one right?
Yeah you saved me
Kangaroo
Pair
Oh damn, that would've been tough
Crow
Pair
The difficult topic candidates are gradually ruled out
Alright...I matched the cat
Cat
Pair
However, on Hamada's end...
Cho!
CHO!
Are you serious?
It's "Cho mate yo."
*TN: Line by Takuya Kimura
CHO MATE YO!
Only Hamada is left with the starting cards
Joker
Nope that wasn't it
Could you please face the cards to the camera...
Sorry
The inner workings of TV...
How much is it worth, having the cards face the TV?
Are you all stupid?
Okay you done filming them?
I'll go with this one
No matches, really?
Cho mate yo...
You're familiar with "Cho mate yo" huh
Okay, I'll take this one
Lion
Pair
Hamada surges forward from last place
Joker
This is fun
Got another!
Elephant
Pair
Damn, you're first!
Put the cards in the circle properly, OK?
Maybe he should be disqualified for that?
Stop saying stupid sh*t!
Just because it's sticking out the circle!?
Okay, from now on, don't do that
It gets confusing otherwise
Okay fine
since it's a game of nerves
Hurry up and take it
Hamada
Let's see if this matches your card
has won!
No pair
Cards Remaining
My cards at the beginning came back...
The first ones?
Joker
Thank you so much!
Damn really?
Pair
Sea lion
Endo
has won!
Wow
How come it seems like I'm in an unfair position?
Cards Remaining
Everyone draws to win
No, you're in a super good position
You have a 2/3 chance
Matsumoto draws for the win
I have one card
Lemme show the cards
If you draw the right one you win
Wait stop
I just need to avoid this for Matsumoto to lose
Joker
Come on no more!
He switched
Here I go
Yes...yes...
YESSSS!!!
Schadenfreude
YES YES YES YES
Your draw
Yes
Why didn't he get it with a 2/3 chance
From here it gets tough
Cards Remaining
Tanaka draws for the win
So you've got a 1/3 chance right?
Yep
This is gonna be tough
Hosei-san...
Let's just stop, just let Tanaka be punished
Joker
Stop it
Yes
Tanaka should get punished, he likes animals anyway
Amirite?
Gimme a break
Stop it
Stop that, don't win
Aaaah, and it's flipped too
How is this gonna end up?
Yessssss
Who will do the all-out animal imitation?
The three are in a stalemate battle
Cards Remaining
Hosei draws for the win
Please
THIS ONE
What's it gonna be
Joker
God's Right Hand
Stop that
Maybe the cards were switched...
I'm doing it
One more chance!
Okay okay okay okay
One more chance, Yamasaki Hosei wasn't able to clear!
Cards Remaining
Matsumoto draws for the win
No luck for Yamasaki
I should be able to clear, right?
It's all down to this draw
Joker
This one
What's the verdict?
Lose
Ha! He wishes for your loss
This one
Let's see
Cards Remaining
Matsumoto draws for the win
What's the verdict?
Lose
Joker
Pair
Pig
Matsumoto
has won!
The pig is matched
The worst cards are left
If this matches your card you win
Cards Remaining
Tanaka draws for the win
Yep
Anyway here's his card
Joker
SHHHHHHHHH
This could match
PLEASE BE A PAIR!!
It really sucks doesn't it
F*CK YEAHHHHH!!
YATTA!!
Otter
Pair
Tanaka
has won!
It came finally!
Awesome
He did a weird pose
Bear
Bear!?
Everyone knows bears, right?
Animal Sound Imitation
Bear
Go all out.
It's not even bear-like.
Oh, he went for it.
The world of comedy just
sank in quality
3rd Round: Batsu Game
Next up: Batsu Game!
"A punishment without pain" is waiting for them!!
Cards Remaining
Crayfish Earring
Hamada talking
Underground
Fighter
Kick
This is messed up...
Joker
"Mustard Pie in the Face"
Mustard Pie in the Face
Pair
That's screwed up
This is so messed up
Ridiculous
I've got a pair
Pair
Rubber Strap to the Adam's Apple
You'd die
You'd actually die
As they fear the punishments on the cards,
"Old Man" starts
Endo-san, please draw a card
Cards Remaining
All of these are scary
I have a pair
As you should
"Gulping Down Squid Ink"
Joker
Gulping Down Squid Ink
Pair
WTF!!
Ah
Shouldn't this be an instant out?
Nothing!!
Come on...
There are so many
I got a pair
Really?
Hammer to the Shins
Pair
"Hammer to the Shins"
Hammer to the Shins!?
What the hell are they doing to us...
The scary cards continue to match
Yes, got a pair
Endo lays pair
Pair
Stinky
Hair Dryer
I can't do this
As I thought,
this one is crazy
"No Distance Tennis Ball Machine"
No Distance
Tennis Ball Machine
Pair
Out of their minds
Pisses me off
Pisses me off just from reading it
There's no konbu batsu right?
I haven't seen it yet
Konbu Slap
Last Ji-ji
We don't know, could be hiding somewhere
The members tremble in fear at the punishments...
Cards Remaining
The first to take the lead is...
Joker
Here I shall take the opportunity to draw...
Thank you very much
Sorry
What the hell are you saying
"Golf Ball Press to the Temples"
Golf Ball Press to the Temples
Pair
Which means...
Thank you very much
Hamada-san you're first!
Hamada
has won!
He has 0 cards
The konbu minerals are working
Protecting him
Joker
Following Hamada,
Don't match
Tanaka
has won!
"Nipple Clothespin Serve"
Nipple Clothespin Serve
Pair
Scary.
Shozo you draw from him right?
Cards Remaining
Endo draws for the win
If this matches I win right?
Don't match
I hate being left until the end
Shozo don't match
Please
Joker
Shozo stop it
I think it's fine if Shozo gets punished...
You have a chance to match!
Jumping on
Foot Rock Mat
Is it gonna match?
Did it match?
Wrong!!
Flash Cotton Scarf
The battle starts here
I've gotta get a pair here
Cards Remaining
What the helllllllll
Yep
Right?
What the hell is this
Well, you do have 3 cards
He's probably got a pair there
Right? For sure
Joker
God's Right Hand
He said that earlier too
The one that he didn't draw correctly
Right?
YESSSSSSS!!!!!!
Flash Cotton Scarf
Pair
"Flash Cotton Scarf"
Cards Remaining
Matsumoto draws for the win
Now it's Matsumoto's turn
If Matsumoto doesn't match,
Damn I've always been left until the very end today
Joker
Excuse me?
Makes my heart pound
IF you match here...
Please!!
Please!! This is important
This is important
Please
You can do it
What will happen?
Jumping on
Foot Rock Mat
Is it there?
Vertical reveal, vertical reveal...
Wet Slap
Vertical reveal......
It's backward so I can't read it
How annoying
Really?
Pair
Wet Towel
Slap
"Wet Towel Slap"
Alright, so that means Shozo you take this card
Matsumoto
has won!
Cards Remaining
Endo draws to win, Hosei to Batsu
You don't have a choice
That's correct
IF this is a pair,
Then you'll win.
Are we doing this already?
Joker
On the count of three
WAIT WAIT wait up
What happens if this matches my card?
What do you mean, matches?
Wait what? That's my...
This is Shozo's card
Can I show my card?
Yeah you can
You don't need to show yours
You don't need to show yours, but...
You can show yours, but
Nobody
will be watching
It's about if it matches
Wait, so if this matches my card, I win?
To summarize, if my card matches Shozo's you win
If it matches, right?
If it doesn't match you draw from Shozo
Ohhhhhh I get it
Cards Remaining
Endo draws to win, Hosei to Batsu
So the moment the card matches Shozo's you get punished
Who will get the punishment, Hosei or Endo?
Joker
Ready and...
Jumping on
Foot Rock Mat
Pair
Endo
has won!
So, Hosei Yamasaki,
Hosei, what do you get...
Eh? "Powerful Low Frequency Electric Shock"
Powerful
Low Freq
Electric Shock
I F*CKING HATE THIS!!
POWERFUL SHOCK MACHINE
Please stand on the punishment stage over there
Are we ready?
Joker
Powerful
Low Freq
Electric Shock
You got the bear punishment too
Here I would like
to make the announcement
This batsu will be
an air
punishment charade
So lame
It's how you always fake your punishment anyway
No I'm not
I'm not faking my punishments
This will be tough huh
This is a charade and is not real
Damn damn damn damn
There will not be a real shock machine
Recreating the batsu through an "air punishment"
Please act as if you were being punished with
the powerful low frequency shock machine
An "air punishment" game for Hosei!
Punishment with a powerful low frequency electric shock!
As the punishment progresses,
the shocks will get stronger
Yeah, as the levels increase
There's 10 levels
Up to 10 levels.
Switch on!
Right now it's level 2
Oh sh*t here it comes
It's only level 2
Okay level 3
Wait...
What the f*ck is this!?
Let's go from level 3 to level 5
Jumping from 3 to 5
Don't increase it so quickly!
He's even moving horizontally
I wonder why
There's no pain at all!
D-d-damn it hurts!
Let's use the "clenching"* switch
*TN: Matsumoto and Hamada misread "massage"
The "clenching"* switch is on
He's clenching
Level 6 and "clenching"
It's not hurting at all
He isn't saying anything either
Ah, eh, wha-, is happening?
It's at 7 now!
It's super powerful now
Wait, sto-, stop it!
It's at 7 now, 7!
Beating, beating and "clenching!"
Sto-, stop!
He isn't raising his voice at all!
*TN: Bonchi Osamu
It's Osamu-san
Come on doesn't it look good? It's Halloween-y
Halloween!?