TPF
The First Challenge of Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende
Risk your life for this taste! Get the 100 thousand yen! Kiki Non-Alcoholic Beer!
Hey guys, apparently Hamada is quite confident this time
Cocorico
Downtown
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hōsei
He said he would get the right one so quickly
No, that's not gonna happen
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
100 thousand yen will be given as a prize for correct answer, and a punishment for the wrong one!
Drink one non-alcoholic beer while blindfolded, and find the right one among 12 kinds,
Kiki Non-Alcoholic Beer
Yanaoka (staff member) was saying that Hamada is amazing
He said it can't be possible
So I have always been the last challenger so far, but today I want Hamada to be the last
Oh, so he's gonna go the last?
Yes let him go last
Let me be the first challenger today
This is the first time for me
You are the first!
You will be the first challenger then!
So, what about your experience?
Have you ever tried non-alcoholic beer?
I think I drink it about once a week
But I suppose you don't particularly choose "non-al" beer?
This is "Non-alcoholic beer"
Don't give it a shortened name like "Hama-sho"
Note: Hamada Shogo is a famous Japanese singer.
"Hamada Shogo", ok?
Non-alcoholic beer is a sparkling drink with beer flavor
Non-alcoholic Beer
Sparkling drink with beer flavor
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
We strictly picked 12 non-alcoholic beers which have 0% of alcohol
For the first challenger, Matsumoto
Premium Alcohol Free
(Asahi Beer)
*This is produced for people 20 years old and over
For Matsumoto
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
"Sapporo Premium Alcohol Free"
It has a rich taste which is quite close to the real beer
Ok, here I come...
Are you familiar with the taste?
I've tried this before!!
You have tried it huh?
You know the taste!
Yeah, tried it before
It's unexpectedly bitter...
I feel this challenge will be easy
It's gonna be so easy to be picked, otherwise I'm just an idiot
Yeah we will be happy if you get the right one by first challenge
Staff of Gaki are famous among TV industry
As they are a bunch of morons
Everybody's saying so
Who's saying so?
Even just ordinary housewives are saying so too
Staff of Gaki no Tsukai are morons?
Yes most of them are morons
Correct Answer
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Oh boy, so this is the first pick, right?
First challenge is the toughest
I didn't know that the opening challenge is that hard
Yes and you can't see how the atmosphere changes
I said bad things about the staff a while ago
the atmosphere got even more awkward...
Yes their attitude is cold
They must be so pissed
They are so mad
They must be thinking that we are disrespecting them
They are such morons that they take us seriously...
You're ruining the atmosphere again!
They are not taking it seriously
Let me try this
"Ion Top Value", I think I haven't tried this yet. This is the first time for me
Now Tasting
Ion Top Value
Barreal Free 3
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Here I go!
This is absolutely not
Its sweetness and bitterness are utterly different from the one I had
I am absolutely sure about it
What I drunk was not "Ion Top Value Barreal 3 Free"!
*He is disposing an empty can
I am not impressed at all
Was it completely different?
That bitterness...Let me try this "Asahi Dry Zero". I think I might have tried this one
Now Tasting
Asahi Dry Zero
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
It doesn't help even if you peek into it
Is it the one? But...
The one I had left a bit stronger bitterness on my tongue...
I better not pick this one!
The one I drunk was not "Dry Zero"!
Oh, give me a break... stop it
It was a long pause
Who the hell is controlling it? He's a real jerk!
This must not be the one...but I dare to try
I'm gonna try.
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free
Black
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
I just wanna keep eliminating. It might have the bitterness
It's exactly the same...
But the one I had remained its bitterness a bit longer
I think this is not the one I had!
The one I drunk was not "Sapporo Premium Alcohol Free Black"!
They always take time...
They are absolutely merciless
I suspect he must be someone who had left this job
And yet he is placed in quite a crucial position now
Even though he resigned
Ok it's gonna be pretty tough
Even Orion Beer has this kind
BINGO!!!
You reacted as if you just noticed the Orion product!
I noticed it! Your face is a bit red!!
Why the hell are you like that?
So what?
So...?
You didn't know that Orion has it. You just realized it now, right?
I got you
You will be punished by Hamada later
No way!
Tanaka must be so nervous now
You must be thinking of what will happen after filming
He's gonna beat me up?
"Hey you screwed up..."
Hamada must be so pissed as Tanaka screwed up
and he will say "Get Tanaka here!"
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents
Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Karinko
**Please support us on Facebook and follow us on Twitter**
Can they win 100 thousand Yen?!
Contributor:
GakiFanSub
James (Team Gaki)
JoJay Gutz
Mike F.
Otviss
Proofreader:
The 35th series  Kiki Non-Alcoholic Beer!!
Translator:
Typesetter:
Xiyu W.
Now Tasting
Nippon
Ryouma 1865
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Correct Answer
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Oh, this also has a different flavor. I think this isn't the one.
Matsumoto successfully cleared 3 beers in a row
Now Tasting
0.00%
for day offs
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Now Tasting
Kirin Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Cleared 6
Out of 12
German beer is suspicious
German beer's ridiculous bitterness
The bitterness that was brought by German beer
We have no idea how it tastes
I'm glad Tanaka is laughing
He's getting relaxed
I'm gonna get it done anyways
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
"Sapporo Premium Alcohol Free"
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free
Oh damn you...
It's not the one, I'm sure
Sorry but I'm gonna get this out
The one I drunk was not "Sapporo Premium Alcohol Free"!
My heart exploded
This is how scary to challenge the first
Stop drinking nothing but protein drinks!!
Wasn't that too long?!
Are you okay?
Too cold! Too cold!
He's like a snowball
The beer for Tanaka is the one and only black beer
Premium Alcohol Free Black
(Sapporo Beer)
*This is produced for people 20 years old and over
For Tanaka
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
It has a mild and smooth taste, with rich malt flavor.
Here I go!
He has emphysema
His nose has always been stuffy
Always?
Always
He doesn't have to sniff then
I can't find any "Tesaguri (groping)"
You mean,"Tegakari (Clue)"?
Clue, right?
Correct Answer
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free Black
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
I'd rather try this "Kirin Free"
I'm gonna try this first and compare how it tastes differently
Now Tasting
Kirin Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Yes, the first one is important
Then I will find the average taste
No, it's not the one
it simply has the different taste
The one I had was not "Kirin Free"!
See?
*He is disposing an empty can
See? Oh yeah, the German one you mentioned
I didn't drink that one after all
Now Tasting
VERITASBRÄU
Pure and Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
No you didn't
It's cold
That's not the point
It's not the one...I can see. It's easy to drinki...
Easy to drinKI?
DrinKI?
It's not the one!
Is he from Tosa (Kouchi pref.) region?
Note: The way Tanaka said sounded like Tosa direct
It has a different taste
Tanaka successfully eliminated the German beer
I clearly distinguished it BY taste with my tongue
You mean you distinguished THE taste with your tongue?
He keeps saying things funnily today
Now Tasting
Orion
Clear Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
He discarded the Orion beer without any troubles
They had different flavors?
Cleared 3
Out of 12
Different flavors
Let's try the Black
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free Black
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free Black
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free Black
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free Black
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free Black
That's the only one black beer
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free Black
No!
That was quick...
This is typical black beer... no, not this one
The one I drunk was not Premium Alcohol Free Black!
It was hard to resist cracking up
What's wrong with you?
It's gonna be long, Tanaka...
You Unfunny Comedian!
He's frozen
I guess she was so pissed with Tanaka
No! This isn't the one
No kidding!
What's the right one then?
What's wrong with you?
Endo is hoping to win after 7 years.
Premium Alcohol Free
(Sapporo Beer)
*This is produced for people 20 years old and over
For Endo
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
The beer for him is Premium Alcohol Free, which is the same one Matsumoto had
Sapporo is proudly producing this beer, which tastes like genuine beer
Kokoriko, Endo...
It is so bubbly...
Have you planned what to say since last night?
No way
So you can be on TV as long as possible?
Correct Answer
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
I'm gonna try this Kirin Free, as I guess it's the least likely choice
Now Tasting
Kirin Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
It's totally different, and sweet...
The one I drunk was not Kirin Free!
Yes!
Were you confident?
Yup
Let's try this. "Full Malt"
It's Belgian beer
Now Tasting
Full Malt
from Belgium
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Oh it tastes good, but still totally different. It tastes really nice though
The one I drunk was not Full Malt!
See? If you see it, it looks as if he's gonna get the right one, doesn't it?
But it's not that easy...
I'm gonna try "Premium Alcohol Free Black"
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free Black
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
It's absolutely different
Kuwata Keisuke (singer) Official Non-alcoholic Drink
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
It's Kuwata Keisuke's official non-alcoholic drink...
This part is not gonna be on TV. Go quick
If you drink it, you may become like Kuwata
What?
You gonna be like Kuwata
He's imposing on you... this part might be on TV
Correct Answer
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
That's the way it works
"It's totally different!" (talking like Kuwata)
Ok it's gonna be deleted
I guessed as much
That was terrible...
No. No. No.
It's heartbreaking
It won't happen
Now Tasting
Non-alcoholic beer
from China
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Endo successfully got right answers twice in a row
Cleared 4
Out of 12
"It's totally different!" (Talking like Kuwata)
Don't keep copying
But it's getting funny
I was kinda surprised at the moment though
If he does that once again, I might be laughing a lot
I'm gonna try this "Kumamoto Free Green Orange"
Now Tasting
Kumamoto
Free Green Orange
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Seriously?
"It's totally different!"
He's pathetic...
Not funny at all...
That was terrible...
That's messed up
What's wrong with him?
Look at Endo's face...
That's really messed up
No, it's not the one
The one I drunk was not Kumamoto Free!
Yes!
He made it
It has a description...Sakamoto Ryouma established Kameyama-syachu in 1865...I don't give a shit
Product Information of "Ryouma 1865"
Sakamoto Ryouma (historical person) established
Kameyama-syachu (political group) in 1865
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
He's gonna be Ryouma this time?
He's such a challenger...
No, that's not gonna happen
He's so fearless...
No I don't think he's gonna do it...
That's a damn introduction...
Let's see this Ryouma 1865
Now Tasting
Nippon
Ryouma 1865
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Hope his attempt goes well...
"It's absolutely not Beer! " (talking like Sakamoto Ryouma)
How should we react?
He touches my heart...
He almost made me cry...
Being unsettled, Endo barely cleared two beers
Now Tasting
Orion
Clear Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Now Tasting
Ion Top Value
Barreal 3 Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
However...
It's not the one?
Uh oh, it's pretty long...
It's gonna be long
It really is gonna be long
Get lost you potbelly!
"Ja neee yoooo...."
I have no idea what she said
The fourth challenger is Housei
(Nippon Beer)
For Housei
Ryouma 1865
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
His beer is Ryouma 1865
Made from 100% malts. Authentic one that makes beer lovers impressed
I've had this before!!
Ok his loud voice didn't seem funny...
Yes yes yes yes!!
If you can, please try Kuwata Keisuke as well
I'm not gonna be caught by the trap...
Correct Answer
Nippon
Ryouma 1865
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
There's one thing I have tried before
The one I've had before is this: Kirin. This is the only one. I have never tried the others
May I try this? It's so quick though
May I try this Belgian one?
How come?
I wanna see how it tastes differently
So you are that confident then
What?
I thought you would pick this one
WHAT THE HELL!?
What the hell...
I messed up. Sorry
What's wrong with you?
I totally messed up
I apologize. Please focus on it
Ok I'm gonna try Orion
Orion?
It has nothing to do with the one he chose at first
That's a sudden change
Oh he really picked it
Now Tasting
Orion
Clear Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
He actually picked it, so he's gonna try it
He must be just making sure
Yeah just checking
The one I drunk was not Orion Clear Free!
*He is disposing an empty can
Thanks
The next one Housei picked was Kirin Free
Now Tasting
Kirin Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Correct Answer
Nippon
Ryouma 1865
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
He somewhat wondered, but...
Please...!
That was close...
That was so close!!
So creepy!
That's scary!
Now Tasting
Sapporo
Premium Alcohol Free
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Housei successfully cleared 4 beers in a row
Now Tasting
Ion Top Value
Barreal Free 3
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Now Tasting
Non-Alcoholic Beer
from China
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Full Malt
from Belgium
Now Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Cleared 6
Out of 12
Gimme a break...
This one or this one...
Now Tasting
Kumamoto
Free Green Orange
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
You should say, Housei
Please declare that you gonna drink it before you do
He pisses me off...
The one I drunk was not Kumamoto Free
Is he sleepy?
He's getting sleepy
He's almost falling asleep
Huh?
Give me a sec...
Now Tasting
Nippon
Ryouma 1865
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Now Tasting
Nippon
Ryouma 1865
Say Something!!
Now Tasting
Nippon
Ryouma 1865
Now Tasting
Nippon
Ryouma 1865
Now Tasting
Nippon
Ryouma 1865
Now Tasting
Nippon
Ryouma 1865
You have to declare!
You should say "I'm gonna drink this"
Yeah don't just pick
The one I drunk was not RYUMA...
Ryouma!
It's messed up!
Hey, don't screw around!
He's screwed up
What's RYUMA?
You were just playing around with Ryouma though
And it was actually Ryouma
You are...
ZERO percent as a human!!
That's no good!!
That was way too long!
Hamada often drinks Non-Alcoholic Beer
His Beer is Asahi Dry Zero, which has similar feelings to the throat and dry taste that Asahi Super Dry has
Asahi Dry Zero
(Asahi Beer)
*This is produced for people 20 years old and over
For Hamada
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
I feel the same as Tanaka. What's the main clue?
I think it's bitterness...
Yes, bitterness
Right
It doesn't have much bitterness though
Asahi Dry Zero
Correct Answer
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Same as Housei, I have tried this and this
I definitely have
But I didn't feel it as the same...
Did you feel it as if you had it for the first time?
Let's try this first
Now Tasting
Asahi Dry Zero
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Now Tasting
Asahi Dry Zero
Let's try this first
Now Tasting
Asahi Dry Zero
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Now Tasting
Asahi Dry Zero
The taste is still on my tongue
It's his first trial
It's very important
Yes it is
He's tasting...
I have no idea
huh?
He's smiling
He's so smiling...
I am so confused more than you think
I didn't sense the bitterness...I just felt its sparkling texture
I don't argue if someone says this is it
I don't argue if someone says it's not the one
He reminds me of Mori Shinichi (singer)
Yeah he reminds me of him
He's trying to antagonize Endo...
But it must be not the one!
The one I drunk was not Asahi Dry Zero!
You picked the right one!
You are amazing!
No kidding!!
Seriously?
You are unbelievable
You don't drink beer
But Mugichai (Barley tea)!
That's long!
Seriously??
You picked the right one first!
It was amazing to see you reaching it
I thought "Oh he got that!"
I thought he's got luck
Absolutely
No way...
It's hard to tell the difference
I don't find any difference as you said