0 0 m -128.375 -28.125 b -132.875 -28.625 -145.375 -28.125 -144.125 -17.625 b -144.75 -11.875 -132.25 -0.5 -129 0 b -123.75 3.25 -121.75 -0.5 -118.5 -1.125 b -114.5 -5 -110.625 -6.25 -106.625 -15.875 b -105.375 -24.75 -113.875 -25.5 -114.5 -26.25 b -119.75 -28.625 -124.375 -28.125 -128.375 -28.125 m -125 -24.75 b -119.125 -26.25 -111.25 -22.375 -112.625 -18.5 b -117.125 -23.5 -121.125 -23.5 -125 -24.75 m -158.5 -81.25 b -155.875 -81.25 -133.625 -76.75 -136.875 -47.375 b -141.5 -28.625 -153.875 -19.75 -157.875 -17.625 b -159.875 -17.125 -170.375 -8.875 -184.75 -22.375 b -188 -28.625 -194.625 -35.875 -190 -51.75 b -188 -58.25 -184.75 -70.5 -173 -77.5 b -169.625 -79.25 -164.375 -82.5 -158.5 -81.25 m -99.5 -82.5 b -98.125 -82.5 -82.375 -87.125 -68.625 -63.25 b -66.625 -57.5 -61.375 -50.375 -64.625 -32.5 b -68.625 -17.625 -75.125 -17.125 -79.125 -15.875 b -82.375 -15.875 -87 -11.875 -102.75 -22.875 b -108 -27.25 -115.875 -30 -119.125 -47.875 b -118.5 -47.875 -126.375 -59.625 -110 -77.5 b -106.625 -80.125 -103.375 -82.5 -99.5 -82.5 m -159.875 -61.375 b -178.25 -58.25 -167.75 -38.25 -159.125 -40.375 b -156.5 -40.375 -150.625 -41.625 -149.375 -50.375 b -151.25 -60.875 -155.25 -60 -159.875 -61.375 m -159.875 -55.625 b -155.875 -57 -153.875 -51.75 -154.625 -50.375 b -154.625 -45.5 -158.5 -45.5 -160.5 -45.5 b -163.125 -46 -164.375 -48.625 -163.75 -51.75 b -163.75 -53.125 -162.5 -55.625 -159.875 -55.625 m -158.5 -53.125 b -160.5 -52.375 -159.875 -50 -158.5 -50 b -157.25 -50 -155.875 -52.375 -158.5 -53.125 m -94.875 -61.375 b -109.25 -58.875 -102.75 -39 -94.875 -40.75 b -92.25 -40.375 -85.625 -41.625 -85.625 -53.125 b -87.625 -60.875 -92.875 -61.375 -94.875 -61.375 m -94.875 -55.625 b -86.375 -55.625 -89 -45.5 -93.5 -45.5 b -94.875 -44.75 -100.125 -46 -98.75 -51.75 b -98.75 -53.125 -98.125 -55.625 -94.875 -55.625 m -93.5 -53.125 b -95.5 -51.75 -94.25 -49.25 -92.875 -50 b -90.875 -50.375 -92.25 -53.125 -93.5 -53.125 m -161.125 -50 b -162.5 -50 -161.75 -47.875 -161.125 -47.875 b -160.5 -47.875 -159.875 -50 -161.125 -50 m -95.5 -49.25 b -96.875 -49.25 -96.125 -47.375 -95.5 -47.375 b -94.875 -47.375 -94.25 -49.25 -95.5 -49.25 m -194.625 -92.875 l -60.75 -92.875 l -60.75 37.25 l -194.625 37.25 m -62 -91.625 l -193.25 -91.625 l -193.25 36 l -62 36
TPF
Memory Ryokan 2!!
Shocking Confessions!
Alright
Okay.
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Okay
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Yamasaki Housei
This looks good
Yup
Yea
I didn't wanna do this again.
This episode
Last time you had to do it 3 times
3 times, yea.
Tofu Panda Fansubs Presents:
That's right.
Down Town's Gaki no tsukai ya arahende!!
At first, you know...
Exactly
Fran
Otviss
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
**We also have facebook and twitter.**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
If you see this video uploaded somewhere but not by us. Have in mind that individuals might make money off of it. GO BACK and support the original creators. Thanks for watching!
Kenny
Akane
Translators:
Typesetters:
______________________________________________________
If you think "this is the card" then it won't be.
It won't be, right
Exactly
I wonder why
That's right
There's times where you don't want a card
but you have to take it
'past' based on the given topic.
The person who pulls the "Storyteller"
a
card will have to tell a story from their
That does happen
But there's nothing you can do.
That's true
Like 'ahhh'
Michael J. Fox
"Back to the Future"
A highschooler, Marty, goes back
in time 30 years with scientist Doc's time machine.
Back to the Future
Marty
(Michael J. Fox)
r
Ready, flip
Tanaka
It's getting warm out, huh
It is getting warm
Very warm
Well,
I think you all,
probably don't know me very well...
What do you mean?
Well,
there's something I wanted to tell you guys about...
Seriously?
Yes
Have you ever ridden in a time machine?
There's no way we could've
That's impossible
No, right?
Of course not
Well I have.
Again with this...
I rode in a time machine,
and went back and forth
between the past and the future.
Recently?
I stopped doing it.
When, then?
When was this?
I actually, uh
used to go to an
American high school
Wait, you went to Teshima Elementary School.
But I went to an American high school.
Oh, just for high school
Just high school.
I never knew where you went
I used to
ride a skateboard to school
Just kinda
I can't even imagine that
I really did.
And in my neighborhood,
uhhh,
There was like
this idiot scientist
"idiot scientist"
There was a scientist,
He was pretty old.
Oh, an old guy.
Yes.
And he
"finally did it"
He "finally made a time machine"
Yea, some old guys say that kind of stuff
A lot of them do
You shouldn't talk to those guys
"It must be something else!"
They just want some money
Is that what they want?
But no.
I thought he meant something else,
but when I checked it out
There was a car
That was the time machine.
Well you hear that story a lot,
about those guys
Right??
Cars are quite ordinary aren't they?
Right?
But when I got in,
before I knew it
I was in the past.
What time period did you go back to?
50's (1950's)
The 50's?!
I went back to the 50's!
50's...
I was like "is this real?"
And then,
Someone...
Someone fell in love
...who?
Be a little more specific!
Who fell in love?
My mom
Your mom?
My mom.
Your mother?
My mother,
She...
It was the past, so she was really young
Oh,
Since it's the 50's
Right right right
My own mother,
fell in love
with me.
Do you understand what that means?
If I messed
something up
I wouldn't ever be born.
That's right.
And then,
I was like "this is bad"
then,
I played some guitar...
Right, right...
This makes no sense.
Then,
My father,
My really young father was there
so I had to do something about it,
And at a party,
I hooked them up
"hooked them up?"
Yea.
Your mom and dad?
My parents
Your young parents
It sounds weird when you say you 'hooked them up'
That just sounds wrong
I hooked them up, and then
some lightning struck
and I was home
Yea
I don't understand
I don't get it
You're mixing up reality and...
He drank too much.
You were just drunk.
Were you drunk?
No no no
I hoped you would believe me
No...
It's true!
I mean...
No way that happened.
That's quite the story
Unbelievable...
Seriously
He's really gotta cut it out
Tensai
Bakabon
A Dad Ingenuously Does Stupid Things
With His Son, Bakabon, and Creates Chaos Around Town
Bakabon
Tensai Bakabon
r
I don't want this one
I don't know this one...
Please not me
Ready, flip.
Yamasaki
What's wrong?
Wanna head to the outside hot spring?
What time does it close?
9:30
Let's go.
Wait a second!
What?
Can I tell you a story about my family?
Why now?
Why so suddenly?
Well...
My family,
We're a family of 4,
and my dad is
well, an idiot...
You shouldn't say that about him
That's right.
Now,
when he sees this on TV,
he's gonna be real sad.
I mean...
"My dad is an idiot"?!
It's not something you say...
I know that, but
And we don't know what to say either
Right?
I'm really sorry, but
How far in school did he get?
He graduated from a college.
What, then he's not an idiot at all!
Maybe you've heard of the school,
It's uh,
Idiot University
What is that?
The hell is that
"Idiot University"?
A few times his friend came over,
Oh, I've heard this
Like he lost something right next to himself
Exactly
Really?
Yea yea yea yea
Oh, that guy went to Idiot University?
He went to visit you guys?
That guy's arms,
they were really long
His arms were long?
I don't get it
No, his arms were normal, but
his sleeves?
his sleeves
His shirt sleeves?
they're unusually long.
And there was a guy
who wore a Tokyo University hat,
and pretty much everyone's noses...
were runny
Your father's friends?
Your friends?
Right.
My neighbor,
He was pretty weird too
In what way?
Like, he was always cleaning...
Some people are just like that
That's not that weird
That's pretty normal
No but,
with this giant bamboo broom,
he was constantly cleaning around his front door
What's wrong with that?
It helps make the neighborhood look nicer
He helped a lot
by doing that
Making it clean
What did the guy used to say?
He would say
like,
Re re re no re~
or something like that
All he could say was 're'
"Re re re re"?
Re re re re
He was probably just messin' around with the kids
Well we never really got involved...
We were scared of him, so
So, you avoided him?
Then you should've talked to the police
Right, the police.
The policeman, he...
Over and over,
He would run towards us
just unloading.
Unloading what?
His gun.
What?!
There's no way!
Like 'bang bang bang bang bang!'
There's no way.
He can't do that
I know it's reckless but he was THE officer for that area
That's a problem
But that's how it was
What was his face like?
You know,
At first, I was scared so I couldn't see it.
But I took a good look after,
and his eyes were connected
There's no way that's true
That's just idiotic.
Some people have connected eyebrows,
but this guy was his actual eyes
That's scary!
Seriously?
Oh yea?
You lived in a crazy place
That's amazing
After moving, my life's completely different though
You guys have a lot of interesting stories, huh.
That surprised me
That's just, ya know...
The Godfather
Michael Corleone
(Al Pacino)
The Godfather
The Mafia's Boss's Son Michael
Get's Caught in Some Family Trouble
r
Ready, flip.
Endo
But seriously, let's head to the hot spring
Alright, let's go
Yea
It's open 'til 9:30
Let's go
If we only get in by 9
we'll have to get right out
It's not enough time
It's too short
We'll have to get out quick
Should we bring some food?
Uhm, I'm really sorry, but
Sorry, I'll make this quick
Really? Are you serious?
What's wrong?
Just tell us in the...
It's not something I should
talk about in the hot spring.
What is it?
Well...
I'm sorry,
It's just there's a problem with my father...
Your dad too?
Yes.
He's, uhh
Well he's the Don
'the Don'?
of well,
a scary organization.
'the Don'?
He's the Don
And well,
He's in a dispute with
another scary organization
What's a 'scary organization'?
'scary organization'?
What kind of...
Put simply,
like the Mafia...
kind of.
And I don't think you'll believe me, but
Stuff like cutting off horse's heads,
and exchanging them.
"Exchanging"
Exchanging...
Horse heads?
What does that mean?
Just harassing each other.
Since they're quarreling.
Oh, with the other scary organization?
But I said I didn't wanna join the family business.
Well of course, it's scary
I was done with it.
Actually, this is
a really long story...
You said you'd make it quick
Well, there's a lot of different parts to it.
But in the End
I Followed in His Footsteps
Wait, you followed in his footsteps??
You're in the Mafia?!
Unfortunately,
I'm kinda the
Don now
What the hell?
I mean,
it's complicated, you know
That's scary
The End?
But anyway,
that's it.
After hearing that,
What's wrong with you!
we can't just go to the hot spring!
Seriously, though
But It's not like that anymore, so
You ruined the fun!
I'm really sorry.
Space Battleship Yamato
Kodai Susumu
To Save the Earth From Crisis, Kodai Susumu
and His Girlfriend Mori Yuki Embark on a Space Battleship...
r
Ready, flip
Matsumoto
I'm really lucky today
Very lucky.
Amazing
Right?
Incredible
Truly.
Ready to go?
Let's go!
Let's go already.
Alright
Really, though
Hey hey hey hey hey
Now now now, now now now
What?
We're gonna go, but
just sit down for a second
What is it?
We don't have much time, so
I have something I gotta talk about
uhhh,
Destruction...
Let's go, guys
Wait wait wait wait
Let's go already
There was a time
when I prevented some destruction...
Destruction of what?
The earth...
"The earth"?!
You know,
I don't think you guys will believe me, but
I kinda protected the earth once.
Seriously?
For real?
Yea.
There's no way you'll believe me, but
There was a really bad...
well it wasn't
a foreigner, but
Not a foreigner, but
like a foreigner to earth
Right
This story sounds important
Yea
This foreigner was
always drinking something
and he,
he would always come up
on this giant jumbo tron thing
What does he say when he comes on?
Like "Ladies and Gentlemen!"
Where are you guys
during this?
But you won't believe me, will you?
We don't know until you...
Just tell us
Well, it was a boat
called the Yamato.
Oh, I know about that
It's a pretty old one
It's famous
Right right right
We rode on the Battleship Yamato
You rode on it?
Well, yea, in space...
Huh?
Who else was with you?
Tare was also there*
*Translators note: Couldn't hear the name (Tare)
This girl,
She uh,
I don't really know why, but anyway
the boat had a special function,
where it could warp.
It disappears and reappears ahead.
And whenever we would warp...
and she was a beautiful girl,
but
She would become
completely naked
Only that one girl?
I wonder why
I remember it in my fantasies
I don't really get it...
But who cares about that.
But you know,
I mean...
The parts I never saw...
Honestly, I don't know
anything about this either
Yea...
Not a thing.
I really wanna hear
a story from Hamada-san
Me too
It can't end until he tells one
Maybe he doesn't want to?
I don't have any stories!
We don't need excuses, flip the paper
Alright
So it doesn't matter if I'm lucky?
101st Marriage Proposal
A Boring Man Dates 99 Women
and Fails, but Falls in Love on the 100th try
Hoshino Tatsurou
Takeda Tetsuya
r
Ok, let's leave
Wait, do I have to tell this story?
Well, everyone else already went
It would be our second time.
What should we do
Something happened though, right?
What happened?
Just briefly...
Well...
I'm married, right
Right.
The truth is...
What
Up until I got married,
I kind of wanna hear this now
I used a matchmaking service
Really?
A matchmaking service?
I've never heard this
I mean like,
100 times
Wait wait wait
That many times?
That's crazy
Were you always that unpopular?
Did you wanna get married that badly?
Even though it's not me, I feel...
It's kinda weird
Did you always break up with them?
No, they all broke up with me.
Every single time?
This is depressing
Really.
No matter what I said to them...
It never worked, huh
Like, I'll protect you...
"I'll protect you for 50 years"
Ah, that's too heavy
It's too much
Too much.
That's offputting.
I see
I was always thinking
about what I should say
you know
And what I thought of
for the 101st girl
was eventually,
to jump in front of a truck.
No no no
Why?
You can't
That's dangerous
You'd get hurt
You'd die
But I said
"I ain't
'gon die!"
to her.
That's so weird
There's no way that worked on her.
Absolutely no way.
Why did you
propose with "I ain't 'gon die"?
What the hell is
'ain't 'gon die'?
Like, even if I get hit
I'll protect you,
or something like that.
But that wouldn't work
That's too much
The 101st time was also unsuccessful
No, but the truth is...
The truth is she's...
my current wife
So weird!
It's been a while
It has...
These are the people
who we sent home when they wouldn't cheer last week
Oh, this crowd?
Well, not everyone, but
Oh, but generally
I see
I really uh,
went too far, so I got on
the ground to apologize
I wasn't strong enough,
so I had to send you home."
And I asked them to at least
give them some Anko Buns
Anko buns?
At least some Anko buns
But since I was weak,
they gave them meat buns.
Isn't that better though
Oh really?
Meat buns are better than anko buns?
Between those two, yea
Is that so
That's true, anko buns really...
piss me off.
Really?
Like "what's up with that anko bun"
Well some people like them
Seriously?
Probably.
Are you serious?
People like sweet food...
It's sweet, but
there's no point in heating it up
Recently, have you...
said "Huhhh!?" at all?
Like, to a person?
Yea, to a person.
You mean have I snapped?
Yea like, flipped out
I haven't
"Huh?", right?
Like "Huhhh!?"
Not recently
I've been alive for,
40 years, right?
And I've said "Huhhh!?" plenty of times,
Yea, yea
but recently I said the biggest one of all.
What was the situation?
I just couldn't hold it in.
I never thought I'd let out one like that.
There'll probably never be a "Huhhh!?"
bigger than this one in my life.
Really?
Yes.
Tell me, what happened.
Well,
I was drinking at like a bar
Right right right
Right?
Right.
A place with just a counter.
yea yea yea
Two old ladies come in,
right?
And they were really drunk.
I guess they were regulars there.
I see
So they were really drunk and happy
Then one of them,
she said "my bra feels weird."
I was like "what is she saying?"
"My bra feels weird"
This old lady was saying.
Even then, I was like "Huhh!?"
No one wants to hear
that in such a loud voice
Oh, in the bar
It has nothing to do with me
Right, right.
Absolutely nothing to do with me.
Exactly.
"What is she saying?"
That's reverse sexual harassment!
But I just ignored them and didn't look.
It felt weird I guess, so
one put her
hand under the other's sweater
trying to unhook the bra.
Okay.
Like "more to the
front, no towards the back."
"Woohoo, woohoo!"
I just thought
"I'm definitely not gonna look"
I kept ignoring it, but I could tell what was happening by the conversation, right?
I get it.
I know what they're doing, but I just thought "hurry up and finish it already."
And at this point,
no one ever thought,
a "Huhhh!?" that big
Not at this point.
would ever come out.
Then they were probably
trying to take off the bra to fix it.
I wasn't watching, but.
Then they said,
"oh, you try to get it off" or something.
I wasn't looking but that's
probably what they were doing.
At one point they got really excited,
Like "WOO!"
Then, just to kinda say
'alright, that's enough',
I quickly looked for like a second.
Then one of the old ladies said
"Stop staring, stop staring, you creep!"
"HUHHH!?"
Pen name 'Kugetto-san"
What kind of pen name is that?
"I hav..."
"I have a question for the famous leader of the Church of Thieves."
"What is the most awkward thing for a thief to steal?"
Oh, that?
There sure are some.
You know them, right?
Of course I know them.
Like, 'of course this won't get stolen'?
Things any humane robber wouldn't take,
of course there's some things.
Oh, really.
Thieves are people too, after all.
That's right
There's some things.
Then what are they?
Don't think you can get the answer
so easily.
Don't think I'll answer
just anything right away.
I'm not a drum that will give you a sound right away
I don't know about that, but just tell us.
What do you mean?
I mean,
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
What do
you think it is?
What's the most awkward thing for a thief to steal?
What do you think?
Are you coming up with it right now?
Should I skip it?
'Am I coming up with it'?
It's not something you come up with.
Then please tell us.
Tell you what
Tell us what's the most
awkward thing to steal for a thief.
Awkward thing?
Yea.
No idea. Shoes, maybe?