Seen last week,
A series of shocking truths unveiled
Yamasaki Hosei Sneaky Thief Trial!
The first one...
Even though he lost the quiz,
Yamasaki ignored the rules and asked Umezu for an autograph!
Excuse me, your autograph?
A rule violating sneaky thief!
Like an autograph,
It's fine isn't it, to get one?
No it isn't!
- That's what we're telling you!
When Tanaka did that thing with Ikko, you didn't even approach her!
Well I couljn't joo anything then-
"Couljn't joo" he says
And the second one ...
When Yamasaki tried an image change, he stole the entire outfit!
Oh this is kinda scary
No way...
This is straight up theft!
You can't do this!
There's a limit to how much you can steal!
This is horrible
What did I do wrong here?
And the third one...
An incident where Yamasaki stole gags from two young comedians!
"Cause it doesn't matter, cause it doesn't matter!"
"That don't matter, oh that don't matter!"
"Cause that's no problem, cause that's no problem!"
A shameless gag theft!
But just let me say this,
I used that gag I remembered, the "doesn't matter" gag
And I remembered his rhythym, and all I did was combine them!
That's what we're saying is wrong!
We're telling you that's bad
Why are you calling this theft, you're making me look bad!
You can't copy and combine them!
And tonight, another victim makes an appearance
A shocking revelation awaits
What will Yamasaki's fate be?
subbed by senor_wristband
If you'd like to support my subs, I've set up these accounts :)
patreon.com/senor_wristband
ko-fi.com/buresurettosan
By the way,
All the gags Yamasaki has done, his material ... It looks like this
It's not really that special
In November 1992, he came up with this
This, "Yey yey yey"
This is the one I most...
I wish I could remember them
There's also "Yosha-Ko", "MA" ... "Chopsticks"?
"Face Paku Paku", "Doi Takako", and "Chucky"
What was this "Face Paku Paku" one?
So it's like this
Paku Paku, Face Paku Paku
What's with the hands...
When do you use this...
When do you pull that out?
When do you use that?
If someone doesn't tell you-
It's for times like this
Meaning?
If someone says "Do that one"
If they tell you to do it?
TN: Doi Takako was a prominent Japanese politician
And this "Doi Takako"?
"Murayama Tomiichi has been appointed as Prime Minister"
It was that age
Well that's how it is
So Yamasaki-san, would you say these are you original creations?
Indeed
You thought up all of these?
Yes
I see. Your Honour,
We have another victim in regards to his gags
Can we call in this victim?
Understood
Witness, enter
Haranishi
You all know him already, this is Haranishi from FUJIWARA
Yes, that's right
Now, Yamasaki invented everything on this board,
According to him
As he says
You know, honestly, up until now he's been changing things other people did,
He straight up stole from me though
He blatantly stole from me, he didn't change anything
Really? Exactly the same?
Exactly the same
This is shocking news isn't it?
Do you have any proof?
Yes, let's watch the VTR
How he stole "Doi Takako"
September 1999 - 9 years ago
This was material he came up with for Matsumoto's 36th birthday
So, Yamasaki-san?
Using an impression of Doi Takako, I will wi-wish you Happy Birthday
"Matsumoto-san"
"Murayama Tomiichi has been appointed as Prime Min-"
What does that have to do with him?
You didn't say "Happy Birthday" at all!
Yamasaki finally came up with a great new gag at this occasion,
This became one of his signature acts, and there are many scenes of him doing it
However, there is one thing that sticks out about this gag...
This happened 1 year before that performance...
This was an Osaka TV show that FUJIWARA were regulars on
This is the scene that sticks out;
An imitation that a comedian shouldn't do
An impression a comedian shouldn't do? Alright then, do it
Former speaker of the house, Doi Takako
Please begin
"Murayama Tomiichi has been appointed as Prime Minister"
You straight up copied him!
"Murayama Tomiichi"
"has been appointed as Prime Minister"
The exact same performance,
Is Yamasaki a serial gag thief?
You ... you went this far?
It's just one after another!
I guess coincidences do happen
What'd you say?
Is he laughing?
So you didn't know Haranishi did that a month ago?
Well I've never watched that show before
I don't mean the show,
In private,
I did it in front of other comedians,
and Yamasaki was there too, no doubt
He said you were there
First off, the choice of Murayama Tomiichi is outdated
It was something happened a long time ago
It doesn't match his generation
That phrase is from Haranishi's generation
You know, I....
I feel really sick all of a sudden
That's unacceptable
No way, we're only just starting
Can I be excused?
No no no
No way
Incidentally Haranishi-kun, do you have more to add? Other than that one
Nothing else?
Actually, can I say it?
There's more?
Can I see that board from before?
Those are supposed to be Yamasaki-san's original creations
This, "Face Paku Paku"
He got some laughs with that before
The discussion before of "when do you use that?"
"what's the setup?"
It does have a setup, because it's my gag!
It's unfortunate
Really?
What kind of face is that?
Stop your cheap acting!
The origin of how he knows this,
On that TV show, there was a weekly skit corner
I see
Miyagawa Daisuke and I were supposed to have a conversation,
I thought it would be boring if I did it normally, so I thought up a character,
And it was this, exactly this
I thought talking like this would be funny
"Hey dad, dad listen"
So I was gonna talk with that face, I thought that up
So I showed that to Yamasaki in the train, since I was scared
I thought it might not work
You tried it out on Yamasaki
And he found it really hilarious
I thought it would work then
But I never got to do that skit,
I see
So I never showed that gag to anybody,
But after a while, that person...
He was getting big laughs using that "Face Paku Paku"
What is the meaning of this?
There's no footage bu-
Don't just listen to him
Look carefully, they're totally different!
Then Yamasaki-san, how did you come up with that?
Yes, why that gag?
Well, certainly, in Osaka we worked on the same TV show
I might've seen a little bit
So that was just seared into my memories,
So in regards to him,
Um, can you stop that? Looking at me with those dirty eyes
You guys are all so dirty
You should apologise-
Apologise! Why do I need to apologise?
Can I say something?
Back when we worked together in Osaka on a TV show, there were many times when I went to him for advice
Oh really?
It was along the lines of
"We wanna leave for Tokyo soon,"
I see
So I asked him, and he said "It's the time for you yet"
"I know best about these things. Don't leave yet.
"I'll tell you when you should come to Tokyo"
So he said he'll have your back?
But that's messed up isn't it?
It is
The only reason he said that,
If I use that gag he wants to steal before him, everyone will know he stole it
Exactly
So because of that, he told me to stay
That's awful!
For that reason
And in the end, he never told me to come to Tokyo!
"I know best about these things"?
You're the one who knows the least!
This one is terrible
It's not terrible
I need some advice,
Advice?
What do you mean?
For example, if a criminal admits his crime, the punishment is lessened right?
Slightly right? It's only slightly.
How much will it be lessened?
I'm not really sure about that
Will we still be able to smile together and be friends after this?
If you're found guilty, you'll be banned from using the stuff you stole
This is a trial after all. You can't use them anymore.
But that "Doesn't Matter" one,
They were chanting it in the bar
That made you really happy didn't it
You keep bringing it up
And that's never happened to me, in my 20+ years of comedy,
So that made me really happy
So then shouldn't you make one up yourself?
Yeah, make your own original gag
It's not my fault I can't think of anything
You might come up with something right now
Right now? Maybe, that could happen
Naits
I can't think of a thing
What was that "Naits"?
I heard that "Naits" somewhere
It's a bad habit of mine
Finally, it's time for Yamasaki to be sentenced.
Alright, please announce his sentence
There is no end to the defendant Yamasaki's sneaky thievery,
Since he has caused trouble so many people, we had to take that into account,
His sentence is ... to be slapped by Chono!
WHAT?! HOLD ON!
You're kidding!
You have to be slapped by him, there's no escaping it
Now come here
What do you mean "Mouuuu"
I don't like Chono-san
I seriously don't wanna!
What the hell?
Also, after this, you can't do those gags anymore
You're banned from those gags
Hold on...
C'mon, you gotta get past this
I did didn't I? I said sorry at the end.
No you didn't say that
You didn't say that!
I did say that! I said it at the end didn't I?
You didn't
I said "I have a bad habit. Everyone please help me fix it"!
However, the strength of the slap,
If you really ask Chono-san to make it weaker, he just might do it
Do I absolutley need to take this?
If I have to- Alright then,
I'll take it. I will take the slap, but,
Chono-san, I am genuinely...
A nice guy
I'm really a nice guy! So, just,
Chono-san, which is your dominant hand?
Just tell me that
I'm really sorry!
Check this out!
I'm really sorry! But, this hand, could he use this hand?
I'm not sure about that
This is supposed to be your sentence after all
In fact, because it's this hand,
But in the past,
I got slapped on New Years right? Because of that, 3 months later ...
What happened 3 months later?
I was hospitalised
You weren't!
Why?
But I seriously can't do that. For real, and this is true,
The doctor looked at me
and got on the phone immediately
"WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?!" he said
Enough of that lie now
No really!
It's true!
Idiot!
Let's move on
Wait wait wait wait!
What the hell is it man?
Please, just wait
No really, the doctor really did get mad
Why'd he get angry
He told me to say "Stop messing around!"
To who?
Chono-san
Chono-san?
Yes, exactly
Why do you have to tell him?
Well he didn't know Chono-san's phone number!
No seriously, because what if,
The hospital might shut down!
The hospital will shut down?
That doctor might get fired! Who will treat me next time?
What kind of worry is that?
Let's move on!
Then you get slapped first please!
You get slapped first!
If Hamada-san takes it I'll do it!
Just let Hamada-san do it!
I'll do it if he does!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
ENDO!
I'M GONNA GET MAD FOR REAL!
Zaki-san, Zaki-san please!
I'M GONNA SNAP FOR REAL!
What happened?
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU! YOU STOLE FROM ME!
Enough idiot!
Enough already!
Wait wait wait wait! Hold on, wait!
What happened
You've become a frantic miserable man
That's true
Put your mic on
I went a bit frantic there...
You just stole that line from Ryu-chan!
Wow, just now!
He just stole that from Ryu-chan didn't he?
That is his phrase
And he copied the whole thing!
I'll take it
I, too,
Am a man after all
Of course
So I will take this slap,
But with your left hand please
No, you can't do that
That's not allowed, otherwi-
Then, then!
Then I won't do it!
What the hell!
Where should he stand?
He's so uncool
Are you gonna do this bit again?!
He's doing this shit again!
Enough already!
I got it
Come stand here already!
I got it! I got it
Do it when I say please
When I want to
I'm sorry
You're making the guy who has to slap you wait
Yeah if you keep wasting time...
Yes, exactly
I'm sorry everyone, really, but,
I'm scared
Well that makes sense
Even after all I've been through in life,
I'm scared
That was funny just now!
Very funny!
It doesn't matter that I'm a fully grown man,
I'm scared
Hurry up!
I said I got it!
Did I really do something that bad?
You did!
It's because you did!
I have to get smacked by a Pro-Wrestler?
Did I do something that bad?
Yes, you did
Sorry, it's just,
Can you not spread your stance like that?
How else would you stand?
Sorry, it's just
Have you seen a wrestler slap like this before?
HEY ENDO!
I'M GONNA HOLD A GRUDGE AGAINST YOU
Why? Why me?
I'll never forgive you!
What do you even mean?
You know, it's more dangerous if you try to dodge it
So let's do this
Wait!
The punishment slap!
That's dangerous!
Put your hands down, your hands
The punishment please!
Dirty! So dirty!
His shoe!
How did it come off
That was amazing as expected
That went like "BACHIKYON!"
So the trial has been decided. Yamsaki-san, never again can you use those gags.
You must promise that,
Do you understand, Yamasaki-san?
yes
Hello!
Quiet down!
Shut up!
Go ahead
How does it feel to see a star in the flesh?
You've been saying that a lot recently!
Recently? I don't know about that, I've always been a star
You weren't famous
Some of the guests here might have come here again, after last week
Oh poor things
Last week we were supposed to have this talk segment right?
But then they told you to come again today
Do you know the reason why?
For real, last week Hamada said "Let's not do the talk man"
Because of that, we didn't do it
It was you
Hold on, my memories of being hit,
I've been hit 2 times
I've been hit twice, OK now three times
And alright alright, FOUR times
You wanted to skip too didn't you?
What do you mean?
You were feeling sick and said you couldn't do it
Ah yes, I was feeling a bit sick in the opening
So we had to stop cause of that, and you had to come again, and we have this bad weather again
Well, that's-
So I was standing outside with an umbrella, I even wanted to give out starbucks
TN: I'm not sure Matsumoto said Starbucks here
Did you really?
I did want to
Well sometimes there's trouble on set when people come to watch,
But you know it was cold,
I thought about handing out 2 Starbucks per person
Well, I'm sorry, really
I really did think that,
Things like that happen sometime,
Excuse me sorry, I've been feeling ill lately
Well yes, last time you were
I noticed something after getting sick,
I think, if you timed me,
You'll find I'm really fast at inserting suppositories
I won't lose to anyone,
Inserting suppositories?
You know, in Japan, uhhhhhh
I'm the 80th-
Spit it out already!
That pause is unneccessary
You can stick them right in?
I'm probably the 80th fastest
For example, have you ever used suppositories?
I have
Oh really?
They're like these,
these white things
So if you put a bunch of unwa-unwrapped ones on a table, a table like this,
And I have my hands to the side,
Start the stopwatch and ...
That's...
And my fingers will be completley clean
Just smooth
Are you inserting all the way?
All the way, it's amazing
If you hold them for too long they dissolve
Yeah exactly, so I'll just be like this. "Ready, start" ...
Slides right in,
My fingers won't be sticky at all,
They'll be strai-
Enough already
I can do it with anything
Why are you eating Sushi?
You know, it's not that impressive to be quick at that...
I do want to do that for an episode
It's amazing you get it in right away, usually you need to look for it a bit,
"Here? Oh here!"
That is just plainly stupid
It's impossible to be good at it!
You're dumb, you're dumb
You have a messed up asshole!
Your asshole is all loose is why!
Are you saying you don't know where the anus is?
It's cause your asshole is always wide open!
Are you saying I need to put a cork in it?