[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai, Thanks For Watching!]
Before the recording of "Gaki No Tsukai"...
As usual, the members are having a nice chat in the waiting room.
However, Matsumoto is nowhere to be seen.
-I mean, he's married and all...
-Right, right.
Excuse me.
Good morning.
-Good morning.
Ehm... Matsumoto-san has asked me to deliver this.
Please take a look at it.
Again with this?
Today's card is pretty big.
Letter of challenge.
"You lot are a bunch of uncultured fools that don't understand sexuality."
"It pains me to hear how you fools philosophize about the meaning of sexuality with your wives."
Here he goes again.
"So let's see who's the real sex technician, the real leading man."
"Let us see who truly is the uncontested key master of this craft."
"We will find out today."
"Hitoshi Matsumoto."
He's drawn a map again.
What in the world is this?
It's like one of those ancient maps.
What does "Old CX" mean?
That's true, it says "Old CX".
It's pretty far away.
"Old Edo Castle"? What's this?
What does that mean?
I know where the old Akasaka Prince Hotel is...
I mean, it's in the neighborhood.
It's here, just downstairs.
Isn't it here?
-Right, it's just the second floor.
-He must be down there.
He should have just told us it was downstairs.
Is he waiting for us?
-Yes, he is waiting.
-What's with him?
I mean, he can do this because he's not losing every round.
For now...
Let's go.
Let's just go and get it over with.
In the past, the members have put their male pride on the line and fought each other.
Matsumoto came ahead in the first round, "Bra Unhooking Contest".
And Endo won last time's "Nipple Caressing Match".
On the other hand, Tanaka came last both times and got punished accordingly.
Now, who will be the one to take the punishment?!
Over here.
Whoa, that scared me.
So scary.
-He looks so scary.
-He seems super pissed.
-But why? I don't get why he would get mad...
-Right?
W-What's up?
Who was it?
Who said, "Let's get it over with"?!
I was listening to you!!
-That was me... Sorry...
-It was Endo.
-Endo.
-It was me... Endo...
-So he was listening...
I'll replace you with "Hello Keisuke"!
What'd you say?
I still don't know how "Hello Keisuke" is...
-He's "Hello Keisuke"!
-He's the same age as me.
Do you guys know what we're doing today?!
You fools!
I mean, you always say the same thing...
But you never have anything prepared...
You're always winning by pure chance.
You're right...
This project is pretty half assed.
Right?
That's true.
Only the location of the first one was different.
Right.
I mean that's true.
However!
Today's project is one I have been really wanting to do.
I wanted to strip off some underwear.
It's the first time we've heard anything about "underwear".
You did say "underwear" right?
I did.
So are we stripping off some underwear today?
Is this the first time I said it?
-Yes.
You didn't write anything on that challenge letter.
Oh so it must have been a careless mistake on my part.
How can you mess that up?!~
You could have noticed what we were doing if you were paying attention!!
I see...
Anyways!!
We're all ready to do.
Let's do it.
Alright.
Didn't you guys see it?
Come on!
You fools!
Whoa, this is pretty great.
It's a pretty amazing set.
That's amazing.
Listen!
10 women will drop down!
The rules are simple.
You can only use your feet to remove the underwear of the 10 mannequins that drop out of the machine.
The fastest contestant wins.
And the slowest contestant will have to suffer a humiliating punishment.
So for example...
Endo! How do you take off your partner's underwear?
-Can I be real with you?
-Of course.
My partner takes off her clothes first and I actually like my clothes taken off me.
I don't wanna listen to such graphic talk.
How about you?
I haven't removed panties with my legs either...
I just tell them, "Undress".
That's the worst!
Really?
What about you, Hamada?
I haven't done it either...
You guys haven't lived.
That's the funniest part!
I mean, do you go like this with your leg?
Basically, yes.
Whaaat?
-I've never done that!
-Me neither.
Like a cicada hanging from a tree.
That's really weird, isn't it?
-And then they suck on the resin.
-Resin?
That's so nasty!
The girls suck on the resin.
Alright, Endo!!
Huh?
Let's go!
Endo again?
I always go first!
I don't want to.
Let's go with someone else.
-I can go first.
-You're right Tanaka.
-Really?
-Huh? What?
-It would be great if Hamada went first.
-Please do.
Alright, then.
I'll go first.
-Alright!~
-Let's go!
What a man!
Okay then, it's decided.
Let's go with Hamada first!!
Isn't this impossible?
Do you think so?
I mean...
Look, look at it from over here.
Those are some crazy moves!
I've never done this before!
Will our Top Batter, Hamada, have the confidence?
How will he fare?
-Here we go.
-Let's go.
Here we go.
Start.
Here it comes.
Whoa, here we go.
Isn't he too fast?
You have to take off everything.
And you can't use your hands.
-Amazing!
This is a bit...
Second one.
Isn't he too fast?
He's super fast.
Whoa! Amazing!
It fell off in one swoop!
-So fast!
-It fell off immediately!
You're kidding me!
-The shape of the underwear is also important.
Yes, they are all different.
-Amazing!
-The shape of each one is different.
Amazing.
This is pretty tiring.
-Whoa, awesome!
-That was so fast!
You just tore it apart!
-He's pretty rough.
-Awesome!
-That's rough!
-Yeah!
What was that?
That was pretty fast.
You did that on purpose!
That was on purpose!
This is looking more like a wrestling match!
-Just 3 left...
-Just 2 left!
Amazing!
He's so fast!
-He really is.
He's got great timing.
He's just breezin along.
Last one! Last one! Last one!
This one's got a big belly.
-Its belly is sticking out.
-Oh, you're right.
-The end!!
-Amazing!
That was super fast.
-Hamada, you were so fast.
-For real?
Amazing.
This is super tiring.
-Alright, let's take a look at his time.
-Okay.
Go ahead!
-That's so fast.
-Whoa!
-This must be super fast.
-1:30 is pretty fast.
I guess anything below 2:00 is pretty fast.
He was below 1:30.
-Okay then, who's next.
-Who's next?
-Whoa, Hamada... That was too fast!
-You should have gone first then!
Look at him.
He's already out.
Hamada, how did you do that?
Were you hugging it like this?
What do you mean?
It looks like Yamasaki has no confidence...
How will he fare?
Alright, here we go.
I'll do my best!
Start!
Look, look, he's struggling already.
It's getting stuck there.
-Did he get stuck in his feet?
-The button!
Oh, he just lost some time.
He just lost a lot of time.
Watch out for his hands!
Push it!
This is bad!
Don't you have any self-awareness?
That was good.
He's so red!
How is he doing?
I guess it's easier from the back.
-It's harder from the front.
-He's so inefficient.
Hold on...
Look at his face.
He's so desperate.
He's desperate to avoid the punishment.
Oh no! It's stuck!
Come on.
-You don't have to kick it!
-Only 3 left.
Almost there.
You really need some stamina for this.
This one is pretty stuck.
She doesn't want them off.
It's off, it's off.
He's very rough.
-Last one! Last one!
-At then end you have to ******.
-It's off, it's off, it's off, it's off, it's off!
-Don't kick them in the head.
If he didn't press it this time...
-Right...
-It made a sound for a while.
Saki!!
-Saki!!
-You look so tired!
How did you feel?
-Of course I was slower than Hamada.
-You were so slow.
-But not by that much... I think...
-That was an average time.
Alright, let's see it.
What's his time?!
Alright!!
Whoa!
it's below 2 minutes.
I see!!
I see, I see...
-Alright!
-He did it below the 2 minute mark!
I mean, you were still close to 2 minutes.
-But it wasn't that bad.
-Let's go!
It really isn't that bad!
Alright.
-Who's next?
-I'll go.
- I wanna go too.
-I wanna see Endo next.
-I wanted to go next...
And we can save Tanaka for last.
-I see.
-Let me do it.
Let me do it first.
Let me pull those panties first.
Alright.
Hold on... This way...?
Which side you go is important.
Right... It changes.
You know... I have some muscle sores today...
Endo, who is used to getting undressed by a woman himself
is now taking on the challenge with a bit of uneasiness in his heart.
-Let's go then.
-You can do it.
Start!
Here it comes.
Alright, first one.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hold on...
Alright, that's good!
That's good.
-He looks so desperate.
-You can do it!
That's good.
This is tough, it's tough.
Seems like the rest will be tough.
The rest will be hard for you.
He's moving his body a lot.
Here it comes!
-You'll start drifting away from the button if you move too much.
-That's right.
This thing is very well made.
Alright, alright, Endo is screwed here.
-This is bad.
-It's bad.
It's bad.
I don't think I'll make it.
Endo, you have to be more swift.
You have to make good use of the bed to be good at this.
Have you gotten the hang of it on the fifth try?
Oh, he's going for it.
What the heck?
-The panties from before are stuck on his leg.
-Right, the ones from before.
It's still there.
The previous panties.
The soup is getting cold...
You're talking too long.
Wait!
Oh my god.
-He's managing...
-He is.
What was that?
What's wrong?
Endo looked like a mannequin just now.
That one just now was good.
-This is the last.
-The last, the last.
It's the last.
Alright.
Why are these things getting stuck?!
Hold on!!
What's wrong with him?
Come on, Endo!
Look, it won't come off.
Hold on.
-Endo! Endo! Endo!
-Hold on, I'm trying here.
That was so bad!
-This was bad.
-This was really bad.
-Alright, what is Endo's time?
-Please...
Please...
Alright!
It's alright, it's alright.
It's not that bad.
He got 1:59 and you got 2:17.
It's alright.
But he was the worst in terms of beauty points.
Right.
-There's beauty points?!
-Yeah, there are.
That was bad.
You were carrying it like this.
No way that's possible.
Oh man...
But Tanaka, now you can relax.
That's right.
Hold on, let me just do this.
-What do you mean by "this"?
-You idiot.
Just like this.
What do you mean...?
I really can't move this part much.
You're really opening up your legs to us...
That's true.
Why are you doing it in this direction?
Sorry, just let me do this quickly.
Tanaka has gotten last place in the past 2 challenges...
He's burning with fighting power.
But how will he fare?
Alright.
It depends on how you move it.
Let's go.
Start!
Here comes the first one.
Oh, this one...
-Right...
-He's turning her around.
-Huh? He seems very calm.
Amazing.
Alright, that wasn't too shabby.
-That wasn't bad.
-Right?
He's pretty good at lifting them up.
That's good.
Whoa.
He'll get some beauty points for that.
-At the moment he's got those extra beauty point.
-I see...
Amazing.
It's stuck.
You lost some beauty points there.
-That wasn't too bad, was it?
-It was fine.
It was fine.
What's wrong with you?
Don't you think about the woman's feelings?
-He really doesn't care about the woman at all.
-Right, he's being too rough.
Huh?
Alright, here comes the seventh one.
He's gotten very good at catching them.
Since the first one I mean.
Whoa! So fast!
That was fast!
But he only has 2 more left.
This is good.
He's pretty good.
So fast!
-This!
-This was a surprise.
Last one.
He's going from behind.
Right.
Alright!!
I think I'm in the lead now.
Alright!
-You're right, there wasn't much wiggling around with him.
-Yeah.
Is he getting first place?
Come on, please.
Tanaka's time is...
This!
Amazing.
Alright!!
1:45.
-That was pretty fast.
-Right?
Okay, Endo is really in trouble now.
You're right, everyone else was below 2 minutes.
Everyone.
-Endo?
-Yes?
In that sense, Matsumoto has to be feeling the pressure as well.
Let's go then!
He might lose.
What is he doing now?
He must do this every night at home.
I'm always doing this whenever she takes a shower.
What's that?
Some stranger would be shocked if they walked in on you doing that.
That's so true!
I'm getting nervous.
-It's nerve wracking, right?
-Of course.
I don't like it at all.
Our last contestant is Matsumoto.
Will he manage to retain his self-proclaimed title of "King"?
It's all mind and spirit.
Can you quit it already?
-Just get it over with already.
-You know, we're all waiting here.
-Hold on! Wait! Wait!
-Oh no!
-I didn't mean to!
-It's coming! It's coming!
He pressed it, right?
You pushed it!
-It's started.
-You pushed it!
Look! He's wiggling around!
He's squirming a ton!
See? See?! See?!
He's doing it! He is!
He's squirming around.
Look!
This is not good, is it?
He's squirming a lot.
I mean, was I moving this much?
He's having a tough time.
Right?
He's gotta hook them.
Look, look.
Right, right.
He's struggling.
Look, look, look.
A miracle might happen for me.
You bastards!
Stop commenting on my every move!
What's he saying?
That one was clean.
-Yeah, that was good.
-It was.
Look, here.
Not yet, not yet, not yet!
Not yet!
I already did that!!
That's no good!
It's no good!
You're not done!
-No matter how good your time is, you're already out!
-He's out!
Look.
All done!
I'm safe, right?
What is it?
One of them wasn't completely off the mannequin, right?
-Yes, there was one.
-Yeah, there was.
You dirty bastards!
The next one had already come down the hatch!
-But those are not the rules.
-It will come down if you press the button.
This one.
He definitely went over the 2 minute mark.
He definitely went way past 2 minutes.
Right?
Ready?
What will happen to Endo?
I think I'm safe.
I also think he's past 2 minutes.
-Or we can do a playoff with the loser from the first challenge.
-Right.
-He has to beat 2:17.
-Playoffs?!
-Here we go.
-Alright.
-Then let's see the last number first.
-Here?
-Yes.
-Five...
-Five seconds...
-Hold on...
-Five... So it can be 2:15...
-Or even 2:25....
-Right...
Come on, give me something higher than 1.
Bam!
Isn't this bad?
-I mean, it could be 1:35.
-No way!
Alright!
Here we go!
Here we go!!
-No way! It's definitely a 1.
-Yeah, it's a 1.
It's a 1!
No way it's a 2.
-It's definitely a 1.
-Here we go!
Let's go!!!
You're kidding me...
I knew it was this.
2:35 would have been bad.
Endo will take the punishment!
You're kidding me.
For real?
Endo!
Alright, for the punishment...
-Endo...
-What is this?
Really... What is it?
So the punishment this time around is...
Wear panties and go around a trendy part of town!
In my head?
Yes, you'll have to wear the panties on your head.
And you'll have to walk around in a trendy spot within the city.
-For real?
-Yes.
And the camera will be very far away.
For real?!
Yes.
A town for young people, it's Omotesando.
No one is coming near me.
They must think I'm a big pervert.
I was last place in the underwear competition so I'm here for my punishment.
I'm Endo from Cocorico.
Today I'm in a town for young people, it's Omotensando.
I'll be going then.
This is the worst.
This is really the worst.
These stores are so cool though.
As you'd expect from big brands...
No one is coming near me.
They must think I'm a big pervert.
They must think I'm a pervert.
I'm wearing women's panties on my head and all...
Everyone's looking at me.
This place looks alright.
Let's see.
How is the size?
It's perfect.
Do you only have this size?
Yes, only that size.
Do you think it goes well with these kinds of panties?
Yes, I would say so...
Is this some kind of dare?
No at all, I'm here on my own.
On your own?
But even so... I never see you on the street.
I mean, these are panties, right?
What do you mean?
Sorry.
I mean, this is not a hat, is it?
See you then.
-Say hi to your wife for me.
-Oh, thanks.
Look at him, he's shameless.
This store...