Again this year, at Lake Yamanaka, the Entertainer Fishing Competition begins
1st Competition Winner:  Matsumoto
2nd Competition Winner:  Matsumoto
3rd Competition Winner:  Endo
4th Competition Winner:  Hamada
There have been many heated battles up until now, and we have reached the 15th competition
5th Winner - Haruhiko Kato
6th Winner - Tamio Okuda
7th pogchamp - Matsumoto
8th winner - Tamio Okuda
10th winner - Hamayanen
11th winner - Ma-tsun
12th winner - Tamio
9th winner - Tetsuji Tamayama
Who shall be victorious this time?!
13th winner - Endo
14th winner - Tamio
15th ever - Gaki no Tsukai Ya Arrahende - CHIKI CHIKI
Entertainer Fishing Competition!
Ho we have begun!
Ho?!
What is it?
You said it before,
There's a million little bugs all over you!
I scratched and scratched and they just won't stay off
And this time, Tanaka is helping me out!
Look at Tanaka's face
He's totally not into this
He's not into this!
I didn't want to do this
My senpai requested me
I don't get it though what is this?
This opening act right?
Yeah exactly
The opening is supposed to be like this
There's no need for a reason
"Do funny things!", that is what an opening is
This time as well, we have a fantastic group of participants
Yes we do!
So let's begin the in-to-dukshuns!
"In-to-dukshuns"
"In-to-dukshuns"?
A man of his generation, who created many trends
He sucks at speaking, and really sucks at being funny,
A bitterly smiling copywriter - Itoi Shigesato-san!!!
Wow, look at Itoi-san, once again,
Bass Fishing Experience - 14 years
Longest Fish Caught - 40 cm
What a cool t-shirt!
Very fashionable
What is this?
He's come 3rd place every time
Oh yeah that's true
I didn't wanna hear that!
That's pretty bad
It's amazing you came 3rd every time
I am aiming for 3rd place again, then
Not 1st place, but 3rd?
That's actually pretty difficult to achieve
The next competitor,
The revival of "UNICORN" is earning him lots of royalties
A 1 in 1 million musician,
The defending champion, Okuda Tamio-san!!!!
Bass Fishing Experience - 17 years
Longest Fish Caught - 34 cm
You're tied with Matsumoto for number of victories
Oh yeah, true, true
So you could end up winning, well so could Matsumoto
Do you think you can win this year?
I can, I can
If I perform normally, I can win
Go for it!
Ok, let's introduce the next competitor
Even though he is a fantastic actor with a lot of presence,
He is shit at catching bass
Forget about winning the competition,
Will he be able to catch anything today?
Asano Tadanobou-kun!!!
Bass Fishing Experience - 7 years
Longest Fish Caught - 29.5 cm
Asano is that bad at fishing?
He has participated in 4 competitions,
He came last 3 times
Oh yeah, you're right!
This is.....
Being last is ....
That's terrible!
That's not a good look for TV
Do your best this year!
We're counting on you!
Let's move on,
His last name is Hayami, but he is not Hayami Yu
He's no Hayami Kentaro neither
An actor with a perpetual erection,
Hayami Mokomichi!
Bass Fishing Experience - 4 years
Longest Fish Caught - 34 cm
"erection actor" he said
right?
What is an "erection actor"?
He is the miraculous runner up
Last year Mokomichi came close to winning
"Was 100g away from first place"
34 centimetres
Right?
You were pretty close
He matched Tamio
TN: Players win by catching the longest fish. A tie is broken by weighing the fish
Yes, they were the same length,
It came down to weight
Yes exactly
Do your best please!
Win this year!
Yes, I aim too
This was bound to happen,
He has a dream of winning the Gaki Bass Fishing competition!
Bass Fishing rookie, Ichihara Hayato-kun!!!!!
Bass Fishing Experience - 1 year
Longest Fish Caught - 30 cm
Hayato-kuuuun!!!!
Hayato was pretty bad last year, huh?
I came 8/9
Why did you do so shit?
"Why"?
Isn't it obvious?
I couldn't catch a big one
Exactly, he didn't catch a big one
Couldn't catch a big one-
So many insects!
Amazing quantity of bugs
Catch this many fish!
Yes, I will
Catch this many black bass
As delicate as a spiny lobster,
As noble as the Ise Shrine,
He is nothing else but manly!
Iseya Yusuke-kun!!!!
Bass Fishing Experience - NONE!
It's your first time?
You have any experience fishing?
Absolutely none
So this is like your first time?
There's a chance you could win on your first fishing trip
There's a chance you could win,
Do your best please!
I will!
This time, to assess your fishing abilities,
We have invited a prolific psycich
Come here please!
I think you all know this person,
Shimo-Ochiai's mother!
First off, Itoi-san's assessment
She's really staring at me
He will marry soon, his second wife will be much slimmer
TN: Thanks to /u/xmog123x for this translation from German!
He's a genius at taking credit for other people's work
Other people's work?
She's saying you do lame things
She's saying bad things about you all of a sudden
He will be very rich
Everyone you know,
thinks you're a pain in the ass
Ok, let's move on,
Mokomichi-kun's assessment
He is a good looking young man
Can this dark skinned man and Shozo step forward please?
She's calling on you
He also looks pretty good
You both look like Beat Takeshi from behind
If you both do a Beat Takeshi impression, your fishing will go well
Declare your enthusiasm for today as Takeshi-san
Me first?
"We're gonna fish today, Dankan you bastard"
"Time to fish, you bastard Dankan"
He likes nice cars
You too, please
"I'm gonna win today you bastard!"
"You bastard Dankan!"
That "Dankan!" got laughs
Next up, Ichihara-kun!!!
He is very white
High school graduate and cute boy, step forward please
I'm the cute one?
He is not so white
"What happened? This is serious!"
Your crotch is bright red, does it tingle?
What the hell are you saying?
He will have two kids
You,
You smell like mackerel from the balls down,
Or am I imagining things?
What the hell are you saying?!
Maybe he will return soon
TN: "Dekichatta Kekkon" means a marriage that happens because of a pregnancy.
Referring to Matsumoto's surprise wedding announcement.
If you two touch the cock of man who had a shotgun wedding,
You will have good luck today
I see!
You see?
This cock here had a shotgun wedding
Then, go ahead, get some good luck
Sorry for this
Here I go!
First time-
It's my first time meeting them
Use this good luck to fish!
Competition chairman,
Tanaka-san's opening declaration
Understood
He's the chairman?
Never seen him before
I shall deliver the opening declaration!
Once again, these shit participants,
These B-Grade comedians,
THESE B-GRADE actors,
On top of that!
This B-Grade musician
HUH?!
What is your occupation again?
I don't have one in particular...
I mean you have one
What the hell generation are you from?
Right? I don't get this copywriter
I don't either!
Tanaka-san,
go ahead, keep going
You!
Enough! Enough!
That's enough outta you!
Go fish, and come apologise to me after!
German translation by /u/xmog123x
Subbed by /u/senor_wristband
The fishing competition begins!
The man who catches the biggest fish wins!
On this boat: Hamada, Asano, and Iseya
If someone yells "I got one!" I'm gonna get startled
Gotta catch a fish quickly
Do you have a catchphrase for when you catch something?
Wouldn't that be embarassing?
Damn, everyone on this boat is good at fishing
On this boat; Matsumoto, Itoi, Okuda; Veteran Fishers
And here we have Endo, Hayami, Ichihara; Handsome Team
I'm gonna catch a big one
Of course, they all aim for the first catch
Not yet huh?
Got one!
Got one! Got one!
Really?
Endo suddenly catches one!
It's coming, it's coming
Coming, coming
Huge
HUGE! IT'S HUGE!
Is he for real, he's just saying that right?
YES! Come on!
It's huge!
YESS!!!!
Endo got one, and it seems pretty huge!
YES! It's a big one!
Really?
Seriously....
Huge! It's super huge!
It sure is huge
It's a big one, amazing
How big is it?
45 cm
Forty Five!
I caught it!
I got one! I got one!
Then Mokomichi gets a bite!
... or not
Ah shit!
Damn it I almost had one
Ichihara-kun, you can stop now
I won't lose to you
I think I've won
I won't lose
C'mon, be serious here
I'm still, I won't lose to you
Ok, Ok
40 minutes later, how is Hamada's boat doing?
Damn it....
That's enough of that spot right?
Right
Enough already?
You need to tell me, I've been waiting for a while
I can recast?
Yes!
Ok ok ok, I'll cast again
It's Ok if they catch instead right? Asano and Iseya
Maybe in order?
I don't mind at all if we catch in order
I can't go until Hamada-san goes
What are you saying?!
Meanwhile, a serious atmosphere surrounds the concentrating Itoi
Ok
Got one! Itoit hit!
Itoi-san got one
I got one huh?
Here it comes!
Itoi's first catch!
Thank you very much
He caught one very quietly
Quietly caught one?
I won't be last place now
I also wanna try that,
just like Itoi-san,
I want to try out that grown up reaction
That "Hmm"
Not making a loud sound, just "Hmm"
Next time I'll try doing that
Like that?
My reaction might be hard to understand however
Unless you catch something, you can't relax and talk normally huh?
Like Mokomichi and Ichihara-san
They aren't speaking at all huh?
I will not speak
Not until they catch something
Ichihara-kun in particular,
Hasn't said anything in half an hour
Not speaking at all huh?
Meanwhile, Hamada's boat doesn't seem to be catching anything
Are you getting any bites?
Bites? Mine is-
Huh? It's gone
It's gone yeah
Senpai get a hold of yourself!
Can you get that guy to stop laughing?
I've been hearing him laugh since the dressing rooms
I've never heard anyone else's laugh but his
He's laughing by himself isn't he? There's nobody else there
1 hour after the start,
Only Endo and Itoi have caught something so far
Tamio didn't catch anything?
In the previous competitions,
We've had a bunch of people not catch anything
Worst time was when Asano-san came,
nobody caught anything
It's your fault
This is Asano's fault
I have to overcome that today
Yeah
Still no fish caught on Hamada's boat;
Iseya changes his lure
I got a new, different lure put on mine
Really?
Ahh that looks easy to eat
Ah I got one!
Really?
Really?!
Asano gets a hit!
You got it. It's coming, it's coming!
It's coming!
It's coming?
Is it good?
You did it!
Why you?!
Asano finally catches one!
First guy on our boat
This puts more pressure on me
I'm so glad, I got one this year
This is bad
Yeah
They keep catching stuff
This is bad
Mokomichi shows his anxiety, and then!
I GOT IT I GOT IT
Ah it was just caught on something
EHH?
He was mistaken
That's the first thing you said in an hour
Heard your voice for the first time in a while
Meanwhile on the veteran team,
Matsumoto and Okuda have not caught anything
Their harmony is off
There's that weird performance again...
I can see what he's trying to do from this distance
I get it yeah
Are you all doing well?
Yes
We've prepared something to lift your spirits!
Yama-Chan QUIZ!!!!
TN: Impression of Kasuga from Audrey
Tooos!
We will ask one of your boatmates a question
The rest of you will guess their answer
First off, this boat
A question for Itoi-san
Itoi-san Personal Quiz!
What is Itoi-san's favourite wordplay right now?
Itoi-san will write the correct answer on here
You can't think of anything?
Ah he got one
He laughed at it right now
Yeah that might give it away
He laughed yeah
Ehh what could it be??
The right answer....
I don't know what the right answer should be
Actually you did a pretty good job here
Really?
So it's a good wordplay?
I laughed at it yeah
Really?
Ehh what could it be?
It is related to fishing
I see
We've practically given you the answer
It starts with "Tsureta Tsureta"
TN: Tsureta means fished
Yes, so guess the answer please
Seriously?
"Tsureta, Tsureta ..."
"Christmas Tree!"
Funny, that was funny
Ehh that was funny?!!
Yeah that was funny!
Really? It's that sort of pun right?
Yes, exactly Matsumoto-san
Eh? "Tsureta"-
I'll give you a big hint, Tamio-san you answer too please
"Tsureta Tsureta" and then somebody's name
A famous person
Another hint,
He is a retro celebrity
Tsure-Tamiya Jiro?
AHH! Incorrect, however,
You were close!
Really?
It's that sort of name!
Tsure-Tamba Tetsuro?
AHHHH
So close!
Last chance!
It's more punny
More punny?
Tsure-
Tsure-Tako Hachiro!
No more chances!
Unfortunate!
We got so close!
Itoi-san, the correct answer please!
Tsureta Tsureta - Tsuruta Koji
The correct answer was "Tsureta Tsureta - Tsuruta Koji!"
Yamasaki that's bullshit man, you
You saw that and said it was funny!
You can't tell us that is funny!
You made us panic over here!
Iseya-san Personal Quiz!
Name a male entertainer you'd like to spend the night with
You love those kinds of questions huh?
They're asking Iseya right, but,
you don't want it to seem like your actual opinion, right?
That's true
Right?
That's true right?
That is surprising!
It's like "Oh wow really?"
Our reaction to the answer is a hint
But wouldn't you react like that at any name?
Like "Ahhh him"
Tackey
Unfortunately,
Incorrect!
Ok so Hamada-san likes Tackey
No hold on that's not what I meant!
Ok, Asano-san?
You made it hard for him to answer
You should be able to get it without a hint
Yes exactly
Is he Japanese?
He's Japanese
On top of that,
It's like "Would you really pick him today?"
Asano!
Incorrect
Asano-san-
But you're on the right track
You're getting warmer
He's on one of the boats over there!
Matsumoto-san
Incorrect!
Last chance, Hamada-san
Tamio!
Unfortunately!
Who is it?
The answer,
was Endo!
It was Endo
When we were introducing ourselves to each other,
Endo-san had the brightest smile
We were all smiling!
We were all smiling
Okuda and Matsumoto want to catch something soon
They spotted something surprising!
Woahh that startled me!
If you see that all of a sudden it's startling right?
That's pretty funny
That's embarassing, I was more startled than I should've been
I was startled!
Yes, that's true
After the massive goose
Matsumoto concentrates on fishing again
He wants to switch his lure for better results,
But then he feels something!
Ah,  I got one
Did he finally catch one?!
Slowly spinning his reel, wanting to change his lure
but then
Ah, I got one!
He got a bite!
It's coming
A big one?
I think it's a big one
Could be a good one
Oh shit!
Oh shit I got too excited
Not bad,
That's not too bad
That's a good one
Matsumoto catches one!
This can compete with Endo's
It has eggs
Seems heavy
Okuda is feeling the pressure, but then
Tamio-san?
Yes?
*Not Good?*
Only I haven't caught one
Right?
You could come in last this time
Are you guys okay over there?
We're fine,
You're experienced,
Your pride is on the line
Is that so?
Nothing caught since then huh?
Nothing at all
Honestly my first catch was a fluke
Something just tugged on my line all of a sudden
But, I got something again
No way
Really?
Another hit for Asano!
You got it!
Sorry about this
What the hell man?
You're catching them by not caring
Sorry for this
Asano's second fish!
Just keeps on catching them
This is pretty fun
Yeah you're right
That's what a fishing competition is about!
The people who caught something are having fun
But the ones who haven't feel the pressure building
And then the veteran Itoi,
Catches his second fish!
Really?
It's a small one
A small one
Then Matsumoto gets one!
and then Ichihara!
However,
Which line is it caught on?
Wow!
Woah what's this?
You both-
Ehh what?
It's caught on both lines
The same bass caught on both lures!
Seriously?
This can happen?
It's coming here
Amazing
What? what?
Who gets the fish?
Woah what the hell?
It got caught
Who gets it?
It's not big enough to fight over
Allow the young people to have it
The young people can have it
Matsumoto-san, thank you for this
Ichihara catches one thanks to Matsumoto's kindness
That's amazing
I wonder what happened
Then, Iseya feels a bite
Is it coming?
It's coming
I did it!
Lose it, Iseya lose it, I haven't caught one
Huge!
Congratulations Iseya! The first bass you've ever caught!
Woah what's this?
I did it!
Why does it look like that?
It ate too much food
Ate too much?
Gross
It's so...
I did it though, I'm glad I caught something like this
Once you catch one you start speaking more
Last year's champion Okuda enters serious mode
Gotta catch one soon!
Me too
Am I gonna get one?
And then
Okuda got lucky!
He got one!
I caught one
This is a small one
Tamio-san caught one
Eh, no way
No way......
This is kinda...
Okuda escapes last place!
Last place is between Hamada and Mokomichi!
Will they catch a black bass?!