Matsumoto - "Um...Seriously, his forehead is getting big as iPad..."
Tanaka - "Yeah it's terrific."
Matsumoto - "His hairline is receding each year!"
Endo - "It's rare that forehead is that shining..."
Matsumoto - "Right, What do we do today?"
Hamada - "Nah we never heard of anything..."
Matsumoto - "It's not time to relax and chat."
Hamada - "Of course. We don't have much time."
Itao - "Good Morning."
Everyone - "Good Morning."
Matsumoto - "Are you kidding me!?"
Itao - "Oh, My moustache?"
Matsumoto - "Yeah."
Itao - "Well, It's good to do something like this once in a while."
Itao - "I can have much better nightlife.(This can also mean sex.)"
Yamazaki - "Oh, you lewd."
Itao - "Anyway, My wife will take part in Indian TV show, and they are gonna shoot in Japan."
Itao - "So I thought if guys gonna visit."
Everyone - "No, No, No."
Matsumoto - "How he invites us is weird."
Itao - "They are broadcasting it to ASEAN 10 countries."
Matsumoto - "So many people are watching it."
Itao - "This program really is popular in there!"
Matsumoto - "Okay, We got it. I'm gonna send you an SMS."
Itao - "Seriously, They also want to broadcast in Japan."
Itao - "Why don't we Gaki coorperate with them."
Hamada - "But we need to acceptance by the producer."
Matsumoto - "Did we have a producer in this show?"
Matsumoto - "I didn't know this show had a producer. I thought assistant directors are running it".
Itao - "Let's just go and visit."
Hamada - "Can we just visit?"
Itao - "Yeah, just visit. They are gonna shoot an introduction."
Matsumoto - "Mr.iPad, What are you gonna say?"
Producer Nakamura - "Ok, let's just visit then."
Itao - "Yeah, We'll just see how they do it."
Matsumoto - "The end of his words faded away..."
Voiceover - "Members visit Indian ultra popular show..."
Voiceover - "Members unwillingly decided to visit "Indian ultra popular show" Itao's claiming..."
Itao - "Everyone, over there."
Hamada - "Yeah I see some weird figures..."
Itao - "Yeah they are shooting in here."
Matsumoto - "That's true."
Hamada - "Oh they are so loud..."
Yamazaki - "Can she make up that close?"
Yamazaki - "She's just making up right there."
Text - "Itao's wife making up just before the take."
Itao - "They are currently briefing."
Itao - "The guy with turban - He is a very popular national MC."
Itao and Text - "He is a very popular national MC and known as India's Hideyuki Nakayama." (Hideyuki Nakayama is a popular MC known for "Uchikuru!?" which is parodied this time)
Itao - "He is very popular."
Hamada - "I have no idea what are they talking about..."
Matsumoto - "It's not main shot, right?"
Itao - "Yeah."
Yamazaki - "Is he producer?"
Itao - "Yes, um I am going to greet him a bit."
Hamada - "Can he speak their language?"
Turban Guy to Itao - "Namaste! (Indian greeting). How are you?"
Hamada - "What are they saying..."
Turban Guy - "Namaste!"
Turban Guy to Matsumoto - "I regularly watch your movies. I have seen Dainipponjin."
Itao - "He saw Dainipponjin and he loves it, he even bought DVDs."
Hamada - "It's also famous in India."
Itao - "Yeah that's what they say."
Hamada - "They loves movie."
Turban guy to the rest of the troupe - "Okay guys let's start."
Response - "Okay, okay."
Text - "The take has began finally."
Hamada - "Her shoes doesn't fit."
Itao - "Looks like they are gonna shoot."
Hamada - "She's usually barefoot."
Guy - "5, 4, 3, 2, 1!"
Matsumoto - "That's not good."
Guy in golden clothes - "We have a great show for you today. Everyone keep watching. Sherry (Name of Itao's wife), come here"
Itaos's Wife - "Wow my friends and fans. My Romeo and Juliet."
Matsumoto - "They are really quickly introduce guest."
Itao - "They said they don't really talk before introducing guest."
Itao's Wife - " So, will you come to my home? (Theme of the show)"
Everyone - "Yes, we will! We will"
Itao - "They are saying, Come to my house, come to my house."
Endo - "There's similar show, isn't it?"
Hamada - "There is, there is."
Guy who stands up - "Great work! Cut! Great work."
Woman standing over guy - "What happened? What happened? Someone call a doctor!"
Guy in red clothes - "What happened to him?"
Female voice in background while shot is focused on Gaki members - "Call for an ambulance!"
Itao - "Looks like that's serious."
Male voice - "We need to take him to the hospital"
Matsumoto - "Oh, isn't that part of the show?"
Endo - "He spoke very fine just before."
Guy in red clothes - "There's a hospital nearby in that direction. We need to take him there quickly."
Hamada - "He was like suffering from stomachache."
Endo - "What's wrong?"
Guy in red clothes to Itao - "Can't you see that there's something wrong with him? What will we do? What do we do about the show?"
Guy in red clothes to Itao - "Please do something. (Pointing towards Gaki members) Please ask them to help."
Hamada - "What's wrong? What's wrong?"
Itao - "Well the MC has got uh... food poisoning, got from mackerel in lunchbox?"
Itao - "Then I'm sorry but now I'm gonna be MC."
Endo - "Are you okay? He's nationally popular MC, right?"
Itao - "Yeah but the MC's gone now."
Yamazaki - "It's Indian show, right?"
Itao - "There will be subtitle."
Itao - "So then that's asking from producer that members join the take as Japanese friends of the wife."
Endo - "Wasn't it just visit?"
Itao - "But they just shoot and broadcast, no reserve."
Matsumoto - "Even it's popular show?"
Itao - "Yeah no reserve."
Itao - "Looks like they will move to restaurant, Let's go."
"They now taking part in Indian popular show reluctantly..."
Voiceover - "Members now have to take part in Indian popular show that is totally not "Uchikuru!?"."
"Arrived at firt recording spot."
Itao - "Take will start."
Hamada - "Take will start you say but..."
Guy in golden clothes - "Everything is alright. Just act natural."
Itao - "He said let's just act natural."
Guy - "5, 4, 3,2,1"
Itao - "Ok let's start."
Itao's Wife - "Will you go with me? (Name of the show)"
Itao and Wife - "We will! We will!"
Narration over the map - "Today's show is about our guest's favourite restaurant. Let's talk to our guest while eating her favourite food!"
Itao - "This time, My wife's Japanese friends, Members of Gaki no Tsukai is the guests."
Text in the box - "Members of Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende"
Itao - "So you guys are my wife's Japanese friends. How is it? What's the best memory with my wife?"
Itao's wife - "Of course it is."
Some whispering and text - "There's a cue card. What's that mean?"
Text on paper - "Speak"
Itao - "Best memory."
Endo - "He's too much foward."
Hamada - "Mic will catch the sound if you bash paper like that..."
Tanaka - "Ok I got it. I got it."
Matsumoto - "It's scary..."
Itao - "Let's just stop shooting."
"Shooting interrupted."
Guy to Tanaka - "Why didn't you say anything? You're useless. Just do as you're told. Why are you not working properly?"
Itao - "Because you are her friend, They wanted comment immediately."
Hamada - "Indians are so harsh!"
Tanaka - "Do we have such memory?"
Itao and text - "It's nationally popular show, after all."
Itao and text - "Aren't you passive all the time? You almost didn't speak in outside shooting. You are in popular show. You need to be conscious about it."
Itao and text - "It's not Japanese show. Audiences don't know you!"
Tanaka - "I'm sorry."
Itao - "Do you understand what's it like to be popular show?"
Itao and text - "What's the definition of popular do you think?"
Tanaka - "Popular... uh..."
Hamada - "You don't have to scold him like that I think..."
Itao - "Did you take part in any nationally popular show? By the way."
Itao  - "What's the impression?"
Tanaka - "Nationally...
popular show?"
Itao - "Then that's not an attitude."
Itao - "Definitely not."
Tanaka - "Sorry, no."
Itao - "Ok, Let's do it again."
Guy in golden clothes - "Let's try one more take. (To Tanaka) Don't mess it up this time. Got it?"
"Restarting take."
-Guy- "5, 4, 3, 2,1"
Itao - "Ok, Let's look at my wife's past, adolescence review show!"
- Japansese Text - "Playing back the wife's adolescence"
- Text - " Secret recording of the wife"
- Narration/Voiceover - "Let's have a candid look at the guest"
- Itao and text "This is when the wife was 19 year old as gravure idol... Yeah She's from gravure. It's gonna be a little shameful but we've got secret VTR, nostalgic one. So let's take a look."
- Text -"Irritating a sleeping Sherry" (Itao's wife)
- Itao "It's an variety show".
- Hamada "Music is similar..."
- Bald guy - "Greetings! Good morning. Today we're here to have a look at the guest in her natural habitat. Let's go inside and see for ourselves"
-"It's irritation mission."
- Itao "That's shameful!"
- Text - "Inside the room"
- Itao "Movie like this still exists."
- Text - "Sherry Sleeping"
- Tanaka "She doesn't notice at all..."
- Hamada "Who is this on the corner of VTR?"
- Itao "He's at studio."
- Hamada "Oh studio."
- Itao "He's smelling it!"
- Text - "The scent of the shoes!"
- Bald guy - "These shoes smell so nice."
- Bald guy in the bathroom - "Let's see what's inside."
- Bald guy - "There's her toothbrush."
- Matsumoto "Was there any gravure idol in India?"
- Bald guy - "Smells so nice."
- Itao "He's reckless!"
- Text - "Placing the toothbrush in his mouth!"
- Itao "She doesn't notice at all..."
- Itao "Bare legs!"
- Itao's wife - "What's happening"
"Stop it."
- Itao "It's sexy!"
- Itao's wife - "What are you doing?"
- Both of them - "Irritation mission successful"
"Success"
- Itao "How is this? Huh guys?"
- Itao and text "You guys got horny, don't you?"
- Endo "No, We're okay."
- Itao "My wife at that time around doesn't wanted to be gravure idol."
- Itao and text "In fact, She wanted to become an actresss."
- Itao "By then, she was really wondered whether she should become an actress..."
- Itao and text "There was a dear friend really supported her."
- Itao "They were very close!"
- Itao's wife "Of course it is."
- Fat woman - "Guess who"
- Itao's wife - "Who is it?"
- Itao's wife - "It's my friend!"
- Itao "Isn't that friend we were talking about?"
- Text - "A close friend appears on the show"
- Itao "She's An Jata."
- Itao "There was a game you two always played, right?"
- Itao's wife "Of course it is."
- Itao "Then why don't you play it, It was long time no see after all."
- Itao's wife - "You always win. But not today!"
- Text - "Competition between them to drink spicy tea"
- The friend - "I'll win like always"
- Itao "This is Chai drinking battle - If some one loses, the one will drink very spicy chai."
- Matsumoto "Very spicy chai, huh?"
- The hand gestures are them counting down for Rock Paper Scissors- "3, 2, 1"
- Text - "Itao's wife loses"
- Yamazaki "Looks like there is."
- Itao's wife - "I almost died last time. Go easy on me. No no, not so much. I'll die! That's enough!"
- Itao "It's gonna be spicy..."
- Itao "It's gonna be spicy!"
- Itao "Do you recall your old times?"
- Itao "You people did this kind of thing."
- The friend "Yeah.(Soudesune, in Japanese)"
- Yamazaki "Soudesune!?"
- Tanaka "Hey!"
- Itao "Well She likes Japan."
- Matsumoto "Oh ok. It really surprised me..."
- Itao "They were classmates. So speaking of classmates, Downtown is also the ones. Why don't you play it once?"
- Hamada "Why!?"
- Matsumoto "Seriously?"
- Itao "Serious."
- Matsumoto "Actually, I REALLY don't want to lose."
- Yamazaki "It's getting serious!"
- Matsumoto "Yeah this game is serious."
- Text - "After the break - Downtown attempts the spicy tea challenge!"
- Voiceover - "The men of Downtown take on the spicy tea challenge!"
- Downtown "the first one is Rock, Rock paper scissors!"
- Matsumoto "I won!"
- Text - "Hamada loses"
- Itao "Hamada loses!"
- Itao "This is ordinary Chai."
- Matsumoto "Yeah Chai is usually mild."
- Yamazaki "It has to be hard one."
- Hamada "This is bad!"
- Itao "Well then Hamada, drink it please."
- Hamada "This one will be extreme..."
- Itao "He drunk all!"
- Hamada "What's so funny about this?"
- Voiceover - "Hama-chan! Your facial expressions are way too cute. Thank you!"
- Voiceover when Sanbancho cafe appears - "But where are they headed next? In this cafe, let's find out what awaits Sherry and her husband!"
- Itao "Now here we are at the cafe!"
- Itao "What memory do you recall from this cafe?"
- Matsumoto "Why are you whispering? You can just say it normaly."
- Itao "She spent time with her old lover in this cafe."
- Matsumoto "Is it ok to say that to husband?"
- Itao "That's ok, yes, It's all gone."
- Matsumoto "Why do you drink now?"
- Hamada "She was always eating back in the restaurant."
- Itao "The saying from her old lover become her motto."
- Itao "There was such saying, right? What was it?"
- Itao "The cow that swims about reaches Ganges shore."
- Text - "A cow swimming in the Ganges river"
- Itao and text "This means how much you're in the bottom, with struggle you only raise up."
- Itao and text "In Japanse, "The sun also rises"."
- Matsumoto "It's so different..."
- Endo "I guess It's just means "pull together"?"
- Matsumoto "What now, What now?"
- Itao's wife - "Even you're here?"
- Matsumoto "That's enough..."
- Matsumoto "I'm fed up!"
- Itao "He's the old lover!"
- Text - "An old lover appears"
- Itao's wife - "Everyone here is looking."
- Old lover - "So what?"
- Matsumoto "She doesn't hate it, does she?"
- Yamazaki "It's funny how she became ashamed for it..."
- Itao "He... He's good at Japanese."
- Itao "He's been in Japan for long time."
- Matsumoto "How long were you in love?"
- Old lover "About three years."
- Old lover and text "She and me had very good sex."
- Hamada "You shouldn't say that!"
- Matsumoto "What now?"
- Yamazaki and text "Looking at each other too much."
- Endo "It's not good!"
- Tanaka "Stop it."
- Itao "If they get high... they dance."
- Matsumoto "But this has something to do with mixer's will, right?"
- Itao "It's necessary in India."
- Itao "They do it all the time. By each scene, they dance."
- Matsumoto "Yeah I can see that from their movies."
- Itao "It was long time no see for them, they did it enthuastically."
- Itao "We can't see something like that very often in Japan!"
- Matsumoto and text "Staffs are not happy it seems."
- Itao and text "Indian staffs usually don't smile."
- Itao "In India, Dancing involves with even variety show."
- Itao "Back then, in elementary highschool, she learned how to dance."
- Itao "She was discouraged, but there was one who saved here from discourage, right? Who is it?"
- Matsumoto "Just say it openly!"
- Itao "There was dancing teacher, like her mentor!"
- Matsumoto "I fed up... This is enough!"
- Itao's wife - "Sensei!"
- Matsumoto "Gimmie a break..."
- Text - "A Sensei from her past appears"
- Voiceover - "The guest lived a life dedicated purely to song and dance. The Sensei who helped and supported her for so long is now in front of her. Let's see what he has to say"
- Sensei - "You never had any interest in academics, and just barely made it through school. I scolded you a lot. You left in a fit of anger. I'm here to apologize to you. Please forgive me."
- Itao and text "I think this is about fun memory."
- Itao and text "It's getting serious."
- Itao "Sensei started to cry..."
- Downtown "It's not over!?"
- Sensei- "I did not respect how hard you were working towards your dreams. And now, you've done India and Indian dance proud, here in Japan. I'm proud of you. Please never forget your roots and where you came from."
- Itao "They speak long in India, you know."
- Itao "I think she suffered a lot."
- Itao "It makes us think."
- Matsumoto "Yeah, yeah."
- Itao "She is getting high, for thanks for her sensei and his letter."
- Endo "What kind of emotion she's trying to express?"
- Endo "I really don't understand..."
- Itao's wife - "I'm going mad!"
- Itao "Oh look, Sensei started to dance!"
- Yamazaki "No wonder this is popular show..."
- Itao "Dancing scene usually get so high viewer rate!"
- Itao and text "AD is provoked by the dance!"
- Yamazaki "What are you doing!?"
- Matsumoto "Are you kidding me!? You are too impressionable!"
- Matsumoto "No way!"
- Itao "Hey you are now provoked! Let's dance!"
- Itao and text "Oh music stopped."
- Itao "That was great!"
- Yamazaki "Hey he's gone! Stay with us!"
- Matsumoto "What's wrong with our AD?"
- Endo "He's gone alongside with them."
- Itao "Is it gonna be ok?"
- Guy in red clothes - "I think that's enough material. This will make for a great show."
- Itao "The shooting was very good he said."
- Itao and text "It was great that everyone took part in the show."
- Matsumoto "I'm glad."
- Itao "He says it was very good."
- Guy in red clothes - "Let's get down to business. All these actors and dancers weren't cheap."
- Itao "Yeah, That's true."
- Itao and text "So he say we made the show together, so he wants to pay part of their staff's travel expense."
- Itao "It's okay if it is part of it."
- Members "No, no, no!"
- Itao "If you pay it, you'll feel ease."
- Hamada "No way, no way, what are you saying."
- Guy in red clothes - "We have to be paid for our work."
- Itao and text "He said you guys are forgetting this is popular show."
- Itao "So with participation discount..."
- Itao and text "...$10000 will work."
- Itao "It actually costs more, but they discounted."
- Hamada "You are paying it..."
- Guy in red clothes - "Namaste"
- Guy in red clothes - "Let's go, everyone."
- Matsumoto "We are tricked again..."
- Hamada "No merit for this show. We couldn't take these cuts."
- Matsumoto "Not only we couldn't take cuts, but we've lost an AD..."