De De Demae-can (Japan food delivery site)
Demae ga sui sui suiii
Atsu Atsu...ahhh
wait a second, wait a second...
this is awful...
AHHHHH
How is it?
Umm...what do you mean by how...
I really want to catch up Hamada
I just now thought that I can do it
But when I actually try it...
it turns out to be quite difficult
Well yeah, it was awful just now...
So nervous,
I was terrified just now
Terrified?
Think about it...his song sold for double millions
Well yeah, so he's used to be on stage
I never sold any song
The vitality that Hamada showed us in Demae-can's CM,
urges Matsumoto to deeply admire him
While Hamada is not here,
Demae-can's studio set has been rebuilt,
and Matsumoto challenges himself to catch up Hamada
however things are never easy...
It really is difficult isn't it
Yeah it definitely is difficult
Let's try it one more time?
We'll pay full attention to watch it
He sure is warmed up now
Let's go
My face is going numb
Just relax, take it easy
De De Demae-can, Demae ga sui sui suiii
Ah no, wait a second
My hand can't help from becoming like this
Because I'm terrified
It's like this, like this right?
Sweat is coming out from a different gland
from a different sweat gland?
Like a subway...it's from a different place
Oh really...
Sleep well
I'll be right back
Should we rewatch Hamadan-san's CM?
Let's watch it again
and make sure everything is good
Housei suggests to rewatch the CM
and observe Hamada's reaction and movement
But I've actually watched many times on YouTube already
De De Demae-can
Demae ga sui sui suiii
Warm, warm, delivered to you warmly
De De Demae-can
Demae ga sui sui suiii
I want to hear your true opinions
Excuse me...
Yes
The dance is completely different
He's clearly dancing in Box steps
Oh I see, I see
Matsumoto-san's steps are somehow wobbly
Please pay attention to the steps
His legs are clearly stepping
Yeah it is
Although it's hard to notice
he's definitely doing those steps
Yeah that's clearly box steps
because he's doing box steps
so the upper body becomes stable
Yeah
Housei is now lecturing Matsumoto about Box steps
Try it like this, with rhythm
Oh I see, so like this
As if you're going for delivery right now
Oh I get it, I get it
This cultivates your emotions as well
Feels like you're delivering on a motorbike
Exactly, just like a delivery
This seems to be good now isn't it
Remember your rhythm
Music start!
His face is different
De De Demae-can, Demae ga sui sui suiii
Wait a moment, it's completely different
What happened?
Box steps took all my attention
Your face also went numb
I'm feeling even more terrified now
This is no way going to surpass Hamada
Yes, you're right, that's for sure
To be honest, he looks scary sometimes right?
But that face was never shown in Demae-can's CM
He's really awesome isn't he!
Yeah he's awesome
At the same time
Why?
Why are there 2 syrup and 2 milk
Having 2 is not necessary is it
You're not adding anything to it?
No, I can't drink it
Try to drink it man
Don't be picky
Are you interested in anything now?
Not at all recently
You can't go anywhere
I didn't even eat outside these months
What do you think?
What could I do?
Well...
While watching it,
I think appearance is important too
It's not the official jacket
and the mic is also different
Yeah your right, this is just prepared by our staffs
Can I confirm with Hamada's manager?
Having the official jacket makes a difference
Please excuse me...
I feel sorry...
I really underestimated it
I thought I can do it
Hands are like this?
But it becomes like this
Because Ueki-san did it like this
Ueki-san is like this
But Demae-can is delivery so it's like this
and this concept is not in my mind
Come on
I found it!
It's official!
It's really Demae-can
And the mic is completely different isn't it
Yeah completely different
Wow, it's just...even the fabric feels much better
yeah
fabric is completely different
Feels like silk
It's official
It's the one that Hamada wore
and the mic he used
yeah, awesome
please take the mic too
It's completely different, even your face is different
I can do it!
I can feel the shine coming to me
Yeah, you definitely can do it now
Ok, I feel like it now!
Wait a moment
I've heard another important information
The box step Hamada did
it was actually not in the scenario
Hamada-san improvised the steps on stage
How awesome can he be!!
Really?
How awesome is he!
Can I even surpass him?
It's those steps that made it feels like delivering
What an amazing idea
Well, just try your best
The appearance is much better
Music start!
Looks much better than last time
It's even worse isn't it?
It's becoming even worse
Your face becomes terrified at the moment it starts
Like Zabunguru's Kato
Like feeling struggled
I'm much more struggled here
Sorry Tanaka
I feel really sorry for bothering you guys
No we're good, we want you to surpass him
You're not going outside at all right?
Yeah, so you guys are definitely better
we're being recognized by the public
people would know that "he's at that shop"
and if that shop turns out to be in trouble
people would say "he's also there"
well, you guys won't understand
it's definitely better
Excuse me Hamada-san
Yes?
Sorry for being a Senpai like this
But the appearance and atmosphere has changed
What about doing it with Hamada's voice?
So basically lip-sync
Singing out loud is definitely a pressure
If there's no need to sing anymore
then I can focus on the movements
Yeah, you can do it this time
There's no need to sing, just focus
Please try again, music start!
De De Demae-can
Demae ga sui sui suiii
Ah my hand becomes like this again
Ahhh
It's so difficult
It's really difficult
Also because bits of chicken meat is stuck in my inner teeth
Please take it out then
So it makes you into that face?
Yeah
Hamada-san
you're going home right?
Ah, yeah
Excuse me Hamada-san (15 minutes before)
Matsumoto-san says he want to be like Hamada-san in Demae-can CM
But it's not going smoothly
He's still making fun of me
Anyway please go help out Matsumoto-san
No it's none of my business
He took it upon himself to do it right?
It's none of my business, what are you talking about
Get out of my way
Can you stop please?
Hello, Hamada-san
How is it over there
They're still working hard
Ok, I got it
Wait, Hamada-san
We're together since primary school
Please take care of Hamada-san everyone
Excuse me,
can I change the destination?
Sure, change to where?
This is such a shitty episode
let's change it to god episode
people are gonna say it's shitty on the net
No don't think about it, please don't give up
our difference in level as a combi is apparent
When you think of Hamada-san
Rosary comes to mind right?
You're not wearing any rosary right?
Never saw you wear any rosary
Betting on the very last hope
Tanaka suggests to wear rosary
which is like Hamada's trademark
This really looks like Hamada
We can feel it
Sometimes he wears so much that it becomes like abacus
Yeah, it really looks like Hamada now
Wow, that's awesome!
It's Hamada if just looking at the hand
Wearing it already makes me feel secure
Like being wrapped up by Hamada
Let's try again
His face really changed
He changed at the moment he wears it
His face looks completely different
De De Demae-can
Demae ga sui sui suiii
Warm, warm, delivered to you warmly
How is it?
Isn't he wearing too much?
There's too much rosary
Makes me feel like what CM is it
Yeah you're right
It feels really heavy
Let's confirm again about the rosary
But I successful removed the chicken meat
He's not wearing rosary
He's not wearing rosary at all
I thought it's strange too
Keep making noise kasha-kasha
This is really my mistake
This just came to my mind when talking about Hamada
Wait...wait...can you take a photo for me?
Well, yeah, well, he really is showing a good facial expression
It's really a good facial expression
That face is never shown on TV shows
Yeah, he makes faces separately
And that hits Dentsu and Hakuhodo's heart (CM company)
Yeah, that is really a technique
Yeah, it's not even in our mind to do so
-Hey     -Good morning
Hey good morning
Hamada is now here at Nippon Television
What a deep double eyelid
I want to watch it objectively
Can you guys do it for me?
I want to watch it
Oh I see, to watch it objectively
Well, Endo can you do it?
Are you serious?
That was awful, really awful
It's not feeling vibrant
Not vibrant, and his legs are not moving
Did my legs not move?
The face is also terrified
Really?
Tanaka's challenge
Remember your face
Stop! Enough, enough, it's enough
It's enough, let's stop, that's enough
You look like the face of an armor
with a turned-up chin
Can barely watch it
Yeah, you're right
You're trying too hard to open your mouth
Although Matsumoto watched the 3 member's performance,
however, he still can't find a way to be like Hamada
Wait, wait, wait
Sorry, I though I can do it
This is really quite difficult
Ahh, I really think I can't make it
I'm really struggling
I wonder if there's any way
Sleep well
I'll be right back
Hamada heads to the studio with the 4 members there waiting
By having an appearance like Hamada
I thought it's definitely going to work
Well, you're right
our appearance is different
Yeah, so excuse me
Give me a second
Well yeah, you're probably right
Is there anything useful though?
I found it!!
Wow, that's really useful
Wow, that's awesome
It's really awesome
Amazing (face mask & wig)
it looks like Hamada from the back
He looks like this from the back of the stage
This is how Kouhai sees Hamada
It looks just like Hamada
and moving like this
"Hey, what are you talking about!"
Wearing the face mask and wig
can Matsumoto be like his admire Hamada-san
Okay, music start!
How is it?
Well, it's not bad...but...
Why? why? why?
The facial expression never changes
I see
That smile is not on the face mask
Yeah, it's not
Hamada actually changed his facial expression for 8 times, just within those few seconds
Having only one face is not enough
Yeah, you're right
I really underestimated it
What an amazing partner
I really hoped we can help more
Hamada-san is coming
De De Demae-can
Demae ga sui sui suiii
Warm, warm, delivered to you warmly
De De Demae-can
Demae ga sui sui suiii
Yama-chan,
are you having a balanced diet?
Have you been eating vegetables?
For the upcoming season,
have hotpot with your family
and eat a lot of vegetables
Endo,
are you sleeping well?
The size of your pillow is not fit right?
If the pillow is too high,
that harms the quality of your sleep
your head is gonna hurt again
Tanaka,
this year's summer is really hot isn't it?
Is it not hot?
Matsumoto,
have you visited the medical examination yet?
if I don't ask you to go,
no one else will do it for you right?
Being healthy is the first priority
Well training yourself is good,
but remember to check your body regularly
It's not just only your body anymore right?
De De Demae-can
Demae ga sui sui suiii
Warm, warm, delivered to you warmly
De De Demae-can
Demae ga sui sui suiii
How is it Tanaka?
It's really touching
Matsumoto?
What an awesome partner I have, there's nothing else for me to say
Are you accepting any disciples?
No I'm not though
Thank you so much
I'm leaving, thank you!!
Thank you for your work!
See you
(Director) Okay!
The first time he sings was awful isn't it?
The first time he sings was awful right?
No, no
I did it on purpose to be like you guys
Oh so that's it, I see
Anyway, can you stop mocking me on this?
I'm really suffering!
I came in earlier than you guys and took a lot of scenes!
Good for you, good for you
Hamada actually arrived 2 hours earlier than others,
and have been taking scenes and rehearsals
And this surprising guest was here during the filming
(Imada Kouji) Hello Hamada-san, what are you doing here?
It's Gaki with Demae-can
You wanna do it?
May I? For such a big business
I'm just asking you, are you using here too
Well, I do want to do such a big business though
Thank you and see you