Once again, it's Jiji-Nuki
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
You can tell cause of this set
I really hate this corner, but we're doing it anyways
Who likes doing this?
Who likes doing this? Tanaka?
No no no, me? Is it me?
Facebook
You're always posting about this on
I'm on Facebook doing this?
I'm posting about it?
You really find it funny
Jiji Nuki indeed
There's a punishment?
There's a punishment today
There always is something
What the hell man
I've never gotten it
Punishments received in previous Jiji-Nuki episodes
That's true Matsumoto-san!
My record is like perfect
Wow
I wonder why huh
It's a matter of luck after all
You know actually, this time, I'm not really,
I'm not into doing this
What do you mean by that?
They're not bringing the b!tches out this time
The Bunny girls
you mean?
Bunny Girls?
You've only been doing this because of the
Downtown no
Gaki no Tsukai
Ya Arahende
Gaki Jiji-Nuki
Presenting: Gaki Jiji-Nuki
The cards being used will have various different original subjects on them
Like the game Old Maid, match the cards to deplete your hand
Whoever is left with the one unmatchable card must follow its orders
So first, we must decide who the dealer is
This hasn't really rotated that much
Dealer decided by roulette
Hosei-san will be the dealer
And the 5 were presented with cards that have famous songs with their singers drawn on them ... What will the theme be?
You must sing your heart out in A capella
A capella? ...
Sing Your Heart Out Acapella
On the card, there are what anyone would agree are famous songs
The one who holds the remaining card,
Must turn to the camera and sing that song with all their heart A capella
Doing it in a playful mocking way,
Joker
Kenji Sawada - Stripper
Doing it in a playful mocking way, is totally wrong
No impressions or anything
No impressions at all
Incidentally, I do have some matched up
Yes, some are
Ikuzo Yoshi - I'm off to Tokyo
Pair
Then what about this?
Yeah, glad this one is gone
Sera Masanori & Twist - Gun Claw
Pair
I have these ones too
That's a good one to get rid of too, actually
Pair
Tahara Otshihiko - Embrace Tonight
I seriously can't sing that one
No more? Oh no more?
"Jiji Nuki" Start
This might be nothing
Joker
Sawada Kenji - Stripper
Hmm not sure
It's not always better to have fewer cards right?
Now, it's gonna start now
I gotta look carefully, I might mess up. Got one.
Yes, please pay attention
I'm kinda glad this one got eliminated
Kayama Yuzo - Call over my wife
Pair
This is a pretty tricky song
This one then please
Eh? Do you have to sing for a long time? It's not just the one song?
It's the one song I think,
Maybe sing it twice?
No no no...
I have nothing. I have nothing. I have nothing
This one...Ok ok
Alrighty
Please don't mess about when you sing
This one is not good...
It's quite hard to get a match isn't it
This sucks
Damn, it came back
This one, c'mon
Nice to meet you new card...
You suck at this!!
Just let Tanaka be out!
No no no, that's not true
Tanaka didn't get a single pair yet
Tanaka get a pair
Yes, I got one
Tanaka after pairing
Pair
The Blue Hearts - Linda Linda
It takes a hell of a lot of energy
Yes yes yes yes yes yes
Alright I've got one
And he gets another pair in his next turn
Pair
Ueda Masaki - What a sad color
Ah this one
As well...
Got it
He gets 3 pairs in a row, and is in the lead right away!
Pair
Watanabe Misato - My Revolution
Tanaka
has won!
Joker
Yes! Thank you very much!
Pair
Fuse Akira - My Way
Ahh I have one!
Following Tanaka, the other members also proceed at a great pace
The Game Proceeds Quickly!
The next one to get out?
And, the one who won after Tanaka...
Pair
Saijo Hideki - YOUNGMAN
Here it is! YOUNGMAN!
YOUNG MAN
Hamada
has won!
Which means...
Please let me pair up with this card Hamada-san gave me!
Please! Please!
It came back!!
Came back
Just 3, now Hamada-san is gone
If you get this one
Current cards
C'mon, I keep getting the same cards
I hate this, I really hate this
I
Joker
Endo's continued whining
Seriously hate this!!
And it's rather a long song too
Yes
Please. Oh please.
Please please please please
Hui!
AAAAAAAHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!
Wrong!
This one,
It's alright if I get this one right? And take Endo's
Yes that's correct
C'mon please! I was almost there!
C'mon!
TUBE - Season in the sun
SERIOUSLY?!
Matsumoto
has won!
I could win here too right?
Cards remaining
Yeah if you get this one
Yeah, you could
Here I go!
Joker
I hate this!
Please!
C'mon-AHHHHHH!!!!!
Now it's become a 1v1 battle between Hosei and Endo
Yeah, you could win this
Cause Yama-chan could make another unlucky draw
Yes, Yes
Joker
Match point
It depends now if it'll come back to him
For real,
Don't laugh or anything
Take it seriously, or you have to start again
What the hell?
Are you two Don Frye and Takayama?
AAAAAHHHHHHH!!!!!!!
Oh dear!
What the hell?
YES! YES YES YES!
I'm still in this
It was a 50% chance too
Amazing though.
Oh please!
Can we look at it?
Yes, we should be able to
It should be fine for us
That one...
This one would suck to do
Alright
This one sucks
C'mon decide
NOOOOOO!!!
For real?
This is amazing
Will I be able to sing this? My voice is gone.
Just how will this battle turn out?!
Yes
Yeah good job, this banter is funny
Joker
I won't look, and just use my hands to sense it
What do you mean?
That's what you've been doing this whole time
Alright
Matsuzaki Shigeru
Pair
Hosei
has won!
It's been decided
The Jiji was Sawada Kenji-san's Stripper
How did this one go again?
It's Stripper
A capella soulful rendition of Stripper
Singer
No no, he's gone back to the start
That was unneccessary
He was messing around in the start
Yeah, the start you were too playful
Like an imitation, you shouldn't do that
I did think it was an impression
No no, that was from my heart, a proper rendition
Right from the start?
Was that song always that long
Even Julie wouldn't have sung like that for The Best 10
Next, the 2nd round
2nd Round: Creative Nursery Rhyme
The theme, a creative nursery rhyme
Ah, that's what it is huh...
The cards have the title of a nursery rhyme. If you lose, please come up with a nursery rhyme based on the title.
And the joker this time; "The Oinari General"
TN: Inari is sushi rice stuffed inside fried tofu
This is fine right?
Ah, I have one
The Napping Hermit
The Napping Hermit, got rid of that
Pair
The Napping Hermit
Here I go
Jiji Nuki - Start
I don't have anything
Joker
Somehow, yes!
I got the Lying Tanuki
Lying Tanuki
Pair
Well, there are a lot of cards
Can you not see?
This one?
Tanaka is doing pretty good...
That's true
Wow
Ah, I have one
Pair
The Chorus of the Toys
"The Chorus of the Toys"
Well, there's no point wasting time here
Yeah, just draw the card and look at it
Just have to hope you get a pair
Alright, this one?
First time seeing this!
Yeah...What should I do?
If I get a pair that would be amazing
Yeah
Well, I guess not
The Old Man of the North Wind
We already saw him sing Stripper
Endo, who lost last round...
I got one, I got it I got it
After getting a pair...
He remains on a streak!
Pair
The Old Man of the North Wind
I got it, alright
Pair
The Kappa's Pajamas
Endo is on fire and gets 3 pairs in a row!
Guppy Sui Sui
Pair
Last one!
Joker
Are you done?
Wow
Yes, I'm done!
Tanaka background
YES!
Endo
has won!
And the next one to win after Endo?
Joker
Alright!
Pair
The Ant's Inner Monologue
There it is!
"The Ant's Inner Monologue"
He's so good!
Hamada
has won!
Seriously?
Cards remaining
I would hate this too
Yama-chan, take his card
I did it!
Well that's it,
Joker
He has to take his card
All that matters is if this is a pair
Yeah, theres' no helping it
It's a matter of chance now
If I get a pair, I'm done right?
Yes! Exactly
The probability is pretty good here
Yes, it is
No, no, hold on
No, no, no hold on
Yes, I'm done now
Alright
Tanaka
has won!
So if I get a pair, I win
Cards remaining
Yes
IF you get a pair
Please!
He didn't get a pair!
I thought I was screwed!
Chance! You've got a chance!
I thought you got a pair!!
Can you stop yelling like "BIYAA" please
You needed to get a pair then!
This just got dangerous
Cause 2 out of the 3 cards will make a pair
Yes
If I get this, then I'm done
You're done
ALRIGHHHTTTT!!!!!
You can do this
Please, please for real
This is it
I have almost a 70% chance of winning
Yes yes yes
It depends on your luck
Please, please get the joker!
When you're not sure ...
TAKE THE MIDDLE!!
NOPE!!
YES! YES! YES! YES!
YES!
This is unpredictable!
We don't know how this will turn out
That's some luck you have there!
It was like that before too, just like now
Yama-chan,
You have to make him take the punishment at least once
(Everyone) Yes that's true
MATSUMOTO IN TROUBLE!!
It's almost a 70% chance
He's never gotten the punishment before
Joker
I'm calm
I don't care
I am free of greed
Either card is fine with me
C'mon, c'mon
It's fine if I lose ... It's fine if I lose
He's being very gentle
Yes, yes you're alright
Please! Please! Please!
Just keep being gentle
This sucks
He's going to check like that again
YEEEEESSSSS!!!!
Pair
The Horse at Dawn
Hosei
has won!
What?! Which one is it
It's either one, either nursery rhyme
WHICH ONE?!
I hate this!
Sing one of those 2
It's between those 2
You have to start immediately
Here it comes!
Here it is
This one!
Ok!!
Please!
Matsumoto's Improvised Nursery Ryme
I thought it was scary so I headed there,
The General came over from the other side
*Paku Paku* - It was so tasty!
That was the fucking worst huh?
That was the worst
I didn't even mention the word Oinari
You didn't say Oinari once!
That was not it, that was not it!
That was not it!
My brain is gonna melt
You were moving your back so much! Like this
Your back, just bending and bending
It's so hot
Moving his whole body
The final round, the Batsu game!
Third round: Batsu game
This time, please enjoy while trying to guess the Joker card
Jiji Nuki - Start
Right away the game starts!
Joker
They definitely can't do this one
I think this is a good one to get rid of
"Ceiling Suspension"?
Why would they do this?
Ceiling Suspension Consolidation
Pair
It's too much
Allow me to choose...
EH!?
I just went
If you even touched it slightly,
If you even touched it slightly, you're out
But I didn't, I didn't touch it
Ok
He said "Allow me to choose"
Nothing...
This interesting looking one
You have 5 now
Not that many
Ahh, where did it go. There it is
You have one?
Face Balloon Box
Pair
That was a risky one
The game seemed to be progressing smoothly...
Shin Ruler
First time seeing this, this one is scary too
Joker
This one
That's not it..
Hmm?
Pairs become rare
Surely by now we'll get one
From those cards?
From those cards. Hmm?
This is messed up
A right jab to the face
That does sound messed
Messed up?
They can't do this one!!
Yeah that one...
AHHH! Please let this work out!
Again...
A right jab to the face
What the hell? There are cards like this?
Joker
This is messed up!!
I'm not getting any at all...
I have like 6 of them
Endo you should get one by now
If we can't end this in the next minute Endo is the loser
No no no no no
We definitely won't end in the next minute
You don't have a pair huh? Even with that many cards
I don't
No matches at all...
The game continued like that,
8 minutes passed by
For 8 minutes
I think this area will work out
You said that last time too...
Nipple sucking old man
Overhead nipple throw
Smelly Face Shield
Why are there so many nipple ones?!
There's so many nipple ones
They're definitley suggesting soemthing
Yes exactly
Trying to make us mess up,
Trying to make us mess up, you can see the staff's evilness
You guys can't do that
Let's go with this one
Nope. Here you go
Ah, I think I got one
Joker
Nothing?
Are you playing Mahjong?
I thought I had one!
I just thought I had one
You made us nervous
Do I have one?
Nipple Overhead Throw
Nipple Sucking Old Man
Portable Shrine Bondage
Right Jab to the face
Yeah cause, there really are so many nipple ones
Nipple and nipple ...
Joker
This is a pair right?
He's playing Mahjong
Hmm? Hold on...
He's trying to trick us again
No no, it's just...
what the ????
I just can't believe it, I keep getting the same cards\
Niplle Sucking Old Man
Nipple Overhead Throw
You have so many too, I guess this one
It's nipple & nipple again!
Nipple Sucking Old Man
And it's the wrong nipple one that I pick
Tanaka's got all of them, they aren't circulating past him
It's become stagnant
I keep seeing the same nipple ones
It came back...
Right Jab to the face
Spout hot water on head
They just come back right away
Joker
The same cards
This might be a record
That's true
It came back!!
Right jab to the face
This one!
That one too,
Everything I took from Yamasaki,
You have all of them right?
Oh really?
So like the same goddamn cards keep coming back
Joker
15 minutes since the start
Surely now
Yes, I got one
"Continiously dropping..."
Continously dropping chestnut burrs on stomach
Pair
I've never seen that before!
The game finally gets moving
Joker
Ah I got one! Finally I got one
Instant nose hair removal
Pair
Joker
And once again, Hosei...
Which means I'm done yes
Electric Massage
Pair
YES!
OKAY!
Hosei
has won!
And riding on Hosei's wave
I got it!
Nipple Overhead Throw
Pair
Tanaka
has won!
Johnson!
And then Matsumoto too
Johnson!!!!
Seriously?
Spout Hot Water on Head is gone!
It's been eliminated. Just this.
Pair
batsu game
Matsumoto
has won!
If I get this I'm done yeah?
There is a chance
Cards remaining
This is a pretty terrible one too
It's pretty bad
Konbu Slap
Joker
Really?
If this is the joker then it would be pretty bad
Hamada-san could win
Nipple Sucking Old Man
Right Jab to the face
Konbu Binta
Nipple Sucking Old Man
Right Jab to the face
Joker
This has taken a turn
ENDO GETS A CHANCE!
I could end this
You have a chance here
Who gets the batsu, Endo or Hamada?
You gotta take this seriously
The probability is very high
Cards remaining
This is just...
Matsumoto talking over Endo
Endo you gotta take this seriously
Joker
It's nearly 70%
Yes
You're still riding that wave from Stripper
I am
Singing Stripper
Singing Stripper made my head spin
Please, c'mon
YES!!!
Pair
Right jab to the face
Endo
has won!
The "Right Jab to the Face" is gone!
Exactly!
Show us please
"Old man"?
This, this, and this
It's the "Konbu slap"!
BATSU GAME
What does it mean?
What is a "Konbu slap"?
Put the goggles on please
They keep making us do terrifying stuff!
It sounds pretty daunting
Maybe it's a bunny girl
Hold on!
This is bad!!
The diver is here
The konbu is wet
Sit down, sit down
Umm,
Please, don't resist
If you try to resist you'll get hurt!!
If I try to resist?
What're you gonna do?
Konbu slap
Eh, you're joking?
Place your hands behind you
Get ready
Ouch!
Hamad-san?!
That was bad, that was bad!!
Hamada-san are you OK?
Ow!
It really hurts your ears
Thank god it wasn't me!
Thank god!
Ugly!
UGLY!!!
UGLY!!!!