First time on Gaki No Tsukai Arahende:
Einstein Inada Shichi Henge!!
Ina-chan is finally here.
I don't know why he hasn't done this already.
I heard something shocking happened before we started recording.
Well, your partner there did something to Ina-chan.
What did he do?
Kicked the shit out of him!
That's because Ina-chan did something bad, right?
Yeah, that's right.
No, he was just standing there.
1 minute before recording.
An entertainer's skills tested in a Shichi Henge.
Nervousness seeps out of Inada before the show starts.
Hamada lingers near Inada.
Owww!!
You were giving off an evil vibe.
Please forgive my partner!
It's a sickness.
Oh its a sickness.
Well, let's welcome our guests for today, Einstein!
Einstein
Inada Naoki
Kawai Yuzuru
So, how are you feeling about doing this?
I was a little nervous, I couldn't even sleep last night.
Everyone gets a little nervous.
Now I am finding it enjoyable.
I've overcome it.
Due to the violence earlier.
Kicked in the ass when I wasn't even doing anything.
That mystery will be never be solved.
You're the 55th person to try, where are you aiming for?
Obviously I want to aim for 1st place!
Yuzuru, how do you think he will do now that he's finally here?
He's been nervous about this for a while.
I have no idea what that color is on his face today.
It looks like the back of a peach.
Typset, Timed & Translated by
Baumkuchen
Quality Check and Support by
GakiDave
*This is a fan sub for fans,
do enjoy! :)
Project Meeting
- Don't lose momentum! Kokoriko vs EXIT Lactic acid out exertion battle!!
- Endo Family vs Hokuto Family Costco Cooking Binge Eating Battle!!
- Experimental planning! Let's break the right clavicle of License Fujiwara!!
- Looking for a successor to Yoshinobu's hot bare-handed eating!!
- Masatoshi Hamada mimics youngsters in Dramas Judgment
- Matsumoto blond hair graduation! Next is afro!
- Our Tanaka gives ZIP a revengeful hammer blow!!
- Producer Otomo 24-hour boxing!!
- Street survey challenge! 1 million yen to thosewho read "Imoto" as "Inomoto"!
- Tsukitei Housei & Tsukitei Ryusei vs Moriman Intense Revenge Tag Match!!
Gaki No Tsukai Project Meeting
There are many projects. What should we do?
Who is this?
Tsukitei Housei      &      Tsukitei Ryusei
He's my student.
T/N: Housei is now is a mentor/teacher/master in Rakugo.
Really!?
I've taken a student under my wing.
Wow, really!?
Ina-chan, don't go yet.
Didn't expect this to happen.
It's fine, just go.
That was some time to leave.
Shichi Henge Start
Now you're a master.
Yes.
T/N: Inada is doing one of his famous gags.
He's so annoying.
Don't do that.
He's laughing so much.
Using his face as a specialty.
That was just accidental.
T/N: Kabuto Agency provides for vision/hearing
impaired materials and support for cultural arts.
Source @ NTV Holdings
The money collected from this episode will be donated to the Nippon Television Kobato Cultural Agency.
I thought he was going to pull it off easily wearing that mask.
He was putting it on then it snapped.
The snap hit his chin, he went "Eh―"
Well you have an apprentice so let's make this Moriman battle happen, 2vs2.
Actually, I'm really good at impersonations
and I have a repertoire full of them.
I want to demonstrate it.
I have so many of them,
I am not sure which ones I should do.
I made an Impersonation Roulette.
When I say "Pi pi pi...", you can stop my roll anytime.
I'll think of an impersonation on the spot
and demonstrate my repertoire.
Let's do this together. Hamada, please say stop anytime.
Stop!
Wait, Hamada...
You told me to say stop,
it was too fast for you wasn't it.
Please go to sleep.
Housei, please stay stop at your liking.
Stop!
It's Ashida Mana!
T/N: Inada impersonates a famous
young tarento's voice, Ashida Mana.
It's...Ashida Mana.
I still have more. Endo, please say stop.
Stop.
It's Ashida Mana.
I am...Ashida.
Is everyone...Ashida?
Matsumoto, your turn. Ashida is coming up a lot.
I have others as well. Please try to roll for others.
Stop
Do you go by Totoro?
T/N: Ashida Mana calls Guillermo del Toro "Totoro"
during the movie Pacific Rim's debut.
Source: excite.co.jp
Do you...go by Totoro?
What's your name?
It's Hamada.
You go by Totoro, right?
I still have more. Last one, Fujiwara, if you will.
Stop!
You go by Totoro, right?
YOU GO BY TOTORO, RIGHT?
I'm not doing well. I still have more though.
Everyone's roll is so bad.
I laughed at Hamada earlier.
Why were you acting like a comedy duo?
Don't think you can do that.
Feels like you're conspiring together.
This should be fine, I don't have to pay, right?
I'm a Busu-Meter.
I can measure a human's hideousness.
When someone says "Busu" to me,
I say "Busu" back to them
proportionally to how ugly they are.
Matsumoto, please say "Busu" to me.
Busu.
Busu!
Housei, please say "Busu."
Busu.
Busu!!
Endo, please say "Busu."
Busu.
Hamada, please say "Busu."
BUSU!
BUSU! BUSU!
BUSU! BUSU! BUSU!
It's broken!
B U S U !
Damn, I know it already.
This guy's so annoying.
B U S U !
He's making a real scary face.
He's scowling so hard,
BUSU!
He's still saying it.
B U S U !
I know already, damn.
He hurt our feelings too.
With roughly the same extent of measure.
Because its proportional.
He's racking it up
NEXT: A comedian of Downtown's generation arrives?
My ex has been bugging me to get back with her.
I'm in a pickle.
What should I do?
It's her again.
Highheel Ringo
T/N: Highheel Ringo is a female comedian
in the same generation as Downtown.
Hello.
Hello!
You at work right now?
That's dirty.
What's up?
My husband ain't cutting it for me in bed.
It's on speaker.
He's a good person, right?
Yeah, he is.
Every time I meet Ina-chan on other shows
I would remember the times we went out together.
That's in the past, isn't it?
I know that too, but every time we meet
I end up remembering all the fun and interesting things we did together.
Would you tell me honestly
why you broke up with me?
What happened to us?
Just talk it over Line privately.
I didn't really hear it from you
so I can't really get over it.
That's some heavy Osaka dialect
You're really cornering me though
I used to.
But now I won't do it anymore.
It's not just that.
You still haven't paid back money that I lent you.
I'll return it.
I will pay it back, unlike Downtown.
You can hear pages shuffling.
Yeah, you can hear it.
Please tell us how many pages are left.
I didn't get to say this but...
...I don't like that you're Downtown's classmate.
Why though?
I don't even know their Line info even if I'm their classmate.
But they've seen you nude before.
That's because Downtown are peeping toms.
Peeping from the mailbox.
It's a famous story of theirs.
Watching me as I came out of the bath...
Saying that its like a stag beetle
stuck on my nether region.
There's no stag beetle down there!
Its a butterfly,
you've seen it before, Ina-chan?
That was all because Ma-chan likes me.
Forgive me, but it's over between us.
Sorry, I am going to hang up now.
Newspaper?
The size of a newspaper?
It's large and it sounded like it was raining for a bit.
That's some intense tearing sound.
That's a crazy amount!
He might go all the way.
NEXT: Rapid penalities with a face gag
He's getting me every time.
Will I make it?
Shit, there's no time.
Will I make it in time?
I made it!! Yaaay!
I thought I definitely wasn't going to make it.
I've made it before too now that I think about it.
What exactly did he make it in time for?
He was saying he won't make it in time.
He said he's made it before.
Why would he say he won't make it if he's made it in before?
Bicycle Chinman
A story about Chinman's dream.
I'm Bicycle Chinman.
My dream is for lots of people to ride me.
But no one wants to ride me.
Chinman's dream is for someone
to sit and ride the bicycle.
Matsumoto, come get on.
Come giddy up and get on.
No one else will.
Then, excuse me...
Go ahead.
He's a freaking idiot!!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Thank you.
Hamada, too.
That's the same thing.
Come giddy up.
He's sweating a lot.
Yeah he is.
This is quite the shift in gears.
He's gonna die!
Thank you, everyone!
Now you say that.
That hurt...
Chinman brought this onto himself.
Oh yeah, next is last one.
NEXT: Body stretching do-or-die transformation
That's quite a lot in there.
Sensei, let's do a small face remedy, please.
Alright, lay down here.
Excuse me.
Please, if you will.
Alright, let's begin.
Safety is taken into consideration by an expert. Actual treatment is different.
Don't make that face.
You just can't do that!
Your legs are straight up in the air!
It's impossible with that chin!
I feel like my face is becoming smaller.
Alright, I'll finish up now.
How is she going to finish this?
That's more than enough
You told her to do this, have her stop it!
All done.
Thank you.
No way, she punched that chin.
That's freakin' too much!
It's smaller!
No way it is, idiot!
Your chin is swelling up!
What the hell is with this guy?!
Ah, I'm glad.
That's considerable, isn't it?
I went out in all of them.
He probably got 2nd or 3rd.
57,000 Yen
He got 2nd??
That's 3rd place!
After Koumoto and Naomi.
T/N: Koumoto (Episode #753) and Naomi (Episode #1359)
You're here now.
Really, 3rd place?!
3rd Place
57,000 Yen
Earned Amount
I would like you all to meet someone
who helped me today.
It's that person, isn't it?
Ina-chan, I'm here!  <3
HighHeel
Ringo
I came from the 9am bullet train!
We heard all the pages shuffling!!
I wasn't reading at all!
Next week: 100 Yen Items Costume Clip Show.
Previous scenes can be viewed!
Past episodes can be streamed exclusively on Hulu(JP)!