Downtown no
Gaki no Tsukai
Ya Arahende
Typesetting: u/This_guys_a_twat; Translation: u/classicalover
Tonight's Gaki no Tsukai:
The highly-rated Gaki Jiji-Nuki!
The cards being used will have various different original subjects on them
Like the game Old Maid, match the cards to deplete your hand
Whoever is left with the one unmatchable card must follow its orders
I'M NOT GETTING PUNISHED EVEN ONCE TODAY OKAY?
Alright, let's do it
The theme is All-Out A Cappella Performance
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
A famous song title is written on each card
Enthusiastically perform a famous song a cappella
The last person remaining must sing that song
First Round: All-Out A Capella
Here are the cards this round. Try to guess the "Old Man!"
Hosei draws from the player to the right and turns go clockwise
"Old Man" starts
Joker
Oh, I got one, so suddenly
B.B. Queen's "Odoru Ponpokorin"
"Odoru Ponpokorin" by B.B. Queens
Pair
B.B. Queens, huh?
Matsumoto-san takes a card, correct?
Yes, that's right, in this...
order...
I don't think that's right...
Staff
Eh!?
Endo-san takes a card right?
Staff
Just now Hosei-san took a card right?
Next
Endo takes
a card from Hosei...
Right, you messed up the turn direction
That happens
It's Tanaka's fault! If it's anybody's
This was all on Tanaka!
I even asked earlier whether this was okay
My position changed so
now I have no idea what's going on
Your position changed...
So Endo draws from my hand, correct?
Yes, that's correct, the game goes clockwise
Okay
Why does it look like you have an advantage
Joker
Yes, it's like that
Because he's the dealer?
Correct
You didn't match right? So now I draw
Gimme!
I got a pair!
J-WALK's "Nanimo Ienakute... Natsu"
"Nanimo Ienakute... Natsu" by J-WALK
Pair
This one is hard so good thing it matched
Ah, I got a match
"Daitokai" by Crystal King
Pair
Crystal King
That one's an enthusiastic song
That one really uses your voice
I want to get a match soon
Yes I do
Card text: "Yosaku" by Saburou Kitashima
This drawing is kinda funny
Cards Remaining
He came back
15 minutes after starting,
Joker
Saburou Kitashima's card circulates endlessly
He came back
Yes yes yes
Ah!
The cards all have a yellow background don't they
It's a new one...
Yama-chan, what are ya gonna draw...
You really wanna match soon right
Why are you holding the cards so strongly?
Ah, I've seen this one before
Alright, going with this one
What? It's my first time seeing this one
Linda Yamamoto takes Saburou Kitashima's place in the infinite loop
Gimme something good already
Please take it
She came back!
"Nerai Uchi" by Linda Yamamoto
Matsumoto's card is Linda Yamamoto
Oh come on, do I really have to...
OHHHH YESSSS!!
I'm soooo glad
"Nerai Uchi" by Linda Yamamoto
Linda Yamamoto's "Nerai Uchi"
Pair
Matsumoto
has won!
Staff
Yama-chan's card gets drawn
YATTA!
Yama-chan you've won too
It's up to whether your card matches one of mine right?
Hosei
has won!
Damn, why didn't it pair
No no no no
Cards Remaining
It's been a while since it felt like this
All-out a cappella performance...
GIMME!
YESSSSSS!!!
"Banzai~ Suki de Yokatta" by Ulfuls
Pair
Ulful's "Suki de Yokatta"
Tanaka
has won!
So it's one of these, hol' up
What do I do?
Hamada-san draws...
Yes, yes
I draw right?
If it matches Hamada's card...
It all depends on this draw
If Hamada pairs Endo loses
Damn hold up
Please I'm counting on you
This is an important draw
For sure huh
Wait please please please please please please please please
Hold them for me
I see. Oh, I didn't know this card existed
PLEEEASE!
The card has been delivered
I'm gonna do it, here I go
JACKPOT!!!!!
Hamada
has won!
"Champion" by Alice
Pair
When Downtown does that as a pair
of course they win
Nuh uh
Come on... wait what's the song?
"Ora Tokyo sa Iguda" by Ikuzou Yoshi
Here it is
Endo-san, it's by Ikuzou Yoshi
"Ora Tokyo sa Iguda" by Ikuzou Yoshi
All-Out A Cappella
Go all-out okay? Do it seriously
There ain't no TVs! Ain't no radios!
The cars ain't even goin' that fast!
No pianos! No bars!
The cops come round 'n round everyday
Wake up in the morn', take the cows out
For a lil' two hour walk
There ain't no phones! Ain't no gas
Bus only comes here once a day
I've had enough of this village
So I'm goooooooooin' down to Tokyo
And when I get down to Tokyo
With all my saviiiiiiin's
I'll be rearing a cow thereeeeee
NYAAAH~!
It's gotta be Shozo doing this kind of thing
It was good that Endo-san sang it
I could never do this
HUWAAAAH!
That HUWAAAAAAH at the end
This round's theme is
*TN: famous sports commentator
In the style of Ichirou Furutachi*,
Improvised Commentary
improvised live commentary of an ordinary object
What the hell?
An everyday object is written on each card
Perform a live commentary on a commonplace object
There's no way I can do that
The item will appear in front of the loser,
who must do a live commentary about that object
Even Furutachi-san wouldn't do that
Improvised Commentary
One of these cards will have live commentary!
Guess which one will be the "Old Maid."
I wanna avoid this one
Dealer Endo begins the game by drawing
"Old Man" starts
Endo-san
please draw a card from me
I see...
Joker
No matches right? Right?
Hold up...
Staff
You're going the wrong way
Eh...
no way!?
Eh?
Who?
Who? What happened? Who?
Dude it's your fault
Endo-san draws from Hosei-san
Staff
Earlier Tanaka clearly said
draw from me
Actually,
you shoulda drawn from Hosei right
Who?
Hold up
Endo
Wait, hold up a sec
WTF are you saying?
This was a bad mistake huh?
What do you mean?
He shouldn't have drawn from you
How about you sing "Yosaku"...
Wait please, wha-, really,
did I really f*ck up that hard?
Well of course, and it's the second time today
Excuse me, I apologize
"Yosaku" by Kitashima Saburou
All-Out A Cappella
Yosaku cuts the tree~
So quiet
Hey hey ho, hey hey ho~
And it echoes back~
His wife...
Forget it
Gotta be all-out
It was all the same
I feel sick now
"Old Man" starts
Endo's card is returned, and the game restarts
Joker
I got a pair!
Really?
Isn't that too fast
Pair
Spatula
Now I shall draw a card
Your pupils are wide open
Is, is this right?
So scary
It should be right...
Drawing from the right, here I go
Got a match
Compass
Pair
Please take it
Joker
After that, the game goes smoothly
I got one
Pair
Roller skates
Yes, here's folding fan.
Folding Fan
Pair
The number of cards quickly decreases
Daruma
Pair
That one ticks me off
Joker
The next time you laugh
it's punishment time
Please stop holding them so tightly
Or else I'll get punished
Joker
Du-duuuuuun
So simple minded
You laughed amirite?
No I didn't
Hosei you're laughing
You are tho
I didn't laugh
I'm normally like this
He told me not to hold them so strongly, so I didn't,
but he laughed anyway
No way you were holding them so tightly
He makes this face
Cards Remaining
Endo to draw
Endo, with one card, draws for the win
I wonder if the match is in there
Joker
I'll take this one
No way
Really?
Bike pump
Pair
Endo
has won!
That's awesome
Damn
Joker
The game suddenly quickly advances
Ooh, here's one!
Cactus
Pair
He got the right card...
Yessss
Geta
Pair
Wow
He won
Hosei
has won!
I'm so glad
Hosei-san has won
If Tanaka matches...
If I... yes...
Yeah, he'll win
It'll be a battle between Downtown.
Damn, no pair
It's all from here
Tanaka please c'mon
Wouldn't it be nice to be a spectator
I want to win too you know
Joker
Gimme somethin'
Yesss a match
Pair
Teapot
Teapot, huh...
Tanaka draws to win
Joker
No good?
Yessss
Yes, another chance for me
This is a big chance
Hamada draws to win
Right?
I'm counting on you!
GIMME!
Joker
YESSSSSSSS!!
Wow awesome
Hamada
has won!
Alarm clock?
Alarm clock
Pair
He won
Wait, if this is a match...
If this matches yours...
Matsumoto draws to win
I don't have a choice of card
If Hamada's leftovercard matches one of Matsumoto's, Tanaka loses!
Who will perform the live commentary?
Will it be Matsumoto or Tanaka?
Wait, wait, I'm gonna cover the card up
Joker
It's gotta match for sure now
Like this, like this
Stop, stop, stop...
*dead frog noises*
That's good, isn't that good?
ISN'T THAT GOOD?
STOP! PLEASE STOP!
NYAAAAAAAAAH!
IT'S STOPWATCH!
Pair
Stopwatch
Matsumoto
has won!
Which means...
The question is what the object is
This card is...
Pair
Sunglasses
I matched sunglasses, so
Here you go, it's this
The punishment theme is "purse"
Purse
Ichirou Furutachi-style live commentary!!
Loser Tanaka gets the punishment!
3... 2... 1...
Purse
Please begin
Oooh, what's this in front of me?
What, what, what is this?
Appeared in front of me, it has indeed
This has appeared
This is, oh, the feel in the hand is
brown feeling of something
Here it opens wide, spread wide open, what is this
In-, inside there's also an open,
Inside there's also an open, it's got two levels
This is so-called, yes,
so-called, is this really what they call a PURSE!?
It's wide open, spread wide open, wide wide open
What the hell?!
This is, what color is this?
Oh my, it's a gold colored case
Eh, large bills can fit in here
*TN: b. 1948, Muranishi TÅru is an adult video (AV) director,
It's Director Muranishi
aka "Emperor of Porn"
*TN: 2019 Muranishi comedy-drama series
It's "The Naked Director*!"
Always saying it's wide open, spread wide open...
Somehow it became perverted too
Spread wide open huh
Someone quiet in the background, Hamada maybe?
You get super flustered from this
It's karma because you messed up earlier
"Oooh! What is this?"
"It's open wide,
spread wide open"
"Inside there's an open"
EMBARASSING!!
You get flustered and panicked doing this
I'm so glad I didn't do this
In the end you got two punishments
Tanaka you're all over the place today
No kidding
I'm really sorry
What's the last one?
I'll spin the roulette
Deciding the dealer by roulette
It's gotta be Endo
I do it a lot huh
Is it Endo?
Similar to last time,
it's a punishment, but
also like last time,
it will be an "air" punishment.
Acting out the punishment through charades
Hosei-san you did this ridiculous batsu right
Last time's batsu, powerful electric shock machine
Hosei had the batsu last time
Right now it's level 2
Oh sh*t here it comes
Okay level 3
What the f*ck is this!?
Going from 3 to 5
3 to 5!
Don't increase it so quickly!
I wonder why it's like that
The hellish "Air Batsu Game!"
Who will get it this time?
That's gotta be tough
It's really bad
This time is also the air punishment game
The punishment card has already been drawn
Aren't I supposed to deal the cards?
Hmm?
Ooooooooooh!
This is crazy
Please nooooooo
Endo you're the dealer right?
I'm sorry nooooooo
Wanna wear that thing again?
No more nooooooo
How about the teapot?
Let's do the teapot
Teapot!?
Teapot
Ichirou Furutachi-style live commentary!!
Tanaka messes up the order,
and receives the punishment!
3... 2... 1... Go!
Teapot
Oooh, what, what is this
What has appeared in front of me
Is this what they call a teapot
What a mysterious object
There's the handle part,
and this part which opens wide
Don't say that, "opens wide!"
"Is this what they call a teapot?"
No sh*t!
Final Round
The final round with the "air" batsu at stake!
These air batsu, aren't you good at them
Joker
No way
I never act my punishments
Please
"Party Poppers in the Mouth"
Pair
It's charades so you can do it all you want
Oh, I have another one
"Stag Beetle Nose Piercing"
Pair
Stag Beetle Nose Piercing
There are lots of bad ones
Woah, this one's terrible
Alright, so dealer Endo...
Please...
proceed...
Tell him what he's gotta do
Ooooh?
This right? Open wide
Draw from Hosei-san on your right
"Old Man" starts
Already only two cards?
Yama-chan, only one card left...
Joker
I hope I get a match-
Yesssssss, yess yessss
Wow nice
150 kph Spiked Chestnut Shot
Pair
So fast
"150 kph Spiked Chestnut Shot"
If you don't do the batsu
there's no way you can get a good reaction
Two of you only have one card?
Well, but yeah
A pairrrrr
"Hot Fried Tofu Bazooka"
Hot Fried Tofu Bazooka
Pair
You, gimme somethin'
Oh, I got a match
Pair
Ramen Noodle Water Shower
"Ramen Noodle Water Shower"
There's no actual punishment so
they're really writing whatever the f*ck they want
These ideas are interesting though
Joker
The first to win is...
A pair
"Golden Spray to the Face"
Pair
Endo
has won!
WTF? It's gotta be a record speed
Probably the fastest heh
Which means... yesssss
Cards Remaining
Yama-chan wins too
Yesss yes yes yes yes yes yes
Joker
The f*ck is this
It's Tanaka Day today
No no no, no way, the viewers won't want it either
Please
Yes yes yes, I got one
Staff
Wrong! you're doing it wrong!
EH!?
Hamada takes a card from Tanaka
Staff
Oh me?
And then we continue
It was Tanaka's mistake
Staff
He just said it
He just said it so clearly now
What the f*ck man
No no , please, really
I'll quit being moderator
Really, I'm reflecting on my mistakes
We'll be in trouble if you do though
Please, one more chance
I've got this drilled in my head now
There's no next time alright
But wait
I didn't notice my mistake so
this might repeat many times over
It's scary
That's true
If I can get a hang of it,
I can repent my mistakes
If you can get a hang of it
True
Today really is Tanaka Day huh
Hamada draws to win
Tanaka gimme GIMME
Damn, first time seeing this
Joker
I think it's fine if Tanaka gets it
No not happening, someone else
Ah, I got one
"Turtle Shell Bondage Swing"
Pair
Turtle Shell Bondage Swing
How the hell do you act that out
Turtle shell bondage...
The bondage part has nothing to do with it
Can't act that part out
Alright, I'm gonna finish this
Cards Remaining
Matsumoto draws to win
Then...
I wanna win
Joker
It's "Wasabi Soy Sauce Eyedrops"
Pair
Wasabi Soy Sauce Eyedrops
Huh he got a pair...
So?
No no, ask Tanaka what to do next
What should he do?
If he doesn't get this...
The cards are always
drawn from the person to the right
Right, right
The cards are alw-
So tell him what's he supposed to do
Matsumoto-san just...
matched the cards titled
"Wasabi Soy Sauce Eyedrops"
Don't just regurgitate facts
Yeah, tell us what to do next
Everyone knows what you just said
Matsumoto just got a pair, so...
now...
Yama-chan draws right?
Yes, ri-, yes
I draw from Matsumoto-san,
Matsumoto-san wins
Matsumoto
has won!
Yama-chan if this matches...
Yeah, then I win
No match
Cards Remaining
It's all down to this
It was so fast
It's been narrowed down to us
Narrowed down to the last three!
Who will get the air batsu?
It's gotta be this one
Joker
Yess got a pair
I got a pair
Wait hold up
"Tickle Hell"
Pair
Tickle Hell
I also hate this one
It was suck to do a charade of this
Damn, down to this one card?
Hamada draws to win
It's all down to this
No wait, I have two cards
Oh really?
Joker
OOOOOOH!
What was that now
Ooooh?
Did you see that now
Away from the camera
he kicked my left foot
Hurry up and gimme
Just one card
It's down to this
What's going on
"Billiards Ball Enema"
Hamada
has won!
Billiards Ball Enema
Pair
Hosei draws to win
Hamada-san you won right
So if this card matches one of Hosei-san's,
If this matches with mine
then you win too
Who will get the air batsu!? Hosei, or Tanaka!?
Joker
It's worth seeing either of them do the batsu
No no no please no I'm good
Okay
Please...PLEASE...
STOP!!!!!
Looking good
All-out
Can you even see?
Can you even read the card
*TN: variety comedy show
That face was on Shouten*
Yama-chan you can do it
Pair
Super Boiled Water Bath
Hosei
has won!
It's gotta be that way
It was decided for him
Tanaka today is just like that
I don't want this really
So what is it Tanaka-san?
"Giant Metal Tub Drop"
"Giant Metal Tub Drop" it is
Air Batsu "Giant Metal Tub Drop"
Loser Tanaka gets the air punishment game!
This is really scary Tanaka
It seems to be huge
It's huge?
Gigantic
Alright are we ready?
Have you never seen one this big?
It's about the same size as the studio
No I can't do this
Alright, Tanaka-san
"Giant Metal Tub Drop"
please proceed!
This looks so painful
It's what he does all the time
The usual
The usual faking
And it's so long
And he's trying really hard to improve his act
We're always seeing this
Sure enough we got it on film
Thank you very much