Translation: TeaVilla, Nexusangel, Mickstar813 ~ Typesetting: HouseiGIFs
100 Questions
Matsumoto Hitoshi's
Matsumoto Hitoshi, who is respected
by many comedians, the truth about him...
I have a lot but I wonder...
Q: What does
Matsumoto have a complex about?
Just say the most obvious one
My educational background?
A: Educational
Background
You're kidding!
The man described as a genius' mind is something else...
Surely your chin...
Jokes wise...
Q: Who's Matsumoto's
favourite young comedian(s)?
Jaru Jaru.
A: Jaru Jaru
Oh shit! He did say that...
Q: What's Matsumoto's
favourite fruit?
Got to be peach.
Loads of questions which even the guys who
have worked with him for so long couldn't answer...
A: Peach
Yeah, um... Paper Moon.
Q: What is Matsumoto's
favourite movie?
Yeah, um... Paper Moon.
A: Paper Moon
Alright!!
The battle which decides who gets punished
comes to its conclusion tonight.
Ino Tadataka.
* First person to make an accurate map of Japan
Q: Who does
Matsumoto respect the most?
A: Ino Tadataka
Right, right.
The guy who made the first map...?
I can't understand people who don't respect him...
No, that kind of reply won't do...
Who will get punished?
The person who gets the least correct
answers gets punished, who will it be!?
Umm...
(bleeped)
Amazing!!
Every day...
(bleeped)
Question 53.
Matsumoto gets excited by what kind of costume?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q53: Matsumoto gets excited by what kind of costume?
Yama-chan?
I think it's changed since the old days...
I guess so...
Ages ago...
we had a conversation about this.
Really?
Reveal answers.
* OL = Office Lady
--------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------
Housei: Nurse    Hamada: Sailor Moon
Endo: OL    Tanaka: Normal OL
Nah...
When we spoke
he didn't like anything unnatural.
Right.
He likes normal.
Really?
I'm pretty sure he said that once before.
This will be a tough question to answer here...
Time for the answer.
He could say anything.
Matsumoto is in a different room to the other 4 and cannot hear them
What kind of costume are you excited by?
He definitely prefers normal girls.
Umm...
Like a nurse thing but like...
a caregiver nurse.
That's what I prefer, I mean,
what the hell man...?
He's laughing all by himself...
---------------------------------------------------------
A: Caregiver Nurse
Apparently that doesn't count.
Nurse doesn't count?
You were close.
Maybe it's the pants...?
Ah, that figures.
Probably the trousers.
Matsumoto would choose to be which SMAP member?
* A popular Japanese boy band (1988 - Present)
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q54: Matsumoto would choose to be which SMAP member?
Ah geez, this is such a difficult one...
Oh man...
I wonder...
What will he say?
Reveal answers.
Yeah, right?
----------------------------------------------
--------------------------------------------
Housei: Nakai    Hamada: Goro
Endo: Goro    Tanaka: Shingo
Goro-chan is a bit like "mysterious" right?
I think so too, I think Nakai is too like proper.
Maybe...
Yeah, exactly
Time for the answer.
Inagaki Goro.
There it is!
--------------------------
A: Inagaki Goro
That's a big point.
Ask him why...
Why did you choose Inagaki Goro?
Putting it honestly, by process of elimination,
like not this guy and not this guy...
I guess he would be the most likely.
Did they get it right?
He asked...?
I shouldn't have asked...
What is Matsumoto's favourite gag?
"Gag"?
---------------------------------------------------------------------
Q56: What is Matsumoto's favourite gag?
His favourite gag?
Reveal answers.
"Surprise Tamegoro" Hana Hajime character (1969~)
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Charlie Hama wordplay:
"Excuse me, please (kudasai) <> it stinks (kusai)"
Comedian Norio Nishikawa
Housei: Norio-chan Pon!   Hamada: Atto Odoroku Tamegoro
........Endo: Gomen Kusai    Tanaka: Yatteru Yatteru
Jimmy Onishi's
"Doing it, doing it" *shakes hand at crotch* (masturbation)
I'm the only one who chose
one of the really old ones...
That's such an old episode...
That's really old...
Time for the answer.
It depends on what era he decides on.
I might have chosen one that's too old...
But seriously, weirdly enough...
* A comical dance Endo does
I do like HO-HO-HOI...
At this stage... HO-HO-HOI...
---------------------------
A: HO-HO-HOI
It was HO-HO-HOI?
But I'm kind of happy...
You should do it.
Do it for real, go for it.
You love it too, right?
I do love it as well.
"Do it for real."
I would definitely do it now...
What did Matsumoto recently quarrel about with his wife?
Geez, come on...
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q57: What did Matsumoto recently quarrel about with his wife?
Oh man, I don't know.
Yama-chan, has he never told you?
He told me something last week.
Really!?
You have a huge advantage then.
Amazing... I have no idea.
Reveal answers.
----------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Didn't reply    Hamada: Way of speaking
Endo: About food    Tanaka: Long time on the phone
I have no idea.
It could be about the way he speaks to her...?
No, no, I don't think so.
Let's ask him then.
Time for the answer.
I told her to put in more water for the humidifier.
I told her to put in more water for the humidifier
I'm very noisy about the humidifier.
-------------------------------------------------------------
A: Didn't put water in the humidifier
What the...?
Does this sound like
something he may have told you?
No, first time I've heard it.
Oh right.
Must have happened this week.
What does Matsumoto like about Hamada?
Oh come on...
This is another...
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q60: What does Matsumoto like about Hamada?
Oh man, that's hard.
What kind of question is this? How do we answer it?
it's kind of embarrassing to say something
nice about your partner after all
This...
I don't know.
Reveal answers.
Well...
* Tsukkomi = Straight man retorts
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
--------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Good at Tsukkomi    Hamada: Good at conversing
Endo: Talented     Tanaka: No regrets
He said himself he wasn't good at conversing...
I get it.
So it's got to be that.
I see.
Time for the answer.
Matsumoto, what do you like about Hamada?
I wonder if it's something else.
If you spend too long thinking,
it's going to you know...
The fact he...
will die before me.
-------------------------------------------------
A: He'll die before Matsumoto
That's better for me.
I don't want to be left behind and
have to say some words at his funeral...
Whatever happens,
I don't want to have to go up to his body
and be like, "Hey, Matsumoto..."
Matsumoto is most engrossed by which folktale?
Q62: Matsumoto is most engrossed by which folktale?
Reveal answers.
----------------------------------------------------------------------
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Momotarou    Hamada: Hanasaka Ji-san
Endo: Momotarou    Tanaka: The monkey and the crab
Well, they're all very popular stories.
It should be one of them.
Come on...
Time for the answer.
Umm.. I think...
The Crab and the Monkey.
* A crab is killed by a sly monkey, later its offspring kill the monkey in revenge
Wow, you got it.
----------------------------------
A: The Crab and the Monkey
It was always going to be one or another.
Yeah, they're all famous after all.
Got it.
The time in his life that Matsumoto laughed most?
In his life...?
-----------------------------------------------------------------------
Q63: The time when Matsumoto laughed most?
In his whole life...?
I know...
Laugh? He laughs so much...
How about that thing
he was talking about recently...?
Reveal answers.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: When he first met Hamada    Hamada: Miss Hanaka on the radio
Endo: Middle school trip    Tanaka: Brother's CD
Like recently,
he was telling me when he put the radio on
Ahh, yeah, yeah!
He did say that
and he couldn't stop laughing or something, right?
I don't know if he laughed
most there in his whole life though!
That's true.
I don't know...
Time for the answer.
I mean, you just ask me all of a sudden...
Yeah, that's true.
Probably that...
Nakamura eating paella bare handed.
Eat hot food with hands challenge!
GnT #1080 2011.11.13
That was like up there...
like it comes straight to me.
-------------------------------------------
A: Nakamura P's Paella Stunt
I mean, I get that.
Well yeah, it was funny.
Everyone was laughing so hard...
In what way will Matsumoto be foolish with a toilet plunger?
Really, we're going down this road?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q65: In what way will Matsumoto be foolish with a toilet plunger?
Reveal answers.
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Run with it as an olympic torch    Hamada: Lick it
Endo: Olympic torch    Tanaka: Eyes popping out on stalks
I mean, this would be...
It could be just simple.
Time for the answer.
Do something foolish with this toilet plunger please.
This is ridiculous!
Err...
That would be tough.
Uhh, I wonder what I should do...?
Put it on your head.
I wonder what to do...?
This...
Do you have this, one size smaller...?
Oh man...
A:Ask if there is one size smaller
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Smaller...
I would never have got that.
No, no chance.
Where does Matsumoto want to live when he's old?
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q66: Where does Matsumoto want to live when he's old?
A place?
It's got to be here.
No, there are loads of places...
Yeah I guess, but overall...
Reveal answers.
------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------
Housei:Tokyo    Hamada: Guam
Endo: Okinawa    Tanaka: Okinawa
I think here...
This year, he went to Guam as well.
He did.
That's right.
Time for the answer.
I think one of us is right.
It depends how I approach the question...
What's he on about?
Oh, abroad or in Japan?
Switzerland.
Eh, Switzerland?
--------------------
A: Switzerland
Switzerland is freezing...
Switzerland, for real?
He went because of some film thing...
No but still...
I would never have got it.
Q69:
What would Matsumoto like most right now?
----------------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------
A: Shoes
Housei: Second child    Hamada: New tools
Endo: iPhone Case    Tanaka: Muscle training equipment
He definitely couldn't be bothered just now...
He just saw the staff's shoes and just answered...
Ready, start...
Q72: What's
Matsumoto's
pulling power in kg?
Question after question on Matsumoto.
A: 178 kg
(40 Algebraic Average 120kg)
Damn!!
Amazing, huh?
There are a lot of new discoveries for the 4.
A rhino.
Q75: Who would Matsumoto like to be for just for one day?
A: A Rhino
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------
Housei: ??    Hamada: Noda
Endo: Masa    Tanaka: Hamada
Masayoshi Son, billed as
the "Bill Gates of Japan"
Noda Yoshihiko,
Prime Minister of Japan
A rhino!?
Not a manager...?
I thought something like that.
Apparently a rhino.
Currently 75 questions done
Housei: 14 Correct     Hamada: 12 Correct    Endo: 17 Correct   Tanaka: 14 Correct
After 75 questions, these are the results.
His partner Hamada may get the punishment!
Who would Matsumoto not want to be reincarnated as out of the other 4?
This is hard, I think me though.
-------------------------------------------
Q76: Who would Matsumoto not want to be reincarnated as out of the other 4?
----------------------------
Right?
Yeah.
I think...
Got to be.
Yeah.
Reveal answers.
This has to be me.
------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Hamada-san    Hamada: Hamada
Endo: Housei-san    Tanaka: Hamada-san
Hmmm...
It has to be you, huh.
Yeah, it has to be.
Time for the answer.
Who I don't want to be...?
Tanaka.
-------------------------
A: Tanaka Naoki
Me!?
Eh, Tanaka huh?
What's with that?
It was... me...?
Let's ask why.
Why did you choose Tanaka?
Somehow...
his everyday life just looks boring.
That's the reason...?
What's that about?
Everyday looks boring.
What the hell?
What kind of image does he have of him...?
I'm a bit shocked though...
What would Matsumoto want put inside his coffin?
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q79: What would Matsumoto want put inside his coffin?
What kind of question is that...?
There were no questions like that before.
I have absolutely no idea.
Reveal answers.
-----------------------------------------------------------
--------------------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Own creations    Hamada: Shoes
Endo: Own creations    Tanaka: Photo of his family
Oh wow, me and Housei-san.
Exactly the same.
Oh yeah.
I don't know.
Time for the answer.
Yeah.
Come on!
Well... I've said it in my interviews and stuff
Oh really?
Um...
My own creations.
Alright!
Right!!
I see.
Like my DVD's, along with the movies I made.
Yup.
------------------------------
A: Own creations
Thank you very much!
I got it totally wrong...
Shoes...
Family photo, no way shoes...
Shoes is an awful answer.
Out of 100, how would Matsumoto rate himself as a man?
I mean come on...
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q81: Out of 100, how would Matsumoto rate himself as a man?
I wonder...
Like depends on how he feels today
Right?
Could be anything.
Like today...
Like in this situation, what will he say?
I think...
I don't know.
Reveal answers.
--------------------------------------------------------------
Housei 90 Hamada: 90  Endo: 80  Tanaka: 70
I don't think he can say 100 himself...
Yeah, so he'll lower it a bit.
Right?
Yeah.
Time for the answer.
As a man?
Can I answer honestly?
You should be the whole time...
100.
God damn...
-----------------------
A: 100 Points
He gave himself 100...
He actually gave himself 100..
Yeah...
Matsumoto would like to appear on which variety show again?
What, damn that's another tough question.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q82: Matsumoto would like to appear on which variety show again?
Variety...?
Variety... geez...
This maybe...
Right?
Yeah, that.
Reveal answers.
---------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: TORE    Hamada: Nep League
Endo: Shabekuri    Tanaka: Kinniku Banzuke
Hmm...
Tanaka's might...
I get it.
Same.
Time for the answer.
Just say it...
Umm...
Shoten.
* In the oogiri rakugo style, guests must give witty answers to questions (1966 - Present)
-------------------
A: Shoten
Shoten huh?
I see, mhm.
Yeah, I see.
Not bloody, "Yeah, I see"...
What is Matsumoto's favourite adult video genre?
Genre?
---------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q85: What is Matsumoto's favourite adult video genre?
Oh damn, ages ago...
we spoke about this.
Genre?
Like at Nakameguro...
What did he say?
I don't know...
This one, yep!
Reveal answer.
This is so true.
-----------------------------------------------------
-------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Simple    Hamada: New girl
Endo: Story line    Tanaka: Picking up
I mean,
It's got to be this
I totally get it, I really do.
now I've seen it written.
It has to be that.
He does.
He does love it.
He writes it all the time!
I totally get this.
Really!?
Time for the answer.
I though it could be this...
Oh, is this a genre?
I mean, from the start I've been saying
I can only watch girls on their debuts.
Alright!!
Amazing.
Pulls it off here...
You really got it here, Hamada-san.
Right here...
----------------------------------
A: Debut scenes
You really did it.
This must feel good.
That's a huge point right there.
But you all knew too, right?
I get it, I get it..
When you tell me, yeah.
Right?
Ask why.
I want to know why.
Because... from the second one
they're just doing it for the money.
What the hell...?
The first one,
they do it 'seriously'...
What's he on about...?
Yeah...
Ow!
Seriously?
For real?
He just hit his head...
I mean it has to be kokorozashi.
Q88: What's
Matstumoto's favourite kanji character?
-------------------------------------
------------------------------------------
A: Kokorozashi:
Ambition, will,
purpose, motive
Housei: Laugh    Tanaka: Love
Hamada Kokorozashi Endo: Kokorozashi
That was the turning point for Hamada, who's now on fire.
Q92: How many
children does Matsumoto want to have?
Two.
A: Two Kids
That's great.
He gets a few answers correct in a row.
Q95:
Which celebrity Matsumoto thinks is most fashionable?
Ah, um...
Masaaki.
A: Sakai
Masaaki
Amazing!!
The battle between the 4 heats up!
Alright!!
Oh man.
What did Matsumoto say to propose to his wife?
---------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q99: What did Matsumoto say to propose to his wife?
Ho-san, haven't you heard this one?
I have no idea about that...
I'm sure he should know.
Yeah.
I haven't a clue.
I wonder...
Reveal answers.
I thought just straight up.
------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: Didn't    Hamada: Didn't
Endo: Let's be together    Tanaka: Let's get married
Yeah like, "Let's get married."
I think so.
I honestly think even if he did,
would he honestly answer...?
I guess...
That's how I am thinking.
And you know?
He's never told me.
Ah, Ho-san hasn't heard anything.
Eh?
And Hamada-san?
No, I haven't.
Hamada-san, have you heard?
No, I haven't, and would he
really be able to say it here?
I see.
Even if he did, would he be able to say it?
Yeah, would he say it?
Oh I see, that's how you're thinking.
I get it.
Reveal answers.
What did you say to propose to your wife?
Umm, I...
I didn't, we just happened.
There wasn't...?
Umm...
When she fell pregnant,
we were like, "OK, well then we, you know..."
What an idiot...
-------------------------------------------------
A: Okay, well then we, you know...
What the hell is this...?
What the hell?
Surely you should...
Yeah.
Well, I guess we had to be more precise.
I guess.
After this
Who will receive the punishment?
Is that what it's about?
That's tough.
Question 100.
When does Matsumoto feel contented?
---------------------------------------------------------------------------
Q100: When does Matsumoto feel contented?
Oh come on...
This is hard...
I got it.
It's got to be one or the other.
I see.
Reveal answers.
One of these.
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------------------------------
Housei: When he finishes a creation    Hamada: With his kid
Endo: Going to sleep    Tanaka: When he's working
Oh, I'm not sure.
Either kid or creation...
I get you.
Come on!
Time for the answer.
I am, umm..
when I sleep,
I listen to Shiyaku-san's Rakugo...
I think maybe when there,
listening to it whilst lying on my futon...
-------------------------------------------------------------
A: Listening to Rakugo, lying on his futon about to sleep
It's when he's listening to Rakugo.
Not precise enough.
It's like Yama-chan's from before.
Yeah.
If you got this right, Yama-chan would be like, "HEY!"
I would have been so angry...
Finally, the results, who will get punished!?
Time for the results!
Who knows the least about Matsumoto?
Right, the person who had the least
correct answers about Matsumoto.
Oh damn, please...
Oh man...
Wait a second...
In last place was...
Please...
RESULTS
Yamasaki Housei!
NO WAY!
-------------------------------
Last place
Yamasaki Housei
Man, you scared me.
You're kidding!
I caught up at the end.
Eh, hold on now!
Yeah, the "new girl" one really...
And then the next question...
Yeah.
You can't be serious!
Wait a minute!...
After this
Very severe punishment!!
It is.
This is amazing
Eh, no way...
He's going to be so angry...
Shall we then?
The time...
Right..
Yama-chan...
Housei-san, come to the front.
Right, we just finished...
Yamasaki-san, please come forward.
AND?
And...?
WHO IS IT!?
This guy right here...
Right here...
Seriously...?
Like out of all of us...
ARE YOU FUCKING KIDDING ME?!
He was all like, "Oh yeah, I know the answer for this!"
Then wrote it, and got it wrong time after time...
I heard Endo did quite well...
Oh, thank you very much!
And Hamada, in the first half...
Yes, I was a bit...
You were in danger but then caught up in the second half.
Yes, the second half was much better.
And Tanaka, your life is just so boring...
He was quite hurt about that...
Even though you were hurt by what I said.
Yes, please don't say that kind of thing about me...
Please... I will get depressed...
Tanaka always gets his feelings hurt in 100 questions...
That's true.
Yes, every time.
Did anyone get the question right about the adult film genre?
Umm... Yes, I did.
He knew straight away.
I've said that so many times.
As soon as an adult entertainer
seems professional, I'm done with them
You really have told us that so many times...
Hamada-san saw right through you.
He did.
Amateurs are truly the pros.
That's what I believe.
But who gives a shit about that!?
YOU!
Yes...
You're going to get punished.
This will be bad.
Punishment!
What are you going to do?
100 Shouts of Matsumoto!
You will go to loads of different places
100 Shouts of Matsumoto!!
and scream "Matsumoto-san!"
Right.
But it might not be all bad...
You might go to that place
you're not a member of anymore...
I'm going to shout there...?
As soon as you get there.
100 Shouts of Matsumoto!!
Punishment:
Punishment: Commence!
Next week... the punishment commences!
But Tanaka is the one who will be upset...
I'm going to go home and...