That just means you've got old.
I mean, who can live without it?
What? Don't you think so?
What makes you talk like that. You are not convincing.
What I want to ask you is
To let me have that in this show, pleeease.
You're a lousy actor.
There're some programs for that.
In which two TV talents dates.
There are a lot in these days.
Let me do it.
no sub
They've found you a wonderful date.
Really? You've already arranged for me?
She is definitely rich.
Is she?
And she seems to be your type.
Does she have this(big breast)?
I don't know if she has that.
Why should she have to have that?
To me a beauty means this.
no sub
Rendezvous at Hibiya Park
There's a woman waiting for him in this bad weather.
Oh, Ms. Nishikawa Ayako. Look at that fluffy thing.
TN: Ayako Nishikawa is a Surgeon and TV talent.
Ayako Nishikawa
His date
Heipo with a nervous look on his
face goes to the meeting spot.
It's cold outside.
Here he comes! From behind.
They come from behind in those other shows too.
Excuse me.
Look at that.
Are you?
Oh, yes.
Are you my date?
My name is Nishikawa Ayako.
Nice to meet you. My name is Heipo.
Worldly acclaimed Heipo, the director of the show.
He said "worldly acclaimed Heipo".
Mr. Heipo.
Of course you are familiar with the show, aren't you?
Yes, on TV.
Look how presumptuous he is.
He presumes a lot.
OK, shall we?
Very aggressive.
Yes.
It's a shame it's raining.
Yes, it is.
He's holding the umbrella only for himself!
She's a bit different from what she usually is.
More feminine. Don't you think so?
Maybe hooking her up with him wasn't such a bad idea.
They arrived at a cafe
What kind of man do you like?
Well... I like a competent man.
He's getting right into the point.
Really? That's great. People always say I'm competent.
Really?
Yes.
What do your other family do?
My father is a doctor.
That means your family is genetically horny, right?
No, we are not!
He's trying to offend her?
Yes?
They have to follow
the instruction in the letter
It says "Heipo and Ayako's love plan".
There's a instruction.
Can I open this?
Yes.
The guy makes the girl happy.
I think "the girl" refers to me.
I should do something to make you happy.
This is crucial.
What's your hobby?
Golf is my sports.
Is it? I'm very good at it.
You are?
Single digit handicap. I can give you a lesson if you like.
Really?
He said "single digit".
I'm impressed. Can you give me a lesson?
Yes. Can I give you now?
I got a very bad vibe about this.
No, that's no good.
You have to use your waist.
Stick your hip. Yes, that's it.
Is this OK?
May be a little more, OK?
What's he doing?
Let's swing in this position.
Like this?
Oh, very good.
This is bad. He's grabbing her ass.
OK, I get it, you can let your hands off now.
Now you understand you have to stick your hip
when you swing, don't you?
Yes, I do, thank you.
If you want more lessons let me know.
By the way, I read this article in some magazine.
That women like to be carried in men's arms.
Off course we do.
So, as in this letter, I can make you happy by...
Do you want me to do it?
His intention is too obvious.
What?
Oh, no.
Oh, this is very very good.
OK, thank you, now please let me...
She's fighting back.
No, please, I mean it!
She's fighting back really hard.
No. Really.
No, no, no.
No, no! Stop it!!
What's the matter with you?
She left her microphone.
I can't take it any more.
What should I do now?
Due to his sexual harassment of her
shooting was stopped.
Heipo. Come here.
What do you think you're doing?
What do you mean?
What are you trying to do?
You did all that to get exciting feelings?
No, I did that because I had a feeling of excitement.
And I read in a magazine that women like that.
What are you, still in school?
You have to apologize to her.
OK, I'll write a letter of apology.
So please give me a second chance.
Nishikawa certainly did not expected this.
She is furious and went back to her dressing room.
We have to do something.
Otherwise the shooting is over.
So Heipo reads a letter of apology to ask
her forgiveness. And ask her to continue.
How are you doing?
Hello.
He wants to apologize to you.
I come here to apologize...so please listen...
No. No. I don't want to listen.
I understand your feeling, but please.
I write this letter very earnestly. Please listen.
I, worldly acclaimed Heipo, offended
Ms. Nishikawa Ayako, TV talent and surgeon
during the shooting...
Just a minute.
Sorry I will do it right. Ouch.
Why the hell did you laugh, huh?
I shouldn't. There's absolutely no reason.
I don't want to hear. Especially when he's laughing.
I'm really sorry.
I really need to apologize.
Please, for our sake.
I, worldly acclaimed Heipo, offended
Ms. Nishikawa Ayako, TV talent and surgeon.
I express here, my deepest apology to Ms. Nishikawa.
First I would like to explain how I come to do the act
which, in Ayako's claim, falls into
a sexual harassment...
I'm sorry. Please let me finish.
First I would like to explain how I came to do the act
which, in Ayako's claim, falls into a sexual harassment.
When I try to carry Ayako in the cafe
Ayako's ass made this very erotic move.
So I said to myself "Wow!".
And I grabbed her ass.
Before this shooting began there was
this talk among the staff
that a broad like her can surely take
abuses to some degree.
However, the fact remains that
I grabbed Ms. Ayako's ass.
But it's also a fact that lady doctors, in general,
are thought to be very horny.
Therefore, since both sides are to blame,
I ask you to let bygones be bygones.
The director of Gaki no Tsukai
wordly acclaimed Heipo.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Please give me a seconds chance.
I think his choice of words were
far from appropriate, but...
We are just doing business.
Yes, I understand.
Don't you ever forget it.
I won't. Please forgive me.
OK.
I know it's difficult, but please forget what happened.
I'll try.
Ouch.
The date resumes.
I'm really sorry.
It's alright.
Let's enjoy the time we have.
Yes, please drink a coffee.
Thank you.
I think it's extremely hard for him
to win her heart after this.
Heipo and Ayako's love plan.
Yes.
Do something nice to remember afterward, together.
Wow!
This is a nice. A necklace.
Today's my birthday.
Oh, is it?
It's true.
Can I ask your age?
I'm 35.
35? You looks lot younger!
It's very nice of you. Thank you.
Very beautiful. Very prurient.
Didn't he get the message?
Does he have any idea at all
what his problem had been?
Can I put this on you?
Thank you.
This is sweet.
Oh, it's not...
It's... Your hair...
Yes?
What?
Excuse me, but I have to hook up.
What's he doing?
Stop it!! You Jerk!!
Due to his sexual harassment of her
the shooting was stopped again.
You screwed it big time!
What did I do?
Didn't you get what we were trying to tell you?
I was just trying to put this on her and...
You already told her she's sexy before doing that.
But she smells so good.
What's that got to do with it?
I'll write another letter of apology, really earnestly.
Please give me one more chance.
Don't you ever laugh this time, OK?
I won't, off course. Straight words and straight face.
This is a second offense he made to her.
And he beg her forgiveness for second time.
The question is would she, after all this.
I'm sorry.
We are all sorry for what he did.
I'm very sorry.
Heipo, just get to it.
Yes.
I wrote another letter. Please listen.
I don't want to hear it.
Just give me one more chance, please.
Ms. Nishikawa, I would like you to give it a try.
After that it's up to you to decide.
OK.
Before I express my deepest apology,
I would like to explain how I came to do that act.
It's said that in adult entertainment establishment
in Ikebukuro average fee is from 30,000 to 50,000 yen.
Therefore when I thought about expensive
performance fee we paid you.
Pressing myself to you hardly seems excessive.
This is the reasoning behind my conduct.
What's more, when I pressed myself to her.
Her expression was not that of a rejection
but that of a lecherous joy.
So the waves of "Wow, this is good" kept coming to me.
Which eventually leads to my pushing her down.
So if I describe this incident in more vulgar terms.
It's like I was so excited in adult
entertainment establishment
that I forced a worker to have sex with me,
which is not in the options of the service.
So I didn't feel any moral qualm when I did it.
There fore I ask you to agree to settle this out of court.
The director of the show, worldly acclaimed Heipo.
Please forgive me...
We are sorry too.
I'm sorry.
His choice of words, again, is very lousy.
But he's really sorry for what happened.
I am.
How could you call tha an apology?
You can't.
We ourselves are surprised to hear that.
I don't want to do this.
Please.
Would you please give me another chance?
For Hamada-san's sake too.
I really don't.
I can't do it any more.
Nishikawa completely lost her patience this time
and called the producer of the show.
Can we continue the shooting?
What's this? "Before I express my apology"?
Apology first!
Oh, I should?
Why you mentioned entertainment establishment?
So I should do this for my own benefit?
After a desperate appeal, the producer
managed to make her agree to continue.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
I'm very sorry. And thank you.
I will do it right.
You really should.
Restart
Many things happened today, but I enjoyed it.
Thank you. It's been the moment of my life.
Yes.
Thank you.
I enjoyed it too.
Did you? Thank you.
Yes.
Mr. and Ms. this is for you.
Thank you.
A lovely kid.
Cute.
What's in this box?
Oh, another letter.
The guy confesses his love to the girl loudly
and kiss her through this glass.
So I hold this in front of your mouth?
Oh, through glass.
Like this, I think.
Just do the thing, Heipo.
All he have to do is just to follow the instruction.
May I begin?
Yes.
I couldn't express how sorry I am for all the things.
I'm so sorry for all the offenses.
Still, I enjoyed every minute and
had a excitement of romance.
So if you don't mind, please marry me!
Marry him?
Hey, please.
Use the glass.
What are you doing?
No, no.
Glass, where is it?
No. Really.
Stop it!
He's grabbing her ass.
I mean it. No!
Ouch. Ouch!
Why are you doing this!
She slapped back of his head.
Don't you get it?!
Why he's laughing?
That hurts.
That's way out of line.
Pervert!
He's slapped and kicked and crying like a child.
What should I do?
We have to stop the shooting for the 3rd time
because of the sexual harassment.
Don't you ever learn?
Learn what?
I expressed my love very affectionately.
The letter said you have to use this glass.
But Ayako seems ready for it.
Don't talk like she's your girlfriend.
You've only referred to her by Ayako so far.
And only adjective you use to describe her was 'sexy'.
Heipo, I'm afraid we can't help you any more.
I'll write another letter for one last time.
That wouldn't work.
That's just wouldn't work.
Your letters were complete disaster.
Can't call that an apology.
Don't worry. I'll write in sincerely.
Very arrogant.
Just remember you can't expect her to forgive you.
We'll only ask her to listen.
no sub
This could easily lead to a lawsuit.
Is it possible to ask her forgiveness this time?
I just want to say that...
We are not come here to ask your forgiveness.
We came here to ask you to listen
to him for one last time.
I wrote another letter so...
Please listen...
I want you to listen...
Why are you laughing, huh?
Do you have any idea who rude that is?
No! What are you going to do to me!
What's so funny?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for what I've done. Please just listen.
Just do it!
Thank you.
I would like to thank you for taking time for 3rd time.
I thought kissing a talent of your class is no big deal.
That was very thoughtless of me.
And I apologize for the offenses.
This thing originated when Ayako
came for the shooting.
I thought to myself "Here comes a major bitch!"
Let me mention for a moment here about the word.
The word 'bitch' means a slut who sleeps with anybody.
So when I think of that during the shooting
waves of "Wow, this is good" kept coming to me.
I couldn't resist the 5th and I set out to kiss you.
What's more, during the shooting you gave off an
awesome 'pheromone'.
Which doesn't match a cheesy talent like you at all.
So I thought to myself "she's a dirty old slut"
and also thought *******
That leads me eventually to set out to
kiss you for the 2nd and the 3rd time.
This whole thing taught me a valuable lesson.
That I can't force someone to kiss me,
even that someone is a talent of your class.
The director of the show, worldly acclaimed Heipo.
I'm sorry.
Obviously this wouldn't work.
But I did the best I could to show my sincerity...
There's no way you can call that sincere.
I think it's well expressed.
What on earth are you trying to do?
What is this?
I.. went on for so long...
I'm sick of this crap!
We are sorry. We understand your feeling.
We considered what can we do to make up.
So we brought this.
A whip for S&M
You can release your anger with this.
But I had apologized.
She hasn't forgive you.
On your knees. Now!
I said on your knees!
Oh! Yes!
What?
Don't you get up!
Head down!
Oh, no!
Yes.
I want a real apology!
Oh, yes! Sorry!
Give me a real apology!
Here comes a major bitch.
A broad like her can certainly take abuses to some degree.
Lady doctors, in general, are thought to be very horny.
Her 'pheromone' was so awesome for
a piece of cheesy ass.
Wave of "Wow, this is good" kept coming to me.
Pressing myself to her hardly seems excessive.
This whole thing taught me a valuable lesson.
That I can't force someone to kiss me,
even that someone is a talent of your class.