@tofupizza on Twitter
Edited by Mrs. ShibataBread
Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
Standing by for Gaki no Tsukai recording time.
WHAT?!!
Cocorico
Hosei Yamasaki
Naoki Tanaka
Shozo Endo
What did you do?
Downtown
Masatoshi Hamada
What'd you do?
You just gave me a look.
Yes, I just looked at you but...
...I get yelled at just for that?
I don't know how you can ever work together.
You must've woke up on the wrong side of the bed, Hamada-san.
Trust me, I won't look your way.
He got you good.
I'm scared now.
By the way, what's with your small bag?
That's new, right?
No, I've had it for awhile.
You're serious?
Downtown Manager
Naoya Orita
Good morning.
Matsumoto-san has requested that all of you...
Oh, I just assumed he was running late.
Me too.
What do you want?
Well...
...he was wondering how well you know his likes and dislikes.
He seemed very preoccupied with this idea.
He's that curious?
I don't get it.
So what should we do?
Well, he wants you to come to the studio.
But why?
Why can't we talk about it here?
We can discuss it here, right?
He was very set on having it in the studio.
How can I feel good about this?
Am I right?
Downtown Presents:
Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende!!
Wow!
What a huge space we've got here!?
He's in here?
They get invited into one of largest studios
Yes.
In here?
But why in the studio?
Yeah, why?
Wow!
How big is this studio?!
It's gigantic.
It feels huge when there's no set in here.
Where's Matsumoto anyhow?
Matsumoto-san is...
What's that say?
What's this?
What's that sign say?
"Present Something Matsumoto Might Like and Win His Heart!"
There used to be a show like this.
What?
This will tell us if he likes certain things?
So we put an object here?
I see
I see.
Should we go for it?
Yes, let's.
Let's go find stuff he might like.
Since we're here, there's no turning back.
What can we find around here?
They search for items Matsumoto might like...
30 minutes later...
We got some stuff...
We got some random things.
Now what?
What's first?
Let's just pick one.
We can pick whatever.
He likes these kind of snacks...
Yes he does.
Let's start with one of them.
Which one first?
Beef jerky or...
Beef Jerky
...dried squid?
Dried Squid
Which would you pick, Hamada-san?
He likes both of these.
But he's getting too old to chew on these.
Too old?
Beef Jerky
Dried Squid
I know that makes two of us, but...
But you're not that old.
C'mon, you can still chew on it.
I know, but this one seems a bit...
I know he's a big fan of this!
You sure?
He has always liked gnawing on them since he was young!
Could you make it any more foul sounding?
Beef Jerky
Dried Squid
Go with this one?
That's it.
I'm positive about this.
You're 100% sure?
Let's go for it.
Here's beef jerky.
Beef jerky!
I'm 100% sure.
So that idiot's been hiding in there.
Yes, I can hear him inside.
There's he is!
That's him.
What a moron!
That's him alright.
Oh, he's taking it!
He's taking it.
I thought he'd go for the dried squid, but it's beef jerky, huh...
I wish he'd hurry up.
He's contemplating.
Which is it?
He took it!
But seriously, what the hell's wrong with him?
What's that all about?
I still have a fond memory of trying this for the first time.
He remembers that?
That's why he likes it.
Seriously, what is this?
How irritating.
So he likes it?
That's why he took it!
So you were right!
Right?
You got it, Yama-chan.
I knew he liked beef jerky.
Is that so?
Does he have a sweet tooth?
Like this Swiss roll?
Swiss Roll
Right, the Swiss roll.
I'm stumped.
Does he eat sweets when you guys go out?
He started to recently.
He never used to.
Right, he never touched sweets until recently.
So he orders dessert?
Yeah, I catch him sucking on sweets all the time.
Can you be less graphic?
Did that sound bad?
I didn't mean to...
I'm curious about what would happen with the roll.
It's a mystery item.
I would like to know his position on this one.
Next up is the Swiss Roll.
Is Matsumoto a fan?
He started to eat sweets recently.
You sure?
Yes...
Even Swiss rolls?
What's with the sound effects?
Please let me smack him once.
Seriously, what the hell do you think you're doing?
Take it already!
He must be contemplating.
He's thinking about it?
Does he like it or not?
Can't you reach?
See?
You were right!
You got it?
Why the stare down?
Very hard stare down.
I wish he'd hurry up.
Incredible!
I didn't know...
I had no idea...
Right?
Because of the eating sensation is strong.
Shut the hell up.
He likes it because...
I don't get it.
What's a strong eating sensation?
He lost me.
Let's yank him outta there and beat him up?
Is that OK?
If Hamada-san if giving us permission, then...
We'll gladly help you.
What a combo though.
Beef jerky and Swiss roll.
He likes them for sure.
We pretty much got things we like.
You're right.
I don't know if it's a coincidence but...
But who from Osaka wouldn't be into takoyaki?
Of course, he likes it.
Or the 551 brand pork buns.
T/N: 551 Horai is a famous pork bun brand that is exclusive to Osaka.
Hit him with the takoyaki?
Let's go for it.
He's 100% into this.
We did something like this before...
That's right!
I'm pretty sure he likes these.
Let's put them right here.
Right on the line.
What?
This thing isn't designed well.
Not only that, but...
...something's wrong with his teeth.
Where's his other tooth?
What happened?
Can he take it?
He needs to find a way to grab it.
If he likes it enough, he'll get it.
That's right.
He can make it happen.
It's still inside the square.
He's gonna pull a muscle.
That'll hurt.
Where there's a will, there's a way.
If he wants it bad enough...
If he likes it, he'll get it.
He got it!
He loves it.
Incredible!
Because it makes me ecstatic.
It doesn't take much...
All it takes is takoyaki to make him ecstatic.
Only takoyaki...
He's from Osaka after all...
You've got a point.
Good point.
Yama-chan, your turn.
Offer him something.
Well, well, well...
Endo and Tanaka just went so...
I see...
How about this one?
What's that?
This is more like a "necessity".
It's a hair clipper!
What did you think it was?
I thought it was an electric razor.
It looks similar.
OK, so you choose the clipper.
Matsumoto's good friend, Yamasaki, chooses the hair clipper.
I'm sure he likes this.
A different movement.
What's he doing?
Is he confirming something?
He's looking at it.
Oh, he can pick things up.
I thought he could only pull things in.
He's still looking at us.
He's got it in his hand.
How's it gonna be?
Which is it?
It's not something to like or dislike, right?
It's neither, I guess.
It's not a "like" or "dislike".
See, you shouldn't have picked something like that.
From now on...
...if you're wrong, you will be slapped in the face.
I don't want that.
Seriously, what's this all about?
By the way, his voice is way too distorted.
His voice isn't clear.
It's hard to understand.
Endo, you go again.
Shall I?
I don't want to be wrong.
A face slap?
I don't want to be slapped.
Who's slapping us anyhow?
I choose the socks.
Just pick what you like.
You're right.
These are quite useful...
See these toe socks?
You're going for it?
That's your final pick?
Yes.
Go for it then.
Here we go.
Here's a pair of toe socks.
He sounds a little different.
He's got a different set of teeth, too.
His character keeps changing.
Take them!
There! He got them!
Take them already!
Keep it down!
The machine's broken.
It's completely out of order.
It's sweating bullets too.
He doesn't like them...
A slap from Tanaka.
From Tanaka?
So I slap him?
I'm supposed to slap Endo then?
I see, Tanaka gets to slap me.
Me?
This sucks.
I don't like it either.
What're you gonna do?
Shouldn't it be Yamasaki or Hamada-san?
Well, it was an order.
Ok, I'm ready.
This sucks.
You ready?
He's looking!
He witnessed it.
He peeked.
Yes, he was looking.
Was that good?
OK, I'll take it.
OK.
That was good.
He sounds very easy going.
He's really pissing me off now.
Well, not much I can do.
I'm feeling this one.
This comes in handy when your face is sweaty.
I choose the wet wipes.
I've got a good feeling.
Go for it.
I'll get him.
Good luck!
Here's a set of wet wipes.
What the...?
He's looking!
There he is!
He's out!
Using both hands even!
Pretty good.
That's a new move!
He's acting like he's into them.
Hurry the hell up!
Don't try to break the machine!
He breaks easily.
You hurt his feelings!
He's being loud as hell and sweating up a storm!
Just hurry up and grab it!
Because you tore my spirit in half.
See that?
It's not about just the things he likes.
Slapping him was a bad move?
Sorry about that.
I apologize.
Endo slaps Hamada.
No way.
Phew!
I was just thinking, "Please don't make me slap Hamada-san."
This sucks!
Hamada-san, I don't know if I can...
I need to watch this closely.
You don't get to see this too often.
This never happens.
I'm sorry in advance.
Please don't take this personally.
Damn, he's been staring the whole time.
Right, he's been staring with both eyes.
He's not even trying to hide.
That's beyond peeking.
He might as well come all the way out.
Please excuse me.
Look at him chuckling.
Not hard enough.
I thought that was good enough.
I disagree!
I slapped him fair and square!
Hit him a little harder.
What a nightmare.
Yeah, pretty hellish.
This is the worst.
What a bad deal for both of us.
Endo, there's not much you can do now.
Even Hamada-san can't do anything about this.
Just make this one count.
What the...
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU LOOKING AT!?
He's not shy about this.
Just get over with.
Right, I don't want to have to do this again.
Agreed.
Try to ignore him.
He won't stop looking.
I won't hold back then.
Here I go!
Ready?
You ok, Hamada-san?
OK, Hamada-san!?
Hamada-san!
Tell me you're ok.
You ok?
My ear is ringing.
His ear is ringing.
That was awesome.
"That was awesome."
How dare you hide behind there and laugh hysterically.
That shook my head.
I'm so sorry.
I'm mature enough to keep my composure in front of the camera.
Wait, you'd be pissed if there were no cameras?
What would the viewers think if I got seriously pissed off?
Next up, Tanaka chooses an electric toothbrush.
Electric brush?
Electric or not, he'll like it.
He'll like it, right?
Who doesn't like brushing his teeth?
Come on!
Get it!
Yes, it's electric.
Just scoot it in.
Bring it home.
Just take that with you.
Drag it in.
It's electric.
Hurry the hell up!
Don't discourage him!
Hamada-san!
You knew he'd retract once you hit him!?
We don't have all day here.
But he went away because you hit him!
Maybe he just didn't want it.
Right, he didn't like it from the get go.
I agree!
Well, can we ask him why he left?
Could you tell us why?
Because I was physically violated.
Hamada-san...
So it was Hamada-san...
It makes no sense!
Otherwise, he would have taken it.
And here come the slap.
Hamada slaps Tanaka.
Let's make it quick.
Go easy on me.
Don't worry, I'll go easy.
Slap him using bad aim.
Bad aim?
Not good.
So not directly on the cheek?
He could get hurt.
So hit me over here?
Like towards the back of my head and stuff?
What if I just graze your face?
That's bad aim.
It'll hurt either way.
So that's how it is.
He's looking.
He gets shy once we look at him though.
Ready?
That's the painful type.
What do you want from me?!
That's what I was told to do!
You did that perfectly.
Right!
It was a badly aimed face slap.
Your turn, Yama-chan.
Can I choose pork buns?
No, I don't think so.
Why not?!
It's my turn, and I get to choose!
You can't offer him that.
Nonsense! This is a game!
Of course, he'll like this.
Well, there's no guarantee.
He can choose what he wants.
Thank you.
How about the pork bun loved by all Osaka people?
Here they are.
Pork buns...
He can talk now?!
I did it!
He definitely likes them!
He even said "pork buns".
He'll definitely take it.
Looking good.
He opened it!
I don't want this right now.
He can talk now.
See?
He doesn't want this right now.
From Hamada...
No way...
This is so rigged!
What?
I got slapped too!!
He seems to have changed the rules of the game.
He didn't say what I'm supposed to do to you.
Hamada will do a front kick.
Wait, this show took a weird turn just now.
Agreed.
What happened?
It didn't start this way...
Why a kick?
Why should we even participate?
Seriously, why are we putting ourselves through this?
He won't miss this...
Isn't the way he hides so annoying?
I'm terrified.
A frontal kick sounds...
...it sounds scary!
Seriously...
Ready?
Stomp on his leg.
Stomp on his leg?
No, no, no, no!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
He's looking!
He did!
That's good.
I'm done with this...
I don't want to play anymore...
A surprise ending in the final attack!
Let's do the last item.
OK.
Well...
This is perfect, right?
Ultra-man figurine collection.
Let's do this.
This is good.
As long as he uses his preference to judge this.
Look, he's not even hiding anymore.
Please, take a good look.
Tell us whether you like this or not.
We got the full set.
I think...
I think we got him with these.
Well...
I can see his elbows now.
I'm not a fan after this generation...
I understand but...
I'm only know the ones up to this point...
But here are Ace and Seven...
I didn't watch much of the Ace series...
I've got a good feeling...
He'll accept these!
What's up with him now?
OK, he's swimming...
Maybe the Ultra-man Seven?
Well, he grabbed the Seven...
OK, got him, let's go home.
He likes it then.
We're done.
Let's go home.
He liked it.
Wait a sec...
There's a little more left...
See you next week!!!
What's he saying?
Same time, same place next week!!!
Let's end this.
I'm not kidding!!!
Has your physical endurance gone down?
Endurance... Yeah, it's gone completely down.
Oh, but Endo's hasn't, right?
Has it gone down? Well, normally...
So let's say running a 100 meter sprint...
...my recovery has really...
Speaking honestly here, Matsumoto-san,
If I ran 100 meters with everything I got, I'll seriously vomit.
No, I don't think so, I wouldn't vomit.
Really? I would vomit. A long time ago...
Actually, to tell the truth, I haven't vomited that much in my life.
Oh wait, no, I have. Never mind.
Right?
I've thrown up a lot.
Why would you lie about something so dumb?
I thought, "I have to show off."
"Can't miss his chance to show off!" is what I thought.
I've thrown up a lot. I've thrown up from motion sickness a lot.
Motion sickness?
I've thrown up as much as the Merlion.
T/N: He's referring to the famous Merlion fountain in Singapore that shoots water out of its mouth.
First of all, diarrhea... You get diarrhea a lot, don't you?
I don't even understand the meaning of diarrhea.
So my answer would be...
You're a defective product.
If we were in a factory, getting ready for shipment, you'd be removed!
They'd look at you and take you aside.
In a really nasty box.
That's enough!
My answer would be, I'm not backed up.
Well, constipation isn't good...
Everything comes out of me so my insides are clean.
But as a living organism, you're a ***.
As a living organism, ***...
Diarrhea, people who get stomach aches, people who can't eat hot foods, I hate them.
"I can't eat foods that are too hot!"
Who the hell are you?!
There are so many foods that are so good when served hot.
"I can't eat it because it's too hot" really pisses me off!
Well, if I can say something, I'm very delicate.
I'm a sensitive living being.
Sensitive living being... What do you mean?
T/N: Senpai is someone who is older or more experienced so they should be treated with respect by their kohai who are younger or less experienced.
Uh... Who is the senpai and kohai here?