First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
Toro Salmon's Kubota Shichi-Henge!
- It's been quite a while since we did this, hasn't it?
- He is the 58th challenger.
-58th!
This time the challenger  came directly to me .
- Did he ask you to let him do it?
- "Really let me do it."
- Really?
He has enough momentum to "21 henge".
No way.
- Feel his enthusiasm firsthand.
- Okay.
Now, come the star of today's show, Toro Salmon!
Hello!
- Your enthusiasm is great.
- I am going to do 26 henge instead of 21 henge.
What are you saying?
- It was the first time I had ever been asked directly for h.
- I see.
I don't know if it was because of Shichi-henge, but he didn't say a word during the recording of yesterday's bicycle race show.
That's bad!
That's a bad influence!
- You are too nervous!
- Then don't do it!
This is the ranking list.
What rank are you aiming for?
Of course, I want to surpass Koumoto-san, who came in first.
- Koumoto has been sitting in first place for a long time.
- I would like to be in the top 5 or 6.
It was difficult to make jokes because compliance was very strict.
You're already making excuses?
No, it’s not!
Don't say that before you do it.
I can no longer do dick jokes that make people around the world laugh.
That's not just a compliance issue.
- Please do your best to do as much as you can to broadcast.
- You are aiming for the top 5, so good luck to you!
This is nice.
“Can Matsumoto and Kinni-kun talk to each other using only their muscles?”
- You got up fast!
- I can.
No, you can’t!
You got up fast!
I don't know, I'm a “Shichi-henge Virgin”.
We are all like that at first.
I can have a conversation with just my muscles if I want to.
But that conversation isn't funny.
- That's not good!
-  Even if we could have a conversation, it would have to be funny.
How about having Shoji join it?
Shoji still can't speak with his muscles.
He is not a good talker.
Not a good “muscle talker”.
Thank you for visiting us today.
Touch as many girls as you like that you normally would not touch.
Now the girls will enter, and please go and sit with the man of your choice.
Melon-chan, Strawberry-chan, Marron-chan, come on, go to them.
Now, when she comes next to you, hustle time begins.
Don't just cause trouble.
Have fun today.
Now the "flirting time" starts.
Now, everyone, please touch them as much as you like.
Don't overdo it.
It is a one-shot deal that you can only touch.
Staff, turn on the lights.
Girls please go back.
I don’t know.
I didn't do anything.
Sir, what did you do?
There is a karen in seat 6.
Check.
A short man with a shaggy head.
What did you do to her?
I did not do anything to her.
Our girl is crying!
Please follow the rules!
Get all the customers out.
And park the car out front.
We are in business to entertain you!
Are you okay?
It is nothing....
She is crying.
Look up.
Let's go to the private room.
What are you doing?
What did you do to her?
What happened?
Did he say anything to you?
He said, "I have to do this or I won't get excited."
No way.
I didn't mention this to upper management, but this is the fifth time you've done this, right?
This is the fifth time.
But I didn't tell them about it.
You go back.
Huh?
I know this guy.
Chairman, please come here.
Hey, wait there, short man.
Chairman.
Is it still going on?
This is a long piece.
It's a long piece from the first shot.
There are a lot of customers today.
Is that you?
Hey.
No.
- You messed with our woman?
- No, I didn't do anything.
Who is he?
He is Hamada.
Ah, I know this guy.
I like comedy.
I forgive you.
You have a life ahead of you, right?
Hey, do the "announcement of the results".
- I like that one.
I listen to it on Youtube a lot, right?
- Yes.
Say "announcement of the results".
Say "announcement of the results"!!
- Announcement of the results....
- What's that little voice!?
Is my youtube volume too high?
Say "announcement of the results"!!
Are you kidding me?
- Would you like me to call the police?
- Yeah.
What the hell.
It was long.
Was the last one necessary?
I don't think he needed the second half.
The girl touched you a lot, didn't she?
She kept saying, "Let's play, Hosei-san."
The girls really said that.
That's the kind of thing that bothers me.
It was pretty real.
I enjoyed the movie.
Yeah, I never thought I'd be able to watch a movie with you at my age.
Ah, the traffic light turned red.
This is no time for older man and older woman to be talking about love here.
No matter how much I jump rope, I can't lose any weight.
I want to lose 8 kg.
Ow...!
My stomach hurts!
why does this have to happen right now?
It can't be helped.
Sorry.
He's pooping.
Ah, that's refreshing.
Sorry. There was no bathroom.
Oh, I have to do this while I'm waiting.
- What the hell are you doing!?
- What?
I have to jump rope while I'm waiting.
This light is taking forever.
What the hell are you talking about!?
Stop it!
Sorry, sir!
You're overdoing it!
- "The light has turned green."
- Sorry!
Get the hell out of here!
You stupid son of a bitch!
So sorry!
I was about to shit myself!
I'll leave.
Sorry.
Go away!
Woah, you don’t see this everyday!
There's a flower blooming in the asphalt!
I don't understand the view of the world.
That was a good story?
I thought the acrylic panels were there to protect us from the coronavirus.
But it was to protect us from shit.
That was absolutely necessary.
He's an idiot.
Hi.
Please listen to one ridiculous story.
No, please listen to two, three, or four.
Let me begin immediately.
I work in a small buckwheat noodle restaurant.
No, it is not small, but rather large.
Well, please imagine the size of the restaurant by yourself.
When I enter the restaurant, I see my wife, Omame.
I have been running this restaurant with her for over 50 years.
And there comes a man with a swagger that is well-known in town.
"Shokichi is here!!"
Shokichi was famous for doing bad things.
Shokichi entered the private room and closed the door.
Then Shokichi said,
"Hey, bring me a large bowl of buckwheat noodle!"
Sorry, it's not a large bowl, it's a medium bowl.
No, not a medium bowl, but a small bowl.
Then I said to Omame,
"Omame, give him a small bowl.
"Yes, honey."
Omame went into the room and closed the door.
But Omame did not come out of the room.
I heard a sound from the room.
"Hey, Omame, what are you doing?"
Omame said nothing.
"Hey, Omameh, answer me!"
"@#$#%^&&#$$&"
Did a customer come in?
"Hey, Omame, are you listening?"
I don't know what that noise is, but I can hear it.
I felt sick, so I went toward the eel restaurant
There was a man I recognized at the end of a narrow alley.
"Hey, Shokichi is here"
Huh? What is he doing here?
"Shokichi, What are you doing?"
"I'm having "my rolling pin" held by Omame."
And Shokichi said, "Hey! Why don't you join me?
"I can't do that!"
I found myself holding Shokichi's rolling pin, too.
I found that his rolling pin entered me repeatedly.
What a day, I thought, and went back to the restaurant.
Then I noticed that the manhole cover was open.
"Who was messing with this manhole?"
I opened the manhole and found someone in it.
"Hey, Shokichi is here!"
He came out of the manhole.
When I looked closer, I saw that Omame was touching his rolling pin.
Then Omame did this.
As she did so, a white liquid, like buckwheat sauce, sprayed around from the manhole.
I licked it off my mouth and it was salty.
It tasted like seawater on the beach.
What a wonderful day it is today.
I really hope this isn’t a dream.
He makes jokes like this all the time, doesn't he?
It was like Shibahama only at the end.
It was like a human-interest story?
He is disgusting.
Shangri-La, The utopia she chanted is dazzling
Shangri-La, She spoke quaint is good
Why this song?
Shangri-La, Whatever she does, it doesn't matter
Shangri-La, Ignore the memories lost in Shangri-La
KISS in a dream
KISS KISS KISS KISS KISS
The colorful world that seems to lead to anywhere and everywhere is a beautiful time
KISS in a dream
KISS KISS KISS KISS KISS
My heart was thrilled with sweet feelings that always and forever sparkle like those days
KISS in a dream
KISS KISS KISS KISS KISS
The days are peaceful in the rustling that seems to drift away forever and ever
KISS in a dream
KISS KISS KISS KISS KISS
The rain that always and forever sparkles and falls down was moistening the spring like those days
I want to be a crocodile.
Yeah, I want to be a crocodile.
Is he crazy?
It was messy.
He is insane.
Here comes Kazu-kun, the gorilla genius!
Let's see what the gorilla genius Kazu-kun can do!
First of all, let's thank our visitors!
A...RI...GA...TO....U...
(THANK YOU)
You're so smart, you know how to read!
Ladies and gentlemen! Give him a round of applause!
Kazu-kun, don't touch your butt!
Kazu-kun, wake up!
Hey, visitor next to him! Rub Kazu-kun's back!
The visitor with a banana in front of you, peel the banana and feed it to Kazu-kun.
I've never seen Kazu-kun so happy.
Ladies and gentlemen! Give him a round of applause!
Because you smell it!
Why aren't you eating this?
Kazu-kun, why did you smell that again?
The visitor next to him! Rub Kazu-kun's back!
Kazu-kun has a fruit present for you all today.
Hey, Kazu-kun, give it to everyone.
He has a sense of camaraderie.
Kazu-kun is unusually excited!
But he is so happy!
Huh?
Kazu-kun wants to say something.
PA...PA...
Great! Kazu-kun could speak for the first time!
It's thanks to gorilla papa!
That's all, Kazu-kun, the genius gorilla.
Kazu-kun was talking.
He recovered in the second half, didn't he?
I don't know if that was really Kubota, though.
Please stop now.
Walk!
Hey, fuckin' pig.
How many days have you been coming to this shop?
20 days.
- You've been going here for 20 days straight?
- Yes, thank you.
You're disgusting!
Get down here on all fours.
Yes.
Please be gentle.
Like this? Like this?
Please don't do that!
Please!
I'm going to tease you a lot today with this thing you love so much.
Please don't do that.
You want me to stop?
No.
What do you want!?
I want you to do it!
- Say "I want you to do it, please."
- I want you to do it, please.
Here we go.
It sounds great.
It sounds wonderful.
- Get off.
- Yes.
This is what you really love.
You can smell it.
- How about it?
- I can't resist. I'm back.
- You wanna see what's inside this thing?
- Yes, will you show me?
Oh, I can't resist.
Can I put my finger in?
- Not yet!
- Sorry.
Let me touch it a little.
- I said not yet!
- So sorry.
Look, you can see inside.
I can't resist any longer!
- Don’t lick that!!
- Sorry.
I've rewarded you too much.
Wrap this around your waist.
- Is this the legendary one?
- Yes, it is.
Does this cost extra? Is that okay?
- Hurry.
- Yes.
- Blow on that!
- I can't!
- Hurry!
- Please forgive me!
No! it looks like its gonna pop!
It's overflowing!
I'm already overflowing!
- I can't do anything anymore!
- Come here!
Come here, I'll give you a reward.
I'll give you a reward.
If I do that, I won't be human!
Blow it!
Here we go!
Please extend the time!
Please extend it until I die!
Until I die!
Now I'm going to whip you.
You're going to do that now?
- That no longer works for my body.
- Come on!
- Please spit in my eyes.
Sorry.
I laughed.
- It's a terrible proclivity.
- You seem to like this kind of thing too.
- No.
This seems to make masochists laugh.
Yes, me and Matsumoto-san had laugh.
Who?
Hello?
I just got home.
What I do now is none of your business.
I'm alone now, so I have nothing to do.
I'm going to play alone now.
Leave me alone.
Formula 1 starts now.
I'm hanging up.
...Fuck you.
I'd like to play with this, imagining Formula 1 alone.
The McLaren is in the starting position and the cars following behind.
I love it when these turn like this.
I love to catch up like this and do 400 to 500 km/h in the second half of the race.
I don't want anyone to see this.
I love this part.
At the starting line I turn this thing on.
Yes, from here it's a straight line to the finish line.
From here!
In a battle of 500 to 600 km/h, McLaren is going to get passed.
But McLaren will catch them from here!
From here!
That's enough!
"That's enough"?
Everything is already enough!
There's no stopping them! I can't finish!
My adrenaline is pumping!
I have work after this, but I don't care!
It's rare in this day and age, but I shave so much.
I have to do this.
And I'm going to end up crashing.
That's end up crashing.
And it starts here.
- What are you doing?
- What the hell.
That was awesome!
What the hell is this punchline?
You thought I was going to get a weird haircut, didn't you?
It's neat.
Surprisingly.
Surprisingly neat!
That's fun!
- He also recovered at the end.
- Yeah.
How much is it in the end?
- Thank you!
- There were some worrisome parts along the way, but...
- You rank right up there with TKO's Kinoshita.
Bad luck!
It's bad luck!
Give me a break!
It's just a coincidence.
Don't say that.
Someone please add 1,000 yen! Please!
- I don't want to be like him!
- That is an injustice.
I don't want to be like him!
Sure, you used a plastic bottle.
You right.
But that's not the case.
I just made a sound with that thing.
That was great at the end.
I saw you as Jack Nicholson.
Nobody calls me Jack Nicholson.
It was good.