First time-
It's my first time meeting them
Go fish, and then come apologise to me
Once again at Lake Yamanaka, 15th Fishing Competiton!
Endo caught the first fish
Then Itoi
Then,
Matusmoto and Ichihara double hit!
Woah what the hell?
You both caught it
Ehhh what?!
Miraculously, Matsumoto and Ichihara caught the same fish!
Woah amazing!
It's not big enough to fight over...
Allow the youngsters to have it
Then yeah the youngsters...
Ichihara catches one thanks to Matsumoto's kindness
Iseya Yusuke catches a bass for the first time in his life
Are you kidding me?!
This time,
they are off to a good start,
However, Mokomichi and Hamada haven't caught anything!
What will happen?!
I WINNNNN!!!!
Typeset by kannibleklown
Subbed by senor_wristband
No no no no no no
We don't know yet idiot!
I didn't see anything
Fishing Competition: Whoever catches the biggest fish wins
Only you and Mokomichi have not caught anything
Seriously?
Heipo come help me out
Hmm?
You better cut it out man
There's fish here Hamada-san
You better let that one go
There's fish here for sure
Asano, you......
I can win with this!
What the hell man?!
The excited Asano has caught 3 already!
It's outrageous I haven't caught a single one
You bastards caught big ones too...
Meanwhile, next to the desperate Hamada
Got one!
The first timer Iseya,
Big one?
It's a big one!
Catches his second one!
Seriously...
Goddammit he almost dropped it!
Sorry!
He almost dropped just now
Shit that was close!
Bass fishing is so easy huh?
Right, Hamada-san?
Eh eh what?
Meanwhile, on Matsumoto's boat
Okuda HIT!!
I've started catching them
This is...
That's a good one
Here you come!
Long one!
He is really "Fishing"
I see, he is really "Fishing"
Meanwhile, the fishless Hamada...
But then...
Woah, all of a sudden?!
HELL YEAHHH!!!
So sudden!
Finally I got it goddamn
You got one huh?
Congratulations!
Don't patronise me!
No no no
For now, this is the best I can do
So now only Mokomichi is left
Yeah
Got one
Ichihara got one
That looks like a big one
It's really fighting you!
Did Ichihara catch a big one?
Come on!
You got it!
NICE!
Huge!
Amazing
( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)
Let me see - It's so big!
Amazing
This is so big!
Damn it! It's so big!
It's so heavy!
Nice!
I keep getting more depressed
C'mon, let's get 1st, 2nd, and 3rd from this boat
Seriously
I'll try my best
Endo who enocourages Mokomichi,
suddenly,
Got one
Ahh come on
Alright
Thank you very much
Mokomichi, thank you
What do I do if the fish aren't coming?
This is bad
OK! Got my third one
That tall Mokomichi looks so small now
That confident, tall looking Mokomichi,
Looks so small now
Just wait until the end of the competition
Yeah you're right
He seems pretty frustrated
Suddenly, awkward singing from these two
OK Everyone!
Can we have your attention for a moment
This is a small break time
You will all enjoy this lakeside live performance!
OK~
Let's begin!
Who is that?
A woman?
"Tairyo Matsuri" huh?
Original Song is by Sakura Maya
Tairyo Matsuri (Big-Fishing Festival)
Singer: Yamasaki Housei
"Hokke mo hotate mo ataridoshi"
It's a good year for scallops and mackerel
"kotoshi wa kegani mo yoku toreta"
Horsehair Crab was also bountiful
"Hontouni to-chan"
From the bottom of my heart father,
"arigatou~"
Thank you~
"matsuri no taki ga"
The festival drums,
"don don to yureru"
are thumping 'don don'
"hama-ja happi no yanshu ga"
The happi clad herring fishermen,
"mikoshi katsui-de iwai bushi"
are celebrating with their palanquin shrine (Mikoshi)
"Yaren Soran tairyou da"
It's a 'Yaren Soran' big-catch (folk song)
"yaren soran matsuri da yo"
It's a yaren soran festival
Soran (x4)
"tairyou matsuri"
Big-Catch Festival
He laughed at the end
He laughed right at the end
Thank you very much
As well, everyone
This time, you can enjoy one more special guest
Please turn your attention to over there!
Tsubaki-sama is here
Singer: Tsubaki Oniyakko
TN: I have no idea what she's saying lmfao
I don't understand
Scary
Why this song?
Amazing!
Is this even English?
What an idiot
She's putting her all into it
I like how she's ignoring us
This is amazing
She sucks, she's doing a normal performance
Only I haven't caught anything?
Seriously
Everyone has caught something
Below this, below this is a big one
Besides the sweating Mokomichi
Ichihara HIT!!
This one is really pulling
Ah it got caught like that
Mokomichi do your best!
I shall
Itadakimasu
Eh did you get one?
I think so
Me too
All three got a simultaneous hit!!
I got a small one
It's quite...
All three of us got one?
AHHHH
Matsumoto unfortunately...
Mine's is coming
Damn I wish all three of us got it
Yeah
I got mine ... my apologies
It's big
Looks like a good one
Got a good one again
This one is not bad...
Right? What a specimen
It's a bit on the short side
People are similiar to fish, huh?
It's like that
It sounds like we're talking about dicks
Got one! Got one!
The fish are really coming
Outrageous
Thank you very much
Ahh he got one!
Mokomichi finally gets a hit!!
Mokomichi let it go!
It could be a big one
Damn it!!!!
Finally ...
Well Done! Mokomichi's first catch!
Thank you very much
Got one
Keep up this excitement
Using this excitement
I'm catching a bunch
Got one!
Excellent fisherman Ichihara, once again!
Again? Seriously?
That guy says "Got one!" too much
I can hear his "Got one!" the most clearly
His catch rate is amazing
Can't even keep track of them
There's not enough room in the fish tank
Just release it then
Not enough room...
You caught so many you have to release that one?
So cool
He's releasing it cause there's not enough room
He caught so many he has to release some
This guy
God I hate that!
This is messed up
All you need to win is a big one
I want to win
A manly resolve aiming only for victory
That Hamada...
Shit did I get one?!
That branch flew like "PIIIIN"
Got one
At any rate, today he shall fish! Endo hit!!
I caught this without any bait
Without bait?
Oh you got one
Then Mokomichi as well
This one is fighting a lot
Thank you very much
OK!
Amazing
Matsumoto changes his lure at the pier
Will he get results?
It's hard to tell when you've got one here
I was surprised when I got one
There's no splashing?
See?
Ehh what?
That was fast!
And it's on the bigger side too
Oh crap me too
Which is this?
That was quick!
It's big
HUGE!
I WINNN!!!!!!
No no no no we don't know yet
Isn't this huge?!
Look at it!
Outrageous...
Looking at this I gotta say, did we need the boats?
C'mon c'mon c'mon
No drama at all
Hmm?
You haven't lost a catch yet
Got it!
I'm taking this lightly
It's coming
You caught it
That is...
It's a small one
Okayyyy got it
Me too
I got one too here
What the hell is this?
After dad takes a bath you,
you'd find something like this floating in there
oHhh it's coming it's coming
Oh me too
Iseya gets one at the pier
Did you catch mine?
I think so
Ah you caught mine
Alright I got it
You can catch it like that huh?
How many have you caught?
It's only my 3rd one
You really caught it huh?
I really caught-
You dropped it!
Idiot
Unfortunately, he lost his 3rd catch
What the hell Moko-chan
Mokomichi quickly catches his 3rd fish!
How much longer till we finish?
30 more minutes
Oh really
You're all fishinga lot
Yeah you're right
There's just one event leftover
Of course yeah
That father right?
That's not a father
That grandfather right?
Yes that grandfather
Ah, I see
I haven't seen that old man today yet
Right at this moment...
John
John is right over there
JoHHHn!
It is time for refreshments
For the refreshments, we have a special guest
The special guest ... Is this person!
Creepy
That's creepy
A Namahage? (folklore character)
Somehow, $!$!@# dat fiding, s!@$ real one!
gahaha!
What the hell did he say?
The end, the , the ending, for the ending,
TN: Not sure I translated this properly
Keep fishing to the end
I brought snacks for you guys
Ahh thank you
Please, take some snacks
Eh? You don't want any?
No we do,
You need to come closer
Yes Heipo, it's snack time after all
Can you bring the boat closer?
We don't want to hit their boat
Exactly
WAIT WAIT
Wait!
What the hell are you doing?!
Oh man the snacks...
I told you to take the snacks!
What did you say?
What are you doing Heipo-san?
I told Hamada-san "take the snacks"!
I took them!
That's enough
Matsumoto-san, snacks!
No I don't want them they're sopping wet
Eat them please!
Let's bring you back in
Deep! DEEEP!
What?
Deep! It's deep!
Deep?
Let's bring you back in
Come on back
What does he mean by deep?
How old are you again?
Fifty-Four...
Heipo is interested in what's under Yamasaki's skirt
I want to see that. I don't want to see that
That's creepy Heipo san
You're getting excited!
I like that~
Fishing restarts with a fresh mood
That's another one huh?
You got one?
The guys in caps sure can fish
I didn't catch that many
No, no...
Asano catches his 4th one!
It makes me happy just to catch one
You're so goddamn motivated
There's some here
Oh that's amazing
Seriously?
I picked a lucky spot
I literally just caught one
You bastard....
What happened this year?
Time up for fishing
Who will win the competition?
So, Matsumoto-san
The battle is over
Yes
We're just waiting for Yamasaki and Tanaka to finish showering
They had some greasy sweat today
I see
They have to take a shower, yes
That's why huh?
It's going to rain soon
Yes the weather is,
does not look very good
See
They're walking on two legs already
You just got out of the shower huh?
Literally just took one
Let's continue, time to find the results!
Well done everyone!
Well done!
I've heard good things about today
I think we all did well
That's what we've heard
You all went at it today
First, Shigesato-san!
Shigesato-san
He has a ton of fish
No way!
Big ones too
You caught so many
He did pretty good
They're so big!
They're big yeah
This is the 8th one right?
Thirty? Hold on please
It's 37!
37 centimetres!
This is impressive
Tamio-san!
Tamio-san's turn
Everyone caught so many
6 of them
Tamio-san, thirty-five centimetres!
What the hell
Ahh that's no good
Not the winner
This one, this one
Masatoshi-kun, thirty-seven!
Thank you very much!
Masatoshi-kun?
Even though he used his first name...
Next, Mokomichi-kun
Moko-chan did good at the end
What do we think of this size?
You will pick yourself?
So responsible
It's moving around
Amazing
34.5
Okayy that's great!
I apologise
Iseya
Yusuke-kun
First timer
You did good for your first time
Really?
Look! Look at that fat one!
This is...
Disgusting
It's cute!
It's full of stuff
This is a black bass?
This is disgusting
Let's measure this
So fat
Amazing
Creepy!
What did this thing eat?
So creepy
This is... 35 centimetres
Thirty five!
Tadanobu-kun
This one, this one
This is .....
Pick one please
They look the same
That one, that one
This is a big one!
How big?
Wow! This is...
39?
Hold on AHHH!!
Did it pass 37?
It passed! THIRTY EIGHT CENTIMETRES!
Impressive!
That is huge!
So, only three left
The first you caught was big right?
The very first one
It was big
HUUUGEEE!!!
That is massive!
So big!
It's big, right?
If this wins, what the hell was the point of the second half
So let's measure this one
It's over 40
Over 40
Eh?! Forty-Five?!
Forty Five!
YESS!!!
Endo-san 45!
YESS! I might win this!
I got a good one!
Hitoshi-kun!
Ahh Matsumoto-san!
How many did I catch?
How-WOW
It's so big!
That one
This one huh?
The fifth one
Matsuomto, miraculously!
Why didn't you say Matsumoto-san?
36.5
You might as well say 37 I'm not winning anyways
Get the hell out of the way please
So rude
So that means
Last one
It's just this one
This is it
Last one, lets go
Hold on
Woahh it's huge!
This is close
Hold on
How big?
Woahhh!
50?
It's bigger
It's 49 right?
Forty Nine!!!!
Amazing!
So that means
So big
The winner is
Ichihara Hayato-kun!!
Congratulations on 49!
49!
Congratulations!
15th fishing compeition, winner Ichihara Hayato
This is the final scoreboard