Silent Library - Second Half!
On tonight's Gaki No Tsukai we'll see
the second half of Silent Library
Guest
Hakamada Yoshihiko
Let's rewatch the best punishments with our guest Hakamada
A review of the first half
HAVEN'T WATCHED PART ONE YET?
YOU CAN FIND IT ON
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
Endo
Rice spoon on forehead
First half's punishments
Hakamada
Oral cracker
I'm so scared
First half's punishments
It's fine, just open up
Don't forget the tongue
Ready? Don't forget your tongue
Three, two, one...
No way
No friggin' way
The impact was way stronger than imagined
Hosei & Tanaka
Static electricity kiss
First half's punishments
This is the worst
He's too tall
It's making things worse
Oh shit
Not yet
Shut up!
*toot*
Huh?
He just farted
What the...
He farted!
Endo
Hamburger Set Mix Drink
First half's punishments
Why do you have to do this?
Let me eat it normally...
There's also a cola
I don't think we can air this
I agree
I'm freaking out
Matsumoto
Ping Pong Smash in the Face
Wait a sec
First half's punishments
Ouch!
Oh shit!
That was a strong one
D*ck missile
Hosei
Too far! Too far! Too far!
First half's punishments
Scary
Too much
It's way too far! Too far!
I'm scared for him
Here comes
Get ready
3... 2... 1... Go!
So fast
Hakamada
Old Dude's Freshly Removed Pants
First half's punishments
He's so unlucky
Yeah
What now? Should he sit?
Really?
It reeks!
Hakamada!
Don't move
He's not coming back
It stinks!
Is this the return of Hentai Kamen?
hentai kamen (masked pervert) has returned
It stinks!
SECOND HALF
And now our six men will face even harsher punishments!
He got run over!
It didn't jump
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SHION
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI ~ TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI ~ KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
THIS IS PART TWO OF A TWO-PARTS EPISODE
MAKE SURE TO WATCH PART ONE FIRST!
Downtown's
Gaki no Tsukai
ya Arahende!
That was impressive
It's too much
Ultra-spicy humidifier
How can this one be fine?
topic
It's one of those...
What the hell is a spicy humidifier?
Really...
Please
You go first, Yamazaki and Tanaka
Sure
Let's see...
This one
Ready?
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Finally!
Matsumoto
Shh
Ultra-spicy humidifier
Finally, finally!
Alright, alright!
Gimme a break...
Here comes
Enough...
Enough with the unknown stuff...
Instead of water, the humidifier has been filled with tabasco
I hate stuff like this
The unknown ones, I hate them
Enough already
Eh? What now? I'm scared
You gotta get closer
Do we have to get him closer?
Forward
Your face goes here
Move forward
Push him hard
Like this, yes
Really?
Let's turn it on
Has it started?
It stinks!
Oh shi-
Oh man, it stings
The hell was that?!
Oh crap, it's so strong
That was incredible
Unprecedented
My nose hurts
Liquid nitrogen time bomb (☠ x2)
What's this now?
Huh? What the-?
What is this?!
Liquid nitrogen time bomb
topic
I've had enough...
Why is he choosing for us? Geez...
Let's start with your side, shall we?
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Ready and...
I don't want to!
Come on, man...
It wasn't on purpose, I swear
His luck is really something
His pull rate is incredible
I can't help it
Your turn now
Countdown, please
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Three, two...
I'm so glad
Hakamada & Tanaka
Liquid nitrogen time bomb
Shh
Oh no...
You share the same height
You're right
I can't do this
It's fine, it's fine
We can't do much about it
What's this?
Move forward
In front of the desk
It's this guy again
Prof. Ichioka Genki
Yonemura Denjiro's disciple
It's him again
Oh boy, this looks freaky
See? Same height
Right
What a coincidence
It's dangerous if you move too much
It's liquid nitrogen
Ugh... watch out please
You're right, their height is just fine
I told you so
Now you see it too
You were right
I'm way shorter than both of them
It would have been awkward to film
Yeah, right
Oh...
What now?
What is he doi--- whoa, scary!
Ugh, that's scary
This is freaky
Eh? What is---?
This is really scary...
What's this for?
It's gonna explode
For real?
I don't know when
What now?
Huh? Again?
Oh, I get it
They're gonna hold it?
Don't move around too much
I won't
I have no idea why he's doing this all over again
It's about time
What's his deal?
I think it's almost done
I don't like this
Looks dangerous
It is
Can I say it?
Alright, here we go
3... 2... 1... Go!
W--wait!
Wha--
Scary scary scary
This is scary
What is...?
Huh?
What?
Eh?
Huh?
It's not bursting at all
Is this normal?
What?
What are they doing?
Huh?
What?
Nothing's happening, what's going on?
Is this a failed experiment?
Huh?
It's not exploding
Holy crap
It went to their lower back
It took forever
It took so long for it to burst
For a moment I thought it wasn't planned
Me too
How was it?
Is your back fine?
I fell on my butt
You did?
He fell on his butt
That much?
They both flew away
What exactly happened?
It's the liquid nitrogen
The cooled-down, shrunken air inside the balloon was warmed
up by the liquid nitrogen, which made it expand and explode
For a second I thought "let's just do this again from scratch"
Yeah, I thought that too
There's still more
This is never going to end
Really
Whole body electric machine
Oh no
Enough with all of this...
Whole body electric machine
topic
I don't like this one
Seriously Hakamada, you do it
Please, draw the skull
What the hell did ya come here for!?
You can pick your card first, you didn't do it before
Pick it and flip it
Just flip it already
Hakamada
Tanaka
Ready?
Flip them
You gotta be kidding me
Tanaka & Hakamada
Really?!
Ready? One, two...
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Hamada
Shh
Whole body electric machine
Yes yes yes
YES, YES, YES
Electroshock again...
Do I have to do this?
Don't shout too much
It's an electric machine
Hamada in pure agony!
THIS EPISODE WAS BROUOGHT TO YOU BY SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
TRANSLATION BY SHION | TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
[TO SKIP: 9:57]
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!
Special episode!
Oogiri Daigassen Special!!
The first Oogiri Daigassen in 8 years!
Think about your juniors!!
An unfair and unsquare comedy battle!!
Team Matsumoto challenges Team Miyasako
At 11:00 P.M.
Downtown's
Gaki no Tsukai
March 25th (sun)
Special episode!
ya Arahende!
Get ready for Gaki no Tsukai's special episode, on 3/25, 11:00 P.M.!
Hamada
Whole body electric machine
Whoa, what's that?!
This looks terrifying
This is so scary
Don't hit him
Violence is no good
Don't use violence, sorry
Are you kidding me? What's this?
These guys are doing their jobs
Looks bad...
Eh? What are you supposed to do with that?
He's talking so normally
Huh?
I'm freaking out, man
Keep quiet please
Don't raise your voice
We're in a library
Eh?!
Don't shout please
5 electric machines are placed on him
They're putting so much stuff on him...
I really hate this
The hell are you doin'?
Well, it's for the whole body
It's full-body, you know
There's a lot of things to put on
Did you place one on my butt?
It's full-body after all
There's still more
Just let them do it
What?
My neck?
Of course, your entire body
Maybe it's better to have one there
How can it be?!
So it won't be tense, you know
Are you kidding me?
What the--?
Not done yet
It's their job, treat them well
Huh? My stomach?
Is it ok to do it on my stomach?
Now you're all set
The entire body
Are you really making me do this?
Shut up
It's not on yet
I mean-- wait a sec
Matsumoto, press the button on the count of 3
You gotta press that
I'm not joking, this is not ok
I have no idea how it's gonna be
Make it weak, ok?!
Three...
Two...
Really, set it to weak
Three...
Does it have an option for it?
Two...
It doesn't
That thing...
There's only this one
Oh? Only one?
That's weird, it should have that setting
Set it to weak, pleas--
Electricity
This looks freaky
It hurts so bad!
Ouch
Scary scary scary scary
Switch it off, it's still going
Is it?
See?
Stop pressing it!
I'm not pressing it
Whaat?!
Electricity
Oh man
He's in pain
Please
What's going on?
I can't I can't I can't
It hurts so bad
%$&
@#%!&△〇
I would hate this so much
It's the worst
Yeah, it sucks
Enough with that
No more electric machines, please
Holy shit...
It's finally over
Don't hurt him
Just stop, it's fine
Tanaka?
Who---
Who got the least punishments?
What's next?
Endo  2 times
Tanaka  4 times
I got it twice
Hakamada  4 times
Matsumoto  2 times
Hamada  2 times
Hosei  2 times
Me too
Same here
It's pretty balanced
You too?
We're all getting it today
You sure?
And now we're all talking like normal
Shh, we're in a library
We gotta keep quiet
Let's move on
Large-breed dog licking action
Come on...
What the hell...
Large-breed dog licking action
topic
Isn't this enough?
Please go first, Hamada
Alright then, like this
Ready?
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Hamada
Large-breed dog licking action
Shh
That's ok
There's nothing we can do about it
Senpai, please
Senpai
Thanks so much
Thank you, senpai
Thank you
On your knees
Kneel down, please
This will be on your face
Salted butter to smear on his face
What are you doing?!
It's just butter
It's butter
Come on, don't do this...
The whole face
It smells so good
Who cares about the smell
It smells really good
Isn't this too much?
You're looking cute
So cute
Very cute
Cutie
Lookin' good
On the nose too
All set
Now he looks so good
Ok
We're done
Here it comes
Here it is
Oh no... please no...
It's so cute
I'm scared
Come on, it's cute
It's so cute
I'm sure it's hungry
Cute!
It's scared
'Cause he's too yummy
I'm the scared one here
Too yummy...?
I don't like this---
Good boy, lick it all off
Nice and clean, ok?
Lick to your heart's content
It's all gone already
Lick some more
That was very quick
He's so clean now
Incredible
Can't believe it
Right
Clean in a blink of an eye
Look at its tail
It's happy
Look at him
Completely
All cleaned up
It's taking its time
And it's still going on
He's all clean
It's so interested in him
It's wiggling its tail so much
It's so happy
And it's done, nice huh?
Just look at it
It's going for the butter
It wants more of it
Let's put it aside
It's there
C'mere boy
It cleaned me up
Yeah, isn't that good?
I better not lick it myself
Yeah
That wasn't bad
Yeah, you're right
It was cute
It's just a nice dog
I wouldn't have minded it
Man I'm tired
We've done so much today, can't we just stop?
Hang in there
We even got to feed a dog
A lot of variation in this episode
Way too much, I'd say
Let's see the next one
Nail drop on palm
Wha-?
What is this?
What's this now?
Nail drop on palm
topic
So irritating...
There are too many new things today
Wow
Why are we doing this?
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready and...
No way
What?!
Hamada
Nail drop on palm
Shh
Thank you, God
This is proof that God exists, thank you
Please, Hamada, go over there
It's him again, I'm scared of him
By the time you see this guy, you know it's about science
Am I right?
That's right
A terrifying punishment!
One...
Hamada
Nail drop on palm
Like that? Really?
Like this?
This is seriously scary
Don't move an inch
What?!
Really, if you move here they're gonna stab you
Don't do it
Don't move
I'm freaking out so much
Those things are huge
What are those nails?!
Too long
Wait---
So long...
I'm scared as hell
Stay still, don't move
We don't want you to get hurt
Is it all ready now?
Here we go, Hamada
Don't move
3... 2... 1...
It grazed me a bit
Holy shit!!
He's right!
It's almost in
So close!
Maybe you were shaking
so much you moved it a bit?
This is so freaky
It's getting dangerous
This is too much
It's dangerous
Not a single scratch here, I'm fine
It would've been better if there was blood so we could quit
Geez...
Seriously, I've had enough
We're not done yet?
Really, let's stop
I want this to end
Really, that's enough
There's still more...
Still more...?
Bicycle run-over
What now...
What the-?
"Bicycle"...?
Enough...
Bycicle run-over
topic
We're gonna die if we do that
He's right
Man, today's stuff is so bad
Run over by a bicycle?
What's the deal with this episode?
It's too much
The authors are gonna hear from me later
This can't be good
This isn't ok
This time it'll work
Oh my
Let's get over this
Ready? Two, one...
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
No way...
Bicycle run-over
Shh
Tanaka
Well, that's how it is
He's perfect for this
Am I?!
Is he really...?
For getting run over?
He just snapped
I'm not angry
It's rare to see him punished at the end
Whoa, I'm scared
Ok, all set
It's one of those, isn't it?
This is gonna hurt
Oh? From there?
I know these
Over here?
This must be a joke
This will hurt for sure
Yeah I mean, he's getting run over
Oh, here he comes
Oh shit
Oh my...
Careful
Can we rely on him?
See?
He's not at his best
Today's not his day, Tanaka
He's not in shape
Brace yourself, he's coming
Whoa, wait---
He's not feeling good
Wait-
Wait a sec-
Not yet I guess
And now he's back
This is so scary
He knows he's gonna get run over
Careful there
Maybe he's going to stop?
Like, first he charges him and then stops?
Watch out!
He ran him over!
He didn't stop
Well, after all...
It was written here
He didn't brake!
He ran him over
No brakes at all
I see...
My junior got run over
Not a brake
It was clearly written there
That's right
He raised the front wheel and ran him over with the other
Today my boy got run over
It hurts
You can see the tire's mark
You're right
It's a clear hit
Last one!
Is it really?
Yeah
Isn't it about time for Hakamada to shine?
He's right, do something
I mean, he's the guest and all
Yeah, a grand finale
For the last one
But we don't know what we'll get
Endless grated yam
What the--
topic
Here's a dumb one
Is it gonna be a shower?
Well, yeah
You bet it is
An unexpected tragedy on their last punishment!
Not this one...
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!
Again?!
Hey I've subbed this ad before!
Here's the same ad you've just seen before!
Visit shionnotsukai.wordpress.com!!
Remember to show your support!!
If you feel like it, hit like on my FB page!
Downtown's
Gaki no Tsukai
Showing support is important!
THIS IS JAPANESE
We need your support to sub more!
ya Arahende!
How about leaving a nice comment for Kedomas's work? <3
Endless grated yam
topic
One by one? Fine by me
Let's flip it one by one, ok?
Let's see
Alright, flip it
Here I go
Please...
Tanaka
Alright!!
Oh yeah
God, I don't want this
I have a bad feeling about it
One of this kind was still missing
Come on
You're right
Let's get this over with
I still don't want to do this
I beg you
Please
Hosei
Alright!!
Wanna go now, Matsumoto?
Or Endo?
Me?
I have no idea what to do...
Just pick one
I don't really want to get this one
Come on, Endo
Go for it
Here goes nothing
Please spare me
Endo
Endless grated yam
Shh
Something's wrong
That's not how it's supposed to be
It should have been Hakamada here
Why me now?!
This sucks in so many ways
I know
But we can't help it
It shouldn't have been me and you know it
Yeah, but...
That's not fair
You're right
You have to keep on eating a big quantity of grated yam
which is going to be poured down in your mouth
That's pure bad luck
You gotta be kidding me...
Come on
Lay down here
Like this
Ehh? Gimme a break...
You gotta lay down exactly under it
Maybe we can use Hakamada to measure it
What do you mean?!
What the--?
Oh, you think so?
What does that mean?
I see, let's check how it is first...
Hakamada--- I'm gonna do this
I'm really going to, but before that
Just lay down here
So I can get how it works
We gotta make sure it works
Size and everything
Then you can tell Endo where to lie
That's right, it's a matter of size
Sorry for this, I swear I'm doing it
I don't know the size of it
It's just for a second
If I see it on him, I'll get it
Your mouth should be under this
How is it? Good?
Lower, a bit lower than this
How about now?
A bit more
Is this spot alright?
I think it's ok
Let's pour some down to check
Yeah, just a lil bit
Just a bit of it
Make sure it goes to your mouth
Ah, is that how it is?
Open up
Just like that, it works
Now I see
That's how it works, here comes
Let's pour some more
It's falling straight down to his mouth
Stay still
So that's how it is...
This---
Aren't you ready to swap in, Endo...?
Now I know how I'm supposed to do it
He's eating a lot
We know how it is now
What do you think Endo? Wanna do it?
Ohh, I see how it is...
Can you do it?
It's coming out
It's everywhere
Ohh, looking good
I see, I see
Still not done yet?
He's so good
He can eat more
How are you doing?
He's good at piling up
There's still room for it
Eat some more
Oh, shut up
#"&%°
Ok
There's still half of it left
&$!%#
He's doing well, isn't he?
Oh, he calmed down
He's breathing
It stopped
Wanna go on?
He's so calm now
See? That's how you have to do it
I see, that's how I'll do it
Next time
Next time?!
Thanks so much
We learned a lot
Thank you for teaching it to me
So that's how it works...
Alright, we're going home
Wait!!
Stay like this
Yeah, you'd make a mess
Why?!
Sorry for this
You're gonna make a mess
Thank you so much
Don't make a mess here
Switch that thing off!
It's fine
Hope we can meet again
W-wait
You're gonna be famous, Hakamada
That's for sure
Somebody!
Somebody help me!
Stop the yam!
"Stop the yam"...
The yam--
'Scuse me sir
You, over there
Someone
Stop the yam!
They'll ignore him
It's gonna itch so bad
No doubt about it
TRANSLATION BY SHION | TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS | MORE EPISODES
AT SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM | FOLLOW ME ON SOCIAL MEDIA:
TWITTER.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI // FB.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI | IF YOU
WANT TO SUPPORT MY TRANSLATIONS, LIKE MY FB PAGE AND LEAVE SO
ME FEEDBACK! YOU CAN ALSO DONATE FEW $ (IF YOU WANT TO) ON MY
KO-FI PAGE (KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI) OR BY BECOMING A PATRON
ON PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
Most punishment members: Tanaka & Hakamada (5 times)
The harshest Silent Library in history