0 0 m -220.625 -66.25 b -228.5 -67.875 -249.875 -66.25 -247.625 -42.25 b -248.75 -28.75 -227.375 -1.75 -221.75 -0.375 b -212.75 7.5 -209.375 -1.75 -203.75 -3.375 b -197 -12.25 -190.25 -15.375 -183.5 -37.875 b -181.25 -58.75 -195.875 -60.375 -197 -61.75 b -206 -67.875 -213.875 -66.25 -220.625 -66.25 m -215 -58.75 b -204.875 -61.75 -191.375 -52.875 -193.625 -43.75 b -201.5 -55.875 -208.25 -55.875 -215 -58.75 m -272.375 -190.875 b -267.875 -190.875 -229.625 -180.375 -235.25 -111.25 b -243.125 -67.875 -264.5 -46.75 -271.25 -42.25 b -274.625 -40.875 -292.625 -21.25 -317.375 -52.875 b -323 -67.875 -334.25 -84.25 -326.375 -121.75 b -323 -136.75 -317.375 -165.375 -297.125 -181.75 b -291.5 -186.25 -282.5 -193.75 -272.375 -190.875 m -171.125 -193.75 b -168.875 -193.75 -141.875 -204.25 -118.25 -148.75 b -114.875 -135.375 -105.875 -118.75 -111.5 -76.75 b -118.25 -42.25 -129.5 -40.875 -136.25 -37.875 b -141.875 -37.875 -149.75 -28.75 -176.75 -54.25 b -185.75 -64.75 -199.25 -70.875 -204.875 -112.875 b -203.75 -112.875 -217.25 -139.75 -189.125 -181.75 b -183.5 -187.875 -177.875 -193.75 -171.125 -193.75 m -274.625 -144.25 b -306.125 -136.75 -288.125 -90.375 -273.5 -94.75 b -269 -94.75 -258.875 -97.875 -256.625 -118.75 b -260 -142.875 -266.75 -141.25 -274.625 -144.25 m -274.625 -130.875 b -267.875 -133.75 -264.5 -121.75 -265.625 -118.75 b -265.625 -106.75 -272.375 -106.75 -275.75 -106.75 b -280.25 -108.375 -282.5 -114.25 -281.375 -121.75 b -281.375 -124.75 -279.125 -130.875 -274.625 -130.875 m -272.375 -124.75 b -275.75 -123.375 -274.625 -117.25 -272.375 -117.25 b -270.125 -117.25 -267.875 -123.375 -272.375 -124.75 m -163.25 -144.25 b -188 -138.375 -176.75 -91.75 -163.25 -96.25 b -158.75 -94.75 -147.5 -97.875 -147.5 -124.75 b -150.875 -142.875 -159.875 -144.25 -163.25 -144.25 m -163.25 -130.875 b -148.625 -130.875 -153.125 -106.75 -161 -106.75 b -163.25 -105.375 -172.25 -108.375 -170 -121.75 b -170 -124.75 -168.875 -130.875 -163.25 -130.875 m -161 -124.75 b -164.375 -121.75 -162.125 -115.875 -159.875 -117.25 b -156.5 -118.75 -158.75 -124.75 -161 -124.75 m -276.875 -117.25 b -279.125 -117.25 -278 -112.875 -276.875 -112.875 b -275.75 -112.875 -274.625 -117.25 -276.875 -117.25 m -164.375 -115.875 b -166.625 -115.875 -165.5 -111.25 -164.375 -111.25 b -163.25 -111.25 -162.125 -115.875 -164.375 -115.875 m -334.25 -217.875 l -104.75 -217.875 l -104.75 86.875 l -334.25 86.875 m -107 -214.75 l -332 -214.75 l -332 84 l -107 84
TPF
The first annual Gaki no Tsukai Arahende Chiki Chiki, Bet it all on this mouthful
You're so loud
for 100,000 yen, Kiki Tomato Juice!
Wasn't he loud?..
Wasn't he really loud?
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Yeah, your voice was really loud today
It really was
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
You really were loud today
We have been doing this for more than 20 years you know...
No, your voice has gotten louder and louder
No, we're saying this because
it's louder than usual
You never used to be this loud even...
Right then
Everyone, it's tomato juice, how are we feeling?
But Hamada-san, you don't like tomatoes, do you
That's right
I mean, I will like, lick it
But he loves ketchup..
Oh really, do you?
I wouldn't say I love it...
But I am happy to eat ketchup is what you mean
No no no, like with anything
I don't always use it or anything
this is the same thing as ketchup
Yeah
This isn't sweet though!
Ketchup is really sweet
Is that something for a 50 year old man to say?
"It's nice because it's sweet" he says...
From the 10
find the tomato juice you drank
The rules are really simple
Just find the tomato juice that you drank from the ten available
Get it right and receive 100,000 Yen
Who will get the prize?
Get it right and receive 100,000 Yen. Who will win the prize?
I mean, you always go first
Yeah
so Tanaka, you go first
Oh okay, then I will go first
And do you drink tomato juice frequently?..
No I hardly ever drink this
Like seriously
I think it's nearly been 10 years since I drank one...
It's a lie, right? He's lying  right?
It's a lie
It's a lie, right? He's lying, right?
There it is, a lie!!
No no!
That's taking it too far
Your cowardliness has shown itself
No no!
After saying something like that...
First Challenger
Tanaka Naoki
Being accused of being a coward, Tanaka goes first
Choosing one is quite...
Yeah..
The first one is...
The one chosen for him is from Hokkaido, JA Biratori
Nispa's lover tomato juice unsalted
It's sweet, thick and rich
This taste, will he be able to distinguish it?
The scent is really...
The scent is really standard
Standard?
Can someone who hasn't drank one in 10 years
know what is a standard scent?
You shouldn't know
You're so full of it
Ittadakimasu
It's thick
Huh?
Tomato juice has always been...
It's so easy to drink
How was it 10 years ago?
It was way more difficult to drink
I mean even so
Yeah?
It felt maybe like Kagome-san's tomato juice...
Text
Tomato Juice Unsalted
That's what you feel?
Yes, I get the impression that...
Okay, I will start with this one
Toma-ju... That's what we used to call it in cafe's...
Yeah, they used to have it in the cafe's...
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Correct Answer
It always came with salt
Wrong!!
It's like 'Kiki yeah yeah' or something...
Like 'Kiki yeah yeah'
It's this different!
It's the start of his stage show
Really get the crowd engaged
Yeah, he's trying to engage them and all
This is amazing, it's so different, I'm so confident so I'm going for it
The one I drank was NOT Kagome's tomato juice
Correct!!
Really different?
It was so different
Bit weird
But it was like a difference from 100 to 0
It was this different!
I don't get what the hell you're on about
Not a clue
That's a weird comparison...
It was this different
Like 180 degrees different
Like if you were drinking water different?
Yeah
That's basically what you're saying right?
It really was,
So 9 more
Yeah, 9 more
That's right
You can do this
I'm going for Itouen's mature tomatoes
Mature tomatoes
Text
Because
When I really drank it
I felt the tomatoes
"When you really drank it"...
Yeah
I really felt the tomatoes
I see, I see
You know, Tanaka
He loves his mature women as well...
Yeah, he really does
Do I?
So he's a coward and likes mature women
Correct Answer
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
So he's a coward and likes mature women
Exactly
He steals other guy's old women too...
He just loves really old women...
Yeah..
At this point
like it's a bit weird
bit weird?..
It's possible to say it's not this one
Well obviously...
Go for it
You can do that
You can say that
No as in because the scent is different
Oh no, it's wrong
Damn!
I can get this!
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Correct Answer
Tanaka's confidence might be real
He distinguishes the subtle differences
and gets 4 in a row!
4 cleared in a row!!
Amazing
He's not had any doubts so far
Right?
Aeon!
Organic Tomato Juice unsalted
Text
Correct Answer
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Your one man show is so damn long
Yeah, he's doing his stage show
It's not a show
You have a complaint
It's not a show, I really want to get it right
Huh?
Hang on a minute
It's this one!!
No matter how many times I drink it, it's this one
Then hurry the hell up and go forward
Is it okay?
I did not think this would happen!
Seriously
But I'm going to get it right then
The one I drank was Aeon Organic Tomato Juice!
Incorrect!!
You didn't get it at all
He seemed so confident...
Here he comes
Damn he looks scary
He does
You shameful comedian just to the tomatoes!
Scary, that's scary, damn it
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on Youtube
individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own. Please go back and
support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit. You can
download episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching!
Mickstar
(Team Gaki)
Otviss
Translator:
Typesetter & Proofreader:
___________________________________________________________________________________
Get it right, get 100,000 yen Get it wrong, punishment
Kiki Tomato Juice
Kiki Tomato with the incentive of a prize
Hamada Masatoshi
Second Challenger
The challenger, Hamada
I don't think anyone has tried this one...
The one chosen for him is Aeon Top Value
It uses organic tomatoes
and concerns its product to taste fresh
Will he get it right?
I'm going to drink it
He said he was going to lick it anyway...
Look at that...
What's wrong with this guy?
Hamada hates tomato
Text
There's no way...
It's as Tanaka said, it's quite thick but it's
also quite thin
The ones with salt are easier to drink
I think...
That's true
But seriously
the whole 'tomato' factor has died down a bit
Well I've never drank so it so I'll go with the most basic Kagome...
Text
Tomato Juice unsalted
As you'd expect, he knows that Kagome is the most basic one...
Of course I do...
He was sniffing it so hard before...
It doesn't smell at all!
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Correct Answer
I doubt it doesn't smell at all...
But he said the one before was odourless...
I don't think this is right
The one before was odourless, seriously
If this is wrong
I'm going to flip the whole set over
Flip it all over...
The one I drank was NOT Kagome's tomato juice!
Correct!!
You're too slow
Hold on, hold on...
You got worried didn't you...
Yeah, I really did
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Correct Answer
Hamada got more confident, and gets 2 in a row!
2 cleared in a row!!
The one I drank was literally odourless
And the taste wasn't that...
He keeps saying that
But surely that can't be true
Yeah, you would think
Shall we go for another one...
Organic Tomato juice unsalted
Text
Correct
This is
I'm going for Aeon's...
Nope, I have no idea when I sniff it...
Even though he was sniffing it that much before...
He was sniffing it way longer than he actually tasted it..
That's true
Correct Answer
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
This one doesn't taste...
"This one doesn't taste"...
What kind of a thing is that to say?
What kind of a scene are you doing?
Ready, start...
"This one doesn't taste"...
But at the end, there's a little something...
The one before didn't do that...
Oh damn
This one's sooo similar
(Note: Using kansai dialect for added effect)
And out comes the Kansai dialect...
Hey, this one's really similar!!
Don't say it like you're telling someone
"Hey, your dogs ran off!"
He said it so many times to me in the past
This one is so hard!
"Hey, your dogs ran off!"
Matsumoto-san!!
It was so annoying
"Hey, your dogs ran off!!"
I always used to think "Why would he run away?"
I gave it food and all...
The last bit where the taste comes in is confusing me
Should I be going for it though...
It's just that last part confusing me
That last part...
I don't know
The one I drank was
NOT Aeon's organic tomato juice.
Incorrect!!
No way!
I knew it!
It was that one!
You were literally standing up there...
You came up to that point
Are you serious?
The aftertaste was a bit different...
This hurts so much...
Shall I pay your salary with tomatoes!?
I'm sorry
I got that one
Damn that's scary
Hold on a minute...
Body blow..
It really hurts, right?
So I was right?!
It was just as you said!
Aeon-san...
But seriously, you came up to here...
I thought "Oh, he's got this"...
Yeah, I did too
You picked it up at a great time too
If that's the case, then you should give me a hint like...
As if!!
Why the hell would I?
Endo Shozo
Third Challenger
Next, the chosen one for Endo...
Yamagata's Tackle Farm's Rozorio Silver
It's got a mellow sweetness and slightly creamy
Will he be able to distinguish the taste?
Oh man, I'm scared
I'm really scared...
Just give it to me normally...
OWWW!!
Wait, what...
Wait...
You'd never want that..
Come on..
You'd never want that done to you...
I'm scared
I can't concentrate at all...
We're bored with this Kiki Hamada game!
We know it's Hamada every time
It's so obvious...
Oh man, yeah...
It's very nice
It really is
It's really thick and creamy though
It's not refreshing, it kind of comes down slowly
Slow and creamy?..
Sorry...
He always does this
He loves doing this, the one finger...
Yeah
It's like the worst manner, hated by the whole world
So true...
I wonder what he plans on doing with that finger of his...
For crying out loud, he wiped it on himself...
This one uses 6 tomatoes, I'm going for Kagome's 'Sweet tomatoes'...
Sweet Tomato
Text
Damn he's quick.
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Correct Answer
He didn't say anything...
The one I drank
was NOT
concentration 10 sweet tomato...
Correct!!
That's a great pace
What's up Endo?
Keep it up, keep it up
He's doing well so far
No one's tried this one so far so..
Black Prince Juice
Text
Tomato with celebs
This one costs 15000 yen (£90)($136)...
Damn that's expensive!
He's going for ones that no one's tried yet
He's such a pro at Kiki...
You're going to get so full...
You're definitely going to feel sick later...
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Correct Answer
It's fantastic though, the taste
It's really delicious
It's like sauce
That's bad!
Not ketchup but
sauce?
What the hell?
Sauce?
It genuinely
tastes like Tonkatsu sauce!
Tonkatsu?!
That's awful! I don't want to drink a cup full of that
This is amazing
The one I drank was NOT Tomato with Celebs' Black
Prince Juice...
Correct!!
Oh wow
He's clearing through them so quickly...
Good job
Endo-san
He really is a pro...
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
His dormant talent finally awakens
With a great tempo, he gets more of them correct
and Endo gets 5 in a row correct!
5 cleared in a row!!
So fast
Rozorio Silver
text
This one is also quite expensive
Yamagata's Tackle Farm
Rozorio Silver
Correct
This is
This one costs 926 yen (nearly £6)($8.5)
What? Just for that?
Damn that's expensive
Correct Answer
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
He became Mori-san!
He had to bring him out at least once
Here he is!
You have to bring him out
Is he doing it on purpose or not, I'm not so sure lately...
It's not on purpose...
Did we need that?..
It's been a while, it really has, huh?
It was so fucking lame
It really has been a while
That happens to you a few times a year huh, Endo
Here I go...
The one I drank was NOT
Tackle Farm's Rozorio Silver...
Incorrect!!
Such a loser...
And on top of that...
You're kidding me?!
On top of screwing up your joke...
Like so badly...
This really hurts...
I heard it really hurts
Your brain is a cherry tomato!
I got that, his brain right?
Oh, his brain?
There it is...
It really does hurt
When he started doing his Mori-san impersonation, I was thinking
"Oh man, now is not the time"  you know?
Because this one's the correct one...
When I did the impersonation of Mori-san...
For a second, I just totally forgot the taste
Literally
Fourth Challenger
Tsukitei Hosei
Next up is Hosei. The one selected...
Yamagata Tackle Farm's Rozorio Silver
It's sweet and creamy
Will he be able to distinguish the difference?
Do you drink it a lot?
Mmh..
Hold on?
Give me a second
I've never drank this one before
Oh really?
I don't know which ones he's drunk anyway...
I've never drank this one before
It really is odourless
It's the one he was talking about
I know
You desperately want to hear some laughs soon
When you screw up a joke you'll forget the taste...
You're right
I'm not going to talk anymore
I don't think it's any of these
Can I start over here?
Oh, from the opposite side?
Yeah, to you guys
Marre100 % tomato juice unsalted
Text
Oh, the smell is different
It's totally different
The one I drank
His eyes...
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Correct Answer
Look at the one you're holding!
Are you really that blind?
What does it say?..
His vision is worse
then his sense of taste
The one I drank
was not Marre
Correct!!
tex
Black Prince Juice
Oh, that's the 15,000 yen one
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Correct Answer
The one I drank
is not Tomato with celebs...
What character is he playing today?..
Correct!!
It's the first time I've seen it
If you muck around too much, you'll forget the taste...
Sugar filled Yellow Aiko Mini Tomato Juice
Text
Yeah, he really will
Correct Answer
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
I'm getting the feeling I'm starting
to approach it
Approach?..
I don't know what he's on about...
I'm starting to approach the one I drank
So is it in the end
right or...
Wait a minute...
Would you choose yellow now?
That's what I am on about...
Would you actually choose a yellow tomato juice for the 4th challenger?..
What was that?
What the hell was that
God he pisses me off.
What the hell was that?
Is he angry?
I have no idea
What on earth does it mean?
I don't know
He's changed his face
He did...
So, what are you trying to say?
God if you saw him in town, you'd be so creeped out...
You would...
Would you choose this?..
I mean
It's this one!
Thank you
Oh man, it's been ages. But it can only be this one
The taste is identical
The scent is also identical!
Right, please!
Can you not see it?
Of course they'll take the piss out of you...
His eyes...
It's Yellow Aiko
Oh yeah, I did say that...
He can't read that... That's so bad...
The one I drank WAS
Yellow Aiko!
Incorrect!!
So fast...
Not at all...
Get the bottle off him
Oh yeah
Give him the bottle
Here he comes
It looks so painful...
Making crap comments all the time
you half-assed comedian!
Oh my god that hurts!
Did it hit you...
Oh man, it hit him there...
This is what happens when you get it wrong...
Man I don't want to do this
Hosei-san, it's this one
Just wait a second...
And he can't read it...
I'll just leave it here...
So Zaki-san...
Wait, did I get it right?
No no
It was next to it
Just next to is
It would've been the next one you'd chosen
If you got it correct, you wouldn't be punished!
Get it right, get 100,000 Yen, Get it wrong and get punished
Kiki Tomato Juice
Up to this point, all 4 have got it wrong in Kiki tomato juice!
Fifth Challenger
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Last challenger is
Matsumoto
I'm last
Here, it starts to become a psychological battle
Man they're being
so quiet it's creepy
But this must be tough for them to choose one
Seriously, the rubber is going to leave a mark on my face
And finally, after choosing carefully, the most standard one...
Kagome tomato juice!
It's been loved and sold for a long time
This taste, will he be able to remember it?
Oh man, this is tomato-ey, like way more than I was expecting
He slurped...
It's a bit thick...
I got to remember this gooey feeling
It's like Hamada's house,this gooey-ness
It's like Hamada's house this gooey-ness
Do you want to get smacked?
He's really defending himself...
This is like really, and I always say this
Why I hate going last is because
it's like a psychological battle, isn't it.
It's not about taste but more about having to guess what you guys will choose
It's like
Members
feelings guessing game
Just hurry up and drink
But you know
It was quite simple in my opinion
so it will be one of these...
Correct Answer
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
what should I do...
I don't think I can pick one...
What?
Wow wow, just hurry up man
You're not going to choose one?
Please hurry up
hurry up
First time ever... Can't choose...
I'm going to like go backstage once
But seriously, this is hard
Like if I choose the wrong one to start with, it could all be over...
But we knew the ones that were wrong, right?
No, I think I will start from over here
But anyway, I will start with this one
Text
Tomato Juice Unsalted
Correct
This is
But if it is this one, it will be finished real quick...
Here I go
Kagome's tomato juice
It's so wrong
It's totally different
Correct Answer
Currently Tasting
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
The refreshing feeling
is TOTALLY WRONG
You're so noisy!
Seriously...
Shut up!
He was shouting so much...
It's totally wrong
He really is loud
I mean this is so... Oh, I get though what Tanaka was saying
The one I drank was NOT Kagome's tomato juice...
Incorrect!!
Hang on!
Please, just hang on a second!
Just hang on a second!
Man!!
Come on!
Wait, wait, wait!
This video was brought to you by tofu panda fansubs
You're kidding!
Tell me you're kidding!
Seriously!
We are serious!
You were like "It's totally different"
Seriously, I am like
literally in a state of shock
I can't speak!
My legs gave out..
Seriously
His legs gave out...
He was all like "Totally different!"
"I get it.. Totally different"...
Stand up
No seriously...
In my long time doing Kiki...
I've NEVER been this shocked...