Translated & timed by saalow
encoding by FreshUdon
Good evening.
Tonight, unfortunately, we have some sad news
To share with all the viewers at home.
Housei-kun has been a regular on this program
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende, since our second episode
...and he's been gibing it his best shot since then.
Housei-kun has, after much thought,
Decided to move on from the show.
There's talk that he may leave the industry altogether,
Not just the show.
Yes, I've heard that too.
Might just be a rumor, but it seems he's made his mind up.
Without further ado, allow us to bring out the man himself,
Tsukitei Housei-kun.
Well, uh, a word or two on why you've come to this decision.
A reason for your retirement, because we're not quite...
Not quite clear on why you've gotta abandon showbiz.
So an explanation would be appreciated if possible...
...Yamazaki?
...an explanation?
Yes.
I'm already 50 years old, you know?
So much has happened, so much, and so I quit comedy.
And now intend to singularly devote myself to reproducing.
I want to have children!
That's certainly no reason to quit, though. You cold make that work.
My wife, her name's Aya, you know?
She just turned 40 and...
And she's just so beautiful, such a beautiful woman...
Such an exquisite woman, my wife...
Matsumoto-san, he...
He leers at ther and makes the most horrid faces...
Whenever I bring her up in conversation.
When we went drinking the other night,
Yeah?
You seemed weirdly interested in how my sex life was going.
I didn't mean it like that.
That's enough!
Ah, well I don't quite recall asking about that,
We'd had quite a bit to drink after all,
So I apologize for offending you. That wasn't my intention.
If my actions at all influenced your decision to retire,
Then that's on me and I'm sorry.
So just to confirm,
You're not leaving the program, correct?
You're leaving the entertainment industry entirely.
Yes.
...and, so...
Your reasoning?
We'd love to hear it.
Tanaka, why is it, you think?
That I've decided to quit?
Well I mean, I don't know.
Of course I don't want you to quit...
And I feel that if you don't have a clear reason to leave
Maybe you should give this decision a little bit more thought.
There's no reason for you to quit,
So if you would reconsider this choice...
He's right, maybe give it another shot.
Thank you...
What bliss...
But this is the way it must be.
And now we'd like to present a selection of
famous scenes curated by Housei-kun himself.
Please roll the tape.
Tsukitei Housei, 50 years old.
Narrated by Ashida Mana
Appearing on Gaki no Tsukai since its second episode,
Housei-kun has made his mark in dozens of memorable skits,
And is now retiring from the world of comedy.
Tonight, we look back on all the joy he has given us.
At number 5, Yamazaki vs. Jimmy:
The Blood Feud.
What's  your problem, dick?!
You got a screw loose or something, dumbass?
There was no greater enemy for little Housei.
None other than his Yoshimoto senpai, Jimmy Onish-san
Whenever they crossed paths, a bloodbath ensued.
Looking back at the two of them, one can't help but feel nostalgic.
Damn you're an annoying little fucker.
You're the one that's annoying!
Thinkin' you're such hot shit with this car.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
Only a dumbass like you would drive this piece of junk.
Who you calling a dumbass, dumbass?
You, dumbass!
With your dumbass clothes and your dumbass car.
Number 4, Yamasaki vs. Moriman.
Jimmy wasn't the only villain in Housei's life.
Yes, that very personage responsible for so many great fights:
Moriman-san.
BURDOCK BEATDOWN
That got him in the face just now.
Hit right in the face with a burdock root.
A burdock root... is just a stick.
Number 3: Yamasaki, Music Producer.
Oh man, I still remember this.
- Is that right?
Aiming for a lifetime of royalties,
This song, right?
Housei embarked on composing hiw own pop music,
And completed a catalog of 20 original songs.
Let's bid farewell this evening with a very special performance.
Ah~ Yamasaki-san The star filled sky we gazed upon
Still rings in my heart as if it were yesterday
Ah~ Matsumoto-san The promise we made on that day
I keep it in my heart because it's precious to me
Ah~ Tanaka-san Did you find what you were looking for?
I know you'll find a way to make your heart whole
Ah~ Endo-san In your room, you told me of a dream
The way you nodded and smiled, I'll never forget that kindness
Just out of reach, so close yet so far
Those stars that shine so brightly
Somehow, always, take us in your arms
For we are far too weak
At number 2, Yama no Ishimatsu: Slayer of 100 Men
Whatever the situation, you were always up for a challenge.
For your 20th anniversary in the business,
You shought to cut down 100 men.
The battle went smoothly at first, but...
Your strength was gradually sapped by your enemie's attacks.
And finally...
Hamada's mean streak is peeking out.
- No, he tried to run away, see?
No, no, Hamada-san, this is...
Really showing your worst qualities.
You fled from the set.
You ain't gotta cry like that.
My back hurts.
From now on we'll wait until you attack us to go after you, ok?
- We promise, we promise.
No, not you.
YOU?
Who the hell are you calling y--
Number 1, Yamasaki's Moving Wedding.
- Again with this? Come on!
Seriously, how many times do we have to watch this?
Always childlike, our little rascal finally tied the knot.
You selflessly allowed us to share in your joy.
This looks like some sort of "How To Get Married" video.
Right? What the hell is this?
What's with this weirdly high production value?
This is... that kind of high quality you don't see on TV, right?
You're kidding me!
There's no way.
What happened that made you cry like that?
No way!!
Housei-kun, we watched you grow up alongside the program.
But the time has finally come for you to end this chapter of your life.
Even as time goes on, our memories of you will not fade,
For we keep those moments in the albums of our hearts.
Yes, for now and for always.
Farewell
And thanks for the memories.
And now for some parting words.
She changed jobs in 2014,
Our former receptionist, Uchino.
Uchino-chan?
You came back?
In 2014-
Here.
Everyone signed it for you.
Thank you!
Don't ever drag me back here for dumb shit like this again.
She came all this way, so...
A waste of electricity (lightning dept.)
Hell yeah! (manager)
Keep your sorry ass in Osaka (NTV)
Stop taking my IPhone charger (AP)
The next time I see you I'll kick your ass (Irie)
WE DID IT (the ADs)
We saw him shoplifting the other day (front desk)
Weird body (wardrobe)
Your ears are rotting (sound dept.)
disappear (all Yoshimoto)
this rules (Hulu)
We also have a few words we'd like to share,
Starting with Cocorico.
It wasn't until last night, actually,
That I heard you were leaving Gaki.
So when I went back home,
to my wife and my mother-in-law, who's in town visiting her grandkid,
and told them the news...
They were like "Thank God!"
Semms like they both really hated your guts.
They're really jazzed about this, so thanks.
Nice work.
Tanaka's turn.
Yes. I've always hated you.
I hate your face.
We've also prepared some words tonight.
You and I have know each other for many years, and...
Well, we've never met up outside of work for a meal or anything,
But these days there's tons of people going into retirement
And I don't think any less of them, so, you know.
So yeah, good luck out there.
Thanks for all your hard work.
Let's see, *** and I first met back in...
Oh, sorry, that's what Aya's been calling you lately.
Sorry about that.
So, as I was saying,
This was back in my twenties when *** and I...
You must have been about 20, right?
There's no way I'l never forget you, ***.
And I'll be seeing a lot more of your wife from now on.
You'll be great, ***!
Thank you!
And lastly, from Housei-kun himself, some parting words.
Who was it?
Who was it that...
That made these flowers bloom?
It was five men.
All five of us, together...
They all went away...
I dream that suddenly I was alone!
AND I WAS SO VERY LONELY
BUT EVEN THEN
EVEN THEN!
I shed no tears.
But even then...
Even though I was the only one from Gaki left...
"Don't cry", said a voice.
Over and over again.
Oh, I'm remembering now...
That dream, I'm recalling more of it...
HAMADA-CHAN WAS THE ONE SPEAKING TO ME
It was him! HAMADA-CHAN, he spoke to me!
How tragic...
Whas this how you pictured it would end?
In all these tears?
Did you anticipate the tears?!
Who would thought?!
I'm not feeling so hot...
For real.
No, seriously, I think I'm gonna barf.
I'm serious.
Finally.
Tanaka Naoki.
You're
My
Best friend.
Tanaka Naoki
T A N A K A  N A O K I
I don't want to let you go...
I can't let go of you, Tanaka Naoki!
I LOVE YOU
TA NA KA
NA O KI
Ok, well, Yama-chan, thanks for all your hard work.
Is that still not enough?
I haven't even heard Tanaka's response!
Tanaka's... HEY! LET ME GO!
I DON'T WANNA QUIT!!
Hey now, someone's gonna get hurt.
I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE!!
YOU CAN'T MAKE ME!! I WON'T DO IT
You've gotta make this your last show.
LET ME STAY LONGER, PLEASE
- No, no one wants to see this...
I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING TO DESERVE THIS
I'M NOT LEAVING
What a mess.
- Well, yeah, I mean, I know.
But leaving the entire industry?
- That certainly happened.
It turned out that it's not the show he's retiring from...
Well, gentlemen,
Starting next week, let's do our best as a foursome.
WAIT!!!
Well, gentlemen,
Starting next week, let's do our best as a foursome.
WAIT!!!
HOUSEI AIN'T
QUITTIN' SHOWBIZ~!
All you out there in TV land, did I scare ya?
I let two year pass, bided my time...
AND I GOTCHA FOR THE 16th TIME!
Housei will...
NOT! Be leaving Gaki no Tsukai NOR show business!
NOT QUITTING NOT QUITTING
NOT QUITTING~!
And now he does his skit, yeah?
I guess that's me.
Is that me?
Yeah, that's gotta be you.
Can that bald guy even sing?
This is too much...
At least get rid of the glasses.
He's super quiet.
His Japanese was a bit shaky.
The bald guy doesn't even have his mic up!
He was so focused on the lip-sync that he forgot.
HOUSEI AIN'T QUITTING
NOT QUITTING SHOWBIZ, NOT QUITTING GAKI
AND DEFINITELY NOT RAKUGO
Somehow, always, LET ME STAY
HOUSEI AIN'T QUITTING!
Somehow~ Always~
LET ME STAY~!
Long, long, too long.
Too long!
Really shoulda picked up the pace.
Thank you very much.
What?
- Doesn't he do one more?
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE YOU SUNOVABITCH
What?
- Doesn't he do one more?
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE YOU SUNOVABITCH
We heard you were plannin' on retiring...
- Yeah yeah yeah!
And came all the way down here from Hokkaido!!
It's Moriman!
And now you say you're NOT quitting?
It's cuz of YOU that we had to wake up at 6 this morning!!
Damn straight!
We didn't sit in that traffic jam for nothin'!!
What's your freakin' problem?
Cue card says "Hamada-san, if you please"...
And?
- Oh, I get it.
BURDOCK BEATDOWN
Can't be helped, buddy!
You've gotta fight, it's the only way out!
You'll win this time, you'll win this time!
You gotta fight!! It'll be easier if you fight!!
You can't run away!! There's no way out!!
Fight her!
- Don't run away!!
The hell is going on?
Hit her, You gotta hit her!!
What in the hell is this?
Don't hit the crew!! Stop hitting the crew!
Too bad, huh?
If we had known you hated burdock so much...
Then maybe the staff could've used something else.
Yeah, that's why...
That's why I went after Takasu and Yanaoka.