Subbed by Mickstar813 (Team Gaki) & HouseiGIFs
Previous Week
Back after 8 years:
Silent Library
With Azuma Mikihisa as a guest
Back after 8 years:
Silent Library
and after 8 years, Silent Library!
Narrator:
Yamada
Shinichi
Matsumoto Trembling Earbuds
Whilst sitting in a library
Whoever gets the card with the skull and bones gets punished
Hamada Piping Hot Shumai Glasses
Note: Those are Pork Dumplings
And during this...
Azuma Mikihisa chooses the skull and crossbones card again and again...
Azuma Mikihisa consecutive hits!!
Eyeball Clothespins
Vinegar Facial Device
Brazilian Nose Hair Wax
Number of times they've been punished
Azuma
Endo
Hamada
Housei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
As you see above, this is the number of times they've been punished
Will they be able to survive the even harsher punishments coming up?
Will they be able  to survive!?
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
I will pick last from here on...
Azuma Mikihisa
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Hamada
Masatoshi
Matsumoto
Hitoshi
Tsukitei Housei
Okay then...
Reflexology
Virgin Road
* Wedding Aisle
Something for our feet...
Reflexology
Virgin Road
* Wedding Aisle
Whoever picks the skull and crossbones card gets punishment written on the card
You guys haven't been punished yet so you pick first...
Yeah
Okay then...
You sure you're okay for us to go ahead..?
Yes
You're okay to choose the last card?
---------
Housei
-----
---------
Azuma
Endo
Hamada
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready, set
---------
Housei
There it is!
* Wedding Aisle
Housei
Reflexology Virgin Road
Shh
It was bound to happen
This is where things start to change...
Yeah, you're right
Damn, that road is long...
Yeah it is
That's going to hurt...
There are some which really stick out too...
But if you're healthy and all, it doesn't hurt right?
But none of us are really healthy...
I see...
I see, he's going to walk alongside him
You can't just walk at your own pace
You have to walk with the Dad
So you can't run away
In order not to be a pain to the people around them, they must not make any noise
That's horrible
So the Dad will walk on that side
Yeah
What the hell is this?
He's actually doing it pretty well...
Yeah I know
He did it pretty well...
You're kidding me...
You did well
You're healthy, huh?
Didn't it hurt?
A little bit
He didn't shout
Just a tiny bit
Amazing...
He didn't make a noise
I know
I would never have been able to...
That was like seriously...
That was tough
Monkey
Palm
Strike
That thing they did to Endo...
Monkey
Palm
Strike
Monkey
Palm
Strike
This really hurts
-----
Azuma
Ready, set
---------
Endo
Hamada
Housei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
-----
Azuma
Azuma Mikihisa
Monkey
Palm Strike
Shh
Are you serious?!
No way!
Things haven't changed at all!
I know...
Here he comes...
This is bad
It's so scary
Look at him...
I'm really scared
Wait here
What is this?
Wait a minute
He's huge
Damn...
Close your eyes
Wait...
Wait a minute please...
Hey man...
I can't do this
It's dangerous to move
I'm feeling so much pressure from it!
Like seriously
We can't help that, you picked the card
Matsumoto-san
I do get how you feel and all
I'm sorry, man, but...
What do I do?
There is quite a bit of a pause...
That's true
This must be torture for him
What...
I will hold him back
QUICKLY
No no no
Why is he just...
The pause is just so long
Is there some kind of thing the timing..?
of the monkey?
Just hit me straight away...
See...
It's because you keep moving
This is like really bad
But like seriously, this is an animal
It's because you move
It's bad
No, before I wasn't...
Go down?
Just go down
Isn't that even more dangerous?
It'll be fine
Shozo, hold him from behind
I did it like this
in the no-laughing special...
Okay, hold my hand then
Okay then
On my knees?
On your knees...
Don't move too quickly or else
Damn, wait...
This is...
You've got to be quiet
This is yeah...
This is scary
Nothing you can do about it
Shall I close my eyes?
Sit here?
Don't move
This is scary...
But Shozo had to do this as well...
Wait, what, what do you want?!
Wait, who did that on my shoulder just now?!
It was him!
That scared me!
He pushed here really hard
That was amazing
He did accidentally
He did it here...
Thank you! Sorry about him!
He looks pissed...
I would hate to do that
How many more are there?
Raw Egg
Drinking
Pipe
This is really tough
This is...
Everyone, please take your cards first
You sure?
-----
Azuma
---------
Endo
Hamada
Housei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready, set
-----
Azuma
No way!!
Mikihisa
Azuma
Raw Egg
Drinking Pipe
Shh
That is scary!
Are you serious right now?!
Matsumoto-san...
I chose last though
We haven't tampered with it or anything
We haven't done anything
For any of them
Seriously
You took it yourself
If you could lie here
Your head here
Yep, like that
That is amazing...
Here you go...
Surely this is enough...
You're right
Is it tight?
Please have a firm grasp on it
It'll all come at once
Are you ready?
Ready?
3, 2, 1...
Here it comes
Not yet, not yet
Whilst Azuma Mikihisa tries to deal with his punishment,
please look at this picture of pretty flowers...
Mikihisa was throwing up so much there...
Couldn't help it
That was scary though
You can do it however you want
But seriously...
What are the odds?
The viewers are going to suspicious of us...
Can you just give me a second?
Thank you
You can decide
If you want to decide which one to take
Yeah
Or choose the last remaining card
Yeah. You going to choose the same one as before?
May I?
Oh yeah
Here we go
Piping Hot
Oden Stew
Drone
What the hell is that?
This is...
It's hot...
Hot...
Piping Hot
Oden Stew
Drone
---------
Matsumoto
-----
---------
Azuma
Endo
Hamada
Housei
Tanaka
Ready, set
---------
Matsumoto
Piping Hot
Oden Stew Drone
Shh
Yes, yes yes
It's come
Can you just lie down on the table please
Put your head over here
Here?
Oh, where the camera is
I hate these kind of ones...
So the camera from above can get a good shot...
Yeah
If they make you lie down, it's going to be a hot punishment
That's true
The glasses as well
Oh my God...
That's bad
It's boiling!
It's boiling
It's literally boiling...
Wait, I'm scared...
Yeah, I would be too...
It's boiling!
How we going to do it?
I'm so scared...
Okay, if you would.
Damn, that's scary
It's coming
Here it comes, it's gone up!
Wow, amazing
This is so stupid...
Here it comes
So stupid...
What the hell is this?
Just use your hands for fuck's sake...
That was the boiling hot Oden carried by a drone
The drone was so loud...
It's the waiting time though...
Yeah
That's what is scary
Lending Reception
Return slot
That was scary
Ceiling
Hold
What?
Ceiling
Hold
That one...
Ceiling
Hold
It's that one, right?
This one, I just...
You're handing them out?
You're handing it out, huh?
---------
Housei
-----
---------
Azuma
Endo
Hamada
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready, set
---------
Housei
Yes!!
* aka Surfboard Stretch
or Romero Special
Ceiling Hold
Housei
Shh
Yes, yes, yes
This is terrifying
Why did he come around from that way?
This is ridiculous...
Damn that's tough
This is horrible
Be quiet!
Be quiet
It hurts!
This is a library, be quiet...
Be quiet...
You must be quiet
It's a library, please be quiet
What the hell are you doing?
Housei-san...
I'm sorry
What the hell are you doing?
This is the last one
Old Men
Sneezing
Oh hell no
Old Men
Sneezing
What is it?
This is the worst
Old Men
Sneezing
This is the worst one
Old Men
Sneezing
This one is just a no-no
Old Men
Sneezing
Let's not do this one...
Please man... This is so bad...
I think I hate this one the most
I definitely don't want to
Mentally, it kills you
But once we get this done, it's over
This is the last one... Concentrate...
Last one...
But seriously...
This one...
Yeah, I get you
This one is just a no.
Shall we do it one at a time?
One at a time?
So in order?
Damn, you're good at this
Hamada
You're so lucky
He's out
Who's going next? Tanaka?
May I go?
Yes!!
Well done
Tanaka
Get in!
Yama-chan, you want to go?
I'm begging you, please, please...
Don't get it...
Okay
Who do you want to get it?
Him (Endo)
Housei
He's done it
Mikihisa-san, you should go next
No, I don't think
You go
You just don't know now...
Matsumoto-san?
Who's going first?
Mikihisa...
Me?
Please just pick the card though..
But if he doesn't pick it here, you guys...
I know, I haven't had to do anything yet
That's true
But seriously, please
I will pick the one which I least want to pick
I see
YES!
Azuma
Mikihisa
Wow, amazing
It's one or the other!
You don't know yet
Who's going first?
Matsumoto-san first?
You going first?
Rock, paper, scissors?
Rock, Paper...
I will
You're going first?
If you are safe, it's Matsumoto-san
So pick one.
Flip it on three
I'm begging you
Right then...
Yes...
Ready, set
Pick one
Flip it on three
I'm beggin you
---------
Matsumoto
Endo
Right then...
Yes...
Ready, set
---------
Matsumoto
Old Men Sneezing
Shh
Get in!!!
Shozo, you are something else!
I'm so happy
Get in!
Change with me...
Shozo, your luck is just...
This one is so bad
Endo...
This is...
Endo, I will give you 10,000 Yen!
No
10,000 yen: I'm saying I will give you 10,000 yen
I'm saying 10,000 yen...
Matsumoto-san...
Here he comes
He's looking at you so much, he's locked onto you
What's he going to do?
This is so bad
Stood up?
This is...
This is what happens...
Oh man
Damn
This is just
This is
This is harsh
That was disgusting
This is mentally
This is the worst
It is
Mentally...
When you think you're going to get it, you get it.
I know, right?
You just know when it's you...
When you have a bad feeling, you always get it.
You're so right
I was convinced I was going to get the last one...
You were so against it too...
I just knew it...
That was the best final punishment...
In a different sense...
Aired May 1st
Recently we aired the show
Impromptu!! Ghost Story Inn!
where you must make a ghost story from the cards given
Impromptu Ghost Story Inn!
The unseen part
of the impromptu ghost story inn
This time, we will show the unseen parts
that we couldn't fit into the original episode
First up is Hamada's ghost story
Hamada's ghost story
Unseen footage
An old woman...
I see...
And old woman and...
An old woman and...
Oh, scary...
That's perfect
A hospital...
Shall we choose one more?
Yeah, let's do three..
I agree.
As a special treat...
These 2 are easy to do..
A special treat...
Suspension bridge...
Oh man...
But you know, let's choose one more...
It's a special treat after all...
That's right
A French doll...
This is, wow...
You got so much potential here
You can do this
What a treat...
Well...
It's about an old woman acquaintance of mine
Old woman acquaintance?
That's quite weird, no?
You're right
Sorry, she's this person I know's grandma...
So this person's grandma...
Oh right, I see...
And old woman, right?
Yes..
And she's a bit old so she's starting
to become a bit forgetful...
and so she's going to a hospital kind of
and that kind of place
kind of?
In a hospital...
and her family put her in one
If she's at home, she wanders so it's a bit dangerous
And so
that old woman
is always holding this French doll
Oh man, why?
That's because
She's becoming forgetful so she thinks that it's
her newborn daughter...
and she holds this the whole time
and she was like this at home, so that's why they put her in a hospital.
That's so scary
at the hospital, in the corridor or wherever
even when it's light out, she holds this French doll and just walks about
even when it's lights out, she holds this French doll and just walks about
and they say "Oh man, that old woman is gone again"
So they start being like "Oh man, she's escaped her room and wandered off again"
And this carried on for days...
And this one time, they searched the whole hospital, but they couldn't find her.
but it's a hospital in the countryside...
so there was this really big suspension bridge
and if you cross this bridge, you can go into town.
But they thought "Oh no, what if..."
"Surely she hasn't escaped the hospital and crossed that bridge"
That is dangerous
and when they ran to the suspension bridge to look
she had fallen...
There it is, again
She fell again?
Your character always fall over...
The suspension bridge isn't important then!
She hasn't crossed the suspension bridge then!
She hasn't crossed it, whilst she was crossing it
She fell?
Yeah
She wasn't like going up stairs though...
That's serious
What an incident...
Housei's ghost story
Unseen footage
Next up is Housei's ghost story
Tell me when to stop
Stop!
OK.
First up
A rusty door...
Top! Ah...
"Top..."
Erimo Misaki
Note: Erimo Misaki is a place in Japan but, also a song sang by Mori Shinichi
Erimo Misaki, huh...
Stop!
He's going for three...
Another suspension bridge
There it is again
It's come again
This is good
How many do you want?
I did 4, so he should do 5
That's true
Let's do 5 then
Stop!
Vinegared mackerel
vinegared mackerel...
Vinegared mackerel...
Stop!
Wow, a fifth one?
5 would be amazing
It would be amazing if you did 5.
That's amazing
Hide and seek.
Hide and seek...
That's a mix...
Right then, with this
A rusty door, Erimo Misaki, a suspension bridge, vinegared mackerel and hide and seek...
I mean you are
a rakugo-ka after all...
Yes
Please
So please make it a good one
But please make it a really scary story...
I will.
Please do
But not too long either.
I will make it a short and scary story
This is about when I went with my family to Erimo Misaki
Do you know of it?
There are loads of suspension bridges there
Oh really?
Yes
And when we got there and we crossed them
We were like "what shall we do?"
We were like "shall we play a good game of hide and seek?"
With your kids?
Yes
so we did
I became the seeker
because I am the father
I said "are you ready?"
and they replied "Not yet"
Are you ready? Not yet... are you ready?
We are ready
So I started looking for them but I couldn't find them at all!
But none of them were there and I was like "what's going on?"
huh?
Why aren't they here, I can't find them at all
And of course I won't find them
It was the first time I've ever been to Erimo Misaki after all...
What the hell is that style of story telling...
I know
That's not how you tell a ghost story...
And when I was walking for a while,
there was a door, a really rusty one
It was really rusty
So I thought "oh, my kids are definitely in here"
so I pushed the door
but it wouldn't open at all, because it's so rusty
So I thought "what!?"
I thought "if this doesn't open, I will be the seeker forever!"
Is that the real problem here?
Yeah...
That's a weird way to think...
I thought "I want to hide too, not seek forever"...
You really hate seeking that much, huh?
Eventually, I looked in
there were some mackerels there...
You're kidding me, right?
They were stuck
To that rusty door?
Yes
And then
the mackerel was caught to the door and therefore became a "Shime-saba"
(NOTE: SHIME CAN MEAN CAUGHT, HENCE THE PUN ON WORDS)
So the mackerel was caught and was a "shime-saba"
Anyone can do it...
It didn't escalate at all...
Yeah...
Anyone can do it...
I see...