Last episode’s broadcast:
Become an Anime Character Bus Tour!!
Cosplaying an anime character for the bus tour as Arare-chan from Dr. Slump* is Yamazaki Housei.
*Dr. Slump is a manga by Akira Toriyama from the 80’s.
Once the game begins, the results are pitiful.
He’s sent off to Ueno while he’s still in costume, where all eyes are on him.
On top of that, he must go buy spaghetti as part of his punishment.
Chosen one is Yamazaki!!
HOWEVER
I haven’t gotten the spaghetti yet.
Yamazaki, embarrassed, escapes the area and together with Miyasako, went elsewhere to buy the spaghetti.
AND FROM THERE, AN ANGERED MATSUMOTO…
That’s no good. Get over to Italy!!
Get over to ITALY!!
ITALY?!
Over in that heel area of Italy. You know how it looks like a boot, go to the heel.
Like when I went to Evian.
HOLD ON, WAIT PLEASE, WAIT!!
The scale of this batsu game area has become humongous!!
And so with that, Yamazaki must go to Italy. This week we present to you his travels with blood, sweat, and tears.
And so, Yamazaki must make a journey to Italy…
Chorus: Hamada Masatoshi
Composer/Lyricist: Matsumoto Hitoshi
“Hamada's Ear Hair, You Know~”
Don't fall
Don't fall in love with ME~
Hamada's
Hamada’s Ear Hair, you KNOW~
Flutters in the WIND~
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Well uhhh… everyone, you may be here, looking forward to tonight...
What do you mean, what is there to look forward to?
Eh…
This isn’t free talk.
In fact, uhh... this is going to be terrible…
You’ll just have to see. You know, it’ll even be a really long time since it’s been seen on here, but this one’s a very lame video.
It was pretty bad…
Nothing we can do about it...
Well well, without further ado...
The video is…
Ah yes, that’s right.
Let’s bring in the man himself.
Alright, come on in.
Yamazaki Hosei
Ncha!*
*Ncha is a phrase that Arare­chan says in Dr. Slump
Ncha!
Uhhh... I’m just gonna let you know, the loud cheering was for Cocorico.
NO WAY!
NO IT’S NOT!
Cocorico
Tanaka Naoki
That cheering was totally for me!
See, what’s all this clapping for?
Yamazaki, you went out looking like this, right?
Yes, this is how I looked.
Wow.
Amazing.
This was incredibly difficult.
You say that, but I bet you went out and did some sightseeing.
No, not at all. I didn't do anything like that. Really, I stayed for 0 nights.
0 nights and 3 days.
Just for one-way? How long did it take?
Let's see...
14 hours.
Wait, why are you answering?
That surprised me.
Hey!!
Don't answer my questions for me!
You forgot the answer!
Wow, it takes 14 hours.
So we got to Italy, right? And then you said to go to the heel, right?
Oh yeah, right. The heel area of Italy.
Getting to that heel area took another plane flight and then a car ride.
So that means... In total, that was twenty... Uhhh...
24 hours.
four hours?
Yes.
24 hours.
So that heel area... Where is that?
Nietzsche.
Lecce.
Lecce!!
What the hell are you doing?
Saying Nietzsche...
Downtown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Translation: OolongCha
Timing: DuckToaster
September 26th
6:30am
Nihon TV Parking Lot
At the crack of dawn, we find this man in the Nihon TV parking lot.
It's early.
Your change of clothes.
Change of clothes?
And now, Yamazaki transforms to Arare-chan.
Ncha!!
What low spirits...
Uhhh, well, I still haven't really accepted the situation, but right now...
I am going to Italy to go buy spaghetti.
Since this is so sudden, I don't have much time.
0 nights, 3 days is how long I have to obtain the spaghetti.
I don't want this.
I will also be taking Kewpie-chan* with me.
*Kewpie is a popular brand of dolls whose name is based off the word, "cupid." This doll's base is Kewpie with a Gacchan design.
Gacchan.
Kewpie...
I will also be taking Gacchan* with me.
*Gacchan is another character in Dr. Slump
Here I go.
Yamazaki Arare-chan on his way to Narita Airport by car.
The punishments are only this severe when it comes to me.
To be honest.
Even though my pays sucks.
Making me take this useless thing.
Why this song?
Last episode, Yamazaki fails the task of getting spaghetti on his own.
He ends up getting it with Miyasako.
For this reason, he's sent off to Italy to get spaghetti.
Lucky... He's gone twice now.
11:10am
Departing Narita Airport
He even gets this
occasion filmed for him.
Yamazaki Hosei 0 nights and 3 days:
Going to Italy to Buy Spaghetti!
Yamazaki leaves for Japan, for the sake of finding spaghetti, and heads towards Rome, Italy.
Length of Flight: 14 hours
The length of the flight is 14 hours.
Not only that, this entire roundtrip is in economy class, so this long trip will be particularly exhausting.
I'll now present today's menu.
The meal looks like this.
This guy is drinking beer.
What?! He can't have beer!
Why not?!
It's a 14 hour flight!
This guy is such a pain.
Endo or Hoto-chan or the others don't have to do this?
They don't have to go anywhere?
Um, yeah, I guess not.
Aren't I the only one who gets the hard tasks?
Like Cocorico is...
Is treated like the favorites.
Only I get this harsh treatment, right?
Well, it's not really a matter of harsh treatment.
Cocorico's schedule is completely booked.
I'm busy, too!
If you think my schedule is open, you're wrong.
After a while, the effects of the alcohol starts kicking in and Yamazaki, not realizing the camera is still rolling,
Yamazaki, thinking the camera is off, expresses what's on his mind.
starts talking about Downtown and other topics.
Amazing. Just amazing.
Those 2 (Downtown) are really amazing, I think.
In what way?
You know, when I first saw their manzai, I thought,
"Wow, these dudes are gonna be the kings."
Yeah, when I first saw them, I didn't know them at all, when I first saw Downtown, I thought...
"These dudes are gonna be the kings" and now look, they're at the top!
I have a sixth sense for these kinds of things.
Oh, I see.
Recently, you know, Hamada-san...
Didn't he dye his hair?
What do you think about it?
What do I think, well, I was surprised!
Because... "If you dye your hair, you're garbage!" is what he's been saying for a long time.
So now, he's become garbage.
That is just garbage.
And now, after enduring the long 14 hour flight, the plane has landed in Rome. Yama-chan is still in his Arare-chan outfit and his number 1 priority is to seek out spaghetti!
Leonardo da Vinci Airport
We made it. Italy.
Looks like we finally made it.
That was crazy, too intense. Seriously.
I didn't even get to sleep at all.
Pizza, let's go get that pizza.
Pizza?
Yeah, pizza. Oh wait, not pizza, spaghetti.
We made it, we're here in Italy.
Here.
Is this the city of Rome?
This is Rome.
So he said the heel, right?
No way, we shouldn't have to bother with that.
We made it all the way here. Let's just buy it in Italy and go home.
But Macchan said the heel, so we need to go all the way over there.
Are you serious?
We'll need to board another plane.
For reals?
Yes... For reals.
Whaaaat... No way...
From the airport in Rome, Yamazaki takes a domestic flight, yet again in economy class, to the city that faces the Adriatic Sea, Bari.
Non-stop traveling since the morning has caused
Yamazaki sleeping like a corpse
Yamazaki unable to hide his exhaustion
and is now sleeping soundly.
We're here,
we're here.
We've made it.
Wow, it's all dark now.
Time in Italy: 10 PM
It's so dark.
Okay so... So now...
Um... the heel.
Um... What was it again?
Let's just buy spaghetti and go home.
Can't do that!
Why can't I just do that?
This place is called Bari.
Huh?
Bari.
The heel of the boot, right?
We're still only at the achilles heel!
Archilles heel?
We have to ride in a car again?
We'll be traveling by car now~
For about how long?
Uhh, for about 2 hours. I hear.
2 hours?!
By car.
So damn far!!
Because I mean... We've been going...
For 20 hours. We've been traveling.
Let's see...
6am.
In Japan.
In Japan?
Yes.
We had you come in to Nihon TV at around 6:30am so...
It's been right about 24 hours.
After arriving in Bari, Yamazaki immediately resumes travel by car.  He heads towards his destination, the city at the "heel," Lecce.
From Bari to Lecce, the distance is about 200km.
Traveling the distance of 200km by car.
His journey still continues to attain spaghetti in Italy.
Yamazaki, sound asleep, again.
Around this time, Yamazaki,
with so much international traveling, is dead asleep.
The city he seeks is Lecce.
A city that gleams in bronze light and one of the most beautiful and aesthetic cities in Southern Italy.
It's been 24 hours since starting the journey from Japan.
The car takes them to the heart of Lecce city.
Yamazaki, though falling apart from fatigue, finally sets foot in the final destination.
We've arrived in Lecce!!
We've made it.
We've finally made it.
Yamazaki is only allowed 4 hours in Lecce.
4 hours is all he's allowed in Lecce.
Within this time, he must attain the spaghetti.
Yamazaki hurries in search of a restaurant.
Isn't this one?
This?
Is this a restaurant? This?
No, not this one.
Spotted a restaurant!!
Immediately, they spot a restaurant-looking establishment!!
In order for Yamazaki to make the purchase, they give him a note of Italian translations on it.
Yamazaki is handed an Italian language cheatsheet.
Bringing meat to Japan from a foreign country is incredibly complicated, so he must order a spaghetti with no meat.
And his task is to order a spaghetti with no meat in it.
Can Yamazaki procure this spaghetti without a problem?
Good evening.
I come from Japan.
There's something I'd like to order.
Okay?
I'd like to order a plate of spaghetti.
We're already closed.
I'll pay for it.
Huh?
The kitchen is all closed.
Please make it a spaghetti with no meat.
We're completely closed.
We're not open.
They said they're closed.
Huh?
Closed? Why?
We're closed.
No No No No No
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes
"Si" is Italian for "yes."
We don't have any food right now.
Why?
Why why?
Are you serious?
They said they're done.
Let's go already.
Thank you.
Good bye.
Why are they closed?!
Let's go search for another one.
Why are they closed...
Because it's already past midnight!
That can't be the reason.
The cuckoos are chirping and they're just doing nothing!
Yamazaki, thinking he could quickly order and go home,
They drive around by car in search for the next restaurant.
was refused and is searching for the next restaurant.
But because it's so late at night, they aren't able to find another one so easily.
Finally, they find the next restaurant.
Ordering from the second restaurant.
Yamazaki approaches, in hopes of ordering.
Nchao!*
*Translator's note: He's trying to be clever by mixing Arare-chan's "Ncha" with "Ciao."
We're in the process of closing shop.
We're closed.
Closed?*
*Translator's note: He pronounces the word phoenetically in English. "Close-ed"
Closed Closed Closed Closed
No No No No No
Yes Yes Yes Yes Yes
Don't take it personally.
Thank you.
Good night.
It's not good!
They're not open!
Because it's late.
It's late but...
But we left at 6:30 in Japan!
We're just barely late.
Huh?
The restaurant is still open, but they're not serving spaghetti anymore.
What do you mean they're not serving spaghetti, that's not right.
You have a point.
After that, Yamazaki walks around Lecce in the middle of the night, looking for information on a restaurant that's still open.
After that, Yamazaki wanders around the town of Lecce by foot for about an hour.
But unable to get any promising answers.
Come on...
We don't have much time left until we have to go back home, right?
We have only about 3 hours.
Whaaaaat?!
Geez, this pisses me off!
Oh, this place is a restaurant!
Spotted another restaurant!
Somehow, Yamazaki spots the third restaurant!
However, will Yamazaki be able to order spaghetti?!
Good evening.
I'd like to order a plate of spaghetti.
No.
No?! Why why?!
Please make it a spaghetti with no meat.
You're still ordering?
You just keep going, huh.
Please, I beg of you.
Beg of me?
What is that? Is that Bingo Bongo?*
*Translator's Note: Apparently, Bingo Bongo is a movie that is the comedic Italian equivalent of Tarzan.
Bingo Bongo!
For some reason, the restaurant staff are amused by Gacchan and ask the chef to make an order of spaghetti.
Thank you! Thank you!
Pippo, make an order of spaghetti for Japan, will you?
Good evening.
I'd like to order a plate of spaghetti.
We've already done the cleaning, we're closed.
What?
We're closed.
Please, I beg of you.
We don't have anymore spaghetti.
Really?
What?
Will Yamazaki ever be able to get his hands on some spaghetti?!
There, an older gentleman who looks to be the owner, reaches out to Yamazaki.
He says to make do with this.
Make do with this? No no no.
I'd like a plate of spaghetti with no meat, please.
A plate of spaghetti with no meat, please?
Come back tomorrow?
You don't have any?
We don't have time to come back tomorrow. We're on a time limit.
No time limit.
(I have unlimited time.)
Suddenly, the old gentleman...
What's this? Boil it! This is no good, boil it for me!
They bring him a package of dried pasta.
1 piece of spaghetti for 1,000,000 lira*
Translator's notes: Lira was the form of currency before Italy changed to Euros. 1,000,000 lira = 60,000 yen = roughly USD $600
No! Expensive, too expensive!
*Translator's notes: 120,000 yen = roughly USD $1,200
2 pieces of spaghetti for 2,000,000 lira*
*Translator's notes: 180,000 yen = roughly USD $1,800
3 pieces of spaghetti for 3,000,000 lira*
Do you want 1 piece of spaghetti for 1,000,000 lira?
That's so expensive!
The prices for spaghetti are incredibly inflated,
what will Yamazaki do?!
The price for spaghetti has been incredibly increased! This Italian man is be feared! Is what we thought, however...
Well, let's make it for them!
Let's treat Japan to a plate of spaghetti.
Thank you!
He says he'll treat us.
Treat us? You will treat us? Oh, thank you!
Let's give this spaghetti to this child (Gacchan).
Let's give a friendly applause for Japan.
Yamazaki has no idea what's going on with the strange turn of events.
At the words of a lively saint, Yamazaki is finally able to get spaghetti.
In the midst of cooking spaghetti.
At this time, they're cooking a Lecce style spaghetti with parmesan cheese and basil in a tomato-based sauce, no meat.
They make spaghetti for Yamazaki as representatives of Southern Italian cuisine.
They're making a lot.
Oh, thank you!! Thank you, thank you!
Yamazaki acquires spaghetti!
It's done!! It's here, the spaghetti is finally made!
Due to this kind saint, Yamazaki is miraculously able to acquire the spaghetti he needed.
As Yamazaki departs, the restaurant bids us a warm Italian farewell.
I've acquired the spaghetti!
Thank you!
Yeah! We got the spaghetti!
This spaghetti looks so delicious. I'm so touched. This here...
I'll bring this back to Japan and let's all eat this with everyone!
After acquiring this earnest plate of spaghetti, Yamazaki travels another 24 hours just like before.
And makes his way straight back to Japan!
Yamazaki's spaghetti that
he bought home from Lecce
This is really
authentically Italian.
It was kept frozen
and naturally thawed.
That's no good, it's like a sherbet then!
Then by microwave...
Eh? You put it in the microwave?
Yes, please heat it up in the microwave.
Ughhh, I don't want it anymore...
No way, you can't do that!
This is that spaghetti, right?
Yes, this is the spaghetti.
Is this it?
Yes, this is really it! That's the real thing! So I told them not make a replacement.
That is absolutely unforgivable, I told them I will definitely bring you guys the exact dish that was given.
I don't understand what the hell you're saying.
How did you freeze it then?
I froze it over there.
What do you mean, "over there?!"
Where is that?
What the hell do you mean?
In Italy.
That made no sense at all.
Okay, it's ready now!
It's done now!
See, now it's warm!
Well... I'm not so sure about the inside though.
Yeah, we don't know about that.
Regardless, Hamada is going to inhale all of this in one go.
Really? Do your best!
What the hell are you saying? Come on everyone, eat!
It's all stuck together.
This is no good. I don't want to eat this thing.
Come on, eat!
I guess we should have a little. Hurry up and eat it already!
Eat it!
I'll help myself then.
This has no flavor at all.
This is gross.
Gross.
Eat all of it please, eat up.
No, you.
No, you're the one who should eat all of it.
Yeah, you.
What the hell?
Why is that?
Why did you change from casual to polite?
You eat it. Seriously.
Ow!
See, you're so harsh with me!
Isn't it odd that it's only me!?
I'm the only one who gets hit like this! Ow ow ow ow ow
Why are you pinching me?
That hurts, geez... Why are you doing this?
This is just weird.
You're not even scooping anything.
It's all dry and crumbly.
What the hell are you doing?
Why only that much?
This isn't even funny, so take this off.
It tastes bad, right?
Right?
What the hell is this?
Matsumoto, give him this.
Oh, we have some condiments.
For the occasion, you know.
Condiments.
It'll improve the taste.
Let's add some flavor.
There's no way I can eat this.
Tabasco.
I will add dashes of this... To the back of your head.
Please, no, please!!
It's okay, the flavor will be improved.
Your way of thinking will be improved.
That's right.
Is this going to be okay?
Isn't it written on the label?
It's okay, it's okay.
Why would that be written on the label? To not pour this on one's head?
It says "Only for use on the back of the head."
Those are the instructions.
Wait wait, it actually says, "For use on the back of the head."
That's the same thing!
It's one of the many purposes.
It's definitely okay to pour.
Hold on a minute.
It's okay.
Massage that area for him.
What the hell.
Am I going to be okay?
What kind of situation has this developed into?
I'm going to soak his scalp.
Oh that seems pretty good.
It's applied very nicely.
Eat it, eat it now!
Hurry, hurry!
Do your best! Do your best!