@tofupizza on Twitter
Edited by
Mrs. ShibataBread
Shibatabread
Translation by
www.shibatabread.com
Gaki No Tsukai presents
Hosei Yamasaki's Solo Project
Yamachan Knows He Will Be Punk'd
Cocorico
Downtown
Hitoshi Matsumoto
Hosei Yamasaki
Masatoshi Hamada
Naoki Tanaka
Shozo Endo
Could you speak a little loud please?
Put some more punch in your voice
I tought I spoke loud enough...
No, you sounded like a nice mom
Ok, here my project
Yeah, what's up with it ?
Well, I haven't been tricked recently....
We might be too old for it now
You're past your prime
No, I'm still good
But don't we get laughs when I get punk'd??
It's really funny stuff
Says who?
His wife Aya says so
Right, my wife says I'm funny
His wife Aya is his world right now
Whatever he says, she said it first
He's right, my family is my world
I wanted to show you how good I am
at being punk'd
Acting skills?
Objective
Yamasaki demonstrate his 'getting Punk'd' acting skills
So it's all premeditated
Yeah, I will already know it's a prank
I think it will be funnier
If I pretend like I don't know I'm punk'd
Seriously, don't let us down
Don't worry
I got this
Don't make me say, "I should've watched another show"
Downtown Presents
Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende
Wow, I'm getting excited
Right?
Your nose hair is sticking out right now
Serious?
Is it a joke?
Look at your nose hair
Have I just been punk'd?
Yes, you've been punk'd
Don't punk me!
It looks like beetle legs coming out from your nose
We don't need to be punk'd
Let us begin!
How do we do this?
I'm about to choose how I will get punk'd
Rule
Yamasaki picks one of the nine pranks
That's the reason for the board
Nine options
Nine choices
I'm gonna start with No. 1
Yes, No. 1
Sexy Prank
The usual...
Yeah, we've seen this a lot in the past
Very popular trick
Celebs fall for this
We've seen many celebrities fall for this trick
I see
Ecstatic Yama-chan!!
Sexually Charged
So Sexy XXX
Good morning
Here comes Komurasaki, the instigator of the trick
Excuse me, but
we have a new Assistant Director
Is that so?
Let me do a quick introduction
A new Assistant Director
It's been a while
We haven't had a new one in a while...
Excuse me
Please introduce yourself
Sexy Assistant Director
Today's my first day
Nice to meet you all
You too
Nice to meet you, too
Let me clear away these magazines
Yamasaki can't help looking at her
Yamasaki peeks at her cleavage
Excuse me
Can you get me a coffee?
Yes
An underwear shot
Perverted Yamasaki stares at her underwear
I can see her white panties
He acts innocent
Thank you very much
Excuse me
Can you organize the clothes over there?
Cleavage Show
Cleavage
Happy Perverted Yamasaki
How can I not look at that?
Stares between his fingers
Hey, listen
You haven't stopped looking at my boobs
Well...
If you wanna se then so bad,
I'll show them to you!!
Punk'd
Can this be...!?
Is this...
They said "punk'd"?!!
Damn...
I knew something wasn't right
You're right
There's no way we'd get an Assistant like that!
Kazuhiro Fujiwara
License
Takafumi Inomoto
Right, something was wrong
How did I do?
did you see me doing this?
Yeah, I noticed that
It was supposed to be the funniest part
I would point out
that your acting was cheap
No. 9!!
Ghost Prank
Ghost...
That's a toughy
Toughy??
"What Was That Sound?!"
Terrifying Paranormal Activities
Yama-chan Screams!!
What're you reading?
Endo Reads a Ghost Book
i just happened to find this but
It's one of those scary books...
That's scary
Don't we attract ghosts by reading about them?
Yamasaki's mind is on ghosts
I've heard that
I didn't mean to scare you...
Bang
Yeah, this book is scary
That scared me a little...
Speaking of undying spirits...
Bang
Yamasaki is uneasy about the banging noise
What?
Did you hear that?
I heard a banging noise...
I don't think it's anything...
No, but seriously...
It's like a Poltergeist
Countdown to the
Tissues Moving
The unexplained events leave Yamasaki jumpy
The tissues just moved...
You sure ?
Countdown to the Plant Falling
I'm not kidding
I'm getting scared...
What?
I'm getting scared!
Secret Trick
But...it moved!
Yamasaki...
"I'm getting scared!!"
is so unrealistic and fake
What do you mean, "I'm getting scared"?
But why?
"I'm getting scared"
I was conveying my emotion
You could tell how emotionally charged I was getting
How about reacting after you find out you've been tricked?
Right, you didn't react at all
That's the crucial part of the show
Your mood didn't change at all
And that's fundamental
I agree
I was anticipating the change...
No. 5!!
Whoopee Cushion Prank
This is a ...
Old school...
This could be a game changer
If you can execute this well, it'll be good
I just farted
Toot
Yama-chan Becomes Embarrassed!
Excuse me but...
My stomach is...
Yamasaki conveniently leaves the room
Let me go trim my nose hair
Which is it, your stomach or the nose hair?
Well...
what a terrible actor
You two young comics shouldn't be watching this
You won't learn anything from this
It's not informative
I haven't heard comments like that in the past 10 years
Is that right?
Here comes Komurasaki to start the prank
Whoopee Cushion Set Up
It won't be easy
to act oblivious
He will need to be convincing that he doesn't know
That felt good
Yamasaki has no idea
You OK?
Yes
It's good that I went
You shouldn't hold that stuff in
What?
What the hell?!!
I thought I heard something!!
I didn't hear anything
Punk'd
I didn't hear a sound
Nothing,
I heard nothing
I didn't hear anything unusual
How was that?
A do over?
No. 3
Yakuza Prank
This is another standard gag...
We've all seen comedians tricked by this one
Right
This is a perfect one for him
This one should suit me perfectly...
Fear!
Yakuza Raid!
Yama-chan Cries Out
Don't mind us
Here we are
Fake Yakuza shows up
Oh man,
Hey
Is that Matsumoto and Hamada over there?
Oh!
I watched them on TV
Let's ask for something
Go for it
Fake Yakuza bothers Downtown
Hey, do something
Listen
If you don't mind...
C'mon man
I don't care, do something
Sorry about that
Who the hell are you?
We're having a meeting
Get outta here
Please leave us alone
Wait, wait, wait a minute
Yamasaki shows some balls
Who are you?
Get the hell outta here!
Please leave us alone
Please excuse us
Yamasaki is shocked by the gun
Hold it, hold it!
The instigator is shot
Get up!
Wake up!
Chest compression?!!
Yamasaki desperately tries to resuscitate the victim
Wake up!
W...Why?!!!
Way too dramatic...
Get your ass up!
Get up, asshole!
You shot him
And you're next in line
No!
No, no way!!
Say your prayers
Gun is aimed at Yamasaki
No!
Bye Bye
Bye bye
I don't wanna die!!
A
di
Adios
How many times...
Where's your reaction afterwards?!
That's the most essential part
What's with you?
Where's the reaction after you find out it's a prank?
Other than your, "Yeah" or " Ahh"
What is this ?
But how was it?
What?
How did I do?
What happened to your voice?
Did you blow out your vocal cords?
Toot!
How come you can't react to that??!!
It finally worked!!
You missed your chance to shine!!
A missed opportunity!
But all you do was turn red
What the hell are you doing?!
That was terrible...
You were like a little embarrassed girl
What's with you?
Get it together
No. 7
Well, here's another classic prank
Here Comes a Gorilla
Yamasaki, please get this right...
So, like we said...
Hamada-san, please...
Show us your reaction after
you find out you've been punk'd
He's said this numerous times
Since the beginning of the show
They might be edited out but he said it like four times
I know, I get way too into it sometimes..
I understand that
No, I'm cool with you getting into it
Even Tarzan Is Scared
Gorilla Raid
Yama-chan Panics!!
Goooorilla!!
Goorilla!!
Goorilla!
You missed again
That was the cue
What the...?!
Your initial reaction was...
one of the better ones I've seen today
Great idea
Shouting its name out loud
That was unprecedented
You called it,  "Goorilla!"
I was smelling gold
I thought, "Nice, he's a professional after all"
But you can't finish strong
What's this?
I'm having a stomach issue
I just can't shake it off
well, better take care of it now
I don't want any accidents in here
I just farted
Toot
Yama-chan Gets Embarrassed!
Komurasaki Arrives
to set up the Whoopee Cushion
Yamasaki has no idea
You OK?
Yes, i think I took care of it
That should be the last time...
You've always had issues with your stomach
Thanks for you concern
Toot!
You didn't do anything just now
Seriously, what's up?
We're no asking for an Oscar moment
Just show us something
It's been awhile, I'm still rusty
You're still rusty?
No. 6
Time Bomb Prank
Much respect if you can pull this off
This one's tough
This is complex
It calls for a very tense mood
Right, it's a life or death situation
It's an unrealistic situation
Unrealistic, but very tense
And you know it's fake
Premeditated
You'll have more admirers if you can pull this off
That sounds good
This won't be easy
Disable the Time-Bomb
Red
Yama-chan Saves the Day!
or Blue!?
May I have you attention?
The Fake Cops Arrive
We've just received a bomb threat
There's a bomb set up somewhere in this building
Please check your surroundings for anything suspicious
It could be anywhere in this room
Oh!
Wait
What's this?
Suspicious bag found under the table
Where did this come from?!
That's a huge bag
Place it on the table
Please open it
Whose is this?!
If you could open that, please
Open it here?
Yamasaki struggles to open it
So it's true...
Time Bomb Discovery
Wait a sec!!
It's a time bomb!!
OK, you!!
Take this, take this!!
Less than a minute left!
Officer hands him the wire cutters
47 seconds left!
No way!!
I don't want this!
You'll be fine!
No! I don't want them!!
I don't wanna do this!!
Wait!!
Cut the wire
40 seconds!
Cut it!
No way!!
No!!
Wait a sec!!
35 seconds left!
Please hurry!
look!
It's gonna explode!
Yamasaki panics
Please!
Hurry up!
14 seconds!
which one?!!
Cut it!
6 seconds!
3!
I got it?!
Well, well
Yamasaki-san
"I got it!?"
It was like a punchline
What the hell??
I understand it's very tense but
Yeah, I would for sure
You're sure?
Yes, especially with six sticks of dynamite
I have to point out
how carefully you held
the wire cutters so no one gets hurt
I thought, "Man..."
That was really calm
I lost it right then
If you wanna go there...
Show me how it's done then!
I'm telling you it's difficult
I don't know why you're pissed off
I mean, this was your idea after all
But who do you want to see do this?
Yeah, who?
OK then, Matsumoto-san, you try it
Which one?
Please do the "Time-Bomb" segment
What?!
Anything but that!
"Time-Bomb"!!
No, the "Time-Bomb" is very...
I can't do that all yelling and screaming
I know, I just went through it
OK then
Let's roll, "Time-Bomb"!!
I need to really focus
Yes, it requires a lot
I might need about two bananas to get through this
I'm burning some calories for this
I'm ready to go
Diffuse the Time-Bomb
Mattchan Saves the day!
Red
or Blue?
May I have you attention, please?!
We just received a bomb threat
The Fake Cops Arrive
the bomb is somewhere in this building
What?!
Are you serious?
Please check your surroundings
Check for any suspicious items
How can it be?!
Is this it?!
Suspicious bag found under the table
Whose is that?!
Carefully place it on the table
I'm scared, this is scary
Open it, please
I'm opening it?!
Please
That doesn't make sense!
Not good, not good, not good
This is bad
Time-bomb found
This is bad news
No, no, no!
Ok you, take this!
54 seconds left!
Why do I have to do this?!!
Give it to Hamada!
Matsumoto Gets the Wire Cutters
This isn't right!
I don't know what I'm doing!
Why don't you do it!
I'm not trained for this!!
It's gonna blow up!
34 seconds left!
Cut, cut, cut, cut it!
Please cut it
I'm terrified
Matsumoto is in full panic mode
10 seconds!
I'm scared!
Cut it
One!
Impossible...
This was...
I've never heard you be so loud
Very loud
The persistent feeling of humiliation
Someone else has to try this
I don't wanna be the only loser
We might as well...
We gotta pick someone to do this
Ohnuma-san...
I like it
"Gorilla" Prank
Pretend it's a real gorilla, OK?
if you let yourself think it's a gorilla costume,
you won't make it
Even Tarzan Is Scared
Gorilla Raid
Ohnuma panics!!
You serious?
How lame?!