1st Gaki-no-tsukai-ya-arahende!
Duo competition! The Game of Comedian's Life!
Meet the participants!
Cocorico!
I won't lose!
Jicho-Kacho!
I'll do it!
Football Hour!
I'll do my best!
And today we have special guests!
So please come on in!
Downtown!
- We made the Game of Life.
- I see.
It's very well done.
You spin the roulette and various events happen where you stop.
- Is this place like Osaka?
- That's right.
The theme is about a comedian just making his debut.
Each duo will get $20,000 each.
The team with the most money will win 100,000 yen.
Do we get the same as them, only $20,000?
- Yes, you all get the same.
- Is that right?
- Is that okay?
- Well, that's all right.
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]
Let's start with Cocorico!
May I spin this?
Well, that's okay.
- How about this?
- Please read the text out loud.
You plan a singles party for Nicho Kenju.
You got an allowance of $3,000 from them.
We don't do that kind of thing for our juniors.
- Here you go.
- Thanks!
You stopped at a nice square.
Jicho Kacho!
Come on big number!
4!
You perform at a local show in Akita Prefecture, but you are not paid for transportation.
You pay $3,000.
Then you must pay it.
- That's not an option.
- It happens.
Football Hour!
Come on!
Because I'm nervous.
Same as them.
I'll give you $3,000.
Thank you.
Next up is Downtown.
Go ahead.
He is good at spinning this.
You forgot all your lines in your first stage performance.
You got mad at Master Kyojin and stayed up all night drinking.
You have to pay $4,000.
Don't worry!
Yeah, I don't mind.
But...
Master Kyojin won't get mad at us for this.
We have never been mad at him for such a thing.
But It's just...
He has never been mad at us for forgetting a line in our manzai, but he has been mad at us for not saying hello to him.
And we couldn't drink these days.
This is not about you guys.
This is just the game of life.
We are willing to pay for this, but if we do so, we are affirming that Master Kyojin is the kind of person who does this kind of thing.
Are you guys taking Master Kyojin into consideration?
This is just a game and I don't think you need to worry about that.
He might say, "I won't be offended by that!"
This is just a board game.
In the meantime, would you mind paying me $4,000?
It's your first turn.
Then I will take $5,000 and give you back $1,000.
No, I'll pay you $4,000.
The game has just begun.
Reversing the situation later is also a real pleasure.
Excuse me.
I only got $2,000.
- I thought it was $2,000 for the two of us.
- It's $4,000.
$4,000 for the two of us?
This is confusing.
Do what you want.
- Write it down plainly.
- Sorry.
- Can I spin the wheel?
- Okay, Cocorico!
Second turn!
"STOP!"
STOP!: Moving to Tokyo
You get a congratulatory gift for moving to Tokyo from same generation comedians at the roulette numbers.
1-4: You get $5,000 each from all of them.
5-8: You get nothing because they are all jealous.
Then, pay them $5,000!
- Congratulations!
- You guys should come to Tokyo soon!
- You're early!
-I'm not the same generation as you guys!
In this game, we are the same generation.
What do that mean?
We don't have to pay, right?
We are not of the same generation as you.
In this game, we are comedians of the same generation.
That's unfair.
That's kind of confusing.
Is that so?
- But two of them have already paid, so we don't have to pay anymore, right?
- You guys already got $10,000.
- You shouldn't talk about money so much.
- That's not what I meant.
But this is a game where the team with the most money wins in the end.
You should pay rightly.
Yes, let's do it right. If you do it right, we won't say anything.
And I think there is a contradiction here.
Is that so?
Okay! Let's move on!
Okay, let's take one more turn.
It's confusing, let's take one more turn.
- Will you pay us next your turn?
- Well, you guys keep that in mind.
Guys, keep that in mind.
Next up is Jicho Kacho?
"STOP!"
Same as before.
- Come on, give me a 1 to 4!
- Roll a 5 to 8!
Yeah!
Thanks, I'll take it.
- Let's work together in Tokyo!
- Next up is Foot!
Wait a sec.
Pay them $5,000.
Will you also pay us now?
Will you pay us $10,000 altogether now?
To put that on hold for now.
Let's go, Foot.
Okay, keep that in mind, too.
Downtown hasn't stopped here yet, so maybe this will offset that.
So you guys keep that in mind as well.
6! "STOP!"
So please roll a 1 to 4.
It's not that easy.
It's not going to be.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks!
Hey, hey, hey, wait!
- Please pay Foot.
- To put that on hold for now.  It's our turn.
Anyway, now it's our turn.
- "STOP!"
- If we land exactly on this square, do we get anything?
No, it's all the same.
- 5 to 8!
- Yes!
- Yay!
Everyone else got a congratulatory gift except you guys.
You guys are making everyone jealous.
Why don't you give each of us $5,000?
- I'll pay for it, right!?
- Yes ...
I'll pay it.
There is such a thing as a promissory note.
It allows me to lend you money.
I'll borrow it when the time comes, but right now it's fine.
But right now it's fine.
It does not need me now.
I'm not in the mood.
Mood?
Let's keep this in mind.
They will eventually pay everyone $5,000 each.
3!
That's not good at all.
You blew up writing a crappy comedic theory on your blog.
You lose a turn.
Take a break.
It's 6!
You win the ABC Rookie Comedian Grand Prix for Best Rookie.
You get $10,000 cash prize.
Congratulations!
Hey, we won Best Rookie, too.
I know.
Then give us our money, too.
You really got the prize money, didn't you?
- Yeah.
- It's a game.
Why do players get money when the real winners don't get any?
We have never won it.
But this is a game.
I have no idea if this is real or a game.
It's a game.
It's just a game.
Is it a game?
Well, congratulations!
Great!
You got sunstroke and collapsed at an outdoor recording of Narutomo.
You pay $10,000 for hospitalization.
You idiot!
Pay up now!
$10,000 is a lot of money!
You were given $10,000.
That's enough!
Pay up now!
Is that going to happen at the outdoor reco...
Don't keep talking about it, just pay up!
It's okay.
Next, Downtown.
Come on!
6!
You failed to make it to Tokyo, so you're going back to Osaka.
Back 6 squares.
You guys are not doing well at all.
So, Tanaka, you think we failed to make it to Tokyo?
- The actual Downtown?
- Yes.
I think you guys were very successful.
Then we don't have to go back.
This is a game.
Huh?
This is what happens in the game.
What are you guys talking about?
I think this is wrong.
Why are we going back 9 squares?
Why the hell do we have to go back 9  squares?
It's 6 squares.
You're reading that upside down.
Then please go back 6 squares.
So, is it our turn next?
You guys are losing this turn.
Oh, I forgot.
Hey, you just broke the rules!
Pay up!
That's not right, you're losing this turn and you're trying to spin the roulette wheel.
This is outrageous!
It's like being on TV despite your misconduct.
You guys definitely have to pay the fine!
This is absolutely unacceptable!
- If you do it in the Bon (gambling house) , you have to cut off your finger.
- This is terrible!
Bon...
You've understudied Edo Harumi on a prime time show.
In an atmosphere of disquiet, they spin the roulette wheel.
Then Football Hour stepped into the forbidden area.
Here we go.
7!
Oh, this is dangerous!
You're in the middle of a recording for a cooking show, and a mischievous Hattori-sensei pushes wasabi up your nose.
The punishment game!
Please come to this stage.
Here we go!
- Ouch!
- Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Is it serious!?
Give me a break!
Ouch!!!
- After days of all-night recording sessions, you eat copious amounts of frisks to keep from getting drowsy.
- Punishment game!
Downtown is next.
1!
You guys eat a lot of Frisk!
Punishment game!
Please come to this stage.
Okay, Jicho Kacho do it to them.
Please come here!
I must see this!
Downtown?
Downtown, this is your punishment game.
That's enough.
What's with the vibe?
We can't do it at this timing.
- If we're going to do this, we should do it quickly.
We can't do it anymore at this timing.
- Right.
You guys are not good at leading us.
I could have done it if you had led us quickly.
But I've already reset my mood.
Now is not the time for Frisk.
I think we got here pretty smoothly.
What are you guys going to do with this vibe?
You think it's funny that we're drinking Frisk now?
What's the fun in us doing it now?
Now is not the right time for Frisk at all.
"The time for Frisk"...?
I've never heard of the time for Frisk.
Let's keep playing the game.
Let's just pretend we already did it and keep going.
Let's keep the game going.
If Downtown gets punished in the next game, let's take them there right away.
You guys are being too exuberant.
You don't have to get excited just because it's Downtown.
Just do it right away.
Then we can do it with good reactions.
We should have done it right away.
The timing wasn't good.
That wasn't the right time for Frisk.
"The time for Frisk"...?
- It's Downtown's turn.
Keep up the good work, you guys are a little behind.
- It's okay.
2!
You were in a panic because the oden you had in your gourmet report was too hot.
Let's do it!
Don't touch me, you idiot!!
You're hurting me.
Why are you pulling so hard?
Because it's timing to do this.
It hurts when you pull too hard.
- But you said...
- Ouch, ouch, ouch...
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
I'll pull gently, so let's do this.
The timing is not good anymore.
This vibe is not good.
This is not the time for hot oden.
We wanted to do it right away.
That's why we tried to take you.
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
You need to think more about how you're going to take us.
Hamada is very sensitive.
I'm not pulling him so hard.
But you guys need to take better care of him
You have to take his mentality into consideration.
That's the only thing I've been concerned about since our debut.
- Is he sensitive?
- Is it wrong for us to pull him?
If you guys verbally tell us, we'll definitely do it.
If he pulls like that,
we're going to lose our shoes.
We don't like it very much.
So, I should just tell you guys verbally?
So we are supposed to verbally lead you without touching you?
But do it as if you are pulling us along.
Okay.
I want to roll a large number
1!
You're reporting on a baseball all-star game, pissing off the players, and getting your butt whipped with a bat.
Over here!
- This way, please!
- Let's go this way!
- Come on, this way!
Hamada-san, this way please.
Don't pull them.
Wait a minute.
Hamada says he doesn't want to do it.
Does he wont  to do it?
He's not mad, he just doesn't want to do it.
- That's what a punishment is.
- Is he sick?
He's willing to do anything different, but getting his butt whipped with a baseball bat is bad for his image.
What then?
- So you want to do it alone, Matsumoto-san?
- I see. Hamada-san does not have to do it.
But it would be strange for me to do it if Hamada doesn't do it. That would make the audience think that Hamada is selfish.
"Why only Matsumoto? Why doesn't Hamada do it?"
It's fine if I'm the only one doing it, but I don't want people to think Hamada is selfish. And Hamada is not that kind of guy.
Hamada is working very hard today.
He's wearing shoes.
(You are being pelted with a lot of pies by mischievous pop idols on a late-night TV show.)
They've overcome many obstacles and the game has entered its final phase.
8!
STOP!: Challenge The Gubernatorial Election.
You declare a number, spin the roulette wheel, and if the number you declared comes up, you win.
You get $500,000 to celebrate.
If you miss, you lose $100,000, which means you lose your job for a while.
Okay, that's not an option.
Now call out a number and then spin the roulette.
- It's 7.
- 7! Okay, spin the roulette.
- Will it come out, I wonder?
- It won't come out so easily.
The odds are 1/8.
Please pay me $100,000.
Hey, it's a 7 now.
It's 7.
Okay, that's enough.
If you guys are going to talk like that, I don't need the money.
I'm upset.
If you talk like that, I don't want the money.
Please continue the game.
That's enough.
If it were true, you guys would get $500,000.
It's okay, let's call it even.
- You are hit by intense cold weather during filming in freezing Alaska.
- Punishment game!
Cocorico do it to them!
It's already cold.
- So scary!
- Are you ready?
Here we go!
Let's go!
Thank you!
It's even colder because of Frisk!
Oh, it's cold!
Let's continue the game.
Huh?
- Football Hour!
- Spin the roulette!
No, no, wait a moment.
Our money is gone.
All we have is a promissory note.
You guys had a lot of money.
Yes, we had pretty good money.
Matsumoto-san?
Let's go, Football Hour.
Matsumoto-san.
Did you guys have this much money?
Go next.
Why do you guys have so much money?
- Did you guys have that much money?
- Yeah.
What the hell!
- You guys are in a lot of debt.
- You guys don't stand a chance.
- So we're the winners?
- Anyway, let's spin the roulette once.
Yeah, 8!
Goarl!!
- Okay, 1st place!
GOAL: The first to arrive gets the prize money.
1st place: $1,000,000
2nd place: $500,000
3rd place: $300,000
$1,000,000.
Is there?
- No...
- Either way, we're the winners.
Then give us the prize money, please.
Is thsi it?
- Okay, thanks!
- Thank you.
Yeah!
Thank you!
Yeah! Okay!
I didn't think we could win.
Yeah, I didn't think we could win at all.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Me too.
Come again.
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]