First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai Ya Arahende!
Life of the "Ogoo" Pteranodon Endo!
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Housei
Alright!
Matsumoto-san      - Well, that's how it is
There was that gag on our last New Year's special
And that's Endo's Pteranodon
Yes
I think it will be forgotten soon
Wouldn't it be good?
PTEROSAUR
THE PTERANODON'S  UNREASONABLE REQUEST!!
Endo was suddenly requested to act like a pterosaur
And that gave birth to a new character:
From "No Laughing Prison" (2014)
Endo Pteranodon
Raise your voice more!!
Mooooooore!!
That's completely off!
His character was born from a cornered situation, but still...
I think that...
I can't let it sleep like this yet...
I want it to make a comeback this year...
But I have to come up with something good
For the sake of its comeback...
Endo promised to bring his Pteranodon back
He promised a comeback
What will his challenge be?
But how will he?
Today Endo is going to be alone
And he'll show us the life of Endo Pteranodon
The whole thing, from its birth to its death
Endo will perform all by himself its circle of life
In a 60-minutes-long play in 5 acts live on stage!!
L I F E   O F  E N D O  P T E R A N O D O N
In a theatrical form      - That's fucked up
Yeah, I agree
That's a pretty wide scale!
But you see, when he was doing this before
He made a lot of mistakes
He had troubles
Does it mean he's ready now?
Well, I think that
When Endo tries something and makes mistakes is the funniest!!
And if he succeeds?
When he does
And he's like "I got it", that's unreasonably not funny at all!!
That's because it contains Endo's peculiar unskillfulness!!
It does get boring
His harsh taste comes out !!
I really want them to have high hopes for today's play...
And when it's over
I want them to think "So that was its comeback"
AN
UN
KNO
WN
Tonight's episode of Gaki no Tsukai
LENGE
CHAL
Lies on Endo's hands
Curtain Raising
Endo Shouzo in:
Life Of The "Ogoo" Endo Pteranodon
Hundreds of million of years ago, in the Cretaceous Period
The four of them are monitoring the play from another room
The Earth was shrouded in warm temperatures
I like this clip
And full of rich natural environments
Such majestic plateau
Was the kingdom of enormous dinosaurs
That's amazing
The winged Pterosaur soars the sky
That's it, that's
the pteranodon
On the land, both carnivorous and herbivorous dinosaurs
He mistook it
for this, right?
Lived in such era of fighting for the survival of the fittest
Yeah, I think so
He did the
Triceratops
And in the midst of such era
A singular new life was about to make its first appearance...
Seems interesting
From its birth...
Woah, cool!
He did a good job
The beginning of "Ovo" looks like this
note: a touring circus production by Cirque du Soleil
Did Ovo had this?
Yeah it did
He's born
Endo Pteranodon
That's the birth of Endo Pteranodon
Can you smell the
unskillfulness?
Well, if you ask me if I can, then I'll answer:
I can smell it!!
I thought it
would take more!
It just started
It's already set
- Yeah, he said it
He said "Ogo"
Just when he
was born
So, that's a baby
What's going on?
I can already say
This is way better than "Busjack"
ENDO'S FIRST MOVIE
The Bus Hijacker
note: you can watch the reaction episode for its sequel on www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
I mean, I know
this
what I'll get from
I see
Here comes his
harsh taste
STAGING TIME
Look! His hand
is kinda...
Their shape is...
- Yes, right
It's forming up
The hell is he--?
Let's stop here
He stood up
He's finally up
note: I'm not subbing any "ogo" he shouts, it's just his cry
That was clear
That much?
Was it necessary?
What is he doing?
- Yeah, he ate it
He ate it
Eating the shell to stuff his belly
Endo Pteranodon is eating the shell of his egg
That's his
nourishment
But in that moment...
Oh!
What is--
ROOOAAARRR
A carnivorous dinosaur suddenly draws near
There he goes
His hash taste rolled out from him!!
Well, you see
I did warn you
STAGING TIME
8 minutes passed
since it began
I told you so, guys
The hell is he doing?
As soon as it starts raining, the carnivorous dinosaur leaves
It started raining
Right, woah
He should have
used the leaf now
- That's right
- Yeah...
Poor thing, huh?
He took it again
Are you sure that
is the right way
to use it?
With his hands
Are those his
hands?
At this point he--
What the? Why
is he eating again?
Eating the shell to stuff his belly, once more
He ate a lot
The hell!
He's eating a lot,
what the hell
Matsumoto-san,
Do you think our audience can endure this?
For our Endo Pteranodon,
born in the age of dinosaurs,
A voyage known as "life" is about to begin
- Oh, yes
It's starting now
End of Act One
I see...
That's the end of the first act
STAGING TIME TILL NOW
Why aren't we watching it under the stage?
If we were there, we would talk too much
Oh I see
We'd be noisy
He would hear us
We'll be heard talking by him
I see, I see
And then
If he notices we laughed a bit, he'll repeat that same thing forever!!
Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Translation & Subtitles by Shion
Want to support my translations?
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Act Two: Childhood Arc
The season changed?
- It did change
It surely changed
He can now
perfectly stand
He has a pattern...
True, on his body
How old is he
supposed to be now?
Well, looks like
he feels at ease
He's lively
Yeah, a lot
He surely is lively
He's an infant
now, right?
He's playing with
interesting
what he founds
Ok but seriously,
what are those?
Are those hands?
- Right
Not fangs?
I mean, he always did this
Yeah, he did that last time
And now he's doing this instead
And now he's
doing this instead
So hands-- hands?
Those are hands!
Looks like it
I'm pretty sure
by the time this
will be over
He'll end up with
two broken fingers
He smacked em
Why is he-?
He's wiggling
He probably thinks he's cracking us up with this!!
I bet he's
thinking that!
- Just now, yes
You think so?
He found a lump of meat stuck in a tree
STAGING TIME
Endo Pteranodon, who just found some meat on a tree,
Decides to climb it to acquire it
Come on,
Those are hands...
Prove me wrong
He goes "ogoo" whenever he can't use his head
That's because "ogoo" means he's thinking...
Oh, he made it
Good, good, he did it
Huh? Looks like he
still can't reach it
- And what now?
He can't reach it
Oh, come on! He's
clenching his fist
Where did his fangs go ?!
Geez...
This is no good
By this point our audience probably changed channel !!
They're all watching YORUTAMORI
- Yeah, most likely
note: A variety show broadcasted every sunday (2014-2015)
That's bad
End of Act Two
Geez      - Oh! We're done
STAGING TIME TILL NOW
I have thousands of complaints about this
Well, we can't speak directly to Endo at the moment
Yes
So, let's call the staff and told them to say him "the situation's harsh"
Now!?     - How can that be better?
If we say that now...
- Yeah, it'll probably influence him
Act Three: Adolescence Arc
That's his adolescence
His tail!
It became huge
- It really grew up
It grew so long
Even his face...
Right
He became an adult
Never saw that
face on him before!
It's a new face
He became handsome
For our grown-up Endo Pteranodon, the season of love is about to arrive...
The season of love..?
I guess for us humans
It's around the 20s
It's a female Ogoo
A female Pteranodon appears
Yes, a female
- Creepy!
Disgusting
- It's freaky
What the...
It's an Ogoo girl
Ogoo girl...
What will he do?
COURTING DANCE
That's his
courting dance
"Ogo" at all
He's not saying
- He's not...
You're right
His hands again
So that's how it
works with Ogoos
Here goes
- Yeah right
He didn't hesitate
Endo felt the urge
to add this scene
What the hell
- He made her a pillow
So considerate
I see, he used his
tail as a pillow
A tail pillow
Then what's the
point of that arm?
He keeps using
his hands!
I guess they're a couple now...
They are
Is that so?
Yeah
Endo Pteranodon has found a partner
, but suddenly...
A rival-in-love dinosaur appears
A
lival
in rov--
A rival
-in-love
Wha-?!
dinosaur
appeared
He stuttered!
I didn't know
it was live
That's what
surprised me
Really...
So it's not
pre-recorded...
- Got him
He made it!
Like that, go!
"I protected you"
He's saying
"until the end"
He protected her?
I think that's
what that meant
But it's still there
What the?
That's the sweat
of someone who's
trying his best
What was that?
I don't think there
are types of sweat
I think that's
that type
I don't think we
YORUTAMORI tonight
can win against
We can only hope they're doing the exact same thing on YORUTAMORI
If that's the case, we're good
You think so?
Endo's still
not done yet
They've been glaring each other for 6 minutes
There's still more
Of course
- Yes?
And once he's done
The dummy still
won't move
I see
And he'll
get confused
I see
This is a battle between him and his other self
What's that battle
supposed to be?
That stage assistant
is such a bad guy!
He's not moving
He won't move
that thing off stage
He's just waiting
for instructions
Yeah...
See? Now he's---
What the?
Oh! He's going away
Of course he has
in the end
to do something
[censored]
End of Act Three
When it began I thought it won't have much story
But by now
STAGING TIME TILL NOW
We're at the fourth act, how will the story unfold?
Good point
I must say, it really got my attention somehow
I agree
I think that
Our audience must be thinking
"What the hell are those idiots talking about?!"
What are you being so serious about?
Don't worry, we've been just spitting out lies right now!!
Act Four: Adulthood Arc
After experience love many times
Endo Pteranodon, which is now an adult,
Has now a family
Oh! I thought so!      - I'm glad!
He wasn't that
small before
That's a human baby
- The shape of his
They're raising him
shoulders changed
Ok, I got it
Those are definitely hands (not fangs)!!
It's a sort of pond
Some fishes discovered in a pond
There are fishes
His baby!
He fell
- I don't think so
Did he noticed it?
His mom's
stance is weird
Is he mad?
This is...
This is the scene
In which we get
to briefly see
This father and
son bonding moment
All live
STAGING TIME
But even with such an happy family...
It's coming
What?
That must be
pretty big---
Oh, it's the same
A rival-in-love dinosaur appears
So irritating...
The hell is this?
He came again
- Yes
It must be his
natural enemy
That's the same
scene from before
He likes his wife?
What's his deal?
Is that why he's
targeting him?
- It's not, right?
- Yeah...
That's not really clear
He passed by
- Did he noticed him?
He just passed by
He hugs his wife
He protected them
He looks relieved
So, he protected his family?
That's right
What the hell...
- Yeah, all of them
He picked em all up
He's back
Again!?
The rival-in-love dinosaur appears again
He's back at it
I wasn't
expecting that
I mean, one time
or two is fine, but...
Oh! He got him!
He's like "don't
ever come again"
Exactly
He got angry
He hurt him good
The moments spent along with
his beloved wife and son were
the happiest for Endo Pteranodon
About the "ogoos", it's more about variation than frequency...
End of Act Four
STAGING TIME TILL NOW
Meaning, that's the...
Hardest part      - Exactly
But in the end he didn't shout for us any remarkable "ogoo"
I can't understand why!!
He must be lost in thoughts
Is that it?
Must be that, yes
Amazing
As expected from him
I think
I think a nasty ogoo boom is going to happen this year
There will be statues of him!!
note: he actually says "hagoita", japanese ornamental paddles
Final Act: Old Age Arc
Endo Pteranodon: last chapter
Woah! He became
so old!
He surely aged
He aged all at once!
Is that the way they grow old?
He's just an old man!!
His son has left the nest
and his wife was gone before him
But something is about to unfold before his very eyes...
Come on, he's too
old for this now
You're right
An UFO comes flying in
Well, that's an
unexpected twist!
- I know right?
It's an ashtray
Isn't this a surprising turn of events?
This...
An alien appears
So it happened
What a great finale
that face
Can't blame
It was too sudden
That's the first
invader he saw
He bowed before him
It's like a God
I don't get this
What is he doing?
But just on that moment...
Meteorites
Huge meteorites crash down on Earth from space
Huge meteorites crash down, the Ice Age approaches
The sky becomes covered in hot clouds
And the Ice Age starts instantly
STAGING TIME
The ice age, huh
He's still small
You're right
Didn't he left
the nest?
Enough with that
- So long!
Why?
It's taking so long
I gotta say, it's
kinda touching
- It is, right?
It would been good if the dinosaur popped out now...
His rival, right?
I don't think
he'll pop out now
STAGING TIME
There's nothing
left to do
- You think so?
Is that him?
Just when it was
about to end!
He was ready to die!
He's a gradnpa
A fighting grandpa
And yet he's still
protecting him
Protecting is ok, but
come on, fight!
What now?
What will he do?
He's standing!
He's standing
nonchalantly!
Sorry, I'm lost
I have no idea
what's going on
They're glaring
at each other
His opponent is...
Ohh, he hid well
STAGING TIME
He must be tired
It's almost over
I want it (the dinosaur) to appear one more time
I won't let this play reach an ending!!
He's unkillable
He's back!!
He came again!
What will he do?
Ogoo!
What now?!
This is the best
He doesn't give up
Of course he's doing
The inoki-ari-jotai
note: a MMA style consisting in fighting while lying down
He's done for
What the hell
The End
In the end the last act was the longest
TOTAL STAGING TIME
Yes, you're right
It never crossed my mind
How long this was taking
What?
Are you for real?       - I swear
After this...
An unexpected situation: they'll call for a retake!!
Hi
Hey
Congrats
So...
Do you think the "Ogoo" will become popular?
Well...
To be honest, we all agreed that
You hardly ever said any "ogoo" all over the play
Oh, I see...
He's right, that was the main issue
Would you  mind do it one more time for us, please?
Only the beginning was good
Ohnuma, come here
Ohnuma Akihiro
producer
Raise your voice more!!
You're scared when you shout
At least with the first "ogoo"
But then, the more you shout it, the less scared you become
The more you do it, remember
Come on, one more time!!
He didn't shout much...
Yeah, too soft
That's the issue
Come on, you gotta shout more,
wait a sec!!
It's not coming out from your very first "ogoo"
Translation & Subtitles by Shion
Again
Ok
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Shout it from there
www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
I still can't feel it
Want to support my translations? Consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
Please, don't ever say "ogoo" again in your entire life!!
This is a no-profit translation made by a fan for other fans, all copyrights
are reserved to their respected owners
for updates & support like my page: www.facebook.com/shionnotsukai
main website (archive): www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
want to support my work? Buy me an Oyan Fifi: www.ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai