0 0 m -221.25 -49.125 b -229.125 -50.125 -250.5 -49.125 -248.25 -31.375 b -249.375 -21.5 -228 -1.75 -222.375 -0.625 b -213.375 5.625 -210 -1.75 -204.375 -2.875 b -197.625 -9.5 -190.875 -11.625 -184.125 -28.125 b -181.875 -43.5 -196.5 -44.625 -197.625 -45.875 b -206.625 -50.125 -214.5 -49.125 -221.25 -49.125 m -215.625 -43.5 b -205.5 -45.875 -192 -39.25 -194.25 -32.625 b -202.125 -41.25 -208.875 -41.25 -215.625 -43.5 m -273 -140.25 b -268.5 -140.25 -230.25 -132.625 -235.875 -82.125 b -243.75 -50.125 -265.125 -34.75 -271.875 -31.375 b -275.25 -30.375 -293.25 -16.125 -318 -39.25 b -323.625 -50.125 -334.875 -62.375 -327 -89.75 b -323.625 -100.75 -318 -121.75 -297.75 -133.75 b -292.125 -137 -283.125 -142.5 -273 -140.25 m -171.75 -142.5 b -169.5 -142.5 -142.5 -150.25 -118.875 -109.5 b -115.5 -99.625 -106.5 -87.5 -112.125 -56.75 b -118.875 -31.375 -130.125 -30.375 -136.875 -28.125 b -142.5 -28.125 -150.375 -21.5 -177.375 -40.25 b -186.375 -47.875 -199.875 -52.375 -205.5 -83.125 b -204.375 -83.125 -217.875 -103 -189.75 -133.75 b -184.125 -138.25 -178.5 -142.5 -171.75 -142.5 m -275.25 -106.25 b -306.75 -100.75 -288.75 -66.625 -274.125 -70 b -269.625 -70 -259.5 -72.25 -257.25 -87.5 b -260.625 -105.25 -267.375 -104 -275.25 -106.25 m -275.25 -96.375 b -268.5 -98.625 -265.125 -89.75 -266.25 -87.5 b -266.25 -78.875 -273 -78.875 -276.375 -78.875 b -280.875 -79.875 -283.125 -84.25 -282 -89.75 b -282 -92 -279.75 -96.375 -275.25 -96.375 m -273 -92 b -276.375 -90.75 -275.25 -86.5 -273 -86.5 b -270.75 -86.5 -268.5 -90.75 -273 -92 m -163.875 -106.25 b -188.625 -101.875 -177.375 -67.75 -163.875 -71 b -159.375 -70 -148.125 -72.25 -148.125 -92 b -151.5 -105.25 -160.5 -106.25 -163.875 -106.25 m -163.875 -96.375 b -149.25 -96.375 -153.75 -78.875 -161.625 -78.875 b -163.875 -77.625 -172.875 -79.875 -170.625 -89.75 b -170.625 -92 -169.5 -96.375 -163.875 -96.375 m -161.625 -92 b -165 -89.75 -162.75 -85.375 -160.5 -86.5 b -157.125 -87.5 -159.375 -92 -161.625 -92 m -277.5 -86.5 b -279.75 -86.5 -278.625 -83.125 -277.5 -83.125 b -276.375 -83.125 -275.25 -86.5 -277.5 -86.5 m -165 -85.375 b -167.25 -85.375 -166.125 -82.125 -165 -82.125 b -163.875 -82.125 -162.75 -85.375 -165 -85.375 m -334.875 -160.125 l -105.375 -160.125 l -105.375 63.75 l -334.875 63.75 m -107.625 -158 l -332.625 -158 l -332.625 61.625 l -107.625 61.625
TPF
Are you fucking kidding me, OI!
Tonight we pranked Hamada
Tonight, we pranked Hamada
WHAT?!
That was a 'Great Quotes Journey'!?
Without knowing anything, will he give us some great quotes?
Great Quotes Journey  to Enoshima!
Hamada Dokkiri
This journey will reveal it all
Oh man, there are loads of elementary school kids here
The quote he came up with on a really packed and shocked train
And the quote he came up with on a really packed and shocked train
I'm going to
Furthermore, he continues with his shocking quotes
You seriously can't  say something like that!
Secret Camera
catches him saying another quote
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
And the secret camera catches him saying another quote
No one is saying anything!
Tofu Panda Fansubs Presents:
DownTown's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
**We're also on Facebook and Twitter**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
Christian
Mickstar
(Team Gaki)
Otviss
Proodreader:
Translator:
Typesetter:
TPF
On this day everyone in the studio was nervous
On this day, everyone in the studio was nervous
Good afternoon
We pranked Hamada
That's right, we
dokkiri'd Hamada
Good afternoon
The other 5 who are all involved as well enter the studio
The 5 who are involved in the Dokkiri come into the studio
After this, we reveal all whilst filming
Allow us to explain what the Dokkiri is about
What the Prank is about
when speaking casually
A rumour has it that Hamada comes up with
great quotes
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
To find out if this was true
they sent him on a fake filming outing
We heard a rumour that Hamada comes up with great quotes when speaking casually
So in order to find out if that was true...
We sent him on a fake filming outing.
What will Hamada do when he finds out...
And Hamada has no idea yet what is happening
How will he react?
We are rolling in 3...2...1...
So um....
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
basically...
apparently...
Quotes,
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
you know
Have you guys come out with like... quotes during your careers?
Quotes
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Have you guys come out with like... quotes during your careers?
I think when I said, "A burdock is just a tree and only a tree" is like my quote...
Tsukitei Hosei
It's like something only I can say
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
That's true
A quote
cannot
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
just be
created because you want
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
to create one
I think it's when you're speaking normally and
a quote
comes out is when it is a 'quote'
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
What I just said
is
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
now my quote.
I've also heard a rumour recently...
What the hell are you on about?
I see
Hamada-san...
You casually come up with great quotes.
That's what I've heard.
Rumour about Hamada
When casually speaking, comes up with great quotes
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Really?
Without trying to?
Yeah.
If that's true, that is really amazing.
What are you talking about?
So, umm...
You know...
You went and did something for us, didn't you?
Huh?
You went there and did a little something for us?
Where?
A Great Quote
Journey
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
A Great Quote Journey?
You went on a little great quote trip, right?
What the hell is this
Great Quote
holiday?
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Umm...
So umm...basically
Note behind camera
The recording we did yesterday as was actually
about you coming up with great quotes
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
So Hamada-san
Huh!?
Great Quote
trip!?
Wait, are you telling me that was a little
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Don't mess with me!!
You went
Yes yes
to film for the promotion video
Was invited by Nakada Yasutaka to film for
Hamada Bamyu Bamyu's new promotion video
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
of Hamada Bamyu Bamyu, right?
Yeah, to Enoshima.
Right, Enoshima.
But actually, we didn't tell you this...
This is ridiculous, you've got to be kidding me!
A prank!!
No seriously guys, like...
They made me walk so much
Yeah
In Enoshima
I think I said it while filming, but
I totally understand how Yama-chan feels now.
I have no trust for the staff here at all anymore.
I know, right?!
Yeah, you've lost all trust for them too, right?
I'm sorry that you feel like that,
but let's try to build some trust up again.
So, let's hear your great quotes and...
come up with a single quote
I have not
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
come up with a single quote!!
They just made me walk around
and that was it.
But it's when you're acting normally...
While you were walking around normally
great quotes
have come out of your mouth.
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
No seriously, I haven't come up with one.
Well we have a lot to watch.
I want to see it now!
Oh man oh man...
I think there will be a few.
Are you fucking kidding me, OI!
So did Hamada-san naturally come up with some
great quotes
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
during his trip, let's check it out.
VTR start!
You've got to be kidding me!!
A string of great quotes from Enoshima
After the break
After the break, a string of great quotes from Enoshima!
There are so many elementary school kids on there
I will
Hamada goes to Enoshima special!
Inamoto Junichi
License
What the hell!
What's wrong?
Invited by Nakada Yasutaka, Hamada has been dragged out for a shoot
for his Hamada Bamyu Bamyu promotion video
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Like, seriously...today
I'm going to moan so much like Heipo
Please don't do that.
Inamoto didn't know either, right?
I'll do it in a really polite way as well.
Correct.
Like, really polite and correct Japanese.
"It really is like this, right?"
That's totally Heipo-san.
This is a special episode for Hamada Bamyu Bamyu.
I've already said I've had enough.
It doesn't matter how many times you say you've had enough,
you've been invited by Nakada Yasutaka-san.
How much of a big shot is this Nakada guy?
Nakada-san has nothing to do with it really..
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
A quote to hurt the feelings of a man he's never even met
Someone I've never met...
How much of a big shot is this Nakada guy?
No no no...
I'm saying that I don't want to do it though
But you've got to do your job there properly, right?
Isn't there anyone I can speak to about it?
That would be Heipo-san...
We explain to the moaning Hamada what he's going to be up to on this 'fake trip'
After this, putting up with the moaning Hamada, we explain what he is going to be up to today.
Are you guys kidding me??
We gave him the money he needed for the trip and he was ready...
We gave him the money he needed for this journey and he was ready to go.
I don't get why I've got to do this.
Please smile when you're being filmed today, okay?
You just want me to look happy, right?
Yes, please.
I'm going to be like this the whole day.
That's no good...
Please smile.
Off camera, you're
so nice to everyone usually!
You never make that kind of face!
Journey Begins
He doesn't seem too happy about it,
but his journey begins!
This is horrible.
Since we are going to Enoshima, you're going to ride the Eno train.
Staff
Wait, we're not going by car?
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
A quote only a super celebrity can come up with:
Wait, we're not going by car?
They're just making a meal of it.
No! No! No!
Man, he's a proper celebrity.
When you go on a trip, you ride the train.
First, he heads to the train station.
He really is a star.
He heads for the station.
When...
Oh, hello there.
Oww...
There's no need to film that, man!
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
A desperate quote to hide the fact that he's an old man:
What the hell is this?
Oww...There's no need to film that man!
Why is he speaking with like no emotion in his voice?
Won't people think that I'm doing a new program by myself, like about my adventures and stuff?
It looks so crap, man.
I can't be doing this when I'm by myself.
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
A quote for his beloved partner (Matsumoto):
No no no, what the hell?
I can't be doing this when I'm by myself
That really
Hit me in the feels right now...
Oh piss off!
Hello, there.
Everyone looks like they're having fun even though it's so hot, are they all okay?
Sup!
He waves to the people, starting to look like a journey program
He starts to talk to the people around him, making it look like a show about his journey...
This really is truly amazing.
You would be happy if Hamada-san waved to you.
But...
Can we finish now?
No no no...
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
An awful 'boke' joke...
Can we finish now?
What the hell is this, seriously?
After 5 minutes of walking...
We see Shichirigahama Station
I see, the Eno Train.
Shirichirigahama is meant to be a nice place, right?
I would have helped her if she had waited.
Buying a ticket to Enoshima
First off, he must buy a ticket to Enoshima.
Enoshima, right?
It's so easy, it says right here that it costs 220 yen.
You were close to pressing the button next to it there.
No I wasn't...
What you eating there?
Ohh I see, Bara-zushi?
(Note: Bara-zushi is basically Sushi with a variety of ingredients sprinkled on the rice)
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
A quote only someone so frank could say:
This pisses me off so much!
Bara-zushi?
What the hell!?
Wait, that part?
Not the  'What are you eating there' part?
You're right!
They quote the 'bara-zushi' part?
This happened when we were waiting for the train.
It just casually came out of Hamada's mouth...
Is the lens getting cloudy? If it's getting cloudy, let's just stop recording...
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
A remark to scare the staff:
I wasn't trying to scare them at all!
If it's getting cloudy, let's just stop recording...
Who the hell is doing the narration here?
While we were doing that...
Here it is.
A train came from the opposite direction
A train going the other way came in
There really are quite a lot of people
on the train...
Do we get on this...oh, we don't get on it?
Oh, we're going the other way.
Please hurry up and go...
Please just hurry up and go...
I get how you feel.
you know?
That's terrible of you!
Unbelievable...
They're just taking pictures of me without permission.
On top of that...
Lady, wow, you really are something else...
Oh my god!
Usually I would get really angry, seriously...
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
A quote banging on about image rights:
I would get really angry,
Usually
seriously...
Oh just leave it out!
Isn't this like...
If I stopped her, it would become a huge thing...
So isn't it the staff's job to stop her?
Train going to Enoshima pulls up
This time, a train going to Enoshima arrives.
Oh man, there are loads of elementary school kids on the train...
WOAH!
Woah...!
Wow!
Oh my god...
That is tough!
Yeah, it is.
And because it's tough, we'll get some great quotes out of you.
Gets on a train with school kids and everyone, causing panic
Coincidentally gets on a train full of school kids
and other customers.
The atmosphere in the train goes crazy.
That's great.
Seriously...
(to the staff) I'm going to kill you all.
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Along with the staff
a quote to scare the citizens:
No no no, that's wrong!
I'm going to kill you all.
This is genuinely something  you can't say!
The train leaves with everyone in a state
The train leaves with everyone in a state.
Please just stop this...
Why are there so many kids, is it a school trip?
School trip?
(Staff) It looks that way...
Oh, a junior high school trip?
This is truly amazing.
Just out of curiosity, but where are you going?
Enoshima...
Hamada
Oh, I see.
Oi Hamada
Who the hell is calling me without the honorifics?
I'll smack you one!
He's getting close to his destination, Enoshima
We are now getting closer
to his destination, Enoshima
When...
Which TV channel are you from?
Excuse me?
TV channel?
NTV (Nihon Television)
Oh really?
It's my favourite TV channel.
Oh is it? Well thank you very much.
I love Miyane-ya.
Oh Miyane-ya? But Miyane-ya is on Yomiuri TV channel, though!
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
A quote to make her feel the 'Kansai' love:
(Note: Kansai is Osaka, where Hamada is from)
But Miyane-ya is on Yomiuri TV Channel, though!
That's true, though.
Ten minutes pass on the train and they arrive
Ten minutes pass on the train,
and they arrive at Enoshima station.
This was so annoying, I really got done over here...
Were you by yourself the whole time?
He exits the gates and after 15 minutes of walking.
15 minutes of walking
It's amazing weather.
So what, do I need to walk quicker here or anything like that?
No, not at all.
Oh, right.
So I just have to go over this bridge now.
Enoshima
A small island which is famous in it's prefecture, Enoshima
Just before the temples, there is a famous pathway for it's food
and is busy all year round
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Just before the temples,
there is a famous pathway for it's food
and it is busy all year round.
I know this place, I have been here before.
I've been here, too.
Straight ahead?
What kind of quotes will come out of his mouth here?
So...what kind of quotes will come out of his mouth here?
This shop here is famous for their octopus crackers.
Staff
It's a very famous rice cracker shop you can line up for...
Wow, that's amazing.
Oh, really?
(Note: Honten means main store)
Asahi Honten
Enoshima's most packed shop, Asahi Honten
350 Yen
Octopus cracker
and the reason is...
their famous rice crackers which use real octopus.
That looks amazing.
Octopus crackers
Something you want to line up for
Something you definitely want to try, even if it means lining up.
So what are we going to do?
So, basically...
Staff
We want you to line up and try one.
Are you serious?
Well yeah...you should.
They're famous for their octopus crackers, right?
But the woman over there said that the spiny lobster cracker was really good.
This time, Hamada decided to choose the spiny lobster cracker.
You didn't choose the famous octopus cracker?
Cook
Hamada-san, why don't you give it a try?
Come over here and give it a go?
Cook
It'll be even tastier if you make it yourself and eat it.
How the hell has this happened?
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Making a huge deal out of something so small:
This is ridiculous, just cut it out you guys!
How the hell has this happened?
That's normal.
How to make it
Just put the spiny lobster on the rice cracker and press it down hard
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
It's very simple to make. Spread the rice dough...
Place the spiny lobster on it and push down hard.
And close it?
Yes.
And turn this slowly.
Like this?
Oh wow, it's making a hell of a sound now!
Now just quickly push it to the left.
Surely I've cooked it too much?
After waiting 5 minutes
After waiting 5 minutes...
Can I open it?
It looks good.
And how does it taste?
Damn, that looks good.
Well since I cooked it myself, it tastes really good.
After exiting the shop, Hamada again...
And after leaving the shop, Hamada again...
Well if you make something yourself, anything will taste good.
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Thinking no-one heard what he said the first time
he really grinds to get heard a second time:
'Really grinds to get heard a second time'
anything will taste good.
If you make something yourself,
Arrives at the entrance of Enoshima Shrine
So hot...
Before we know it, we have arrived at the entrance of Enoshima temple.
Enoshima Temple
Enoshima has the three Gods of wealth
Three Gods protect the temple.
After climbing 326 steps, you can get a great view of your surroundings.
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
They are known as Miyashiro and
after climibing 326 stairs
you get a great view of your surroundings from the observatory.
On his way to see the shrine and observatory
Soon...
My working hours on my contract
finish for the day...
Had we not decided something like that at our union meeting?
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
A really old joke to try
to cheer up the staff:
Had we not decided something
like that at our union meeting?
Okay yeah...this is a bit....
So we are right at the top now?
Umm no...this is the bottom level
Staff
You're kidding me...
Praying in Enoshima Shrine
Anyway, since he's gotten this far, he prays.
Shall we go home?
He goes and sees a street performance
He next comes across
a street performance taking place.
I do remember this part.
Bits of his Spiny lobster cracker
This is what I'm talking about...
No one is saying anything!!
That's the kind of thing I'm talking about...
Hidden Camera
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
A little break
Huh?
Hamada-san...So if you can eat your meal, do the final few scenes and then we will be done.
Staff
Can I just...?
Oh, thanks.
Inamoto
It's been on your face for ages.
Then tell me!
It's literally
Inamoto
been on your face since you left that rice cracker shop.
Are you taking the piss?
It was here the whole time.
But when I saw you up here again, it had moved up your face a bit.
Inamoto
You...
I thought I shouldn't tell you.
Right we're going back to the bottom, we're doing it all again.
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
33 years in showbiz, today's number one quote:
Today's number one?
What the hell, man?
Right we're going back to the bottom,
we're doing it all again
What the hell is this, seriously.
Man, this pisses me off.
Hidden Camera
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
I was thinking, "Oh man, it's still there."
It might not be at Yamazaki's level, but man I don't trust the staff here at all.
After the break,  the journey continues
The great quotes journey continues
The great quotes journey still continues.
Oh dear...
Come on, what do you want?
There was nothing there, so...
Oh shut it...
So I was wondering what tripped you up...
This.
Hello
Thanks for having us.
Enoshima-tei
It has been open since 1909, Enoshima-tei.
A terrace seat to take in the surrounding beauty
What a lovely place.
You get a terrace seat to enjoy the beautiful surroundings.
And because they're experts about fish, their Shirasu Zanmai Gozen is beautiful.
(Note: It's like a fish-based tapas.)
2500 Yen
Shirasu Zanmai Gozen
That's great.
It's lovely.
It's good.
But seriously...
Do we need a part with me eating (for the Hamada Bamyu Bamyu PV)?
I think you do, no?
Surely not?
If you look at the idol's marketing their videos, there are scenes of them eating too.
They don't eat Gozen though, right?!
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
A short and useless quote:
They don't eat Gozen though, right?!
That's kind of true, though.
You're not eating at all!
I am!
You really don't eat at all, do you?
I'm eating so much.
If you don't eat and can still do everything normally,
there's only one explanation for it...
You're doing drugs, aren't you?
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
Only because he knows the industry inside out,
a very Hamada-like quote:
You got straight to the point!
There's only one
You're doing drugs, aren't you?
explanation for it...
And there we have it, Hamada's Great Quote Journey!
That's it for Hamada's Great Quote Journey
You guys, seriously, cut it out.
Stop taking the piss.
The first thing I do when I leave here, I'm going to smack Yanaoka (producer)!
Well that's understandable...
To be honest, that was also
a quote
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
right there
First thing when I leave here, I'm going to smack Yanaoka!
Quote
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
"First thing when I leave the studio, I'm going to smack Yanaoka!"
This is just ridiculous!
I can't actually believe they would lie to me...
But that lie got all those quotes...
They're not quotes! It's just me reacting!
What's your favourite?
For me it's the  'Bara-zushi'
That is a great one!
For me though, it has to be
'They don't eat Gozen though, right?
It's got that Tsukkomi in it as well
and it just compliments the phrase really...
'Miyane-ya is Yomiuri TV though'
is something I will remember for a while, too...
I'll just remember that if something bad ever happens...
I'm honestly shocked.
Seriously, we have no working relationship (staff).
Quote
We have no working relationship.
m 0 0 l 0 15 l 18 15 l 18 0
There's another great quote.
No no no.
I seriously understand what Yama-chan was going on about now.
Hang on a minute...
Who here actually
trusts the Gaki staff??
Yama-chan and I don't trust them at all.
I don't trust them at all either.
I don't trust them at all.
I've had a lot of shit happen to me,
so I don't trust them,
Seriously, they've got me real bad in the past,
From the moment they got Endo really badly,
I've never trusted them.
The trust died 20 years ago.
20 years ago, right?
No one trusts the staff in the slightest.
It's so ridiculous.
Wait, did Inamoto know or not?
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
He didn't know?
No, he didn't.
So Inamoto, you were tricked too along with me.
There was a camera next to me the whole time and I was thinking, "Is it rolling or not?"
But you've just listened to this whole conversation.
What do you think? You might have been pranked but how do you feel personally?
I'm really touched.
Right?
That's exactly it.
We got to do a great episode together.
He's so touched by this experience.