Matsumoto, out of 100 how would you rate yourself?
Subbed by: HouseiGIFs, Dael, GodzillaRadio, J-Hive, Mickstar813, Razuberii
Q: Out of 100, how would Matsumoto rate himself as a man?
100.
100 Questions
Matsumoto Hitoshi's
Last week on the show was a quiz:
Matsumoto Hitoshi's 100 Questions!
I've said this from the start,
Q: What is Matsumoto's favourite adult video genre?
I only watch girls debut performances.
---------
Alright!
He got it.
A: Debut performance
That must feel good.
New Recruits
But you all knew that, right?
Punishment on the line - Everyone does their best
With a punishment on the line, everyone was serious.
And so...
Who will receive the punishment?
The loser is none other than...
Yamasaki Housei!
Last place
Yamasaki Housei
No way!
-------------------------------
Oh my god...
You're kidding!
What will his punishment be?
So, what will his punishment be?
100 Shouts of Matsumoto!!
You're going to go to loads of places
and shout "Matsumoto-san!"
Punishment
Commences
And now Yamasaki Housei
will live out his sentence!
Cocorico
Downtown
Endō Shōzō
Hamada
Masatoshi
Matsumoto
Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Yamasaki
Hōsei
I'm still angry personally!
You knew too little about Matsumoto.
You didn't know anywhere near enough.
He has every reason to be angry.
But wait, Matsumoto-san,
it's true I didn't know a lot about you,
but Hamada-san knew even less than me.
But me and him are just like 'business partners'...
While you, er...
Him and I have been together since we lived in a Yakult apartment.
It's a long history between them.
Very long, you know.
With a vending machine of only Yakult to drink.
Seriously...
Let's move on.
Ahh, Matsumoto-san!!
What was that?
MA~tsumoto-san!!
100 Shouts of Matsumoto Punishment
Will they be able to endure such a harsh penalty?
What are you on about?
Ow!!
Shall we look at how you did?
So, Yama-chan, please introduce the video.
Please enjoy watching.
So now, this video...
START!
Enduring this is also a punishment.
At 6 in the morning,
the 100 shouts punishment starts at dawn.
In the morning?
Yamasaki arrives at today's
meeting place, the Takeshiba Pier.
At dawn!
Staff: Good morning!
Today, Yamasaki, you're going to
do your punishment "100 Shouts of Matsumoto."
First, I'll explain.
It's a heating belt but
touch it here and see.
SWITCH
You see it vibrates, now...
Yamasaki-san tie the belt around your waist
and when it vibrates
you think of Matsumoto-san and yell:
MATSUMOTO-SAN!
So he can't
decide himself.
Whilst thinking about Matsumoto-san...?
It's to help
with timing.
When the vibration starts he shouts
"MATSUMOTO-SAN" as his punishment.
Also, we'll give you directions with this transmitter.
May I attach it?
Yeah.
Right, we'll give it a test, then begin.
Face towards the sea.
Ah, that's
a nice spot.
Don't laugh!
Your punishment will begin
at the same time as the test.
Right.
Well, good luck.
Just a second...
Can I shout then, if I'm meant to shout?
You've got to wait
for instructions.
I see.
It was so early
in the morning...
Starting in:
What was that?
STARTS!!
100 SHOUTS OF MATSUMOTO STARTS!!
He freaked out
when it vibrated.
Good, we'll go somewhere else now.
Wait, I'm going to be
by myself the whole time?
That's right.
Did  I do something that bad...?
Yeah you would
be feeling unsure...
To accomplish his punishment Yamasaki travels by car.
This is amazing.
OK, I'm in the car.
Aw man, what will happen to me now?
The car heads towards the next location,
right next to Tokyo Tower, in Shiba Park.
You'll get out here.
Ah, Tokyo Tower?
Where?
Can you turn left and enter the park?
Geez, this is stressing me out, I dunno why
but I feel something bad's gonna happen.
Doing this alone is really worrying me.
Stop saying "AHH!"
I can't help it, I'm not
used to it at this point
Then get used to it.
Yeah.
I think your screams aren't loud enough.
It needs more guts.
I am shouting loudly.
Er, see the bench?
Where there are elderly people.
Yeah, I see they're doing something.
Can you go talk to them?
Good morning. What are you doing?
Stretches.
Ah, stretches.
Aren't you a comedian?
Ah, Yama-san!
That's right.
You looked fatter on TV.
When you were imitating a lawyer.
When I played a lawyer? That's true.
Shout louder!
Yeah, for real.
Is Matsumoto-san here?
I wonder if Matsumoto-san is around here somewhere?
No, no, no...
What are you filming today?
* Gaki = kid, hence the confusion after
It's for Gaki no Tsukai.
* Hidden camera show following kids on their first solo errand
Hajimete no Otsukai?
Hajimete no Otsukai...? Yeah, well, uh...
It's time to go.
OK, excuse me, goodbye!
Good luck!
OK, thank you very much!
This is...
Are you not just sending me around random places...?
Is it going to be OK?
OK!
Aah...
This is exhausting.
I still haven't heard
one I'm happy with.
* Business area of Tokyo
The next step is to Shimbashi.
It has the most people travel through it during rush hour per day
Yamasaki prepares to do his punishment during rush hour.
For now just head to the station.
The station?
Put yourself under the traffic light.
Under the traffic light?
Eh seriously? This is so tough...
Can you be a little more in the center of the square?
Uwah, woah!!
Wow, this is...
Eh, you see this?
Just look at that!
This is so tough...
The camera shoots
from quite far!
Here we go.
No way, you didn't
even shout.
Please shout louder.
Of course.
Just make it loud enough that we can wrap it up.
Ugh, that's just...
It just looks like you're
calling someone.
You're like one of those little old Japanese men
waiting for you at the airport to rent a car.
----------------------------------------------------
Yamasaki-san on the sidewalk in front of you is a bakery.
Bakery
You can go there.
There's lots of different
delicious-looking bread!
This isn't what
I was imagining...
It's so quiet..
Pardon me.
This is really bad.
Come on!
That'll be 1620 yen please.
OK.
Can I get a receipt?
Sure.
Matsumoto-san, correct?
Right.
Hey this... is pretty intense.
3 hours after beginning,
Yamasaki is only on his eighth shout.
You haven't done a damn thing yet they feed you.
* A prominent TV channel which also airs Gaki
The next place is the NTV headquarters.
Eh, where? What?
The cooking segment of "PON!" should start soon.
Go and shout during their broadcast.
Woah! Seriously?
If "PON!" is starting,
it's probably about 10:30am.
Aw, I don't like this...
What is this, I have to shout here?
Geez, come on...
They will think I'm crazy, geez...
Weekly Mon ~ Fri
10:25 Live
(Except some areas)
"PON!" LIVE
On the morning broadcast of "PON!"
the goal is to shout live.
I really dunno about this...
See, now that
was a shout!
Yeah, that was.
Good, good!
This is your best
shout so far.
So he didn't give
his all before!
True!
"PON!" LIVE
You had no
intention of yelling.
It's not like
I didn't want to!
Yamasaki
MATSU MOTO -SAN~!!
MATSUMOTO-SAN~!!
MATSU MOTO-SAN~!!
This is awful.
It's good.
Ah, it's freezing!
"PON!" LIVE
Next is to interrupt the segment for The Touch.
* Comedy duo
Takuya
But it's not good if I interrupt them.
I'll actually be interrupting them, seriously?
Yes.
No way!
He's really happy!
"PON!" LIVE
Is it here you really
wanted to yell?
It's not about
wanting to or not!
He's loving this...
"PON!" LIVE
Matsumoto-san!!
Huh?
Wait a minute...
Matsumoto-san!!
Not bad!
Have you finished?
I'm sorry.
Even The Touch
apologises.
In here?
Tower Records
Yes.
You went everywhere!
Yamasaki tries out his own CD
But here you don't
have to hold back.
22nd Shout
of Matsumoto
Geez...
Oh dear...
In the Elevator
Totally wrong.
Wha??
27th Shout
of Matsumoto
Hibiya Park's Matsumoto (restaurant)
36th Shout
of Matsumoto
Matsumoto KiYoshi (pharmacy)
You can't get
anything out of him!
* As if the shop is a person
Look at you, shouting "Matsumoto-san!"
Woah...
What a bitch!
This is harsh.
Are you doing something?
Yeah...
What a bitch...
41st Shout
of Matsumoto
Ahahahaha!
King of Gyoza
For one person.
OK.
You're gonna eat!?
Of course, everything
I did is in this...
But you haven't
done a damn thing.
Thank you for the meal.
50th Shout
of Matsumoto
This is so bad.
Zaki-san, honestly!
Just go for it.
I am doing it.
Man, I waited ages for that meal.
Ah, this is irritating!
Irritating!?
Yamasaki has shouted 50 times,
just half of his punishment.
You kidding me?
The car now heads towards its next destination.
He said it's irritating...
Oi, you can't be serious...
What's up?
What am I doing here?
What is it?
Ah, wow!
This is the house of parliament.
Eh, you're serious!?
Well of course,
that could happen...
I can't shout here, it's not possible!
Besides there are lots of police...
There sure are!
The atmosphere here is different.
See the pair of guards?
There's a space in front of them.
Go over there.
I can't do that, no way!
Yamasaki
I'm not being held responsible...
Well, are you ready?
No. no, no way, no way, no way, no way!!
The place itself
makes it scary
It is a punishment after all.
True.
See the pair of guards?
There's a space in front of them.
Go over there.
I can't do that, no way!
Yamasaki
I'm not being held responsible...
Well, are you ready?
No. no, no way, no way, no way, no way!!
I can't, seriously, there's no way!
I can't do that, no way, no way...
Oi oi oi oi oi oi oi!
Oi!
I can't do this.
Geez...
It was too quiet so it doesn't count.
No, no, no, I can't, no way!
It can't count as a shout.
I can not shout here... No way.
He's been infront of the gate for 3 minutes.
His voice just will not come out.
What the hell does that even mean,
"His voice won't come out"?
This is impossible...
It's not impossible.
Let's go.
Seriously? Seriously?
We're counting on you.
Ahh, come on...
This is awful.
No no no no!
Yamasaki-san, you weren't even heard!
Not in the slightest!
You love running away...
Geez...
We can't count that one.
Too right!
So Yamasaki-san, ready to move on?
* A big production agency for stage artists
2PM, heading to 'Lumine the Yoshimoto' in Shinjuku.
Ah, you're on stage.
Hello.
Imada Kouji's once per month performance
Today he's playing a part with comedian Imada Kouji.
OK.
Yamasaki receives a bracelet.
They prefer a wristband for him instead
I can't wear this,  please!
During the real thing?
I can't do it, there are customers...
---------------------------------------
Will Yamasaki shout!?
Will Yamasaki be up to it, facing so many people?
Look how his
belly sticks out!
But here, you should
really be able to go for it.
Yoshimoto New Comedy Troupe
Hold on now!
* A popular stage gag of Housei's
MA~!!
Eh, what're you doing here!?
Wait, what's with that tone?
Huh, what did you say?
You know I could
make you disappear from this world in 3 seconds.
Go on then.
Right then.
In 3 seconds?
Yeah, I will.
MA~tsumoto-san
What are you on about?
Ow!!
Why yell someone's name?
He's done so well to play along and get people to laugh along...
Hamada-san, that's not it, it's not even about that...
Tokyo Metropolitan Government Building
63rd Shout
of Matsumoto
It should be like this.
Right, yeah.
Shinjuku Station
Shinjuku Station, East Exit
So embarrassing.
These kind of places,
he should really...
Yeah, yeah.
71st Shout
of Matsumoto
Meh...
Are you just here to shout "Matsumoto-san"?
Yeah...
I'm only here to say "Matsumoto-san!"
Hahaha.
That's so annoying...
Shinjuku Station, East Exit Escalator
Yeah...
"Is that it?"
78th Shout
of Matsumoto
Ah, it's too quiet!
On to the next location
What's with this?
83rd Shout
of Matsumoto
Why here?
Geez, they don't let me
rest for a second, seriously...
* An upscale Tokyo district
The next place is Ginza.
I'm in the heart of Ginza.
Everyone here is
upper class and stuff..
Yamasaki-san, see the little police station?
Ah, there it is, a tiny police station.
OK, let's shout standing right next to it.
Police
Station
Eh!?
Police
Station
I was terrified of yelling
by a police box like that.
Police
Station
Yamasaki
Why?
It was scary somehow,
I didn't wanna get in trouble.
That's pathetic.
Trying to pretend he's
looking for someone.
He's just pretending to
look for someone!
Seriously!
To try and make
an excuse.
So true.
Ah, I was
really scared...
Look at what
he's doing!
You're not
doing it at all.
Yamasaki
The police are watching me...
No they aren't...
Next is a place where silence is mandatory.
Next place, a gallery
An art gallery.
It's super quiet...
Wait, I absolutely can't do it here...
How can you shout in a place like this...?
I'm counting on
you here, okay?
Please do.
Ideal place for
this punishment.
This is impossible, no way, no way, no way!
It's not right to shout in such a place.
Don't say that, it's a
punishment after all.
Eh...?
Right, come on.
No good Yamasaki-san, it doesn't count.
But it's too risky to shout here.
That was no good.
Do it once then immediately return.
I'm sorry.
What the hell is this?
Plus, he quietly
apologized.
I dunno about this...
They were just so shocked, ugh...
-----------------
So pathetic~!
Only 14 shouts are left.
86 shouts
complete
It's time for
the climax!
I haven't heard any shouts
and it's already evening.
Now it's time for the climax!
-------------------------------------
12 hours since the start
Yamasaki's nearing his limit...
Yamasaki's stamina has reached its limits.
No, no, no, no...
Arrived at it's final checkpoint
The car comes to its last destination.
No, no, no, no!
Seriously, where are we?
Where are we?
Hold on now, oi...
What is this!?
Yamasaki-san?
Eh?
Currently for your "100 Shouts of Matsumoto"
you've completed 86 shouts.
86 Shouts
of Matsumoto
14 Shouts
Left:
So now there's 14 shouts left.
Really?
Yama-chan, see the mannequin before you?
This is a model of Matsumoto Hitoshi.
A dummy of Matsumoto-san?
It's really similar to Matsumoto-san...
Right, can you turn to the path you just took?
You'll carry the Matsumoto-san mannequin
using all your strength.
Then, run to the red cones doing your last 14 shouts.
Are you ready?
Wait a sec! Wait!
Uwah~ This is revolting!
"Revolting"...!?
Are you alright?
Give me a second...
What did you mean?
Starting in 3 seconds!
What you trying to say??
Well...
Two!
One!
Start!!
Shout Counter:
Starting in 3 seconds!
Two!
One!
Start!!
Shout Counter:
HOT! HOT! HOT!!
You bet it's hot.
He was like, "Waah!"
SO HOT!!
Yamasaki-san, you still need three shouts!
HOT!!
Yamasaki-san, still three left!
I protected you!
I saved him!
With this the "100 Shouts of Matsumoto" punishment
has been successfully completed.
Good job.
THANK YOU!!
Just the last one...
That's so bad.
Just the last
one was loud.
100 SHOUTS OF MATSUMOTO ENDS!!
What did you think, everyone?
He wasn't shouting at all...
Are you happy with his volume?
No, I cannot accept that.
It really wasn't shouting at all, right Zaki-san?
What!? Really I--
After all, it is a punishment.
It's a punishment!
It's pointless if you try to fit in with your surroundings,
Right!
for a punishment you had to belt it out.
Like wherever you are...
Sure.
You have to do it like that.
You should've screamed like that in the gallery.
The gallery!?
You're seriously able to
do that in an art gallery!?
Like seriously,
if you had properly yelled
100 times "Matsumoto-san"
your voice would have gone...
That's true.
But you're fine.
Your "THANK YOU!!" was incredibly loud without restraint.
It was his best shout.
What's that about?
Come on, seriously shout, let us see.
That's not what we saw, right?
Yeah.
I did do that...
It wasn't in the video.
What did you do in the gallery?
As if!
Don't just shamelessly lie.
But I did do it...
Wait, in what you just saw...
what was I doing wrong?
You had to shout "Matsumoto-san"
at the top of your voice
regardless of the situation or place.
You'd really belt it?
Come on show him.
I would!
Like that in Shinjuku or an art gallery.
Like with that much energy.
That's the way.
There's absolutely no way--
Endo show him, go Endo, go.
That's good.
You had to shout like that 100 times.
In a gallery or wherever.
I did it before as well...
Go for it.
That was superb!
He's the best.
Hamada you don't need to use the "-san" you know.
Oh, who gives a shit...
But the phrase is "Matsumoto-san."
Ah OK, it just surprised me.
Come on, try it yourself.
Now that's a shout!
Honestly, Yamasaki's been especially awful this year.
Indeed, I've been awful.
Like you're late all the time...
Right.
Since last New Year's party.
* New Year's Yama-1 Grand Prix - GnT #1090 29/01/2012
"Indeed, I've been awful," he says.
Right, the New Year's party, you were just dawdling about.
Yeah.
* Katamari Grand Prix - GnT #1093 19/02/2012
Then after that, you couldn't read
the atmosphere in the Katamari contest.
This time too, for this punishment, again
you weren't able to figure out what we wanted...
Seriously, what are we to do with you?
Do you want to take like a 8 month break?
No, no, no...
You're finished for this year.
Really...?
Uwah!! Matsu--
Matsumoto-san! WAHH!
HOT! HOT! HOT!