DTR Subs
Remaster by Shappuri Agemasu Subs
May 16, 2004
Yeah...
Gaki No Tsukai Green Room
What would be good?
Radio? Yes, that'd be nice.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hello.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
You get it, right?
Well, in the past you have come to the green room in that outfit.
Right?
If I've come in this outfit from the start, you get it, right?
Well, it has been a while since the last time.
Right?
When it's about this,
you get a call directly on the previous day, right?
From Matsumoto?
Right, right.
By text!
Text? By text?
At the end, there's a
smiley face.
A smiley face.
The first one, that's at the top. It's easy to use.
Right, right.
He's in a good mood.
Yeah, he's in a good mood.
The dream that Matsumoto has envisioned!?
The event that Matsumoto set his sights on this time is
Limbo Dance
the limbo dance.
His challenge is a limbo dance of fire!!
Furthermore, not being satisfied with a regular limbo dance, the bar will be set on fire.
(Move) The height!?
And the height of the bar will be...
He says he wants to do it at 50 centimeters.
That's crazy low.
50 cm is really...
50 cm is...
I know, right?
I don't think we can do this one, right?
But it depends on you guys. And I've been entrusted to do this. I need you with me on this, you know?
What if he called you? You'd be desperate for help, too.
But you're apparently
already intending on doing this, right?
You're already dressed as a kuroko*.
Note*: Kuroko is a traditional Japanese theater stagehand. Kurokos dress in all black to imply to the theater audience that they are supposed to be invisible and not part of the onstage action.
Don't just say that
Yeah, but...
So we'll do it for you, Hamada.
Well, right, that's right. That's why we'll do it.
I see. Thank you. Really.
We'll do it for you, Hamada.
Well, right, that's right. That's why we'll do it.
I see. Thank you. Really.
From the kindness of their hearts, the men have stepped up again.
Matsumoto Hitoshi - The 50cm Limbo Dance of Fire Challenge.
Challenge!!
Matsumoto Hitoshi
The 50 cm Limbo Dance of Fire
Matsumoto Hitoshi - The 50cm Limbo Dance of Fire Challenge.
Let's say what we have to say to him.
Let's say it, seriously.
He needs to put in some effort. Otherwise, there's a limit to what we can do.
Yes.
We can't do it.
Right? We should tell him that.
He's coming.
Huh?
Hey.
Hello.
Um, I did explain it to everyone.
And we're ready.
Everyone showed up, huh?
Yeah.
Yes.
Sorry for the trouble.
Why don't you tell him?
Um, it's the same thing as last time,
Please, thank you.
Matsumoto, we need you to put some strength into it.
or we
I don't know what you're talking about.
No,
Matsumoto, if you could... I'm not saying put in some effort, but if you could put in some effort.
If you could put in some effort.
I am putting in effort.
I see.
I think I'm putting strength into it, too.
But there, aren't you the ones who are to realize my potential?
Aren't my juniors and my classmate the ones to do that?
If you were my seniors, maybe I'd describe it differently. But,
you're my juniors and my classmate, so I want you to unders...tand that.
Then, let's give it a go.
Yes, let's do it.
Yes, let's do it. The fire is really something, though.
Let's try lighting it up. Let's try lighting it up.
Just as before.
Matsumoto, you should really get vigilant.
This is pretty scary.
His 1st Attempt!!
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Matsumoto's 1st attempt.
This is good. It looks like we'll get some really thrilling footage.
One mistake and you'll get injured.
You need to be on your A-game.
Let's go.
Ok, go.
This way a little more.
Watch out.
Can you...
Stand up!
Could you stand up?
Hey.
He's completely limp.
Matsumoto?
Matsumoto.
Hamada, tell him.
He's completely limp.
Just stand him up. Stand him up.
Stand him up. What are we supposed to do with this?
Move him this way.
Forward a bit. Let's go over here.
What are we supposed to do with this?
Yeah.
This is awful.
This is just... This is just...
What the hell? What the hell?
Could you not go limp? Could you... Could you...
This is no good.This is no good. This is no good.
This is no good. This is no good. This is no good.
What...?
What the hell?
Huh?
Matsumoto gets angry and leaves
No, come on.
Wait. Matsumoto?
We haven't done anything.
That's messed up.
Let's go see him. What the hell is wrong with him?
Please talk to him, Hamada.
Seriously. Just like that?
Wait, we didn't do anything wrong, right?
No.
Nothing at all.
I think that's what it is.
The group go to Matsumoto's dressing room to see how he is doing
Completely, right?
That's right.
Hi, Mr. Matsumoto.
Hi. Hi, teacher.
How are you, how are you doing?
Matsumoto was doing an English speaking lesson
How can I go to Shiodome Site?
How can I go, what? Huh?
How...
How can I go to Shiodome Site?
Could you...
One more time.
Sorry to... while you're in the middle of your lesson.
How can I go-
Uh, teacher, sorry. What?
The way we see it... right?
Yes. We did as you requested of us.
... is what we think we did.
Mr. Matsumoto
Could you just...
Mr. Matsumoto?
Well, the teacher doesn't know the situation here.
Right, right.
OK, Shiodome Site
How can I go to Shiodome Site?
You see,
what I'm thinking is,
why would you make the fire that big?
It wasn't...
Well...
So, I'm a beginner at this, right? And so I'm just, I'm just doing this so that I can feel like I've done it a little bit.
I want to do this as if I just came by and happened to do it. So when you make the fire that raging,
it's like the heart shrivels, or the heart withers, you know. Who would think it'd be that hot?
I thought it'd be around 20 degrees Celsius.
How can I go to Shiodome Site? Mr. Matsumoto?
As long as it isn't hot, it's fine, then?
Let's think about that.
The fire is a bit dangerous, so, yeah.
Think about that a bit.
His 2nd Attempt!!
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Matsumoto's 2nd attempt.
So at least the heat is totally...
Yes.
So that should be fine, right? As long as he makes it under 50 cm.
Right.
That's the thing, yes.
That's the key.
Right?
I mean...
Here he comes.
He's here.
So we're ready.
Yes.
In general, as you can see, it's with the fire.
Right. The visual aspect.
Yes. I think it satisfies the visual aspect.
Ok, then.
Ok. Let's go.
Are you ok?
Let's go, already.
Should we start?
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go.
Why don't we start.
Hey.
What's he doing?
That's dangerous.
What do we do with this?
Let's go, let's go.
What's he laughing about?
What's so funny?
Who the hell knows.
What's he laughing at?
Ready and go.
Attempt with an office chair
Here. Like this.
Got that attached.
Tanaka, this side.
Let's make this work in one shot.
Let's go.
3, 2, 1,
Go!
The bar was a bit...
The bar was a bit low, wasn't it?
Why'd that happen?
According to our plan, it should've been fine, but...
The bar...
But that was 50 cm, right there.
According to our plans, it should've be fine.
Let's try it again, with something different.
Oh, should we go at it with a different way?
The next one will definitely work.
Let's make it work with this one.
Here we go.
Ok, let's go.
Ready and... Ready and...
Attempt with rolling pins
Put him on top.
Ready and... Ready and...
Now if everyone can go to their positions.
Good, good.
Yeah, let's go.
Ok.
3, 2, 1.
Go!
Ok!
No, no.
This isn't it.
No.
Let's just go to the last one.
The last one.
The last one, the last one.
This will work.
Yes.
Hey, that's wrong, Tanaka, it's the other... yeah.
Hey, that's wrong Tanaka, it's the other... yeah.
Attempt with a bar with casters
This'll work. This'll work.
Yama-chan, you play the part of the horse.
It should be higher. This way more. He's soaked in sweat.
Ready and...
He's sweating like crazy.
Ok.
Here we go.
This should be good.
3, 2, 1,
Ok, 50 cm limbo, go!
Go!
We got it?
Completed!
Cleared! It was cleared!
Success!
Yes!
Matsumoto gets angry and leaves again
What was that, is he angry?
What, is he angry?
His attitude seemed a little angry, yeah.
Yeah, he wasn't happy.
No, he can't be angry.
I don't think he can be angry.
Well, we cleared it.
Right?
Let's go meet him in a good mood. Like, "How was it?"
Yeah.
In a plain and normal way. Just plainly, like "How was it?" That's fine, right?
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes.
All right.
The group go to Matsumoto's dressing room to see how he is doing, again
Hey.
Great job.
Great job.  Thank you.
How was it?
That was great.
Accomplishing it?
Matsumoto was doing an oil painting of yakisoba (fried noodles)
It's too close.
Hmm?
What?
Well, I mean we...
Yes. Congratulations.
accomplished what we wanted.
Congratulations.
Why is it that it's always like that? That I always get wounded.
Huh? Wounded?
Your bumpy boards that you set up,
they were pinching my flesh. The flesh. See?
Oh.
Don't give me "Oh."  It was grinding me.
But with the one after the one that pinched you, we did clear it.
Yes, we did.
The— what "cleared?"
Well, going under the 50 cm bar...
I'm not talking about getting through a 50 cm bar or whatever.
Make it so that
when you see it, you go
"Matsumoto is really doing it!"
You're getting paid for this, right!
Every week.
You're getting paid for this, right?
Do your jobs!
But, what you mean by, "Matsumoto is really doing it..."
Uh, no, no, I don't need to hear your ways of
shutting people down.
I don't need that.
Now, everyone say how you're going to work hard henceforth
and your zodiac sign.
In the end, say that.
Hurry up.
Ok, well, well, I'll think about how to make it look like "Matsumoto is really doing it," and work towards that.
I'm a rabbit.
I, also, will give it my best.
I'm a monkey.
I, also, will give it my best and make sure you don't get injured.
I'm a boar.
I'm hoping to make it happen in our next attempt.
Excuse us.
We'll give it our best.
His 3rd Attempt!!
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Matsumoto's 3rd attempt.
Well, in the next one we just gotta pull him.
Yes.
And I think it'll look like "He's really doing it."
It does.
Visually, right?
I think it'll work.
It quite looks he's really doing it, right?
Yes.
Where is he looking?
How is he managing to walk straight?
Ok, we're ready, so... over here.
Yes. Thank you.
Please come this way.
Thank you.
This is amazing.
This is great.
This will work.
This is perfect.
Visually, this is really,
Attempt with a huge swing set
um, the feeling of "really doing it" is pretty great.
We think it will work.
Yes.
It'll work?
It will work. This will work.
Over here.
Thank you.
Higher up.
Yes.
Ready and... there we go.
According to the plan, he'll go like this.
Right underneath.
Zoom!
Then let's have the staff help us a bit here.
Thank you.
Ready and...
All right.
Ok. It's good, it's good?
That's good.
We're good.
Is it straight?
It's straight, yes?
Ok, we're ready.
All right.
3, 2, 1, go!
Go!
That was close. Should we try raising it a bit?
Should we raise the bar? Yes, for the next one. Yes.
Let's raise the bar. We'll raise it.
Raise the bar.
Let's make it the highest one.
Yes, yes. Let's do that.
Ok, we'll go with this for Matsumoto.
Who cares about how many centimeters or whatever.
Yes.
Yes, that's true.
Can you raise this?
Ok. Ok.
Thank you.
Ok. Be careful there. We're going.
Straight, ok?
3, 2, 1, Ok!
Ok. Be careful there. We're going.
Ok!
Ah, that was close.
That was close.
Ok!
Man, that was close.
That was close.
Why'd that happen?
Yes, why?
The feeling of "really doing it" is there. Yeah.
Yes, it is.
Maybe it'd be better closer together?
The bar, right?
50...
Matsumoto gets angry and leaves, yet again
Wouldn't it have worked if we attempted it a few times?
Yes. I think if we could move it a bit
further this way, it would've worked.
Make the lowest point a bit that way.
Oh, I see. Then let's just tell him that.
Yes.
If we put it close by, it'll go right through.
The group go to Matsumoto's dressing room to see how he is doing, yet again
Great job.
Matsumoto was fixing a punctured tire of a bicycle
Matsumoto, we got it.  The bar was a bit far out, right?
If we, like, put it closer in...
It will work fine.
You three were fine this time.
Yes.
I did feel you were trying pretty hard.
So I'm not really angry at you three or anything.
Wait, wait, why is that?
You said "Who cares about the height," right?
That...
we don't need to care about the 50 cm, you said something like that, right?
That completely put me off.
That, well, was a slip of the tongue.
Do you want to let me do this or not?
Is this like a rush job? You just want to get it over with? What?
No, that's not true.
Every one of you, say this.
Every one of you, say why you want me to do the limbo dance,
and at the end, say your mom's name.
Everyone say that. Go.
Well,
well, you said you wanted to this and we're on, you know, we're doing a TV show together, so I'm doing this with the hope that we can work together as a team and succeed at this.
Um, my mother is Nobuko.
My senior has told me that he wants to do this
so, um, I hope to assist him as much as possible.
Um, my mother is Aya.
In the same way,
I am not thinking about this as a rush job at all.
I will henceforth give it my very best.
My mother is Kiyomi.
Yes,
I'm giving it my best. To realize
what my senior wants to do,
I will henceforth give it my very best.
My mother is Akiko.
What?
Akiko.
It's the same.
My wife and my mom have the same name.
And I don't want to insistently say the same thing over and over.
One last time,
I'll bet on you guys.
Yes.
Thank you.
My mother is Akiko.
His 4th Attempt!!
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Matsumoto's 4th attempt.
Um
to create that feeling of "really doing it,"
we thought up something that's different from the previous ones.
Yes.
We also think it will be
quite impressive visually.
Yes, we do think it will be.
We are confident it will succeed.
All right, let's go.
Let's go.
All right. Let's do this as if it's our last chance.
Let's really try to make it happen with this one.
Let's make this happen.
Whoa, wow.
Whoa, it's pretty large.
Attempt with an extra large slide
The view does look different from here.
This will be great.
All right.
If you could, please.
Let's go!
Yes! Let's go!
Was it at the waist?
The waist...
This should be good. Yeah.
Looks good.
Make it absolutely sure.
We're good.
Ok, 3, 2, 1, go!
Go!
After overcoming many trials, finally,
Matsumoto has accomplished the 50 cm limbo dance of fire.
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Success!!
The 50 cm Limbo Dance of Fire
A true congratulations to you!