/r/GakiNoTsukai
Downtown's Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende!
Timed by : Rylix
Translated by : DCSubs
What's wrong?
While eating, Matsumoto suddenly got food stuck in his throat.
What's with you?
Get me some Evian Water
Huh?
Get me some Evian Water!
Get him some Evian!
No, You go get it!
Get me some Evian!
Go to where they get it from and get me some!
Batsu game!
Hama-chan! Go to France to get some Evian Water!!
Ma-chan is so mean!!
First, He needs to find out where Evian is from!
Hamada calls the Evian Company
Evian Water right?
Uhh....
So I want to go to where you guys get the water from...
Where exactly is it though...
We get it around Mont Blanc...
Mont Blanc!?
So you wanna get there on a plane.
Ah, Alright! I'll fly there.
You can also get there by boat.
Ah. Alright, I see...
So where is Mont Blanc exactly?
It's a far place from Tokyo
12 hours on a plane to France
The alps are here
Aiming for Mount Blanc!
Hamada's Trip has begun!
Narita International Airport
Hamada is brought forcibly by two managers
Let's go shall we?
You guys are going too?
Yes.
What the hell do you have on me?
It's because of the Batsu game.
What the hell do you mean "because"
You have to fill it up
There's still a little bit in here. This is fine right?
A Souvenir!?
Get us a souvenir!
Shut up!
Soon after, Hamada's plane takes off!
Hamada's plane to Paris leaves
What the hell is this?
Huh?
What seat are we in?
Economy.
Economy!?
Who the hell sat us here!?
It's a Batsu game, isn't it?
Suga
What is it?
They have Evian here!
Look! It's Evian!
I should just take this back with me
But it's a Batsu game...
I guess you're right.
Uwahhh!
4 Hours Since Departure
Matsumoto is still struggling
12 Hours since departure and Hamada has landed in France
So are we getting there by foot?
No, We still have another plane
EH!?
With the thought of getting on another plane, Hamada runs away!
However, With some information they find him at the transit room
Transit Room
I've filled it up. Time to go home.
Flying from France in Economy they make it to Geneva Switzerland
Arrived at Geneva airport
We're here...
We've finally made it huh?
What the hell are you carrying?
EH!?
We're going to the hotel?
No...
Where!?
Mont Blanc
Are you stupid...
And then 4 hours after...
Hamada once again being carried by the staff
We probably still can't see it!
Geneva (Switzerland)
Lake Geneva
Heading towards Evian, Hamada gets on a boat
Let's get going soon
Can he make it? Trusting the instructions he got on the phone they leave!
Suga!
Suga acting like a tourist
What the fuck are you doing! Who are you waving to!?
Are we even heading the right way?
Definitely!
I'm gonna ask the old man.
Hamada's French
Are we really headed towards Mont Blanc?
Thank you!
We don't understand each other!
He said you can't make it by boat.
Hamada's Translator
We can't get there with a boat!?
SUGA!!
He said we're not going to make it there!
No way!
We can't get there by boat!
Change of plans! They purchase a rental car!
We made it right?
This is the border.
Border?
The border of France and Switzerland
It's been 26 hours since he departed. They've arrived at the town of lovers, Chamonix!
Chamonix (France)
Matsumoto is still struggling
Hamada joyfully ignoring the Evian task
Basically, We gotta climb it now.
It's scary! Try looking at it!
What the hell are you doing?
Hamada being forced to wear Tyrol clothing by the staff
It's just so we can spot you out easy.
What the hell is this.
I came all the way here now I have to wear this?
Heading towards Evian! The cable car begins to move!
The rope cart begins to swing as it reaches its destination altitude at 2000m.
Scared Hamada
He's reached the midpoint!
However, Matsumoto is still struggling!
Will he be able to get the water in time?
Mont Blanc
Hamada continues to attack! Is Evian close at hand!?
Holy. We're over the clouds already...
Hamada riding a cable car to his destination 3842m in altitude.
Uwaah!
Hamada shaking from fear
There's definitely no water in a place like this
He finally reaches his destination at the top!
Due to the high altitude, The air gets thinner.
Temperature -10
Uwaaah!
There are people climbing down the mountain!
Let's get the water and get out of here!
Well, There's none... No water... I was told...
Huh!?
If we go a little north and head down there's a waterfall. That's where we can get it.
Dumbass!
If I just put this in and it melts that's fine right?
Ma-chan would probably be angry.
No. Well...
He's on the verge of death isn't he?
Right everyone?
Well it's a Batsume... Batsu game
BATSUME!?
From such a cold mountain to this hot place...
Climbing down from Mont Blanc in search of the Evian Falls.
By the way, It's about an hour away from here.
EH!?
Here.
Enough already. Huh?
What?
Well... We're gonna be waiting.
Why the hell are you laughing?
I will have to fill it with Evian water, right?
Please get it!
Alright, Let's all go together!
Eh?
Hurry up guys!
Oh! Oh! The waterfall!
So here we are...
The Evian Falls!
There's a lot of Evian!
What the hell is this?
This is good right!?
How do you expect me to get it!?
I'll die!
Being so far away from Japan, Hamada finally gets it!
I've got it!
Finally, Hamada has gotten some natural Evian!
Congratulations Hamachan for successfully getting the water from the alps!
This is the Batsu game of your Youth!
Our dreams are fulfilled with the cool breeze of the Mont Blanc!
Hamada in good spirits has forgotten the pain he went through to get the bottle.
They reach the neighbouring city
Evian (France)
Come on Suga... Let's go shopping.
Huh?
Evian...
Well, It's the city...
Eh?
Evian natural spring waters
They have the Evian water?
Yeah.
Over there?
Well we got it from the mountains...
I didn't say it before but the water from the alps is the water from the alps.
The water that flows from the alps to Evian is then labeled as Evian.
So if we just came here...
We would have got Evian.
Oi!
Where the hell are you looking!?
So what's this water!?
The water I got from before.
Waterfall Water.
WATERFALL WATER!?
If we just came here after getting off the plane we would have done it fast!
Well... It's a Batsu game...
DAMN YOU!
What are they doing?
A beautiful woman washing her dog with Evian
Washing her dog?
Seems so.
"Seems so"!?
Evian:
The snow and water from Mont Blanc flows down for over 15 years to the city called Evian.
Ahhh!
There's just getting it from here?
Yes they are.
Coincidentally, There are a lot of towns like this
So this is the same water as the Evian in Japan!?
Yes.
This was so painful.
It's just water...
Alright!
Got it!
32 Hours since the start
He's finally gotten the real Evian Water!
This is for real right!?
This is real Evian!
He's got the Evian water from the alps
This time, Congratulations!
Despite being an Idiot,
Our dreams have honestly been fulfilled!
35 hours since departure
Hamada and the crew get on the plane home.
50 hours since departure
Matsumoto is still struggling
Hamada makes it to the Downtown break room!
It's painful huh!?
Nah, I'm alright now.
EH!?
Whats your problem? You should be happy!
My throat is cleared up though.
Why do you look so tired!
Wait a minute...
Listen here...
12 hours.
In Economy.
Ah!
You flew in Economy?
Just drink it!
This is real?
It's just water...
God damn it!
It's just water! It's not a big deal!
What!?
Alright, Hamada your Batsu game is over with this.
Shut up!
Congratulations!
Not gonna do a competition again.