Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
First Annual Gaki No Tsukaiya Arahende
"I Have Always Wanted to Try Making This" - Part 2
Absolutely Tasty - Pizza Round !
You just BARELY made it through the introduction
Where's the "@#$% Machine" when we need it ??
Downtown
Hitoshi Matsumoto
Masatoshi Hamada
If he keeps stuttering,
Cocorico
Naoki Tanaka
Shozo Endo
We might need to bring the "@#$% Machine" up
This is actually our second cooking series
Hosei Yamasaki
Yes, it is
Just like last time, we're each presenting two recipes
Objective
Present and critique each participant's two pizzas
How well do you think you know pizza ??
I'm very confident
Last time around,
the theme was "Rice," correct ??
Right, we used the rice cooker
I heard it was a hit
Some viewers told me that they routinely fix them after watching that episode
Get outta here
Exactly whose dish are you talking about ?
But there were good ones...
And who won ...
I'd say the "Edamame Rice with Beer"
Edamame Rice with Beer
That was the best
What about my Okonomiyaki Rice ??
Okonomiyaki Rice
Seriously, many people told me how good it was
after they cooked it themselves
They actually made it ?
Yes
Are you serious ?
Yes, I am
I'm serious about this
I heard it was good
I've noticed Tanaka lies every now and then
Trust me on this
Downtown Presents
Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende
Matsumoto Kiyoshi
Sponsor
Tanaka's Pizza
First up is Tanaka
What are his choice of toppings ?
Here are my first items
What are they ??
What's this ?
Cheese
Ingredients
Japanese Sake
Sake Lees
Shiokara
We have Sake, Sake Lees, and *Shiokara
I don't know about this...
*Shiokara is salt-cured fish guts
It's amazing that you chose to combine these ingredients,
since each can be difficult to eat on its own
I'm positive this will be good
Pizza will go great with Sake...
Sake...and Sake Lees....Get outta here !
They're basically the same thing
You're serious about this
I'm not a big fan of Sake Lees
I'm not sure Sake Lees will be good cooked
since they're already good raw
I think you've got enough on there
You're not gonna cut it in pieces ?
A bold move
Spectacular
I see, they're already cut to fit the dough
I hope you're not just messing around today
Please, I'm really serious about my dish
Well, we're all serious about this project
That's a lot of Shiokara
Compare this to anchovy pizza
I hear you
it's a similar flavor
Well, well, that might be a stretch
Hey, I like anchovy pizza
It's good, isn't it ?
I like the saltiness
I don't like it
I don't think Hamada-san is sold on this
So, I got the idea from anchovy pizza ...
OK then
And your second recipe is ?
Here it is
What...??
Cheese
Ingredients
Strawberry
Yukimi Daifuku (Mochi Ice Cream)
Are they...??
I don't know what to say...
My intention is to make dessert pizza
This one already looks better than the last one
I agree
It looks good already
The key is to add strawberry with the mochi ice cream
Endo's Pizza
Next up is Endo
What are his ingredients ??
I decided to use "High-End" ingredients
I wanted to give these a try
Here they are
That's a one bold...
Blowfish
Cheese
Grated Daikon
Ingredients
Ponzu
"Blowfish Pizza"
I came up with this idea...
You're an idiot
May I...
May I say this is the ultimate luxury ?
I would agree
Pour the sauce like so
Pour a cup of Ponzu over blowfish sashimi
And you can't call it a pizza without this...
Cheese
I don't know about this
Pretty out of control
I want a restaurant owner to tell me they've tried this recipe
I somehow doubt anyone would try this
I don't think a family would try this
I mean, just think how much it would cost
His second pizza is "Frisk Mint Pizza"
Cheese
Frisk Mints
Ingredients
Pizza sauce
The secret is to add 150 mints
I'm guessing this could be
a hit among women
You're right
I don't know about that...
Women tend to like minty stuff
Yes, they really do
Yamasaki's Pizza
Here's Yamasaki's pizza
What are his preferred ingredients ??
Yama-chan, let's see what you got
Are we good ?
It's *Hiyashi Chuka
(Cucumber, Egg, Ham, and Tomato)
Cheese
Hiyashi Chuka (Cold Noodles)
Ingredients
*Hiyashi Chuka is a cold noodle dish
Why aren't you taking this seriously ?
Wait..
I told you we're all taking this very seriously
Please, I'm totally serious
I'm going to pour all of this on the dough
You're not holding back
With the broth ?
Yeah, everything
That's some creation
This adds color
How's this ?
You're trying to make it look exactly like Hiyashi Chuka
I see
But once you slice it into pieces...
Each will have a different topping
Then one person could get stuck with just eggs
You'll have to share each of your toppings
It's more fun that way, don't you think ?
I don't want the cucumber piece for sure
I'm really particular about the appearance of this dish
Here's my second pizza
I'm shooting for a dessert as well
Looks like you have a lot of stuff under there
You can't wait to see it, can you ?
What could it be ?
Here it it
What is this ?
Yes, cotton candy
Cheese
Cotton Candy
Ingredients
I wonder what will happen when it cooks ?
I see
Why not just put it on like this ?
How else would you do it ?
So...
this is more like dessert
Yes, it's sweet
But this is more...
But you still need the cheese
That should do it
That's a simple dish
Yes, it is
The cheese should melt around the cotton candy
Hamada's Pizza
Next up is Hamada
What's his specialty pizza ?
I'm using more common ingredients
Any family can do this
Unlike the blowfish over there
Here they are
I see, this is a very common dish but...
(Beef, Chinese Cabbage, Green Onion, Tofu, etc)
Cheese
Egg
Ingredients
Sukiyaki
What do you mean ??
Who wouldn't fix Sukiyaki from time to time at home ??
I hear you
Do you see ??
So you're using Sukiyaki ingredients
Not a bad choice...
So I'm just gonna go ahead and...
just as Yama-chan arranged his toppings
Arrange them by groups ?
Right, just like Sukiyaki
You're keeping the integrity of the dish
Right, keeping it true
Then someone may end up with a meat slice
I don't want the Konnyaku piece
I second that
Here's the soup
And here's some cheese
You just ruined it
But what makes the pizza complete is this item right here
Oh, I see
That's for later
Just like Sukiyaki,
You dip your pizza into the raw egg
I've got a bad feeling about this
I'm feeling this
So just use the egg as a dipping sauce
Cheese
Egg
Ingredients
Rice
Soy Sauce
Hamada's second idea is to use Rice with Beaten Eggs
This idea could end up being delicious
Could this be like Doria ??
Oh, I see where you're going with this
Just pour it on the dough like so
This actually looks good
This looks delicious
My stomach just growled
Matsumoto's Pizza
And Matsumoto is the last
I wonder what his plan is
OK, so it's my turn
I'm very confident about my presentation
Check this out
It's *Gohan Desuyo
*See www.shibatabread.com to find out what Gohan Desuyo is
Cheese
Gohan Desuyo
Ingredients
I'm positive this will work !!
I see
You can't go wrong with this !!
It's quite simple, too
So you just spread it on, right ?
You're correct
All kidding aside,
This could be good
It's like seafood after all
After spreading the Gohan Desuyo,
the cheese completes the pizza
This could come as a surprise but...
What ??
What the hell is this ??
What the hell...?
A pig ??
Cheese
Goya
Ingredients
Mirin
Skin of Pig's head
Soy Sauce
This is the skin of a Pig's head
Okinawa-style ??
Yes, I thought, "Why not go with an Okinawa theme?"
There's never been an Okinawa Pizza
I don't like this
I won't want to slice this pizza
That's amazing
The interior side looks good, too, right ?
Well, I supposed I can...
How about making this into a wall decoration ?
A wall fixture ??
Yeah, put this up on the wall
And put a long and short hand right here to make a clock
This would be the 15min mark here and...
We've got it already
It's like I'm about to shave its face or something
Yes, indeed
How are we gonna eat this ?
Well, the pig will be happy for sure
And I have yet another idea !
And this is a really special ingredient
that I wanted to use
May I present it to you ??
Well, I just used the Pig's head
And I wasn't quite sure if this one would work but...
Think of it as the Head vs. the Head
But here it is
Who would WANT to eat this pizza ??
Cheese
Ingredients
Tuna Head
What the hell is this ??
This will be awesome !!
I don't think so
How do you even slice this ?
How are we eating this ?
This will be delicious
Seriously, how are we cutting this ?
So, this is a tuna's head
I can clearly see that
I'm just gonna put it right on the dough
And bake it
Everyone presented their ideas, and now it's time to bake them
Who will come out on top ?!
I'm smelling something good
Yes, you're right
Rank each pizza on a scale of 1 to 10
There, I can smell it
I can smell something good
Tanaka's 1st : "Sake and Shiokara Pizza"
First up is Tanaka's "Sake and Shiokara Pizza"
How does it taste ?
Wow, that looks delicious
Here
It looks good !
See ?
Look
Well, well, well
You just might have done it
See this ?
Nobody would question this at a restaurant
I'd say this is perfect so far
Yes, it is
So these are all Sake Lees
Yea, Sake Lees
That burned piece looks good, too
Looks awesome !
Smells great
You've done well
Some viewers will try this for sure
I'm not a fan of the smell
Hamada-san, you're not into the Shiokara smell
This is....pretty good so far!!
Good, good
Isn't it ??
Itadakimasu
Delicious !
I'm not into this
No, this is good, really !
This is delicious !
Everyone has different taste buds, right ?
I'm giving you a zero for this
Are you serious ?
I'm giving it...
Seven
Then, I'm giving it a...
That's a high score
I'd say five
This is pretty good but
the flavor can be overpowering
I agree
You can't eat a whole lot of this
The first bite is great but
it gets a bit tough after that
The flavor can be too much
Highly anticipated but receives a mere five points
Tanaka's 1st : "Sake and Shiokara Pizza"
Tanaka's 2nd : "Yukimi Daifuku Pizza"
Tanaka's next pizza is "Yukimi Mochi Ice Cream Pizza"
How does this fare ?
It sure smells good
The strawberry compliments it well
The mochi is still there
Check this out
All I can smell is the sweetness
Looks like something you can buy at Fujiya Cake Shop
This could be very good, don't you think ?
Women would love this for sure
Itadakimasu
Delicious !
See ?
This is great !
How can this be ?
Tasty, isn't it ?
Delicious
This is very good
This is very tasty
Awesome !
This recipe is something anyone could do
You can make this at home
Kids would love it, too
Yeah, they'll love this
I agree
Girls would be really into this
Endo, there's a piece of cheese hanging from your chin
Yeah, there is !
This is so good, I didn't realize...
I want more of this
Upon rave reviews,
Tanaka's 2nd : "Yukimi Daifuku Pizza"
it received eight points
Endo's 1st : "Blowfish Pizza"
Gourmet toppings is the selling point of Endo's "Blowfish Pizza"
Not bad looking at all
Will you look at this ?
Looks like any other pizza
What do you think ?
What am I tasting ?
There's really no flavor
I can't pinpoint it
This is the worst way to serve blowfish
This isn't pretty
There's no kick to this
None at all
Then you should have just left the blowfish poison
Despite the expensive ingredients, it only received three points
Endo's 1st : "Blowfish Pizza"
Next up is the unpredictable "Frisk Pizza"
Endo's 2nd : "Frisk Pizza"
What's that smell ?
This looks good
Yea, I can smell it
So far, it looks perfect
You've seen pizza like this before, right ?
I can still see some Frisk mints
Put your face closer to it
I just felt a minty breeze on my face
What the hell is that ?
It cools my face !
It almost feels cold
It chilled my face !
So the frisk mints can melt
Wow, it really does cool off my face
Very refreshing
This could cure your sinus issues...
Are we ready to do this ?
By the way, how would you score it ?
What ?
We couldn't even finish a bite
About how many points ?
This is outside the realm of points
This deserves a skull and cross bones !
Just as expected, mint doesn't go with Pizza
Endo's 2nd : "Frisk Pizza"
It received the cross-bones
Expectations are low, but how will Yamasaki's dish really taste ?
Yamasaki's 1st : "Hiyashi Chuka Pizza"
I guess anything is possible ??
Miracle ?
Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
This must be a miracle !
See ?
Interesting
It didn't change at all
Looks fake
It's like a store display
It's interesting
It looks like a restaurant display item
Here's the egg section
You're messing it up
May I ?
Go ahead
So this is the ham piece
And this isn't bad at all
I have one thing to say, too
I got the egg piece and...
it's pretty good
May I say that my piece is
pretty good, too
I got the tomato piece
And it's perfect
See ??
This is really delicious
Not bad at all
The soba broth mixed well with the pizza
It's a great combination
What's my score then ?
Seven ?
Seven
Despite the bad first impression, it received a surprising seven points
Yamasaki's 1st : "Hiyashi Chuka Pizza"
Next up is his "Cotton Candy Pizza"
Yamasaki's 2nd : "Cotton Candy Pizza"
How did it turn out ?
Nothing is left !
It's gone !
Serious ?
See ?
You're right
It melted nicely
It does look tasty
Man, this is over the top sweet
This is some serious business
Really...
There are crunchy pieces of sugar, too
It's hard on my teeth
The crystallized sugar wasn't a hit, and it received two points
Yamasaki's 2nd : "Cotton Candy Pizza"
I'm shooting for a back-to-back victory with this
Don't forget your dipping bowl
I don't know how I feel about this...
Beat the egg to your liking
The way you usually like it
Hamada's "Sukiyaki Pizza" with egg dipping sauce
Hamada's 1st : "Sukiyaki Pizza"
How does it taste ?
First let me take a look
Can it be...?
This could be the surprise item
What the...?
I have to admit it looks awful
If I was served this at a restaurant,
I would demand to see the manager for sure
Look at that meat
I'll put some meat on all of your slices
I can definitely smell the Sukiyaki Nabe
It smells just like Sukiyaki Nabe
How should we eat this then ?
Well, it's really easy to eat
All you have to do is
eat it like any Sukiyaki Nabe
Like Sukiyaki ?
Dip the slice into the sauce like this
Make sure it's in there good
And get some egg on it
That's not how you eat pizza
You're just messing around
You're lying
Trust me, it's good
Don't be shy
See ?
Good
My team agrees that this is
Delicious
Our review also is "very good"
That's your review ?
Yes
How could this be...?
I know, how can it be so good ?
Why is this good ?
The egg really compliments the pizza
The egg is a nice touch
I would say this is...
Delicious
You can make this at home
Right ?
It would be very easy to make
Hamada's 1st : "Sukiyaki Pizza"
With the help of raw egg, it receives nine points
Hamada confidently presents his second entry; "Egg Rice Pizza"
Hamada's 2nd : "Egg Rice Pizza"
Here it is !
Looks familiar
Like Doria ?
Yes, like Doria
It certainly resembles it
I see...
I have to say...
This is very similar to the "Blowfish Pizza"
They belong in the same food group
Hamada's 2nd : "Egg Rice Pizza"
Despite his confidence, Hamada receives only three points
Matsumoto's 1st : "Gohan Desuyo Pizza"
Next up is Matsumoto's promising "Gohan Desuyo Pizza"
You ready for this ?
Remember, there's not much to this...
I don't know what to make of your reaction
Please don't pay attention to its appearance
It looks pretty burned
It's charred
After the commercial
Matsumoto distributes his pizza !
I have high hopes for this one
How does Matsumoto's "Gohan Desuyo Pizza" fare ??
Delicious
Very tasty
Really good
Good
Delicious
The saltiness is perfect
This is incredibly good
It brings out the best of Gohan Desuyo
The best
I feel this deserves a perfect score since it could be sold in stores
A perfect 10 ?
I agree
Let me say the Sukiyaki was good but
think about how much it cost to make it
You're right about that
In this economy,
you don't have to spend much at all
It costs about 20 - 30 yen per piece
You might have done it
You can have this every day
And save money for your Mom's salon expense
Like money for the perm ?
Right, the p@#$%...
It received a unanimous 10 points
Matsumoto's 1st : "Gohan Desuyo Pizza"
Here's Matsumoto's Okinawa inspired entry, "Pig Face Pizza"
Matsumoto's 2nd : "Pig Face Pizza"
How does it look ?
It looks the same as before it went into the oven
Nothing has changed
Right, there isn't any "Before" and "After" image
There's none of that
And it's looking right at me
Yes, it is
It's aimed at him
He's looking at me...
Staring right at Hamada
Amazing elasticity
You can't slice it with that
You might need a different tool...
It like a Halloween mask
I bet you can't cut through that snout
You'll have to put some muscle into it
What do you think ?
How do you feel about this ?
Itadakimasu
I didn't realize how tough it would be
Man, that's tough
The texture is hard
Stop complaining and EAT IT !
Can I just say...
this deserves 7 or 8 points ??
I don't think so
No way !
Matsumoto's 2nd : "Pig Face Pizza"
The dish scored a double skull and cross bones
And here's Matsumoto's most prized ingredient on his "Tuna Head Pizza"
Matsumoto's 3rd : "Tuna Head Pizza"
This is the big finale !!
"Tuna Head Pizza" !!
Here we go
We had to bake this in a bigger oven
This will be difficult to appreciate
How come ?
Because I have already seen that gross looking tuna head
If "Pig Head" represented the Land
Then this one represents the Ocean
I haven't got a clue how it looks after being baked
Thank you very much
That's a huge box
It came straight out of his delivery bike
Thank you very much
See you later
Wow, I can already smell it !
That's a strong smell
I just caught a whiff
After the Commercial
We Reveal the Tuna Head Pizza !
I can smell it from here
That's a strong smell
That's overpowering
Here we go
It smells like seared fish
You can pull the top off ?
Pick it up
It's still the same
Thank you very much !