First Ever Gaki no Tsukai CHIKI CHIKI
100% Rola Produced! Take tons of cards! Kaurta Compeition!
Matsumoto-san, what does this mean?
Well before I explain,
Yamasaki-san pissed me off and is getting fired from this show
I saw the newspaper!
Seriously what was that?
"Matsumoto Fires Yamasaki"
Yeah for real
Tokyo Sports actually published the truth for once
No no no!
It's not true!
It's not true at all
One day we'll find out if it's true
It's lies, lies
Ah the explanation!
Oh yes please
Well as it says on the banner,
Rola handmade some Karuta cards
She did everything herself I heard
Really?
She wrote the words and...
For real?!
She drew the pictures too?
Yes
So we're gonna be competing for real
Oh really?
I'm looking forward to that!
Is it really that exciting?
Yes, I don't know what the cards are gonna be like
It's hard to understand her reality
Yeah Rola's reality
Shes an eccentric person
So! Let's begin!
Introducing, Rola!
Rola-chan!
So cute
Cut that out!
Yeah for real
So you wrote the words and drew the pictures?
Yes!
1 year... Ah! It took 1 week
1 year?!
1 year?
That's unnecessary
So, whoever comes last,
There's a batsu that Rola though of...
Really?
Yes!
A batsu-game, so if I had to explain...
(A department store)
Do you know about 109?
Don't make fun of us
Of course
So you'll stand in front of it doing an impression of me
That sounds horrible!
And what's horrible is,
It's not even that funny
An impression of Rola?!
It sounds awful Im telling you
Timed and Typeset by Henry0310 and GakiDave
Translated by senor_wristband
100% Rola produced Karuta Competition
Rola drew the pictures and wrote the words on these cards,
The first to get 10 cards wins
The one who does worst has to do an impression of Rola in front of 109
So, who will lose?
They seem so close to Tanaka Oi!
Tanaka you cheater!
Oh yeah they are!
There's goddamn nothing near me!
It's the same!
Alright alright
And Endo keeps peeking at them!
ENDO YOU KEEP PEEKING
I'm not!
Yeah don't mess around
You're so passionate about this
Alright then here we go, begin!
Don't look down
Read it!
Yeah Rola
I thought something else would happen
We're obviously waiting for you!
Why didn't you go?
Alright
Alright look up!
Here I go!
(Re) "I mixed up lettuce and cabbage!"
So fast! He was so quick!
So Rola-san? Is it just what it says in the card?
Yes exactly, I always mix them up
Even now?
Even now!
Ah right of course
You can tell once you eat it right?
I can't
Then what's the difference!
Alright here we go
Next one
(Ka) "I found a handsome person!"
It's not here?
It's not!
It says "Let's go to the jungle" on it
"Let's go to the jungle"?
You like people like this?
Yes, people like this, wild people
This guy is not my type, but this line...
Then draw your type!
You get to draw the pictures
OK!
Here I go
Look up
(Ke) "Does it surprise you I'm a germaphobe?"
He already took it!
Hold on!
Stop this!
Stop stop stops stop
No listen! Listen!
All he did was go "EHH!"
You have to take it too!
Exactly right?
But I touched it first!
Endo you don't get a point, but that doesn't mean you get a point!
Why?!
Endo you can't do that, this
You can't just hit it and go EHHH
She said this is Endo's point!
Yes
No no!
Endo you messed up
He messed up right?
Why is this my fault?
You messed up
See even Rola is saying it
You can't do that?
Yeah!
You have to take it
No wayyyy
Well that aside,
What about just stealing it from the side like that?
But Rola said it's fine, right?
Yes, it's fine!
Thank you!
No way, for real?
Sorry, what does this "I dont wanna touch it" mean?
Yeah I hate germs so I always press the elevator buttons like this
This part gets dirty then
Yeah but I can just wipe it later
Then what's the difference!
It's the same thing
Oh yeah
Here I go
Look up
(To) "The Toilet is too long, my grandmother"
OW!
What about this, he can take this one too?
HAMADA-SAN YOU CANT DO THAT
Yeah I don't wanna play anymore
If he's doing that I'm done
I already took it
Tanaka explain
I think 3 of my fingers are broken
You were quicker than me?
Yes right now
Sorry sorry
Here I go
Ok
(Ni) "Don't smirk like that Tanaka-kun!"
AHASH I got it
I GOT IT AHHH
You're so fast! It's scary!
He should stop smirking?
This is Tanaka-kun
Oh, this is about me?
Yes! I see Tanaka-kun smiling all the time and I really hate it so,
You hate it?
You mean Tanaka right?
Yes
You dislike Tanaka the most out of all of us?
Yup!
She said it so clearly. "Yup!"
Then there's no point in taking the cards, if she already hates you
Yeah, exactly
Alright, next one
(Sa) I love cherries
Wow!
Just like it says on the card?
Yes I wrote "I love cherries, and Tanaka too?"
I see
It's so obvious you're following up from the last card
That's what I wrote for real
Oh wow!
What do you mean?
Eh why?
I love cherries,  so I wonder if Tanaka likes them too
Ah, you're asking Tanaka-kun?
Yes yes yes yes
I thought you were saying you love him too
Oh no no no no no
I'll ask you again,
Which one of these members do you hate most?
Tanaka-kun
C'mon!
Did you need to ask that?
(He) I found a strange old man
The one who comes last must do an impression of Rola in front of 109
Trying to avoid that embarassing fate, the 5 desperately snatch cards
I love visiting sick people, do you guys too?
AHAA BITCH
MORONS
Oh no!
You're too fast!
This is guy is just straight up good!
For real
Seriously look, Hamada has 5 points
And me...
He really does!
Endo you're in trouble
I am I am
Oh right, it's up to 10
Yes
Alright next one
Alright
(Ra) Do you know what rackets are?
AIYO!
This was cause of the picture
You didn't even read it
And did you notice, this guy goes AIYO! every time
As if it's an official rule
It scares me
Alright here we go
Alright!
Swinging Swinging! Let's all do Bun-Bungee
You're too excited
This-
Bun-bungee?
What is this picture?
It's bungee jumping,
And I thought the rope was too long, so it's Bun-bungee...
It's supposed to stretch though
Yeah it's a bungee rope. Bun-bungee sounds like a Chinese dish
You want to go Bungee jumping? You like it?
I love bungee!
Oh really?
Yes!
You're not scared of that kind of thing
I'm not scared!
So you've done it a bunch before?
Nope!
Nope!?
You haven't?!
I haven't
Amazing
Alright next one
(ii) "Super dope! Today was so sunny so I hung up a lot of laundry"
AIIII!!!!
You're gonna stab him
Let's watch our hands
But Tanaka that was rude of you wasn't it?
She didn't finish reading it at all!
The phrase is so long
Rola c'mon read it
"Super dope! Today was so sunny so I hung up a lot of laundry"
You didn't listen to her at all
Yeah!
It's so cute too
She went through the trouble of coming up with the phrase
Oh yes, right
Yeah!
So that one doesn't count
Take away a point
I have to return it?
Yeah she hates you
100% Rola Produced Karuta - Hamada is far in the lead, and Endo still has 0!
Endo you're awful
I have nothing at all...
I hate this!
Seriously Endo, what's going on?
What happened? You have NOTHING
I don't know at all
You gotta do better
I mean as a person, you are so dead
I'm not dead! I'm having fun playing and bantering
Alright here I go...
(Ee) Endo-kun &-
Oh!
See he's also too fast
You're too fast!
All she said was "Endo"!
You're too early!
Yeah!
Endo-kun & I had a location shoot the other day. Endo-kun didn't talk to me at all. Why?
You have to listen to the whole thing!
Yeah!
Why Endo?
Why? I mean we did talk though
No not "Why Endo" Yama-chan, put it back
Yeah put it back, I had to do it too
Yeah
Exactly!
Right?
It's cause she hates you right? You don't hate me right?
Hmm I think I hate you more
There it is!
Don't worry
Yama-chan you gotta put it back
Yeah, I told you to
This is taking too long
Yeah you cant do that
Here I go
(Ta) Throbbing Hearbeat
AI!
How do you know she's done?
No I listened and I waited!
I waited just now! I waited just now!
I already found it a while ago! But I waited for her to finish!
I hate it when you guys complain, so I waited!
C'mon...
I got this one properly
Really?
This was a short one
Yes it was
Throbbing Heartbeat?
Yeah, I thought "Wow that's a cool word"
This illustration is Yamasaki-san?
Eh? This is Yama-chan?
Eh?! That's me?
Isn't this an alien (?)
There are short phrases too then?
Yes there are
Ok...
What are you doing?!
No way!
You're kidding right?
Sorry it just felt off. Here I go
Hold on hold on
Endo, what happened?
What happened Endo?
Yeah, why aren't you more lively
I AM being lively
Just like always, I'm being lively
Sorry, can I get something cleared up? What timing should we reach for the cards?
How about when she stops talking?
Ah ok, when you stop talking?
Wait until she stops talking
Until you stop talking?
And even if you see it, you can't do this
Look up until she stops talking
Yeah you're right
Oh yeah, its better not to look
Here I go
Hold on hold on. Hold on.
What?
Endo what happened?
Endo!
You're doing it way too early
What happened?
Oh really?
C'mon banter around a bit more
Do it after the "don don" sound
I am bantering around
But the thing is, I have no points and Im freaking out
Im feeling really anxious. Let me concentrate please.
Yeah Hamada is way in the lead still
Alright, so when she stops talking
Here I go
This is so hard to do
Ill keep talking till the end
OK
Matsumoto-san, do you love your daughter?
AIYAHAAAIIYAGHAAA
He's going AIYO again
Can we ban him from going AIYO?
Yeah it scares me
This is a picture of Matsumoto-san?
Yes! Do you love her?
Well of course I do
How much do you love her?
Well uhh I love her a lot
What the hell?!
Rola keep going keep asking him
No more!  No more!
Turn to the camera and say something to your daughter
To the camera? Hey...
This is camera number 4!
What was that?!
This is camera number 4?
Here I go!
(U) Pickled plums and rice go great together
Here!
It was right in front of your eyes
So you were looking at then? From the start
C'mon stop doing that, don't do that
No way!!
You were looking the entire time huh?
You can't do that man
What are you people saying?
You know-
I was looking at him,
He was peeking like crazy!
Liar! Liar! Liar!
No way
I didn't peek at all!
What're you gonna do? Keep it or put it back?
I didn't do anything wrong at all, im keeping it
2 point penalty
2 point penalty!
You're at 3 points
This is so strict!
Here I go
(Me) Pollock roe and rice go great together
Downtown is really scary.
Matsumoto-san hand touch penalty!
WHY ME?
THAT DOESNT COUNT AS TOUCHING HIS HAND
I DID IT ON ACCIDENT
Rola is saying it though...
Yeah you touched his hand just now
So what about his points?
Minus one.
Matsumoto-san loses a point.
"Short sleeves please, Im eating out today"
Hand touched again
This doesn't count!
You put your hand on top of mine Matsumoto-san!
You touched his hand!
Minus one.
This is not what the touch penalty is for
MINUS ONE!?!
I'm so close!
Let's try to sleep some more - Ah! Im late
Wait a minute...got it!
Because of the penalty I cant play this at all!
Rola Karuta Competition
The 5 are subjected to Airhead Rola's rules
I just cant stop yawing!
Yes!  Here.
I think that's worth......two points!
Without even noticing it Im doing so shit!
You're right!
No not "You're right!"
Here I go!
Wa! You scared me! Why would you do something like this?
That was fast!
Yama-chan is quick!
Hey Rola, isn't this weird? Look how good Yamasaki is doing
He always gets the cards right near him
I think maybe he's peeking
I'm not!
So that's why...minus four.
OY!!!
ROLA NO! HOLD ON! NO! THAT IS NO!
Stop fighting it, there's no point!
I also got unfairly penalised
Four is so many!
That's how bad your penalty was
Yes. Here I go!
(Shi) "Shh! My puppy is sleeping right now, so be quiet Yamasaki-kun"
That was close...
That was kind of weird just now...
Hold on really?!
Why did you say "That was close"?
Well cause I almost just only touched it again like last time, so I thought it was gonna get stolen again
Are you sure it's not because we'll find out you were peeking?
Since the same thing happened to Yamasaki-kun...
Minus two.
Ehhhh!?
I'm going back to 1?
I cant play anymore!
Did I really do something that bad?
Yeah for real!
Endo you cant do that, seriously
Eh why? That makes no sense
This is fine.
He can't have it right?
He can have it
Whatever Rola-chan says goes
Alright Yamasaki-kun here I go
(No) There's so much seaweed on my teeth! I cant take it off
You didn't
You didn't say AIYO
You didn't say it right?
You told me not to!
That deserves a massive penalty
He told me not to say it
You didn't say it
But, he told me not to go AIYO
Everyone was expecting you to say it
AIYOO!!
That started her!  It was scary!
Ah my goosebumps!
Minus five.
Finally!
You're the same as Tanaka now
This will never end!
How is anyone supposed to get 10 points now?
We've taken so many cards but our scores are so low
It's anyone's loss in this Karuta compeition. Only 5 cards remain!
(ki) "So beautiful! I love forests...What about you guys?"
He touched his hand!
No I wasn't!  Wait wait wait wait!
You get.....minus four.
NO NOT MNIUS 4! NOT MINUS 4!
That move now deserved it
She stopped for a bit!
She wasnt finished at all
Wait, really?!
OK, here we go.
(Ri) "I want to eat an apple. Let's go to the grocery store"
Right?
But, you didn't really say anything
I said "Hai!"
Rola no, you're totally mistaken!
The one below 0
Ok, now I've really lost all motivation
This is just-
You could get a +5
(everyone): Yeah there's always that possibility
For real?
"Koko-chan is waiting for me! I gotta go home soon!"
GO!
What was that?!
This guy was looking!
We were all looking up!
I have minus one point!!!
Here I go...
Tanaka-kun minus four.
WHAT THE HELL?!
Sit down!
WHY THE HELL I GOTTA GET -4?!
Alright!
This makes no sense!
What did he do wrong?
I felt bad for him,
That's not a reason!
So I thought Tanaka-kun should be punished instead
Alright next one
(Na) "Anything is OK!"
Hamada-san touched my hand!
He touched his hand!
He didn't say "HAI!" I said it in a loud voice
Minus five!
Yes!  Back to zero!
Wow I'm at the top now
You barely took any!
Finally, one card is left. Who will have to do an impression of Rola?
Here we go:
Ring-ring-ring. Ring-ring-ring. The Bell Rings
Ring-ring-ring. OK that's it.
He touched it.
You touched it! You cant do that
He cant right?
Well maybe but this guy is depressing right?
I'm not depressing! I said "HAI!"
I went like- Rola-chan listen- I went like this.
So you touched your hand again
So according to Rola, you get the penalty
My energy was good right?
Yes it was
His energy was good. But he didn't say AIYO again
No I said AYY! just now
This guy didn't say anything
No I said "Hai!" - You heard me right?
And Tanaka is just talking it easy
I didn't hear anything
I have nothing to do with this
Im getting bullied by Rola here!
Ive been penalised so much! WHAT DID I DO NOW? WHAT DID I DO NOW?
Rola will decide!
Tanaka-kun you were super loud just now
Tanaka-kun, he was too loud so...
Since he didn't do anything,
...minus two.
Well, that's the end!
Nice judging!
This is not possible! This is not possible!
You didn't even do anything
I didn't do anything
In fact I took a ton of cards!
And Rola kept penalizing me!
Alright Rola, what's the batsu game for Tanaka?
The batsu game for Tanaka is...
He will have to go to Shibuya 109...
...and do an impression of me in front of it.  By doing this, for example.
There's no helping it, Rola decided you lost
There's no way I'm accepting this!
Next week, Tanaka does an impression of Rola! Look forward to it!