The 2nd time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!
When will Hamada notice, verification test!
It's the 2nd time   -Yes, 2nd time
We did this last February   -Yes
Last February, we pretended to play these world tabletop games
But actually played a few mini pranks on Hamada
To see how far can he Tsukkomi   -Yes, we did
He's probably off his guard now
And won't expect this to come again
So yes, that's why we're doing this again at this timing
But when we were asked to take this opening
Yamazaki-san thought Hamada will be taking this with us
And I'm really shocked now
That's unbelievable
I thought Hamada is coming, and my heart was beating so fast
Because just look at my face...
This is the first prank
So they made it like this, huh?
He's definitely going to notice this!   -Looking good
Of course he's going to notice this!
I really think it's perfectly done   -Seriously?
He's gonna be thinking "huh?"
And well, there're quite a lot of pranks today
This is a fake one. I always use this
It's actually empty
And I'll use it like this...
I'll be doing this very frequently
Oh, so you'll do it for many times?
Yes, I'll do it for many times
And see when will he stop me
"How many times did you use that, dude!"
Tanaka prepared something too
For me...
Actually, under my jacket...
I'm wearing this T-shirt
This is the one before, right?
This part is pixelated now   -Yes, mosaic
This is the T-shirt from "The judgement of Hamada is getting older and older"
And I'll showing it at some point in time
I see
This time, I'll pretend to have erection
It's not erected now though   -Got it
I'll make it look like it's erected after the show starts
Okay, Hamada is entering very soon
So let's get ready!
Let's do it
Getting ready to prank Hamada
Waiting for Hamada to enter the studio as usual
And then...
Hamada is entering
Please prepare the mic   -Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you   -Nice to meet you
Tanaka, do you know the rules today?
Yes, no problem. No problem for today
I'm confident
Seriously, I'm gonna punch you, dude
No, please don't punch me
Generation gap?   -Exactly
No problem, definitely no problem for today
No worries
Will Hamada notice it?
Hamada-san, please read the title   -Got it
Five seconds countdown
Four, three, two...
The 7th time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!
Let's Play Tabletop Games from Around the World!
The 7th time   -Yes, the 7th time now
You have to know about the rules, there's nothing we can do about it
Yes, of course, I've entered earlier and learnt the rules
Let's have a look then?
Let's see what kind of games are there
Many of these games are German style
And they are very interesting
Easier ones are better   -You're right
Don't make it complicated   -Yes, exactly
Don't fool around with elderlies
That's so true   -Yes, got it
We simply want to enjoy the game together   -Yes
To begin with
Which one should we play first...
You can decide it   -May I?
Yeah, sure
There're many different games here, but...
How about starting with a German game?
German game?   -Yes, let's start with a German game
German games are interesting   -Yes, very interesting
German games are regular, huh?
Yes, it's a regular
So let's play this game together   -Yes
I'll explain the rules while playing
5 cards are on the table
Each person will have 4 cards on hand
There are 5 cards on the table, right?   -Yes
Please look at these cards carefully and memorize them
Eh? Memorize them?
Then I'll ask everyone to close their eyes
And for example, for this card...
The front side and the back side are slightly different
Yeah, it is!   -I see
Each card is slightly different on each side
While everyone closes their eyes
The host, which is me, will flip one of the card
Ah, I see where this is going
I hate this kind of games!
We need to find out which card is flipped, right?   -Yes, exactly
I see
Aren't 5 cards too much?
2 cards are enough
No way, that's too easy
Definitely not enough
That would be too easy
The first person to find out the flipped card, gets to put his card on the table
And the person with no more cards on hand wins
Since there will be more and more cards on the table
It will become more and more difficult   -I see
So, I'll be the host, and let's start the game
Please memorize the cards now
Maybe there're some traps, huh?
We don't know which part of the card will be changed
Time's up! Everyone, please close your eyes
And I will...
I don't remember them already
The host must be having fun
Okay, the card is flipped
So everyone, please open your eyes
Okay, please find out which card is different
What is different for this card?
I think the cow didn't have flowers in it's mouth before
I think it was all grass before
Correct!
Amazing!   -Eh?!
That's incredible!
Seriously?!
He's right!
No way...   -Incredible!
Absolutely incredible
This is amazing, right?   -How did you even notice that?
I had no idea   -Me too
Incredible
Matsumoto-san got it right
So Matsumoto-san can put one of his card on the table
This one?
Sure, just put it on the table
After Matsumoto-san added his card, there're more cards on the table now
Hey...
You did this to me again, huh?
Eh? What?
Huh?
Eh? What do you mean?
What the heck happened to that dude's chin?
No, no, no...
Phew, finally...
Come on, let's play this properly
However...
Too late!!
No one really looks at the face
No way, of course we do
I actually thought you'll notice it at the opening
No, come on, I didn't even think about it
It has been quite a while
Come on, please do your job
Honestly, I just simply wanted to enjoy the game
Yeah, we want to enjoy the game too
Let's do this properly!!
Sorry, please forgive us   -Yeah, let's do it properly
It's fine for me to continue like this, right?
Yeah
This game was really entertaining
Yeah, I enjoyed this one too
I thought it was incredible for him to get it right
The stage is cleaned up and the game is restarted
I didn't think about this at all
No more pranks, seriously
There are many interesting games today
But Matsumoto-san is really good at this game, incredible
I think you have to narrow down your target
And only memorize a few
That's a good strategy
It's impossible to memorize all 5 cards
Hamada-san, let's enjoy this game
Yeah, of course
Your face looks scary
Let's just enjoy it
Matsumoto-san won the game and put his card on the table
So Matsumoto-san will be the host
And we will close our eyes
Memorize it first
Three...
Two...
One...
Okay, stop
Okay
Please open your eyes
Eh? Seriously?   -Wait a second...
Eh?
Did anything change?
Ah! I got it!
Wait Endo, don't flip it yet
Tell us the difference first
Yes, tell us before you flip it
What was changed?
The dolphin was jumping before, and it's now facing down
So it finished jumping   -Yes, after jumping
Correct!
Incredible!   -Really?
Awesome, that was awesome
So Endo, please put one card on the table
I'll put this one
Whao, they all look similar
Oh, so this time Endo is the host   -Yes
Okay, so please memorize them now
Please take your time   -This is too difficult
Five
Four
Three
Two
One
Okay, time's up!
Please close your eyes now
Ready?
Ah, I closed my eyes just now
Me too
Yeah, the way Endo said it...
We have to look at it first, right?
I thought there's another memorizing time afterwards
Wait...don't you think it's too much?
Here it comes
Fabulous!   -I knew you could do it
This is inappropriate, dude!!
Why the heck are you squeezing it all the time?
Good job!
Very well done
I didn't expect him to say "that's too much" though
"That's too much"...
Come on, you said you won't do it anymore
Yes, let's stop it, no more
Hamada is exhausted already   -Exactly!
Yeah, he can't even enjoy the game
He can't focus on the game
Please, please, stop it
Yes, of course, all of the staffs are here, right?
Yeah, that's true
He's distracted, right?
Yeah, he can't focus on the game
That's pathetic
Okay, let's play this again
Please memorize the cards
No, no, no way   -What happened?
There's a kid over there
There's a kid mingling with the staffs
That's too awkward
Well done
Very well done
There's a kid over there?
Why is the camera assistant a kid?
He's here long time ago   -No way!
Wasn't he?
He's here like 8 months ago
Yeah   -Exactly
He said he's very interested in being a camera assistant
Despite of being so young
He's admirable   -No, no way...
He's a primary school student!
Primary school student...
He was already laughing when he met Hamada's eyes
He laughed?   -He completely laughed
Okay, no more!   -Please stop it, please
Let's cut it out
Shall we play another game?
Yeah, let's change it
Change it as a change of pace
The stage was tidied up, and the game was changed
This is a German game called "Ride on the crocodile?"
Crocodile?   -Yes
Basically more and more animals will be placed on it
But before that, roll the dice
For example, if it's one, then put one on it
If it's two, then put two on it
Different numbers have different rules
And I'll explain it while playing   -Got it
What is the next prank to be played on Hamada?
Rock, paper and scissors?
Yeah, that's a good idea
Rock, paper and scissors
The game begins with Matsumoto's turn
Please roll the dice and follow the rules
I'll roll it now   -Yes
Here it is
You're lucky
You can choose one of your animals
And instead of putting it yourself
You can ask someone else to put it for you
Since you're not the one putting it, you don't need to worry even if it collapses
So I don't need to do anything
I'll give this to Hamada-san then
This one   -The sheep
Yeah, the sheep
You can put it this way, or even the other way around
Oh, I can put it this way?   -Yes
So I can't control anything about that?   -Yes
He can put it however he wants
Is this fine?   -Yes
I passed it to him too early   -Yes, that's true
It's now Hosei-san's turn
One
For number one, you put one of your animal on it
I'll put this snake...
It looks shaky
It's tilted!
Eh? This is awful
It's a bit tilted
Well, we just have to continue
Okay, Endo-san
What is this?
It's the crocodile!
It's really good to have the crocodile
If it's crocodile...   -It's even possible to get the crocodile?
From the animals that you've got...
Ahh...you said there's no more, right?
Huh?   -From the animals that you've got...
You said there's no more!
Shozo is having an erection!
Thank you very much   -What the heck, come on!
Bravo!
Well done
Thank you very much, excuse me
-It's a physiological phenomenon
-Yeah, it's inevitable
I realized it as soon as he stood up
I was looking over here
But when he stood up, I was like "whaooo..."
Really? Thank you very much
Come on!
Cut it out, Endo!   -Yes, please forgive me!
We're recording now!   -I'm sorry
What did you get?   -Crocodile
If it's the crocodile
You can put another animal beside, and it will become another base
-And you can put it on the new base
-So the placable area becomes larger
Better choose a flatter animal as base   -Yes
Be careful though, don't break it
Endo-san finished his turn
It's then Hamada and Matsumoto's turns
Hedgehog
The animals are placed with ease
Oh, one!
He didn't even notice Tanaka's prank...
The way you placed this is so annoying
The game continues
And it's now the 3rd round
Roll the dice carefully
It may even collapse because of the dice
"Becoz" it will vibrate
Becoz?
That was a strange pronunciation   -"Becoz"
Excuse me
What was that? Was that relevant to the game?
No, completely irrelevant, I'm sorry   -"Becoz"?
Are you fooling with me, dude!   -Huh?
That T-shirt!
Finally...   -Finally!
Come on!   -He finally noticed it
I didn't notice it at all!
Come on!   -Finally noticed it
It took him quite long   -Yeah, that was long
I didn't look at that at all
You didn't look at this?
We're doing this although we know it won't be aired!
This part will all be pixelated
Come on! I just suddenly saw that
If Tanaka didn't say "becoz", it's gonna be awful
Exactly   -Right?
I see, so that's the turning point
Did you say that on purpose?
No, sorry for saying something weird
You sound like Hamada Tsuyoshi saying "Becoz you bit my ear"
Same pronunciation as "Tyson, becoz you bit my ear"
Yeah, exactly, he did
Excuse me
The game continues, and it's now the 4th round
Eh? I placed twice already
-Yeah, that turns out to be the case
-But that's the rule, right?
Yeah, it is
But that looks quite possible
Do it slowly
"De De Demae-can, Demae ga sui sui suiii"
"Warm, warm, delivered to you warmly!"
"Demae ga sui sui suiii"
"De De Demae-can"
Stop the music!
What the heck is going on?
What the heck are you guys doing?
Safe, safe
Very impressive
Very impressive   -Well done
No, no, come on...   -Superb
It really was superb
The number of pranks is much more than before
Is it?   -Yes
But I have to say, you're not going senile at all!
What does that even mean?
You are well-honed
Yeah, he noticed it quickly
Are you taking something (drugs)?
In order to be well-honed   -Thinking backwards
What can I even take, dude
His five senses are super sharp
Nothing special
Who's next?
Yama-chan?
Yes, Matsumoto-san just finished, so it's Hosei-san
This is a tough one   -Very difficult
Maybe it's gonna end here   -My turn?
This one is really tough
Please wait a moment...
That's impossible
You're boorish
That's true, he's not cautious
I wanted to have palpitation feeling
It ended in one shot
In this case, according to the rules
From those that fell off
Two of the animals will become yours
And the other two are gone   -I see
I see, these two, so the game continues?   -Yes, it continues
After that, he didn't notice the prank at all, and it's now the 6th round
Eh? You're facing the camera with your butt?
Yeah, this is the crunch
This is very crucial...
Let's stand away from the table, just in case we hit it
Would that ever happen?
Amazing!
He's really good at this   -So Matsumoto-san wins?
Yes   -Congratulations
Hooray!
That was interesting
Let's change the game
Okay, got it
Let's see
Which game should we play...
He scared me!
Who the heck is he?
Awesome   -He was frightened
No, no, not "hooray"...
Finally noticed it
No, come on, seriously...
Too much! Too much!!
Finally noticed it
He was there quite a while ago   -For real?
I tried so hard to hold back my laughters
I didn't notice him at all
Okay, let's change the game
Up till now, this is the third restart
Is someone irrelevant mingling with the staffs?
No, no, no more pranks
Really?   -That's what they told me
Hamada's cautiousness is at maximum
And now, the new game starts
This is a 5 player game
Let's flip one card, for example this card...
There are three kinds of color, right?
You need to find out the Matryoshka card with all these 3 colors
Then stand up and do the same pose as the card
I see
After all of the color cards are distributed, the person who got it right the most wins
Got it   -That's all for the rules
Let's start
Okay
Ah, this one is really hard to judge
Yeah, very difficult to judge
Whoa, wait a second, this one is so hard to judge, wait a second...
Well, you know...
People call me the legendary comedian
Sorry, Endo wins   -Eh?!
Sorry, that was difficult to judge, but I think he's a bit faster
That one was difficult to judge   -Okay
After that, he didn't notice the prank, and 8 minutes has passed
I'll flip this one   -Okay
Blue, yellow, red...
Isn't it smelly?
I knew it
It's really hard for me to say though
Glad that you said it
Awesome
Thank you very much
It's actually smelly all the time
The correct answer is, it smells like poop under the table
It's the smell of poop
Please don't think that it's body odor
It was so freaking smelly
It's the smell of poop
We really wanted you to notice this as soon as possible
I bet so
Well, because there are people on both sides
It's either Matsumoto or Endo
But talking about body odor, it must be Matsumoto
In terms of age
I thought like "Matsumoto-san is already smelling like this?"
So he's smelling like this recently?
No way!
That's so pathetic!
It's actually the smell of poop though
Anyway, this time...
It ends here
But actually, there's one more thing that we hoped you will notice
He's probably having a difficult time now
A difficult time?
This prank actually started right from the opening
For about one hour already
This one?
Hello
Please come out
So you finally noticed me
Why did you put Fujiwara inside?
He left the hospital
Ah, I see
Do you feel well now?
I thought I can finally stretch my body, but then they put me in this cramped place
It must be cramped, huh?   -Yes