The First Annual Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende, Chiki Chiki
My gun is my finger and mouth!
Finger Survival Game~!!
Thank you very much!
Thank you?
What do you mean?
For having such a peaceful event
Please explain the rule
-We will be playing survival game today
-Yeah, that's why we're dressed like this
However, due to budget constraints,
we weren't able to prepare the guns
That's the most important thing though
You have to prepare that dude
It was impossible. All of the money was spent on these costumes
And this banner as well
No way, we don't need this banner
But guys, look, we have fingers right?
So we will be using these today
You mean to use our fingers as a gun...
Yes, use your fingers as if it is a gun
Give it a shot, Endo
Not even close dude, take this seriously
The gun doesn't looks like it's fired at all
Yeah, it's fired
You just wanted to embarrass him
Please stop that
Let's welcome the guests
These 3 guests will be joining today's game too
It's always these 3 guests
Are you the stressed out version of Mukku?
*Mukku is a wild man mascot for the kids tv show "Hirake! Ponkiki"
No, I'm not the actor inside
Should we all try to shoot our gun once?
To check out how it looks
Yeah, let's give it a shot
And we will choose our team members based on your shot
You're right, so we have to take a look first
We want to choose the most destructive members
Can this even be destructive?
We need to show our destructiveness?
Yes, of course
Show us your attack power with your fingers
Let's start the game!
Rock, paper...Scissors!!!
-That's a scissor
-So you lost
This gave me a headache
Because you're shouting out loud all of a sudden
Anyway, Hamada can choose first, and I'll choose next
Tanaka, can you show us your weapon?
I brought a Rifle today
You're not using your fingers dude
That is cheating
That's a Tanegashima gun dude
*Tanegashima gun is a type of arquebus firearm introduced to Japan through the Portuguese Empire in 1543
Yeah, that's a firearm
I'm just loading the gun
That's a shotgun right?
Buff
Buff?
-Your gun is wet
-What's up with him?
I told you your gun is wet!!
Fujiwara show us your weapon
-I brought a rocket launcher
-I see
Wow, really?
That must be powerful
That's amazing
Endo, show us your weapon please
I'll be dual-wielding two .44 Magnums
No one use that in a survival game dude
-The one in Dirty Harry right?
-That was really cool
That's not a dual, that's singular
But it's amazing
It seems to have a high hit rate
I can go like this too
Inamoto, show us your weapon
I'll be using grenades
So I'll be hiding somewhere, and then...
That's so quiet
Shout it out louder dude
You're listening to the sound of your own voice
Yama-chan, show us please
I just want to use the machine gun
And it's a huge one
That's weak
What was that "huuu" in the beginning
Because some bullets are empty
What do you mean by empty?
Seriously, some bullets could be empty
Fujimon, please show us
I will use a gun with silencer
Okay, I see
What are you doing dude
-There's no sound because of the silencer
-Well, I know
Tanmen, show us
Tanmen is familiar with these
Sorry, but I'll be professional
I'll use land mines
So that's game over
Eh, no sound?
That's just a sprain
It's absolutely fine to step on it
But it's actually very powerful
How about Non-chan?
I'll be swinging the axe
It's not the end of an Oogiri
But there's no more other weapons
It's fine to overlap too
I'll choose Fujiwara
The leaders are choosing the members, and forming their teams
These are the members of the two teams
This is the map for this battlefield
To win the game, you need to take
the opponent team's flag at the other end
And you're out if you got shot
The two teams are now having a
strategy meeting before the game starts
So let's start the meeting
This is the map of the battlefield
Maybe we can make use of these obstacles
But let's predict their attack first
Maybe they'll split into two groups?
Split into two groups...
Inomoto, how will you attack if you are Hamada?
Keep in mind that he's an idiot
If I'm Hamada-san?
I'll just go straight from here
Will Hamada-san even be the one to attack though?
Then maybe everyone except Hamada
But we win if we get Hamada right?
No, we need to get their flag
You know nothing about the rules
We have rules for this?
We lose if they take our flags
We don't even have guns, yet we still have rules?
There's nothing we can do about that
But we do have a flag though
-We can't let them take this?
-Yes
So someone must stay here right?
Yes, you're right
On the other hand, for Hamada's team
We just need to take that red flag in front of us right?
Yeah, it's right in front of us
But frontal assault is risky
I am short and I move fast, so maybe I can attack from behind
That's amazing
But Non-chan should be able to move without being noticed right?
Maybe I can hide in the bushes around Matsumoto's team
If they are in danger, help them out with your Bazooka
Then I will cover them at the back
Just shoot it like "Don! Don!"
-It's actually right there
-Yes
It's not that far
-Just to be safe, can you stay behind Endo?
-Yes, no problem
So Endo will be staying here
And we four will split into two groups
So I'll pair up with Inomoto
-I'll pair up with Housei-san
-Yes
And we'll attack from here and there respectively
Who will be attacking from the front?
Maybe I'll go, because I brought a scope as well
But you're using rifle though
You need a lot of time to take aim
My gun is automatic so I can just go like "Ba ba ba ba ba"
Having the captain to attack from the front is very helpful anyway
That's the most dangerous role
Someone should stay and protect the flag right?
-Tanaka can just snipe the approaching enemies
-I see
Then I will stay here
-Snipe them with you rifle
-I got it
So the defense is perfect
Yes, it is
Both teams finished their meeting
The fierce battle of finger survival game starts now!
Are you guys ready?
The battle...
START
Ok, let's do this
Should we move forward?
Let's go over there
-Tanaka, can you do it?
-Yes, please leave it to me
Please instruct us if something happens
Okay, got it
Start moving if you're attacking from behind
They're moving
Nice Tanaka, that's a nice one
Did they notice me!?
I thought I was disguised in the bushes
Please come back and help if I'm in danger
Cover me, cover me!
They're not dying at all
Nothing?
He didn't notice me
Someone's coming
Someone is coming!
You're out dude!!
I got you dude
I got him, I got him
Cover me, cover me
They're all out!!
Hey, stop for a moment!!
Stop for a moment guys
Stop!!
Gather up!!
Just stop for a moment
You've just bumped your head
But he never dies
Wait a moment guys
Let's do this properly
Yeah, let's do this properly
You guys never die
You were shot for several times
For many times
You actually missed it
I even shot you in the head for so many times, and you just pretend you didn't notice it
Because he was wearing a helmet
Yeah, the helmet saved my life
-Even the rocket launcher was fired
-But it didn't hit us
It's a launcher dude
It was very close though
You guys should all be dead already
For example, who are you talking about?
You guys were all standing here like idiots
You guys should all be dead
Because Komoto never dies
-All you guys stepped on my land mines
-So you all should be dead
I got everyone
You're just making it up now dude
What pisses me off is that Fujimoto punched me in the head
That's because I put a grenade right in front of you,
and you're still not blown away
Why aren't you blown away?
Because I already shot everyone, and still no one is dead
There was a hole in your stomach, a big hole
Even before that, I shot you in the head
I told you the helmet saved my life right?
I knew that, and I shot you in the neck as well
There was a big hole in his stomach, and he can still run
Wait a second...
Where have you been Iwao?
I killed Fujimoto with one shot
-No you didn't
-With one shot
He confused me with the bushes,
and kept on shooting the bushes instead
You were just shooting at the bushes, not me
Just look at his costume, of course I'll confuse him with the bushes
Yeah, so you were just shooting at the bushes
This is difficult
You have to make it clear if you were shot
Let's just shout that "I was shot"
That's the manner for survival game
You have to be honest and say it yourself
Only if it hits though
And leave the field after that
Let's start again
Let's do this properly
I'm gonna play seriously this time
We were always serious though
The two teams returned to their base again
Komoto why were you surrounded by them?
I've set up the land mines before they came
But even if I shout "bomb, bomb", they just ignore it
When I arrived, you were already surrounded by them
Yeah, like being honeycombed
For this time
Endo can be attacking aggressively
And I'll be protecting the flag
If someone approaches here, then I'll shout "Gather up!!"
And we all gather to shoot him, and make him a honeycomb
So they have no excuse
Yes, no excuse
Maybe we can even hide and let them approach
So like a trap, let one of them approach first
And shoot him together, so he must die
Exactly, after Matsumoto shouts "Gather up", we gather and attack
So we won't be moving a lot this time
They must be terrified
Like "why aren't they coming at all?"
Are you guys ready?
Yes we are
The battle starts
Okay, let's go
Don't let them come near here
-Tanaka, you have to stop them
-Yes, no problem
Don't go far guys
Maybe we can just hide over there
They're coming
I'll move forward from the left hand side
I'm moving from the left side as well
Good, Fujiwara, keep it up and attack from behind
Is everything fine at your end?
No one is approaching yet
They're coming
Two people are coming
Enemy at 11 o'clock!
They are here! One enemy at 11 o'clock!
How many meters away?
Eh, 10 meters
One enemy at 2 o'clock!
He's over there! Iwao is over there!
They're coming!
-Keep on going Fujiwara
-Please! Fujiwara!
Fujiwara, remember to fire the launcher at a good timing
Good job, Fujiwara!
They're here!
They are in front of us!
Captain! Please give the order!
Not yet, not yet!
They're coming!
One enemy, one enemy is here!
They're coming
It's Iwao! Iwao is here!
Please! Captain! Please give the order!
Gather up!!
I'll throw a grenade
Launcher!!
Here comes the launcher
I got them! Come on!
They should be blown away!!
They should be blown away! It's a launcher dude!
Why are they still shouting "Bang bang"
Come on, you can do it!
Let's do this properly!!
Ouch!
What are you doing?
You guys were all standing over there
And Fujiwara fired the launcher at all you guys
They should be dead
They should all be dead right?
And I shot everyone again to make sure they're all dead
Everyone should be dead
Why are you guys all standing here anyway?
Captain!! Where are you captain?
Captain, captain...
I went to take the flag on my own...
I thought you asked us to fight here
Because no one was defending
I'm asking why are they all standing here?
-Captain was also here
-Really?
-And launcher killed all of them
-Yeah, they must be dead
Well, we have something like Sentsu beans
Sentsu?
The beans from Dragon ball, it heals us immediately
No matter how severe the wound is
You need to eat it though
They didn't eat it, I went "bang bang" before that
Can you stop saying "that was close",
and pretend you weren't shot?
No, that was close
It almost got me
I chopped your head off with beam saber dude
So I immediately put my head back, that was close
You're just making up everything
Let's take some good scenes
What do you mean by good scenes?
Just take some good scenes separately and combine them
This will be the same forever
Even if we start again
No one will die
Let us discuss about this first
Why are they trying to decide everything?
If we just combine the scenes, it's no longer a game
And we were completely advantageous
They are just too weak
Let captain decide it
Yeah, let captain decide it
Agreed
What was that discussion for?
Captain?
So agreed?
Everyone agrees?
Their captain said yes
As this seems to last forever,
we decided to take separate scenes instead
Okay, good work
That was good, that's a good scene
Okay, done
Thank you
Endo, do you want to die in one shot
Or should I shoot many shots like "da da da", which one do you like?
-The latter one please
-Okay
Okay, done
That was amazing
It's pitiful
All scenes finished
Here comes the launcher
Leave me alone and move on!
What the heck are you talking about!
-We'll survive together
-Sorry
Watch out!
Shoot it!
No, I can't! It may hit Hamada-san!
It will be fine, so just shoot!
Papa will be back before your birthday
Papa will be back for sure
Only the two leaders survived till the end
We will break the tie with a contest on quick shot
Beat him captain
So everything ends here
Finish him captain
Let's end this game
Start!
One, two...
Three!
That was fast
He missed it
Hamada is apparently faster
Finish him captain!!
What are you doing captain?
That must be a new version of SmartNews CM*
*Matsumoto and Hamada took many versions of CMs for SmartNews, and they "act" like very close friends in the CMs
That must be for SmartNews
(Staff) Okay!
(Staff) Thank you very much
Hamada turned around at two
Eh, really? That's so mean
That breaks the rule