Absolutely No-Laughing Tycoons GoTo Las Vegas
Fujiwara
Talks about
Vice President
Yoshimoto Kogyo
We'd like for you to do a PR comment this year as usual.
Mine?
Thank you very much.
If you make a mistake, or fumble your words
Yes
There's a punishment game.
What? Okay, got it.
Vice President Fujiwara puts his life on the line to do the PR comment!!
Okay, here we go
3... 2...
It's happening this year too!
(PR Comment)
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende, ah, sorry, Downtown no
Darn it
Excuse me
This? Okay
What's this?
Safe... huh?
Hmm? Safe? No?
Wait, what? What?
Armlock
Excuse me
Female MMA fighter
with a total of 19 wins
Shizuka Sugiyama
Are you tapping out?
What is this?
Excuse me
Thank you
Sorry
Thank you...
Really...
Thank you
Sorry about that
Um, we're only finished with the title...
Right, I'll do my best
Continuation
This year's setting is Las Vegas and of course
(PR comment)
at the many events and shows and
in the bus when it's going between locations
the members Matsumoto, Hamada, Hosei, Endo, and Tanaka will
bring you powered-up laughs
and on top of that, lots of, eh? Sorry
Fujiwara is OUT
Oh no...
Okay
Here we go
Scary, scary
Seconds? Seconds?
Seconds?
Excuse me
Sorry
Just now I did the arm, so this time I'll go for the lower part, okay?
Right, thank you
Ouch, ouch!
I'm going for the other side, okay?
All right
Ouch!
Are you tapping out?
Yes!
Excuse me
Thank you
(PR comment)
Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende New Year's Eve Special
Absolutely No-Laughing Tycoons
GoTo Las Vegas 24 Hours
Look forward to it!
Absolutely No-Laughing Tycoons GoTo Las Vegas 24 Hours
Begins at 6:30 PM
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende! New Year's Eve Special!!
m 0 10 l 0 100 1350 100 1350 10
m 0 10 l 0 120 340 120 340 10