1st Time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arrahende "I'm the One Who Understands you Best!"
"Anyways, You'd Look Great in this Thing" Tatekawa Shiraku Edition!!
Matsumoto-san, we've done this 15 times already...
Ah is that so
What's with this title... cut it out already
"Anyways, You'd Look Great in this Thing"
(Sounds old fashioned)
What time are we in?...
Cut it out...
Change it already
Change with the times
A special series on Gaki, where the members buy gifts for guests based on their interests
It's safe to say we've done pretty poorly so far
Suprisingly...
Leave it
Leave it, you're the worst of us...
I'm not the worst
Suprisingly, we've got the previous results, and apart from Hamada-san, we're all terrible
No way
No way that's true...
Suprisingly... the worst, Look
I've only lost once
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Yes, Hamada-san was missing for one but
Matsumoto-san has 6 losses
Look at Yama-chan
Hosei-san with 9 losses...
Wait, you're the one with no style
When you think of someone with no style it's Tanaka
The board says otherwise
Anyway, without further adieu...
Let's welcome our guest Tatekawa Shiraku-san!
Rakugo-ka
(Storyteller)
Both a commentator on various shows and an active Rakugo-ka, Tatekawa Shiraku
This time the Gaki members will choose a top and an accessory to present to Tatekawa Shiraku
Ah yeah this is what we're used to seeing him in
Yes, this is my usual getup
I've no idea how he dresses casually though
That's true
Surprisingly... you dress quite differently right, in your own time?
(Hysteric Glamour is a Japanese fashion brand
known for western style clothing)
Usually I wear Hysteric Glamour and rock style clothing
Ehh... Really?
I've seen him in it
Shishō in Hysteric Glamour clothing
Shishō = A term for a master in their field
The five of us are going to pick out stuff and you'll choose your favourite
The worst will have to pay
Timed, Typeset & Translated by Inepped
Before the show the five searched for a top and an accessory they think will suit Tatekawa Shiraku
I can't really picture him in casual clothes
He's actually the same age as me (58)
Understated but kind of scary sort of image, right
What about something cute instead?
I think everyone else is probably thinking about one kind of thing
Make it wild or something...
Someone is definitely gonna get something wild
How about something kinda like this
A red parka or something
He likes baseball right? Shiraku-san
A baseball shirt... hmm
I mean I think he likes baseball but I don't think he's a huge fan or anything
A hat, that's definitely more Tanaka's thing
I don't want to see him wear something like that
I haven't really seen anything so far
It's a great feeling when they choose to keep the item you picked for them
It's a lot harder than it looks, looking for someone else
I don't think he would go for something I would wear
How about this?
I can't imagine him in that
Right, I can't picture it
It's a poncho, isn't it? The pattern is quite cute
"Ethnic" poncho
What's does "Ethnic" mean?
I have no idea what "Ethnic" means
I also like Hysteric Glamour style stuff
It's kind of Rock n' Roll
The style goes with the music
Heavy Metal
Rock
80's and 90's Heavy metal suits him perfectly
This is bad! You guys know who this is? ACDC Angus Young
A legendary guitarist
What's this? Wait a minute, this is cool
An angry skull
A skull right?
Hey?
Wait a sec...
This is bad
No good?
Sunglasses are a great style item, they can change your look quite a lot
I was looking for LEON or similar styling
Since we've come this far...
This looks like something Renege-san would wear
These... well they're pretty interesting
Top Gun
Like from Top Gun
These are a little more wild
Today you're searching for a top and an accessory
What about this?
What's your best price?
121,000 Yen (approx. £730/$900)
This looks good
It's nowhere near as warm as it looks
What do you think of this?
I think this would be pretty good
Total comes to ???,??? yen
This is the most expensive item so far
But, I did just win 100,000 yen from Kiki
Shiraku will take home his favourite item, the worst will have to pay out of their own pocket
So first off, which of our tops will suit Tatekawa Shiraku-san
I hate to be last in this
I'm gonna go full attack on this one
First off is Endo to present his top to Shiraku
Here is the product I came up with
I've never really seen the Wild look of Shishō
When I was looking for wild kind of stuff, I thought this might suit Shishō
The idiot side of Endo is coming out
A leather jacket
But don't you think it really suits him, the size is perfect too
It doesn't suit him at all
Not at all
It's supposed to be wild, right?
This time it's wild themed, yeah
This isn't wild at all...
It's not wild whatsoever
Maybe he hasn't worn anything like it before, but I can see him wearing stuff like this more and more
Endo
How many years has it been since you became a member?
How can you have so little understanding
It's pretty good
It's wild and it's not too long
I mean, leather jackets can be quite wild and all but...
Here it looks alright but I don't know when Shiraku-han would wear this
Well let's leave it to Shishō
Chiaki is gonna be super mad
Chiaki is Endo's ex-wife
It's been 7 years already
Next up is Hamada to present his top
I know that Shiraku-han has kids
I was thinking of the cute Shiraku-han image
Cute?...
This kinda image is what I was going for
The colour is kinda off
Overalls?
These are great for spring and summer
I thought the colour would be more POP
He's struggling with his 50 year old shoulders
Am I going fishing?
The colour should definitely have more POP...
It's kinda like work wear...
All you lot do is complain!
Look it's a LEGO man
I think having something like this works occasionally
Pooping is gonna be difficult
Shiraku-san takes loads of dumps
Matsumoto is confident with his top
I am super confident with this one, Shiraku-san
You're definitely gonna want to keep this
Definitely?... The overalls are pretty good
Shiraku-san's wife is quite young, right?
Yeah, 18 years younger
That feeling of youth
Also this year it's been quite in...
Sty sty sty style...
Sty sty sty?
Isn't this awesome!
Long jean jacket
Jean jackets have been in style this year, am I right?
See everyone is agreeing with me
Nobody has said anything...
See it's super awesome!
NO WAY!!
NO WAY!! LOOK AT IT!!
This is...
Would you mind spinning around?
It's super cool and cute
Cool and cute
Where would you wear this...?
He could wear this on stage
No way he could wear this on stage
Of course he'd then take it off
Are you sure about this one?
You maybe can't wear it all the time but...
It'll be just right about now, with a t-shirt underneath
Shozo's was a bit less aggressive
Shiraku-han, do you think you'd enter a Yose wearing this?
Yose = a theatre where rakugo perform
Soon you'll see all the Rakugo-ka wearing this
Tanaka, who is overflowing with confidence, presents his top
I was trying to find something a little different
It'd probably suit everyone apart from me
What... I've no idea what that is
Shishō let out a little Eh? Eh?
What is that?
Don't you think this colour is perfect for Shishō
Shishō usually wears a Kimono, a Japanese Kimono, this is sort of like a Kimono, but maybe a bit more casual
See, what about this colour?
What country is this from?
He looks like one of those guys at the UN
Africa...
African kind of style
I think it can be worn whenever, like in summer maybe
The material also kinda...
Are you laughing?
Shiraku-Shishō is definitely not laughing
What top has Hosei chosen to challenge with
I think I understand Shirakushō the best of all
Shirakushō?
I understand Shiraku-Shishō
I know that he loves Hysteric Glamour
He still can't speak...
I also like Hysteric Glamour
So I think we have the same mindset
I guess people who like Hysteric Glamour should be able to understand each other better
So I thought, what would you not buy for yourself
You're joking right...
Enough already
You're just bullying Shiraku-han
I'M NOT BULLYING HIM
Are you kidding around?
I'm not kidding around
It looks great
Kids'll cry...
Everyday when I'm taking my kids to kindergarten
It's cool don't ya think
Looks like it's searching for water
Which top is Shiraku going to choose?
Shishō, please pick honestly
I want something to wear in my spare time, taking my kids to kindergarten etc.
Without further adeu, Shiraku-san, which top is your favourite?
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Can you tell us the reason?
I wouldn't normally wear such a long one but
I like the feel of this one
I really like the various colouring and patterns
Taking or picking up from kindergarten...
YOU CAN'T SAY ANYTHING!
You say anymore and I'll throw you to the lion
Please tell us, which is you're 2nd favourite?
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Tanaka
This is good for when I'm playing around with my kids
Like for when we go to the park
Please tell us, which is you're 3rd favourite?
Endo
Hosei
Tanaka
Of course it's gonna be that one
It's nice and clean, but a bit bland
A bit bland, okay
We're down to the last two
Forget about the kindergarten run
Let's go to the zoo
Which top is the worst?
Hosei
Tanaka
The worst is...?
It had to be
Shishō, are you serious?
Everyone would be looking at me
It's Dainoji
Hosei has to pay 3,295 Yen (approx. £20/$25)
Next, what accessory will Shiraku choose, first up is Hamada
Similar to earlier with the overalls, I was going with the cute look
The total image
Something his kids would like as well
What a long bag
Shoes?
Sneakers
Something's attached to it
A dog?
Eh? This is from Adidas?
Yeah, Adidas
I'm not sure about this, it's neither good nor bad
He might love it or hate it
I think Shiraku-Shishō will hate it
He hates these the most
Think of how his kids will feel, "Dad, these sneakers are so cute"
"It has a tail!"
Not gonna happen
Isn't a bunch of stuff going to get in between there...
Where?
Between the cover and the shoe
What are you rambling about?
The design is good, nothing's gonna get in between
The hem doesn't go all the way down
It's cute
I don't think it'll be first...
You guys do nothing but complain!
Tanaka hopes to challenge with his item
Mine is quite simple
A hat?
Thanks for your time
It's a sauna hat
It's a sauna hat, Shishō
It's to wear in a sauna
All you've been saying is sauna
Do you often go to the sauna?
From time to time
I don't really have a sauna hat
What's the effect of wearing a sauna hat?
It keeps the heat out
It'll stop you from feeling feverish and stop your hair from frizzing
You look like an idiot though
You look like ET
Endo is unsure of his item
Along with the leather jacket earlier, I've also gone with the overall look
It's a tiny bag
Glasses?
Sunglasses?
The Wild kind of feel
What is wild about these?
Super cool
Hamashokan
Suprisingly... they do suit you
Ah, really, I can't see anything out of these
These are a popular brand of sunglasses, Ray-Ban
Do you wear sunglasses at all?
I actually do wear them quite a bit
Endo has done alright this time
Really, I think with the wild theme
Hosei has a pretty tricky item
I'm going all out with this one
You can't just be messing around like earlier
This isn't really for everyday use, more like for playtime
What is this?
And... there it is
The worst of all
Yama-chan, what is wrong with you?
Haven't we seen this before?
We have, from Endo
Mine had a different colouring
This is just awful
You just copied Endo
It's just a different colour
You're just bullying him
Shishō, it's absolutely perfect for you
Seriously... This is...
Is this for when you're taking out the trash
Kabukichō in the morning
Kabukichō is an entertainment and red-light district in Shinjuku
Last up to show his item is Matsumoto
There's no way I'm losing this one
Going last always sucks
This time I went
for something adventurous
It's quite large
What is it?
A hat?
It's a sun visor
No, it's a bag
LAME
It's an over the shoulder one
This is...
Could you sling it over your body?
Ah that's it, that's it
How about around the back
It's got loads of style right...
This is kinda...
Can I tell you the price?
This was 161,700 yen (approx. £990/$1,190)
Who cares...
Seems like a nuisance
Having it around the back is the best method
The practicality...
You can fit loads of stuff in it
There's no way you can
The cap part is just in the way
It's not about what's in the way or not, it's about fashion
Then what about the tail on the sneakers!
Those are cute...
If the cap is a nuisance then so is the tail
It's just in the way
If this goes wrong I have to pay 160,000 yen
The one with the worst item has to pay, who will it be?
Which item is in 1st place?
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
C'mon miracle
Miracle...
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
I can wear these to play with the kids
But it may be a little hard to wear them at work
Your 2nd choice please
Endo
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Yeah, they suited him
That's true, I think they really suit you
Well, these are quite normal
Wear them to feel to wild
He said earlier that they're not that wild
Your 3rd choice please?
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Think of the parties
Let's get him paying 160,000 yen
Right, of course
Thank you, Shishō
Right, that's all for today...
We've still got the best part of the program
It's between these two
There's not a chance I can lose to THAT thing, if I do there's something wrong with Shiraku-san
Is the worst Matsumoto's sun visor bag or Hosei's crow mask?
Time to decide the worst item
The worst is?
YES!
Hosei pays 5000 yen (approx. £30/$40)
That was close!
I can't think of a single use for this, it'll scare kids, it's something that no one would ever need
I thought there'd be something I'd really like but in the end I was just being bullied
No way, no way
It was these guys