ShinobiSubs
Gaki No Tsukai Presents
Never been there before, let's ask what the best 3 is!!
Wow really this again, how many times now?
4th time
The 5 of them will go to a town they have never been
to before and ask the locals what the best 3 points are
There are raffle tickets for every station
from 6 prefectures in the Tokyo area
Shall we draw one then?
Okay go for it Endo
Idol Endo!
- Everyone's idol
Everyone wanks over you
Okay this is where we will go
Where will it be??
- He's short sighted!
Sorry!
- Where?
Nagata?
-(staff) It's in Chiba
Chiba AGAIN?!
It's pretty far from here
(Staff) It's on the Sotobou line
It's here
It's miles away!
The Sotobou line
- That's pretty far
This is the station...
Wow it's basic to say the least
Look at this atmosphere!
It'll be hard to even find people there!
It's been decided!
We are off to Nagata in Chiba!!
FunnyJapan/ShinobiSubs
Reddit/r/FunnyJapan
Facebook/ShinobiSubs
Twitter @ShinobiSubs
(One week later)
Well everyone we are here in Oamishirasato, Chiba prefecture
The Japan Railways Sotobou Line Nagata Station
- Here we are...
I'm a bit worried here
We just got here by car
There is literally no one in sight...
Hardly none!
Let's get to it and ask what's number 3 around here!
There has been 2 trains in the last hour...
People are coming out
There's an archaeologist
Do you have a moment to talk?
We're shooting here today and...
Here in Nagata... Nagata right?
- Is there any good places?
How long have you lived here?
Around 23 years
How have the archaeological digs been going?
- He's not an archaeologist!
What line of work are you in?
You have a great archaeologist air about you
I draw for a living
Have you heard of Nikakai? (Public body of art culture)
They do all those amazing fine works
I'm the Director of it.
That's something else indeed!
Just what will the Nikakai Director, Kawauchi-san, resident of 23 years
Recommend as his number 3 attraction in Nagata?
We basically go to places we haven't been
And as the locals where the best places to go are
So we would like to know your number 3
Just one is good
- 3rd place
Number 3
There really isn't anything good around here...
There must be!
- I'm sure there's something!
When did you get here?
- Just now
Why did you choose here?
To put it simply... It's a batsu game
It's not a punishment!
I lied!
Tanaka, go and ask that kid
Excuse me! Can I talk to you for a moment please?
Thank you!
After giving up on Kawauchi-san, they move on to asking this school girl
How old are you?
2nd year High school
Are you in a club?
- Yes
You're pretty dirty
You're covered in it! What club are you in?
- Climbing
- Ah! That's why!
We're looking for places in Nagata and asking what the best 3 are
Anything is fine
There isn't anything right?
- No! She is just thinking!
There has to be something!
Recommendation...?
- Yeah! Anything about this town
Anything is fine!
Nothing coming out
Sorry about all this sudden pressure!
- Where do you always go?
Tell us where you hang out
Really nothing huh...
She's thinking about it!
Suddenly during the interview...
Hamada spots a new target!
HEY KID get the fuck over here!!
You will traumatize him
It's good to gather a lot of information
After parting ways with her, next up is...
The questioning of the young lad Hamada collared
How old are you?
Where you born around here?
Yeah
Well then...
He's been here 17 years
What could Haruhara-kun who was born and raised here, number 3 be??
When I was a kid... We always used to play around
You see that home center over there
- Yeah over that way
There is a 5 parks close to that
- There's a shit load of them!
5?!
I used to go and play there often
Do the 5 of them all have individual names?
Number 1, Number 2, Number 3...
Isn't it just one park?!
They're probably separated
Let's go see it
They might look different
Which number is good?
I suggest... Number...
Number 1?
It's definitely just one park!
Sorry to hassle you
We need to show the sign
- Bet it shocked you huh?
You got your lunch money on ya?
Don't extort school kids!
They make toward the park recommended by Haruhara-kun
But en-route...
Eh?! Look how difficult that is! What's with that one way
Wow, that is backwards complicated
That will get you panicked!
How do you where?!
Looks like a driving school!
Where do you go?!
Due to the complex nature of the intersection as go can see here
After asking the local police, there was many incidents of wrong direction
And so they erected 9 no entry signs to guide traffic around
So you're meant to go straight?
We're crossing here?
He said behind the home center here?
On the right hand side?
He said the number 1 park was best
"I like the Number 1 park" he said...
What sort of park is it going to be!
They walk for 5 minutes
Here?
- It doesn't say number one though...
Hello~
Surprised to see us huh?
Is this the Number one park?
It is
We asked what the good points of this neighborhood are...
And this is where we landed first.
The student said "I recommend the Number one park"
So here we are but...
Well... Yeah
We made a tunnel in the sand box
Really?!
Have a look at it
Is it okay to check it out?
It's not even a recommendation!
It's just something you did yourself!
This is surly number 2 on the list
We need to get an autograph
It will crumble in the rain
- Isn't this wonderful!
If you put some water in it, you can see it's connected!
You can't imagine it at first glance
You sure are a young looking mother!
I'm the grandmother!
Okay here we go watch
Wow it really is
Hold on a sec... This is surly number 1
NO!
And as expected, it was just a normal park
But what with the residents recommend?
Pretty much everyone just says nothing
It's nothing but hesitations when answering!
This tunnel is worthy!
Number 3 at least
Nagata Drive in-san...
If you follow that road back there
It's around there
- Drinve in?
There is plenty of raw delicacies
You might enjoy it
What's the Drive-in? Like a service lay by?
Just a restaurant
It gets pretty busy in the evenings though
Shall we go there and check out a bite to eat?
- Let's do that
We will check it out
But really, can we keep this tunnel on the list?
The 5 of them make way toward the recommended Nagata Drive-in
What`s behind that there?
The name of the restaurant was Drive-in she said
Why would you have a actual Drive-in there?
Oh that's what it means!
I asked if it was a service stop, she said no
It's the name of the restaurant!
The name!
What was up with that 5 park after all
I wonder what the rest where like
Out of the 5 parks I like Number one he said
That was Number one...
It was just park play equipment
I wonder what Number 5 would have been like!
It's far huh
I thought we would have been there by now
Having walked this much
But... I still can't see it
- Not at all
Further?
The sun is setting earlier and earlier
How long are we gonna be round here
Why?
Because there's nothing here
Ah, now you gone and said it
But really, everyone is...
Like...
Damn this is narrow!
It sure is
We can only go single file
Even after 10 minutes they have still not arrived
But then!
WTF!!
I'm sorry!
I was about to fall
I thought there was a monster appearance, I'm sorry to startle you
It took me by surprise
Look, it says "Drive-in"
They finally arrived at the Nagata Drive-in!
It's open
Is there seats? -I wonder if it's gonna be busy
It's crowded!
There's biker's here too
A Harley!
She said it was busy
After getting the okay to film, they head inside!
That took my by surprise
Aren't you glad we walked, it gave it more merit
Welcome!
Thank you for coming!
What is the recommended dish here?
I recommend the sashimi
We have a supplier that gets them direct
from the sea and brings them straight here
Your on the borderline of crime then
No, they have a legitimate supply route!
How about Horse mackerel...
Have you had the fried mackerel?
It's delicious
Yeah? Let's order one piece then
- One?!
- One he said
In the end they order the Sashimi and Aji fry
No doubt about it...
That pole is a real good one huh
What's it here for?
Shall we ask?
It's nothing to do with the food
Thre could be something to it
There won't be.
We have a question not related to the menu
What's this pole about?
There used to be wooden slats in here
She's laughing while explaining!
That's why there is a groove in it then!
I see!
- That's why there is 2!
It was connected lengthways across here
Stop calling her out for every other thing
Sorry to bother you
If you look here...
What?!
There are 3 phone jacks
Shall we ask about it?
- She was just here!
Why wait till she's gone to ask!
But there's 3...
This will definitely be the last
I'm sorry but...
I see you have 3 phone jacks on the wall here...
That was...
There used to be payphones there before
3 of them?
Just one...
But there was 3 just in case, like...
So that's how it was
I'm sorry but...
What's this about
Give it a rest already!!
It's like that for a reason!!
So it doesn't drip I guess
I'm sorry for the bother
She seems a bit flustered and busy...
Because you keep calling her over and over!
I want to get this shoot finished up before it gets dark...
There might be something good after dark though
Like an amazing illumination
There isn't anything like that.
Something of a public viewing spot
In that park
A celebrity from round these parts
Shall we enquire?
Are you local to the are?
We're from Mobara (The next town)
That place is pretty big
Yuko Ogura is a former early 2000 idol from that town that had some kind of imaginary star named the Korin Star http://ja.uncyclopedia.info/wiki/こりん星
Mobara has that star planet Yukorin
There is a planet there?!
There is a star in the earth?!
And so..
Sorry to have kept you waiting
This looks amazing
Assorted Sashimi
Big AjiFry
Delicious!
This tuna is great!
It's soft as anything
You should all try it
Next is the famous AjiFry
This is seriously good!
Great!
Look at this
Tuna like this?!
Can I ask something?
How many years has this been here?
He is second generation
He's 3rd
And we're siblings
She's a big fan of yours!!
Do you want to eat with us?
And so 3rd on the list is Nagata Drive-in
In business for 60 years, this place gets the official recommendation!
Is it really okay to give this number 3?
This can be first, the tunnel 2nd...
And the archaeologist 3rd.
He's not an archaeologist
He's not an archaeologist!
I'll go and ask some of the other customers
They ask the guest for their number 2 recommendation
It's called Arere-chan house, you can roast your own stuff there
In Nagata?
- Yes
They have home made soft cream and hand toasted senbei also
I highly recommend it
And so they make their way to Arare-chan's house by car
(Staff) Please wear your seat belts properly
No belt is best right?
- It's better to wear it
We can't not wear it?
You have to wear it
It's okay to smoke right?
You can't smoke here
It's better not to wear a seat belt right?
- No, you have to wear it
It's okay to just go home like this right?
I don't know about that
I'm glad it was delicious
Endo, didn't you drink a beer?
I did not drink!!
Didn't you have a Mizore Sake? (A partially frozen sake slushie)
I didn't have a drink
I definitely won't tell anyone
Well you know for sure in these recent times there has been drinks
You know that thing, well we didn't have it today but...
When someone says "Please shake my hand"
I do it but...
Do you get people that squeeze it as hard as possible?
It's just because you're ripped now Matsumoto-san
Nah! It's nothing like I start arguing with them or anything but...
You'd be mistaken for them doing it out of spite
Like what, what you starting?
I don't think it's on purpose to that extent
Not squeezing the life out of me but, still hard gripping
You can feel the rage
Like I'm unable to move for a moment
WTF?!
There are those times indeed
No, not there are those times
He got caught out
Conversely, I have many of the opposite
Okay enough's enough~!
It's pretty much all guys, gripping like fuck
Oh! Yamasaki-san!
- Hello
Is it okay if I shake your hand?
I'm such a huge fan!
They do it that much!?
Matsumoto-san please stop that!
It's like the Hulk
Wouldn't it piss you off!?
I didn't like that just then
You can't help but forgive them because they're your fans like...
"I'm a huge fan! I've seen all your shows!"
"I got all the DVD's too!"
Well, I'm grateful for that of course...
Then they shake your hand as hard as possible!
I just don't fucking get it!?
I thought it would be me that gets got
I can feel the overwhelming pressure here
Next week! The conclusion of Nagata station Best 3!
The 5 of them forget the shoot and become regular tourists
But will they be able to draw a close on the best 3!?