8th Ever - Gaki No Tsukai Chiki Chiki
"Are their hearts connected?"
No Smartphones Meetup!
So loud
It's been 2 years
2 years?
He was really loud wasn't he?
I wasn't being loud
The 8th installment of a project designed to test their bonds!
The Rule: They head to a location using the theme card given to them
The challenge ends if  they all meet up
Looking back at past installements, there is one troublemaker who holds them up
What do you mean? That's-
Tanaka always hold us up
Tanaka, we're really counting on you
You guys-
You always head straight to Komazawa Park don't you?
I just went there for the parking lot one
He spends so much time there it's like his neighbourhood
You get me right?
Like maybe he can find a cast away dog to bring home
Time for the first theme
"An Oasis in the City"
What's that?!
This is difficult
What is that?
You don't want us to meet up at all do you?
Honestly!
What cruel bullies!
Such a vague concept
Well, let's say farewell for this first one
Yes, I think we won't meet up
But you know, it's OK if none of us meet
No it isn't!
subbed by senor_wristband
If you'd like to support my subs, consider donating @ ko-fi.com/buresurettosan
Any support is appreciated :)
There's no way I would go there!
I've gone and done it!
13:05 - They depart from NTV
It's been 2 years?
What does this theme even mean?
I have no clue where to start picking a place
Well I thought of that sauna, the one I always go to
But who the hell would head there. To my Sauna
I think Yama-chan, and Matsumoto,
I've heard there's this sauna they both went to
There was one
But I don't know what sauna that is
If you asked me to go to a sauna I mean
Hamada and Hosei are thinking along the same lines,
In this project, it's important to consider what other's might be thinking
TEXT I'll get really flamed if I end up on the highway,
TEXT I'm going to avoid the highway as much as possible
And then the troublemaker Tanaka, who wants to rid himself of that name today
You can't think of anywhere?
Nothing comes to mind
It seems that once again Tanaka will draw the ire of the other members
It's not exactly an oasis, but,
It was a place you looked forward to,
In the past, you know,
When I was really into golf,
We just, hung out, chilled afterwards
Got something to drink, smoked our cigarettes,
And just chilled out
Can you tell us the destination please?
My bad, my bad
"How many balls do you think we hit?"
We just hung out there afterwards
If I think along those lines, it's JIngu Gaien's driving range
Should we go there?
It seems one man has confidence in his choice
Keeping another person's thinking in mind will help meet them faster
Let's do this
What sort of place do you have in mind?
I can say this,
It's gotta be Hibiya Park right?
Oh, you're thinking along those lines?
Yeah. It's an oasis for salarymen to relax in the afternoon
And consdering the TV show angle,
My real answer is Gotanda though
TN: Matsumoto might be referring to Gotanda's red light district
Oasis can mean "a place for workers to unwind"
That's the intended meaning
There were 2 other men who thought the same as Matsumoto
One of them, is Endo
The first one,
Hibiya Park
Salaraymen really do think of that place as an oasis
And the other one,
In Daikanyama,
The TSUTAYA, that image
Let's go to [!@$!@$!@]
Which location did Endo choose?
And there was another man struggling to pick a place
You can't think of any place?
I do have some ideas in mind
An idea ...
For example?
For example, Hibiya Park
For working salarymen,
Them eating there lunches in the afternoon,
That's one idea I had,
That's the first one I thought of
Any others?
As for others,
There's gotta be water I think,
When you think of an oasis
Shinobazu Pond
Yes, in Ueno
In Ueno
The migratory birds too,
They think of that place as an oasis, and they rest there
Thinking in that sense,
Shinobazu Pond
Your second choice?
My second choice
Which one should we go to?
Mr. Driver, can we head to [!$@!@] please?
What will Tanka's answer be?
Right away, there's a chance 3 people will meet up
Healing places ... like temples, or fun places?
The first one I thought of, SensÅ-ji temple, in Asakusa
And in Yoyogi, Meiji Shrine,
Ueno Zoo,
Shinjiku Lumine Theatre
And also that sauna in Shimbashi I keep brining up
But there's no way they'd go there...
Let's try Panda-chan!
Panda-chan?
Isn't Ueno Zoo an oasis?
I think someone will show up
If Tanaka is heading for Shinobazu Pond,
There's a chance they can meet!
There's a good chance 4 people could meet someone at the first theme!
What will happen?
"Are their hearts connected?" No Smartphones Meetup!
With the first hint, there's a good chance 4 people will meet someone!
Things like "Oasis", stuff that is...
Sensual, something that heals the soul,
Those guys don't do that
They're the type to have a lot of plaque in their teeth
Well we're almost there
7 minutes after leaving NTV, Matsumoto arrives at his City Oasis
Colder than I thought
Hibiya Park, an oasis for salarymen
There's no way nobody will come
If that happens then we're just done
Expectations remain ... Tanaka and Endo said Hibiya Park as well. They are yet to arrive.
It depends on what they think an oasis is
Almost there
Did Endo arrive at Hibiya Park? Or at Daikanyama's TSUTAYA?
Thank you very much
Woah the air is totally different at this oasis
Ahhh, feels nice
Endo chose Daikanyama's TSUTAYA...
It's sort of like seeing Diamond Head in Hawaii. "Woow I feel refreshed!"
That feeling is exactly the same
"Aloha Table"
Wow it even says "Aloha Table"!
It says "Waikiki Aloha Table"
That's exactly what I'm talking about!
And the other one who said Hibiya Park, Tanaka arrives
We'll arrive soon
Yeah already, we're here we're here
We're here
Is he arriving at Hibiya Park? Or Shinobazu Pond?
Alright we're here
Ueno Zoo, very nice
What do you think, it's nice isn't it?
Even these buildings, it feels like an oasis in the city
Unfortunately, they did not meet up
Even if nobody comes here,
They definitely won't complain that I chose this place
In the end, nobody came to Hibiya Park
I told you right? They're idiots
I have to go to the hospital today
Meanwhile, Hosei gets out at Ueno Park
Aiming for Tanaka!
Cocorico's Tanaka Masayoshi
See, look. It's an oasis!
This is an oasis in the city
C'mon come here
He targeted Tanaka alright,
But even within the same park, Hosei is at the zoo, and Tanaka is at the pond
Since they're in different spots, there's no chance they'll meet
I have no expectations really
And of course, nobody came to Hamada
Meeting is really difficult
With that, time's up!
Of course right? They won't come here
There's no way. I bet nobody met up for sure.
They call to report their locations
Matsumoto-san, whereabouts are you?
Seriously,
"An Oasis in the City", right?
It's gotta be Hibiya Park then!
What do you mean "Uwaaahh!"
Seriously?~
I've gone and done it!
It's gotta be here, there's a fountain and everything
I've really done it now...
Hold on, where's Hamada?
I'm at Meiji Jingu's driving range
Man cut it out!
That's not an oasis
Just cut it out. There's no way I'd go there!
Man I can't rely on you
Endo, where are you?
I'm in front of the TSUTAYA in Daikanyama
What the hell?
What the hell?!
This place is super Oasis!
He's touched a nerve I think
Yama-chan where are you?
It's gotta be a park
Yeah, Hibiya Park
It's gotta be Ueno Park!
Oh man you're at Ueno Park?
There's a lot of people who feel it isn't an oasis!
Alright, the troublemaker Tanaka
I'm at Shinobazu Pond in Ueno
Enough of that
Why are you at Shinobazu Pond?!
I can understand choosing Shinobazu Pond at least
Just let me say this; Which of you thought of Hibiya Park
Endo here
I did
And you Hamada-san?
I did, I did
You lying idiot!
There's no way
Absolutley not
I'll just tell you, I have to go the hospital today. I have an appointment
So get this over with
Let's do this!
It was Hibiya Park after all
If we all went there we could have had 4 people, excluding Hamada
They all went to parks huh
I did say Hibiya Park. But I thought the theme was more general than that
So I'm still feeling good about this
50 minutes since the start, and nobody has met up
Starting fresh with the next theme
"A large overhead pedestrian crossing"
This is very general
In Namikibashi, from Daikanyama to, I think it was Ebisu,
The one in Namikibashi is pretty big
Take me there. Take me to that place in Shibuya
That one,
Since Hamada-san is at Meiji Jingu, he'll head there right away
It's gotta be that one right?
In Shibuya, that one is pretty remarkable
There's one in Shinjiku also...
Either one
It really is either one
Already, three people have said Shibuya. A good chance of a meetup!
It doesn't have to be a single crossing right?
Right? Then it has to be that one
Is there one?
There is!
Do I have to say it?
It has 4 crossings!
It's huge!
It's not just 1 crossing, there's 4 of them
What do we do here, it's gotta be that one!
Which crossing is it that Hamada has such confidence ?in
What driving range was Hamada talking about? I didn't ask that
It was Meiji Jingu I think
Oh yes, Jingu
Maybe he'll go to Shinjiku ... He probably won't think of that one
It's definitely the one in Shibuya
Is the crossing Hamada heading to in Shibuya? Or ...
There's two of them in Ueno
Ah I see
But still there's a chance they could turn around and go to Shibuya,
I think there is a chance it's Shibuya, but ...
There's 4 crossings!
If he's not going to Shibuya, then where?
Hold on, considering the direction...
Shibuya, or Roppongi,
In Roppongi, in Arc Hills, I used that pretty often
Either Shibuya, or Arc Hills,
Excuse me driver, can we head to [!@#!@$!]?
Where did Tanaka choose?
If it's Shibuya, there's a chance 4 people will meet!
However,
However, If I see a bigger crossing on the way there,
Let me choose that one
And then...
That one is pretty big isn't it?
Hmm?
Hold on ... Sorry, can I change mine?
This one is pretty big
That is huge
Now that I've seen this,
After seeing that one, I'm feeling unsure,
With that, the slim chances of meeting up are gone
Thank you very much
He changed his choice on the way there ... This is what makes him a troublemaker
It's bigger than the one I thought of. There's no way they can complain about this
2, 3
There's more for sure, 3
4,
5, 6, there's gotta be more on the other side,
This is a lot
This is a lot, I didn't know about this one
Meanwhile, Matsumoto arrives at his Shibuya crossing
This is what I'm talking about
Doesn't that look impressive?
Right away, he waits at the meeting location
He waits for the other 2 who said Shibuya
And then!
Good work!
TN: Matsumoto can't see the orange subtitles so he doesn't know Endo is speaking
Who is it? Who is it?
Yes yes yes yes yes!
Right? Right?
Is that Endo?
Good work!
Oh it's Endo!
Endo where did you come here from?
Oh yeah Daikanyama, that's why it took so long
It's definitely here right?
It's gotta be here
I think this is the biggest in Japan
It's the biggest in Japan
It's gotta be the biggest in Japan
They're messed in the head if they don't come here
They're idiots if they don't come here
They really are idiots
However I haven't forgotten you went to Daikanyama
Meanwhile, Hamada also arrives at the crossing
Where is this huge crossing he has confidence in?
Look!
There's 4 of them!
It's so big, look at it!
It is the Tengenji Pedestrian Bridge in Shibuya
They're idiots if they don't come here
Idiots
No, just look at it. Ryousuke (Camera-man) film it properly
There's 4 of 'em!
Exactly that moment, Hosei arrived ...
He's heading towards Tengenji where Hamada is!
Ah, that one is pretty big
Is that the Tengenji crossing?
This one is huge too
There might even be someone here
But I never thought of Tengenji though
Hosei's destination is not Tengenji...
However, at this place ...
Ah, there!
Where?
Hamada-san
Oh shit he's there! Hamada-san's there!
Oh no!
Ah! Hamada-san!
Huh, is that Yama-chan. Wait, he's not stopping at all!
He's kidding right?
What do I do? I can't go back there can I?
Yes that's right
Damn Hamada-san was there!
A near miss for Hosei!
Then where is he heading?
Hosei passed right in front of Hamada's eyes. Where exactly is he heading?
This one here, this one
It's big right? That's a big pedestrian bridge.
Shibuyabashi
Since Ebisu is right there, we would meet up here a lot
This bridge is pretty big right? This place here,
I thought someone else would be here
Hosei is smack dab in the middle of Hamada and Matsumoto,
They've just missed each other by 2km
And with that ...
No way!
Really?
They call to report their locations
Tanaka where are you?
I'm at the bridge in front of Ueno Station
In front of Ueno Station?
Man, you think about yourself too much
No listen, it's so big I can't see all of it!
Shut up!
No no no, that's not the point,
But that is the point. Where are you guys then?
Matsumoto, and Endo have met up!
You met up with Endo?
Besides Shibuya Police station, there's a massive overhead crossing
There it is, someone met with Matsumoto
You guys get it right?
Yama-chan and I had a near miss
I apologise
I'm at Tengenji right now
It's just a normal crossing
There's 4 bridges here, 4!
How many do you think we have?!
Yamasaki where are you?
I'm in Ebisu,
The overhead crossing for Shibuya-bashi
If you're already in Shibuya then why didn't you keep going?!
There's a bigger one just ahead of you!
Well this is one is really convenient
Convenient?
Next week!
No Smartphones Meetup Finale!
Tanaka has an epic fail!
I've gone and done it
And one man tries to break the rules!
Maybe I'll go home
Don't miss it!
C'mon, let's get off,
I don't wanna