j-addicts.blogspot.com
Facebook: J-addicts
Next a "must" see date with Matsuko Deluxe
Hey someone!!
Don't go before us!!
Really... Who's in front of us?
Someones's trying to go in front!!
Really?
I'm...
Oh... my!!
Thank you for your hard work!!
Hurry it up!!
Hurry up, hurry it up!!
Just leave it.
After breakdown they're getting ready to go to Sky Tree
Matsumoto returns to change clothes.
Yamazaki!!
Thanks for your hard work!
It's hot!!
I'm exhausted!!
Thanks for your hard work!
I worked so hard...
Why am I being punished?
Then what have I...
Done!!
What are you expecting from me!!
Isn't that right??
What am I to reflect upon?
What am I to do from now.
You done your best!!
I did my best!!
To be punished!!
You did your best!!
You had 5 out 6, but didn't get punishment!!
What do I reflect upon?
15 minutes later
Matsumoto is still not content.
He had changed clothes.
He headed to Matsuko in dressing room.
Plase come in.
Seriously you want me to go?
What? I guess...
I'm not sure what to expect.
Regarding the "Karuta" cards...
Wow, you have a nice body!!
Yeah!!
I'm no comparison to your body.
You have an awesome body!!
Not at all. let's get going!!
What!!
It's so hot!!
You're so dressed!!
Wow. My outlook on you has changed!!
What are you saying!!
Oh.. my!!
I'm looking at you sexually!!
Let me look at you!!
Shut up, quiet.
Quite already!!
Have a good time... have a good one!!
Strange, strange!!
You're going like that?
You look so good!!
I'm being touched all over!!
I'm feeling him out sexually!!
A date... Date!!
I won 6 cards, but.
I don't understand the batsu game!!
How many did you win?
I won only one!
Have a nice time... Have fun!!
It's hot, it's hot!!
It's really hot!!
Wow, I'm looking at you differently!!
What are you saying!
Wonderful!!
You look so good!!
So hot!!
Where is our ride?
This one!
You scared me!!
I thought it was that one!!
This one is the camera crew!
Shall we go with that one??
No, no, no!!
We can't??
A driving date to Sky Tree with Matsumoto
Matsumoto drove for 30 minutes, with only Matsuko
I'm getting in?
Who else is there??
Does this go all the way back?
Matsumoto who is the escort will be driving.
Matsuko will be next to him.
I want to be in comfort.
You gotta get comfortable.
Is this for real??
I have to use my imagination.
You must not like it, eh?
You must not want to be here?
You don't like it right, right?
Not that I don't like it, but...
Why me!!
I too was feeling uneasy, but
after seeing your body, I was confident!!
What the...!
Will this go around me?
It'll work!!
Where is the fastener??
Let's see.
Oh, no, no, no!
It's good!!
It's all good, good!!
You are so kind!!
So kind!!
I want to get there already!!
I felt that you wanted to get this over too!!
Not that I don't want to, but...
They are telling us to drive on.
Matsumoto is 49 years old.
Matsuko is 40 years old.
The passion begins between them.
The bystanders are clapping/cheering at us!
We are a couple!!
Who you waiting for??
I'm unavailable now!
Who are you waiting for??
Are we really going to Sky Tree together??
Yes we are.
What the...
What are we going to do  there??
Don't go there. You make me feel sad!!
It's not that!!
Am I that bad?
I don't mean it in that respect, but I'm dense.
You can't be dense!!
Really. I'm okay now.
Really??
I'm confident and alright.
I was worried at first, what to talk to you about.
I'm okay with silence too.
Being together in silence is awesome!!
Yes it is.
It's like being married!!
I'm fine with it.
Wow. Why is that??!
Why I don't know. It's beyond me!
I'm amazed!!
Is it your body!!
What is it?
Is it your solid body!!
It's hot!!
Frankly. I don't like being just one on one!!
In response. Me too!!
That's why for over 10 years.
What's why I haven't had a dedicated person in my life.
We don't know what's gonna turn out from this!
Yeah... I don't mean it as Okay!
What do you think of me?
Wow, this is my first time here!
First, first time here.
Are we going up to the top?
What the heck is this?
It's no joke!
What's with this!
Why.
It's such a hot night.
It's awesome yeah!!
Finally they arrive at Matsuko's destination, Tokyo Sky Tree.
They ride the elevator to 350 meters
The two of them get into the elevator.
They get onto the elevator to the "observatory".
dec to 350 meters.
How long was our drive from the studio?
About 35 minutes...
It was 35 minutes.
As you pinch my nipples, the noise is distracting.
I feel like we are going to heaven.
Wow, 600 Km... Not really 600 Km.
Wow, we're going really fast!
We're here already?
We're here?
This is the "observatory" level.
In about 50 seconds, they're here on the "observatory" deck.
Please excuse me.
No please excuse me.
It's awesome, it's really awesome!!
Matsuko, your nipples keep poking me.
Yes, I've been trying to aim them at you.
Matsuko, your body temperature seem a bit high!
I wonder why, but it's awesome!
What we're going to do?
The two of them will take a commemorative photo with "Sorakara-chan"
We will take a photo when Sorakara gives the go!
One a one and two... We'll take your photo!
From the Sky, We'll take a shot!
Hey, you weren't smiling!
I was smiling.
Really?
I was really smiling!
What's the problem?
Smiles!
Hey you!
A week later.
Last week you must've been tired.
Ah, kind of because of work!
Yeah really!
Really, Matsuko's high calorie.
When we were taking a smoke break outside.
There was the Jeep in the garage?
Yeah, I saw it too.
Did you go with that?
The Jeep was for something else, right?
For the camera crew
The Jeep was for the camera crew.
Oh, for the camera crew.
The convertible one!
After the event, the Jeep would've been better.
Why is that?
The van was "enclosed" and Matsuko
kept on reaching for my Crotch!
Regardless that I was driving!
She was feeling my "crotch", but
the camera wasn't filming there!
And it wasn't a few times!!
She was touching my Sky Tree!!
The camera was rolling.
I'm not sure.
She must've been kidding.
I'm not too sure.
She wouldn't touch me when the camera wasn't rolling.
To an extent, I think she was serious.
Does it mean it was part of the script?
Was Matsuko touching you knowingly?
Matsuko knows the camera wasn't filming below my waist!
If there was a camera here, she would've known.
From here, below the camera wasn't filming.
The camera was only taking your facial reaction.
She kept on touching my Sky Tree constantly!
I was scared!!
I thought they were only going to film
us going to Sky Tree, and end the filming.
They actually made us go to Sky Tree together.
Oh, my!!
Did you go up to the top?
Yes to the top.
That was great!
What do you mean to the top?
You wen't up?
My psychological part...
Like a "challenger".
About the Sky Tree.
We couldn't go all the way up.
Very top is 360 meters.
But you did go up!
The view I anticipated from Sky Tree, was with Matsuko?
But it was alright!
I was afraid!
With the anxiety, right?
I want to see the replay of Endo's inability
of the Karuta card game.
I would really like to see it too.
Why was your reaction so slow!
I'm pretty good at it, but...
I really thought you were all so fast!!
You were only able to get the cards closer to you.
You are right!
You weren't motivated.
I was trying my best!
I had second thoughts about you.
Endo wants to go to Sky Tree with Matsuko?
Intentionally!
That's not true!
You are gay?
You were gay?
No, no, not true!
It's not possible, but...
You didn't get much of the Karuta cards?
It was fishy.
Yeah fishy!
We all know!
Not true, maybe with Hamada-san...
When it's read, do you look for 7-8 cards around you?
You see it and you grab it?
Yeah, I look near!
That's were I'm different, I look everywhere.
I look at all the Karuta cards.
Why is that!!
No sub