Edited by Mrs. ShibataBread
@tofupizza on Twitter
Translation by Shibatabread
www.shibatabread.com
Gaki No Tsukai presents
"I've Always Wanted to Try This - Absolutely Tasty Series"
Bibimbap Tournament!!
It's been a year since our last challenge
Downtown
Hitoshi Matsumoto
Masatoshi Hamada
We had an amazing battle...
Let's review our scores
Absolutely Tasty - Nukazuke
Aired on
Boiled egg
Cream puff
Dumpling
Endo
Frisk
Hamada
Matsumoto
Nata de coco
Tanaka
Yamasaki
What the hell's wrong with my score...?
That looks right
Your score was a "turd"
That's not right!
It means you scored below zero
Cocorico
Naoki Tanaka
Shozo Endo
Unprecedented
That's a terrible feat
You scored a turd on television
But that's old news!
Hosei Yamasaki
Now we're back with an even better challenge!
TODAY WE'RE COOKING OUR OWN BIBIMBAP!!!!!!
Each member will make their own Bibimbap
and the others will give it a score
Why so loud?
Why all of a sudden?
Something's wrong with your volume
You spat right in my eye
Downtown Presents:
Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende!!
Absolutely Tasty - Bibimbap Challenge
Naoki Tanaka's Turn
Tanaka will be the first to face the Bibimbap Challenge!!
Time for my two dishes
And here's my first dish!!
Here it is
Ingredients
Seasoned Dried Seaweed + Seaweed Tea
I have Miyako Konbu (seasoned dried seaweed)
and seaweed tea
These are readily available at any convenience store
But they have a dramatic effect on Bibimbap!!
Basically, it's all seaweed...
but in a variety of different forms...
Tanaka starts cooking
Base
Ingredients
Rice, Namul + Egg
by adding *Namul and egg over rice inside a heated stone pot
*Namul = general term for a vegetable dish with Korean seasonings
I could eat it the way it is right now...
You're not holding back
I'm not gonna waste any
Your arm makes me lose my appetite
Are you clean?
Of course, I washed my hands
But you meant my hairy arm?
And then!
I'm adding the seaweed tea powder
You're going for it!
And that's it!!
It's ready!!
Bake for 10 minutes
Serious?
Now we bake it
Right, now we just wait for it to cook
Tanaka's second dish is
Here it is!!
Corn Flakes + Salad + Banana + Yogurt
Ingredients
No good
Please, hear me out
Too risky...
It's Corn Flakes, salad, banana, and yogurt
Like breakfast...
Right!!
It'll be a hit among office workers
But bananas...
Who would cook with a stone pot in the morning?!
Right!
Precisely!
That's precisely why!
No sane person would drag out a stone pot in the morning!
Why not eat the ingredients separately?
Why not eat them as they are?!
Like a normal person
Seriously though, we don't know how good this will turn out
Base
Ingredients
Rice, Namul + No egg
I have high expectations for this dish
Here's the sliced bananas!!
I don't want hot, burned bananas...
I'll call this, "Start the Morning Right Bibimbap"
I would turn violent if I caught my wife fixing this in the morning
I'd be like, "In the morning? WTF?"
Cook for 10 minutes
Please, save your judgment for later
Here's Tanaka's first dish, Konbu Bibimbap
Konbu Bibimbap
Tanaka's Idea
It doesn't look too bad
Not bad at all
And it smells pretty good
How's it gonna taste?
Very promising
Itadakimasu!
I don't mind digging right into this dish...
Delicious!!
This is really good!
I agree
The seasoned dried seaweed adds a nice flavor
This is delicious
What's that?
Just in case
you wanted to enjoy *Ochazuke
Ochazuke = rice with seasonings in hot water or tea
you can add some hot water
and enjoy the dish that way
How about it, Hamada-san?
What?
How about some tea?
Hot water
Hot water?
You get to enjoy the tea flavor if you add water
Nobody else?
Because none of us are into hot water like you are
I'm serious, he loves hot water
Is that so?
I had no idea
You really like hot water?
I'd say it's better without it
It was better witout the hot water?
It's not as good as real Ochazuke?
Why not try it then...
I have to also point out
that the flavor gets a little too spicy
Yes, it gets too overpowering
I agree
So maybe it's better to add hot water to take the edge off
I could get into this
Hot Pepper Paste
This is so good
Really?
Why the hell are you acting like a food snob?
This paste makes all the difference
Now YOU are the No.1 hot water fan
Tanaka, you did good with this
This is very good
How would you score this?
I give it 6 points
Agreed!
OK then
Wait a sec, please
Everyone agreed this was a delicious dish
6 points is harsh
How about 8 points?
You scored 6 points
That's it
It's final
Matsumoto Computer Calculates 6 Points
Konbu Bibimbap
Despite the high praise, it only received 6 points
Banana
Breakfast Bibimbap
Corn Flakes
Salad
Tanaka's Idea
Yogurt
His second idea is geared towards women
How is it?
I can smell it
I can smell the cooked banana
I can definitely smell banana
Right
Why don't I mash this up a little?
It stinks
Stinky
Serious stench
Please wait until you've tried it
Man, I don't even want to try it
I can tell by its foul stench
Yes, it really does stink
This could attract some serious city flies
This is...
Seriously, no flies could miss this stench
Do I eat the bananas?
Please, go ahead and try it
Banana is the main ingredient
No doubt this is full of healthy ingredients
I don't deserve this...
Why am I being punished?
Seriously, this has the worst texture
The worst texture
What the hell is this?
There's nothing good about this
This is bad
How should we score it?
Here's what he scored!!
I give it 6 points
It's broken!
That's way too high!
The computer is broken
That's too high
I'm kidding, of course
I'm just messing around
Breakfast Bibimbap
His risky choice backfires and he gets one point
Absolutely Tasty - Bibimbap Challenge
Masatoshi Hamada's Attempt
Hamada, whose scores were awful last time, is up next
You'll like the looks of this
You mean the ingredients?
Here they are!
Ingredients
Monjyayaki batter + Pollack Roe + Crispy Noodles
*Monjyayaki = type of Japanese pan-fried batter with various ingredients
What?!
This is almost cheating!
How come?
How can this not be good?!!
Didn't I say you'd like the looks of this?
You're just throwing the batter in there?
Why not?
Really?
I'm curious how it'll turn out
Base
Ingredients
Rice, Namul + Egg
Here's the crispy noodles
You're not cutting that?
You put the fish eggs over an egg
Once everything cooks, it'll be an amazing dish
And what do we have here?
Here it is!
Ingredient
Soy bean Flour *No sugar
Soy bean flour
Soy bean flour?
It's full of nutrients
Athletes can't be fit
by ignoring rich nutrients from beans
That's right, beans are good for you
Base
Ingredients
Rice, Namul + Egg
I guess you just pour it in
That's a lot of flour
That's a lot!
Seriously, stop messing around
This is it, this is all
That's a lot!
Hamada's Idea
Monjyayaki Bibimbap
How does Hamada's Soybean Flour Bibimpbap taste?
You can't go wrong with this
I have a good feeling....
It smells awesome
So good
We all have spatulas
I've got one
I have one too
Eat it with a spatula?
I see, it's like eating Monjyayaki
Why not, right?
Like Monjyayaki
Like this
Give me some fish eggs too
Of course, you get some
Don't be shy...dig in
Good
That's good
I told you this would be good!
How can it not be good?
This is really good
Better than I imagined
This is so delicious
This turned out good, huh?
Delicious!
It would be even better if was more burned
You're right
It could use more crispiness
This is exceptional
Sometimes I wish I had a bowl of rice when I eat Monjyayaki,
I guess I just have to ask for it
So rice with Monjya?
Rice Monjya
Someone should start that idea
This is good, right?
OK then, if you would
give it a score
How about a high score?
Got it
Let's go around
Yamasaki-san, please?
This is better than the previous one, right?
What's your score?
6 points!!
What the...?!!
That's pretty fair
Are you sure?
Get outta there!
We're scoring it right now
I'm so into this dish
I give it 9 points
See?
Why don't you two get a freakin' room?
Endo's been whipped
OK, no personal gossip!
Monjya Bibimbap
A strong score of 7 points compared to the last time!
Hamada's Idea
Soybean Flour Bibimbap
Hamada's second dish is for the health conscious
I'd say you added too much
What are you talking about?
Too much flour
I don't think so
It just needs to be mixed well
It looks like sawdust...
Yeah, it does
Itadakimasu!
So dry...
I wish the flour would go away
The flour blocks the flavors of the other ingredients
A dog would scream in agony if it ate this
with its tail between its legs
This is terrible
Awful
I would say...
This can't be scored
It's not THAT bad
It's just soybean flour
You scored "Pubic Hair"
He's done it
First time
What the hell kind of score is that?
Pretty much the worst
That's the first ever "Pubic Hair"
Soybean Flour Bibimbap
Pubic Hair
Soybean flour bibimbap received the worst - "Pubic Hair"
Absolutely Tasty - Bibimbap Challenge
Shozo Endo's Turn
The third challenger, Endo, has a theme
Here's my summer themed ingredients
Beer + Edamame + Mixed Nuts + Turmeric
Ingredients
We have beer and snacks
As well as turmeric which cures your hangover
Base
Ingredients
Rice, Namul + Egg
First add mixed nuts with the Edamame beans
And beer?
That's right
I don't need that
Please, listen to that sound!
That's really nothing special
Lastly, this turmeric will prevent a hangover
Would I get pulled over for this?
Don't worry, it evaporates
Right, the alcohol will be gone
Why bother then?
Here's Endo's second dish
Here's some more summer-themed ingredients!
Ingredients
Watermelon + Salt
Now he's done it!
Not good
Watermelon!!
Seriously, I'll pass
I guarantee this won't work
But if it's successful,
I bet people will try this at home
It can't get simpler than this
Base
Ingredients
Rice only
I'm only using rice as a base ingredient
Nothing else?!
No, just rice
How come?
I'm willing to take a risk
And this will work!
To finish it off,
I'm using some
salt
I don't think that's enough salt
Beer
Beer + Snack Bibimbap
Edamame
Endo's Idea
Mixed Nuts
Turmeric
The cast is ready to try Endo's beer, snacks, and turmeric dish
That's unappealing
Nothing is too burned...
I lost my appetite
Shall we?
Itadakimasu!
This is a seasonal dish with beer...
What the hell am I smelling?
Is that Turmeric?
This isn't so bad after all
No, oddly enough....
Surprisingly
I'm not a fan
I actually hate this
Endo, how would you score this?
Can I be honest?
Let's be honest
Perhaps, 10 points....
You asked for that
What I meant was perhaps 10 is too high so...
8 points?
How in the hell does this deserve 8 points?!
How about...
5 points??
No way!
Absolutely NO!
I can't go any lower...
No way!
Beer + Snack Bibimbap
Not everyone's favorite, it received 2 points
Endo's Idea
Watermelon Bibimbap
Another summer-themed dish, Watermelon Bibimbap
I see some of it is burned
Endo, why don't you go solo on this?
I really don't want this
It's just mush
Damn it...
Watermelon with salt...
I can have seconds
I doubt it...
How is it?
It's not so bad
Thank you!!
No way, I hate this
It isn't that bad, right?
It's better than expected
It's not that awful
It is edible
Right?
I can only smell trash
It has a reasonable sweetness to it
Right, it's sweet and
And it has a good flavor
I agree
Right?
Shouldn't the combination of flavors equal a perfect 10?!
It's a perfect dish
We all have different taste buds
Watermelon Bibimbap
Unfortunately, not everyone liked it, so it received 4 points
Absolutely Tasty - Bibimbap Challenge
Hosei Yamasaki's Attempt
Next up is Yamasaki who scored a perfect 10 last year
Ingredient
Pudding
What do you think?
Please, can we stay away from sweets?
Because I love kids so much,
I wanted to make a dish for kids
I seriously hate anything sweet
Base
Ingredients
Rice only
Sweets have no place in cooking
All I'm doing is dumping the pudding on rice!
Here it is!
Who cares what it looks like at this point
And that's it!!
What?!
Once it's cooked, I'll have one more thing to add
It's all good
Ingredients
Tapioca + Coconut Milk
Next, Yamasaki chose tapioca, a Chinese dessert
How will he use it?
I'm replacing rice with tapioca!!
What?
Whoo!!
WTF?
So no rice
I see what you're doing
Think of the tapioca as the rice
So you're thinking tapioca can replace rice
It's a replacement
But you're still putting that in?!
*Namul
Base
Ingredients
*Namul = a general term for a vegetable dish with Korean seasoning
Otherwise, it's not Bibimbap
That's something else
So you're serious
Now you're just messing around
I'm adding some of this too
Coconut milk?
You're taking lots of chances
And that's it for me!
Pudding Bibimbap
Yamasaki's Idea
Yamasaki targets kids with Pudding Bibimbap
Look, it's like egg over rice
I'll pass
Looks can be deceiving...
Check this out
What's going on?
What the hell are you doing?
He's just playing now
Please, this is serious business
Cut it out, will you?
You wouldn't let your kids get away with this, would you?
I know I would
Watch me closely
I'm not surprised
It can't be that easy to do
See that?
Now what?
Pour caramel
Then on top of the caramel....
Every kid's favorite - whipped cream
Then my own kids' favorite, a cherry on top
Now it's complete!!
I have to say
It looks OK
Right
I give you that
This isn't even Bibimbap anymore
I won't deny that
Prison food is better than this
I don't deserve this
The only thing I can taste is
caramel...
Yes
There's zero flavor
On rice?
Right, none
It's tastier than I thought
Hell no!
This is utter garbage
Then how many points?
I would score this as
nothing other than
Ass Hair
The better question is
How many ass hairs does this deserve?
So the more ass hair, the better?
I'd say yes
I'd say Ass Hair is bad enough
4 Ass Hairs
What is this, a card game?
Pudding Bibimbap
A nice looking dish, but it received 4 Ass Hairs
4 Ass Hairs
Tapioca Bibimbap
Yamasaki's Idea
Itadakimasu!!
This dish needs a miracle
What's this?
It's tasteless
This is surprisingly bland
It's kind of like when I'm in the dentist's chair
And I'm like, "Doc, what did you just do?"
"Tell me what you just did"
Like when your mouth is numb?
I'd say sweets doesn't go with this
But I think it's better than Ass Hair
Athlete's Foot
That's the worst
Bibimbap has athlete's foot?
You set me up
Tapioca Bibimbap
A great idea that didn't turn out well receives an Athlete's Foot rating
Athlete's Foot
Absolutely Tasty - Bibimbap Challenge
Hitoshi Matsumoto's Turn
Can Matsumoto beat Hamada's 7 point dish?!
Behold!!
Ingredient
Instant Coffee
Instant coffee
I'm telling you this is so good
So good you guys are already drooling all over
Not at all
I'm flabbergasted
No, no drool over here
Flabbergasted
That's us
Zero drool
I can't believe how much you were all drooling over this
You won't be disappointed
Base
Ingredients
Rice, Namul + One Egg
That's too much
I was just thinking the same thing
And what's in Matsumoto's second dish?
Here it is!!
What?
Can you tell what these are?
What are they?
No?
I can't even smell anything
There's no smell
Here's the answer
I see
I'm only using
the toppings from the Cup Noodles
Ingredient
Meat from Cup Noodles
These have got to work well with Bibimbap!!
Talk about a flavor explosion!!
Well, it is meat after all
Of course
This is a great idea, isn't it?
It's a great idea to only use the meat
Base
Ingredients
Rice, Namul + No Egg
That's an impressive amount
All of it?
Why not use it all?
That seems like a lot
Lastly, he adds hot water to tenderize the meat
Seriously, what's with all of your drooling?
Are you....?
Endo, you're crying?!
There's no way I'd cry over this
OK then
It's game time!
Instant Coffee Bibimbap
Matsumoto's Idea
Matsumoto goes for a mature flavor with his Instant Coffee Bibimbap
Open
Amazing
Stinks!!
Stinky!!
That stinks!!
Stinks!
This is terrible!
It doesn't smell that bad!!
It's not coming our way
Come over here!
You've gotta check this out
It's a serious stench
It isn't that bad!
Hamada-san, please
That stinks!!
It smells awful over here
You're right!!
Well, there's a hint of...
It smells like sea snails
It smells like the tip of a sea snail to be more precise
It does stink pretty bad
But how did this happen?
"How did this happen?"
It doesn't smell like coffee either
That smell is overpowering
We eat it as is?
Go ahead and try it
Eat it as is
Well then...
Thank you all for your hard work
Do you do that at home too?
Here we go
Why did I say that anyhow?
I couldn't come up with anything better
I know I was put on the spot but
Itadakimasu!
That's bitter
This is so bitter
That is bitter
It's burned too
Bitter
So bitter
Just awful
Way too bitter
Of course, this is bitter
So I'm adding this to the dish
Adding Cream
Help yourselves to some
Guaranteed awesomeness
C'mon, this is impossible
This isn't right
Nonsense
This deserves the lowest score ever
I honestly hate this thing
It's the worst ever dish in the history of this show
But I predict
the instant coffee in your kitchens will disappear little by little after this
My score is
D#$% Cheese!
Instant Coffee Bibimbap
D!@# Cheese
Instant Coffee Bibimbap got the worst score ever - D!@# Cheese
Cup Noodles Bibimbap
Matsumoto's Idea
He's shooting for the best score with his Cup Noodle Bibimbap dish
Open
Looks delicious!!
Can I say...
this could replace a birthday cake?
No, I'd still want something better than this
Check it out!
You're probably already feeling defeated
I need to try it first
I'll hold my judgement
until we try it
Well then...
Itadakimasu!
Delicious
Good
The meat tenderized very well
Am I right?
Tasty
The meat turned out great
This is really good
Good, good, good
Delicious
They don't mess around with these
What's the score?
I would give it 5 points
I feel you
Seriously...
5 points it is
No way
No way, no, no, no
Tanaka?
4 points!
It's gone down!
Hamada-san!?
2 points
I give it a Pubic Hair
I freakin' quit!
This dish is so awesome!
20 points!!
4 Ass Hairs
Absolutely Tasty - Bibimbap Challenge
Athlete's Foot
Beer + Snacks
Breakfast
Cup Noodle Beef
D!@# Cheese
Hitoshi Matsumoto
Hosei Yamasaki
Instant Coffee
Masatoshi Hamada
Monjya
Naoki Tanaka
Pubic Hair
Pudding
Seasoned
Dried Seaweed
Shozo Endo
Soybean Flour
Tapioca
Watermelon
Matsumoto gets 5 points making Hamada's "Monjya" dish the winner!
My vote goes to Monjya Bibimbap
His Monya is better
What??!!
If you were super hungry, which would you choose?
Monjya
You know what?
You just lost us a *Nissin sponsorship
Nissin manufactures Cup Noodles
They would never sponsor us anyways