1st Time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arrahende
"I'm the One Who Understands you Best!"
"Anyways, I Think You'll Like this Item!!"
So Matsumoto-san.
Well, I can't say I dislike this segment but
I think it'd be better if we replaced Tanaka.
Every time Tanaka!
A special series on Gaki, where the members buy gifts for guests based on their interests!!
This time, who could the guest be!?
This time, I'm actually pretty confident.
This is before I was married, but I did spend some time with him outside of work.
Ah, with today's guest?
Yes
I'm gonna take it this time!!
Downtown-san
You see each other quite often.
Whilst we do see him
it's usually on set.
When we see him on set, he's always basking in the wind.
Let's welcome today's guest in!
There's the wind I was talking about.
Nishikawa Takanori
Even today, this wind is blowing.
Wow!!
He's really got the wind at his feet.
That's so cool!
Have you learnt how to manifest wind?
I have, I flew over.
No one even called me.
Did you just invite yourself onto the show?
Because of that stupid fan, I had to arrive 3 hours early!!
An artist with a huge following, T.M. Revolution Nishikawa Takanori.
The Gaki members will have to present a top and an accessory they think will suit him!!
How would you describe yourself as far as fashion goes?
Like are you very specific about a certain style.
I see what you mean
well, this year I'm 45.
45 really?!
Yes
So...
I thought you were around 11.
It's been a while since we've seen each other
but I was over 20 when we met for the first time.
What's really important to me is a sense of freshness.
Freshness?
I need to dress in an unoffensive way.
What sort of clothes do you wear casually?
It's gotta be futuristic!!
Just one thing
normally we get the guest's sizes given to us.
How come we didn't this time?!
I had to guess what Nishikawa-kun's size was!!
So I just thought of what size Pepper-kun would wear.
Before the show started, the Gaki members went shopping.
Harajuku
In search of a top, Hamada heads to Harajuku.
This is Nishikawa.
I feel really out of place in here.
A leather jacket, hmm...
Staff
What kind of image are you thinking?
Wouldn't something a bit flashier be good?
Something like this?
This?
I wonder if he'd wear something this flashy.
Maybe something unexpected like this would work.
Doesn't this look good?
You'll like this sort of stuff right?
Shibuya
Tanaka is in Shibuya searching for an accessory.
Nishikawa-san, I think a cap would suit his image.
Have you ever seen him wearing one?
Staff
When I think about it...
No!!
I really think a cap has such a big impact as an accessory.
I definitely want one of these.
These look good.
Maybe this one. It's definitely one of these.
My only concern is, is this too cute?
Let's go for it!
Tanaka picks out his cute hat, how will it fare!?
Takeshita Street
Meanwhile, Hōsei visits the bustling Takeshita Street.
Worrying about being recognised, he dons the perfect disguise.
Luckily for me
I worked with Nishikawa-kun only a month ago, so I've got a good idea of what to go for.
With his disguise on, he has no trouble getting to his destination.
Even before going in, I can see a bunch of stuff that's good.
In this narrow store, filled with unique outfits
surely able to find something great, Hōsei is...
Forgetting about time, he tries on items that take his fancy one after another.
Staff
You remember you're searching for casual clothes for Nishikawa-san...
Marunouchi
Endō, searching for an accessory heads to a certain store.
Man, I don't know.
Endō choses a totally unexpected item.
Harajuku
Meanwhile Matsumoto is...
Good afternoon.
I see.
I don't like this.
But he would wear this!!
Which of the 3 colours looks better?
The black is cheaper than the red!!
I wonder why.
NTV wants to lower production costs...
The cheaper the better, even if it's only 1,000 yen!!
Everyone is trying their best to select a great item, how will they do?
Nishikawa-kun will take home his favourite item
and the worst will have to pay themselves.
Just as always.
Yamasaki-san, today have you come as Watanabe Tōru?
First, let's take a look at what tops the Gaki members selected for Nishikawa Takanori.
The ever confident Tanaka is first up, how will he do?
'You really chose this?'
I'm going places no one would ever think, that's how I'll get 1st!!
Of course!
The worst thing is to leave a potential winner behind.
Please take a look at this.
Nishikawa-kun
Don't let any friendships hold back your true feelings.
This is from Shibuya right?
This isn't good.
This sucks.
His face looks a bit...
(£67/$102)
Price conversions are approximate for time of airing.
Look closely
It's double-breasted.
It looks more like his stage clothing.
The double-breasted?
Not at all!!
It isn't even his image.
That's because it isn't!!
It looks like a school uniform.
Double's are really fashionable right now.
To be honest, Nishikawa-san does look pretty cool in it.
It really does suit him, right?
Don't you think this completes the outfit?
The pants, the shoes?
The size is right.
Is this for Shichi-Go-San?
Shichi-Go-San (lit. 7-5-3) is a festival day held on 15th Nov for 3 and 7 year old girls, 5 year old and sometimes 3 year old boys, to celebrate the well-being of young children
Who just said Shichi-Go-San?
It's for Shichi-Go-San right?
Do you have some sort of problem with me?
Subbed by Inepped
This is a free fansub
Please support the official release
Gaki members are presenting items they think will suit our guest.
Hamada is next to present his top to our guest Nishikawa Takanori.
Hamada-san
When it comes to Nishikawa-kun
I've only really seen...
I haven't seen him in his casual clothing very often.
We've gone out to eat a few times...
This is bad...
This is so bad!
This is so so bad!!
(£148/$225)
It's not bad.
It's a crow man.
I also saw one with a tiger pattern but
I didn't think that was the right image.
That's well avoided.
It might not be work great with a shirt, it'll go better with a t-shirt.
You don't understand T.M. at all.
It probably doesn't go with the pants you've got on but...
The colour matches.
No way!
I think this was the way to go.
I feel sorry for T.M.
I saw other things on the shelf, but picked out this.
We can't see the shelves, so who cares.
Next to present his top, Endō.
I'm really...
I'm really sorry.
These two weren't aggressive enough with their picks.
You wear various styles and are super fashionable.
I think you'll like this sort of thing the most.
It's a parka.
I'm totally into this!!
I was looking for something with a tiger or leopard pattern
(£38/$57)
but I saw this, with the tiger's maw right in the middle.
Are you...
Dainoji!?
Ōchi "Dainoji" Yosuke is part of the comedic duo "Dainoji"
and two-time World Air Guitar Champion.
Ōchi and Nishikawa-kun are poles apart!!
Kuroyanagi-sa~n is something I don't think I've ever said.
Likely referencing a skit by Ōchi, in it he keeps yelling to a Kuroyanagi-san
You can see him showing up to recording in this.
The size is way off too!!
It's pointless being a zip-up, if it's open you can't see the tiger.
Problem is, it gets worse when it's zipped up!!
Looks good!
Stop messing around!
Endō, this is awful!!
Really?!
The expression says it all!!
Rather than the tiger, I'm looking at his distraught face!!
Next up Hōsei shows off a surprising top.
Well, last place has already been decided.
I feel nice and relaxed now.
Nishikawa-kun
You mentioned earlier that there was something important to you
Nishikawa-kun, what did you say?
Freshness
and after that comes ROCK.
Yeah
I kept thinking about that ROCK feeling and
found something to complete your look.
As soon as he opened the bag, his face went pale.
This is just awful!!
Hōsei-san, are you serious?!
You guys are just messing around.
(£59/$89)
That looks great!
Takamizawa Toshihiko is a Japanese singer-songwriter
You've become Takamizawa!!
It's fine if you want to tuck it into your pants as well.
It'll even work with jeans.
This much? You expect me to tuck all of this into my jeans!?
To round off the tops' segment, last up is Matsumoto.
Look at that
the lengths don't match up.
Who would wear such a long jacket?
I want to finish this, these guys are just messing around!!
I just want to make them laugh!!
You can't be thinking like that!!
When you think of it, Nishikawa-kun truly has the heart of a musician.
Musician's usually say "I like this kind of thing"
If it were for me, I wouldn't have picked this out.
Oh
You hear that? He just went "Oh".
It's a stage costume!!
Did you hear it? The "Oh"?
Play it again! Play it again! Audio-san!!
Nobody heard it.
This works great with a long sleaved shirt.
(£52/$79)
It may look like a costume but...
You could totally wear this to Yudetaro!!
Yudetaro is a Japanese noodle restaurant chain
Of all the places to pick from.
I'm old so I can't think of anywhere else
Just get some udon or soba!!
Which of these will be Nishikawa's favourite top!?
So, Nishikawa-kun
in first place is...?
Endō
Hamada
Hōsei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
It's...
...this one
No way!!
YES!!
You're joking!!
SHUT UP!!
Nishikawa-san...
Please tell us your reasoning.
A lot of my work's clothes are black and dark colours.
So I like something a little lighter for casual stuff.
Navy blue is a nice middle ground.
The gold buttons really make it though right?
They're actually a point against it.
You're just saying that 'cos yours have got 'em too.
They look completely different!!
In second place is Hamada's top.
And third is Matsumoto's.
In truth, this should have been first.
Nah, it's not first material.
Third, third, third.
Why is this third?
To be honest, I don't usually choose things this plain.
Then
When you opened the bag, why did you go "Oh"?
Eh? This? It was more like that.
So, which of these tops will come in last!?
I still think mine looks good.
Remember how lame the tiger print looks.
Endō
Hōsei
So Nishikawa-kun...
in last place is...?
Endō
Hōsei
This
Of course it is!
This one wasn't even close!!
It makes you angry right?
It really does.
The shop clerk was wearing it.
The clerk was wearing 'this'?
It's true.
Hōsei has to pay for his poor choice!! (£59/$89)
Make sure you pay the horseshoe crab in full.
Nakamura Yoshinobu
Producer
When someone calls you a horseshoe crab, look at the camera!!
Coming up next, finding an accessory to suit Nishikawa Takanori.
First up to take the challenge, Hamada.
I feel like this guy
just picks up the first thing he sees.
That one definitely wasn't.
But this one, to be honest
it was kinda the first thing.
Ah, there it is!!
Well, it's all about thinking 'what would they want?'
If the person you're buying for likes it, what does it matter.
(£149/$227)
I see
The all white works quite well.
Yeah, they'll go with anything.
I think, when you're relaxing
isn't it pretty uncomfortable
to be wearing shoes with such a high lift.
I mean, they're not exactly for relaxing in, they're smart casual.
You can't go to Yudetaro in those!!
Stop using Yudetaro as your standard!!
Next up, the loser from the last round, it's Hōsei.
I really think Nishikawa-kun will...
Just a sec, before I open this.
This is from the same place.
Zipang Group.
This is ROCK styled.
This can be worn with almost anything, anywhere.
Who would want that!!
What's up with you today?
(£24/$36)
Could I just take it off you, I'll put it on you.
What?
What is it?
What is that?
I don't even know what to call it.
The name, it's that...
It's that...
shar
sharp
cover.
You're as sharp as ever!!
Next up, Tanaka presents his cap.
Ah
Eh? A hat?
As soon as he saw it, I heard an "Ah".
(£32/$49)
We heard the same thing from Matsumoto-san.
It's totally different from that one.
This was an 'Ah'.
Snoopy?
I don't think you guys know
that he can be cute as well as cool.
You guys didn't know that, right?
I did.
Would someone who knew, buy something like that?
It's not bad but, I think you should be more aggressive.
Snoopy suits 45 year olds quite well.
Wouldn't it suit us all?
I wear this stuff all the time.
I wear this stuff all the time!!
Not to be annoying or anything, but I wear this stuff all the time!!
Next, what item has Endō selected?
This is maybe something you wouldn't buy yourself but...
I see.
Shoes and hats you'd buy for yourself
This is something you probably wouldn't buy for yourself, but I think will suit Nishikawa-san perfectly.
He's getting the excuses out early.
What is it?
A cane?
It's a stylish stick.
Who's that on top?
(£96/$145)
It's Beethoven.
I'm saved!!
What would you have thought if Nishikawa-kun walked out with that earlier?
All of a sudden, I feel more like Uchida Yūya.
Uchida Yūya, November 17, 1939 – March 17, 2019) was a Japanese singer, record producer, and actor.
This is supposed to be casual stuff!!
What are you supposed to do with this at Yudetaro!!
I can point to what I want!
This and this.
"I Think You'll Like this Item!"
Will Matsumoto present something Nishikawa will like?
I'm also attacking with this one too.
It's tiny.
No pranks.
I can't stand to see the pranks of mid-level comedians!!
I think, Nishikawa-kun needs a necktie.
(£11/$17)
This is...
This is a loop butterfly tie, which is a combination of a bolo and bow tie.
Since it's a bow tie
Even if you're just wearing a T-shirt, you'll look stylish.
Why are you saying all this with a half-smile?
We're you thinking of me...
When I was at the store, I thought it looked great.
Then when you took it out of the bag...
Seeing it up close, under the bright lights...
I thought 'WOW'
There's still Yama-chan and Endō's, so I'm not sure whether this will come in last.
What d'you think?
Loop butterfly tie
It'll be the number one search term once this airs!!
Where are you guys looking?
They're all completely avoiding eye contact.
Which of these will be Nishikawa's favourite item!?
Nishikawa-kun, you've favourite item is...?
Endō
Hamada
Hōsei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Surprisingly, it's these.
Thank you very much.
After all, white is quite easy to match with
Whilst I don't really wear this stuff all that often, I still like these.
This is just wrong.
The staff must be so angry with this.
Why?
This one being the favourite.
The guest himself likes it.
And in second place is Tanaka's cap.
Well, I could guess up 'til here.
Yep, we all knew.
From here on, it's the battle for the real number one!!
Well said! Very wise!!
Third place is actually first place.
All of that stuff is just useless.
Hamada-san, this is for the true first place.
Something's wrong with you.
An accessory that Nishikawa likes. Who will win third place!?
This is crucial!!
Endō
Hōsei
Matsumoto
It's unexpectedly this.
Thank you very much.
The reason?
It would look pretty strange if you weren't in formal clothes
But, in the right setting, I'd like to try this out.
Thank you very much.
I certainly wouldn't rush back if I forgot this somewhere.
Like in a taxi?
If I forgot it in your taxi, I wouldn't bother contacting you.
I wouldn't go looking for it!!
Which of these will come in last place!?
Which of these items does Nishikawa dislike the most!?
You don't seem to like the neck area too much.
T.M.'s just not in that mode at the moment.
If this were tomorrow, there might be a different result.
He's just not thinking about the neck area right now.
So, let's go Nishikawa-kun...
Please take a good look.
In last place is...?
Please take a closer look.
TOO QUICK!!
Nishikawa-kun, too quick!!
It's gotta be that, right?
I think this'd be impossible for anyone to wear!!
When I put it on, it gave me chills!!
Hōsei once again has to pay the price for his failure!! (£24/$36)
I'm sorry that Yama-chan was just joking around.
That's not true.
Please call me again.
Do you want revenge or something?
Maybe, with a burdock root or something.
Something I can hit you with.
I guess that's how you'd feel.
Terrible!!
It was terrible.
That was awful but even worse was the shirt.
I truly hated that!
I truly hated it!
I think you were just playing around.