Subtitles by: /u/CatZombies
QC by: Yum and Kolibry
For the first time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende Chiki Chiki,
making a big reversal from a blunder!
An apology press conference
to raise your popularity~!!
I see.
Ehhh...
A bit of a bothersome idea.
We're doing it. We're doing it so...
Who is going to be fooled by this plan?
Who indeed?
I'm also not really looking forward to this.
Well, regardless of how much an apology
press conference increases your popularity,
we're still doing it.
That's right.
Well, if it's about increasing popularity,
it's no good, not in the slightest.
I see.
If you get in trouble,
you're obligated to do one.
I think it's good to learn
how to do this sort of thing.
If you don't do this sort of thing
often and you play it strangely,
in a few weeks, it'll be true.
"A lie turned true", that sort of thing.
Scary! Scary!!
Scary, isn't it?
Especially Hamada has got something.
No, no, no.
Even now, he's got many at home.
No, no, no. There's nothing.
He's got a bomb, really.
Apology Press Conference Simulation
Apology Press Conference Rules
m 0 0 l -26 0 l -26 13 l 26 13 l 26 0 l 0 0
You don't know what you did
m 0 0 l -26 0 l -26 13 l 26 13 l 26 0 l 0
Once you apologize, the press conference starts
Improvise a response to the reporters' questions
m 0 0 l -26 0 l -26 13 l 26 13 l 26 0 l 0
The rules are this:
Without knowing the circumstances of what you did,
you first apologize.
From there, the apology press conference begins.
Improvise a response to the reporters' questions.
Aim to up your popularity.
Ok, Tanaka let's go.
We're starting with me, got it.
First up to bat is Tanaka.
The details of his uneasy apology are?
Ah, there it is.
Panty Thief
Tanaka's Apology Reason:
m 0 0 l -26 0 l -26 13 l 26 13 l 28.8 0 l 0 0
m 0 0 l -26 0 l -30.3 13 l 26 13 l 26 0 l 0 0
We already know it, right? The theme.
It's because of that, huh.
Oh, it's that.
Well, it fits his gloomy look.
If you said someone got caught doing this,
Tanaka would suddenly come to mind.
Now everyone, Tanaka is first up.
Let the apology press conference begin.
This kind of vibe, huh?
There's a lot more people than I expected.
This is pretty good. As expected.
His face is good!!
His face is good.
That's an "I messed up" face.
At this time,
I caused a lot of trouble and
I am truly and deeply sorry.
Oh, this is good.
Good, isn't it?
This is amazingly realistic.
It's also about how much you bow.
Yeah.
Woah, they're coming.
Woah, what, what are they doing?
Makes your heart race.
Excuse me.
The crime took place in the middle of the night after 2 a.m. but
right before the crime, what on
earth were you doing there?
He still doesn't know, right?
Yes, ummm...
As usual, um...
work ended,
I was going home, um...
but I was doing so, slowly.
To exercise my body a little bit, um...
"I'll go out", I thought. Yeah.
We're told the scene of the crime was
the veranda of a second story apartment.
How did you get up on a second story veranda?
Yes, ummm, well...
This ummm... a little like...
There was this pipe thing. Ummm...
There was something like a pipe.
Once we watch Tanaka, is it okay if we stop?
We put him through it for about an hour and
then "Is it okay if we stop here?"
I put my feet on there and
entered the second floor.
It's said that you stole several pair of women's underwear that were drying on the veranda.
There were underwear drying that were to your liking?
In a nutshell, that's right.
Ummm...
It's better not to say in a nutshell.
Of course, um... well, you can't take it.
I know that but...
As a result, um...
What was that just now?
I became unable to control myself.
No good, you're no good!
The worst!
That comment was the worst!!
Incidentally, was this the first time?
That is, how many times have you done this?
Ah, this is the first time.
This is really the first time.
Previously, I've not done this sort of thing even once. Yeah, yeah.
What were you going to use those underwear for?
This is important.
The truth is, um...
It's important.
My... my own use, so to speak.
For your own use?
They'll take pictures for that.
Do you want to increase your popularity?!!
It's sliding down.
Yeah.
On that note, Tanaka-san, at your house,
we've heard several thousand pairs of
women's underwear have been discovered.
Were they all stolen?
Is it not the first time?
That's right.
Is everything stolen?
No, some of them I've bought.
Bought them?
He bought them.
But several thousand?
That's good.
In that case, do you have any final remarks to everyone?
At this time, um... well...
For my troublesome behavior,
I am truly and deeply sorry.
I've committed a crime.
Hereafter, as for work, um...
I'd like to return.
Not a chance!
At this time,
I am truly and deeply sorry.
Stealing underwear and putting it on, this guy.
Can you do that in the morning?
Good work.
No, that's really...
You're done.
Your popularity is ruined.
You can't make a comeback.
Eh?
That wasn't an apology to the person you stole from.
Ahhh! That's true, isn't it!?
Because there's a victim more or less.
But I stole several thousand pairs.
Who do I apologize to?
Yeah, because you took it.
Well, that's right.
The next challenger is Hamada.
Apology Reason:
Dine and Dashing
m 0 0 l -20 -1.1 l -20 10 l 20 10 l 20 1.1 l 0 0
m 0 0 l -20 0 l -20 7.6 l 20 10 l 20 0 l 0 0
The apology reason is dine and dashing.
Wow, it's really realistic.
Wow, wait a minute. This is super realistic.
At this time,
for the trouble I've caused,
I am truly and deeply sorry.
Ah, but he's giving a good face.
As expected.
His looking down is good.
That's right.
In any case, you can't really see his face.
Hamada-san, this time,
Yes?
it's said this was a midday crime,
at roughly what time did it take place?
Eh...
Well, my memory is a little unclear but
That sort of thing isn't good.
midday, 2 p.m. or around 2 p.m.
Why did you dine and dash
at a Kawasaki family restaurant?
From here, he already understands.
If you laugh, you're horrible.
Just now, he smiled a bit.
He smiled?
He smirked.
His lips loosened.
Sorry.
Ahhh, no good, no good.
He's smiling.
That's not crying.
He's thinking. During that time.
No good. If he laughs, it's no good.
Well, I didn't have that feeling.
You call it dine and dashing but
it's not really that.
This is the worst denial.
Hamada-san, this your second arrest for dine and dashing, isn't it?
Eh!?
He's done this before.
He's done it before.
I deeply regret this.
This guy is the worst.
Do you recognize that your actions were wrong?
Um, well, I think what I did was bad, but
dine and dashing? In this era,
you can do it?
You!
You did it in these times! You did.
Objectively, he did. Objectively.
No...
I'll pay.
You still haven't apologized to the store owner.
You, where are you?!
Yeah, no good! No good, no good.
He's getting fed up.
No, what's really going on here?
There's a few differences of opinion, but
I dine and dashed at a family restaurant.
I promise to never do it again and
from the bottom of my heart,
I'd like to apologize.
Honestly, I am deeply sorry.
Is that so?
I'm already dumbfounded.
I'm not convinced.
He's no Miyane-san. (newscaster)
I couldn't follow anything.
You couldn't follow it.
I'm not satisfied with that.
You ending this press conference.
I can't accept that.
What the heck.
He's getting fed up.
Already... hahaha!
I hate it, wow.
That place is rough.
Ehhh?
What was that?
Terrible.
They said I dine and dashed.
Your apology...
But you didn't apologize.
You turned back like this and
unexpectedly started complaining.
A lot.
What are you saying?
Do you even understand?
He's laughing too much!
Third up is Endo.
Apology Reason:
Falsification of
Resume
m 0 0 l -20 -1.1 l -20 10 l 20 10 l 20 1.1 l 0 0
m 0 0 l -20 0 l -20 7.6 l 20 10 l 20 0 l 0 0
The apology reason is falsification of his resume.
It's like he's kind of making a face.
That's the face he does for his "Ho ho hoi" gag.
Ahhh, I hate this face.
I also hate this face.
At this time,
for the trouble I've caused,
I am truly and deeply sorry.
He's being theatrical.
Ah, is that so?
For your "Bus Hijacking" performance, huh.
It was smelly, smelly.
Really smelled.
It's been 27 years since
you entered show business.
You've been deceiving the
public for a long time but
how are you feeling right now?
To the members of the public
and everyone it has affected, my seniors,
of course my partner, my family, my juniors.
To everyone that loves me.
Juniors that love you?
Well, it's a problem caused by my own actions.
I made it from nothing, so I'm deeply remorseful.
Endo-san, you took up being a sportscaster.
I think that was a new challenge but
that's dead now. How do you feel?
Ah, so that's how it is.
That's right. Um, well...
Since childhood, I've always played baseball and
been involved in sports.
Well, to have done this
it's really frustrating, I think.
Frustrating?
It's frustrating.
Endo-san, what is "frustrating"?
That's going to be asked.
It's going to be asked.
What's frustrating?
Well, rather than myself
everyone that has cared about me,
wherever they are in society.
About those people that I've betrayed,
it's really frustrating, I think.
"Wherever they are in society."
This controversy.
We're told this originates with Endo-san's last academic career.
Because you say your high school alma mater was in Shikoku but
no school record of you
was able to be found.
You're not a high school graduate but a middle school graduate, is that it?
He's laughing.
Yes.
It's my own inadequacy, but just a little bit,
I wanted to look good, that's what I felt.
It was selfish, but I did it.
On that note, you've told the story that during your high school senior year,
you served as captain and were
scouted to play professionally but
was this also a lie?
He's sweating a lot.
That's right. Um...
Yeah... it is.
Yeah... yeah it is.
That's right.
What about you being a
Hanshin (baseball) fan?
That too, even now, won't change but
on the other hand, the other people...
On the other hand?
What do you mean "on the other hand"?
It came up. There.
It came from the crowd.
On the other hand...
He laughed! He's laughing!
He laughed.
He's laughing!
Just now, he clearly laughed.
Hanshin fans...
The worst thing you can do.
Answer the previous question.
What is "on the other hand"?
Yes?
It's coming from the crowd.
I say on the other hand. That...
For people like me,
when it comes to supporting the Tigers,
it creates problems and
it will create problems for everyone supporting the Tigers, I think...
What are you saying?
Do you even understand?
Exactly.
He's laughing too much!!
Excuse me.
Do you have any final words for everyone?
From now on, I'll reflect and
I really want to do my best with the opportunities that I've been given.
This situation is really serious.
I'm deeply sorry.
As somewhat expected...
A lot of Endo's roughness was apparent in that conference
You! Don't laugh like that.
I didn't understand what they were asking at all.
So that's why you were laughing.
That's right.
You could do that laughing
over and over on "Good Day!"
Is that good enough? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry! Really.
Are you running away!?
Apology Reason:
Neighborhood
Dispute
m 0 0 l -20 -1.1 l -20 10 l 20 10 l 20 1.1 l 0 0
m 0 0 l -20 0 l -20 7.6 l 20 10 l 20 0 l 0 0
Fourth up is Housei.
The apology reason is a neighborhood dispute.
His face is...
What face is that?
Well, the feeling isn't good but
he's making one.
Eh, at this time,
Everyone, I'm sorry for the
great troubles I've caused.
I am truly and deeply sorry.
Well, his hair isn't thinning very much.
Would you like to apologize
to the victims of this affair?
Yes. Since then, I've thought
about it a lot and I'm really
deeply apologetic.
From here on, whatever
I'm able to do, I want to do it.
To go on for 3 years,
I think it has been a long and difficult time for your victim.
He's been doing it for 3 years!?
That's pretty long.
Yes.
For myself too, thinking about it now,
it feels like it's been so long.
No, he's playing the victim card.
What was your grievance with your
neighbor that started all of this?
It was probably the
neighbor's dog's poop.
Then, at that time, I cleaned
up whatever there was but
that became a frequent occurrence.
I gave them a slight warning and
there was a bit of a quarrel
because of that. Yes.
That's the origin of it.
Early in the morning,
you open your window and
play a boombox at max volume but
what sounds were you playing?
Well, usually
enka.
Enka?
So it was enka?
In addition to the music,
it's said you were making strange noises.
I thought by making strange noises,
I could intimidate the other party.
What were the strange noises?
Could you be more specific?
Eh... the strange noises I did then?
Yes.
While the music is blaring,
"Gyaaa~!!" is what I'd do.
What was that just now?
After he said it, he went "pfff".
At times, on the neighbor's
walls and garage
it seems you did graffiti in poop but
what did you write?
"Never erase this."
Hmm.
What was that?
What's that supposed to mean?
What does that mean?
Are you laughing a little?
Is this a joke to you?!
What do you think this press conference is?
Ah, he's laughing again.
I'm deeply sorry. Truly.
He apologized!
I'm deeply sorry.
Is that good enough?
No, no...
I don't feel you're being sincere.
Don't end this on your own.
He said "Is that good enough?"
Saying "Is that good enough?" is terrible.
I'm deeply sorry!
I'm deeply sorry. Really!
Is that good enough? I'm sorry.
Finally, a few words to everyone please.
I'm sorry! Really.
Are you running away?!
I'm sorry.
He's ran away.
You can't run away.
He ran away. He ran away.
That was no good. As expected,
he laughed and ran away.
He laughed for a long time.
He did.
That was the worst.
No, what is this?
No, it's your own remarks.
Ending the press conference yourself,
that's definitely no good.
Saying "Is that good enough?"
"Is that good enough?"
Tie your necktie properly!
That's right.
They're going to say that.
Apology Reason:
Indecent
Exposure
m 0 0 l -20 -1.1 l -20 10 l 20 10 l 20 1.1 l 0 0
m 0 0 l -20 0 l -20 7.6 l 20 10 l 20 0 l 0 0
Last is Matsumoto, who also
has a job as a commentator.
The apology reason is indecent exposure.
He's looking somewhat self-important.
Wait a minute.
Shouldn't he straighten his tie?
Why did he loosen his collar and necktie?
At this time, for the trou...ble I've caused,
I'm truly and deeply sorry.
He stuttered!
Hamada, he fumbled over his words.
His tie is loose and he's fumbling his words.
Pay attention to your tie.
Matsumoto-san, when you were arrested, it seems you were hiding your face.
Yes, ummm...
I don't get his face.
"That was embarrassing", I thought. My own actions, those were embarrassing, so
"I can't show my face to everyone", I felt.
That's what I thought. Yes.
This time, you were naked
hanging around in a park
and a passing couple reported you,
resulting in you getting arrested, but
why did you do those things?
Yes. Well...
Publicly, that definitely isn't
acceptable, I understand that but
in regards to being naked... to do that um...
I had no ill intent.
About that, my thoughts on
being naked are, that happened.
Huh? Huh?
I don't really understand what he means.
He hasn't apologized at all.
He's losing his composure.
You're a celebrity so
what you did was okay!?
Ah, here he is.
Sorry, ummm...
Yes. I'm a celebrity so, of course, I need to use common sense and
I always have those feelings but
perhaps those feelings became
too strong and due to stress
I did those things.
That's an excuse!
Yes, sorry.
Apologize sincerely.
The one you were arrested
at was Komazawa Park but
At Komazawa Park, we've heard that you decided on a circular route but
what route was that?
Generally, that was the marathon course.
The marathon course?
There's a marathon course, but
I was going in the opposite direction around it.
When passing by the people doing the marathon...
According to the information
from when you were arrested,
We're told that Matsumoto-san had phimosis.
Is this true?
Yes. I, um...
Tightly.
Tightly?
He laughed!
Ah, he laughed!
Yeah, he's laughing.
He's laughing.
Is there anything you'd like to say to your partner Hamada-san?
Yes, um, we've really been
together since elementary school,
at Yoshimoto...
Since he was also the one that proposed we work together, really in regards to him
I'm really, deeply sorry about that.
I really hope everyone can get past this, despite what Hamada's done.
Hey, what was that?
This means you're going to quit too?
You're going to quit show business?
Hamada
must stop...
That's really the worst.
It's the worst.
What the heck.
He's laughing so much.
Wait, if I think about Hamada's
feelings, I can't say anything more.
I don't know. Please ask him.
What the heck.
Finally, is there anything
you'd like to tell everyone?
Yes, well, people after all
can't exactly go out without
wearing clothes, I've learned.
That I really understand and
I hope to let Hamada know as well.
Sorry, about that last thing you said,
does that mean Hamada-san
also often goes out in the nude?
No, sorry. I have no comment about that.
No, no, no.
Something like "no comment" isn't
okay at an apology press conference.
Yeah.
It's an apology press conference! You can't say no comment at an apology press conference!
That's right.
What about Hamada-san?
That guy is really
that sort of guy.
No, what sort... what sort of stuff?
He's laughing.
He's a good guy.
Yes...
Yes.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
Stop already.
After all that, bowing that deeply.
Take care of that necktie already.
That really is...
Tie your necktie properly!
That's right.
They're going to say that.
That's no good. This is no good.
Come on, like that guy says.
Ah, this is no good.
That's right.
That was terrible.
Remarkably bad.
He was laughing.
He laughed, yeah.
He laughed the most?
That's right.
Completely worthless.
Ummm...
Amazing, eh? People's energy.
Yeah, it's amazing.
Amazing, right?
It's intense. It's intense in there.
This strange sweating started.
After that...
The one always heckling was director Takahashi.
That guy got me mad.
Takahashi... Takahashi did it.
Ah, is that so?
It was Takahashi.
That was Takahashi.
Ehhh!
Halfway through, I suddenly saw, Takahashi?!!
Because I was thinking
"What's this guy doing?", I got angry.
I thought it was wonderful.
It's a chimpanzee.