Breakroom before filming
I guess so huh!
Good morning!
Morning!
Tsukitei Housei
Do you mind if I ask you something?
What?
Do you know what day
Feburary 15th is?
It's your birthday
That's right...
Thank you!
I didn't think you would answer it so quickly
You thought we were gonna say something off?
I expected you to get it wrong then I'd yell!
No it's enough
Its enough?
Oh, It's your birthday?
That's right
"Oh it's your birthday" you say...
Even though we've been working together for 25 years
How old are you going to be?
I'll be properly 47 years old
What the hell is "properly"?
Do you remember it Hamada?
Remember what?
When it was your birthday
Everyone came and brought letters
It was an amazing storm of emotions
A storm of emotions?
At the bar
Yes that's right!
Honestly, I really don't want to remember it
Episode in May 2013
Hamda Masatoshi's 50th Birthday!
Serious Emotional Surprise!
For Hamada's 50th birthday
An emotional unlike Gaki no Tsukai surprise
Putting away comedy, The crew prepares emotional letters
I was able to make a living as a comedian
With that Housei's plan for this episode
Watching that episode
My wife
's impression of you skyrocketed
Oh is that so?
I
want to do that as well
What do you mean?
Well It's my birthday
From everyone...
Your feelings of thanks
Put them into a letter and
For Yamachan
Alright!
Enough!
I'm going!
Your seriously terrible!
You crushed Yamachan!
We're close enough
Let's get even closer!
It's pretty inconsiderate to push us closer
Sorry but I want to do it!
To me...
So it's for you?
I'll be playing Hamada's role
And everyone will read their Thank-you letter's
Well when you say "Thank-you letter"...
Well I don't know if we can call it a "surprise"
Your right
You didn't know about it right Hamada?
Well If you really think about it
Do you have some thanks for me?
How about it Tanaka
When it comes to a letter...
especially this soon....
I can't exactly give thanks to myself
This is a blunt story
Well wheres the meaning in doing this episode?
That's why I prepared for this in advanced
So weird...
These are (fake) letter's for me
This one's yours Hamada
These (Lie)"Thank-you" letters
I wrote them
I'll be like Hamada
The bar lady
Then you come sort of drunk
Enter the bar
and read!
I want to feel moved
So do you want use to be serious when we read it?
You should definitely be serious when you read it
Maybe some tears too
from you guys
I'm trusting you with this
This is pretty excessive
I'll be waiting
So it's only us that are doing it?
Well, you know...
It's pretty unreliable
If you four do it
He's speaking like hes above us
I've invited some people but you'll find out who
See ya in a bit
I guess we have to get ready
Are we going to have a rehearsal first?
No, there will be no rehearsal
I want this to have no preparation
That way it'll be really moving
Make sure you guy's are ready to do this
Thank you!
An episode full of lies for Housei's birthday
Gaki No Tsukai #1243 Housei's Birthday Letters (1)
Presented by DCSubs
www.gaki-no-tsukai.com
www.reddit.com/r/GakiNoTsukai
Beron Beron Bar, A place only drunks enter
What kind of customers will come this time?
We sure do get a lot of different customer's everyday huh?
Mama
Master
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tsukitei Housei
Well, We sure do get all kinds of walks of life in here huh
When the customer's come
It's sort of like a game huh
It's not a place just for drinking
For a fun time right?
Its a place to come for a fun time
It's like a store to relieve the stress from customers huh
I wonder if someone will come...
I've come!
Cocorico
Tanaka Naoki
He's already drunk!
Your already drunk!
I was wonder if I got the right place!
Isn't this what you expect from Tanaka?
Haven't you drank enough?
Sorry just a bit!
Let's have some fun!
Your really drunk huh!
Seriously!
Sorry!
Well we have some recommended items here
Have a seat!
Do you have some Oolong?
What an interesting character huh
It's getting pretty dark out huh
That's fine!
This is a big welcome
Let's have some fun!
Of course...
Cheers!
What's wrong with you?
Well...
For the most part
It sure has gotten colder huh?
Feburary and all
Well It's probably the coldest time of the year
When you hear about Feburary
They usually say it's the coldest time and....
Isn't it your birthday Housei?
Feburary 15th
Yes
It's Mama
It's Mama's birthday
Well you know
Even if I do this thing
I know your not going to want it but
I've put
all my feelings of gratitude towards you together and
I wrote a letter
No way...
That's no good~
I'm bad at these kind of things
No way... No way
Quit that!
I know you don't want to hear it but...
Well you know Tanka put all this effort into it and all
He really thought it through
Yes, I did
Fine then... I guess...
But seriously I'm bad at these kind of things
Yes.. I know you are
I'm sorry but my feelings up until now
On these kind of occasions
You don't do these sort of things
I'm sorry but
I mean doing it at this sort of place in the studio and all...
Of course, I know its not my intention but
I just really want to express my feelings
Hurry up and read it then~
Get to reading it already!
Alright
A letter of thanks to Housei
To Housei
I know
for sure
your surprised from this sudden letter but
Please just listen to it until the end
Cocorico
was made to do
a Gaki no Tsukai warm-up and immediately
Housei looked at me and said
"Your
like a skeleton!
Are you eating?"
I
answered
"Yes! I'm fine!" but
The truth is at that time,
I had a debt to a company
Just making a living by itself
Honestly,
I had money problems
Of course
I couldn't eat properly because of it!
The bento box I'd get
was the best lunch all week
But
I didn't
want Housei
to notice that
And so I acted
as if I didn't have money problems
However,
Housei
saw through it all
"Because I don't have someone to talk to stick with me"
It was just like Housei,
to not force someone to fuss about it
and with an kind and reasonable excuse
He invited me out to eat
For me at the time,
after eating
some top-quality food that I could never pay back
Housei
went to have a smoke and
took out his pack of cigarettes
Then Housei
"Huh?
It's not here.
I don't have a lighter"
said to himself
So I said
"Please use this!"
and handed him a 100 yen lighter
"Because I'm a heavy smoker I need a light!
So sell this lighter to me!"
He said...
He put the 100 yen lighter in his pocket
Then handed me a 10,000 yen note
I said
"No, I can't accept that"
"Because I'm a star, my sense on how to use money is weird!"
Forcibly, you made me accept the 10,000 yen
For me who had no money at the time
It was money I was truly grateful for
After that, every time I'd go out
to eat with Housei,
You would always say how you had no lighter
and like always you would
give me money for the lighter
I
was so very,
very happy from that kindness
I couldn't help it
But truthfully that money
I only used it to buy 100 yen lighters
The remaining 9,900 yen
I saved it in my bank account
All of that money you gave me
I think of it as the price of your kindness
And even now I am still saving it all
Housei, You've found the wonderful job of Rakugo
I love Housei's Rakugo
because Housei's kindness
always reveals itself
From Cocorico Tanaka Naoki
Quit it!
It's so embarrassing!
Something like this is only embarrassing!
You saved it right?
Sorry about that!
No don't worry that was really....
Even though I've known you for so long
I didn't know about that story
Let's drink and get happy!
Lets do it!
Let's get drunk!
We're gonna get drunk huh?
Cheers!
Thank you
Wow, I've never heard that before
Thanks
But I've never heard of that story before
It was something Matsumoto didn't know about
Good Evening!
Cocorico
Endo Shouzo
Good evening!
Enough already!
So what do you want?
Are you going to be drinking?
Yea, Just a bit
Look's like he's had a drink before
Oolong...
You've got some bad eyesight huh
It seem's that way yes
I'm already 43 after all!
Sorry, Cheers!
I want this place to become a lot more livelier and happier
I mean before Endo came
It was a pretty dreary atmosphere in here
Alright let's make it fun
Let's get happy!
Seeing as it's this occasion and all
I thought I could just borrow a bit of your time
Enough already!
Don't pull it out!
Your pulling it out like it's a trump card!
Up until now
I haven't expressed my thanks to you
So I guess you could call this a letter of thanks
Quit it already!
Your really gonna give me thanks?
Close it already! I don't wanna hear this
A letter of thanks to Housei from the heart
To Housei
It was 19 year's ago that Housei and I met
Properly expressing my feelings of thanks
I think this is my first time
For Housei
who I've been indebted to on many occasions
I have a lot of thanks to give to him but
Today, I think I want to
talk about the event I'm most thankful for
This is
a secret only we know
And something I'm forbidden by Housei to speak of but
The truth is
the start of my Ex-wife Chiaki and my relationship
Chiaki
Housei played a big role in that
What I'm trying to say is that,
Chiaki in the beginning
Wasn't me but Housei
She was in love with you
For you,
Those feelings
I'm just remembering it all
However you did not show any interest in her but
Chiaki
who chased after you
would show up during your dinners every week
And
I, who was always sitting there
After seeing her every time, before I knew it
I fell in love with her
One day, I
prepared myself to get yelled at
and went to talk to you about my feelings for her
It was then you said
"I understand"
and left it at that
The following day you set up
a dinner for just her and me
Thanks to that, I
managed to get married to Chiaki
While it was only temporary, I felt true happiness
For sympathizing about my feelings that time
Thank you from the bottom of my heart
And there's one more thing
When I talked to you about my worries as a comedian
"Endou you have a really funny body so
Why don't you just wear your boxers?"
"Something like a
"Hohhohoi"
sound would be good".
You gave me that advice
And so that was the birth
of what everybody know's as "Hohhoi"
Housei's idea of "Hohhoi"
Truthfully the parent of "Hohhoi"
is in fact Housei
But even about the Chiaki thing
and the "Hohhoi".
You never told anyone
You allowed me, Endo Shouzo, to stand as a man
I am truly grateful for that
Housei, You've found the wonderful job of Rakugo
I really love
your carefree and fun Rakugo most of all
Sorry, I was really nervous
You said it...
You really said it huh
Well... This is....
Another thing I have never heard of before
Even though I told you I was taking it to my grave
Thanks
Thank you
I didn't hear about this
Did you know about it Tanaka?
I had no idea
What did you think when he was saying it
I was thinking "Seriously!?"
I never heard about it though
It was pretty surprising huh!
It really was surprising
After this, Hamada's letter of thanks
Good evening
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Welcome!
You brought something with you huh?
A letter
to Yamachan
Enough with that
It's fine Hamada... I've had enough of that
It's your birthday right?
It is but
So just listen
Yeah but
It's kind of gotten gloomy after those two read their letters you know?
Everyone's doing things you wouldn't call normal huh
We have to change the atmosphere!
I'm really bad with this atmosphere seriously!
Change this atmosphere!
Of course we will
Eh, Hamada giving me thanks
That's bad I'm telling you
What are you doing?
A letter of thanks to the dear Housei
To Yamachan
Seriously...
While we don't hang out with each other privately
And we don't really see each other outside of work
The truth is I'm very grateful to you about something
It was a time before DownTown moved to Tokyo...
While we were on break in Osaka
It was then
Suga and the others 27 year's ago approached us
We were asked "Don't you want to have your own program in Tokyo"
Of course, We were extremely overjoyed as it would be
a first step in becoming national stars
Truthfully there was one thing that was holding me back
It was
Ivory smuggling
Matsumoto doesn't know about it but
At the time, I was smuggling Ivory from Africa
I was selling it in huge amounts
on the black-market
It was easy money
"If I go to Tokyo I won't be able to smuggle Ivory!
What do I do!"
I was lost in thought
Many days of being undecided had passed
When I was depressed about that one day
When I like usual,
for an Ivory transaction
went to Kobe Harbor in the middle of the night
The one waiting for me there wasn't the broker
But it was you, Yamachan
Yamachan was different from usual
Looking like a demon, you stared at me and said
"Ivory or Downtown!
Which one is more important!"
Those words opened up my eyes
and ever since
I stopped handling Ivory
We moved to Tokyo as Downtown
And then we started this program
"Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende"
If you hadn't yelled those words from your heart at that time
I would
maybe still be doing ivory smuggling even now
Downtown as it is now and Gaki no Tsuaki as it is now
Is all thanks to you, Yamachan
Yamachan, You've found the wonderful job of Rakugo
One day, the Hamada family together
Will go to see our beloved Yamachan's rakugo
Thank you!
Amazing story huh!
Wasn't that an amazing story?
Yea, I guess so
Why'd you have to say it?
I thought I told you it was a secret!
That's terrible Hamada!
Can you believe it Tanaka?
"Seriously" I thought....
"Amazing"
What an amazing story it was
About what Hamada did....
What did you understand?
You remembered it huh!
Why are you getting so close to him?
NEXT WEEK
At that time my leg's started shaking uncontrollably...
Matsumoto read's his letter of thanks to Housei
And then a surprise guest will read their thanks as well
The conclusion to the 6 reading their thank you letters!
This isn't like Gaki No Tsukai at all huh!