ShinobiSubs
In the back room of Gaki no Tsukai, and those 2 are no where to be seen...
All 3 of you are wearing glasses!
Why don't you get Lasik or something done?
They're scary
-Wait, what's scary about that?!
-Good morning
Listen to what I have to tell you guys seriously...
I laughed so much I though I'd stopped breathing
It was so bad I was about to die...
We know you just got here
Who was it with just....
You know him?
Him...
Ah, Hamada...
You forgot Hamada?
Well...
I asked if he was coming
If he was coming? Nah forget it that's enough all ready!
It feels like a quiz coming and that's the worst !!
Last time on 'Try to answer the riddles thought up by Hamada'
Bread(Pan) is bread, but what kind of bread(Pan) can't you eat?
As hard as they tried the 3 just couldn't get any answers right
A frypan!
So close!
Why the fuck didn't you answer the question just now?!
CAN'T YOU WORK OUT THE RIDDLE?!
THIS IS NIHON TV BROADCASTING!!
But this time... What is it that Hamada is planning?!
It's a show that features Ameagari
Magical Hatena (Family fun quiz type show)
Well, Hamada sometimes...
He watches it at home
He just can't stop laughing at it
It's so funny he said
People that don't get it find it funny
People that do get it also find it funny
Both kinds of people find it funny
So he wants to give Magical Hamada a go...
Magical Hatena → Magical Hamada Version
After creating the concept he said it would be a good idea to try
It's the only thing he can focus on
There isn't any interest in women any more
He said women's bodies are just no longer magical
The concept was a little hard to grasp at first...
But I said I saw his point
Is this like a normal conversation for you?
FunnyJapan/ShinobiSubs  Reddit /r/FunnyJapan
Facebook/ShinobiSubs  Twitter @ShinobiSubs
Born from the 90's hit TV show 'Magical Zou Power!' the revived version
Now airing on TV under the name 'Kainou Magical Hatena'
The show that Hamada wants to try himself...
Matsumoto takes the 3 contestants to meet that certain comedy duo...
Good morning
Ameagari Kesshitai: Miyasako Hiroyuki / Hotohara Toru
We have something to discuss with you
What are you filming today?
Magical Hatena...
Hamada-san has... Well...
We haven't gone to meet him yet...
Magical... Hamada
It's magical Hatena we're shooting...
That great, it's really popular
But we want to do 'Magical Hamada'
Is that a problem?
If there was something to refuse, then I'd want to refuse...
Well, you mentioned that Magical Hatena is very popular so I'm happy about that
We just have to try and make it fun
I have been laughing all morning since I woke up
Thinking about the Magical Hamada
I want us to appear together
And use the studio set as it is
After explaining the situation to them
They head to the studio where Hamada is waiting...
You're late! I've been waiting~ !!
Come on get over here !!
Let's begin!
Can we brief?
They want to participate too
-Really?!
Is that a wig...?
Right?
What's the reasoning behind the hair change?
Come on, a lead host spokes person without this head is a little...
You wanted to give it a go just once right?
Perhaps the hosts before you had this style?
Everyone has played Magical banana before, maybe long ago but...
You all know what to do then right?
That's why we're all going to play Magical Hamada
Magical Hamada
The Hamada version
Well everyone take your places for now
The Magical Hamada is about to begin
But the content that lies within...
Let's begin with the first game...!
MAGICAL HAMADA !!!
We will be playing the game similar to Magical Banana (Word association)
When you hear 'Hamada' what do you think of?
The word game with rhythm, what comes to mind when you hear 'Hamada'
We're only going to be using the word Hamada?
Yes, just Hamada
When you hear 'Hamada'...
All of us?
I just said that didn't I?
-YAMASAKI !!
-Didn't he just say it?
-How many times must I?
Yamasaki, please stop doing that ok
Sorry
Let's begin!
Ready, set...
Magical Hamada~
When you hear Hamada...
Tough
Fashionable
When you hear Hamada...
Kind
Rich
When you hear Hamada...
Popular
Good at singing
When you hear Hamada...
Comedy genius
Really what is this...
This is depressing me
Can we stop with this feeling?
What's with the 'Tough'? I'm not 'Tough'
What are you laughing at?
Don't laugh !!
Get serious
This isn't a time for joking right?
I really want to do this seriously
You're ok to smile
A pleasant smile feeling
That's good
Pleasant smile...
Show us your pleasant smile
When you hear Hamada...
-That might not be bad...?
How about it Hamada?
That smile isn't too bad
You're laughing too much
We're starting with the face slaps this quickly?
Show us again
When you hear Hamada...
Something, something. Like that right?
-Yeah...
Let's try and enjoy ourselves then?
Here we go!
Ready, set~
Magical Hamada~
When you hear Hamada...
Strong
Midget
When you hear Hamada...
Kansai dialect
Hot lips
When you hear Hamada...
Bad at drawing
Far sighted
When you hear Hamada...
Stinky lap
Haven't you just been saying bad shit this whole time?
-What's your problem
There is so much you can say about Hamada
Look closer at him!
What part of him have you been looking at?!
DO IT RIGHT !!
DON'T FUCK ABOUT
Tanaka also what's your problem
I'm most pissed off at you in particular
For fuck sake really
You make me sick
Change the game!
I can't go on like this
Let's change it
Change the attitudes ok?
Everyone ready?
The next game will be
Hamada Magical Change!
The name Hamada is made up of 3 syllables
So we're going to change 2 of them, for example
Hawaii
Any order is okay as long as it makes a word
There should be plenty of options to chose from
Let's begin!
-The ears...
-Could you please hide the ears
Sorry but...
-Suddenly exposing them like that...
You're so silly
You look like a right silly billy with those ears like that
-That hair style and ear combo is...
Let's begin
Ready, set !
Change change, Magical Hamada...
When you hear Hamada and change 2 syllables...
Hakone (place)
Hakata (place)
When you hear Hamada and change 2 syllables...
Haniwa (pottery figures)
Hagaki (Postcard)
When you hear Hamada and change 2 syllables...
Hasami (Scissors)
They all begin with 'Ha'
Ha Ma Da, there is 3 syllables, you change 2
I thought it would be easy to understand
The most fun is in the variety of words and expression
The first few are okay use that pattern but...
But that far down the line you should be changing it up
Am I mistaken?
Please, you don't have to just use only 'Ha'
Lets begin!
Ready, set
Change change Magical Hamada...
When you hear Hamada and change 2 syllables...
Namari (Lead)
Chimame (Blood blister)
When you hear Hamada and change 2 syllables...
So-da (Soda)
Semai (Small)
When you hear Hamada and change 2 syllables...
Omame (Bean)
That's not related whatsoever
What is he talking about?
Did it change?
Are you changing 2 syllables?
-You said to change 2 syllables from the start though...
If you change 2 syllables I can't keep up
I don't get it.
This isn't interesting at all
It's what you asked...
Should we leave the 'Ha' in place then?
Leave the 'Ha'...
Or how about leaving the 'Ha' and 'Ma'?
-That would be easy to understand
-Leave the 'Ha' and 'Ma'
Ok here we go!
Ready, set!
Change Change Magical Hamada
When you hear Hamada and change one syllable...
Hamaki (Cigar)
Hamachi (Fish)
When you hear Hamada and change one syllable...
Hamane
-Someone's name?
Nah.
It came to mind because of Hamachi!
Hamachi reminded me of it!!
-Hamane can be a name also
Guys please...
Try and understand his sentiments a bit more
What did we do wrong?
You can't just use Hamane like that
That bad image of Hamane who debuted at the same time comes to mind
Hamane Takashi,
53, comedian
It's no wonder he reacted like that
TN; Hamane's gag line is actually 'I'm happy Pyo~n!'
That guy uses 'Delicious Pyo~n!'
He's not funny at all...
Was it my fault?
Well either way...
Let's go apologise
I didn't think we had done anything wrong
How should we apologise
I could just see he was unhappy
Tanaka, your performance was really sloppy
I really wanted to do my best
I was concerned about it the whole way through
-All of it?
My mum even said it before, 'That kid hasn't got any life in him'
Tanaka you should apologise properly
Let's go apologise
They head to Hamada's dressing room to apologise
Hamada?
Yoshimoto Creative Agency
Company President Okamoto Akihiko
Downtown former Manger
Damn his voice is quiet
What's this meeting about?
-Excuse us...
What's this about?
We're discussing foreign plans
Foreign plans...
Everyone has something they would like to say, Tanaka
Hamada-san has put great efforts...
Into making Magical Hamada a really fun show
Because we were not able to achieve your dream idea concept
I would like to sincerely apologise
After it stopped the first time and I saw your feelings....
I understood how you wished the game to be
Next time I promise I will do my best and really make it great
Can we please give it one more go at Magical Hamada?
They just made a small mistake on what kind of fun you wanted
Although it wasn't fun...
They tried to make it fun, but they were somewhat mistaken
After speaking to them, everyone agreed they wanted to make it fun
What are you laughing at!
ARE YOU LAUGHING?!
TANAKAAAA!!
Your inappropriate laughing
Is a huge problem
I didn't laugh
He's laughing
Sorry, I won't laugh
Anyway, Hamada-san can we continue?
What is this?
We're planning international work
From Asia to Ameriyaka...
We talking world wide plans
Seriously what the fuck are you laughing at again!
We just told you to stop laughing
I didn't laugh
This is the root cause of Hamada-san's stress
We have interrupted their meeting
They have stopped for us, and we're are supposed to be apologising...
But for some reason you're messing around
This is completely inexcusable
They are talking about planning global work events
That's right, from Asia to America, after that we have Europe planed
Why are you laughing?
Do you think this is an appropriate time to act the fool?
You're clearly causing Hamada stress
Can you or can you not do it?
We can!
We will do our best
If you can't, then go home now
We want to see faces that are crying but slightly laughing from you guys
-Hamada, he's not laughing at that, it's different
He's crying but it looks like he is laughing
I'm crying
I'm honestly crying
Get serious!
After the break! Hamada transforms into ???
The members await Hamada's return
Just don't do anything weird
Lets just keep the spirits and humour high
Sorry to keep you
Lets do it
Matsumoto-san, the intro please
Ok! Let us begin
Hama Hama PANIC!
We will be playing Hama Hama PANIC
The objective is to quietly take a bone out from infront of the sleeping Hamada
But if you fail and wake him up...
He will be enraged and a huge panic will ensue
He really is asleep
Lets begin
Hama Hama PANIC
START!
You were fine!
Ah, he is stirring a little
He's fast asleep
I can tell
Ah! Watch out!
He just opened his eyes!
They're not open, it means he went into deep sleep
He's sleep watching
He did it when we went to Okinawa
When we stayed at Haimarubushi in Okinawa, he did it then too
He's laughing!
He's having a nice dream!
It didn't take much time to get to sleep
He just lifted his head?
Is he really asleep?
He stopped snoring!
He's just staring at Tanaka
You're talking crazy he's asleep!
Sleeping with eyes open...
Shh.. Listen
See?
I can understand his fears
He is completely out like a light
-He moved
He is really staring
Is he asleep?
-He looks in ambush
What are you doing!!
Do it properly
The nose became an eyepatch!
He's clocking us
-Showing his tongue
Tanaka you ruined it
Anyone would be annoyed if you did that to them while they slept
Yes, but that's what the point of the game was to...
I could tell he was tired and taking a peaceful rest
Then how were we meant to...
He was gently sleeping peacefully and you went and did that
I thought that the game was...
We were being serious so...
Hamada was clearly tired and was taking a nap!
You took his bones while he slept!!
You took his bones, of course he will be mad
I told you to not do that didn't I?
Let's go and apologise
What for?
You took away Hamada-san's precious bone shape bones
We're sorry he didn't get much sleep
Got it?
The bone important shape that Hamada-san didn't get much sleep we're sorry
I don't really understand the grammar...
Look, it was his precious items with dear attachment, that's why he got flustered
The feelings of apology are just so overwhelming you can't even grammar
It's his beloved item
Coming up! An unbelievable tragedy!
They go to apologise to Hamada once again...
Yoshimoto Creative Agency
Company President Okamoto Akihiko
Downtown former Manger
We have Seoul, Shanghai, Hongkong and Bangkok lined up
Also Los Angeles
Managing Director of Filming
Planning, PR, Advertising MD
So, Hamada-san we would like you to participate in these events for the company
Ah, Sorry can I have a second?
Can't you see I'm talking?!
Isn't it obvious?
Sorry, well, as a representative, I would like to say
There is just one thing I would like to say...
Hamada-san...
Was sleeping and protecting his precious bones
Then...
We removed those bones away
Hamada-san was sleeping so to say...
What are you saying?
YAMASAKI !!
Please just say it properly! Seriously...
Don't you get it? How many times have we been over this?
You need to think of Hamada-sans feelings
That's why we're here doing this
We want to do this. Once more!
And when Hamada
When he was sleeping...
The idea was to collect those beloved bones
So Hamada-san's feelings
He was sleeping when we took those bones
While Hamada-san was sleeping
What is he rambling about?
I don't get it.
Just go home already
Honestly, Hamada-san...
What? What? Hamada-san what?
We don't need you lot
This company doesn't need you!
You're not even trying at all
We don't need you
I don't understand
Don't run away!
See you next week!
FunnyJapan/ShinobiSubs  Reddit /r/FunnyJapan
Facebook/ShinobiSubs  Twitter @ShinobiSubs