Good evening. Good evening
Good evening
Speaking like this together
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi                    Hamada Masatoshi
It's great
Just before, us two were just speaking here, now we're here, we don't need you guys
Tsukitei Housei
I'm happy
Actually, the guests here really got to like us
Cocorico
Endou Shouzou                          Tanaka Naoki
They got to like you a lot?
Yeah, they did. I didn't realise how much necks can go up and down
It should be from side to side
And then someone's chin got stuck and we had to stop
But we are really happy to be here
Just one moment
What are you chuckling about?
I just can't get enough of your design perm
Yeah, I get what you mean, it really is something
What is?
Isn't it normal? What's wrong?
Isn't something simpler better? You don't have frizzy hair right?
It's not frizzy
It's on purpose
There's nothing wrong with a bit of fluffiness
Okay, let's do our best
I'll do my best
You're balding!
You've forgotten right?
I had a joint disorder and my chin was in a bad state
Housei has been appealing for his chin's bad state from before the start of this years No-Laughing Game
It's a lie
It's not a lie
I'm being truthful
No. How many times have we been lied to with the end of year games?
When you got hit by the Harisenbon you said your ear was hurt
And then there was nothing wrong with it
All lies. And then your abdomen was broken or something
I'm really sorry for all the lies I said up till now
So you acknowledge that?
You acknowledge you lied?
So you acknowledge that it was just cowardliness
All cowardliness
And then your chin?
This is real
With what proof?
It's really real
But you haven't actually been to a hospital yet, right?
Yeah, he's just saying it hurts
So I let you hear it many times, many times, how my chin makes popping sounds
So then let Matsumoto-san have a listen
It made the sound
It totally made the sound
It sounded like peoples' do normally
Mine doesn't make that sound, but that's not to say it's not normal
This is a very bad sympton
Really
Even though you haven't seen a doctor
What sort of things give you trouble with it?
Today as well - Can I speak frankly?
Well, I went to take a dump
So I went and then as I was going 'buuuh' as I did the deed
My chin came loose
This is being pretty well received
They're so nice
Pretty funny
Was it funny?
It was a lie right?
Was that a lie?
It was a lie?
Are you serious?
So what you are trying to say is that always getting hit by Chouno-san is the cause?
But I have been getting hit continuously now for 10... 9 years, so that effect remains
Honestly, I want to be compensated
Compensated?
The strange thing is, you say that it hurts after getting slapped, but when did it start hurting this time?
Around 1 week after I was told that we were going to do the No Laughing Game...
Isn't that strange?
Because for 9 years -
So for the 11 months since you were last hit by Chouno-san, it didn't hurt?
Yes, it didn't hurt
And then when you heard about the game, it started popping?
Yes
What was it like again when you go to poo?
When I go to poo and clench up, it goes...
It's different now!
This year's theme for the annual No Laughing Batsu Game: American Police!
No Laughing
American Police 24 h
On air from 6.30pm 12/31 (Su)
Now, we reflect on the harsh filming that took place the other day
How many years is it now? How many times is it now?
So actually, it is now 12 years since it started as a New Years Eve event
If we include the ones from before that, it is 14 years
But 12 times now for New Years Eve
No Laughing Game Series
14 past broadcasts (New Years Eve: 12 times)
Before that we split it up into four 30 minute segments
Yes, 30 minute parts
2003 ~ 2017 No Laughing Batsu Games History
It started from 2003
2003: No Laughing Onsen Hotel 2d1n trip
(Mastermind: Hamada, Participants: Matsumoto, Housei, Cocorico)
and then from 2006, it started being broadcast over New Years Eve
2006: 24h No Laughing Police
(Masterminds: Matsumoto,Tanaka, Participants: Hamada, Housei, Endou)
I want to ask everybody about this, but when on route to location, how do you feel?
For me, this is the hardest job each year
Leading up to it, from around 1 week beforehand I start to feel blue
I get what you mean
The first car will come to pick me up from my house at around 8, 9 am
So before it comes, my family are sitting to down to eat with the 3 of us. Then when it is nearly time...
I feel like I will start to cry
Like your last farewell
That far?
Yeah, my heart feels like I will really start to cry
The food gradually becomes tasteless
This year, just before I had to leave for it, I have a kid who is just over 1 years old
I was just silent and embraced him tighter and longer than usual
Like I wouldn't be able to return
That's too much
That's how it gets
The bus on the day that goes towards the filming site, from the hotel it takes around 20 to 30 minutes
Really, no one speaks. It's just completely silent on the way to the site
No one speaks
Not even one word
Everyone is like this
It's so stressful, right
It's like an escort
You don't think it will turn off
And then when they say 'We're here now, please get off', no one gets off and just pretends they can't hear
Age is age after all
We all get older of course, but the punishers switch out with younger people
They switch out and stay young, and they're also getting better, so the gap gets bigger which I think is the problem
Really, I'm not sure how much I should say, but my anus has gotten really sensitive
That's a different illness now
The strange this is, Hamada-san doesn't really say much about this either
But actually, Hamada-san has a custom that he does each time
Before the No Laughing Batsu Games, Hamada-san, myself and Cocorico, the 4 of us have dinner together
Because our schedules match up then
After the first pick up car
The first pick up car comes, and then the 4 of us eat together
Since I'm always a little bit late
And then things like fugu, we have some really good food together - like the Last Supper
The Last Supper?
During this no one is noisy, everyone just eats quietly
We taste each bite
Just like your meal
I think that the behind the scenes of the games are funnier
There a lot of stories, really
Also, people who got a break during last year's game, including comedians
For example, Hyakura - ah, that was wrong
What type of hairstyle does he have?
Akira crossed Hyaku-pa (100 %) equals Hyakura
Akira and Hyaku-pa
You're so embarrasing
You just dropped the plate in front of the cameras
Everyone can see it now
He became big after last year's game, and then went onto win the R-1 Grand Prix in February
That's right
Harada-san, he collaborated with Akira 100 %, he also went onto become the "Obsessed with 5 o'clock" host from this Spring
Yes, also Sunshine Ikezaki-kun also became the ambassador for Sunshine 60
The building?
Yes, the building ambassador. It became the starting platform for a lot of people
Yeah, this year there will be more of that as well
So we can also think about what might happen this year
But if he's still at the level where he is called 'Hyakura' it might not have sunken in
He has to try a little harder
Yeah, he has to work a little harder
Were you trying to drop that?
What happened, Tanaka?
Are you tired?
I'm sorry
Has something gone wrong psychologically?
Tanaka, you went and did your live broadcast the next day properly
Yeah, I had a broadcast for ZIP
How long did you have till it started?
ZIP's staff knew that I had the No Laughing Batsu game on the previous day
And assumed that my butt had taken a pounding
So, on the chair, they actually gave me a cushion
They knew about it, so they gave me a cushion especially
But, there are some who didn't know. Didn't know I had come directly following the game, and saw my special cushion
And thought that I might have become a genie
You just stuttered, right
I didn't want to keep you waiting, so I tried to talk fast
Zip and zi, it was like zi-zip
There were lots of zi's
Ah, I'm so embarrased
But looking at the numbers, there was one I was surprised about
The total amount of times our butts have been hit, for all of us
I want to know that
11 823 times in total
5 person total: 11 823 times
Over 10 000?
Over 10 000 for all of us, isn't that crazy?
It's over 10 000
So first place is Matsumoto-san with 2 867 hits
No.1 Matsumoto: 2 867 times
This year, last year, every year it is the same, but aren't they harder on me?
Even though I chuckled so little no one should be able to see, it goes 'Ba-Baam'
Aren't they always hard on me?
That's true, but also there are the behind the scenes parts where we talk directly to the staff, which definitely won't be used in the broadcast
The parts which you know they won't use
Even during those parts, when we just laugh a tiny bit, it's 'Ba-baam'
You think 'Why now? Even though you guys won't use this part anyway?', right?
And also, the 'Thai kick's
You would have the most
Yes, I have gotten the most
In total I have gotten kicked 18 times
Oh, that's all
No. 1 Tanaka: 18 times
Yes, I thought it was more as well
So you need to get kicked more
That logic's just strange
Matsumoto-san got hit over 2000 times
That was the basic punishment since he laughed
But actually, the first person to receive a Thai Kick was me
Matsumoto-san was the first
To receive the punishment called 'Thai Kick'
It was seriously painful. He went for broke and struck around my hip area
By the way, what is a 'Thai Kick'?
But actually, it was Matsumoto-san, right? The person who brought in the 'Thai Kick'
I brought in the 'Thai Kick'? I brought in the 'Thai Kick'?
You introduced the 'Thai Kick' into variety shows
Ah yeah, I once suggested getting kicked by a Muay Thai athlete as a punishment, and that somehow evolved into the 'Thai Kick' that everyone knows
But I didn't bring it in
Coming up, revisiting precious TV footage: Matsumoto and the first Thai Kick
It was 17 years ago. This was the moment where Matsumoto received the first Thai Kick.
After losing a game, his punishment was to receive the kick
Are you ok? Are you ok?
This, the Hospital in2007
2007: 24h No Laughing Hospital
Megumi-chan - I think it was - had a button, a 'Matsumoto Thai Kick' button that she kept pressing so Matsumoto-san received a ton. I remember that really well
Yeah, yeah
That's because - Housei, being cowardly again - left mid-way
He went for an IV drip
Yeah, I really went for an IV drop because of the problems with my intestines, and blood was coming out
No, there was no blood
That was real. Completely real.
I was in the hospital for 2 weeks, but on the 10th day we had filming for the game
I was told by my doctor to not go, he asked me, 'Do you want to die?'
And?
And then I said, 'No, I will go forth'
Go forth?
The time period changed
Suddenly, the time period changed
'I don't care if I die, I will go forth'
And then during filming he said his condition got worse, so he left to go to the hospital
So I got all of them, that day I was showered with a lot of Thai Kicks
This is that footage
Press it
Matsumoto, hurry up and press it
At this time, Matsumoto got 3 Thai Kicks in a row
And then the drawer items started from 2005
Really?
2005: No Laughing High School
(Mastermind: Hamada, Participants: Matsumoto, Housei, Cocorico)
Yes, and then from this High School version, the drawer stuff has continued on
Before it was pretty tame, like Hamada-san opening his drawer and there were banana skins
So it was basically a nice reprieve
Yes, that's right. That's right
During High School there were stale rolls in Yama-chan's drawer right?
Yeah, that was the level it was at
Yeah, light hearted
There was also an explosion too
When Matsumoto-san's drawer was opened, 'Bo-kaan'
And then after it was over I hit the back of my head
Yeah, that was bad
Coming up, a favourite video
At the start, the drawer surprises were just simple
However, gradually they escalated
The Endou family also, from 2011, started to help out each year
2011: 24h No Laughing Airport
From the Airport?
Chiaki doesn't come out anymore...
No, well, I don't know anything about it
Chiaki, how is she going, happy?
Chiaki-chan is now happily married to another guy
Yeah, he's quite a bit younger than her, huh
Yeah, 15 years younger
He's from TBS?
Yeah, from TBS, a really successful person
Successful
Well, Endou, say a few words for Chiaki
Were you just listening?
I am also re-married and have a kid
Yeah, you have 2 now
Yes, my wife is now pregnant with the second, and Chiaki-chan is also married.
Yeah, you both sound happy
Yes, well, we are just going on with life.
So, tell her 'I love you!'
Chiaki
I love you
Don't act shy just because you love her
My wife hates where this conversation goes
She doesn't get what's funny about it
It's always, going on, the same specified punishment, but do you remember what the punishment was at first?
Of course
If we did it now it would be a huge issue
Now it would be impossible
Was it eye crushing?
Not that hard core
It'd be over in one go
It was blow darts
With real needles
Yeah, that was crazy. The pipes themselves weren't even proper ones, they were ones made by an assistant director
The ones where paper is folded up into triangles
Folded into cones
And then a needle was stuck at the end
Yeah, a needle at one end
And then, the short ones and - they were handmade and uneven. Sometimes there were ridiculously long ones as well
And then they were used on our butts, once they pierced we couldn't take them out easily
I took one out and there was flesh still attached
There was actual fat stuck to the head of the needle
Yeah there were strange ones, like cat ones
And then we got hit by 10s of those
Matsumoto-san, after entering the onsen, his naked butt got hit as well
Yeah, his naked butt got hit
'Ahhhh', he was yelling, 'Ahhhhh'
Do you know why I got hit?
I only laughed
Yeah, it's a weird situation
'My boxers are gone'
Yeah, there was a black guy at the change room going 'My boxers are gone, my boxers are gone~'
You have to laugh at that. It was hilarious. And then the next thing I know 'Ba-bam'
Coming up, we show that shocking punishment
This is the shocking punishment from the first No Laughing Batsu game installment
My boxers are gone. My boxers are gone~
My boxers are gone
My boxers, boxers... Boxers
A lot of things happened after that and they changed the format so our punishment was fixed as butt smacking
I hope people watch this year's as well
Lots of things happened, this year as well
Yeah, it was stressful
A lot of things changed up, this year that is
I don't know how things will continue on, it's all up to Hamada-san really
You're the one with the authority
I wish you would stop doing that
I really wish you would stop doing that, even with the guests, everyone thinks I decide everything... but not even once