Popular show
Silent Library
On tonight's Gaki no Tsukai we'll have
one of the most popular shows, Silent Library
Guest
Hakamada Yoshihiko
Today's guest is Hakamada Yoshihiko
For a total of 18 punishments, the highest yet
A total of 18 punishments
Highest number
The cruelest episode in history
It's the harshest episode in Silent Library's history
The curtain is about to raise
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
fb.com/shionnotsukai
twitter.com/shionnotsukai
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
patreon.com/shionnotsukai
Downtown's
Gaki no Tsukai
ya Arahende!
A certain library in Tokyo
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
Hakamada Yoshihiko
We've been too quick today
Yeah, kinda
It is
It's so thick
Just a bit
It's way thicker than usual
The person who draws the skull card will
undergo the punishment as displayed
m 0 0 l -1 -16 l -45 -16 l -45 0 l 0 0
Nose flick
The nose? What's with that?
topic
It sounds painful
It does
You go first
Are you ok with that?
I see
One, two and...
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Nose flick
Shh
Tanaka
How should we do it?
Making noise would bother the others
they can't raise their voice no matter what
m 0 0 l -1 -16 l -45 -16 l -45 0 l 0 0
One for each?
Oh, like this
Shh! Quiet
That hurt!
Next
He's taking his time
I'm going next, ok?
Let's sit down
Rice spoon on forehead
Shit
I got that last time
Rice spoon on forehead
topic
You did? When?
It was a shoehorn last time
That's right
It's basically the same
I really don't want this one
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready and...
Endo
Rice spoon on forehead
Shh
Are you kidding me?
How should we...?
Just one hit
Only one
So loud
It scared me
I swear
What the hell, man
How is it looking?
It's fine
Flip it
Ass flutterboard
topic
I know for sure it's about ass
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready and...
Ass flutterboard
Shh
Tanaka
Man, you're so unlucky
Huh?!
Poor you
Give me a break, please
This is a harsh one
Hamada?
Today's not my day
Go as hard as you want to
There
Wait--
Why flat?
Come on
Why like that?
Don't use angles
On this side, please
Not like this?
No, sideways
Like this?
Yes
Alright, I'm ready
Stay still
Can I?
Oh boy
What's next?
It hurts so bad
Haven't we agreed to trick him
into getting the card?
No way, it's random
That's so mean
Tongue grab
What?
Seriously?
Tongue grab
topic
Eh? Really?
The hell is this?
This one sucks
Give me a break...
Tongue grab? Is that it?
It's disgusting
Really, it's the worst
Please, not me
Here comes
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
One, two...
Hakamada
Shh
Tongue grab
Of course it happened, it had to
You're our representative here
Is he gonna do it?
Yes
Of course
He's our leader
No way...
Do I grab it with my hand?
Yes
Like this? Ok
Wait
Sit next to him
Your tongue
Let it out more
I told you more
More!!
Easy...
Don't slap him around
Let it out, dude
It hurts!!
This sucks
I'd hate it so much
Yeah...
Aren't we going too fast?
He's right, I don't like this pace
Whatever
Trans d*ck grip
topic
What the hell...
I don't want this one
I don't really get it
Yeah, me neither
Please
Ready and...
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Hamada
Shh
Trans d*ck grip
Alright, he's the most suited for this
Alright alright alright
I'm so glad
Wait, what now? What?
It's fine, stay still
Scary!
She's so tall
So intimidating
It was no big deal, hun
Sure...
A bad one, huh?
She went for my balls, not my dick
Ouch
Did she tell you something?
At the end
At the end?
What did she say?
She said "no big deal, hun"
Whoa, that's harsh
Extra emotional damage
I guess so
Does it mean she'll get back to you?
My balls really hurt, I swear
It's a grip after all
Ready for the next one?
Yes
Oral cracker
Can I pick first?
topic
For real?
Let's go together
Ready?
One, two and...
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Hakamada
Oral cracker
Shh
Alright
Magnificent
A way too dangerous punishment for Hakamada!
Have mercy
You'll have to bite on this
Hakamada
Oral cracker
Shh
Are you firing it inside his mouth?
Let's move him
I've never done it before
Use your tongue
Protect your throat with it
Open up
This looks terrifying
Wait-
Open your mouth
Say "aah"
I'm so scared
It's fine, just open up
Don't forget the tongue
Ready? Don't forget your tongue
Three, two, one...
No way
No friggin' way
The impact was way stronger than imagined
It's a cracker after all
Incredible
I couldn't do it
I don't think I could have done it
That was really something
You haven't gotten anything yet
Right, both of them
You're right, those two here
Static electricity kiss (☠ x 2)
There it is
Oh shit
I hate this
Static electricity kiss
topic
I really don't want this
This one sucks
What now?
Oh, right
Two skeleton cards will be used for this round
this punishment requires two victims
m 0 0 l -1 -16 l -45 -16 l -45 0 l 0 0
Here
'Cause it's two skulls  That's right, it's for two
Geez...
Oh, is that so?
It's even worse than usual
These two are still unharmed
I don't want this
These two, yeah
You got the last one, you go first
I'm so scared
I hate static electricity
Remember it's for two
Please!
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready?
Lucky me!
Hosei & Tanaka
Shh
Static electricity kiss
Alright!
It's Tanaka and Yama-chan
Hosei stand there and get charged
Eh? Me?
Yes, just stand still
Crap...
We'll load Hosei's back with electricity
How about Tanaka?
He's fine
electricity generator device
This is terrifying
Can't blame him
It's making sound
Can you hear that?!
It's so scary
I'd be so scared
Man, it's making such a loud sound...
Normally your hair would raise up a bit
But he's balding so they're not moving
Such a shame, right?
What a shame
Oh, it's working!
I can see it
Is this enough?
Ok?
This is the worst
He's too tall
It's making things worse
Oh shit
Not yet
Shut up!
*toot*
Huh?
He just farted
What the...
He farted
He farted!
He farted...
What the heck
He farted and it stinks too
So lame
I'm glad it wasn't electric
He even farted...
What's wrong with him?
I don't like stuff like that
Matsumoto is the only one left
Amazing, right?
That's right
He's the only one, yes
Only Matsumoto
Right...
So far I'm loving this
Endo  1 time
Tanaka  3 times
He got it three times
Hakamada  2 times
Matsumoto  0 times
Hamada  1 time
Hosei  1 time
Three?
Two for him, one for you
Two and one?
And he got one now
Only Matsumoto never got any
Well, I'm fine as I am right now
Hamburger set mix drink
What's this?
topic
What the...?
Doesn't sound horrible
It's not that bad, isn't it?
You think so?
Can I...?
Oh
You're going first?
I am
I don't know what to expect
Ready and...
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Endo Shozo
Hamburger set mix drink
Shh
What's this one?
Doesn't it feel like a reward?
Ahh, it could be
I'm a bit hungry to be honest
This is messed up
It's gonna get messy
I don't think it's gonna be good for me
Looks nice
Why do you have to do this?
Let me eat it normally...
There's also a cola
I mean, it's made of edible stuff
Well, yes
Oh god
Ugh...
Look at that color
This sucks
Look at that
Oh shit-
It stinks
It... it smells bad
This is gonna suck, Endo
Give me a break...
This is incredible
No way, this is horrible
You can do it, Endo
What the... what is this?
Eat up, please
I don't think we can air this
I agree
I'm freaking out
Look at him!
No way...
No friggin' way
How about a refill?
Holy crap
There's still more in there
Yeah, there is
Really?
It stinks
Ping Pong smash in the face
I mean...
topic
It couldn't have been clearer
Why...
Why are we doing this?
Ping Pong? In the face?
This one
It's going to be painful
One, two and...
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ping Pong smash in the face
Shh
It was about time
Finally
I don't want to
The tables have turned
Oh, come on
I'm really scared
This is terrifying
I don't even know him
You gotta do it
I don't want to
A strong smash right on Matsumoto's face!
I don't like this stuff
How are we doing this, Tanaka?
Do I have to wear this?! I'm scared
Come on, Matsumoto
Sit there
Matsumoto
Ping Pong smash in the face
Shh
Is it going to hurt?
Alright
Please
Make sure you don't move
How am I...?
Place your chin there
Like this, here
That's right
Don't move
It could be even worse
Well, it's scary
Whoa, he's ready
Wait--
Wait a sec
Ouch!
Oh shit!
That was a strong one
That's too much!
How was it?
It hurts so bad
Who the hell is that guy?
He simply hit your face
I bet it hurts
I'm glad he didn't hit my forehead
I see
That was a nice shot, wasn't it?
It looked good and it sounded good
Aren't we going too fast?
Too fast indeed...
D*ck missile
Huh!?
Man, you really love d*cks, don't ya...
D*ck missile
topic
Those guys...
This isn't ok, you know?
Why all this stupid stuff?
That's too much
It wasn't like this last time
Why are you obsessed with d*cks?
Come on, Matsumoto
He chose for us
That's unfair
Ready?
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
What?!
Come on-
D*ck missile
Hosei
Shh
Good
You got that
Prof. Ichioka Genki
Yonemura Denjiro's disciple
What now?
I hate this kind of stuff
From where is it...?
From there?
Where should we stand?
Over there
Is it gonna hit my belly?
Stay still  My belly--- wait--
That's a lot
Wait-- that's too far
That's so scary!
Too far! Too far! Too far!
Scary
Too much
It's way too far! Too far!
I'm scared for him
Here comes
Get ready
3... 2... 1... Go!
Go!
So fast
Very fast
Did it hit your stomach?
No
Makes sense
The missile came below the belt
It hit you, right?
Can't you tell?
It did
No way
That's ingenious, isn't it?
I'd hate it
Right?
It hit perfectly
Oh, he's standing now
Is everything ok?
I doubt it's gonna get worse
Yeah
Can't we call it a day?
We did a lot of those
Isn't it enough?
There's still more to come
Old dude's freshly
removed underpants
No way
Oh for crying out loud...
Old dude's freshly removed underpants
topic
This type of stuff...
It's hard to bear
This type-- I can't
Can't we skip this one?
What was that for?
What's going on?
Let him be, he's our guest
That was so pointless
It's fine
They're the same cards we had
Endo
Hakamada
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Ready and...
Hakamada
Old dude's freshly removed underpants
Shh
I'm so glad!
You have it, don't you?
As expected
Hakamada
I'm glad
Alright!
You're perfect for this show
This one sucks
It's the worst
Come here
You'll get even more famous now
Move to the front, please
Come here, to the front
He's so unlucky
Yeah
He's unlucky, isn't he?
He's so unlucky
Yeah
What now? Should he sit?
No, stand up
Ah, while standing?
Like this, just like this
Like this, stand still
Like this
Oh no
Really?
It reeks!
Hakamada!
Don't move
But it stinks
He's not coming back
It stinks!
Is this the return of Hentai Kamen?
hentai kamen (masked pervert) has returned
It stinks!
It stinks for real
So his real identity is Hakamada, huh
Whoa
I thought he would do it
Yeah me too
It stinks...
We didn't know
I thought he was in charge
I know
Same here
He's back, isn't he?
I didn't think I'd see him again
That was incredible
TRANSLATION BY SHION
TYPESET & QC BY KEDOMAS
website: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
facebook: fb.com/shionnotsukai
twitter: twitter.com/shionnotsukai
you can also donate on:
- patreon.com/shionnotsukai
- ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
PART TWO IS COMING NEXT WEEK
(OR IT'S ALREADY ONLINE IF YOU'RE
A PERSON FROM THE FUTURE)
Next week we'll see the second half of Silent Library
The punishments will grow harsher and harsher
Holy shit that's scary
And a tragedy is about to hit our guest Hakamada
Tragedy
What's this?
That's enough, isn't it?
9th silent library, second half!
A tragedy awaits Hakamada!
You're right
He's got nothing more to lick by now