[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
The First Gaki No Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
[Subbed by Thanos-no-Tsukai
Thanks For Watching!]
The First Gaki No Tsukai Arahende Thorough Search Project!
Let's stroll around town until we find a celebrity!!
Daikanyama Edition!
Daikanyama Edition, that's dope.
I can't believe we're still going.
Right, we promised we would keep going.
I see, that's not the greatest of ideas.
That's why we're in Daikanyama.
Daikanyama!
We should run into some famous people in this great city of Tokyo.
Right.
You know, Osaka is full of comedians.
You are sure to find them there.
But you'll find actors and singers in Tokyo, everyone’s here.
Right, right.
Has anyone met some famous people around here?
Well, I did meet someone at the Don Quixote in Nakameguro.
-In Daikanyama, you goon!
-Ouch!
-Of course, there are everywhere!
-You're out!
That guy was making fun of you.
I know.
Tokyo, Shibuya-Ward, Daikanyama.
All the cutting edge stores are gathered in this popular center for clothes stores, hair saloons, and cafes.
On top of that, it is also a celebrity town that hosts tons of famous people.
These are today's rules.
First off, we won't end until we find someone.
And they have to be on their personal time.
-They can't be filming something.
-Oh, I see!
Right, that wouldn't work.
-They can't be filming something.
-Oh, I see!
Right, that wouldn't work.
Next up,
you can't be like, "Who was that again?".
Right, right.
-It's also rude.
-Right, right.
You have to say their full name.
And lastly we have to get permission to film.
-Right....
-We have to get the agency's permission.
That's the scariest part.
So, if they say no, we fail.
In the searing heat of 33 degrees Celsius.
The search begins now!
Will they clear the task?
Let's get going.
It's already hot!
Will we succeed?
I'm already sweating.
I think celebs around here are on high alert since there's a lot of recordings around here.
-Yeah, you're right.-That's true.
And they might even be in a bad mood when we find them.
Yeah, that could happen.
If you imagine how you'd react if they came...
Right, I would be so annoyed if it happened to me.
Of course, we're invading their time.
I'd be like, "So annoying".
I would lose my mind.
First off, the guys head toward the old Yamate street, towards Ebisu.
Then...
Whoa, this brings me back!
-I used to live here, you know.
-Huh?
Here.
Oh, really?
I didn't know.
This building?
Yes.
Whoa!
I was locked inside this parking lot.
Oh, is this the place?!
Here?
Yes, yes, yes.
Is that where Higashino's daughter spilled the wine...?
Yes, she spilled wine as soon as she moved in.
That's hilarious.
I told her to apologize but she never did.
Why?
Why did she have to?
The guys arrive at Daikanyama's central area after a five minute walk.
They must be drinking some tea around here, right?
Right?
The mood is really good for celebs here.
Like in this terrace.
I wonder if Kouji Tamaki is having some tea around here.
Is he there?
-It's super empty.
-There's no one inside.
We're crossing.
If he was drinking, he'd be at the back.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Maybe he's doing some shopping.
-That could be totally possible.
-Yes, some shopping!
I've never seen a place like this.
That's amazing.
Have you seen any famous people around here?
Well, you guys.
Oh no, I mean other than us.
Ehm... Well...
Who was it?
He's got a duty of confidentiality, right?
He can't be telling us who comes and goes through this store.
We just need some info.
I'll say bad things about this store if you don't tell us.
You're the worst.
Sorry about this.
Thanks.
The guys didn't get any useful information... But that was expected.
Oh, there must be someone having a drink here, for sure.
-I'm sure of it.
-This place looks amazing.
They run away as soon as they see us.
Right, right.
Should we try crossing?
-Let's go.
-Let's try.
I'm absolutely positive someone famous is having a drink here.
With that being said, the guys head into Tsutaya Bookstore's T-Site.
However...
-We managed to cross the street.
-Yes, we have arrived.
Which way?
This way?
We can't go that way.
Oh, we can't go this way?
We can't walk that way?!
Oh my!
Having this road blocked is gonna hurt.
We can't go that way?!
I see.
We need permission.
Then, Shozo, you go have a look.
See if anyone's over there.
Good idea.
-Can we do that?
-That's fine.
-We can't take the cameras over there.
-Right, right.
Take a look.
And just in case, don't get caught if they are doing the same thing as us.
Of course.
Right.
So, Endo will be infiltrating Tsutaya Bookstores.
What should we do now?
Let's go in and have some tea.
For the time being, right?
-We have to hydrate ourselves.
-Or we'll die.
But at that moment...
Huh? He's wearing a mask.
Right.
He's holding a guitar too.
-He has a guitar.
-No way, no way.
He’s a musician.
-He has a guitar.
-No way, no way.
He’s a musician.
He's got no aura though.
But he might be someone big.
10 minutes since Endo's infiltration.
-He's back.
-Oh, he's back.
How was it?
I found nothing.
Really?
Then hurry up and get back.
I want you to run.
Yes.
Why are you walking around all leisurely?
I went all the way down there.
Don't care.
It's because you were taking your sweet time.
-I think that's why he's angry.
-Yeah, he's right.
He wants you to come running as soon as you find anything.
He's in a pretty bad mood.
It's because of the heat.
-Shozo!!
-Yes!
Go have a look inside that store over there.
Over there?
-Go on, young man! And hurry
-Yes!
-Roger that!
-Don't get too tired.
Ehm... We should cross this road, right?
Cross, cross!
Alright.
With that, Endo is going searching alone once again.
From where to where is Daikanyama supposed to be?
I mean, the train station is right down there.
So, does that mean Daikanyama is all the way up to the station?
Have you seen any celebrities around here?
Huh?
Have you seen any celebrities down there?
Well, we saw Endo running around.
No, not that guy!
He's not not a celebrity.
What was Endo doing at that moment?
Hamada is on edge today.
He came at me out of nowhere.
He's so on edge today.
I was a bit shocked.
-I'm going in.
-Alright.
Endo hurries up into this popular restaurant to avoid annoying the moody Hamada.
What will he find?
Nothing.
-Nothing?
-Nothing.
They asked me what I was doing.
Endo came up empty handed.
In contrast, Hosei might have found something big!
Huh?
Huh?!
Hold on, hold on!
Huh? Really?
What is it?
Huh?
Who did Hosei find?
Are you that celebrity? Ms. XXXXXX?
Huh?!
It's been 30 minutes since they started.
Did they have a big breakout?
-Huh?
-Hold on, hold on!
You're kidding me.
What is it?
Huh?
Who did Hosei find?
She's a celebrity, Ms. Rina.
Huh?!
-Ms. Rina, right?
-Yes, I go by that name.
What do you do?
I am with CanCam.
Model?
Yes.
A model!
Oh, I see...
We're done!
Amazing!
We won!
What?
Ehm... You're okay with the shoot, right?
As long as I get Repro's permission.
-Your agency?
-What is 'Repro'.
-Oh, your agency.
-Is that your agency?
-She's Ms. Re-Re-Re?
-Ms. Rerina.
Huh?
Repro.
Ah, Ms. Repro.
You're from the agency Repro, right?
Repro is the agency's name!
That's not my name!
The model, Rina!
She's been one of CanCam's, a fashion magazine, exclusive models since 2009.
Starting at Tokyo's Girl Collection, she had worked on countless fashion shows and appeared on many commercials.
She's a top class model!
The show's producers are already getting her agency's approval.
However, something is bothering them.
-You haven't worked with any of us, right?
-I haven't.
Oh, really?
No wonder...
I think I've seen her.
-For real?
-Really?
Yes.
In a commercial, I think.
Oh...
Right?
That one, right?
The one with the salad dressing!
It's not me.
No one knows her.
Hold on a second.
Sure.
I'm just getting things sorted.
-Excuse us.
Well, yeah...
Anyway...
So, I asked her, "Are you a celebrity?".
Oh...
I thought she was Anne Watanabe.
That's a super big name.
If you do find someone of her caliber, just ignore her.
We won't get her on the show either way.
Right.
Yeah.
And the result is...
They said it's okay.
Okay?
Do the rules allow this?
She can be on camera...
But unfortunately none of you were able to say her name.
Right, right.
And the rules say one of you has to say her full name.
-So it doesn't count.
-You're right.
And the rules say one of you has to say her full name.
Did we have that rule?
With that being said, the task is not complete because of that rule.
No way...
I'm sorry.
-She had an amazing aura.
-Really?
I'm sorry.
-She had an amazing aura.
-Really?
Thank you.
-She had an amazing aura.
-Really?
Thank you.
Thanks.
Sorry for bothering you.
Thank you.
Isn't this Abareru-kun?
-Abareru-kun.
-He's not.
He doesn't look anything like him.
That's just an old man.
It isn't Abareru-kun?
Did they let go of a big fish?
Only God knows.
The perfect celeb would be Yoko Kumada.
Yeah, Yoko Kumada would be perfect for this.
She's like the perfect fit.
And she'd be able to be on camera too.
What do you mean by 'perfect fit'?
-She'd be great.
-Right?
And everyone knows her too.
Next up, the guys are going into Daikanyama's landmark address.
Whoa, there's gotta be someone on that terrace.
Endo, go check it out.
Like, there could be a soccer player there.
I feel like Masaaki Sakai would enjoy this place.
Should we have a look upstairs?
-Then go get permission to film.
-Sure.
Endo starts running to get the filming permission.
Why is Endo holding his hip all the time?
Does his hip hurt?
Does your hip hurt?
M-M-M-Mi...
Huh?
It's my mic!
What was that?
That wasn't funny at all.
He was trying to make a joke, wasn't he?
It was that joke...
He was trying to act it out.
It was like that joke you were trying to make at the recording.
Oh, that joke?
It wasn't funny at all.
He went like, "M-M-M-Mi..."
So it's really packed inside.
Is it full?
But they told me it's okay as long as we do it on the terrace.
But it's super hot!
And we can also film there.
Let's go.
But they have some chairs...
We can come up with a strategy.
-And we can search from up there.
-Right!
We couldn't do that inside.
-We can look at the pedestrians.
-Let's go.
Time for the open-terrace strategic meeting overlooking the street.
And they won't know we're filming as long as we're here.
Right, right.
If they find something I'll go down.
If we do find someone, we have to make sure we get them on.
You can jump from here, right?
Right? Endo?
I-I don't think I can jump.
-I don't think that's possible.
-Really?
Let's not do that.
Right.
Hold on, climbing up is impossible.
But you can surely jump down.
Right.
Tanaka's diligent search continues...
On the other hand...
I feel alive!
This is so freaking good.
Super good?
Huh?
Did we give up?
We can't keep searching.
You can't?
You know, I've been trying so hard to find anyone.
My heart can't take it anymore.
It's broken.
But we can't search beyond here anyway, right?
-How much is left?
-About two stoplights.
And there's another street back there.
-That's the area?
-Yes.
I see...
If worst comes to worst we can go up to Nakameguro.
Rather than Nakameguro, I think our chances are better at Ebisu.
The Nakameguro at Don Quixote is pretty, pretty good.
Do you have to say that word twice?
You used 'pretty' one too many times.
You can't be using that many 'pretties' in one sentence.
Leaving the restaurant's terrace, the guys finally arrive at Daikanyama's landmark, Address!
So we're at the center now, right?
I see, I see...
-There's no one around.
-Right.
If Kumada is not here then we're never gonna find anyone.
Kumada has nothing to do with this.
Yoko Kumada is not coming, huh?
There's a supermarket over there.
Yeah?
There might be someone shopping there.
Shopping?
I see...
For real?
I'm gonna take a look.
Sure.
It's hot too.
It'd be nice if some celeb just came out of this bathroom after a dump.
I would hate to be caught like that.
Like, Hiroshi Tamaki coming out of here.
After taking a dump.
It'd be nice he came out saying, "Oh man, my stomach hurts so much!".
10 minutes after Hosei's infiltration.
Huh?
You were cooling off, weren't you?
You just went to cool yourself off.
No way, no at all.
Then why were you making that face?
I mean, I just heard there might be someone in there.
You know, we've been waiting for you.
-We were waiting.
-I thought there was someone in there.
-Was it cool inside?
-Yeah
Of course, it's a supermarket.
In the end only Hosei got to cool off.
Then...
Huh?
Who is that?
-She looks like a model.
-Right, a model.
Are you by any chance a model?
-She looks like a model.
-Right, a model.
Are you by any chance a model?
Yes.
-Do you work as a model?
-Yes.
Whoa.
I knew it.
Have you been on King's Brunch?
(King's Brunch is a morning variety show)
I have not.
Not at all.
After a bit of investigation, we found out that she's only starting out as a model.
What a shame.
Is there anyone famous at your agency?
Well there's a lot of models.
For example?
That's this girl, Anna Yano.
-Anna Yano?
-Yes.
She's been in "JELLY" and in "Nuts".
We didn't understand a single word you just said.
-Nuts?!
-Nuts??
-Jelly?
-What is that?
This the sad reality of a generational gap.
It seems like Daikanyama, the town at the edge of fashion, is a bit too harsh for these old men.
After that, the guys walked around Address without much luck.
Come on, we have to find someone.
I really wanna find someone.
I wanna be shocked.
But, who would you like to see?
I would love to find Makoto Nonomura.
That's great! Mr. Makoto!
That'd be great.
He'd come out screaming, "What are you doing?!!"
Honestly, I would love to meet the daughter of Okada from "Masudaokada".
(Happy Boy is a character of Keisuke Okada's)
I know her pretty well too.
Alright, someone's gonna pop right out of there.
-Just like that?
-Get ready, Kumada is coming.
Here comes Kumada, bam!
5 seconds before Yoko Kumada's appearance.
5 seconds til Yoko Kumada appears.
Damn it.
It would be the best if she was really here.
It really would be.
But no one would believe us.
Right, there's no way.
With no goal, these old guys kept walking beneath the scorching sun.
And once again, they arrive at the T-Site right by Tsutaya Bookstores.
Let's all go inside for now.
-Then we'll split up and search around.
This is a big place so...
-Right, good idea.
And then we'll come back.
-Then we'll split up and search around.
This is a big place so...
-Right, good idea.
-Then we'll split up and search around.
This is a big place so...
-Right, good idea.
-Let's do that then.
-Alright then, we'll be back soon.
-We'll be inside.
-Right.
We're sorry if we don't come back.
If that happens you can wrap up.
Understood?
Sure.
What are we gonna do?
I don't know...
Shall we have some tea?
That is the only thing we have left.
Yeah.
Splitting up is such a drag, just go ask over there.
Or you know, there's an Ousho right by the station.
Let's go to Ousho.
(Japanese chain of Chinese food)
What?!
Ousho.
-We're not going to Ousho.
Are you hungry?
Yeah.
It's Osaka's Ousho, you know?
Shut up!
The guys are just walking back and forth...
But then!
Whoa!
-A bird pooped on me!
-Huh?
-Whoa!
You're kidding.
No way.
It's true.
Whoa, it's true.
Hand me a tissue.
Insult to injury.
That's the worst.
Where is that bird?
The worst.
He's got bird poop all over.
-Senpai!
Ugh, it's not coming off.
I wanna go home.
It's been about 1h 30min since they started looking.
But in hopes of finding someone famous, they keep walking!
You guys also have to look at the biker's faces.
Sure.
We could run into Claude Maki.
Right.
And he could be riding with Mike Maki.
Those two sure get along!
Just then, the guys laid eyes on a passing car...
Huh?
-What?
Oh! Ah!
Huh?
Who is it?
Oh, hello.
Yes, yes, yes.
Who was that?
Who was it?
Wasn't that Sakai, from "Alco & Peace"?
No way, no way.
Wasn't he one of the Alco & Peace guys?
Who? Who?
One of the Alco & Peace guys.
-Alco & Peace...
-Chris?!
One of the Alco & Peace guys?
What?
Wasn't he one of the Alco & Peace guys?
-A comedian?
-Yes
Wasn't he one of the Alco & Peace guys?
-A comedian?
-Yes
A comedian?
-No way...
-It's just a lookalike.
I didn't see so I don't know.
He was driving the car.
-Really?
-It was probably not him.
It wasn't?!
I don't think so.
I know those guys pretty well.
That's the worst!
I'm sure he was one of the Alco & Peace guys.
Forget about it, Tanaka.
It wasn't them.
These two certainly look alike...
But just to be sure, we confirmed that Alco & Peace was in the middle of a shoot in Sendai.
It was a complete case of mistaken identity.
This place is prime for celebrities.
For a moment I thought...
-I thought that was Ayabe.
-Me too.
(Yuji Ayabe)
I though the was Ayabe.
Ayabe... Right, I could see him hanging around here.
He really looks like Ayabe.
What about these two?
I feel like I've seen them before...
There are many lookalikes, but the guys have not met a single celebrity.
So the guys have no choice but to keep walking!
There's no one here.
We got nothing.
Come on...
We came here cause they told us there was gonna be Kumada Yoko here.
There's some AKB looking girls coming towards us.
You're right.
These girls are AKB.
But you have to be able to name them.
No way.
Are you girls from AKB?
They're not.
You're not from AKB right?
Whoa, amazing!
Those are the guys from "Gaki Tsukai"!!
She knows us...
Let's try harder.
Let's try even harder.
Why'd she have to say it like that?
"They're the guys from 'Gaki Tsukai'"
What the hell are we doing?
After a bit of depression... The tables are turning!
Huh?
She's definitely a model.
But you don't know her name.
See?
She's greeting us.
Huh?
You're not a model?
Why did she greet us?
Oh, she's a singer.
-She's a singer!
-Singer!
A singer!
She's a singer!
What does she sing?
Hello.
Could you come out here for a sec?
Is she a singer?
Thank you for having me at "Hey! Hey! Hey!".
(Music variety show)
She's been on Hey! Hey! Hey!
It's been a while.
Oh, right...
You don't remember, do you?
You're an amazing singer, right?
You definitely don't remember me.
The artist, MiChi!
In 2008, she made her major debut with the song "Promise".
She stormed into the music world with her exciting performance and electrifying sound!
She's currently a popular figure in the club music world.
-Sorry for bothering you.
Are you on your break?
-Sorry to bother you.
Since none of them knew her name...
The task is not cleared yet.
There's lots of people like that.
-You guys should have gone like, "Oh! It's MiChi!".
-Right!
Whoa!
Who is it?
%&#&*!!
Hello!
Shiohaku 2014 has been announced!
This year with an exclusive Gaki Tsukai Earth Defense Force Pavilion!
We'll be waiting for you at Shiodome's biggest comedy place!
It's been nearly 2 hours since the start of the search.
The members have an unexpected meeting.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Who is it?
It's Hinoki!
Hello.
Oh!
It's Hinoki!
-Whoa!
-I haven't seen you in a while!
But you don't have anything to do with our current project!
Sorry...
The former comedian, Hiroaki Hinoki!
He made his debut at Yoshimoto Knockoff Club in 1990 as a second generation.
For a while he was also the opening act for Gaki alongside his partner, Tomono.
Hinoki, it's been a while!!
-It has.
-Is this your business?
Yes.
Oh, I see.
-Here?
-Amazing.
This terrace cafe?
Yes.
Why is Hinoki here?
Sorry...
-This is so unexpected.
-Did you quit showbiz?
Yes.
See you then.
Yes, see you.
Alright.
He is currently out of show business.
So the task is still not done.
It's already been 3 hours since they began walking around town in search for a celebrity.
This is their third time at Tsutaya Bookstore.
So what if we don't find anything...?
-It's a big problem.
-Right?
We won't get to go home.
But we have no choice but to wrap up now.
Oh, you're already saying that?
Here it comes.
Just as Hamada said, the end of the shoot was rather disappointing.
That's why I told these guys.
I told them Daikanyama wouldn't work out.
Hold on, the staff are the ones that decided.
-You should have told us sooner.
-Matsumoto, you also said you knew Daikanyama.
It was bad.
But you know, the Daikanyama I know is different from the Daikanyama you know.
The areas are totally different.
It was bad.
But you know, the Daikanyama I know is different from the Daikanyama you know.
The areas are totally different.
But we just went around the whole area...
There's a different way of looking at the Daikanyama area.
And it all depends on who you ask.
-Let's try our best next time.
-Yeah.
It couldn't be helped.
It was a shame.
Let's go home.
In the end, they did not find a single celebrity.
That's just impossible.
You're right.