Before the recording of Gaki no Tsukai
Endo Shouzo
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Housei
@FGRNDNoises
More gaki?
Subscribe!
Translation,
Subtitles,
Encoding
by Shion
(foregroundnoises)
www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
www.foregroundnoises.wordpress.com
It'd be good if we could manage to do that again before May...
We could still do that later though
Hey there!
I'm Endo
Today is the day we record Gaki no Tsukai
Usually I have fun recording the shows in such days
But I actually don't feel so high spirited, lately
And that's because there's a reason I couldn't tell anyone...
You know, all together...
Hey
See?
Yeah, I won't mind
Hamada Masatoshi
Good morning!
'Morning!
Oh, Yama-chan thanks for the other day
Don't worry!
That's right
The reason is
Hamada-san from Downtown
Looks like Hamada-san is targeting my body, lately
Subscribe for→
more clips!
Visit!
Translations / Gaki archive→
← Twitter
The fact he came to sit here next to me
Even though there are other tons of empty seats...
Is without a doubt a proof he's been targeting my body
Isn't it way too hot in here?
Is the air conditioning working properly?
So damn hot!
This is a clear attempt of provocation...
But with such a cheap provocation
I'll never allow him to have my body!
I see...
(Talking about golf) Pretty hard, isn't it?
I mean, striking a ball too high or too low, right?
Oh you're right, it's impossible to me
How is it lately?
Oh I don't feel much like doing it lately
For real?
Yeah...
Something's wrong?
Maybe is my new golf club
Are you spinning the driver properly?
I am
Is that so
Care to show it to me?
I see what he's doing..
With this Hamada will have an excuse to touch my body
In other words he's trying to get his hands on me!
So?
Uh-- But, I'm having lunch right now, plus there's
not much time before today's recording...
Uh? Don't worry about it, there's plenty of time
Sorry but, today's no good, let's do it next time leisurely
Come on, it'll be quick
Just show it to me quickly
Oh yeah?
Yup
Come on, get up
Sure
Get up already!
How pushy...
For how long has this man been enduring all of this?
Come on, get the stance
Ok
I think it would be better to tilt forward a bit
And you're making way too much pressure on this spot
You should bend your knee a bit more
Got it
Come on, bend it more!
Roger
You shouldn't have your arms onwards, the important is that
The movement should come from your waist,
a rotation like this
Crap! I'll get raped!
If the movement of your waist is slow
Then everything else won't work
So be sure to swing 'em this way
Just like this
Shit!
Someone... Someone, help me!
Got it?
Yes...
So, we should do it this way
Yeah...  I think so too
The changes of clothes are ready, guys!
Cool
I survived...
By the way, why is Tanaka
Trying to pretend he saw nothing
Even though his partner is going through all of this?
So even if we're a comedy duo,
we're actually just strangers, after all?
Are we going to change our clothes in here?
Yes please, do it here
Oh, ok
Ok, so here
E-excuse me
Are we all changing our clothes in here?
This is bad..!
To get changed right before this abnormally lustful man...
It'll feel like I'm saying "violate me!" right in front of him!
I have to do something about this...
I have to delay the timing of getting changed...
These?
Yes
Yes, hello?
Sure
Yeah I'm a bit...
Yeah I was about to get changed
That's the only thing I can do
to delay the timing of getting changed...
Endo!
Come on, man!
It seems we don't have much time, come in and get changed!
Sorry, here I am!
Woah, are you kidding me?
That's nothing but a gay party to me!
Sorry!
This shirt's too tight, geez
Yeah, I think you're right...
Mine is a bit loose
That's because they're so long!
Must be it
What's wrong with those nipples?!
They're completely erect!
Ok, let's go!
We're going first!
Shit!
We've been left alone!
This time I'm getting raped for sure!
Just how have things turned out this way...?
I just... wanted to become a comedian
since when I was a kid...
And even though I traveled all the way to Tokyo,
only dreaming to become a comedian...
Why...
Why do I have to be raped by this middle-aged man
around his fifties...?
Just what have I done to deserve this?
Your lunch looked tasty!
It was
You seem to have lost some weight
Maybe a bit
I'm going first
Okay
I see...
He just planned to tease me until now
So he can rape me later all at once...
There's no doubt...
This man is for real!
What the hell should I do...?
Everyone moves towards the location with the rocket bus
Hey, can I seat next to the window?
Sure...
Sorry
No probs
Crap, I'm getting raped!
Survived... again
But one more time, he sat next to me...
I can't let my guard down even as we're traveling...
Hey are there any of those ice creams?
Can I have one?
Thanks
It's been a while since the last one I had
How is it?
Delicious
For real?
Yeah
Can I have it too please?
Is it sweet, right?
Yup
It's good
Told ya
First off
Lick the tip...
And then...
Lick its back...
Then suck it daringly...
Oh-- this is...
Isn't this the "vacuum"?
I just heard rumors about it
But this is without a doubt an outrageous vacuum!
Eat up, Endo
Huh?
Does Hamada want me to perform a vacuum too?
Oh, thanks, I'm fine
I just had my lunch before, so...
Don't want it?
I'm fine
But it's sweet, it's good
Yeah but I'm fine
You sure?
Yup
That was close...
Huh!?
He's having a boner!
Sorry, Endo...
Yes?
Remember we talked about having a lunch together?
Lunch?
Yeah
You talked about it... lunch
Is Yamazaki attempting to lay his hands on me too?
That's why he was having that boner before!
In other words, Yamazaki is taking advantage of Hamada...
So he could steal me from him!
I have lots of things to do, I have to refuse the offer
O-oh yeah?
Mh-mh
What?
He has no intention on laying his hands on me?
I'm sorry
No, no, it's okay
Next time I think it'll be okay though...
What?!
Why is Matsumoto staring at me!?
It'll be fine later I guess
Ok, i-it's completely fine to me
Good
I see, so that's it!
Yamazaki wanted to be looked at while he was talking to me...
So he could try to get Matsumoto jealous of him!
In other words, the one Yamazaki wants
to lay his hands on is Matsumoto!
Well
I'll make you a call
Ok!
Shit... Gaki no tsukai is a den of crazy lustful men...
Are you fuckin' kidding me?!
He just came here in a situation where my  privates
are completely exposed and defenseless
Isn't this situation screaming "rape me as much
as you want!" from everywhere?!
What the hell are they planning to do right now?
Are they both trying to abuse me at once?
Shit!
I never expected them to make a team play against me!
Oh crap, he's coming!
I'm guessing that first Matsumoto will do me from behind...
And then...
There's no doubt that Hamada will come from the front!
How long is that taking you? Come on!
I've been spared...
But can I manage
To get through the recording we're going to have now?
Four... three... two...
First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Team Gaki vs Team Minami Asagaya Shop District
Grass-lot baseball battle!!
Now, now
This is about to get started!  Yeah, you know
Grass-lot baseball battle!!
Everyone from the Minami Asagaya Shop District
will compete in a decisive grass-lot baseball match
Since it got so warm lately we had to give this a try
So, a baseball match
I'm positive if we pour our souls in this match something may happen! - So?
To be honest I didn't want THIS to happen...
Heipo
His existence alone is an event
What are you doing here?
I can do this, I'm fine!
That group of amateurs there from this area
Has told me that you were running with them before
I was running!
Sure you were!
Ok, moving on!
Right, right
I present you the team we're battling against today!
Oh, great!
Here are the members of the
Minami Asagaya Shopping District!
Asagaya Shopping District Team Members
Who are they?
For real...
They look strong!
Let's have a nice match!!
Who are these guys?!
Our opponents
Do they have some sort of relation with us?
Nah, nothing like that
No, actually
The hell is up with that handsome guy?
He's really handsome...
...! And that means...
As I thought...
By the influence of that handsome man
There's a chance that Hamada's lust
could spring up all at once..!
Let's have fun!
Let's have a nice match!
Yama-chan!
Please throw a huge one, a huge one!
"A huge one" he said...
Is he talking about that..?
Crap!
I was right, the influence of that handsome man
Hamada's lust is on the verge of exploding!
Strike!
Come on, Yama-chan
Look closely to those balls! Look at their curves!
Balls? Curves?
Goddamn, that batter was just standing erect...
Standing erect?
He said it because he's having an erection right now?
Tanaka please, will you switch your place with mine?
I can't see much from here
Oh, sure
Ok, come on guys!
Now I see... That's how things went...
Seems like Tanaka was already sodomized by Hamada...
He's just pretending not to see his partner's pinch
So Hamada won't threaten to abuse him again, uh...
Just who can I really trust in here?
Ok, who's next?
Who's next?
Oh, it's me, it's me
Come on!!
I'm ready!
Give it your best!
Go and kick 'em!
Hey, that thing is doing is surely erotic!
To have such an erotic conduct with his partner...
Is literally anyone good for this man?
Ok!
Go!
Yeah!
Go and get 'em! Come on!
It's okay!
Don't worry about it!
It's not going so well
Bring it!
Huh?
The handsome guy is protecting the first base
I have a bad feeling about this...
Show me what you got!
He got it!
Go! Go!
Come on!
It's good!
The hell is he doing?
He's really the worst!
Wait, wait, what the hell just happened!?
Wasn't this a clearly premeditated crime
driven by his lustful desires?!
By now that man
Is merely a pervert
Team Gaki
Team Minami
Asagaya
Shop District
Let's end this!
Let's do it!
By saying this...
*Hamada said "shimatte iku" (let's end this), Endo understands  "shimeru" instead
of "shimaru". "Shimeru" means "to tie something up", and he literally says
"By tying something up... is he talking about that place..?"
He means to do it on my private parts?
Woah, what the hell!
Is he planning to stick that catcher mitt up my butt?
Come on, Endo
You're being swallowed up by the other team's atmosphere!
Eh?
"Swallowed" what?
Come on
The strength of your shoulders... pull it out!
"Pull it out"?
Right here?
You know, it's that
You're the only one with experience here
Do you want to make this become vain?
*Hamada said "tengu ni naru", which could mean lots of things. Hamada meant it
to be "to get stuck", "to become vain", but Endo goes with its other meaning
"to get swollen".
"Get swollen"?!
What the hell, this man
Came all the way here on the mound
Just to spit erotic words right on my face?
Anyway
Let's win against them
Got it?
I'm counting on you
He totally tried to stick his finger up my butt just now
Maybe to Hamada the insertion of a finger
Has the same feeling of a french kiss?
Hmm? What is that sign?
One time...
Two times...
...Three times
Is this man planning on raping me three times?
Shit, someone..!
Someone help me!
That guy is no good...
He completely became a human on Hamada's side
The hell is up with that face?
Could it be..!?
Yeah, there's no doubt!
Matsumoto is jealous of Yamazaki!
Gaki no tsukai's situation is sinking in mud!
Shit! I don't care anymore!
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey, calm down, calm down!
Shit, Hamada is coming!
Hamada is coming along!
Is he planning to take advance of this tumoil
I'm shrouded in and abuse me?
Somebody, stop Hamada!
Calm down, calm down!
Let's stop this right now!
Everything's fine, everything's fine
Getting raped by him... is just a matter of time
I'm sure tomorrow I'll love you even more than today♪
'Cause I can't stop my overflowing thoughts for you♪
And even though I love you this much right now♪
I can't simply put that into words♪
Who's next?
Here!
Oh, Endo
Counting on you
I'm going!
Settle it in a single blow!
We're counting on you!
Go Endo!
"A single blow"?
Did he came here just to say those indecent words to me?
Come on!
Alright!!
Great!!
Good, good!
Go run around! Around! Around! Around!
Around!
Sigh...
Am I going to get #"%&@d after this...
Almost there, come on!
Alright!!
Ok ok!
Ugh... that smiling face is because he's about to #"%&@ me...
Uh?! Isn't anyone actually planning to #"%&@ me?
Not only Hamada, everybody is seeking for my body...
Tanaka...
Yamazaki...
Matsumoto...
And even Yoshinobu...
I think I'm about
To get crazy!
Ok, if I manage to get through this handsome guy
The match will end without me getting molested...
Is everything ok?
Hey, are you ok?
Toss me the spray!
Are you okay?
You ok?
Yes
Looks like he's fine
Huh? What is this sensation...?
Why do I feel so irritated?
Am I perhaps... feeling jealous?
You ok?
Yes
Looks like he's fine
C-come on, he said he's fine, let's keep going
T-there's not much time left, come on!
Why are you acting like a total dick?
So, let's resume, shall we?
Ok
Let's go
Sorry for that
Sorry!
I'm sorry!
Just... what the hell happened to me?
Okay!
Your turn, Jack!
Come on Jack!!
Show 'em what you got!
Come on!
You can do it!
Huh? It feels like... is getting hotter in my nether region...
What the hell is happening inside me?
Strike!
Bravo!
Go Endo!
Come on Endo, almost there!
Strike two!
Good, go for it!
Strike three!
In this very moment I've finally realized it
The reason why I'm here
And my authentic feelings I hold for this man...
Let's start saying that getting to know Hamada
Was something I couldn't even dare to dream about
When I was living my high school period
On that melancholic springtime of my life
Hamada suddenly appeared on my cathode-ray tube
And then I was overwhelmed by the impact
that tsukkomi made to me
And decided to aim to become a comedian
so I could become a tsukkomi as great as Hamada
How many time has passed since then?
If I think about it, I'm now taking part
with Hamada on the same shows
I feel like I'm forgetting those feelings
of admiration I had for Hamada...
But now I finally remembered them
All my feelings of gratitude to Hamada,
who lighted a single ray of light in my life
And
This sensation I thought was "admiration"
I just realized is affection
So, Hamada...
I can finally say this:
I... love... you...
The hell are you doin'?
Quit it, geez
The fuck's wrong with you?
Stop it
That's creepy
Ohh
Everyone, protect!
What are you looking at?
Dude...
Come on
Endo!!  - What are you doing?
Maybe it'll be better if you don't come with us today
Woah, he looked at me again!
Guys..?
Why are you being such %&£#§@ to me?
Are you idiot?
Come on, let's get along!
Come on, let's have fun together again!
Ain't happening!
Like this...
Rotate
Ok
Don't laugh!
What the hell, dude! Come on!
As soon as you go there
You'll be surprised and be like "Matsumoto
is going to abuse me from behind!"
And then "There's no doubt that
Hamada will come from the front!"
That's what I was thinking
Ok, this one's good!
I'm laughing a bit too
It's hard to endure it
But yeah, it's like the tenth time
Pretty crazy, but we can do it
I guess so
ENDO OUT!
No way!
Your face just now was totally "ENDO OUT"!
For real?!
Now Matsumoto-san will try to make an impression of me
Really? - Yeah
Three... two...
[impersonating Yamazaki]  Come on, you're real-
What the hell!
What was that?
He just
He just said he was mimicking me
I couldn't cut away this part lol
Just pretend you're not seeing this
More clips @ this channel/
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Subscribe for more clips!
More subs = more clips