First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
Let's play nostalgic arcade games!
So, Matsumoto
Cocorico
Downtown
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
Yes
We played with Famicom games before, remember?
That's right
But I must say, our target audience is becoming narrower and narrower
We're talking about really old games after all
It's really narrow by now
I mean, even Cocorico probably weren't born yet
Yeah, kind of
We have lots of them, let's go check 'em out
You used to play those, right Yama-chan?
I did, yeah
They're so different nowadays
Oh? We're starting from this?
That's so accurate
So nostalgic
It was really like this back then
That's amazing, check this out
Man, that's so good
This really brings me back
Really well done
So nostalgic!
I can't believe Gaki no Tsukai spent so much money on this
This is incredible
They had all these games?!
They changed their minds
You can tell
Let's take a look, shall we?
This one
Mini Drive (1959) - Operate the handle to reach the goal in a set amount of time
This one used to be in that department store when we were debuting
Yeah, on its second floor
This one was there
It's the same
Play it, please
We need cash for this
I don't understand the objective of this game
This game's...?
I mean, I get the whole thing, but I still don't know
What determines your success or failure
It's the score, it gets higher
Does it give you a prize or anything?
This plate here...
I just thought about it
But could it be that you have to go past these plates?
Probably
We didn't know that as kids
How could we?
Go for it, Hamada
How much is it?
100 yen
Kinda costly
I thought it was like 10 yen
It started so suddenly!
Woah!
So far so good
You gotta be kidding me!
What the hell is this?
Kind of half-assed, isn't it?
But he's going for it
He reached 100
Nice, nice
You're right, it goes "ding ding" as I step on plates
This isn't fun at all, someone take my place please
Hang on
He's really going for it
This is exhausting
No it's not
Nice
Almost there, 100 points left
You were so close to Sapporo...
Dude, what the--?
Isn't it strange it starts as soon as you put the 100 yen in?
Can't deny it was too sudden
So sudden and without sounds...
It's always like this
(song titles, in-episode description boxes etc.)
Translation & edit by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Translations notes are available on my wordpress
Typesetting & QC by RIDDELL
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Rules:  they will compete in several nostalgic game-center games. The winner can request a nostalgic song to play.
Today, they're going to compete in several nostalgic arcade games
The winner of each round can request a nostalgic song to be played!
That
I used to play this, I wanna try it
Man, so nostalgic!!
Shinkansen Game II (1976) - Launch the inserted 10 yen inside the machine like a
pachinko slot: if you manage to get it inside the goal, you win. You have 3 chances.
Their first game is going to be "Shinkansen Game"
Flick the 10 yen inside the board and aim for the goal
If you enter the "goal" area, you win!
Tanaka will be our first challenger
This was really something
You make this start, right?
So cool you use your own 10 yen for this
If it falls here, I'm out
Come on man, don't take that much time
That's it
You gotta find the right timing
Ok, he made it
This part...!
You have to move on
I think I can do this
But if you charge it too much you'll hit that hole
Incredible
It went down Okayama!
This is the worst part
You just have to aim for that goal
You're so close
There's a "goal" between two "fails"
This is really...
It's really tricky
Amazing!
It went in
Something came out
The hell is this guy?!
He got it on his first round
Are you... some kind of God?
I never thought I could do it
Tanaka succeeded in one round
Next up is Matsumoto's turn
[cut] Yeah, it can happen
Gentle touches
Man, if you used 30 yen for this game as a kid, your parents would lethal inject you
At this point I--
I see, if it falls here, it goes there
I see, that's how he's doing it
Maybe you have to do it a little harder here
I expected this
You went too soft
Let me try again
You can try three times
It went through!
Can this happen?!
I see...
Nice one
I'm pressing harder here
Here we are
Here goes nothing
The hell, man
It barely moved
It jiggled
Just give me one sec
Alright!!
You can actually do this
Yeah, it is possible
They both completed it
Next up is Hamada
What the fuck! Are you kidding me?!
Hamada failed miserably
Now it's Endo's turn
What the...? How can I do this?
Endo quickly lost too
Last one is Hosei, who claims to be good at games
You know, it's 'cause I'm used to this
And we're done
Here's the memories song requested by our winner Tanaka
I wonder if you remember this
You know this?
Is it from when we were kids?
It is
This song is so good
Masato Shimon, right?
That's right!
Raideen, right?
Ah, Raideen...
I like this song
♪ The shining skies
♪ The sparkling oceans
You were told you looked like Raideen?
♪ There is no way
They used to call me Raideen
Because of your chin?
♪ I would let them fall into the hands of demons!
Yeah, it kind of sticks out
Was Raideen the one with the long thing here?
♪ Take all of our hopes
The protagonist jumps with his bike on his head
♪ Into your body
And gets on his forehead
♪ And revive!
And then his bike goes down, right?
Inside his chin?
No, he doesn't ride it from its chin
♪ Raideen, Raideen!
He's not inside its chin
And here's Matsumoto's memory song
♪ When I was a little child I used to cry
I don't know this
You don't? It's Mineko Nishikawa
♪ Over this dream of getting hold up by my beloved one
It's Anata ni Ageru (Giving Myself to You)
Never heard before
What are you talking about? She won the "Rookie of the Year" award with it
♪ No, no, no, I'm not a kid
Of course you know this
Ah, I know this part
♪ And if it's a complete love you want
For a moment I thought it was that other song
I remember when I used to listen to this, my mom was like "what is she talking about?"
"This stuff is obscene"
♪ I'll give it to you, I'm giving myself to you
And told me "don't listen to this too much" and stuff
She went too far
Pinball (Big Hit) (1973) - Score points by making the ball hit targets or pass over them:
the one who gets the highest score wins
Next up is a classic pinball, in which you score points by hitting targets and passing over them
Whoever gets the highest score will be the winner
My neighbor used to kick the hell out of this machine once he was done playing
And everyone started doing it too
There was a trick to get one free play
You had to lift this whole thing up and "bam"!
Legend says if you keep doing it a few more times, an angry old dude shows up
Hamada is our first challenger
This one doesn't have a plunger
He's moving so much
Woah, it went right between
You're really swinging your hips, aren't you?
He's getting into it
Feels like he's playing baseball for real
What could I have done? It fell in the exact center
It slipped in so nicely
Alright alright
In the middle again!
Yeah but, that's how we used to do it
I have no idea how to predict where it goes
Watch out
You'll get hurt
Over
1810 points
This is some batsu-game level score
Endo is our next challenger
I think it's easy to beat his score
There are flippers up there too, Endo
Up there?
See? You can control these levers too
Ah, here?
No!
Have you ever seen someone doing this?!
Did you see me do that? Even once?
Are you for real, man? Where were you looking at before?
It's the same lever
That's unbelievable
Ah, it activates both of them, I see
Was that for real just now?
That surprised me
This...
He's totally the uncoolest one
That's what newbies do
Am I doing it wrong?
You'll get bullied
So lame!
That tiny jump of yours, man
I can't believe there's one of those guys here
They really didn't let me play much with these things
Let you play? What do you mean---
Let you play?
I remember there was this public bath house in my home town
It had one of those, but only older kids played it
They played in rounds?
Yeah, only them though
8840 points
He thought there were buttons here...
And he tried to press them like this
Tanaka is our third challenger
Tanaka looks like someone who knows how to do it
He sucks
Tanaka couldn't do it at all, he scored the lowest: 1250 points
No need to wait for his third ball, he's already out
Next up is Hosei, who says he has played a lot of pinball
Gotta watch out
Oh, nice
It's all so fast-paced
I remember seeing this scene in that bath house...
You got that?
Yep, I'm number one
Incredible
Hosei gets the highest score by far: 41460 points
Matsumoto has great confidence on his pinball skills: he'll challenge Hosei's score
You can tell he's used to that movement
He's a strong enemy
You can feel his boss aura
I didn't know Matsumoto was good at this
Look how nice his left-right control is
He's sort of panicking
He's a strong enemy now, that's his responsibility
That's why it's-- woah!
Man, what a stupid way to lose
Geez
I couldn't show at all how cool I am
No fucking way!!
There's nothing you can do when it falls in the center
Yeah, you just give up
What will our winner Hosei's memory song be?
Oh, it's Mizuiro no Ame (aqua blue rain)
I know this one   - Junko Yagami, right?
That's right
♪ Ah, aqua blue rain...
From Popcon, right?
Was it?
I think so
I think this song changed music as we used to know it
♪ Wrap around my shoulders and keep pouring down...
Lots of similar artists started to pop out soon after
Maybe it's from Popcon, I don't know
They decided to take a small break at the candy store corner
Let's just take the ones we want and eat 'em
This brings me back
Wow, Aji Kare...
These used to be everywhere back then
Yeah
I ate tons of these
Man, I remember eating so many of those
I used to love this
Delicious
This is so good
Oh, I won
I really did win, look
He's right, holy crap
Why do you win only when it comes to bullshit like this?
Alright, I won!
Can you spin a spinning top?
Try it yourself
I wonder if it'll spin
It's spinning!
See? I can do it
That's incredible
I don't think kids nowadays can do it
Try it, Endo
Look, firecrackers
Kanshaku-dama:  there's some gunpowder in them, you can throw it to the ground and they make a loud noise
Kanshaku-dama, right? I always wondered what was so fun about them
Yeah, I know
What just happened?
He tried to use a firecracker
A firecracker?
Did he drop it?
Gimme a break
What's wrong, Hamada?
He tried to startle you
Serves him right, yeah?
He went like "baaam"!
Touch Action (1978) - A game about touching the displayed number panels
the one who gets the highest score wins
Our next nostalgic arcade game is Touch Action
Press as many buttons as you can by following what's displayed
Hamada is going to be our first challenger
Who scores most points win
Good
He's so focused now
He's into it
Look at his shape
Look at his hands
He's moving like a snake
You're right
Poor thing
If kids would see him, they'd cry
Shut up, geez!
Is he coming to school tomorrow?
He owes us ice creams
You're so slow
That's impressive, though
He's the first...
- He's done
You're right
Oh, I see
16 points
Not bad
Well done
Not bad, really
Endo is up next
He couldn't see well, so he only scored 11 points
He's doing it like this
Now...
Isn't this too easy?
Tanaka scored an average 13 points
I don't think so
Yamazaki is really quick
Hosei will show his best
This guy can probably do it blindfolded
He can use both his hands
Three seconds left, two, one...
Did he beat me?
17 points, he did
Yama-chan is on top now
Hosei is number one again
And now Matsumoto will try to beat his record
You're so goddamn slow
Uh? I can't find the four
You had no right to criticize us
There's no 29 here-- oh, there it is
Are you a geezer or what?
He's like "uh? there's no 4"
Shut your trap
Matsumoto didn't change much: he's stuck with 13 points
Once again, Hosei is the winner
♪ Come here, come on, with your black eyes
Who was this...
Daisuke Shima?
♪ Don't pout around, let's run away
This is Ginbae, right?
Yeah, it's Ginbae
Johnny from Yokohama Ginbae
Ah, Johnny?!
♪ Come here, come on, with your black eyes
This is so nostalgic, isn't it?
This was huge back then
♪ Don't pout around, let's run away
I remember I was in middle school, first year
Me too, around that
♪ Come on!
I was only like 1.39m tall
♪ We're always covered in scars
And I had just the right music to cheer me up
♪ Drenched in sweat, the sun will set
This was popular, wasn't it?
Piccadilly Circus (1976) - A roulette game based on number prediction
the one to accumulate the most coins will be the winner
Their next game is going to be Piccadilly Circus
It's a roulette game where each game is worth 10 yen
Play up to 4 numbers for each column, and get that amount of coins if you win
Each one will be given 50 yen: the one to have the most coins by the end, wins!
Of course I'm taking this one
It figures, there's a lot of twos
Not taking the 4 column
I'm gonna use them all, ok?
So, nothing on column 4...
Man, if one of the 6 column pops out...
I'm aiming for that 6
Gonna take this 8 too
And I'm taking this 30 too
Matsumoto plays without taking the 4 and 10 column
♪ Come on, come here and come on, come on, come on!
♪ With your black eyes~
Are you drunk?
You got half the coins you had
Alright, your turn
There are these 2s here...
Is this how you're gonna do it?
To be honest, I think a 10 will come
It does happen
I'm taking this 6, and 4
You can also score zero, you know
I'm not taking this 2
Not gonna take it
But I took it and it went well...
I don't think it will come twice in a row
Oh, no 4...
- He didn't take the 8 too
I think it's gonna be around here, that's how it works
Alright
♪ Come here and
♪ Come on, come on
♪ Come on, with your black eyes~
10, please! 10!
See?
You got a 4
Nice one!
My god, this guy...
What the hell, seriously?
But man, playing with Yamazaki is the best
It's no fun at all playing with the rest of you
Don't be like that
It's no fun at all with you, I swear
Endo avoids 8 and 10, but if a 6 comes out, he'll win 12 coins!
Let's go!
It could go well--
It's an 8
No fun at all, man
Just go home, dude
Don't you have any other show to go to?
Not today
He doesn't have coins anymore, no fun at all...
I'm free today
Tanaka avoids 2 and 8
Is it about time for a 30 to pop out?
You didn't take 2 and 8, right?
Yeah
There's plenty of 6 and 10s---
♪ Come here and come on, come on, come on
It's a zero
I swear, no fun at all
Just go home, man
Get away
What the hell?
Who invited this guy?
I don't remember asking him to join us even once
But he's still showing up
Driving his worn-out bicycle around
Hamada removes 6, 8 and 30 columns
No 6, 8 nor 30, I see
Quite the gambler
Woah, three points...
That's a risky one
Hamada removes 6, 8 and 30 columns
No 6, 8 nor 30, I see
Quite the gambler
Woah, three points...
That's a risky one
He's so cool
He got a two, it's 4 coins
Yeah, decent enough
And now, it's between the three of them
Who is going to win?
You want me to go first?
Sure
He's enjoying it so much
We look like those kids with no money
Who just stand there and watch
Yeah, those whose mom is looking for them
And she's like "bring me my bicycle back!"
"I have errands to run, I need that, give it back to me"
Who cares about those boring errands?
That really used to happen
Look at that
He didn't take 4 and 8 column
No 4 and 8, but if he gets a 10 he gets 40 coins
There will be a lot of coins
I hope it comes
If it comes out
You'll skyrocket to the top
Come here, 10!
It's a 6
But it's still impressive, well done
I'll say it again, it's so goddamn fun to play with him
He's so good at this
I could play for hours with him
How...?
I'd never get tired of playing with him, really
Hamada aims for a turn-around by excluding 2, 6 and 30 columns
4, 8 and 10, huh?
Here I go
Aiming for that 10?
Yeah, right
4, 8 and 10
Come to me!
Is he done?
Only me and Yamazaki left, it figures
What the hell, for real...
Wanna go do something else?
Alright, if I want to win against Yamazaki...
I knew it'll come to them
I have to aim for a 10 or 30
It'll be amazing if that happens, but...
Yeah, you'd be so cool
Please
♪ Come here and come on, come on, with you black ey--
A 10 or 30, please, 10 or 30 please!!
I get to choose another song, right?
♪ Say guys, am I big? Yay!
♪ Say guys, am I great? Yay!
This was from the era of delinquents, right?
Yeah
♪ Alright! Let's jump into it!
It was like this before, yeah
It's a sort of comedy-song
Why don't you keep on playing, Yamazaki?
Yes please
It's so fun to play with him, I swear
He left us all out
If Yamazaki wouldn't have come today, I wouldn't have come either
♪ Gonna fix up my hair early in the mornin'
I'm taking 2, 4 and 10 columns
♪ Gonna fix it up real real good
♪ A slather of pomade is gonna make it nice 'n' cool
If he gets a 10 it'd be so nice
♪ Gonna be that guy ya all know
He's a master of this
Look at him
♪ "I don't need a woman, ya know" (hundreds of refusals!)
This is never going to end
This dude is a blast...
♪ I'm a superstar, a rock 'n' roller
I don't want him to move back to his hometown...
It sucks when the dude you like has to move back, doesn't it?
♪ A perfect, flawless rock 'n' roller (but we gals don't give a damn!)
Yeah, you feel so lonely
It's depressing, let's stop talking about it
Aiming high, aren't you?
He's getting greedy
Sorry but, gonna stake it all on this
Seems fair
Not a single 30 from the start
Woah, he got so close!
Zero, huh...
I got a zero
He got a zero at the end? Man, it's so fun to play with this dude
What the hell?
Translation & edit by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Typesetting & QC by RIDDELL
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
EXTRA FOOTAGE FOR THIS EPISODE AVAILABLE @ SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
PATREON.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
SPECIAL THANKS TO RIDDELL FOR TYPESETTING THIS EPISODE!!
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FAN-TRANSLATION MADE BY A FAN FOR OTHER FANS. ALL COPYRIGHT ARE RESERVED TO THEIR RESPECTIVE OWNERS.
TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNOISES