First time on Gaki No Tsukai,
Sushizanmai Marathon 100.000 yen prize
Tokyo 23 Wards, 31 Stores Total Challenge
Thank you, this is our 3rd challenge,
This is gonna be tough
Yes.
We had Gyoza,
We had Gindako, and this time, it's Sushi
This time let's get it
Easy for you to say, we're the ones eating
No no no
Matsumoto-san is on a break right now, so this time,
"Please!", "Please let me take part!"
Amazing
Did he really say that
Let's introduce the special guest, let's welcome this person!
Why?
We're counting on you!
Why Umemiya-san?
SPECIAL GUEST:
Tatsuo Umemiya
"Why Umemiya" you say,
In the past, I took part in a food show,
Oh yeah you did
Leave the eating to me
Of course
I'm a man
But you were younger back then?
In terms of capacity
Doesn't matter!
Don't comment on my age!
Now that Umemiya-san is with you,
The average age has become 48!
It went up so high!
No youngsters here
FORTY EIGHT?
Endo:
Age 39
Hamada:
Age 47
Hosei:
Age 42
Tanaka:
Age 39
Tatsuo:
Age 72
We looked at other variety shows, and none of them have an average age that high
Typeset by GakiDave
Translation by senor_wristband
Narrator: This time, the challenge is to eat at 31 Sushizanmai locations,
Narrator: Starting at Shinbashi, they aim for #31, Akabane
Narrator: At every store, they must work together to finish this Tuna set to continue
Narrator: If they make it through all 31 stores, they win 100,00 yen,
Narrator: But if one person gives up the challenge ends
Whoever gives up must pay for all the sushi eaten so far
License: Near NTV, the first store, Shinbashi
It's the first store, so let's get through it quickly
Let's go
Let's not take up too much time
"No Laughing Hotel Man is on @ 00:00!"
"Website -> TV -> NTV -> Gaki no Tsukai"
Let's go
I'm so hungry
I'm SO hungry
So let's begin,
Yama-chan, remember your words,
I won't forget
Don't give up at the 3rd store
I'll go for 31 stores, I really wanna eat
Narrator: Yamazaki is excited for the fat rich Otoro, starting off with Sushizanmai's special Tuna Set
Narrator: Will these 5 finish the challenge for the first time?
So, this is the first plate of the day
Look delicious!
So starting from the elderly
Elderly?
No no, I mean,
Cause he's our senior
I mean starting from the Senpai of course
I'm very senior to you guys of course
Any is good?
Go ahead,
Then, the Akami
Ah of course
So, excuse me,
Oh, right
Chu-toro!
I wanna go for the fat rich ones early
I see
Alright, I'll get the fatty toro
This is delicious!
It's so good!
I like this one
Eh, that one?
The Otoro and the rolls are still left
Tanaka you can have both
But still
What? This is your chance
It's really good
Can't we just call this lunch and end here?
That would be a simple fun TV show
It's so good
But still, these are still left
Then Endo can eat them
Really? OK
I'll eat one for now
Eating 3 is good too
Oh, but that's... everyone?
3 is one serving
Why are you guys already calculating at the first store?
Endo is like Gaki's "Top Batter"
Yeah he is, on this show
Go ahead
It's still the first store after all
OK everyone, let's continue
Let's go to the next store
Yummy, yummy
It's tasty
This is easy
Shinbashi-ten store was a piece of cake,
They aim for the next store, in Roppongi, Hayuzamae location
Licence? This is too easy
Really?
It's too easy?
Sorry, sorry
You might just end up broadcasting us having a nice meal
Yeah
There's no conflict
There's no obstacles
No obstacles
But right now I really wanna eat
Yeah, of course, we've only been to one store
Soon we'll arrive at the second store
OK, this is the Roppongi intersection, we're almost there
Yippee! Roppongi!
Let's breeze through this one
Yes
Let's go
It's here. Thank you.
Here it comes!
I'll get the fatty ones, I'm quite hungry
Ah, I get that choice
Fatty Toro
You're going for it Hosei-san
That's your second time!
In a row
cause it was delicious
So well, uhh
Delicious!
So,
The Akami
What should we do with this
I'll have 1 for now
But you told us you were hungry
Yup, you did
It'll mess up my pace, pushing on needlessly is no good
What happened? What happened at this sushi lunch?
He's so different from the last place
Why, before this Sushi?
Please go ahead
We ate last time, and I already know how it tastes
But of course, the senpais...
Yes that's good, you can taste it
You can have it, I am you junior of course
OK!
So easy, god damn. We can totally do this.
I'm so hungry~
Everyone manages to finish
They head to a store nearby, also in Roppongi
Let's go in.
Sorry for the wait,
I had Akami last time right
Ah, chu-toro!
Ahhh,
Yama-chan always takes this. (Aburi)
I'll take the ootoro.
The Akami
The Negitoro
Just these left
So what shall we do here?
You didn't eat these last time right?
I did not, yes
Ok, excuse me,
Well it's still the 3rd store, can I have this?
So Hosei-san will
Endo
Alright, no problem look
It's a big piece
It's no problem
This is easy
This is a good pace huh
This is going pretty well
A good 3rd store
I think when we did Takoyaki the 3rd store was already...
We were forcing through it
Making good progress till now, they head into the Ginza 7-chome store
Mm!  Delicious!
Everyone gulps down the Tuna,
But the fatty sushi eating Yamazaki,
starts to feel a little worried
Finished!
OK we did it
Let's go!
OK, OK, this is easy
2 minutes till we get there, Yurakucho store
Right beside this hotel, let's go
5th store, Yurakucho
We can make it to the next one, the next one for sure
That was fast.
Which one have I not eaten yet
Tatsuo-nii, you haven't eaten this right?
Aburi.
Then I'll have that
He got the Aburi
I'm going for the Akami
I'm taking the ootoro, haven't had it yet
I'll have the chu-toro.
Now, Yamazaki, who has his first Akami, utters these words,
Hold on, eating the Aburi, twice in a row,
It's heavier than I expected
It's delicious, but more than I thought, but it's still...
While Yamasaki voices his concerns, Tanaka finishes the three rolls by himself
Rolls OK
Finished!
Until now, Hamada and Tetsuo have had a balanced selection, but Yamasaki has been eating fatty sush, like Aburi-toro & Otoro
They head to the 6th store, AKIBA location
But then,
Of course
You can't keep eating the Aburi, Chutoro, and Otoro
The Aburi gets you
You have to plan it out
Sometimes there's oil on the plate
I get chills when I see that
And yet, you ate it like 2 to 3 times in a row
"Delicious!" "This is delicious!"
He did say that
And suddenly he switched to the Akami!
That's where it started
I'm not making excuses or anything like that, I like Akami
If XXXX was here, he'd kill you where you stand
"This fucker, switching from this to that"
"This conniving bastard!"
Since it seems nobody wants to choose the fatty sushi, a new rule is introduced
If all 5 members choose a seperate card, they can eat whatever they chose
But if anyone matches, there will be 1 extra Sushi to eat of that type
They arrive at AKIBA. Whatever will happen?
It's best not to match right?
It's better not to match
Please go ahead and choose,
I don't really get it, I'll do this once, and then complain later
Please don't complain
So choose which one you want to eat, but don't match
So you might have to consider what other people might choose as well
I see
It's like a game almost
We flip on "Ready, go" right?
Yup. Everyone has chosen, so let's go,
Ready....go!
Aburi-toro
Akami
Chutoro
Otoro
Yama-chan!
Wait Hamada-san you've eaten this already!
Wow there's two of them
Consequently, the Negitoro is still left
Cause I keep eating them, it's starting to take a toll
So the Negi-toro, everyone can decide,
Who's gonna eat it?
It's OK to go ahead
Alright then, I'll have it
Does the Senpai wish to-
No that's alright, Iater, later,
Still have plenty of time
Here, Endo will eat it.
It hits you all of a sudden
The next store is at the top of this building
Really?
We'll go upstairs here
Ah this thing? Sushizanmai
This is a revolving sushi
Even though they just finished the 6th store,
They soon reach Akiba's revolving Sushizanmai
Here, the newly introduced rule brings suffering to the 5!
Well, for now,
For now, make your choice,
(They are all saying "Don't match the cards")
This is also teamwork
I don't wanna match
So choose please,
Here we go......ready, flip!
Akami and Aburitoro matched!
Hamada-san! That's...
You gotta cut it out man
Matching as a duo is the worst
We matched as a duo
There's gonna be a lot left on the plate
Two of each of those
Cause they matched
That one and that one?
Uwahh, I see
Why don't you feed us this stuff, so much variety
We wanna try other stuff too
Negitoro.......ootoro....
Woah, there's a lot
Please, dig in
This is Aburi?
So I'll have this Akami
It seems the Otoro and Negitoro will be left over
I can eat whenever
Ah, OK then
Can you eat them please?
There's too much this time
It's tiny!
That one?
Even though the Negitoro was closer to him
He ignored that area
Then I'll also have this
Oh he's got the Negitoro!
The Negitoro too?
The teamwork is good here
Amazing teamwork
You guys are supporting each other
We can do it if we work hard
On the way back to the bus, Hamada's senility acts up
We didn't go to this Sushizanmai?
We were just here. Hamada-san?
It's that
The root
The trial, we need to put him on trial
Double. Right now was a double.
What else happened?
"We didn't go here?"
He's getting the death penalty
"We should go here" he said as he tripped on the root
We didn't go to this Sushizanmai?
We were just here. Hamda-san?
On the way to the 8th store in Ueno, Hamada complains about the harsh rules
Give everyone cards separately
That's right
That way, we only have to worry about what's leftover
Endo-san, you're still fine?
Totally fine
Tanaka-san?
Easy, so easy
Umemiya-san?
Well since you guys added that matching game,
And because of that, I'm losing confidence if we can make it to 30 stores
So that means, that's your trick,
You guys are making it harder for us to get the 100,000 yen
Exactly
It's Obvious!
It's obvious!
With the team unity solidified, they reach the 8th store in Ueno, near Ueno Park
This delicious looking sushi, Aburi-toro and Otoro with plenty of fat
Who will eat it this time?
I will NOT match
Alright I'm ready, if it's this
That was quick
I've already decided, I decided on the bus
If mine matches it's gonna suck
Ready....flip!
Negi-toro, negi-toro, aburi-toro, aburi-toro, and Akami
You haven't changed it all!
Hosei!
He thought someone would eat the Chutoro
Are you trying to take it easy by eating lean meat?
No it's not like that,
Honestly, I am kind of feeling full now
This thing, this Aburi-toro
They're already ready
So everyone, eat what you're supposed to
So Umemiya-san and I have to finish these ones
There's so many
Lots of Chu-toro and Otoro
With the remainder, if everyone eats 1 piece that'll work out nicely
Should I go for 1 Negi-toro?
Go ahead
Really?
Yes, go ahead
TN: Hosei ate the smaller roll that isn't Negi-toro
OH, he already ate it!
He ate it, and then looked
All you do is try to take it easy
Fine, I'll go for this
And there's one left of those
I got it, I understand
You can still eat?
Absolutely
OK, finished!
So they head from Ueno to the 9th store in Asakusa
So I just heard some information,
Umemiya-san, your dad was a doctor?
Yup
Eh? Really?
My dad is a doctor, I don't think that's very special though
Did he want you to follow his footsteps?
Well yes, at first
I told him, "Just 1 year"
To enter this business
And 1 year passed,
I thought of quitting,
It was almost time to fulfill my promise,
But you did as you pleased
In the end though, I selfishly kept going
Selfish?
I mean, in that situation, by that point
When you're on a boat at sea, you can do whatever you want!
Whatever you want? Could you give an example
"If you're on a boat you can do anything"
I was invited onto a Cruiser-style boat,
TN: I may have missed the joke here
A girl came on board saying "Hiiii!",
and she was prepared
What do you mean by that
They get on board understanding everything
The fatty Aburi-toro and Otoro are hitting like a Body Blow
They head into the Asakusa store, near Asakusa Engei Hall
What you want to eat,
Choose please
That was quick
Yeah it was
Hosei-san?
Let's go!  Ready..........flip.
Otoro, Akami... The Akami matched! Who is it?
These two
Can someone do something about him?
He doesn't change it
Cut it out already please
Let go of the Akami!
Us three could have been consecutive
Yeah you're right, it would have made a good continuation
It should have ended with the Negitoro
Yeah exactly
So 4th time these two have matched on Akami. Right?
And ... Endo-san you had Aburi?
This is Chutoro
I'll take the oo-toro.
Hamada-san got the tekka-maki.
Oh! Hosei-san got it too!
He feels guilty
I'll go
Negitoro for Tanaka-san
Amazing. The power of Friendship
Ugh, I hate Yama-chan
I will not match anymore
That's cause ... I got it
If you got what you wanted, next time,
You have to choose a different one
That's good
Yup
I think that's good, Hosei-san please,
No, I
I literally, shuffle the cards and pull one out
I don't think that's right
You should be choosing the card
You should think about it
You have to pick something different
That way, when we choose seperate cards, it'll feel good right?
The taste will change too
Near by the Skytree which is under construction, they arrive at Kinshicho
This time, they don't want to match,
Everyone, we're here.
Lets pick different cards from last time
I'm gonna shuffle
Can you judge his shuffling
I'm shuffling for real
If it's Akami, it's not my fault OK
Alright. Have you chosen?
Okay then, let's go
We even tried, to differentiate it
Ahh damn, this is how it turned out
But still, it's one additional per match
But the Otoro,
Aburi, and the rolls will be left
I'm really full
He said, totally said it
Yama-chan... C'mon man!
You said you were hungry
Make me work hard
What do you mean "Make me work hard"
Just do it
(selecting the sushi from the card)
The Negitoro matched three times, but it's only increased by 1
I haven't eaten Negitoro
Oh, in that case,
Mmm, it's good
Tanaka-san?
This Aburi
This, this roll
I'll get the roll as well
Hamada-san got 2
If you keep this up, you will surely recieve heavenly punishment
Do you remember the Yama-chan daruma gag?
That's good, they're laughing, it's the Yama-chan Daruma
Thank you very much
I did good here, right?
Alright, I got it,
I'll help you out as much as I can
Thank you very much
You're so different now from before!
You should be helping him out!
Well, if he wants to help me...
Just for a little bit, let me take a break
Break?!
I, I will still take part of course, but ,
What the hell are you saying?
Next week, they head towards Tsukiji
The 5 head towards a Tuna butchering!
And finally, their stomachs at the limit
Will they be able to finish?