First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai Ya Arahende!
Let's play with table games from around the world!!
I've already said it, but isn't this going to be a discarded episode?
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Discarded episode?
Is it?
It must be, right?
Tsukitei Housei
Is that so?
No way that's how it is!
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
I mean we don't have much time to do this
We have to try at least
We must do our best here
I'm excited for this!
So, we've gathered all those game here, right?
Right, from all around the world
What a lame ass hairstyle you have
Give me a break
Please don't say it's lame
I have them shaved only on this side
You know, on last week's episode of "Yamehende"
I thought it could be funny or make them laugh
And so I cut them a bit here
It was funny, right?
Is that the sound a cooler makes?
The air conditioner?
He said "cooler"
Can you hear that?
"Cooler"
He must be like "shit, I said cooler"
Wouldn't "air conditioner" be better?
Air condtioner, right?
It's a matter of period
Times have changed
His household character just surfaced
Let's play play with table games from around the world~!!
Play with the game which caught your attention between the
note: voice = same as black text
the 16 collected from around the world!!
If there's something you'd like to know
Yes
Feel free to ask Naoki Tanaka
Naoki knows them?
I've learned them, more or less
Tanaka understood and learned the rules beforehand from an expert
You mean...
The games from the world, yes
I must say
Some of them seem pretty entertaining
There surely are
Is there some of them you'd like to try?
You know them all for real, Tanaka?
Yeah, I kinda know how to explain their rules
The hell is this?
This one's floating for real!
It is
Aladdin?
It's floating!!
Yeah that's it
It's a game from the Netherlands
From the Netherlands?
There's a magnet here
The S pole and the N pole
Are pulling each other here
You can barely see that
So, there are various items here
Each one will place a treasure in turn, the person who will make it fall will lose
It's a game about placing the treasures over the flying carpet
Netherlands  Aladdin's Flying Carpet
One by one, we'll place them over the carpet
And the person who'll make it fall
Cause it can't withstand the weight, will lose
I see
It's pretty simple
It is, really
It's a simple balance game
Yes
Why is there this wire thingy attacched here?
If there was no wire, the carpet would just collide with the magnet
It's pulling it away from it
So it's not floating
The wire is pulling the carpet to stop it at the very limit
That's not really interesting anymore...
Huh? Why?!
That's not the interesting part of it!
That's not it!
"Toilet trouble"
Right
This looks fun
You spin this roulette here...
This one raises the bar
If it stops here, you press the level three times
Under
stood
At some point of time, the washlet will be activated
Flush the toilet as many times as the number on the roulette shows
Once it will reach the randomly set number of times, it will spray water on the loser's face
U.S.A.  Toilet Trouble
And you'll get your face wet
I see
So it's a russian rosh-- washlet
Exactly
Right
It's a Wushian Washlet...
Translation & Subtitles by Shion
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
So, Matsumoto-san
Yes
Let's just leave everything to Tanaka-san
Let's do it
Let's have him bring here his own recommended ones
We're going to have a positive vibe about this
Of course
Alright
I really want us to have fun today
With all our might
Yes, positively
Please be positive about this
We can't say something like "this is stupid"
Yes, you're right
Yeah let's avoid such things
Let's avoid that
We have to think of it as being a troublemaker for the show
Exactly
Like, avoiding "what the hell!" or such
I see, positive about it
Got it, a good vibe
You're the most-likely-to-say-it type, though
From the start
You've been complaining all day about this!
Which is our first one?
The one we've been talking about before
The one from the Netherlands...
That was the most non-enjoyable-looking among them
Don't say that!!
Can't we just stop this?
Don't say that!
Say what?
What yo
u said
So it's not ok to that degree either?
Of course it's not
We said "positively"
We haven't started yet and you're already complaining
Each one will place a treasure in turn, the person who will make it fall will lose
It's a game about placing the treasures over the flying carpet
Netherlands  Aladdin's Flying Carpet
note: narrator voice = same as text
I can't see them (the objects)
Yes, we're not supposed to know what we'll get
Oh, I see!
Makes sense
It'd be more fun this way
Sounds fun!
So, how about we start a round from here?
Nu-huh
Huh?
Let's start from here, clockwise
Yeah that's important
So, from Yama-chan?
No, make it start from me
Wait a moment
Isn't that strange?
It's way too weird to leave me out like this
So, from Tanaka w-
If we can't see them, the person beside should hold it
Oh, so we just have to stick our hand inside
Oh, I see, good point
As if it's closed
Starting from here, ok?
From Tanaka
Clockwise, ok?
Let's have Hamada holding the bag
Let's have Hamada holding the bag when Tanaka has to extract one
W-wait wh-
Why must there be rules for both this game and for this bag?
He's right, that will complicate things
Wouldn't it be good?
Well...
Let's--- let's just make a round this way
Enough, let's start from there even though it bugs me
Just like this
So, from Endo
From Endo..?
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'll quit it
I'm ready now!!
It's fine from Tanaka
But I hate things like that!!
I'm done, come on Endo
Alright alright
If it falls will it-- wait
First off we have...
A treasure box
Is this going to be hard?
This should be easy
Ok, it's my turn
It didn't budge
How much will it take to make it fall?
Yeah
Here comes the presbyopia...
It's a jar
I think
Anyway, it looks like it
Yes
Done
So that's how it goes
Hurry up and take it
Me?
He should...
Yeah but the person beside should hold it
I'm talking about the bag, hold it so I can extract
I see
You just said it
Let's stop acting this way please!
Let's stop talking this way
The atmosphere is so friggin' stiff!
Let's stop with such conversations!
It's not like it, I mean---
Geez
That's what you just said!
I mean
It was you who suggested to have the person beside to hold the bag
He has always been right beside me and had no clue
Looks like a gem
It's a jewel
It seems so
It's getting riskier
Yes, the problem is where to place it
Ok Matsumoto-san
He just got a sort of beetle
It's a beetle
It's a sign of good luck
I must balance it
Yes, it's getting heavier
The carpet is even spinning around
And there's also the air conditioner
I see
Alright
Looks safe
They easily manage to place 13 treasures over the carpet
They kept on placing the treasures
And gathered them all without making it fall!
What? It holds them perfectly fine
It's perfectly safe
What the hell?
I'm going for it
See? Perfectly fine
It's shaking though
We had each type
What if we end up placing them all?
Yeah what if?
They have placed 26 treasures on it! Only 5 items left...
Even more items are placed without problems, only 5 remains
We kinda placed em all
Should this happen?
Really
What's this?
Never played it before so I don't know
Here comes
You placed it so fast
Like, "plop"
You can do it that way?
Of course
This one looks bad!
This one seems to be pretty heavy
There it is, must be it!
This one is risky, Matsumoto-san
Here we are
This is bad
There's not even much space left
Why would you fall on me?
You did good to this point, come on
This carpet can't sense the mood at all
The next game Tanaka chose is
Catch the right answer before anyone else!
Ghost Blitz - Germany
Let me set this
This one
Already looks more enjoyable
What is this?
There's a bottle and...
...a ghost?
Yes
Also a chair, a book and a mouse
Yeah, it's a mouse
You have to memorize each shape and color of them
After that, cards like this one will be flipped over
For example, we have a red sofa here
It's exactly as that
Right
In case like this, you just go for it
Who grabs it first wins
This element makes it pretty similar to Karuta
Exactly
However
So that's how it works
There are other direct cards like this red sofa one
Yes
And these
Bottle and book
A red book
And a gray bottle
So it's not this
Right
This bottle is green
In cases like this
First of all, which one is red? It's the sofa
Yeah it's the sofa
And which is the book? it's blue, but it's still here
It's on the card
The bottle's color is different too, but it's still on the card
And which one is grey? It's the mouse
So, which is the only one missing?
I see!
It's the white ghost! 'Cause there's no white and no ghost!
This is...
Nice choice!!
Thank you so much!!
It makes you use your head
Thank you so much
It seems so good!
I wonder if we can make it
I love this type of games!
You have to use your brain
It's good, it's good!
The missing one?
For example, in the case of the bottom-left card
There's a blue book among the five pieces
So you must grab the blue book piece to win
However, in case like this one where there isn't
anything matching both color and shape of the pieces
By choosing the mouse, whose shape and color doesn't appear in the card, you win
Focus on shapes and colors
It's only one?
Yes, just one
Can't happen to have 2 of them?
Can't happen
The answer is always in a single object
Alright, let's do this!
I'm pumped!
You join us too, Tanaka?
Yep
Yes
Where are you placin--
Ouch that hurt
Can't be helped
We're fighting each other
You grabbed the back of my hand so firmly
This game is going to be intense
This is the matching piece, right?
Yeah, the mouse is white, can't be it
You were pretty quick
Ok
Here comes
Ready, 2, 1, here!
Which one is it?
What is it?
It's not this one, right?
It's this
Here
I think that's wrong
The book is green
But it's not there
The bottle
But there's green, the book is green
You're right
It's red
It's red!
It's the red sofa
This is...
It was that one
Red, right?
It's missing!
We're such a bunch of old geezers !!
True
We all froze up!
Even Tanaka's judgement was slow
Alright alright
Let's go!
Here
It's this
Oh, right
It's that, right?
It's the mouse
- The mouse
There's no grey either, that's it
Right! It's the grey mouse
This one's not there either
The bottle?
Wait a moment...
It's the bottle!
The bottle!
Wait a second
Must be
the bottle
(staff) The right answer is the ghost
The ghost!?
Oh, it's the ghost!
Is it?
That's right
It's the ghost
It's in plain sight too
It's the ghost!
Wait a moment...
You're playing dirty!
You should have told me when I was like "look at how good I am!"
None of our heads realized that
This is pretty hard!
Yeah it is
It's fun
It is
Ready? Here we go
This one, right?
What are you lookin' at?
It's that one
The ghost
I'm not following this
The ghost is the same as the card
Exactly the same
Yes
I see
You only picked up ghosts !!
Only ghosts on his side
You're right
Two cards two ghosts
I got it, I got it
No it's n-- oh that's it
Endo got it
Yes
Yeah that's it
You just took the ghost again
You must be thinking "whatever, just lemme take my ghost"
But I see
Yeah, that's what this german game's about
It's fun
After this, even more
Even more bizarre overseas games will appear !!
Unthinkable games from outside Japan will be presented!
Lay face down your cards without being find out!
Schlafm端tze - Germany
The next game Tanaka chose is Schlafm端tze, from Germany
Let me explain the rules a bit
There are several kids
wearing night caps
Each one of you will receive 5 cards
And the first one of you
who will line up 4 cards
with different colors of kids wearing the same hat
Without shouting "I've lined them up" or such
Must just quietly lay their cards face down
So...
After that
Those who notice the player who layed em down
Even if they haven't lined up the 4 cards
Have to quietly lay their own cards face down too
And in the end
The last one who can't lay them down will lose
What the hell?
I don't understand it
Is it a deceiving game?
Seriously, I have no clue
It's a deceiving game
It's fun, I promise
Trust me, you won't notice if someone lets them down quietly
Are you for real?
I totally would notice it
For example, if someone
Finds out Hamada-san layed them down
Can lay theirs down too, even if he hasn't matched anything
And Housei-san who saw him laying them down, can do the same
And if for example Matsumoto-san doesn't notice and
lays them down last, he'll lose
However, last thing
We don't have to play it quietly
We'll pass each other the cards
So it's a deceiving game
while having a normal conversation
Collect 4 cards with the same type of hat and lay them face down
If you notice the first one to do so, you can face down yours too
Germany  Schlafm端tze
Gather 4 cards with the same type of nightcap
And lay them face down
The last one to notice that will lose, it's a bizarre game
The last one who doesn't lay them face down will lose
However it can unexpectedly turn out to be full of climaxes!
Can we look at them?
Sure
It could be you already have them now
It may be
Here
Can I see it?
Yes, place it with yours, discard one and pass it to Hamada-san
I'm taking the one you don't need
You see, we're
supposed to play it while chatting
Right, right
While we talk, huh...
It is necessary, right?   - Yes
Is your hairstyle ok?--
Don't you think this year's been kinda dry?
Yeah it has been   - Right?
It's been pretty arid
The humidifier I have in my house
Yes?
Is not really helping that much
Oh I see
So, only one can't do the job?
I guess that applies to Yamazaki's house
Are you for real?
I heard it's pretty big
What? Are you for real?
What are you saying?
I'd love to visit your house once
Right, I'd love to see it myself
I think we can schedule an episode set in his house
Let's do it
Can we?
I want to
I'd love to see it, really
I mean, if we have to do this
Wouldn't it be better at Tanaka's house?
No way no way no way
You can't just "nowaynoway" us
We're talking about houses after all
You can't back off
That's Tanaka for you
He wouldn't let us in?
Hm, yeah
No way
You mean his house?
His wife would get mad
Yeah she would
I never saw her mad though, I wouldn't know
Wait a sec... I have now 1, 2, 3...
This is actually my sixth card
What?
Gimme a break
(counting)
(staff) You have them right
Something's wrong
If he passes one, he's back to five
He would have 5, it's ok
If he passes one
And I have to get 4 of them    - Yes
Come on, Endo...
But we have to get 4, right? 4 is ok?
Yes
That's all there is about the rules
You make me wanna quit this
Haven't you got the rules?
That's not it
It's just, that's hard
We haven't matched anything yet
Yeah, that's the timing for the game
It's pretty hard
Could it be that we end up stuck in a loop?
Yeah, me too, this...
...oh, I see
Come on, stop it!
Stop it!
WHAT THE HELL !!
He didn't notice at all!
Wait a minute, wait wait wait
What's so funny about it ?!
He shouted "of course I'll notice!" before!
He did
How is this funny?
What are you saying?
Someone got 4 right? You can't place
them down otherwise, right?
I did, I---    - He's the first-
So being that someone got them
I ended up losing, right?
Can I...?
I've gathered these 4 cards
And I got this spare one
So you closed the round
He layed them down
Yes, I was done
It's ok
And after him Hamada-san layed them down, right?
Yes
I saw that and
I was like "oh shit"
Me too, I saw Hamada's face going like "oh shit"
And went "oh shit" myself
That's how it is
What the hell is this game ?!
That's a bit...
What the hell is this game!
It's not like we can make it clear we won
Exactly, just lay them down
You have to get it
Let's try again, one more time please
That's amazing
But really
Why haven't you noticed we layed them face down?
I was really getting into the conversation
5 cards each
It went so smoothly
I was absorded in our chatter
I wasn't focusing on the game
Schlafm端tze - Round 2
And so they're ready for a second round
Let's start from me, ok?
He's so friggin' motivated now
I see, we don't have them
Yeah we just started, it's all about the timing
We should have all different types now
Third Round
You know I'm surprisingly good at Othello?
Me too actually
For real?
Yup
Nah, I'm positive I'm better
I let the corners be mine
That's normal
That's the game
You let them be yours?
By the opponent?
Yes
You do?
Is that so?
That's how it is
And you can win by that?
I can
Normally that's what they'd aim
It's to find a way to win
Can you win by that?
I could
You'd just be convinced you are winning
Really...
I may be left with tons of them
And you win by that
What do you mean by making me win?
I mean, leading me to victory
Oh, that?
Yep
That was frightening! It startled me!
Who was it?
Hamada?
Was it Hamada-san?
Yes, it was Hamada-san!
You're right
Yup, he got 4 of them
You're all good at this
You rushed pretty hard before
It was quick
I broke my coldest sweat
Makes you wanna rush
My heart was racing like crazy!
The hell is this game!? It's so weird !!
It's so fun
I'm glad we did this, but it was really strange
I like it
Toilet Trouble - U.S.A.
Your face is gonna get sprayed with toilet water!
Their next challenge will be U.S.A.'s Toilet Trouble
Here it is, I knew it
It was about time to try the U.S.A.'s
How close to it?
A bit more, close to the roulette
Do we spin it?
Yes
Two
Two times, huh...
So he must press it twice?
Yeah that's it
Here I go
Go
Wait...
Ok, it's safe
It splashes after the sound?   - Yes
Ok safe, Endo-san is safe
For now
Hamada-san is next
Me!?
Yes
I don't think it was that surprising
I thought Tanaka would do it
It's anti-clockwise from me
No need it to spin it so much
This is?
It's three
What a moron
Here he goes
Here?
Yes, should be fine there
First one is safe
I wonder if the water
Will splash him
The second flush is safe too
Third time
What the-?
Wow!
He's quite lucky!
No doubt about it
Matsumoto-san, please
He did good
Three, it's three times
Like this?
A bit closer
Go
Oh, here it comes
Did it?
I mean, it was so fast I don't even know
It splashed just a bit
What a bad timing
It wasn't
even
that funny...
Next up will be a famous game from Russia!
It's time for a popular russian game !!
What is this?
Give a name to everyone! Can you remember them all?
Nanja-Monja - Russia
This is
"Nanja-Monja"
There are 12 types of characters  - Ok ok ok
In order, we flip a card like this
And we gave a nickname to the character on it
Each one of us will do so in round
And one by one we keep on giving nicknames
To the characters we draw
And you have to remember them
Remember them?!  - Yes
So for example
If you draw
The same card on the table
The first one to say its nickname
First one to say it wins
wins the round
Ok, let's do this
So we must remember them?
Yes   - Ok, good
Just make up some names
give a nickname to the character on the card you draw
Nanja-Monja - Russia
note: voice = roughly same as black text
from the deck, the first one to say its name will win
when a card with a character you've already named is drawn
We're placing the deck here
And flip them
Ok
"Coldy"
COLDY
Coldy
Coldy?
Coldy...
No wait, "Okubo"
OKUBO
Wait a moment...
I thought it was "Coldy"
"Coldy Okubo" then
Coldy Okubo?!
COLDY
OKUBO
That's long!
Coldy Okubo
What the hell
May I?
Yes
From here?
This is "Homa-son"
HOMA-SON
Homa-son...
Here I go
Googala
GOOGALA
HOMA-SON !!
COLDY-OKUB-- No wait
Coldy Okubo? Really?
He said Coldy Okubo!
What should I do? Should I take this?
The first one who said it wins
I said it, didn't I?
I said it! It's Homa-son
You said it?
Homa-son
Ok, Housei-san
Let's reset it, shall we?
Ok, reset
I don't like the way he comes up with nicknames
It's not easy to understand clearly what he's sayin
You speak that way so only you can understand?
He's right
Shall we start from me?
Ok
Here goes
"Ichimaso-chan"
What?
ICHIMASO-CHAN
Ichimatsu?
note: they're complaining over the fact that Ichimaso isn't a real name, while Ichimatsu is
Ichimaso-chan
IchimaSO?
Come on, this is irritating!
Wouldn't Ichimatsu do it?
The hell is "Ichimaso"?
I-chi-ma-so-chan?
Ichimaso-chan?!   - Ichimaso-chan
I-chi-ma-so
The hell is the deal with "Ichimaso"?
I'm going
ICHIMASO-CHAN !!
You didn't even say it
He said it, Ichimaso-chan
He's the only one who didn't say "Ichimaso-chan"
I couldn't see it!
You covered it with your hand!
Everyone said it but he couldn't say "Somaso-chan"
The hell is Somaso-chan now?!
They'll challenge the russian pie game !!
That one caught my attention, how about we do it?
The one from U.S.A.?
Pieface! - U.S.A.
Pies fly on your face in this heart-throbbing game!
Which one?
U.S.A. made loads of games, huh
Oh, that one?
Let's start from Yamazaki, we never did it before
Alright
Oh, that's the deal?
This will be our last one, I'd hate it if it sucks
I bet this is going to be disappointing
You're right, we're about to end
I don't want this
This is something
Move your head there and pull the lever
Here I go
Two
Pull it
The other way
One...
Good   - Mh
The eeeeeeeeeend!
WE DID IT !!
SHOW SUPPORT BY LIKING / FOLLOWING ETC. ETC.
SOME AD I WAS TOO LAZY TO REMOVE, HERE'S MORE SPAM:
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT TRANSLATION BY A FAN FOR OTHER FANS
WWW.FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
WWW.SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
WWW.TWITTER.COM/FGRNDNoises