Where is Downtown?
- They have not come yet.
- They are both not here yet.
But I don't think they will miss work.
- Are they camping today?
- I have heard that from them.
Maybe they really won't come.
I think they're already close.
- Hi.
- Hello!
Sorry for the wait.
Hamada hasn't come yet.
But I have something to tell you first.
What's going on?
Yoshimoto Kogyo is hectic right now.
To put it simply, Hamada's sex drive has not subsided.
Does he still have that kind of it?
I put him on the scale,
minus Hamada's sex drive,
and he weighed only 24lb (11kg).
His sex drive is so heavy...
And now he is being taken repeatedly by gossip magazine photographers.
Yoshimoto is desperately trying to hold him back.
Apparently he is being taken from a position around here these days.
Doesn't he notice the camera?
He is being taken between the FLASH and FRIDAY photographers.
The FLASH photographer has been caught in the FRIDAY photo.
Yoshimoto has managed to hold him in check now, but he is in danger if he continues like this.
So he needs to let off some steam.
Letting off steam of his desire?
I had a long talk with Hamada.
We talked for about two and a half days.
- That's a long time.
- Did you guys stay over and talk?
He wants to let off steam of it in the show.
I see. He wants to release it well.
He has a desire to lift up that now.
“Lift up that”?
He often says, "I haven't lifted up that recently.”
About what?
You know what I'm talking about.
He wants to lift up the man's desire.
But that cannot be done in these times.
But he was taken doing it by a photographer, and Yoshimoto  is hectic right now.
Has he done that already?
That is not good.
So, would you guys change into this?
I see.
It's okay. This will put Hamada in a better mood.
And everyone will be happy.
- I don't want it to be a big deal.
- Of course.
Then get changed in these.
- Okay.
- Shall we change over there?
- I'll hold this.
- Thanks.
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]
Oh, that's nice.
That's nice.
- Your personalities are showing through these.
- Really?
Yours is long.
Some are long, some are a little short.
I think that's good.
He would be rather embarrassed if all of you had short skirts.
Is that because it's deliberate?
I think it's very good.
You guys don't wear pantyhose?
Well, he doesn't like that.
He likes bare legs best.
- Okay, let’s make yakisoba.
- Yeah.
Let's do something camp-like.
- Hey.
- Hello.
Sorry to bother you.
We're camping today, what are you guys doing?
- We were thinking of making yakisoba.
- Okay!
Let's make it!
Okay, let's make yakisoba.
I don't know, I haven't done much camping.
Tanaka, do you know this?
I have some experience.
Let's put oil in first.
Can you put the bean sprouts in first?
Wouldn't it be better to put the meat first?
- Have you put the oil in already?
- Yeah.
It would be better to put the meat in too.
Thank you.
Hey, come here for a minute.
I place the water here.
What are they doing?
Not a chance!
I wasn't watching them enough.
I'll tell them that.
- They don't get it.
- I know.
Maybe you could put the meat in first.
Hey, wait a minute.
What are you guys doing?
About what?
Underware.
I'm wearing those.
He's not aroused by your underware at all.
He wants you guys to wear underware that are more arousing.
More arousing underants?
- Are you wearing your own underware?
- Yes.
That's no good.
He didn't have an erection at all!
I was thinking, "Hey, he doesn't have an erection at all.”
That's no good.
It’s not a release of it for him.
Yes...
I have prepared these.
- Wow, are you serious?!
- Put these on.
Are you serious?!
We should stop lifting that thing like this in these times.
So we alone have to fulfill his desires.
He was furious!!
His gums were bleeding.
He's incredibly angry.
Was he clenching?
He was bleeding from here.
- Scary!
- He is quite angry.
Just put them on.
Put them on right away.
Let's do it right away.
I thought you guys knew I didn't need to say this.
[3 minutes later]
We changed.
You okay?
- Did you put them on?
- Yes.
You don't have to do anything extra.
You don't have to remove the underarm hair.
That's realistic and good.
He said he likes hair.
Really?
- He said, "I like it better with it than without it.”
- He said that?
- Why did he talk you that?
- Then I guess it's good.
Then let's make yakisoba.
Let's do it.
After all, making yakisoba makes...
CAMP
YEHAAAAAAAHHHH!!
It's a beautiful day.
Should I get a plate for you, too?
I see. That's good.
I'll put this on a plate.
Thanks.
I'm sure you're all getting hungry.
I'll take the noodles out of the bag, too.
- What are you doing, Yamachan?
- Everyone find something to do.
Please tell me when to put the noodles in.
Can I put them all in?
Oh, it's all in.
You don't need to put water in it?
Thank you.
- Do you have any water?
- This sauce is powder.
Then put that in last.
What are these guys doing?
I think so too.
Sorry.
When they do that to me...
Come on, man.
i'm counting on you.
- It looks good.
- Can you put the sauce in now?
Should I put that in already?
Hey, hey, hey.
Wait a minute.
What are you guys doing?
He was so furious!
You guys didn't react at all!
No comedian would be okay with being seen in his underwear.
You guys are wearing women's panties.
And you guys have been seen by him.
If you didn't react when he saw them, he wouldn't be aroused at all.
Do you want him to see your underwear?
No!
You don't want him to see that, do you?
Your feelings of not wanting him to see it are the very reason he wants to see it!
All of those things combined make him more and more erect!
Do you understand that?
He was looking at it through the mirror trying to do something about it!
He was trying to get himself up!
But he couldn't do it, he said.
You guys were like wooden puppets.
That's not good.
That's like a brothel.
He wanted reality.
I didn't think it was a good idea.
Sorry.
You have to understand that.
Yes.
- I thought you guys wanted to be seen with it.
- It's not.
- It's not?  Then give him a reaction.
- Yes.
- Are you okay?
COME OOOOON!!
CAAAAAMP   YEAAAAAAAHHH!!
COME OOOOOON!!
So what are you guys making right now!?
We're making yakisoba.
- Hamada, you like yakisoba, right?
- Yeah!
Okaaaay!
The dish will be ready soon.
Now please put in the source.
Excuse me..., please don't do that.
Please wait just a little longer.
Oh, hey!
Hey, please really don't do that!
Please don't do that!
Okay, let's put the sauce in.
Please don't...
I think it's fried enough.
The sauce isn't mixed enough.
Matsumoto-san, let's play a game while they make this.
That's good.
We have Twister.
That’s nice.
Tanaka and Yama-chan, go over here and play Twister.
You guys go make it.
I spin the roulette.
First is Tanaka.
Stop.
Red.
Put your left foot on red.
Put your left hand on green.
Good.
Tanaka, put your right foot on red, too.
Tanaka, put your right foot on green.
Your right foot...yes.
Tanaka, react.
Please stop!
- Yamazaki, put your left foot on yellow.
- Yellow?
This posture is hard.
Tanaka, put your right hand on green.
Please stop! I'm embarrassing!
Please stop!
Please don't do that!
Please stop already!
Tanaka, are you okay?
Please stop!
He's a really troubled senior.
This is different.
It tastes better if it's slightly charred.
Yeah, I think so.
Hamada!
Hamada, hey!
I'll talk to them.
I'll talk to them very firmly.
Did we do something wrong?
Your reactions are still weak.
Please be more embarrassed
- More!?
- I was embarrassed enough.
But he did have one compliment.
Fujiwara's wedding ring got him aroused.
"Oh, are you married?”
Does he see these details?
He said it constantly.
He said Tanaka has a lot of problems.
I think I did the best I could.
Never show your bare butt.
That's extra!
“Extra”?
He wanted to see your butt!
But he doesn't really want to see it!
In fact, he does want to see it!
But he is trying to see it in hopes that you will not show it to him!
Can you understand his feelings!?
You have to understand those feelings of his!!
How many years have you guys been with him!!?
Don't make me say this to you any more!!
So sorry.
Matsumoto!
Yes, sir!
He said “yes sir.”
What's their hierarchy?
They don't need panties.
- Really?
- They don't need panties.
Otherwise they would not be embarrassed.
If they don't want me to see them, they should immediately cover them up with skirts.
It's your fault.
Is it our fault?
Hamada didn't want to do this.
What?
He said, "You guys don't need panties.”
Matsumoto-san, let's not do that!
I'm sorry, I refuse to do that.
He's serious.
- I'm really sorry about that.
- Let's apologize to him for once.
I can't say anything to him.
We'll talk to him directly.
I don't understand at all how we don't need pants.
I can't say anything to him.
So go directly to him.
Let's go, guys!
What?
So sorry.
We are going to react well and arouse Hamada-san.
So we want to put our panties on.
Wouldn't you guys be more embarrassed and work harder if you aren't wearing a skirt?
We are still trying hard enough.
No!! You guys didn't do it earlier!!
Next time we will do it well.
Shouldn't you guys be out there taking your panties off right now?
Please let us wear panties.
Why do you guys want to wear panties so badly?
That's because I'm embarrassed.
If I see it, what's the problem!?
Even so, I'm embarrassing not to wear panties.
I'm embarrassed even now.
- Then you have to react well.
- Yes!
- Can you guys do that?
- We can!
- You guys can do it, right?
- Yes!
Give us another chance.
You guys go back.
Hey, Matsumoto.
If they don't make it next time, I won't care about it anymore.
Tell them that again.
He said, I'll try one more time, but if you guys can't do it again, I'll have you do something new.
He said you guys could do without the skirts.
Then he can't lift up that.
I don't understand the purpose.
Doesn't he want to lift up the skirt?
I don't know the details either.
These things happen, don't they?
You know how sometimes you start out with a 60-minute course, but halfway through you want to make it a 90-minute course?
- So does he enjoy it?
- I don't know. That's half my guess.
He wants you guys to scream more.
He wants you to moan, doesn't he?
“Moan”?
Maybe he wants you to get high.
Anyway, let's do it.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Okay, let's get started!
We've cooked the yakisoba, we've done the twister, what's next?
How about a competition to see who can take the best selfie?
Let's do it!
Let's upload it to SNS.
Compete to see who can get the most likes?
I guess there is a trick to taking good pictures of this too.
Yes, you have to take into account the background and so on.
Come on!!
Come oooon!!
Don’t do that!!
The light is also...
They have no feelings of not wanting to be seen in their panties.
They think all they need is a loud voice.
It can't be helped.
You guys, gather around a minute.
After all, it can't be helped.
You guys didn't even moan.
I'm not sure what you mean by "moan.”
What does that mean?
- You wouldn't even know if you were asked to moan, because you can't do it.
- Sorry.
Take off your skirts.
Are you serious?
We're taking off our skirts?
Doesn't he want to lift up our skirts?
He seems to have gone to the NEXT STAGE.
Does he want to see our panties all the time?
What are we going to do?
We have no choice but to take off our skirts.
That's what he says.
And this year is Downtown's 40th anniversary.
You don't have any more demands from him, do you?
Of course.
There will be no more.
I'll think about how the staff might edit it, so take your skirt off for once.
This happens all the time, doesn't it?
You know, there are things that you take off on the site, but you don't know what will happen when it comes to the magazine
What are you talking about?
- What did you just talk about?
- What's he talking about?
Anyway, now you can gladly take off your skirt.
Do I take it off here?
- Can I take my skirt off here?
- Maybe it's okay.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm already embarrassed.
Would you like it like this?
Does he get aroused by this kind of thing?
That might be good.
- I think a little glimpse is good.
- I think he likes this kind of thing.
I hope this arouses him.
Then let's resume the selfie.
I bend down a little to take the shot.
Oh, that’s nice!
Nice!
Straighten up!
Don't bend over, assholes!
No!! Hamada-san!! I'm so embarrassed!!
I'm so embarrassed!!
Good!!
Yama-chan, good!!
You scored high.
Nice!!
Is this guy stupid?
- Oh, nice!!
- Endo, concentrate!
You're good too.
Concentrate!
Please don’t!
- Hang on, Fujiwara!
- No!!
Get him arouse!
Please don’t!!
Good!!
- Was that good?
- Good!!
- That was good.
- Today was very good.
It's been a long time since I've done something like this.
He's happy!
- There was no problem.  And they're happy too.
- Really?
They didn't mind doing it?
They're just pretending they don't want to do it.
They know what they're doing.
Okay, I'll give them a commendation.
- Commendation?
- It’s no wonder.
Stand up straight and show me your panties.
Stand up straight and show me your panties!!
Show me more, Yama-chan.
Right!
Certificate of Recognition,
Best Lifted Up Person Award.
Mr. Naoki Tanaka!!
You have done a very good job of being just the right amount of sexy without being overdone, while still maintaining a bit of tomboyishness.
In honor of your hard work, I present you with the award as the "Best Lifted Up Person."
From Downtown’s Masatoshi Hamada,
Yoshimoto Kogyo Corp. on November 13, 2022.
When I looked right down your skirt, your's was sticking out through the gap in your pants, and it was a hell of a thing!
I was so horny!!
Thank you!!
- Congratulations!!
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
- Congratulations!
Cherish it!
Matsumoto-san, please do it again next time.
Sure, I'll make sure to do so.
Do we have to do this again?
Of course.
They kind of look like they don't want to do it.
You want to do it, don't you?
Of course.
You can take Tanaka home with you.
That's not what you meant, is it?
What does that mean?
It's not?
- Okay, Tanaka, congratulations!
- Thank you!
Congratulations!
You might just win back-to-back championships in the next one!
Yes!
You guys have to BEAT Tanaka.
No, not in that way!
Yes!
Thank you!!
Thank you so much for today!
See you!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Do you guys need a lawyer?
- I would love to.
- Please.
We will file a class action lawsuit against him.
Even a new lawyer would be able to win against him.
We can definitely win.
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]