Fully Improvise Everything! Liar's Inn
I've heard the guy in the Funayssi costume is you
I was asked to do it for a while
An Impossible Project!
They gotta improvise based on a lie given to them
The Rule: Based on a card with a name and lie level
Either a massive, , plausible or small lie
The person on the card picks someone to continue a lie
Which line is it?
I'm not sure, I'm just sort of on the train
Tonight the exciting finale!
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
Alright, I'll go
Let's see this card
Matsumoto nominates someone to tell a massive lie
This is something that really shocked me,
I wouldn't have asked this if it wasn't for this episode,
Say, Yamasaki ... have you been smacked by a gorilla before?
Oh, is it alright if I talk about this?
A gorilla?
But Gorillas are really strong
Surely you'd die if one smacked you
Yeah, I wanted to confirm this,
Was it on a shoot?
It wasn't during a shoot
Eh? In your private time?
Eh eh eh eh?
Cause I thought this happened on a shoot
Yeah
No, it's actually, I couldn't talk about it before,
How did this happen?
It was at Hanshin Park,
Oh yeah I remember that place
It's gone now but,
They had cages with a male and female gorilla,
And they kept them apart for the most part
And then,
And it was during middle school, I went to Hanshin Park by myself,
And I went over to the gorillas,
And it just happend to be their spawning season
Spawning season?
They don't lay eggs
Cause Gorillas don't lay eggs, they don't have that...
I guess an analogy,
if they were fish I guess
Well yeah, to use a fish analogy,
Did the female gorilla look pregnant?
Her belly was massive
And I thought "Wow that's huge",
It was in the newspaper too
In the newspaper?...
But they kept the male and female seperate?
Yeah
That's why they separated them
Cause the male gorilla would freak out
Cause after all, once a gorilla sees a big belly,
It sets off their fighting instincts
So like, once the male gorilla saw that big belly of the female,
Cause he saw that belly
He ... started hitting
But they were seperated?
He's lost the plot
You said the female gorilla wasn't there
They seperated them
They did they did, but,
The other cage was just ahead, like this distance,
So the female gorilla started fighting-
Which one?
The m-m-male
The male?
The male
So the male saw the big belly of the female,
And it set off his fighting instincts
There's a lot of instincs here
But why?
So she has a baby bump?
You'd think a gorilla would understand that though
Well maybe it might be, the male gorilla,
He might feel like he has to protect the female gorilla
Ahh that makes sense
Maybe that's the main reason
I think that's the main reason
Ah, yeah maybe
You approached it?
I approached it
You went inside the cage?
I went inside the cage
Eh?
But you can't enter, surely?
That's not true right?
I-
The cage thing is a lie right?
Even on a shoot
Yeah, that's not possible
Sorry, my memories of that are really hazy
This sounds like a lie!
This is gotta be a lie!
No no, it's not a lie
Why did you go inside?
Is it because he smacked you?
Yes
You saved him there
I got smacked, so I forgot everything
Well-Alright fine you went inside
Well-
You got smacked? How?
How did you get smacked?
Well that's, like I said,
Gorillas go like this when they're angry
Like bears?
Like bears!
Gorilla really do that?
And then
"You bastard!"
It was as if he said that
I still don't understand why he was angry
But alright it doesn't matter
And then like,
He grabbed me from here
Woah that's dangerous
And then, with all of his force he smacked me down like,
Was the floor concrete?
That's gotta hurt like hell!
It hurt like hell!
I said "I'm sorry!", but it didn't matter
Chono Masahiro
This is a memory about Chono-san
Is it really a gorilla?
It's not a story about Chono-san?
It wasn't Chono-san
It was a gorilla right?
"Im sorry!" - And then he hit me
And the gorilla, with both his hands,
Like that ?!
Yeah
He goes like this, then this?
That's not a gorilla!
I can't tell what the gorilla is doing at all!
Like this?!
He punched you in the neck?
Like I said,
I still don't know why he's in the cage though
Surely he would die
I entered the cage, and then he ran towards me
He ran?
He ran
Gorillas are huge right?
They are!
And then he grabbed me like this, and my neck went down like that
And then the gorilla crouched down and POW!
A gorilla doesn't do that
He crouched down?
With his fists out like this?
He crouched down and jumped?
That must've hurt!
That would kill you!
If a gorilla hits you like that
I don't remember anything after that
And this incident didn't show up in the newspaper?
It did not show up in the newspaper
You'd think they would put that in there
Surely that's more newsworthy
Why?
You're right
You were hospitalised?
I was hospitalised?
Oh you were?
I was
Were you alright?
I got 2 stitches
Just 2 stiches?
Where?
Right around ... this area
You have a would there?
Your neck was cut?
It got cut, with his nails
Your neck didn't break?
Lie TIME Over
Well I wanted to confirm
Yeah
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
That celebrity is now a grandfather?!
The lying improvisation continues
Here I go,
Oui!
Oh!
Tanaka picks someone to tell a massive lie
This- Well segueing from this,
You guys might think "You gotta be lying!",
Hamada-san,
Is it true you were raised by gorillas?
Cause of the story we just heard,
I didn't mean to be, but I was reminded of that just now
That sounds true!
Yes of course,
It sounds like it's true
Until what age?
Umm, yeah you know,
It was before I came to Amagasaki
Sooo before I entered kindergarten
When I lived near Daikokucho (Osaka)
I didn't know that
Why?
I didn't know about Daikokucho
Oh really? Well yeah I came to Amagasaki before starting kindergarten,
And we got to know each other after I got to Amagasaki
Oh yeah, you wouldn't know then
Yes indeed
Surely you don't really remember?
Nah c'mon it was obvious! He was so massive and hairy after all
Obviously that wasn't my dad
Yeah you would remember that I guess
I guess it had a big impact on your memories
Do you have any memories of being taken somewhere?
Well yeah, I was taken to the zoo a lot
The zoo?
The zoo itself?
You went to the zoo?
Well cause I was raised there!
The gorilla took you to the zoo?!
He wanted to show it to me
He wanted to treat you like a human child
Yes, yes exactly
Ah, I can tell he was kind
Oh is that so?
And my dad was busy, and my mom had-
Who are you talking about?
Your real dad?
My real dad was really busy, right?
Eh~?
How busy could he be that he left you with a gorilla?
Oh is that what you meant?
I thought he was found by animals
No no I wasn't found!
I apologise
A gorilla won't take a child home
So like a domestic worker?
It was coincidental, we were looking for help around the house,
Is it a generational thing?
So you got a gorilla?!
I wanna know more!
A go-, A gorilla,
Maybe someone told them
"I know a gorilla that's good around humans"
They should be more careful than that!
What kind of fun did you get up to? With the gorilla?
Well, you know Matsumoto does joke about this, but for example,
Swinging in a tire,
Really?
Gorillas love doing that
Cause that's the gorilla's idea of fun
Yeah, yeah
So how did this end?
In the end,  he went back to Tennoji Zoo
A Gorilla!
That gorilla was from the zoo?
Cause he won't visit there-
Well I'm not sure about "Visit'
So that was when you were 3, 4 years old,
Did you visit him in Middle or Elementary School?
Ah, I see! Did you?
Cause he's at the zoo after all
It's sad, but I did visit him once,
I went to his cage, he totally ignored me
He was a gorilla after all
Lie TIME Over
That sucks
You would expect an emotional reunion
That pisses me off!
He should've remembered!
There was no emotional reunion
That sucks
Yeah
I guess animals are just like that
Yeah I guess
He forgot about me
Endo will pick someone to tell a plausible lie
Endo's plausible lie
Yes
Tanaka, I didn't know about this,
You know that  "Best Jeanist" show?
TN: "Best Jeanist" is an award Japanese jeans industry made up for celebs that look good in jeans
You decide that right?
Eh?!
You decides who wins right?
That's amazing isn't it?
Yeah I thought that too
In that case pick me!
And the "Best Father" award, and all those other ones?
He picks every "Best" winner
Eh~?!
Whaat? No way
First off- well that is true, but,
Who did you hear this from?
Who?...
Shit, now I'm really pissed off
I don't know who,
Who did you hear this from?
I saw something like that on the internet
Someone wrote that?
Yeah
I wanted that to remain a secret no matter what
Cause if people find out, it ruins it right?
Mmm, well,
Ruins it? Well,
If we know, we might ask to be picked
Yes yes exactly. It's, well it's not anyones fault, but,
I don't want to be asked things like that
It will become fixed
Exactly exactly
I pick people purely because they look good in jeans
When did this start?
Since the beginning
How many years?
When did it start?
The Jeanist show started probably ...
12 years? 13 years? I think
I think 13 years ago
So you've been deciding for the past 10 or so years?
Yes
Eh? Really!?
But why you?
Probably, cause, my family,
My family lineage I guess, is involved in jeans
Your lineage is jeans?
I know for a fact your family lineage is not jeans
Well I mean like,
Jeans have always been really important to us,
In Osaka, my family there,
My parents are in the Clothing Industry
They're not!
That's a lie isn't it?
No no-
The clothing industry?
Yes, my dad, both my parents actually. That's why they got married.
Really?
Could you elaborate?
Well, yeah, it's about Jeans
The people who brought jeans to Japan - My family brought jeans here
Wow
Yeah,
I didn't know that
The 4th or 5th generation of my family, brought jeans to Japan from America.
That's amazing
I didn't know that
So every year when I would joke "Why wasn't I picked"
You knew the whole time?
Yeah yeah, I thought "Hahaha he's said it!"
That's kind of rude
Why didn't you pick him?
Yeah? Why not me?
That's cause,
So you don't pick comedians? Is that it?
Yeah is that why? You can't pick comedians?
It's not that I can't do that,
If a comedian looks good in jeans  then it's alright
But he looks great in jeans!
Why is Hamada no good?
Hamada-san, well according to my sense doesn't look good in jeans at all
I didn't want to hear that
It's not Hamada-san's fault of course, it's just the jeans
It's not the just the jeans right? He decides winners of other things too?
Yeah, the "Best Father", "Best Glasses"
Theres the glasses too
What about that one?
How do you decide?
That one as well, of course,
If the glasses look good on them-
Sorry, excuse me, but sometimes the winner of the Best Glasses,
Is someone who you normally wouldn't associate with wearing glasses
Yeah exactly
Yeah
No no,
There are a lot of people who say that
"I don't normally wear glasses, but please pick me"
Like who?
Umm,
Like Takagi Miho-san
Takagi Miho
But she does wear glasses
Takagi Miho wears them!
She does!
But that's where it started,
When she's reacting to a VTR  she usually wears them
That's true
Then, my last question,
Who will win this year?
Oh yeah
For the glasses,
Tell just us
Yeah
Who do you think should win?
Yes yes yes yes
I was thinking Pierre Taki
Pierre Taki
You wouldn't think he wears glasses
Glasses?
He doesn't wear them right?
And what about the jeans?
That guy, umm,
Umm,
The former baseball guy, umm,
Kuriyama Hideki
The director?
Yeah, he looks great in jeans
He never wears jeans!
His everyday attire is fantastic
Normally he never wears them
He looks great normally
Kuriyama Hideki?!
I have no idea how
There's no way it's Kuriyama Hideki
It is
It is him though
Could you tell us the "Best Father" please?
Oh yeah
Yeah who's winning this year?
The Best Father is...
Well I wanted to leave this as a surprise,
Really?
Oh, really?
What do you base it on?
Well after all, whenever he's on Gaki
All he talks about is his daughter
That's not true!
Then you're lying aren't you?!
That's a lie!
Lie TIME Over
That felt kind of rude just now
I got wrapped up in that!
After this,
Hosei consults the members for advice
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Hosei
Can I ask something?
Yes?
I want some advice for this problem
What happened?
It's a real story,
It's your bald spot right?
That's it is it?
Cause this whole time,
The clown of your head- Sorry crown
Crown!
Crown-
I can see it's bad
They say your hair gets scruffier as you age
Yeah sure
Yeah
Yeah-
He's saying "Yeah sure"
I have no idea what to say when I'm being picked on for that
I pretend they're talking about someone else
C'mon no way!
Cause you can't say anything otherwise?
You don't really do that!
No no I do
So you can't really join the conversation?
Yeah exactly
Ah, well that's unfortunate
It puts me in a tough spot,
I understand, I apologise
My apologies
So don't ever bully me about that please
I apologise
He's so mad!
He's kind of ticked off
Yeah
So this problem I have,
Right
My son, he was born recently,
Hosei's eldest son, the 3rd child was born in September of 2012. He is 1 year and 6 months old
Your son was born yeah
Yeah, we have a new boy right?
His 3rd child is a son
So now he's 1.5 years old, and he's totally different from my daughters!
He's really agressive! He really is
So I was taking a nap,
And he goes "Papa papa!", he's aware of me
He said it to me when I came over too
He said it to the chawanmushi too
That's not true
He knows I'm his dad
So I was sleeping in the evening,
And he jumped on me,
And I was so shocked by that pain I almost fainted!
Seriously!
Well it would be surprising
Right
My daughters were never like that
But that's just common with boys
Oh is it?
It's not really that big a deal
I see
No no no no
Can you stop using that tone?
Everyone watching this is probably thinking the same
Well that might be,
But girls don't do that right?
They don't
Yeah they don't
Hmm, I don't know about that
When I'm sleeping,
He tries to wake up, he wants to play with me
I see
He pulls my hair really hard!
Ah that's why? (you're bald)
No no that's not why
Ah that's why he's balding
There's a connection there!
No there isn't!
Ah so this was your joke!
Yeah!
He did say it
No no no
You didn't want us to ruin your punchline
I sincerely apologise
Oh that's why?
No!
We couldn't have known that
We apologise
So we can make fun of you now right?
No, don't do that!
We can't? I don't get it
No!
I thought "His bald spot was the punchline!"
No, that's not it
Nope
Where does he grab? For real
Where does he grab?
Here, the top most part of my head
So Hosei-san, we can make fun of you?
Cause clearly you're trying to make that joke
I'm not
So there's not really a problem then
No there is,
There is, and well he is a child after all,
I want to know how to handle boys,
Cause if I get angry, my wife gets angry at me
She gets mad
Then that's gotta be because,
Generally, the mom just can't help but dote on the son right?
And for the dad it's the daughter
Yeah that might be why
That's gotta be why
Cause I've known your family for a while
And when you had just your 2 daughters before, you would dote on them more
I guess it's different that way
Ahh
Maybe cause he's like you, I don't know
It's different
Certainly, it is different
Yeah
So when he yanks my hair, my wife,
She laughs and goes "That's a funny reaction!"
What do you guys think?
What do we think?
Yeah
What do you say? "Stop that!" or something?
I go "Ow ow ow!"
And when she sees that,
She goes "That reaction is hilarious!"
My wife laughs - What do you guys make of this?
Who is this story about?
It's a little hard to follow
Who is the main character?
Who is the main?
That I don't understand
I also don't get that, sorry
Who are you complaining about here?
Is it your son? Your wife?
What is this?
My son
I also think my wife isn't reacting correctly
But what is your problem? You want to know what to do?
What is your problem?
Well since you two have raised sons,
How should I react to get him to stop doing that? Like jumping on my belly,
Or pulling my hair, how should I handle that?
Did your son jump on your belly?
Well that did happen often I guess,
From "Sesame Street",
Do you know "Cookie Monster? That blue character from Sesame Street
A character from Sesame Street that loves cookies
Cookie Monster
I think so
It's a character that loves eating cookies
I think it was when he was 3 or 4 years old
I imitated him eating a cookie, and he found it hilarious
And cause he wanted to see that, when I was sleeping,
He would force a cookie into my mouth
And you're alseep?
I'm asleep, and he's jamming the cookie
The cookie
And the first time,
The first time I,
I woke up and pretended to do it,
But after that every morning he would shove a cookie in my mouth,
He would shove it in?
Sounds exhausting
It was exhausting
So I wanted to put a stop to it,
I would not wake up when he put the cookie in
So since I stopped waking up, he stopped doing that
He wants to know whether or not he should get angry
How should he display he's mad
Ah, I didn't get angry
That behaviour sort of faded out
As he got older?
Now he's totally calmed down yeah
He's 5 years old after all
Maybe you should make him think dad is scary
I see
Make him think "I shouldn't get scolded by dad"
Maybe just make him think that
I see
Cause they get scolded by mom everyday, they get used to it
Yes
We went to dinner togther the other day,
Ah yes, with our families
With our families
He looks just like Yamasaki!
Oh?
I did hold him once,
They're just different from girls
They are
Oh really?
They kind of smell like old people
No no no
Like old people?
That's too soon!
They don't have that sweet smell that girls have
Too soon to smell old
Boys that is
They aren't as soft?
They aren't
You never know, maybe Hamada might have a new daughter some day
No way!
Of course not!
I'm 50!
After this
That person is now a grandfather?!
That would be a thing to see
Is it alright to mention this?
Kimura Yuichi
Kimu-chan is a grandfather now
Ah I heard that
His previous wife's son right?
Yeah, cause Kimu's been married right?
Um, his 6th ex-wife
Too many!
It was his 4th wife
His ex-wife's children,
He got grandchildren early
He's KimuPa now
KimuPa?
KimuPa!?
He's gonna be pissed at him now. Right?
I did laugh at that but,
C'mon, you guys, you laughed
I don't know about that
You guys laughed really hard
All he ever talks about is his daughter
I don't!
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband