www.shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Modern Japan, a country of peace at any price
Modern Japan, a place of peace at any price
With an increasing number of weaklings known as
"herbivurous males"
"lunchbox males"
The number of weaklings is increasing rapidly
"herbivurous males" or "lunchbox males"
There's a hot-blooded teacher loved by his students
And in this very moment, a hot-blooded teacher is rising
To bring back the forgotten shape of young japanese men!
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
HAMADA MASATOSHI
MATSUMOTO HITOSHI
Welcome to Hamada's Cram School
- Welcome
principal
vice
It's a pleasure to meet you
(cocorico)
(jicho kacho)
(license)
(shinagawa shoji)
Endo Shouzo
Tanaka Naoki
Fujiwara
Inomoto
Komoto Junichi
Inoue Satoshi
Shoji Tomoharu
Tsukitei Housei
[Hamadas Cram School's Students]
The pleasure is ours!
Principal
Yamazaki said he's feeling pressured
About what?
I've been told that for this episode
There would have been 15 students
But I can only see 8 of them
That's about half of em
That's because if there are less people it's easier
for them to feel our principal's spirit
- That's it
I see, sorry
Isn't it better you're not that many?
Yes sir
Of course it is, thank you so much!
Alright
You deserve a slap
Ready?
- I am
Thank you!
That was quick
Komoto, put your head in there
Put it in there
Here?
- Yes
What's wrong?
All the way through
- Yes
Till the bottom
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Let's do some baseball, ok?
20 lt. can catch
catch the ball with a 20 lt can instead of a regular glove
That's the best thing to start from
That's right, principal
Let's do some strikes
Let's do it     - Alright
Let's go
We're ready!
We're ready
Wait, don't--
You don't need those
Just go
We don't?
Wait, principal...
Wasn't it "20 lt can" catch?
That's not it
Huh? What?
But these--
How about you just use
These
Hands your parents gave to you?
What? Principal...?
Get em away
Alright, got it
Ehh? Wait
Don't take em away
That's what the principal wanted
You all have been comedians since a long time, huh?
And you got to know the principal too
And has complaining ever got you anything?
Not even once
No, right?
- Right
Then don't
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Hey, come closer
Here
Whaaaat?!
Excuse me, principal
Huh?
Can you raise your voice a bit? My ears are still ringing...
Get over that line, quick!
Come on, get here
That's too close!
What are you fussing about?
That's way too close!
This distance...
- Too close
We'll die
Can you take it from there if you use the 10 lt can?
Let's try with the 10 lt can, ok?
What does this silence even mean?
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Get it!
Nice catch! Good
Good
Good job
Watch out!
Here comes
What's going on?
Boring
Has no one been hit yet?
No blood yet?
Like, boom! Wham!
Is that what you're waiting for?
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
How about I smack your shin?
But, principal...
It would break
Say, principal, over there
There are some drums ready for use
How about we try to play using them?
By working together
catch the ball with a drum (4 people) instead of a glove
drum can catch
Oh, I see
Let's try that
It's teamwork
Yes sir
Go take em
HOT BLOODED!! HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
It will be 4 people per can
Sounds good
Ok
Can you move? You ok?
We'll try
- We can move it
Nice shot
No good
Holy shit
The vice is pretty good
Ok ok
Just take it!
Take it
Good, good
Come on!
It went in!
We got it!
We got it, teacher
Hey, wait a moment
Those punks on the left are not doing anything
We're ready!
You're not willing at all to go get the ball
We are!!
Counting on you
Man, they suck
You four, get here
Get your ass over here!
Come here
I told you to come
Leave the can and come here
Yes sir
Kneel down
What?
Why aren't you catching it?
We threw it near you and yet you didn't dare to get it
That ball is for you
Yes sir
Are you not enjoying it?
No way, that's not true
Of course
Alright
What's wrong, principal?
Everyone, gather!
On your knees
This is what the principal wants to say
Are you wondering why you're here?
That's why
"I wanted to see smiles and such!"
Understood?!
No one is smiling here
Is this the attitude you wanna show
To the principal?!
No need to say that, I think they got it
Alright, let's move on
Yes sir!
Oh
At least your response is good
Try to laugh... that's it
Laugh more
Principal...
Fujiwara is not laughing at all
Is that really ok?
Listen
If you're not really feeling it
Just go tell your dear vice
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
...or make a small donation @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
NEW
Want to support? Like my FB page: facebook.com/shionnotsukai
more J-comedy @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
or patreon @ patreon.com/shionnotsukai
translation & subs by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
HE CAN BECOME A DEMON BECAUSE THERE'S LOVE IN HIM
HOT BLOODED!! HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Vice?
Yes?
Let's do some throws
Yes sir
Come here one by one
Let's see... License
Yes sir
You're the youngest here
- Yes
So you'll make this spin
You're in charge
The one who spins will be the batter
As soon as it stops...
You throw the ball
I told you it's throwing, so you throw it
But you can't it just roll around
So you go get it
So we throw it and get it back?
That's because
Hamada's cram school is incredible
So we throw it and run around the bases?
Make sure to slide when you get back here
sit on the chair and make it spin; once it stops, throw the ball
swivel chair baseball
then you go get it yourself and go back to your home base
Slide...?
There is so much to do
That's too much
There's a lot
All by ourselves?
I'll see if you're safe or not
Yes sir
You're all doing this
That's right
Yes sir
Tanaka
Yes?
Tanaka is challenged!
Come here
Yes sir
Go get em
Good luck!
Here we go
Alright
Spin it
One, two...
HOT BLOODED!! HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Eight, nine, ten
Alright
He got the ball
Throw it
Watch out
Alright, he threw it
Go after it, quick!
Defend it!
Defensedefensedefense
You can do it!
- Defense!
That's the opposite direction!
It's in the centre
Defend it!
Over there!
- Left!
The other side!
- Go left!
That's a different ball, isn't it?
He took another one
He took one from our previous can game
Are you for real?
Come on, almost there!
You can do it!
Hang in there!
Slide, now!
You're out!
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Ready
Shoji is challenged!
Alright, I'm ready
Let's go
Two, three...
HOT BLOODED!! HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
18, 19, 20... go!
Yeah, like that
Throw the ball
Hang in there
You can do it, Shoji
Watch out
Shoji is dangerous, watch out
Stay focused
- Go for the ball
He's going in the right direction
- Good
Very good
On your left
Almost there
Here it is
Well done
Now go back
He's good
He is
- Hang in there
Be ready to slide
You did pretty good
Next one
You did good
Let's go back, Shoji
That's how you do it
I think he...
Wanted to be scolded
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Next up
blindfolded battle
put the blindfold on and battle by relying only on the sound of bells
It's a blindfolded battle
It's a battle
All our students did this before
That's true
And they've all become presidents or such by now
Presidents?
That's right
All those who went to our cram school
Became presidents or such in various places
Some of them became politicians too
That's right
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Get ready
Strike where you hear the bells
Ouch
- It hurts
It hurts
- Ouch
The bells are ringing
That hurt
it's just "itai" ("it hurts")
I must say, this year...
Sure brought us a bad harvest
Doesn't it look like
They're kind of holding back?
I see
Maybe they don't need the blindfold
You have a point
It makes sense
Let's do it as if you're blindfolded
"As if"?
What do you mean by "as if"?
Do it as if you couldn't see
As if I couldn't see...
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Let's try that a bit
Ready
Go
Come here
What was that?
We did it as if we couldn't see
- Yeah, that's it
Well
They act like students
You're right
That's not good
You won't become a president like this
You won't
You want to become a president, right?
Not really
That's why you came here, isn't it true?
It's not like we want to be presidents
That's not it?
Yes
That's not it
Well, if that's it
Let's just
Let's quit using the sticks
I agree
Let's do it as if you could look and as if you had a stick
So we pretend both to see and to have a stick?
Yes, ready?
Wait
The enemy is right there!
You won't be a boss like that!
You won't become a president this way
Alright, Yamazaki: go solo
It hurts, who was it?!
Who was it?! It hurts
Stop it, stop!
From here?
He's here---
Are you here? Are you?!
Are you here or not!?
It hurts, stop
Alright, Inoue: go solo
Where are you?!
Damn, you got my ear!
Who hit my ear?! Where am I?!
Ok, Tanaka: go solo
Hey! Where are you?!
Are you here? It hurts!
It hurts, where are--
Shoji: go solo
Where are you?!
Stop it! Where are you?!
Ouch!
You can't do that!
Stop-- where are you going?
It huuuuuurts
Spare me!
Let's have him do it some more
Stop focusing only on me
Why only me?! Ouch
Anything but that!
Don't do this to me
I can't do it anymore
You can't do this to me
Not seeing is scary
It's really frightening
This--
I'm dead tired
Alright, go back
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
What do you think, Endo?
Yes
I think
That was very useful for us
Thank you
More
Speak some more
I want you to be the best speaker
Our objective
Was to hold a stick while blindfolded
We did this at first
But halfway
We took the mask off and we pretended not to---
Yeah, keep on talking no matter what happens
Well...
We acted as if we couldn't see
And we fought
And we got to spend some really useful time
So thank you so much!
Don't end it
W-we, I think---
We had so much fun during it and
And while we were feeling it---
Principal?
We had the pleasure to--
Principal?!
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Next up is "steal the bun from Hamada-statue"
Yes sir
steal the bun from the blindfolded principal without being attacked!
steal the bun! Hamada-statue
I'll sit and be the blindfolded statue
The principal
You come here and try to steal this bun, one by one
Yes sir
You can eat it if you take it
Yes sir    - But I'll be holding a paper fan with one hand
And other stuff too
Alright
Got it?
There are different attacks, right?
That's right, you have to dodge em
And just go grab the bun
Yes sir
Ok principal, the mask, please
This?
The principal will wear it
Sure
So, who's going first?
Komoto
You're up
Yessir
Observe the principal...
Principal...?
- The hell do you want?!
That's his cute side
It's going on forever
That was his QT side
Now the principal can't see
Yes
But principal, you have to grab that button
You had to do it before putting that on
What are ya laughin' at?!
We're sorry
It's this one, principal
Check the button first
Alright
The hell are you doin'?
What was that for
Ok, let's start
Alright, Komoto
Yes sir
Let's go!   - Go Komoto!   - Good luck!
Komoto is challenged!
Ready...
Grab that bun
Start!
Take it take it!
Careful
Take that bun
You can do it
Remember, he can't see you
Scary
He can't see you
Here goes
You can take it!
Ok, ok
You can do it
Go grab it
Almost there, you can do it
Just take it, now!
Go, Komoto!
You can do it!
Almost there
Watch out! He almost got you!
Watch out, it's dangerous!
Avoid it!
Enough!
Eh?
That's enough
What are you doing, principal?
Are you kidding me?
He already took it
He's currently eating it
Want to do it one more time?
Yeah it's ok I guess
I really have no idea
Let's go then
Tanaka
Yes sir
Try it
Alright
Tanaka is challenged!
Do your best
I will
Let's do it
Ready and... start!
You can do it
Come on
Stay calm
- Focus!
Like this
- You can do it
Watch out
Hang on
- Almost got you
Watch out!
Move slowly
- Close call!
Woah, watch out!
Watch out!!
- Avoid that thing
Here goes, here goes
Watch his orbit
Move slowly, like this
Woah, that was close!
Enough of that, geez
Take the mask off
He quickly took it
Say principal
When do you plan to press that switch?
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Have you forgotten you had two items?
Vice, I can't see anything
Maybe it's better if you see more
There's another mask which lets you see a bit more
A bit more?
Yeah, like a grid, but you can't see through it
The cloth is just thinner
He can see
The cloth is a grid, so...
No way, I'm sure he can see us
No good, I can't see
I can see he's looking at us
I see his eyes
Ok, so...
Go Yamazaki
Housei is challenged!
Come here    - He said "come here"
Can't he really see?
He told me to come
What's wrong!?
Wait, how can he--?
C'mere
What does this mean?!
What's going on?!
This--- it hurts!
Please stop
Principal!!
HOT BLOODED!! HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
After this
Even more incredible Hamada's Cram School!!
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Next up is this
Vice
Sure
It's this
Do you remember it?
- We do
It's a slinky
With this, you
slinky relay
time attack race: form an horizontal row and pass the slinky
You use your hand and make a relay
With the slinky
Ok
It will be a time attack
Time race?
We'll measure time
Use both your hands
So make it go here, and there, then there etc.
Ok, so
Your goal is until it reaches Inomoto's hands
Who are we racing against...?
You'll become a president with this
You could even become a trader
Get ready
- Alright
As soon as
My watch hits 12 o'clock, you start
12 o'clock?   - We can't see it...
Ready and...
Start
W-wait, this---
What's this?
Looking good
It's coming, good
It's fine, it's fine
We're good
Let's do this
A bit more
Almost there
- You got this
We can do it!
Alright
Done!
35 seconds
Alright!
We did it
I don't want to take part in such tv show
The hell is this?
Is that what you wanted?
I mean, this...
It worked fine
They can't even do it!
- It's just like this
We have to make steps
So it goes down?
That's right, Endo your hands must be lower
That's it, that should do it
Yes
Like this?
It goes way lower
More like this
Just like stairs
That should do
- Stairs
Wait up
Ok
Start as soon as my watch hits "6"
How should we know?   - We can't see it
Ok ok ok
That should do, you can do it
Hurry up
Oh, it's going well
- Ok, ok!
Somewhat ok
Pretty quick
- Done!
I think
We have to cast the blame on 1 or 2 of you here
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Let's have another relay next
A relay
- Yes sir
Here
See those wet towels?
- Yes
Take one and put it over your head
race: break the paper balloon of your teammate (left) with the wet towel
wet towel time attack
Yes sir
In order, starting from here
You have to burst it with your wet towel
Yes sir
Like, bam, bam, bam... I'll measure the time
Got it
As soon as it turns into 4 we'll start
Yes
How do we...
We don't know that    - We can't see
Ready...
Ok!
- Ok, ok!
Only Inoue's ballon broke
See?
This is what I wanted to see
All you did was throw em away
Come this way
Follow me
The principal is...
It surely got really quiet in here
I don't like this silence
- It's not pleasant, I guess
After this
The last class work from principal Hamada!!
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
Because of his love for his unskilled students
Principal Hamada can now only turn into a demon
Get in here
Ok
I'm entering!
- Excuse us!
Don't get away from this bordered area
Exiting from it isn't allowed
Yes sir
Ok?
I used to do this back then
What?
Back then..?
What is it?
I'm sure the vice knows it too, right?
Back then, with a wet towel...
Our principal...
Used to beat his little sister up
His sister...?
- Just sometimes
Yeah with
Towels for bath
Sometimes, yeah
Sometimes...?
- His sister...?
She screamed like "DJA! DJA!"
I mean, his sister
What's going on?!
What's wrong, principal?!
- It hurts!!    - What's going on?!
Stop!
- It hurts!
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
So, what are you lacking?
"I wanted to see a bond or such!"
We wanted to see you guys stand up for each other more
We wanted you to value your comrades more
Someone covering for someone else
That's the kind of feeling
Our principal wanted
What are you doing?
Thinking only about yourselves
You won't become a president
Don't you want to...?
Well, actually...
I mean, some of them want to, others don't want to
Which one is it?
We don't... want to
- You don't?   - We don't
HOT BLOODED!!
HAMADA'S CRAM SCHOOL!!
...and on Twitter @ FGRNDNoises (follow it!)
...or on Patreon @ patreon.com/shionnotsukai
More Gaki & japanese comedy @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Updates, news & more @ facebook.com/shionnotsukai (like it!)
You can support my works on ko-fi @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
this is a no-profit fansub, made by a fan for other fans