Translation: ReconEyebotZeta
Typesetting & Retiming: condoriano90
Subtitle conversion: Rylix
r/GakiNoTsukai
Annual Kohaku battle!
Aired on Heisei 6 (1994), December 18th
I'll go with white
Then, me too...
No, no...
Both wanted to bet for the white team! They then played a game for a decision!
Hamada wins! Hamada bets on the white team while Matsumoto bets on red!
BUGFIX
Heisei 6, December 31st
And there comes decisive December 31st...
Everyone arose at Yakyuken party, but they were preoccupied with the result of the battle!
Note: Yakyuken is a strip game with rock-paper-scissors and baseball themed chant.
BUGFIX
As soon as they finished shooting for the show, they went into the waiting room!
YEAHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!
The red team won! Victory for Matsumoto! Batsu Game for Hamada!
Batsu game for loser Hamada!!
And now, in March 1st, the time has come!
March 1st
Board room
A usual day for Gaki board room...
Tired, yeah?
GnT Special Program
Hama-chan Batsu Game
Yeah, tired!
He's late!
Here he comes, here he comes!
Well, you've done well enough.
Did you really think the white team can win?
Uh, yeah. That's what I thought...
Are you reading the trend of time?
Well, I didn't think that deeply to say for the white team..
Can you read it? Can you?
The fact that the white team lost makes I couldn't.
Yeah, that's right.
Well, if you got something, keep in touch.
Tell him my number.
Ok, your phone number...
Should I give him the office number instead? It'd bad if he gotten your phone number.
You're right! He's gonna prank me.
Huh...?
What's wrong?
I can't find my mechanical pencil.
No, no, that won't do. I need my mechanical pencil, I cannot write with that.
Cannot write with that!? Sure you can!
Where did it go...?
Ah! I remember it now!
Mr. Sakamoto borrowed it from me!
Sakamoto Ryuichi
BUGFIX
Oh no...
Oh no, I can't do this without it!!
Go fetch it!
Go and fetch it!
You can find mechanical pencils anywhere! Just go buy one yourself!
Go to New York and fetch my mechanical pencil from Mr. Sakamoto!!
Batsu Game: Hama-chan goes to New York to fetch a mechanical pencil!!
Immediately and forcibly, after his first batsu game that took place in foreign country, "Hamada's journey to France for Evian water"
He now has to do another one!
Hamada sulking in bed
With 12 hours of flight ahead of him, a cruel trip starts for Hamada!
New Tokyo International Airport
Note: It's now known as Narita International Airport
BUGFIX
Why should I go to New York for a mechanical pencil...
Producer
Suga Kenji
There! Popular producer figure, Suga! By the order from Matsumoto, he'll now act as the saboteur!
What is it?
What are you doing here?
Is he on vacation?
That's right.
I'm going to visit New York for a week, then I go to Bahamas.
Well, What are you doing here?
Don't "What are you doing here" me! I'm on Batsu Game!
Ah, I've heard of it.
You know it, right?
We'll go togethe...
There's no way around. I'll lead you.
Shut up.
This whole thing is lame...
With that, the trip for New york has finally begun!
Plane that Hamada is on board now left for New York...
Of course, Economy class for Batsu Game.
Shimizu, where's Suga, huh?
I think he's at at the front seat.
Front seat?
What do you mean front?
Front all the way.
So he makes actors sit on economy class but not himself.
Hey.
Producer Sugawara is relaxing in business class.
I'm on economy class, goddamit! Why are you in business class?
Hey, He's drinking cognac! Disgusting fellow!
With all these swing, he couldn't sleep at all!
15 hours after departure, they have arrived at JFK International Airport!
15 hours since departure
JFK International Airport
For just one machine pencil, Hamada Masatoshi has landed on America!
GnT Special Program
Hama-chan Batsu Game
We're here...
It's literally the worst... I'm so tired...
Hamada is now en route for Sakamoto's house!
Argh, why the white team lost?
Are you reading the trend of time?
Note: Amagasaki is the hometown for Downtown.
Shit, Amagasaki has developed a lot...
No, this isn't...
Manhattan
They arrives at the center of world's economics and culture, Manhattan!
Heading for Mr.Sakamoto's apartment!
No, we're going to Kyoju's house! Let's hurry up!
Note: Ryuichi Sakamoto is called as "Kyoju", which means professor, named by his friend and musician Yukihiro Takahasi for he knew lots of knowledge and theory about music.
Suga's sabotage scheme has started!
Where are you going?
Kyoju's place's there!
Don't worry about it!
Wait, where is this?
Empire State Building
It's the symbol of Manhattan, Empire State Building!
An unwanted stop for Hamada!
It's so cold here.
So cold, wow...
Oh shit It's cold!
But the view from here is good...
It's impressive...
Let's take a picture.
Huh?
Picture?
Why?
Why the hell?
Why not? It's famous here.
That's it, good, good, it's so cool!
No, it's hella lame!
By punching a one cent coin, it can make pendant with
Popular in Empire State Building
the design of building.
Moreover, Hamada is forced to buy unwanted coin!
What the hell is this!? It's so lame!
Why don't we just leave?
Ok, next we'll go skating.
Don't be an idiot.
Rockefeller Center
Another famous spot in New York, the skating rink in Rockefeller Center!
Oh watch out, watch out...
Hamada wants to go to Sakamoto's house, but he's dragged around for sightseeing!
Times Square
Next, for the center, Times Square!
I must go to Kyoju's house!
Hamada's irritating for late trip.
We can do that tomorrow.
No way! I have no time.
There, a hot dog stand.
Nevermind about the hot dog...
"Nevermind about the hot dog..."
Why don't we get one since we're already here...
Hello...
Hamada has no time for a hot dog. He's irritated, but...
Hama-chan...!
You don't have to take a picture!
Eat it, eat it now...
The city where many artists live, East Village!
East Village
21 hours since departure
21 hours after they departed from Tokyo, they finally reached the apartment where Sakamoto Ryuichi lives!
Oh, he's livin' in here...
Or is this his office?
I guess he's living in here, I don't know.
Don't "I don't know" me!
Who knows...
Finally, reunification with Sakamoto Ryuichi after a long time!
I hope he's here...
Oh, Kyoju!
Hello there!
Sakamoto Ryuichi
Well, I'm here because...Matsumoto's...
Why are you here?
No, um...
I'm here to fetch something.
Um, Matsumoto's...
What's with that attitude!?
I've come all the way from Tokyo, what's with that attitude!?
Oh, is that it?
Through Kyoju's hand, the machine pencil is warmly handed.
Mechanical Pencil fetching success!!
Batsu Game completes splendidly!
Hey! Hey, Sakamoto!
Hey, Sakamoto!
Ryuichi!!
Let's just go...
No, no way that attitude is allowed!
I can't go back like this!
Let me have a talk with him!
Anyway, you're so popular and exalted in Japan, but this is how it is here, huh?!
It's fucking frustrating...
Cold, cold...
Go to airport now.
Who? Oh, me?
You're not coming?
Well, no. I'm here for vacation. I told you earlier.
Ah, right. Then, later.
Ugh, this is the worst...
Bye, Hama-chan...
23 hours since departure
Hamada is now with the pencil, to Japan where Matsumoto is waiting!
Pencil's fetched. Hamada is off from New York.
Board room
Second time...
The one we went through?
Ugh!!
GnT Special Program
Hama-chan Batsu Game
40 hours since departure
Ughhh!!!
It can't be helped, man...Fetchin...
Here.
Yeah, that's right, this is it.
Is that it? Finally!
I mean, it's even got my name "Matsumoto" written here.
Suga kept getting in my way and slowing me down...
Well, this is over now, it doesn't matter anymore.
It was so cold too...
Ahhhhhh!!!!!
23 hours since departure
Hamada is now with the pencil, to Japan where Matsumoto is waiting!
Pencil's fetched. Hamada is off from New York.
Board room
Second time...
The one we went through?
Ugh!!
GnT Special Program
Hama-chan Batsu Game
40 hours since departure
Ughhh!!!
It can't be helped, man...Fetchin...
Here.
Yeah, that's right, this is it.
Is that it? Finally!
I mean, it's even got my name "Matsumoto" written here.
Suga kept getting in my way and slowing me down...
Well, this is over now, it doesn't matter anymore.
It was so cold too...
Ahhhhhh!!!!!
The eraser is missing!
Really? What's up with this?
Wait a second, calm down, what eraser are you talking about?
Well, it doesn't matter anymore since I already fetched this for you...
What are you doing?
I'm gonna call Mr. Sakamoto...
Who cares about this anymore!
I already went there and did the Batsu Game, it was so tiring and all.
Um, hello?
Yes?
Hello?
Yes, hello.
Is this Kyoju?
Yes, this is him.
Ah, good morning.
On the phone
Sakamoto Ryuichi
Good morning.
This is Matsumoto speaking...
Oh, nice to hear you.
Same here...
I have just noticed this, but...
Yes?
I couldn't find the eraser that was with it...
Um, it was left behind...
Where was it...
Here, ah!
D-Did you just find it?
Why don't you go fetch it?
Batsu Game: Hama-chan goes to New York to fetch an eraser!!
New York once again...
Plane that Hamada is on board now left for
Manhattan
Manhattan, New York. A long time no see city welcomes Hamada!
56 hours since the first departure
Huh?
W-Wait...Stop, stop!
Is that Suga-chan...?
I hate this kind of setup...
Stop setting up these coincidental meet-ups already!
Ugh, here I am again...
I just want to go to Kyoju's house...
Hey!!
What?
Don't be saying "What?" to me again!
Ugh...I'm so...
What now?
When I went home, he asked me to come back and fetch his eraser this time...
What do you mean?
I have to go to Kyoju's place again!
Let's go together again!
Don't make me take detours again this time!
Look, I ha-
And I se-
What the hell is your outfit!?
Let's just go! Man!
Anyway, I'm already so mad now!
A reunion with Producer Suga after a long time!
Another Times Square after two days!
Times Square
Why are you here again?
Don't be asking me that again...
Like I told you earlier, I'm here to fetch the eraser!
Let's eat hot dogs.
Y'know...
Yeah?
Haven't we been here before?
Oh, is that so?
It's the same place and the same guy!
It's always good to visit New York again after a long time, huh?
I ain't visiting here "after a long time"!
It's ok, but let's just hurry up on the eraser.
Ah, that won't be any good.
Have you done any shopping here?
Shopping?!
Of course not! I'm on a mission here! I didn't even get any souvenir.
No problem! Let's just go shopping!
Why the hell should we?
C'mon, why not! Let's just go shopping for now!
5th Avenue
New York's 5th Avenue! So many world class boutiques are located here! Truly the Mecca of shopping!
And of course, Hamada is dragged around town once again!
East Village
East Village after two days!
59 hours since the first departure
It is now has been 59 hours since the first departure from Japan!
And the Batsu Game is finally reaching its climax!
How is this also part of the Batsu Game?
Since you lost that bet, can't be helped.
Why must I do this again? That's what's annoying to me.
Can't be helped.
It's cold here!
Another reunion with Sakamoto Ryuichi after 38 hours!
I'm exhausted...
Ah, Kyoju!
The eraser?
You're late...
What do you mean we're late?
W-Wait a second! Hey!
Sakamoto!
Is this it?
Ah, yes. Sorry. That's what I came for.
Through Kyoju's hand, the eraser is warmly handed, describing parabola.
Eraser fetching success!!
The Batsu Game is complete!
It's so irritating...
Let's go, you already got the eraser...
That's how Grammy Awards change a man, huh?
Alright then!
I'll start making music tomorrow!
I'm gonna challenge you! I'm gonna make music...
I'll meet you again at the next Grammy Award ceremony!
Farewell!!
Eraser's fetched. Hamada is off from New York once again!
And now, to Japan where Matsumoto awaits!
Right?
Board room
Well, anyway...
78 hours since the first departure
Is this it!?
Yeah! This is the one...
Y'know...you should've checked for this eraser the first time.
Now it's finally complete.
Oh, I want Evian water too.
Here you go then.
No, not this one.
Why not?
Go over there.
Go draw some Evian water in France.
Gimme a break already!
You should have gone to France.
WHY!?
Considering audience's reaction, it's so!
Oh they are like "Oh he goes to France now?"...
Right?
Still, going to New York was really exhausting...
I've heard that was tiring.
Yeah, VERY TIRING!
Moreover, you didn't have any sleep, right?
Yeah, I just had to go back in a day!
Well, you had to go through that because I experienced similar things.
What's that?
What similar thing?
The next Batsu Game is already decided.
Oh, really?
What is it?
Um...
You go to the North Pole...
...and become Coolmint gum.
Penguin?
Note: Reference from advertising from Coolmint gum, Lotte.
I'm gonna sell that from Lotte.
Like some kind of limited products.
Well, well...
When I was in the plane, there was a couple behind me.
Then, the girl said to me "Can I have your autograph?".
I said it's ok. I have nothing to do after all.
She said, "I'm gonna take my clothes off". I was like, "Huh!?".
She hand me her bra and said, "Sign to this".
It's totally insane!
It was so warm!
I signed that warm bra...
Don't smell it man, don't smell it...
Also, I didn't eat anything on the plane home. Because I was too tired.
No appetite.
I didn't give a shit about food in the plane.
I just wanted to sleep!
When I was sleeping all the way, about 5 hours left,
A foreigner cabin attendant who spoke Japanese very well came to me and said-
"You didn't eat anything, right?". Then, I responded "Yeah.".
"If you go back from foreign country and didn't eat anything-
you'll be mistaken as a drug mule."
Right, right...
She said drug mules often don't eat anything and just go out!
If they eat anything, drugs will go wrong.
So they wrap drugs into plastic bag or something and swallow it-
then they bring it to Japan.
Since I haven't eaten anything, and just kept sleeping...
Other foreign attendants kept looking at me when they pass by.
She said "You are not a drug mule, aren't you?", I was like "Hell no!"
Well, but...you were carrying drugs...