Are their hearts connected? No Smartphones Meetup!
The first theme; A Car Showroom
I'd go to the Honda in Aoyama-Itchoume
They head to where they thought of in a taxi
Matsumoto went to a Honda showroom in Aoyama
And then!
Oi!
Somehow he met up with Hamada right away!
This is kind of annoying
But it's this one!
The next hint; A Large Post Office
DownTown headed to Akasaka Post Office, however Hosei, Endo, & Tanaka didn't show up!
The 2 big bosses ... The 2 big bosses are already in Aoyama!
"What are the 2 big bosses doing?" - That's how you gotta think
Meanwhile, Hosei and Endo met up at Meguro Post Office
Well done, of course right?
These are their current locations; Will they be able to meet up?
Timed & Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
Time for the 3rd hint
Damn this is hard!
A long tunnel
This is a tough one isn't it?
Where would a long tunnel be?
If they're asking about "tunnels", let's forget about the "long" part for now-
No no, we can't forget that part, it said "a long tunnel"
I can't really think of one
I think near Shinjuku Goen,
The one that starts in Shibuya and ends in Yotsuya
Yes yes yes yes, that park
Ohhh yeah, you're right
If they think about where their Big Brothers are, they have to head there!
You met Yama-chan there for the big billboard
For that Onisihi Lion billboard thing right?
Oh really?
Can we go there?
That's a really long tunnel that one
They head to Shinjuku Goen Tunnel, near an intersection where Hosei once met up with Matsumoto
Is this camera enough? Oh, I should hold this?
It feels kind of gross being filmed by Hamada
What is this
There's no helping it
But still, I think if we leave Tanaka by himself, he heads to insane places
We need to catch Tanaka
A long tunnel? Are they are any? In the first place
Ah! Hmm?
In Meguro, wasn't there a road under the highway?
And another one, wasn't there one in Shibuya?
There is
There is right?
Hold on, can we go to [@!@#!@]?
Just where is Tanaka heading?
But next time...Nah we'll be fine. I feel like Yamasaki will come.
Really? Yama-chan should've remembered the last one
The Yamasaki-Endo duo still have a little bit of a human heart left
Tanaka doesn't huh?
That thing, that thing is impossible
He does love animals
Exactly, he's an animal
He likes animals so much he turned into one, for real
And what about Hosei, who once met up with Matsumoto near Shinjuku Goen Tunnel?
What about you?
I think, over there, Meguro Tunnel
But, I feel like there are some major roads too
Isn't [!@#@!] a major one?
I think that's good, let's go there
Right?
Will they be able to meet DownTown?
Still, it's been a while since I've had to wait on someone for that long
Yeah, you made us wait a bit too long, Tanaka-san
It was unbelievable
"Hamada-san told me to go the second one I thought one"
"The second thought I partook in..."
Yeah..."I partook in"
"I partook in" ...
"The second one I partook in..." What the hell!
What the hell!
What the hell is with him? Who does he think he is?
Right? We get to our destination quickly
Exactly...
This, this right?
That's a long tunnel, a long one....Yes, yes
15 minutes since they started driving, they arrive at Shinjuku Goen Tunnel
Well Matsumoto-san, it's here
This one right? This is really long
From this way, if they come here
Nahhhhhh
It's really a problem of how long they make us wait
Until everyone gets here, if they do come here
Those 2 are in Meguro right? The other is, in Sancha right?
That Sancha guy is creepy
This time I've really come to hate the Sancha guy
That guy, he really is, he really is dangerous isn't he?
I'm actually scared of him now
Meanwhile, Tanaka arrives at his tunnel
Will he meet anyone!?
Over there...
National Highway Route 246 Ikejiri, near Shibuya
I think it's here though
Tanaka remained alone, and then the staff said...
We just looked up, the name of that tunnel
It doesn't come up
Perhaps because, this is not a tunnel, but an underpass
Underpass? Ohhh...
Cause tunnels they make by drilling down-
Wait, no, Takahashi please, it's alright
I have a bad feeling about this
Please, for now just stop there
10 minutes since they arrived, DowntTown continue to wait trusting in Hosei & Endo
Any time now, if they're coming
Are they coming?
All we can do is trust Yama-chan & Shozo
And then, Hosei & Endo arrive at their tunnel!
Ara! There it is!
Damn, this is kinda,
I know from my long friendship with DownTown, they're not here!
However, they arrived at Roppongi Tunnel. Nobody met up
Just there
And then
Sorry, time's up
They didn't come!
The 5 confirm their locations
Eh? Yama-chan & Shozo, where are you?
Roppongi Tunnel
Roppongi Tunnel?
It's not that long!
Huh? Can you see that?
That's not right
We can see the other side
It's so short!
You can't do that, no no no
You idiots can see the exit can't you?
I can see it!
Tanaka-san? Where are you?
Yes, Tanaka here
I'm at the tunnel that exits starts in Ikejiri and exits in Shibuya, under 246
There it is
COME CLOSER TO US ASSHOLE!
They're telling me to get over there, they're telling me to get over there
Incidentally, DownTown-san?
Yostsuya-Yonchoume...
Of course!
It's that one!
NO NOT "IT'S THAT ONE"!!
Damn, it's that one
Yama-chan you came here before too
Once, for the big billboard thing, we met here right?
Yes! Yes, that one!
I couldn't think of anything other than Roppongi Tunnel
Think properly!
Yes, I will!
Now I'm definitely going to beat you
Tanaka only please
Please, plea- Please, um,
Look forward to it!
Shinjuku, yeah that one. That one for sure.
Hosei-san, Roppongi tunnel is way too short
We can see the exit! It's bright, it's not dark at all this tunnel
We can see it
2 hours since the start, the 5 want to hurry up and meet already
Will they be able to meet this time? The 4th hint;
Another tough one...
A famous temple...
You know,
Last time, Endo, Hosei and I all met up,
When we passed in front of Sengakuji temple, we talked about the 47 lost samurai buried there
If Yamasaji and Endo actually remember that, I think they'll come to Sengakuji
Then they'll come
That was last time, for the Aquarium card, where they passed by Sengakuji on the way to Aqua
Do you know who is buried at Sengakuji?
Get this right Endo, this is so well known
Do you guys all know?
It's not one person
Oh I got it...
The 47 lost samurai...
They're called the "Akoroshi"
Oh really?
I didn't know that
Can we count on that?...
There's that one too, that one near Tokyo Tower, Zoujouji
Oh, Zoujouji. It's either one...
I think they'll remember though
Sengakuji...Let's try heading there
Should we go? OK
Trusting Hosei & Endo will remember that conversation, they head to Sengakuji
I wonder where Tanaka is going
Tanaka is really something
If Tanaka's in that area anyways, he should juts go home!
Still alone Tanaka; What temple is he heading too?
I have a lot of options
Tsukiji Hongan-ji...
[!@!$@!@] is a shrine I think
That place is a temple
Oh really? Then [!@$!@] sounds good
We've done a Gaki shoot there too. Everyone's been there, so they really should remember it
Will troublemaker Tanaka's choice turn out correct?
DownTown's been doing this shoot all by themselves!
Driver-san, could you turn the AC down a bit?
I'm very sorry about him
Hold on! You bastard...
I asked normally
You kinda disliked that right?
What the hell!
It was scary right? The way he said it
I said it normally
We're about to pass it soon, Hosei & Endo's tunnel
The short one
If they're starting from here, if they remembered that conversation then they'd go to Sengakuji
If they didn't remember then they'd go to Zoujouji for sure
Zoujouji?
They could've gone to Zoujouji
I think so
Endo doesn't know about Zoujouji
Wasn't there a golf practice ground around there?
There was! Oh
In that case he'd know
Endo went there pretty often
Really? Eh? Should we go back?
There's a possibility he remembers that
Should we go back?
If we turn back now, we can make it
What should we do? Do we count on that conversation about Sengakuji?
What should we do? What should we do?
What should we do?
This is where those idiots went!
You can see the end! How is this long?
What do we do? (x2)
The Sengakuji conversation, I don't think those 2 idiots remember it!
They'll probably say "Oh when did that happen?"
This question really threw us for a loop
Actually, let's go to Zoujouji
I feel like, they didn't think of Sengakuji
Right? They don't seem the type to remember
They change their destaintion from Sengakuji to Zoujouji...Will this work out?
Tanaka wouldn't have arrived yet right? If he's heading to Zoujouji
Maybe Tanaka is feeling sick, he should just go home
Meanwhile, Tanaka arrives at his temple. What will happen?
They'll come for sure! It's gotta be this one
He arrived at Akasaka Toyokawa Inari Betsuin, and met up with nobody
I got it wrong?
Not here? Not here huh?
DownTown are almost at Zoujouji
I hope they come here, please
They should've arrived before we did
Yeah. I hope we meet!
Trusting Hosei & Endo to head here, DownTown head towards Zoujouji
They gotta be here
C'mon! But...It doesn't feel like there are comedians waiting there does it?
If they're not here I won't believe it
Trusting Hosei & Endo are here, DownTown head towards Zoujouji
Those guys headed here from that tunnel
Eh?!
No way...
They're not here
They're really not here?
But if they started at Roppongi Tunnel, it doesn't make sense they're not here
It doesn't make sense
Then they're not here
They went somewhere else
10 minutes before DownTown arrived at Zoujouji
Hosei & Endo had this conversation...
I feel like there was one beside Tokyo Tower...
What's it called?
Zoujouji
Endo-san, on your left side is Zoujouji
Where? Oh there it is, it's huge
They already passed by Zoujouji! Which temple are they heading to?
I'm really curious where Yama-chan and Shozo went now
We went out of our way to come closer to them
We were seriously thinking of them
Exactly! Starting from that tunnel
The times really have changed...
Now the Senpai has to worry about the junior
It's scary. Scary
Is it really possible to miss the mark this much?
This is a record isn't it?
It's been a while
And the time we've had to wait
Certainly. Certainly.
The Akasaka Post Office thing really shocked me
We waited so long right?
And then...
Time's up
The 5 confirm their locations
Oi!
Oi. Cut it out already
Their voices are quiet...
First off Yama-chan & Shozo, where are you?
Sensoji...
Sensoji?
They went to Asakusa?!
EH?!
We had best out of 1 match...And Sensoji won...
What? Why did that win?
Why didn't you win?
Listen!
Think about where you guys started
DownTown-san thought of you guys and came here
Incidentally...Where is here?
We, are at Zoujouji
See! I said it! See!
Zoujouji?
I forgot about Zoujouji!
You mentioned it?
Hosei-san said-
Endo just drop it
Hosei-san said it was a different one, or Sensoji
Endo!
Yama-chan? Yama-chan,
Incidentally, did you think of Sengakuji?
You, Endo, & I had a conversation about Sengakuji once
When I asked you who was buried here. Did you forget that conversation?
...Yes
Yes, you forgot right?
It seems you forgot, you really didn't remember
OI HOLD ON FUCKER BITCH ASSHOLE TANAKA FUCKER
This is not good
So much abuse
Where are you?
I'm at Toyokawa Inari
HUH?!
We recorded for Gaki here once!
That's true
So I thought you guys would remember that, and came here
No no, Tanaka, Hamada-san said to go to the second one you think of, right?
I've stopped doing that
You stopped already?!
I got it wrong last time, so,
No no
It's gotta be Zoujouji!
So we were choosing between Zoujouji and Sensoji.
Did you think of Sensoji?
When you're not sure, go to a close by one.
Yeah!
Since we came all the way out here
Yeah. Seriously, do you get it?
We both hate you now
You guys are our enemy
We are going to hit you of course
Please don't
Look forward to it!
FORWARD TO IT!
If you hit me using those muscles I'm gonna die
Alright
It's a journey to get smacked
You shot me, didn't you? I wanted you to say we both decided it
No Hose-san, please. For the next one, can I decide?
"I did, I did"
No way
Hosei-san if we can't get along now it's over
This time for sure! The theme;
We got this one. Matsumoto-san,]
"A stadium"? Yoyogi?
The National Stadium!
Oh yes, of course. Of course.
It has to be the National Stadium!
We can look at this as the last one right? It wouldn't be strange at all if we all met up
That's true
I've never been so confident in my answer for one of these. Can I say it?
A stadium? Komazawa comes to mind
Komazawa Stadium? The stadium is part of Komazawa park
Nah I've always called it Komazawa Stadium
You're kidding right?
DownTown head to their stadium with absolute confidence
Mr. Driver, excuse me, could you turn the tempreture up a bit?
Yes, certainly
Sorry about that. It was kind of intimidating
It absolutely wasn't
Now that I think about it, that guy, Tanaka would arrive first right?
He should be there first
If he is going to the National Stadium
I'm so tired
Fpr sure Tanaka will be at this one
Seriously what do we do if this isn't the end
I can't say corporal punishment, but something like that
Something like that
For an episode
Something that's bound to leave a lump
So if we don't meet Tanaka right away, he's gone off somewhere else
Honestly I'm really scared to meet him now
Conversely
I might speak to him using honorifics
Trusting Tanaka is waiting for them, they arrive at the National Stadium
He should be here
He'll be here
We better meet him
But kind of, if I try to sense if someone else is coming here...
I can't sense Tanaka
I really can't sense Tanaka here
AHHHH!!!
It's Tanaka!
Here right?
I couldn't think of anywhere but here
We're kind of frightened of you.
You're just scary!
Starting today we'll address you with honorifics
No please, please that's the worst
But, this is the only answer right? Everyone will come here
That's what I want to believe
But those guys are coming from Asakusa right?
Would you seriously go all the way to Asakusa?
Starting in Roppongi
Exactly! I thought "Goddamn they took so long"
You're one to talk!
How long do you think we had to wait for you to go to Sancha!
And while we're saying this...
What if the staff tells us they've arrived
I'm really scared of them giving me the phone
You're right. You're so right.
15 minutes since the 3 of them met up
This is just..
Aren't they late?
It's been too long. It's worrying
I'm really worried now
They haven't gone to some insane place right?
It is possible
They might have gone to Komazawa
Komazawa right? That one too
AH!!!
Eh? They're here!
They're here right?
They're here!
So late
They finally came. Finally they came.
Senpai!!!!!
Are they fucking joking?
We waited so long!
I'm sorry
Matsumoto-san and I are thinking about an episode
I think we need to consider this; Making DownTown wait for that long...
That's, that's true
You too
All 3 of you
I'm sorry
Sorry, can I, can I just, call Chono-san?
Mou Chuugakusei - 24 Long Interview
Timed & Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband