- Let's start something fun.
- Yeah.
We were told by them to do a manzai.
- So we do a half hour manzai.
- That sounds like it.
Hey, man.
- Manzai is usually  about 15 minutes, right?
- Yeah.
We have to do it for 30 minutes.
Sounds fun, doesn't it?
You're also excited, aren't you?
Well, when I'm done, I'm going to line up the staff and beat them up one by one.
That's fine, but this time we're going to be able to do our manzai to the hilt.
- Yeah, that's good.
- It doesn't seem like you want to do it
We don't get to do manzai in Tokyo very often.
- So today we'll see how it goes.
- I wonder what will happen.
- Oh, they are looking for students.
- Let's join.
Downtown no
Gaki no tsukai ya arahende!!
#0001
Sorry for walking in so sloppily, even though we' re young.
But it's tough.
Even young people have tough times.
- I can't move the way I want. I know it's the first shot, so I'll do my best, but my joints hurt.
- What the hell.
- It's been a long time since I've done a manzai.
I miss it.
- Yeah.
- People in Tokyo don't know us.
- Of course they don't, because we haven't been to any shows in Tokyo.
- Many people don't know which agency we belong to.
We belong to Yoshimoto Kogyo.
- Do you know Yoshimoto Kogyo?
it's well-known among the public.
- It’s known for its low remuneration and for making us work like slaves.
- That's right.
We can do this calmly in these places, but it's difficult to do it at Namba Grand kagetsu.
- Because the bigwigs from Yoshimoto come to see us.
- They come to see us while we are doing manzai.
The bigwigs from the head office come to the back of the seats.
- If I say "the bigwigs from Yoshimoto," it's too long, so I say "yakuza".
- Hey!
They are not yakuza.
They look like them, though.
- Sometimes the chairman comes to see the show.
- Do you know the chairman of Yoshimoto?
He is an old coot named Shonosuke Hayashi.
He has gray hair and a cane.
He doesn't need it because he is in good health.
- He has a cane because he wants to poke comedians with it.
- Don't lie!
- "I want to poke them," he often says.
- Don't be silly.
Sometimes guys like that come to see us.
So it's difficult to do that.
- He looks at us on stage with a furrowed brow.
- He never laughs.
That's right.
He sees us with this looks on his face.
He doesn't know much about us.
- Even though we are Yoshimoto.
- He doesn't know us because there are so many comedians.
- He called someone.
- While we are doing our manzai.
"Who is that?"
"Who is that on stage right now?"
"They're Downtown."
- "Delete them."
- Don't lie!
No matter how bad he is, he won't say that.
- He says a lot of irresponsible things.
- He doesn't even think of us as humans.
He says a lot of irresponsible things.
The other day I met some bigwigs and I said, "Thank you for everything".
- He said to me, "I still don't know what you said".
- That's too bad.
It seems I'm not very smooth.
Sometimes I can't understand what I'm saying.
I know that, but I can't help it.
Even when I'm speaking now, you can't see my upper teeth.
My upper lip is long.
- It's a disease.
- Yes.
I'm trying my best to speak forward, but my voice hits back here.
He tries to speak, but his voice hits here and it doesn't come out.
- I explained it to him.
Then he said, "Cut around the mouth."
- Don't lie!
If you cut there, I'll see your gums and it'll be disgusting.
I thought I had to do that, so I talked to mom about it.
Did you?
Mom also agonized over it for about three days and said, "If you want to do it, then do it".
Really?
- So I went to the hospital and they drew just a cut line here.
- Where is it drawn?
I became a comedian to make money.
But I can't make much money at Yoshimoto.
Hey, what are you talking about?
- I think we are going the wrong way.
- Maybe so.
There were several professions I wanted to be when I was a student.
Many people want to be athletes.
Pilots, doctors...
I wanted to be a school teacher.
I liked the teachers in TV dramas who worked hard with their students.
There are usually pros and cons.
There are good teachers and bad teachers.
A teacher with a bad personality.
My gym teacher in high school was like that.
I hated him.
He would not admit his mistakes.
- He never tried to fix them?
- Yeah.
"Everyone, today you will have a bar test.
First, I'll show you how to do it.
Do it just like I did."
We watched him.
While rolling on the bar,  the teacher fell to the ground and cracked his head open.
His brain came out.
"Are you okay!?"
The teacher stood up and said.
"Do this."
There is no way he would say that!!
- Everyone's brain was out by the fifth period.
- Stop it already!
You don't have to say that much.
How can there be a teacher like that?
I always wanted to be a doctor.
It's good to be a doctor, but they have to think about their patients.
Suppose your child gets sick and you take him to a doctor.
It's hard for the parents.
"Doctor, how is my son?"
Is Masao going to be all right?
- Are you Masao-kun's father?
- Yes.
Come to think of it, you and he have similar eyes.
Yes...
His mouth looks like your wife's.
Is that so?
He does that move a lot.
Shut up!
I took his X-rays the other day.
Yes.
I got the copies.
There are about eight of them, so I put them up in the hallway.
Let me know if there is a photo number you want.
I'll let you know if there's one I want.
Let's look at one of them.
Here it is.
This is Masao-kun taken from a meteorological satellite.
- You took this picture of him from a distance.
- Yes, I have a good shot of him.
This will be difficult to understand without explanation.
I don't have the knowledge, so please tell me simply.
I understand. Let me put it simply.
He has a problem with his lungs.
His lungs are like "baaaang".
And his gut is like "baaang".
Wish it could have been like "bang" here, but it's more like "bang" here than I thought it would be.
That's why I was talking with everyone earlier about how I wish here was like "bang".
- Thank you.
- How am I supposed to understand that!?
Anyone can explain it like that.
What the hell is "baang", you bastard?
Yes?
- Please be serious!
- I understand.
This is about my son.
It‘s really serious.
Masao-kun has cancer.
It's funny, isn't it?
Doctor, please be serious.
Now I was taken by surprise by you.
Masao-kun has cancer.
There are various kinds of cancer.
His cancer is malignant.
In medical terms, it's a "really bad cancer".
I cannot guarantee his life.
He has six months to live and he will die as early as the second Saturday at 2:00.
Doctor, can't you do something?
Please do something about it.
No.
Don't say like that.
Please do something about it.
There is nothing I can do either.
You must never tell him that he has cancer.
- Is that the only way?
- Yes.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Masao, wait over there.
I'm having an important talk with him right now.
Doctor, please say something to him.
Masao-kun, don't listen to this conversation.
Can you wait outside?
You're a cancer patient, don't move so much.
You're going to die anyway!
If you move so much, your cancer will get even worse.
You are hateful.
Please don't let him find out about that.
Shut up!
You're the one who told me not to let him find out!
Hey!
Quiz shows these days are fun, aren't they?
Don't change the subject!!
You told me not to mention this, and I told him to go over there.
What do you mean, "quiz shows are fun"?
Quiz shows these days are fun.
it's fun, though!
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- There are so many quiz shows these days.
In one show, if you answer 10 questions correctly, you get a prize of one million yen and a travel to Hawaii.
You can make more money by participating in quiz shows than by working.
But it's hard to get the right answers.
So let's do a quiz today.
I'll give you the questions and you answer them.
I just told you.
If you answer the quiz correctly, you get one million yen in prize money.
Plus a travel to Hawaii.
I don't want that much in return, but I would like something in return.
Please consider my feelings.
- If you get the answer right, I'll switch from tomorrow between being the "boke" and the "tsukkomi" with you.
- I don't want to do that!
I don't want a million yen or a travel to Hawaii, but I do want a reward.
Philippines.
So if I get it right, I can go on a travel to the Philippines?
No, but tomorrow you'll be a Filipino.
- I don't want to be!
- You'll move your residency to the Philippines.
Why would I do that?
- Well, think of a reward.
- Yeah.
Do your best.
Okay.
First question.
Taro-kun went to the flower shop to buy flowers.
So, what do you think?
- Tick-tock, tick-tock.
- Don't say tick-tock!
What the hell is that question?
"He went to the flower shop to buy flowers.
So, what do you think? Tick-tock, tick-tock."
Are you fucking kidding me!?
What am I supposed...
- Stomping Quiz!!
- Listen to me!!!
- Time for a stomping quiz.
- What in hell is that?
What's the answer to that crazy question?
Don't say tick-tock.
And what's a stomping quiz all of a sudden?
- It’s stomping quiz.
- So what!?
Listen carefully and answer.
This is the second question.
Hanako-san went to a public bath.
So, what do you think?
Don't say tick-tock!
And what am I supposed to answer?
"Hanako-san went to a public bath.
So, what do you think?"
And what am I supposed to answer?
She got refreshed, didn't she!?
That's so-so.
Give me an answer!
If you think that's so-so, then tell me the right answer!
Is the quiz confusing?
That's not the point!!
I prefer to settle things through discussion as much as possible.
What am I supposed to say to a question like this?
You answer.
Okay, I will make the question easier to understand.
Isn't that obvious!?
- Why didn't you do it from the start?
- Okay.
Hamada-san, I've never done anything like this before.
Since it's you who answers, I'll make the question easier.
I'm sorry, but you'll have to.
Taro-kun went to the public bath.
Because!
Taro-kun loves to take a bath.
He sometimes goes there twice a day in summer.
So, what do you think?
Same as before!!
It doesn't matter to me if he goes there two or three times a summer, asshole!
Give me a clear-cut question instead of that.
You want to get punched in the face?
Say something!
- Exotic Quiz!!
- What the hell is that!?
- It’s exotic quiz.
- It doesn't matter.
If Taro went to the public bath, what would be the answer?
- It’s exotic quiz.
- It doesn't matter. What the hell is....
Ding-dong
What the hell!!!
- The buzzer went off.
- I don't care about that.
This is a bonus quiz.
If you can answer this, it will be doubled.
Good luck!
- What?
- It will be doubled.
What will be doubled?
Usually,  your points are doubled.
But you haven't answered a single question correctly yet.
There is no way I can answer a question like that.
So, I will be doubled.
You will be doubled?
I kinda want to see that, I'll try to answer correctly
Good luck.
- If I double, I will never disrespect you.
- Really?
Hamada-san, you are picky.
- Hey, wait.
- You complains a lot. So...
Everyone will say the same thing to you that I do.
You can pick your category.
Showbiz, history, sociology and geography.
You have already made the right answer.
- Which one will you pick?
- If you had done that from the beginning, I wouldn't have yelled at you.
- Sorry.
- Never mind.
- What can I pick from?
- Showbiz, history, sociology and geography.
Geography.
- Geography?
- Yes.
Geography...okay.
You should not pick that one.
Can't I just pick one I like?
How about history?
What?
Which one would you pick?
- Showbiz.
- Okay.
Showbiz....?
How about Geography?
Earlier you said I shouldn't pick Geography.
Pick whatever you want.
Then history.
History?
You want a history quiz?
- Huh?
- You want a history quiz?
Is there a problem?
- I said earlier that I would be doubled, and now I'm going to be multiplied by 4.
- What the hell!
You will be quadrupled!?
- I'll try to answer correctly
- History question.
Good luck.
Taisuke Itagaki.
So, what do you think?
Wait.
Give the same quiz to the audience.
And give me your answer.
You don't have to give the next quiz, just tell me the answer to it.
You only give a question, but you don't give an answer.
What am I supposed to say to that?
Give your answer.
What the hell am I...
- Last Chance Quiz!!
- Listen to me!!!
- It's time for the Last Chance Quiz.
- Answer it!
- This is the last chance.
- Shut up!
What's that?
- This is your last chance, good luck!
- Better yet, give me the answer to the question you just asked.
Good luck.
What's the answer to your earlier question!?
Is this question confusing?
That's not the point!!
Considering 1 mark as 46 yen would be comprehensible.
What the hell does that make it comprehensible!?
This is the last chance.
If you answer this correctly, Hamada-san will become a Filipino.
I don't want to be that!!
This is the last chance.
You bet on this!
You are messed up.
This is the last chance quiz.
- Make it an easy question.
- Okay.
Listen to the question carefully.
Were there 60 apples in the colander?
Yes.
Ding-dong, ding-dong!
Correct! You are a Filipino!
"Quiz: You are a Filipino from tomorrow."
See you next week at this time!
Oh, I'm tired.
Yeah.
Today is the first time I've ever been tired after doing a manzai.
Enough is enough.
I'm tired.
I spoke faster than I thought I would.
I know.
Were you a littl e nervous?
Maybe so. So let's not do this anymore.
No, we're going to do it,
don't stop.
We didn't have enough time today, we have to do it again next week.
- But...
- What?
But that's enough.
We didn't have enough time today.
Then next week, let's do it for 40 minutes, doubling the time.
How about changing the clientele?
Today's clientele was mostly female office workers.
So next week, let's invite Indians.
Do you mind if they are silent?
- We have a great curry joke.
- We don't have such a thing.
We don't have such a thing.
Curry joke?
Let's think about that too.
Do you want to change the clientele?
Yes.
But I thought today was the best one.
I guess so.
Let's do 30 or 40 minutes on time next week.
Yeah.
The staff probably thinks, "What the heck are these guys doing?"
Hey, don't nod, Yanaoka!
So, let's do a spirited manzai next week after a long time.
Why not this week?
Why didn't you do it from the start?
But this is a 2:10 AM broadcast.
What? You have a problem with the air time?
The guys watching this are probably sleepwalking, too.
Don't be ridiculous.
Let's make people laugh in the middle of the night.
There's probably no other comedy show going on tv right now.
No other TV station does comedy.
Only Nihon TV does this.
This is a comedy show at 2:10 AM.
That's what makes it a joke.
What's so funny?
Broadcast the current part.
Anyway, the first one was still not good enough for us.
So, can you do a half hour next week?
Are you asking me?
Who else but you?
Ah...hmm....yeah.
Say something like, " Of course I can".
Well, let's do it.
Maybe we' ll do it.
"Maybe"?
We'll be airing Downtown's manzai again next week.
In the meantime, please watch plenty of our manzai next week.
See you next week!
See you!
[Subbed by RAIDEN1017]