Third time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!
Let's play with table games from around the world!!
So, this is our 3rd round, Matsumoto
Endo Shozo
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Tanaka Naoki
Tsukitei Housei
Is there more?
Of course
The world's big
So of course we have tons left
There are still tons of fun games to do
Why when it comes to this corner
Do we have to completely rely on Tanaka, I mean
I never agreed on that
Tanaka learned the rules for each game from an expert beforehand
I thought so too
Why don't you just
Learn the rules yourself first?
No way I can take control of this
How much do you think I'll complain over that?
Don't underestimate me!!
Translation & subs by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
facebook.com/shionnotsukai
ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Choose the game which caught your interest between the collected games
From around the world and play it!!
Let's play with table games from around the world~!!
This time too
They'll experience the game which caught their interest
Between the collected items from around the world!
Germany - "Halli Galli"
Once 5 fruits are present on the table, ring the bell as quick as possible!
The first game Tanaka chose
Is "Halli Galli", from Germany!
Long story short
When 5 fruits are present
Quickly ring the bell
It's a speed card game
As you can see, there are 4 types of fruit on these cards
Just 4 of them?
Yes, just 4 types of fruit
And there are cards containing from 1 to 5 of them
And so
And let them down one by one
We'll distribute these cards
As soon as
their number counts 5 pieces, of any fruit
The same fruit must count a total of 5 pieces
So is this one already ok?
Well, this one is...
They're actually 6
Right, they're the same
It's here
As soon as they're 5, right?
Germany - "Halli Galli"
Ring the bell as soon as there are 5 of the same fruit on the table!
On that moment, yes
If you let the cards down and notice there are 5 fruits
This is so easy!
Pretty easy, yeah
Yeah
I can see
- I told you!
All of us pressing it at once
I'm giving each of you 6 cards
That's how it begins
So it could happen we get 5
of them as soon as we start...
Remember you shouldn't look at your cards
Ok
'Cause if you see, you'll know
Are those mine?
- Yes
Do we flip em from the top?
Yes
Let's start
note: I won't translate name labels, the color scheme is always the same: Matsumoto Hamada Endo Tanaka Housei
Don, don, alright
This is so hard!!
Come on we just started
This one too, right?
You sum em all up
- All of them?
So hard!!
The same type?!
Yeah, it has to be the same
What--?
This one's good, right?
Endo got it
- Does it count?
Endo ring it first
I did
So, these cards now are all Endo's
Germany - "Halli Galli"
The first one to press the bell
gets all the cards lying on the table
WHAT?!
He gets em all?!    - Yes
Yeah, the first one to press it gets em
Also, once you lose all your cards, you're out
Germany - "Halli Galli"
If you lose all of your cards, you're out
And can't play
You shoulda said it before then!!
I didn't think they had any value!
Right
Ok, from Endo
- Alright, I'm going
Ah... I'm wrong
These are 7 fruits, right?
I messed up
That's from before
And what now?
You made a mistake
So now you have to give one card
Germany - "Halli Galli"
If you make a mistake, you have to give each player one of your cards
To each one of us
I think he's... already done     - WHAT?!
You're done
One card for each of us?    - There aren't enough
I'm getting these
- But... Endo?
He doesn't get yours
- So he's out?
Yeah, he can't play anymore
Can I start?
Sure, let's go
MATSUMOTO GETS THE CARDS
That's right
Yup
So he gets these?      - Yeah
Pile em up like that
So you won't see them
- I didn't realize
Me too
Anyway, let's go
- Alright
MATSUMOTO GETS THE CARDS
Man I'm good
Amazing
I'm killing it!
This guy
is strong !!
Matsumoto-san?
He's strong!
- He's so good at this!
He's good
ENDO GETS THE CARDS
Who was it?
Me of course    - You, right?
It became a challenge between me and Matsumoto
Oh, Hamada-san, you're out of cards, aren't you?
Why you didn't say it?
He didn't say it
Tanaka too is about to
If he drops that it's over
One, two...
Here goes your last card       - Yes
ENDO GETS THE CARDS
But now it's between them, right?
When only two players remain
they have one last round
Ok    - I see
From this, we'll se who wins    - Can we go?
Germany - "Halli Galli"
The one with most cards after the match, wins
The remaining two players will have one last round until one of them wins it
You can
They're almost even
Starting from who?
Yeah, from who?
Me?     - Ok, from Endo then
One, two...
note: red arrow: "PAY ATTENTION"
That's it, we're done!
He took 'em
You weren't supposed to!
He should have taken only that one
- Right
You should have taken only that one
And the one with most cards, wins
Now we can't make it clear anymore
The ones I got from Endo
were around this...
No way, no way
There were more of them
These are too few
A drawing game based on words you can enjoy even if you're bad at it!
France - "Duplik"
The next game
Is about words and drawings
Which you can enjoy without being good at it
It's "Duplik", from France!
One person describes this picture
- explain the theme of the picture on the given card only by talking
- you choose who explains the picture and who will draw it
France - "Duplik"
the other players will listen and draw by guessing it
The others will listen to his explanation
And just by hearing that
They have to draw it anew
Only with words?
- Only with words
It's kinda like an e-kaki-uta
- Yes
It's about how you draw will come out
For example
The narrator has this card
"4 maids"
What's this?
It's about 4 maids
I see
- You can see it
I'll have to explain this situation, like
"There are 4 maids"
"They're walking facing left"
"Each one is carrying something" etc.
And so, you start drawing while you listen to me
After it, the 10 points hidden on the card's side will be revealed
France - "Duplik"
The time limit is 90 seconds
After drawing for
90 seconds, our time limit,
The 10 points hidden on the
card's right side will be revealed
France - "Duplik"
If you have a match with what's written in here, you score a point
It's not about your
drawing being good
The player who will fulfill
these points, will win!
Drawing:
Endo
Explaining:
Hamada
Housei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Tanaka will be
the narrator
And the others
will draw the picture
Before you start, let me tell you our topic
The topic is
"Breakfast"
BREAKFAST
TOPIC:
Got it
"Breakfast"
So, I want you guys
to draw a breakfast picture
Of course, after I'll
explain it to you
Ok, let's go
So...
A man is sat behind a table and is having breakfast
His face is really unique
So, the man...
Is sitting on a chair and he's facing left
W--wait
He's holding a newspaper
Also, on the table...
There is a cup of coffee and some pancakes
On top of the pancakes
Something like butter is dripping
On the pancakes' left side
There's some healthy looking food in a box, maybe cereal or flakes
So, I already said his face is really unique...
But his most unique feature is his nose
Surprisingly...
You shoulda said it before!!
Surprisingly,
On his head...
There's a chicken on the man's head
About the newspaper he's reading...
The chicken seems to be taking a look at it too
On the outside
On the sky
You can clearly see the sun
So if you thought it was inside a house, it's probably outside
The man is also wearing a bow tie
And he's well-dressed in general
A nice looking steam is coming out from the coffee
So...
On the table...
There are these 3 types of food
And he probably hasn't cut his moustaches yet
Alright, we're done!
What?! Wait a second
I think I've missed the fact there are 3 types of food
Is that so?
That was too fast
He was fast, there were too many informations
First off
- Yes?
I'd like to show the picture
The picture was this one
How is it?
He's facing that way...
Yeah, the left side
I made him face the front
I think I've said everything I could
What are the 3 foods?
Pancakes and also some cereal-looking thing
That's the one I didn't hear
Let's start from Housei's drawing      - Ok
Let's see what he did
This is his nose
This sucks
There's the nose, the newspaper and the chicken
His 3 foods
Pancakes, cereals, coffee
Also the Sun
I got most points
Ok, Endo
Mine is like this
His nose is unique
It's not bad
The chicken is peeping at his newspaper too
But I only put the pancake in here...
There's no coffee
The coffee
No coffee
and cereals
No sun too
The sun is missing too
There is
not, yeah
Ready, Matsumoto?
Why do I have to be the last one?
That surely is an unique face
Yeah but...
But when I first start drawing
the man, I made him face the front
You put a lot in here!
That could make him get points
- Yes, definitely
I see he's holding the coffee,
but there are no cereals
I didn't draw the cereals
That's impressive!
- Yes I think that
This is probably the closest one in terms of mood
Ok but...
We still got the champion here...
You're right
I bet he made a copy of that
- I don't think I can win
Ready to show it to us, Hamada?
He's floating midair
A prison?
The hell is this?
One thing is for sure, the Sun is clearly there
I know, right?
It's clearly there
Such thick lines...
where's the chicken?
I forgot about the chicken
You forgot about it?!
I didn't hear that
How can you forget about it?
Where's the newspaper?
I haven't drawn the newspaper
How do we judge these?
How many points?
I'm going to read you the 10 points
The 10 points written on the card's side are about to be revealed
And so,
It's time to reveal
The 10 points hidden
in the card!
First:
The man's nose
Is bigger than the chicken's beak
So subtle
I don't have a chicken to begin with
From the start
You missed it
How could you forget about it?
Second:
The chicken is standing on the man's head
Again, I don't have it
No chickens again
Third:
About the man's ears...
You can only see one of them
I got this
They're two...       - Eh?!
Did you say that?
Well, he's facing left
- That's 'cause he faces left
Got it?
Fourth:
There's some butter over the pancakes
I got this one, I got the butter
Is that butter?
...Is that but---
Of course it's butter!
I mean, it kinda looks like a 3rd pancake...
Looks like a whirpool to me
What the heck?
Fifth:
The newspaper is placed higher than the cereal box
You mean up?
- Yes, if it's higher, it's ok
Alright
Sixth:
The man has moustaches
AlrightI got them on his jaw too
- Oh, it's ok, there are moustaches
Yours is so smooth
Not a single hair
He's smooth...
- Smoothly smooth
No moustaches, huh...
Seventh:
The man is holding a newspaper
Ok, he's holding it
Hamada the news--
- oh, he's not holding it
Not even on his table
I thought he would
draw em both huge
No newspaper at all...
- Are all the points about these?!
You missed em all
Come on, say something
about the bow tie
Well...
I think it'll be a point
The bow tie I mean
- Yes, I'm sure of it
Eighth:
The piled-up pancakes are
not placed inside a plate
They're not?!
- Wha-!
Whaddya mean?!
Was it like that?
They're bigger than the plate
You didn't say that, Tanaka
You did not
He didn't, yeah
- Not that one
I didn't talk about this, yeah
This is ok, right?
This is not a plate
What's that?
This...
It's a placemat
What!
He never mentioned this before!
I don't think someone who doesn't
use plates would have a placemat
He barely even spoke today
Ninth:
Some steam is coming out from the coffee
Finally
Yes, I remember saying this one
Finally...
Did he say that...?
Tenth:
You can see the chicken's feathers
Feathers? Oh, here
Well, Hamada, you don't
have a chicken, so...
And it's over
Ok so, I scored 8 points
Me too, 8 points
I scored 6... can I see yours, Hamada?
Show it to us
He scored one point
How can he---?
Why didn't the bowtie come out?!
I guess the bowtie didn't come out
It's that...
Maybe it was to easy to remember
- It means it wasn't a point
I see...
Which one made you score your 1 point?
It was the steam
- The steam
Is that thing steam...?
Of course it's steam!
Something's strange
There are some parts seen from above
And other elements which are seen from the side
This table you draw
has a weird concept of space-time
space-time
You're right
It's distorted
- Amazing
Space-time is all distorted
That's what made it overall unpleasant
That's right
I've been thinking about what it could be
The answer was: space-time distortion!
The decisive match! Matsumoto vs Hamada
Now I feel relieved!
A one-vs-one competitive game!
France - "Gobblet Gobblers"
Next up
A one-vs-one battle game:
Gobblet Gobblers, from France!
I think you all did this as a kid
It's basically tic-tac-toe
France - "Gobblet Gobblers"
You win by making a row (horizontal ,vertical or diagonal)
In which you have to line up 3 items
horizontally, vertically or diagonally
I think I got it
Yes, as you can see
There are 3 pairs of pawns: small, medium and big
So, you...
You can use them to cover others?
That's right!
For example, the next person...
Places this here
And then the other does this
At this point he almost made
the row, so the next person
He can both put this one here
Or cover this?
Or cover that, yes
- I see
So you can cover them
- Exactly
- It is OK to place your bigger pawn over an opponent' s smaller one
-It is OK to move an already placed pawn wherever you want
France - "Gobblet Gobblers"
Also, if you've
placed a pawn
You can move it
and eat that of the opponent
You can do that too
Even if you're covering something?
- Yes, you can
FIRST MATCH
ROUND ONE
And so,
We'll have a tournament setting
First match: Housei vs Endo!
Alright, I'm going
Ok
Oh, you went for that?
So sudden
That's the boss
He used the boss
That way you can protect...
You can also move the one you've placed
Oh, is that so?
- Yes
This is complex
- It is
You can also move that one
Would have been better if you couldn't move em
It's an easy game, though
Is...?
Ah, Endo, that--
May I reconsider this move?
But you let go of your hand
That's it, man
You're so dumb
WINNER: HOUSEI
Endo...
"May I reconsider this move?"
Do you seriously think we'd allow that?
I knew you would lose first
ROUND ONE
SECOND MATCH
Next round
Is Matsumoto vs Hamada!
I guess I'll use this too
Of course that's it
That's probably the best move
I see...
I can move that one, right?       - Yes
You can move the ones you've placed
But one chance, right?
I mean, once per turn
- Yes
Damn, he got two bosses
He moved quite a lot
- Can he do that?
He can, he can move em how
many times he likes, wherever he likes
Oh, is that so
Yeah
That's why he moved it
- Yeah, otherwise he'd lose
What now?
Like that
That thing is traveling so much !!
You're only moving that!
He surely can move
Just that one
You're making it restless
The situation got severe
What would you do, Hamada?
You can't move that now
- I can't, true
I mean
That guy is doing everything by itself!!
You won't win like that!
He's not adding fighters to his army!
That's it
Nice move
Wonderful
Amazing, Hamada!
WINNER: HAMADA
That was great!
Well done Hamada, amazing!
Flawless
What!?
Hamada won
He must feel so embarrassed
I'm sorry!!
Cut this part off!!
I've completely forgot about it!!
I see now
The tournament's climax! Hamada vs Housei
What a great match
This game is fun!
FINAL ROUND
Our final Gobblet Gobblers match
Will be Housei vs Hamada!
I wonder how one can be good at this
Come on man, the huge one in the center again
It's going to become a trend
It's a must
- It is
It's pointless
You can feel the tension
This is a good match
This is going to sell well
It's fun
- It will sell
I don't have much moves left
Oh, I messed up
He finally noticed it!
You made it!
WINNER: HOUSEI
But it took him so much
So slow!    - Yeah
This guy is a mess too, but he's slow!
And then he was like "aaah!!"
He totally went "aaah!!"
That was fun
A balance game in which you have to take all the pieces!
Germany - "Bamboleo"
Our final game will be
Bamboleo, from Germany!
First, you place the cork ball over the black prop
Germany - "Bamboleo"
Then you place the board with the 27 pieces over it and make it stay still
First off, you place the
cork ball over the black prop
And over them,
You place the board with the
27 pieces of different shapes on it
Germany - "Bamboleo"
It's a balance game in which you take the pieces off the unstable board!
Each player will take 1 piece off
the unstable board per turn
It's a balance game!
It is already tilted!
- Yeah, I know
That means it's heavier on this side
- Exactly ,that's it
Should I start?
This looks harsh
I guess this one?
I think it's good
- Right?
THIS IS SO FUCKING HARD!!
This is way too fucking hard!!
A crazy difficult balancing game!!
One more time: Bamboleo Challenge
They regained control
And they'll try again
a Bamboleo challenge!
This time is tilted
on the other side
Yeah, this direction
You serious?
Go, Yama-chan
This is scary
This one, right?
For sure
Please...
Woah, it kept the balance
HOUSEI: CLEAR
Alright
Ok, he took it, but...
I see
That's true
It's bad for us
Imagine if it would
have ended here again
This one, right?
REMAINING:
This should be fine
I guess that's possible
MATSUMOTO: CLEAR
Nice move
REMAINING:
Must be this one
The farthest ones are risky
- I see
Maybe this
I want to keep playing...
Amazing
HAMADA: CLEAR
REMAINING:
You all picked up close ones
It's risky at this point
How about this?
The round one? I guess
that's the only one, may I?
Just go
And trust your guts
Ok, I'll take this
ENDO: CLEAR
That was good
Tanaka, Housei and Matsumoto clear their own's next round
After Endo
Tanaka,
Housei
And Matsumoto clear
each round successfully
Isn't it leaning too much
from this side?
REMAINING:
It's way too tilted
This is scary
I don't want it
to end like this today
Yeah but look
It's true it's too tilted
But isn't it even easier this way?
- Maybe
Is that so?
- It will withstand it
He made it
See? Told you
Alright...
HAMADA: CLEAR
I told you so
That was ok
Cautiously, they kept on taking pieces and collected 7 more of them!
After this,
They carefully kept on going
And took 7 more of them!
REMAINING:
This looks bad
This is bad
But maybe
Maybe I should take this....
Yeah, it could be
The middle one?
I think that just for this round, taking it won't be a problem
What really worries me is the
influence your move is gonna make
Don't worry Matsumoto, I'm positive you can do it
I'm sorry about this
and I know you'll all hate me because of this
Are you for real?
I'm leaving it to you, Matsumoto
Alright!
He made it
HOUSEI: CLEAR
He actually took it
He did it...     - Yeah
And now it gets hard
I can only see one possible choice
REMAINING:
I'm going for this, it's the only one
It won't fall
I think that one is fine
See?
MATSUMOTO: CLEAR
Amazing!
What now?
That was
amazing
Hamada, Endo, Tanaka and Housei clear their own's round
After him
Hamada,
Endo,
Tanaka
And Housei win their round
There are only 6 pieces left
REMAINING:
But wait, isn't this easy after all?
It has to be the nipple
I think this is probably hard
I mean, those two are pressing the board down
If you took one from
this side, it will tilt more
Yes, it will
Yes?
More Gaki no Tsukai episodes available on my website: shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Huh?
That's not what I---
Well, we told ya
You were right!
News, updates & bonus clips on my facebook page: facebook.com/shionnotsukai
Well well well...
You told him all the way
- It fell so smoothly
If you want to support this project, consider donating @ ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
He just became Akira 100%!
What kind of ending is this?!
DONATE TO SHOW SUPPORT: KO-FI.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
LIKE MY FB PAGE: FACEBOOK.COM/SHIONNOTSUKAI
MORE GAKI EPISODES: SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
THIS EPISODE IS THE THIRD PART OF A SERIES, YOU CAN FIND EPISODE 1, EPISODE 2 (FIRST HALF) AND EPISODE 2 (SECOND HALF) ON MY WORDPRESS (SHIONNOTSUKAI.WORDPRESS.COM
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT FANSUB, FROM A FAN TO OTHER FANS