Yujiro Ishihara
He's going at max tension right away
Aired last week, Music Memory Drive!
He's singing with his chest
They record nostalgic songs they sing acapella on casettes, and then drive while listening to them
Do we have to listen to this?
Yeah
That's what this episode is about
Ah there it is
His voice really tapers off
They seemed to have a lot of trouble singing their favourite songs
Gross!
It's kinda...
Something to sing before dying
It's like a buddhist chant
It really is, why do you sing so darkly
Eh but it's like this
"Because we live in a digital world, listen to my song in analog!" Music Memory Drive Start!
I was thinking, for this series, I think someone has to play Seiko-chan (Matsuda Seiko)
If we don't have someone like Matsuda Seiko, we can't really finish
I see
If we get Seiko-chan, things are gonna change a lot
No Yama-chan, he means the real singer
Did you think he meant from our casettes today?
He was smirking and checking his casettes
"Ah I'll play this"
Oh I see
What an idiot...
That's not it
Cause all we've heard is old men singing right?
Yama-chan, how about you put one in
I'll go with this one, not sure what it is
That's why
That's why he was smiling
Yeah, that's why
Like "Oh yeah, I got that card in my deck"
He is into it at least
That's true
He's got the right spirit
I get it
Normally if you sing this you'd look like a dumbass. So it's nice we had this episode
That's true
Yeah, it's good for Yamasaki
He excels at this doesn't he?
I think so
Yamasaki excels at this, after all
I got it now, after all this time
He shines when it comes to this kind of thing
Yeah, if you leave at home alone and ask him to do something
I see
And Tanaka is just so goddamn depressing
So, DaHama
DaHama-san if you will
I should've sung with my chest like Yama-chan
So, DaHama, the second song
Last one was Sakurada Junko-san right?
I guess singing a woman's song is different isn't it?
This is a man's song
Is he in the bathroom?
Are you in the bathroom?
He's totally in the bathroom
He should change location
Otoko no yujio sebangou 3 - Yujiro Ishihara
You can kinda hear the echo of the bathroom
He wanted to sing better
Is this Nagashima Shigeo?
Sebangou 3?
It sounds like Nagashima Shigeo-san
What is this?
I thought it was Enka or something
No no, it's Ishihara Yujiro-san
Enough of this song!
You wanted to play this in front of [@!@#!@] right?
Are you dumb
Ishihara Yujiro-san is covering Nagashima Shigeo
The song called "Otoko no yujio sebangou 3"
"sEbaNgoU sAn~" - I've never heard that before, and I don't want to hear it again
What the hell is this? So gross. Creepy!
Endo right?
Oh yes, this one
He did sing by himself at home
The best one maybe
I was able to sing loud
Listen here, Endo... Are you messing around?
It didn't sound like this!
He's messing about, He's messing about
I'm not at all!
No no, this is just strange
Yukiguni - Yoshi Ikuzo
It's kinda
Like he's mocking the singer
No no, I respect this song a lot, Yukiguni
Are you mocking it?
He's singing this while lying on his side
I was singing properly, right in front of the table
He really is
He made a joke of this
Endo you gotta take this seriosuly
But I am! Is this messing about?
You really can't mess around like this
Is this messing about?
Yeah
Chasing her, chasing her, chasing her ... Yukiguni
This is bad
Seriously?
If you do it like that you're finished
Is this messing about?
Yeah, you said "Yukiguri"
I didn't say Yukiguri. I said Yukiguni
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
Listen to my singing voice!
Nostalgic Song Drive!
In this episode, the 5 will drive along as they listen to songs they sung A cappella and recorded onto cassette tapes
That's one strong voice!
He really got us with this one
So, what will the next song be?
Was I really messing about?
Yeah you were
I'm not exactly trying to rank them right now, but this is definitely the worst one
Really?
You don't get a single point
Oh crap. I still have more here, can I continue?
Yeah you better hurry up and continue, you gotta erase the last one
A proper one please
A proper one?
I'm not messing about at all
A head to head battle
If it's with you, I don't mind dying anytime
Tokyo - Yashiki Takajin
Takajin-san?
He's mocking this one a bit too
He is kind of messing about
See
This is just how he sings
You shouldn't try and copy his singing style
Copy? But,
I'm not trying to copy him-
You could've sung with your own style
Why are you trying to imitate him?
You are trying to imitate him
Well of course
Seriously?
You can't do that
That's not on?
This makes no sense
A serious one
It was a serious one
So somber all of a sudden
It got so somber so quickly
So dark!
It's even more somber than his last song
Nagori Yuki - Iruka
Right?
This is so dark
Then wasn't Tokyo a better song?
What is this
It's not dark! It's this type of song
No no
But...
Your voice is gone
Exactly, exactly
My voice is gone you say...but it's that type of song
No it's a bit more-
It's a song for when you break up
You gotta let your voice out little more, sing a little louder
This guy sucks huh
Of course Hamada said that
Of course Hamada will say that
He does suck, I'm sorry, Matsumoto-san...
Matsumoto-san fucking sucks!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but,
I don't suck!
I'm not a bad singer at all
I'm thinking of releasing a cover album
I just don't want to, for real
A cover album, for Iruka?
Matsumoto got told he sucks, and is very displeased
Next, Tanaka will play his nostalgic song
I think the tempo is good, my voice is strong too
Are you confident?
Alright
I'm confident about this
That was a tricky bit, you could've burst your head from singing that fast
Was your wife about to get back home?
I love this song, I had to sing it
Darling - Sawada Kenji
You're kind of off key
Really?
The ending is always off key
This is Julie right?
I'm singing strongly here right?
So messy
Really?
What is that...
so creepy!
You're making fun of Julie right?
I'm not! I'm not!
So gross, this is so gross
I think my song from earlier was better
The Takajin song was better
Really?
It was better
Takajin-san just can't sing like that
Even if you tell an episode about your memory we wont listen
Yeah it seems we don't do episodes anymore
It's just become a singing contest
That's fine
That's true
This one is a home run
Please play it
I wanna redo this, properly
I wanna redo this
I can't stand being called somber so much
You're messing about!
Koibito Shiken - Matsumoto Chieko
It's Koibito Shiken! By Matsumoto Chieko!
You're definitley messing about!
I'm not!
That's not how you sing, you're messing about!
It was so cute though!
For real, it was so cute!
"It was so cute though" he says ... It wasn't cute at all! Gross!
It's not about being cute anyways
This is the one that shows my singing skills off the best
Oh yes play that one
You thought I sucked
This is also barely acceptable
You're off right from the start
Your voice is so shaky
I wanted to get this one done quickly
I couldn't
My voice is steady here, listen
We have to listen till the end, OK?
You're gonna make us listen to the end
Tanaka!
Fucking sucks doesn't it
I'm sorry
This is good idiot!
My "Darling" song was definitely better
This is good singing! Listen again
Isn't the tempo too slow?
It should be, a bit faster
Like;
Yeah, like that
Every song is depressing
Cause he's too slow?
Cause he's too slow
Ahh I see
You just can't get into it
Alright, then Tanaka,
Right now, could you sing A capella?
No preperation? Alright
Off key at the end
It's off key right?
You always go off key at the end
The "Nee" becomes "nEE"
It actually goes;
That's also a bit wrong
What a betrayal
I said so right?
Right?
He even said "Right?"
Innit?
He even said "innit"
He asked me "innit"
Alright then, I guess, next time we do this,
We should pick one song that everyone has to sing
I'd never lose a contest I created myself
I want to enter that contest too
No way... How can you say that?
Why would you say that?
No no, if it's a contest we create...
There's no way I'd lose
If Julie was there I'd be a little nervous
TN: Julie = Sawada Kenji
The real person?
Only the real singer would make you nervous?
I would get nervous, yeah
I would sweat, a little
Just a little?
Do you have a cheerful one Tanaka?
This one, the last one
A cheerful song, for real
Last one?
You really love this guy huh?
Casablanca Dandy - Sawada Kenji
He's already lost it from the start - He's going "keEkEE"
Really?
But what about my voice?
You sure love Julie
Yes, I like him
So cool!
He's so cool, he really is
Very cool
Goddamn what a mess!
You really messed that part up
It's such a mess!
Seriously?
You just yeeeeted off course
You really stretched that part out
No way
I think this might be considered his best song
Oh really?
Yes
He's streching it. He's losing it.
You're just going "GARI GARI GARI" against the guardrail
You've got your foot down on the accelerator....just grinding against the rail
I got it wrong huh
This is a great song
It is right?
I listen to it sometimes on YouTube
He spits out his whiskey and stuff
Yeah he does
This is a cool part
Wow
That was like,
A depressing guy forcing himself...
That's embarassing
The song itself changed
That's true
Dahama
Hamada-san please
I only have dark songs!
I have nothing up-tempo
That's true
For real let's redo this
Yeah, more cheerful songs
Why is there an echo?
He's definitely in the bathroom
He's singing in bathroom
Yuki Saori?
Oh I don't know this one. Do you?
I got it
Isn't this a great song too?
What is this? You're just getting in the tub
For real! Just singing as he gets in
You're just taking a bath
You're halfway inside
He's in high spirits
It's just dark
You know this, it's a breakup song
Remember a while back when Higashino got divorced?
We did karaoke and I sang this for him
Don't sing this!
Well he did remarry
Yes yes yes exactly. It turned out good in the end
"Tegami" right?
Yes "Tegami". It reminds me of Higashino
I see
Next time I guess I gotta do it like Yama-chan. Unless you go all out it's not fun.
That's true
Yama-chan how about you play one? You have so many
Me?
Yama-chan go on
Please let us listen
I think this one
He goes all out
There's a lot from the same artist
You just like them right Yamasaki?
You must have a lot of episodes
He has no episodes at all
I have no episodes at all
None at all...
Wow, is this Akina?
This singing style is amazing
This Akina singing style is amazing
You're so into it!
I would never think of taking on this challenge
Amazing
It's so difficult
It's difficult this song
He's so into it
Amazing (x3)
Amazing right?
It is, it really is
You know,
It makes me wish they increase Yamasaki's salary
I want to increase it for him, on Gaki
Amazing!
It would be nice if they increased his salary a bit more
Yeah
I think a 20% increase would be good
20%?
There's a lot of female singers though
Well for now, let's try this one
I have ones like this one too
A lot of genres right?
Yeah a lot
This is Sano Motoharu right?
Rock&Roll Night - Sano Motoharu
This is awful
You're kind of imitating him
He is.
But I guess that's unavoidable right?
He's surpassed the original
Awful (x3)
Just sing in your own voice
It's so exaggerated you can't tell who it is
Not good (x3)
Just listen to that a little longer please
Why?
Please, it's very-
The second half?
Yes
This is a good song
He's so on board
It's a great song right?
This was difficult..this was difficult
And it's a great song
And the singer is good too...I can understand that
There's a lot to bring together
Yes yes, exactly
I see, it's a lot to bring together
It's a lot to bring together
Understood
You even have to match the song and the brassiere
This time Hosei is on fire ... What nostalgic song will he play next?
For real,
He shut it off!
He won't even listen to it
What the hell is this so annoying
Matsumoto, please play it again, let's listen to it
The first part was so annoying
Enough
Can I take this home with me?
I think I'll laugh the entire time
You can dub it
I'll dub it
I'll dub this, I'l-----
Finally the drive is coming to an end
Tanaka you gotta do better next time
That's true
That's a true insult
You're right
You were so monotone
Yeah I was
So this'll be the last one of the day
Let's end with this
Yes please
Just amazing huh?
Amazing...
He got to sing all alone at home
So impressive
Amazing...
It's either this one... Or Sebangou 3
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband