A Special for the New Year - Yama-1 Grand Prix!
Every year, comedians take part
looking to catch their big break
I've ripened
Last week, every performer got 10 points, a miracle!
We will find the winner in this second part!
Translation by /u/senor_wristband
Typeset by /u/kannibleklown
Downtown
Matsumoto Hitoshi           Hamada Masatoshi
Yamasaki Hosei
Yeah we haven't seen any 8's or 9's
Cocorico
Endo Shozo                            Tanaka Naoki
They've all gotten the full 10 points so far
I want us to maintain this momentum
Let's hope our next performer can do that
Let's continue
Bringing back that famous song
In their 6th year, Double Name
Top Color Agency
Double Name
Hello, we are Chage and Aska
Please Enjoy
(They repeat this line)
Chage is a good guy
Thank you very much
I've heard
Yes
You are a huge fan of Yamasaki-san
We love him
Previously, Housei-san and I
He helped me out at this shady gig
What do you mean "shady gig"?
At that shady gig,
When he was helping us out
Housei-san is a nice guy after all,
He was asking the other performers
"Would you like some candy?"
He was handing out candy
I saw he gave only me a gummy
Do you remember this?
Sorry, I don't remember the gummy candy
But I do remember that shady business
So let's move on,
the score please!
TEN POIIIINTSSSSSS!!!!!
The new queen of realism
TN: Not sure about this translation, I apologise in advance because I think I am missing a lot of what she is saying
In her 9th year, Ume
Sony Music Artists
Ume
What a feast
Uh no please I'm full please no more
No I'm really full!
I literally can't eat anymore I'm so full, I will vomit
I cannot eat anymore than this
I cannot keep going
That is, so, no
I will become sick
I cannot eat anymore you haven't served me that meat yet
You haven't served me that yet
I cannot I can't I didn't ask for this Udon or rice
The rice and the udon that's liquor food I don't want anymore thank you for the meal
Thank you very much
Thank you very much!
Housei-san was really laughing
He really was
He was so into it!
He really liked it
He was laughing so much we couldn't hear anything
The performance?
I've got tears in my eyes
He says he got tears in his eyes
The score please!
TEN PPOOOOOIIIIIINNNTTSTSTSS
Another perfect score
A lonely guitarist with a depressing ballad
In his 13th year, AMEMIYA
A lot of songs this time
You're right
Sony Music Artists
My song is inspired by the words I see on the streets
For example,
"Hyashi Chuka is now on the menu"
TN: Hiyashi Chuka = Chilled Chinese Noodles
I think these simple words have a story to tell
"Gotta be ready by Summer, I've been working on them since spring"
"I've reworked it so many times to get the taste right.
Now today,"
"The 20th of December, finally at our ramen shop,"
"Hiyahi Chuka is now on the menu!"
"While I was busy working, my wife fell in love with a host"
He's good
"Hiyashi Chuka is now on the menu"
"I'm in debt cause someone made a credit card in my name"
"Someone's been committing arson, I didn't know I had life insurance"
"Hyashi Chuka is now on the menu"
Who cares
"It's been half a year since my wife ran off with that host"
"This year I think it's time for that special summer treat"
"I've been skimping on the ham bit by bit"
"Hiyashi Chuka, is now on the menu"
"I get a call complaining about food poisining,"
That's enough already
"Hiyashi Chuka is now on the menu"
Stop it, stop it!
"I've been hosptalised from the stress, my hair is receding"
"Hiyashi Chuka is now on the menu"
"Suddenly somebody appears, and tells me he's my son"
"All over the world, terrorists lurk in hiding"
He's going there?
"Why do people hurt, and hurt each other?"
"Hiyahsi Chuka is now on the menu"
"Hiyahsi Chuka, Hiyahsi Chuka"
"Hiyahsi Chuka, is now on the menu"
Thank you very much
Thank you!
AMEMIYA is very happy
I hope you could hear me
We heard it
I learned a lot
AMEMIYA is very happy
What the hell is that?
Matsumoto you heard him right?
What the hell are you?
He sounded like my brother, it was good still,
BUT!
This time Yamasaki-san...
He might be harsher this time
It's been all 10 points until now
The score please
TEN POOOOIIINNTSSS
I'm very happy, thank you!
This 2011 will be your big break, I think you will be busy
AMEMIYA thinks so too
This guy is so annoying
A new format after 20 years of comedy
in their 20th year, X-Gun! (X = Batsu)
Horipro Agency
I guess we're here, the first job of the year,
Hold on
here at Gaki no Tsukai-
"Batsu-gun!", you forgot our intro
Ah, my bad, I'm sorry
No man, if you mess up our pacing at such an important place
You kill our momentum
Well, sorry, sorry.
Let's get this going, let's go!
Even if you say "sorry, sorry"
It's not about whether or not I'm gonna forgive you right now
I mean If this show calls us on again after that mistake, I'll forgive you,
If they never call us again cause of that, I will never respect you again
Did I really do something that bad?
That is what being on TV is all about
This is our big chance
How many new year specials have we been invited to?
One
We finally got this chance
And you messed it all up
We're truly finished
Seriously
Ok?
You have that one-shot gag right?
You brought a note with you one time
You left it by your feet so I thought
"He's gonna do that gag?"
For seven hours you didn't speak a word
Why?
Why the note?
Why did you bring that note?
I wanted to do it
You wanted to?
But you didn't, huh?
You thought someone was gonna ask you "hey do that gag"?
You can't take initiative, you've always been like that
You haven't changed since our debut
Seriously
You and Arita, you guys met Sanma-san
And you told me "i cAn fiNalLy pErFoRm"
But you went on stage and only Arita and Yamasaki were talking
You didn't speak at all
And that's the result now, Yamasaki is below Arita
This is the clear result
What the hell is he saying?
Seriously
This is nonsense
And then another thing, you were like,
"I'm the tsukommi in our manzai,
but on location shoots and stuff can I boke?"
Of course it's fine
And when we were on that show, you didn't speak for seven hours,
even though it was such an easy environment
Why didn't you Boke then?
Just forgive him already
Seriously
Just forgive him!
Today is no different
I forgot the map, I asked you where the exit is, you said you were at A-1
And I couldn't find A-1, I though "huh?" when I saw something
You were on the other side of the door
That was A-5
If you can't handle that then what can you do?
And you're going "mmm" like you're angry too
But I don't give a shit, you know why?
For so many years I've been dealing with your bullshit
Apologise, just apologise!
It's over if you apologise
sorry
"sorry" - I don't really care cause you've been telling me that forever
I'll be grateful if you change
Sorry about that, thank you very much
He got really scolded you
Scolded? Well another thing-
We've been on Cocorico's TV shows a bunch too
I was a little bit nervous,
"Don't worry, Endo and I are like best buds" - and yet he didn't speak a single word
There's a story about you and Downtown-san...
Yes, Downtown-san and us
Before our debut, on a "Warate Iitomo!" corner,
It was a corner that showcased amateurs
There was a Hamada and Matsumoto team
We were on Hamada-san's team
And we were super nervous when Hamada-san came to say hello
"You guys are comedians?"
"Yes!"
And when Eri-san called Hamada-san over, while he was walking,
He turned to us
"Boke as much as you can, I'll tsukommi everything"
"SO COOL!" we thought
That's cool
and then after, we were on a Gaki no Tsukai "Kinpachi Sensei" shooting
A long time ago
and he's an amazing guy
It would be troublesome to take pictures individually,
So Hamada-san took pictures in blocks of people
"What a nice guy" I thought
So he was taking pictures in blocks,
and when he finally got to our block,
There was an excited high schooler going like "Yay!!!" with Hamada-san
At first Hamada-san was like "ok ok"
The second time he went "Yayy!", Hamada-san went "HEY ASSHOLE!"
"ARE YOU TAKING THE PISS, HUH?!"
And us,
Just looked up from the camera without taking a picture
You would be shocked
I didn't know what his real personality was
I see
And Sagane-san?
Do you have any memories with Downtown
Yes
There's gotta be something
I've always been, uh, watching them on TV
He's gonna scold you again
That is something a non-comedian would say
Yamasaki-san, the score please
TEN POOONTSTSTSTST ST ST ST S ST ST ST
10 points! Another 10 points
So let's keep going
Let's go!
These M-1 winners came up with a new sketch for today,
In their 8th year, Surimu Club
Hello, thank you very much!
Yoshimoto Creative Agency
Surimu Club
Sketch: New Lifeform
What are you?
I am
This star's
most
lowest level gender
Excuse me
I'll leave in 5 minutes
Just a little will do,
Could you provide me some gasoline?
What do you need it for?
For that reason,
I cannot give you any gasoline
GYAHHH
This
memory stick,
contains
until now
the memory of the best sex I've ever had
So what?
I shall give you some gasoline
Thank you
My next request,
Batteries
I will give you two of them
On the places I cannot reach
please rub this medicine
The non-circled spots please
What the hell?
If I apply this medicine everyday at a set time,
An certain organisation gives me 100,000 yen
This is a story from the year 2200
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much
I've heard
From February onwards, you have continuous work booked up
Yes thanks to everyone
We didn't have much work before
M-1 was really good to us
I heard you had 1 job you turned down
Turned down?
It was just me
I was invited to a talk show with Kato Taka-san
TN: A famous porn star
The scheduling didn't work out
Cause you're so busy, Surimo Club is busy
Yamasaki-san, the score please
54454e20504f494e545321
What did you like about it?
Huh, hold on, my ear ...
We'll wait for you
Endo, give me a second
There's water in my ear
Water in your ear?
I can't get it out!
I understand
So Tanaka-san, finally tonight's key performer
Key-perfomer, yes
Let's continue
The filthiest comedian, here at Yama-1
In his 24th year, Mimata Matazo
He's here
Office Kitano
Mimata Matazo
Mimata, Mimata, Mima-mimata!
Oh shit wait
You messed up
Even if you messed up, you shouldn't say it
We wouldn't have noticed
I messed up
You were the key performer too, how was it?
At Kouhaku Uta Gassen
TN: end of year special by NHK
Misora Hibari-san always has this energy as the key performer
So I was really nervous
Excuse me, but your breath smells like shit
What happened?
Even though you're my senpai, it just stinks so bad
I'm sorry
I've been told this before, that my breath stinks
I went to the dentist and got all my cavities done
The nervousness makes the smell come out
A lot came out right now
So Yamasaki-san
Mimata, you really did it
The score please
8 points
That's kind of generous
It's 1 out of 10, normally
That was twisted. Twisted 2.5 times.
Yes! Someone in the back laughed at that!
Guy in the back, come on out!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much
Finally, the results. Who shall clutch victory?!
Entry Number 1
Ume-chan!
I want to do a joint live with you
Joint?
he wants to do a show together
Looking forward to it
Yes
After the recording was over,
An outrageous incident occurred!
Turn the camera on a second
Is it recording?
Is it OK?
You ate my strawberry didn't you?!
Seriously?
There was a strawberry here right?
Yes there was
Yeah yeah yeah exactly
I definitely did not eat any strawberry
Why the hell did you eat my strawberry?!
It was just sitting there ....
You ate it?
Hamada-san that's not right
He ate 4 strawberries
Are you bloody serious?
Did you seriously eat my strawberry?
When?
While watching the performance
The camera definitely caught him
There's footage of it
Just need to know the timing
That was during the top batter, Open Space's perfomance
It was 15 seconds after the performance started
He made sure Matsumoto is focused on the performance
The strawberry glutton Hamada!
Furthermore, he ate the remaining single one!
He actually ate it
You weren't eating it anyways!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
Strawberry, is a sweet
I will of course eat it at the end