On tonight's Gaki No Tsukai,
With Suda Masaki,
Cookie's Woman Diver Classroom
Just stay there!
You dirty chimpanzee person
What will happen in this final part?!
Everyone, your Abalone has been stolen! Hurry!
Hey!
Over the 30 odd years of Gaki,
don't you think this is the worst episode ever?
They head towards a shocking climax
You idiots!
Worthless
Subbed by senor_wristband
Sensei, time for the next training
You know, as divers we need to be careful on land
Land is scary after all
We are people of the sea
Endo, what do you think the dangers of Land are?
Umm, there's a lot of crabs right?
On land right?
That's a good answer
Amazing, clap for him
Clap for Endo
That's alright please
Tanaka, what do you think?
/he commercial vehicles, like the ones moving containers /
Enough man, you're not even close
The commerical drivers are professionals!
They drive carefully and sound their horns!
Who's gonna hit you?!
With their shoulders? !
TN: I have no idea what Cookie is saying here, sorry
Your answer was way off, OK?
Sorry, I'm sorry
Suda, what do you think it is?
He really wants to know everyone's opinion
He really does!
We've said plenty already
I guess something to keep your body warm, like a jacket,
C'mon man, you really think there's people who go like this to warm themselves up?
Of course there are
I've never seen that
Do they come out of the water like this, holding an umbrella?
Like Nagabuchi in the opening of Tombo
Do they come out like that?
You're gonna get scolded
Huh? Like Nagabuchi, wearing that little hat walking out
They come out like this?
(sining the lyrics to the OP song from Tombo)
Move on already!
The scariest thing on Land - thieves that want to steal your haul
Look here
What's that, so off putting
Gross!
So gross!
When rehearsing for today I also jumped back at them
You gotta protect them, from being taken
Seriously,  you better protect these
Cause I'll kick you all in the nose
I'll wear some Doc Martins to do it
Ouch
I'll wear some Doc Martins that aren't on sale anymore
Tanaka used to wear those
I did
Oh really, today?
Not today
Back then right?
Back when I debuted
Then don't say "I wore those" you stupid little shit
Woah, woah,
It's not like Tanaka was the one who said it
Right?
Who said that?
It was me
Oh that's OK then
What's up with that?
He's really listening to his ribs
In last week's episode, Cookie-sensei was really harsh on Hamada
Sorry! I thought you were a really low ranking person!
Huh? What's that? I'm low ranking?
That pain remained with him
I felt a sharp pain when we made eye contact
Actually yeah seriously can I take a break?
Cause my ribs hurt
Everyone, let's take a break
We're taking a break?
Please wait over there
The training is paused for now
The anti-theif training will be resumed later
What's with that guy? Is he for real?
Yeah why did he take a break now?
Yeah, weird timing
Suda, is this good promotion? (for his show)
It isn't
This is like anti promotion
Anti promo?
5 Minutes Later
Hmm?
An old man out of nowhere
We can't let him come on set
We're filming something here
Excuse me!
Yeah tell him
Excuse me, sorry, we're shooting something here,
Oh OK
Sorry about that
He's got an amazing body
A great figure
Smart Phone
Don't film!
Oh no
Macchan
Can I shake your hand?
Sorry
Adachi, take him somewhere
Sorry, please,
Don't film!
Old man, don't film
TN: Tsukommi is the retort in a Manzai performance
Your Tsukommi is great!
Close, you're too close
It's troublesome if this goes viral
You're working right now?
Yes, we are
Good luck!
What a body
People like that don't really interrupt shoots these days
They don't yeah
Oh no, he's taking them
The abalone
Everyone, your abalone has been stolen!
Hurry, let's chase him!
Wait, this?
This was the training?
Stop, stop!
Everyone, your abalone!
Hold on, stop!
Hey, stop!
In the 30 odd years we've been doing this,
Don't you think this is the worst episode yet?
Wait, we can't go any closer!
Why can't we?
Damn it, we can't get any closer!
Why the hell?
Look, he's gone, he got away
Damn! We lost him!
Everyone, your abalone was stolen!
So unfortunate!
If only you guys were faster
We tried, but you stopped us!
We couldn't get any closer
What do you mean
You told us to chase him slowly
I did tell you to chase him slowly ... But we lost him!
What the hell are you on about?
What kind of act is this?
What happened Adachi?
That bastard, stealing your abalone like that
Where is he?
There he is
What is he doing?
Old man!
Sir!
He lives in there?
It does seem like that
Congratulations! We're having abalone!
Tell daddy thank you!
That one's for you
Ah, it's his family
Darling, good work!
He's showing off with stolen goods
I mean, a thief is a thief...
I guess we shouldn't confront him in front of his child
He's staring at us a lot
Our eyes met
These are some people I know, you guys eat dinner
What a nasty face
I-I'm sorry, for stealing your abalone
You know, if I was still young and healthy, I would get a job,
But at some point I became this old, and work became hard to find
That abalone you worked so hard for ... It was supposed to be our dinner
And now you know how we live, I'm sorry!
Please, raise your head
Everyone, I know it isn't much but,
I can give each of you, some Chrome Hearts jewlery
You DO have money
Isn't that more expensive?
You have money after all
That's silver
A tranquil break from training
It's definitely that
Definitely
It really fits him
What a beautiful bike!
It's brand new
Let's eat
Cookie-sensei wil treat the hardworking members to a feast
How do you want your sushi?
You're making sushi?
Yup
Eat up OK?
This "stall"...
It's warm today
I brought the toppings today so we'll be fine
But you know, today this,...
I am a bit worried
Will it be hygenic?
Let's start with Hama-chan's
Here you are
What is this?
It's CEO Osaki's hair
TN: CEO of Yoshimoto
It does look like that
It's not food
I Dogeza'd so comedically after cutting his hair
TN: Dogeza is the act of kneeling and prostrating before someone
My body was so low to the ground
I've got something for Macchan too
Let me put the topping on
What's that?
It's Miyagawa Tamako's hair
Her and CEO Osaki form a set after all
They were holding hands at the Okinawa Film Festival opening
You want some? You can if you want
It's yours
We're alright
He made it for you
Suda-kun, here's yours
A good one for you
Here, this is yours
It's all just hair
This is Megumi Yusuke's hair
It's turned that colour recently
It's got some Kosaki Gazuki mixed into it
Why'd you mix them?
Then, let's do Yamasaki Hosei
Something different now
Looks tasty
TN: Hosei's Rakugo master
This is Tsukitei Happo's skin
The master's
You're making me laugh! Let's move on
Suda-kun, let's move on
Woman divers are, after all, working women
They're powerful working women, so they gotta take care of their husbands
So let's train to take care of our husbands
What's that mean
This is a time attack, using a 3 wheel bicycle
They must rush towards their husband, who is sleeping 30 metres ahead
They must wake and dress him, place him in the bike, and set off
They must then prepare his lunch with lots of love on the way back
Will their fishermen husbands be able to make it?!
So this is about time, and, uhh...
The, uhh, style of the lunch
And the style of how you wake him
And, uh, the style of you placing him in the bike,
What do you mean by "style"?
What kind of word is that to use now, "style"
Alright Suda, sit down
Just sit down
What are we doing?
WHAT?!
I've no idea what you've been saying
I seriously want to punch you
Darling! Wake up!
Training to get the sleeping husband to the fishing boat on time
Suda takes the challenge first
Suda-san, let's go
Faster is better right?
Good luck, hurry
Darling! Wake up!
That's great!
Wake up!
He placed the bike well
The husband is not waking up at all
So annoying!
The husband is not cooperating at all
He should wake up from being treated like that
He's so rough
My husband won't fit
Stuff his knees in more
You can stuff knees?
That is a scary sound!
I thought that thing farted!
The lunch box!
The lunch!
There, right there
Woah, there's a lot
Eh? A lunch box?
I don't wanna do this
I straight up don't wanna do this
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry! Make it with love!
Put your feelings for him into it
The husband isn't waking up at all
Man doing this in 1 minute is impossible
His time?
1 minute, and 43 theckonds - *seconds
What's a "theckond"?
That was the important part
Was that bad?
Garbage! Let's check your lunch
I'm opening it
Well...
Looks fine to me
I put cabbage in and everything
Cabbage? Oh okay then
Despite his performance, his score is 15
A score of 15, this is Idiot Time
Idiot Time, you know what I mean
Idiot Time?
You are IdiotMan
You are not Suda Masaki
You are Tsuketei IdiotMan
Tsuketei is unnecessary
Why is Tsukitei his surname?
Tsuketei IdiotMan?
Next, Tanaka takes the challenge
C'mon!
Hey wake up!
Hurry up!
Wake up darling!
Just look at him once
You need to get on that boat!
Wake up honey!
It would be nice if the buttons were open
Each button is worth 5 points
That sucks
He's telling you after you went
I can't remember a thing he said
He got him in though!
What a terrifying husband
He's in the Inugami Family
On top of taking too much time, there's another problem
Tanaka - 2 min 32 sec
Even Suda was faster!
Sorry, but this is not funy
That's no good?
Being upside down is fine, but these socks
This, this is just a swan
Another swan will show up, and they're gonna form a heart
A beautiful swan heart will be formed
That, is a huge problem
Who cares!
Why is that a bad thing
Are you not gonna do it Sensei?
Cause I'm just extraordinary
We want to see that
I'll just be like-
I wanna see that!
We definitely wanna see that
Cookie-sensei prepares before starting
A person of my class can do this one handed
I'm not bending my elbow
Cause I'm a man of my class
...Let's go
What the hell is he saying
Cookie-sensei is desperate to display his skills after those 2 went
So unnecessary
Amazing seating arrangement
Look at the angle his husband is at
A chaotic awakening for the husband
And the lunch box made with love;
Rice, and a single Takoyaki
Takoyaki isn't really a good side dish
THAT DEPENDS ON YOUR TASTES THOUGH!
That's just, c'mon man what a stupid statement! It's making me laugh, sorry!
What an annoying face!
It's time for Suda-kun to leave
Eh, really?
Yeah, get lost
What a way to say goodbye
Sorry, you aren't cut out to be an Ama-san
You're shit
I'm shit?
I worked pretty hard though
Then let's end this
Yeah, we can stop here
Don't drop out halfway, let's push on
Let's all point our sabres towards the sky,
"THE GLORY OF THIS SABRE, OUR BROTHERHOOD, THE AMA-FIVE!"
Let's do that!
We're the AMA-Five!
Well good luck then!
Thank you, thank you, excuse me
He's so lucky
This next training is our last,
Finally
For the next training, well, the sea is hard to work in
Since sometimes we can't find anything, we will train to steal from the Ama-san of the neighbouring town
We're gonna get complaints
Training to steal?
Cookie-sensei's training to steal shellfish
The winner is whoever steals the most sea food
However, halfway through a guard will appear
The members recieve bags to store their loot, and clubs for self defense
So let's begin
Sea Food Acquisition Training START
Steal please
Steal the sea food please
Whoever steals the most wins
Wait everyone!
The guard is coming!
Whoever steals the most, wins
Wait everyone!
The guard is coming!
Oh no! The guard is the Terminator!
Everyone, run away!
Run away everyone please!
Run away?
Wait, it seems his movements are slower than expected
Steal the fish!
Before he catches you, steal a lot!
We're counting on you-
Another guard has appeared!
Hmm?
He didn't leave?
He's supposed to be gone
It's Terminator's rival, T-1000!
What a terrible combination
T-1000 is here! What will happen!
This is...
This is just...
This is shi-
They're shaking hands
Fighting is Forbidden
Peace is Paramount
That is the meaning of,
Gaki no Tsukai
Uh, no
This handshake brings peace to this city!
Matsumoto-san, let's just go home
We can leave now?
Yeah, there's no point waiting on them
You idiots!
Worthless!
Suda-kun was on his side all along
Yeah Suda was his collaborator
He had me fooled the whole time
PEACE IS PARAMOUNT
PEACE, IS PARAMOUNT
This is so exhausting
Good work
Thank you
KU! Come here
He wants to talk to you
Dinner?
So you and Suda were just messing with us?
From the beginning
Yeah
You're with him, right?
I've been told this whole episode was his idea
That's horrible
There's no way I'd do that
He threw it away
There's no way
Before the shoot started, Suda came to rehearse with Cookie
Sorry about this Suda-san
This may be your first bad performance in your life
It's a wonderful thing to be unfunny
I guess I just have to do as I'm told
I'm happy though
You're so messed up!
I set everything up?
You did all this for your sponsorship right?
What are you saying?!