First time on Gaki No Tsukai CHIKI CHIKI
Sudden Japanese Dance Competition!
Well, we've never dOnE - Done this before today
Sorry?
We knew nothing about this
Just suddenly
With no preparation we did it
And well of course I knew we were doing this a few weeks ago,
I hate cheating, so I didn't watch any videos or anything
FOR REAL?!
Really, really
To preserve that sense of uncertainty
This time they will come up with a classical Japanese Dance, knowing nothing about it beforehand
They choose 1 outfit from 5, and apply the makeup themselves too
And then hearing the music for the first time, they improvise an original dance
No messing about here! Just how will they fare?
After doing this, I think what you need is a delicate touch
Ah, I see
That's true, certainly
Vulgar people couldn't do this
And, and uh
I'm really looking forward to Hamada-san's performance
I think I will do better than Endo
Endo does seem to be the odd one out
Well to weturn your words-
You didn't return them
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
How will their dances turn out?
They rely only on their imagination in this Japanese Dance Contest
This time the five improvise a brand new Japanese Dance by listening to the music
Let's start with Tanaka
Good morning, good morning
First he chooses from 5 outfits the one he wants to dance in
There's a lot here
So I  just decide now? Wow!
(staff)You decide now
Already deciding?
Kagami Jishi, or the Tenaraiko?
I have no idea
This looks really intimidating to me, this thing from the Kagami Jishi
I have no idea what this is for
I'm just supposed to decide now right?
You decide right now
Then I think I'll go with this
Tenaraiko, let's go with this one
Are you ready?
Of course not!
I have no idea what to do after all
Tanaka chose the Tenaraiko, a girl that dances with a paper umbrella in her hand
Before starting the dance, he puts on makeup that should be fitting for a Tenaraiko
This is difficult
But I'll believe in myself
Tanaka aims for a refined makeup look
How will Tanaka's Tenaraiko performance go?
Tanaka's VTR ... START!
This is the first time I heard the music
Right, right the first time. Didn't know anything beforehand.
This is a difficult judgement
I don't think I'm doing too bad
What is this incredibly annoying vibe
What are you a courtesan?! This isn't a Tenaraiko!
This is a Tenaraiko!
You've got that part wrong, those movements are unnecessary
If anything, this is the opposite of a Tenaraiko...
What's with the paper bag?
It seems to be part of the costume, it was prepared for me
I see, right. Well, you sure do move slowly.
Right? That's a dance move right?
Well then ... What happened?
You're really using the stage
Yes yes indeed
What's the point of spinning that?!
They do that sometimes!
Shouldn't you paint your neck white too?
Ah! Should I have?
Yeah you should have
He's backing up!
I'd never think to see backwards walking in a Japanese Dance
See
That face is annoying
It's unsightly,
And this guy's chin is too long
The chin sticks out
The chin is too long
Finally he puts it down. What the hell are you doing?
What the hell is that?
It's a Tenaraiko thing
What the hell?
He's going "OooooOOh"
Ah, you have to do that too?
Yeah like-
Then hurry up and do it!
You should've used that prop sooner
This was pretty long
It was pretty long wasn't it?
It's over, it's over
Could you just tell us what the scene is supposed to be?
I think she's going to a temple school, she has a caligraphy class,
So I think she's supposed to be on her way
She's heading there?
I think she's heading there
Hurry up and go then
But, but that's what Japanese Dance is like. I was supressing the emotions and displaying them.
He's backing up and everything
I see
So next, Endo?
Endo what did you dance?
"Have the plums blossomed?"
I think you should know this one, it's pretty famous
Did you know this one?
Yeah I have some idea
Honestly it's the first time I've heard this song
Surely you've heard the song before?
I think it's a pretty high-tempo song
High tempo?!
I can kind of smell the danger already
Endo chose "Have the Plums Blossomed?"
A famous piece, explaining femininity using flowers and shellfish
First off is the makeup based on the title
The base is white isn't it
Endo applies his makeup with an unusually serious expression
On Sunday, there was a 2 hour TV show, I'm trying to imitate someone from that
I think it was a Geisha
But a Geisha is different to this right?
Are Japanese Dancers the same as Geisha?
Wait I think I learned something from that
Oh yeah!
Alright, I got this. I got it
He bases his makeup on a Geisha he saw on TV
How will Endo's "Have The Plums Blossomed" go?
Oh no
Really?
You're moving so much!
My stomach hurts!
This is amazing!
This is just High Tension!
This is Endo's High Tension performance
I was taking this seriously!
Take this seriously!
I was!
You're gonna do a Hoi Hoi Hoi too?
I wish I could've messed about too then
I was taking this really seriously
I get it though, if you have to dance you just end up moving like that
This is just scary!
So scary!
Where the hell are you looking
It's very obvious you're out of breath
That's correct
What the hell is that?
First time I've seen that
Let's ask about that, what is that?
Wow, he's even doing the other way
He did it both ways
What is this?
Let's ask about this. Just what is this?
So monotonous!
He just repeats those moves!
That's true
He did a 1.5 turn
He's scooping loaches!
There it is!
Eh I got it all wrong?
You got it wrong
What happened? You're trying to convey it's too bright?
Yes, thank you. It's too bright.
He's looking in many directions
He does the same thing for too long
There's no variation
It's like Tanaka's
Thank you very much
What was the point of that "Bright" expression?
What was that?
Well it's called "Have The Plums Blossomed?", so I thought she would be waiting outside
Like she's wandering around looking for plums
What does that even mean
What was that knee scraping?
Oh yeah, that leg move
I was compacting the soil
The beans ... Sorry the seeds, putting the seeds in the ground
Beans?
I said beans by accident
You were planting plum beans?
Are you talking about Setsubun? (Spring Festival)
Let's do Yama-chan now?
Yes please
Good morning
Very pretty
What should I do...
This one...What should I do...
Woah hold on
Alright, I'll go with Kagami Jishi
Hosei chose the Kagami Jishi (Lion Dance) - performed by a lady of the court
He starts applying his makeup right away
Unlike the past 2 performers, he paints beyond his face
You have to take care of all the visible parts
Japanese beauty is in the small details after all
He delicately applies his makeup, to invoke the beauty of a Japanese woman
How will Hosei's Kagami Jishi go?
I see! You start like that?
He's into it, he's definitely really into it
They're round! Look at his eyebrows!
That's not right, they're circles
No no c'mon-
He's got the face right
He's really got the face down
That's how you use the lion head?
Seems that way
I'm the most feminine one
This... What do we make of this?
Man you're used to this aren't you?
Wow!
He's picking it up again?
He picks it up again. He has no idea what to do.
You don't need that!
You don't need that
The song was longer than I thought
The song was longer than I thought it'd be
That's true, it's pretty long
I thought it would be over by then
That's how Shimura-san uses his Swan prop!
What are you carrying the lion head around for?
Yeah
Well well, that was still pretty good
Right?
He had good movements
It's totally different right?
What's the story here?
This is an offering
An offering, the lion is being presented
And this person is being summoned by the Lord
Being summoned?
This person is being summoned?
I see, I see
*Hosei is making this up
That's why you were making it bite
Ah that's why?
Somewhat seductive
Yes a bit
I think there's something to be said about this order, I think Hamada-san has something to do with tit
Good morning
Please pick from these 5
Eh? What's this?
This...
This one is fine
Alright
Hamada chose the Fuji Musume (Wisteria Daughter), which uses a wisteria flower prop
He applies the makeup he imagines a Fuji Musume would wear
Is this the right way to do it? I thought the paint would be applied more smoothly and cleanly
Did I have to apply something before doing this?
Ah! I should have put this on!
Ah man they got me
I've never seen anyone apply this before
I went to Kankuro's show the other day,
I didn't see him putting this on!
All I saw was him applying the white paint. It's all his fault.
Right? He should've shown me the oil application first
He applies his makeup while complaining
Ow
Hamada's Fuji Musume (Wisteria Daughter) ... How will it go?
So now the Japanese Dance I did, VTR start
I was in a hurry to get out
Already?
That's a grandmother
So soon?
That's no Daughter!
It was the hem
Woahhh what was that?
He dropped something
Is that part of the performance
No something came off
I had no idea what to do with that staff thing
It's not a staff, it's flowers
This story... What is this?
Finished?
I thought it ended there
Watch out!
Eh?!
Are you alright?
Ah, he's acting like he meant to trip
It's his senility
So scary
How was I supposed to use that staff?
It's not a staff!
This guy can't decide his dance moves at all
I thought I was finished there, but there's still more
It won't end there. I hope you redeem this soon
Woah
Woah woah woah
You have nothing!
What happened? What happened?
What are you swinging the flowers around for?!
He's spinning it!
That kimono was messed up
The hem of the dress...I apologise
I said this eariler, I, I also did the Fuji Musume
DownTown-san copied each other?!
But I was not like that
Please, we're counting on you
I couldn't watch that
It was like you were Punch Drunk
The Fuji Musume I think, after all
The one that meets my calibre
Somehow Matsumoto ends up doing the same Fuji Musume as Hamada
He applies makeup based on Fuji Musume
I can't belive Demon Kakka does this every day
While applying his makeup, he gradually gets into the role
Matsumoto's Fuji Musume ... How will it turn out?
This is the last one right? Matsumoto-san's Japanese Dance, START
Ah you came from that side?
That's good right?
So ugly...
Disgusting!
This is bad!
So disgusting!
This is what you meant Matsumoto-san?
It's a goddamn hag!
How is that? What about that? Nobody's used that until now
I noticed that just now
The girl notices the flowers now,
It starts now?
How will he use it? Just how will he use it?
You have no idea what to do!
He's not using, he's not using it at all
Finally he swings it
I guess it's just the natural move to make
What now? What now?
He covered his face
What happened?
I've seen this move before
So hot, it's so hot in here
C',mon stop it. But look, I have a lot of variations
What are you doing here?
He's dragging it!
What is this?
He left it on the floor
He has no clue what to do
I do know what to do, it's just longer than I thought
I didn't trip even once
You want it to end soon
Right, look at this
What the heck are you doing
What is that?
Ah, that's a new move
What? What are you doing?
There it is, the face cover
He covers his face in the end
Yeah you sure know what to do. You end up covering in the end
But you could see the story right? She notices the flowers, and then becomes one with the flowers
She's looking for the flowers, and looking for herself
But she thinks "Maybe the flowers are prettier than me" and switches between happy and embarrassed
That's the emotion there?
Happy and embarrased?
She's 15 years old after all
That Musume? She's 15?
So young!
Now professorial dancer Hanayagi Mikachiyo-sensei gives her thoughts on their performance
Tanaka-san was the Tenaraiko right?
Yes the Tenaraiko
Sensei his walking was gross right? So unnecessary
That was no good
That was no good?
Yes, however,
What I thought Tanaka did well was how you made the hairpins shake with your neck
Like we said before, we have to be unique right?
Hmm I don't know
Yes, trying your best, I thought that swaying was nice
Yes yes, I did that
But the longer it went on, the more his chin stuck out
No please, look at the hairpins instead
Next is Endo
I thought it was brilliant you painted your neck white too
Thank you
If you make your neck white, it makes your face look better
Also, I liked that your lipstick didn't cover your lips completely
That's a good thing?
And part way through, you did the pantomime?
I think that was great
Thank you very much, thank you for all the compliments
So next is Hosei
The round eyebrows were a mistake
That used to be in style, but for Kagami Jishi normal eyebrows are best
You got the basic feminine movements right, I think you did great there
Thank you very much
And the way you used the Lion head was good
I see
You seemed to be familiar with it
So Sensei, my dance please
When you first came out and trip, I thought "Oh poor thing!"
Of course right?
That's something that happens often, with new dancers or children, when they come out they trip
She said children!
Hamada-san, she said children do that
It's very common
It's a common thing huh
However you kept dancing to the end despite tripping,
I think that was brilliant
Thank you very much, that's all I could do
So Matsumoto-san did the same thing
That face was scary wasn't it?
It was terrifying
There's nothing I could do about that
That's supposed to be a 15 year old
It's scary isn't it?
But Sensei I feel I had a lot more variation than Hamada-san
You really had the aura
I had the aura
The spirit of using all of the props
I see
Was that noticing part way thing allowed?
It's allowed
I thought it was a great idea
Hamada-san was asking earlier how to use the flowers,
Matsumoto-san didn't swing it, but instead ran around it himself
I think that was a great idea
I ran around the flowers instead
The opposite idea
The opposite idea!
What's with all this praise
Were you already familiar with Japanese Dance?
I had a lot of experience to build on
Stop lying!
You can tell by looking, you had no idea what to do!
But it did seem like I was used to it
No it didn't!
It was wike- like I was used to it
wike?
The sensei will choose the best dancer! Who will it be?
So sensei, the best dancer...
Matsumoto-san
HELLL YEAHHHH
Seriously?
No way!
Is it because of the variation?
The variation yes
The way within a few minutes he switched between different moves
Ah yes
I did seem like I was used to it
Enough already!
What do you mean "like"
Then, who was the worst dancer please
The worst one?
Hamada-san
Of course, that's obvious
Shozo's was better than mine?
I think mine was on a totally different stage
You tripped!
The Musume is tripping and falling...
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband