First time on Gaki no Tsukai
Let's play with nostalgic retrogames: super famicom!
Famicom, huh?
Isn't it nice?
We already played famicom before
Downtown
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Yes, we did
Previous episode
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
On the previous two episodes, they played nostalgic famicom games from their youth
Dig Dug
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Zebius
Mario Brothers
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
And today it's time for its successor
It's time to play some Super Famicom games!!
Released in 1990
They'll play with the Super Famicom, released in 1990
Now that I think about it, I used to play this more
Oh, is that so?
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
You must be an expert, then
Yeah, I had my own super famicom
Tsukitei Hosei
Amazing
But these guys here said they never played with the famicom
Yes, they did
I wonder how are they gonna deal with a super famicom
I have no idea
Look, if you wanna go home, it's fine to me!
No way
Just take a bus
I'm not taking any bus, I'll stay
And for today's episode too
Game collector
Sakekan
We have 297 games from our game collector Sakekan's collection
Super famicom: 297 games
If Sakekan would die I'd cry so much
No you won't
No way you would
It'd be sad
Can't he just cry a bit?
Of course I would
Of course I'd cry
if Sakekan would get a game over, come on
That's not gonna happen
They choose to take a look at every game, starting from the ones published in 1990
Let's take a look at super famicom games
I really loved this one, "Wagyan Land"
Never heard of it
I don't know that
What is this game?!
When Wagyan shouted "WA" just like this
the "WA" (ワ) symbol appeared just as it is
And you can jump on them
An adventure game in which Wagyan (main character) uses his voice as a weapon
Bandai Namco Entertainment
Published in 1991
Super Wagyan Land
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
What?
What's this game?
Remember First Human Giatrus? How he made his shouts into stones? It's like that
Right
Oh, I remember that
But if you're not quick enough, your WAs start to fade
You have to be quick
Yeah, you gotta run
What a surprise!!
ActRaiser! He got it too!
No idea what that is
Never heard of it
This one is great
A game in which the player becomes a God and
fights magical beasts to help develop his town
ActRaiser: released in 1990
Available on virtual console
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
It is, right?
You become a God
This guy...
You play as a God
Yes
And you help the citizens around
And little by little, the town starts to grow
Exactly
Matsumoto told me he got worried for a whole week
Yeah...
'Cause his citizens
And by that I mean the humans inside ActRaiser
Yes?
Ok
That's right
All his humans were feeling gloomy all the time
The hell are these two talking about?
No idea
These two...
Is that the relationship you had?
Just what the hell are they saying?
I bet you know this one, right? R-TYPE
Nope, never heard of it
Are you kidding me?!
I don't know any of these
That's literally my first time seeing it
It's the shooting game which best represents
the super-famicom era
Released in 1991: SUPER R-TYPE
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
We really don't know 'em
It feels like a bunch of virgins coming to a brothel for their first time
Just go home!
Translation by Shion (@FGRNDNoises)
Typeset & editing by Kedomas
more episodes @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
Today, they're going to play with nostalgic super-famicom games
Let's play with Super Famicom games!!
We have a total of 297 titles ready to be played
Each member picks a game among the 297 titles, and they all play it!
Today's plan
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Each member is going to pick the one they want to try and they're all gonna play it
Let's start from the game Hamada has chosen
Hamada's
selected game
I really don't know anything
So what about this one you said it was great before?
Oh!
R-TYPE, right?
Yeah
I think I can show off at this one
Released in 1991
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
The game Hamada has chosen is the symbol of shooting games for super-famicom
SUPER R-TYPE
Its main characteristics are its wave motion and charged shooting system
Let's start from Hamada, who plays for his first time
Hamada's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Try to shoot
Like this, yeah
Like this?
At first is like this
What's this?
You just gotta move up and down
Look out, enemies are increasing
Oh shit!
Wh--- why did you clash into it?
He went through...
Man, your fingers are moving like an old dude!!
Hamada's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Just move up and down, nowhere else
For now those are fine
Keep on shooting 'em
You have infinite ammo, dude
Well done!
Counting on ya
That's right, that's right
See? You just fired a big one
Take that power-up!
He's doing better now---
What the hell!!
What a splendid crash!
Another clash
Such a beautiful crash
Why did you clash into it?
You did it again
Hamada's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
It doesn't make you immune
You told me to take it, so I went for it
Get back on track
I'm trying to
Like that
I'm drawing back all the time
You have to move around
But if you go too far you can get trapped
Watch out
It's important to have space to move
Get that "S"!
Now he's fast
That's what it does
Look, if you advance too much...
You could get---
Oh! It came from above
Dude, don't die while I'm explaining stuff to you
You gotta be careful with your moves once you get that "S"
He died before you got to explain it
Endo's challenge
Next up is Endo, a first timer as well
You can move right and left
Endo's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
You basically have to move in every direction
The way you explain stuff makes me anxious
You're right
Sometimes you gotta move forward too
Grab that power-up!
Watch out!
Careful
Man...
Take it!
Come on
See? Now you're faster
Right
Who needs this explaination now?
But those things keep on getting on screen---- ooh
Yes
Nice
You gotta take 'em all down
Be careful when they pop out from above
Get rid of those
Nicely done
Those things explode
Which?
The round ones
Which ones?
If you shoot 'em, they'll explode
I don't see them
You stick too much on the left corner, go forward!!
If you say it like that, he'd panick!
He's too behind
Endo's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
He gets too much on the left
But Endo's not bad at all, he's good
Ok, ok
Better than I thought
This...?
Did you learn how to play it?
I did
I'm learning
He's good
He is
Really good
Get inside the circle!!
Inside it?!
You have to get inside
Why?!
I just told you so
You're all so goddamn noisy!!
Tanaka's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Third challenger is Tanaka, another first timer
Go forward!
Move forward, you're gonna get hit
Nice, now get inside
Quick, quick!
Get inside the circle
Just get inside it like that, now stay still
Like that, nice
Spot where Endo died has been surpassed
Watch out--- you're done for
You panicked, right?
I did, yeah
Once you got in you went upwards in panick
That's right
I'm unbelievably good at this
This is hard, really
I think I got to its final level
Hm?
for like 20 times so far, I think
What?!
You mean until its ending?
Really?
Matsumoto claims to be an expert at this game: will we see his skills?
Matsumoto's
challenge
Matsumoto's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
It's important to move constantly
He's going forward so much
Look, he's always moving around
You have to always move around, that applies to everything
You gotta think about the enemies, I mean---
Oh, watch out!
Nice
You don't like those who always move around, right?
You must always have the upper hand
I feel like I got it all back now
You're moving differently
Your control is amazing
Nice
Nice one
You can't kill those
Oh, is that so?
Yeah
Spot where Tanaka died has been surpassed
If you're not ready to move, you can get hit by sudden appearing enemies
Woah!
You even knew it was gonna pop out from above...
Endo!
We're having a talk in my dressing room later
Hosei is going to play next: can he clear stage 1?
Hosei's
challenge
Hosei's challenge
Man, it's been so long since I last played with a D-pad...
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Yeah, I agree
I'm sure if the staff would have lend me this game yesterday's night
I could have make it so easily today
Hosei's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
But I didn't even know we were filming this today
That was a risky move
You almost hit that thing
Watch out
Go on
Here it comes
You gotta get rid of that
Just be careful not to hit any bullet
Spot where Matsumoto died has been surpassed
Yes
Load your gun...
And release it
Alright! Grab that
Ok
Woah, it came from behind!
Look
This one's tricky...
Huh? Is it an ally?
Huh? Is it?
An ally?
It is
I thought it was an enemy
It also serves as a barrier
If they get you, you're safe for one hit
I see
Alright!!
Now that stage 1 is finally done, it's time for a boss fight
It's time to battle against the 1st stage boss!!
Hosei's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
This is the first boss of this game
The first boss? Woah, it's fast!
Holy shit!
If it gets you, you're done for
You gotta destroy each of those parts
It's so fast
What is this?
It's so close!
Watch out
You're gonna get stuck
Didn't he get stuck?
It didn't hit him
There's only this one left, you can do it
You should try a charged shot
Watch out!
Don't you need it?
Look, these are time-bombs
Yes
Charge shot---
Oh man, but
If you would have switched with me,
I would have beat that boss so easily
Really?
Hosei's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Matsumoto claims to be able to easily defeat the boss
So Hosei will play again and hand the controller over
What's that?
It depends... you got lucky there, Yamazaki
Woah!
Careful there
Hold that shot
Alright
And it's finally time for Matsumoto to face the 1st stage boss
Matsumoto vs 1st stage boss
Let's get over this already
Matsumoto's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
I wish
Alright! You did it
Nice
What was that?
I said "nice"
Look
You should try to blow up as many time bombs as you can
Watch out
Go for it
Those bombs are a pain
It's moving so fast
What!?
Huh?
You gotta be kidding me
Huh?!
No way
Alright, I'm done
You were so close
Hosei's
Now it's time for Hosei, who says to be addicted to super famicom
selected game
We don't know them
Looking forward to it
I think
Oden would be a fun game to play together
Oden?
Yes
Kunio no Oden
Released in 1994
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
The game Hosei has chosen is "Kunio's Oden"
It's a falling puzzle game in which you have to stock up more than 4 pieces of oden
oden: japanese stew made of vegetables, eggs, konnyaku etc.
As you make them disappear, you get into higher levels, and both speed and difficulty increase
If you can't get rid of them properly, they pile up to the top and it's game over
Hosei starts playing from level 20
Hosei's level 20 challenge
I see
It's like tetris
Hosei's challenge
Kunio's Oden
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Yup
Right
They call these "ochige" (falling games)
4 of them-- yes, it's an ochige
You have to pile up 4 of them
Four of them and then they disappear
Exactly
Ah, a square is ok too?
Yes, anyway you like
Poor Kunio has nothing to do with it
You're right
Hosei's challenge
Kunio's Oden
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
You used to play this?
Yeah
I really like ochige games
Hosei's challenge
Kunio's Oden
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
He's as good as he claimed to be
He makes more and more odens disappear and he gets into higher levels
Nice, look how stable the situation is
Wow, incredible
He entered his stable period
Amazing
Hosei's challenge
Kunio's Oden
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
But he couldn't keep with the raising falling speed, and odens start to pile up
They're piling up a bit
Are you ok?
Aren't those too many?
Doesn't look good to me
Yeah
Not good at all
You're in a pinch, the one you need is not coming
It's not coming at all
You could have placed an egg in there
You're losing it
The screen is so full-- ah
Level 20
Even though it's been a while since he last played Kunio's Oden
Level 23
He manages to clear three levels of it
Following Hosei, Hamada will challenge level 23
Hamada's level 23 challenge
Hamada's challenge
Kunio's Oden
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Your score was like 140 points?
Yes
You can turn them, you know
You can roll 'em around
How do I do that?
Like that
He just made that one roll
Just like this
I think the difficulty is higher because he started at an higher level
I see, it's level 23 now
So it's harder now
You're right
He hasn't clear a single one yet
Hamada's challenge
Kunio's Oden
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
The girl shows your next set
If anything it's rare to see someone not scoring anything
His score is still zero
He didn't get a single one!
What the-- shut up
How is he able to play it like this?
Are you kidding me?
Not even one
Oh! I got some points
He finally did it
That was pure luck
Try to go for a chain
Huh?
You can make combos with chains
Oh, I see
Go for that chain
I think it's too late now
That was quick
It was hard to begin with
Yeah, it was fast
It wasn't easy
Tanaka and Endo are next, but they couldn't keep up with the speed of falling odens
Matsumoto is our last challenger: will he live up to his title of famicom master?
Kunio no Oden
Matsumoto's
challenge
Kunio's Oden
Matsumoto's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
It's "B"
"B" button
This is so freakin' fast
It is
I don't remember it being so fast, geez!
Kunio's Oden
Matsumoto's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
I need more of those round things
Come on
Where did all those round things go to?!
Look, he went for a chain!
Woah, there it is!
Take a look at my skills, ya punks!
And here goes the purple thingy
Alright
The eggs
Take this!
Line up the eggs
Go for the eggs
Look at this!
What's that purple thing?
Kunio's Oden
Matsumoto's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
I have no idea
It's konjac
Konjac?
You think so?
Shit shit shit I made a mistake
Oh no
Come here, egg!
Waiting for that egg
Here comes
Come here!
What have you done?!
It just came
Oh, nice move, ok
Ok, now wait for the next egg
Here comes
Oh crap
You wasted it
Over there
Here's the egg
Here comes the kelp
"Here comes the kelp"...
Well it figures
It makes a difference
It really does
Higher levels are something
Yeah...
Endo's
Now it's time for Endo, who rarely ever plays, to select a game
Selected game
How about this one?
Man...
What do you think?
Oi
Yes
Are we doing this?
What's that?
It's Super Mario Kart
It's Super Mario Kart, the biggest hit on Super Famicom
Released in 1992
Super Mario Kart
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
By using the Virtual Console service, you can download them on your Wii U or 3DS and enjoy them
Lots of titles from this series were released for famicom, super famicom, gameboy and such
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
It's an action kart game in which you play as characters from the Mario series
Like Mario or Luigi
By using the Virtual Console service, you can download them on your Wii U or 3DS and enjoy them
Lots of titles from this series were released for famicom, super famicom, gameboy and such
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
During the race, you can use various items
Like speed-up mushrooms or items to attack other racers
That's one of its charming point
Each one will compete in a single-player time trial!!
Our members will face a time challenge one by one
We're going to start from Endo
Let's start from Endo
Starting from Endo
Endo's challenge
Super Mario Kart
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
The other racers are CPU, aim for that first place
Ok
I see
So 1st place wins, right?
You can do it, Endo
Yeah
This...
It's pretty fast
Grab the item
Get some items
Items?
Inside the boxes
Oi, oi, Endo, are you for real?
You're 8th place, dude
Are you kidding me, oi?
Pretty far from the lead
I can see that
You're so far from the others
You're drunk, aren't you?
Endo's challenge
Super Mario Kart
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
What are you doing?
Get some item
Take it
What should I do with it?
Just press the A button
Use it
It's better to use it when you're not in a curve
They got past you again
You're one lap behind
Now I'm done for
Enough already, Endo...
This is harsh
I'm so slow
What are you doing? It's hard to watch
Look, everyone is now done, your position number is red
Is that what it means?
Geez
They're already done
Endo is left racing alone, while all the other CPUs already finished
It goes without saying for Endo...
But even the rest of us forced to watch him aren't having fun at all
He's racing all by himself
Endo's challenge
Super Mario Kart
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
What are you doing?
It's kinda sad
Ugh...
A well deserved 8th place
1 minute and 32,42 seconds
Endo: 1 minute 32.42 seconds
Alright guys, consider it your standard to beat
Can we call this a "standard"?
Next up his Hamada: will he beat Endo's record?
Hamada's
Super Mario Kart
challenge
Hamada's challenge
Super Mario Kart
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
If Hamada doesn't end up on 8th place, he wins to me
I agree
You're right
He's good
I'm not
Look out
I think our position should count
I'm so slow, what the hell?
But man, look at this...
Where should I go?
I know, right?
Yeah
He cleared his first lap, though
He isn't that bad
I'm not good at all
He's pretty fast
The item!
He's rolling around
That's 'cause Tanaka told you to get the item
That's right, don't tell me that
But if you don't take an item, you can't win
He's right
Hamada's challenge
Super Mario Kart
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
That's the item
You have to get it and use it
Come on
How do I use it?
They're right behind him
How can't you know how to use it?
I don't know man, you keep on telling me to use it
Yeah, which button is it?
I have no idea which button I should press
Hamada's challenge
Super Mario Kart
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
In the end, Hamada gets behind everyone else and is left alone
Look at the map at the bottom
Woah
That's slower than Endo's
Like, 3 seconds slower?
Hamada; 1 minute 40.97 seconds
Eight seconds, actually
1 minute and 40,97 seconds
That means he's out
I think Tanaka is good at this
Alright, get ready Tanaka
You know
I've played the Wii U version before
With your son?
Yes
But that's completely different
Is that so?
Let me try
Super Mario Kart
Tanaka's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Tanaka has confidence in his skills
Huh?
What are you doing?
You should know how to play it
Nope, this is different
You're shaking like crazy
This has nothing to do with the other
Tanaka...
Still on 8th place
This is really hard
He's spending a lot of time over the gravel
Man
It's really hard to use a D-pad
Not going well
Super Mario Kart
Tanaka's challenge
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
He couldn't get used to the controls and sadly ends up in eighth position
Oh
Around 1 minute 38
Tanaka: 1 minute 38.28 seconds
1 minute and 38,28 seconds
I was slower
I was faster
Not good at all
Hosei's challenge
Super Mario Kart
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Our fourth challenger is Hosei, a video-game enthusiast
He's good
He's far from the gravel
I mean, that's how it should be
Right, on the concrete
Yeah, you can speed up properly only on track
Oh no, look
Yamazaki is being reckless too
Hosei's challenge
Super Mario Kart
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
He hasn't played for so long he lost the knack and couldn't race so well
Alright
Woah, so close!
Yet another eighth place
This is hard
Hosei: 1 minute 22.51 seconds
But he did it in 1:22
Yeah, it's the best record so far
Yeah
Coming up
Matsumoto's Mario Kart full speed drive!?
No way! Can we just pretend that last thing never happened?
Super Mario Kart time attack: it's Matsumoto's turn
Matsumoto's
Super Maro Kart
challenge
Will he escape the eighth position hell?
You see...
And there was something wrong in the way you played...
I've been watching all of you
You were constantly
accelerating like idiots, weren't you?
You have to correctly press and release it
Matsumoto's challenge
Super Mario Kart
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
It smoked like crazy
On the gravel already?!
Why so quickly...?
You're always on the gravel
Oh but you used them...
You took a shortcut
Like a shortcut
I see...
Looks like the gravel isn't so bad after all
You can use it as a shortcut
He's catching up
Oh, nice
He relies so much on gravel
The banana!
No way! Can we just pretend that last thing never happened?
Have you ever seen a banana dropped on a road?!
Matsumoto's challenge
Super Mario Kart
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
What?
I think you should give up on that trick
Oh, it worked
He's seventh
Nice, he's seventh
That gravel technique is something
It's going well, he can do this
You think so?
Yeah, easily
Really?
Yes
Oh, he got a mushroom
I see, he cut through
He's relying so much on gravel
Seventh place
But it's still way higher than your scores
Matsumoto: 1 minute 18.26 seconds
Right?
His legs are so long!
Battling against Matsumoto in Street Fighter II!
Coming up
Which super famicom game is Matsumoto going to pick?
Matsumoto's
Selected game
Don't we have any fun games to play together?
Do we have SF II? Let's do SF II
Oh, SF II? Nice one
Wasn't it over here?
It's here!
Not even close, Endo
What were you looking for?
Let's play SF II
I thought it was there
Published in 1991
Street Fighter II
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
A masterpiece and worldwide big hit
Street Fighter II
You can play this on virtual console
Pick one of the many peculiar characters
And defeat your enemies using various techniques
It's a tournament-styled fighting game
Matsumoto has great confidence in his skills, so everyone is going to challenge him
Street Fighter II:  challenge against Matsumoto
His first challenger is Endo
Endo
Matsumoto
Street Fighter II
This was huge
Matsumoto vs Endo
Street Fighter II
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Alright, it's me vs Endo
Yeah
I'm going to pick this kabuki fighter
Matsumoto picks E. HONDA for this challenge
Honda
Matsumoto vs Endo
Street Fighter II
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
This monster is pretty strong
This guy here?
What's his name?
The hell is this? I wouldn't dare to fight him
Endo picks BLANKA for this challenge
I'm choosing Blanko--- I mean, Blanka
Endo
Matsumoto
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Matsumoto vs Endo
Street Fighter II
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
The monster looks strong
Impressive background
He's just kicking around
Blanka!
Man, he's so strong
He's way too strong!
Honda is amazing
What was that?!
He's so strong
Matsumoto wins
Honda is a beast
You ended it only with open-hand slaps
Yeah...
Hosei
Matsumoto
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Matsumoto vs Hosei
Street Fighter II
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
The second challenger is Hosei
He fights as Blanka too, just like Endo
That's a dirty move
Here I come
Oh, nice move
Go Blanka
Really nice
He's trying to reach him
Got him
Take this
What just happened?!
Honda is unstoppable
Oh shit!
Gimme a break
You're in a pinch
Alright!!
Honda is so strong!
Come on...
Matsumoto wins for two consecutive rounds
Honda is really strong
We have to bring him down
Don't underestimate Honda
Matsumoto vs Hamada
Street Fighter II
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Hamada is up next
You can change character
Yeah
You're sticking with Honda?
Honda is everything I have
Which one should I pick?
Just pick the one you like
Oh, that one is pretty strong, the indian guy
Which one?
Alright, let's pick him
"The indian guy"...?
Does he look like an indian guy?
Hamada picks DHALSIM for this challenge
Let's bring him down
Hamada
Matsumoto
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Matsumoto vs Hamada
Street Fighter II
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
His movements looks light
Woah! Look how long his legs are!
Amazing legs!
Alright, alright!
Isn't Honda in a pinch right now?
You can do it
You can totally do this
Oh shit
Crap
Honda is in a pinch
Go for it!
Honda did it again!
Alright!
How strong is him?!
Almost there
Oh yeah!
I almost made it
You got so close
Matsumoto wins for three consecutive rounds
He had barely any health left
I only needed few more seconds
He's really good
Honda is a beast...
Avenge us, Tanaka!
Alright
We're counting on you
Matsumoto
Tanaka
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Matsumoto vs Tanaka
Street Fighter II
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
I want to defeat all of you
Like that, nice!
Good
Use your long legs
Nice
Like that, don't let him get close to you
Block his open-hand slaps
If you don't, Honda will get you
That's right, no open-hand slaps
Nice, go from the above
Oh no, that's a risky move
Like that, yeah
Get away from his slaps
Don't let him slap you
Honda is gonna get you!
He's going to
Keep on doing that!
Don't let him slap you!
Shit, I'm in trouble
You can win this!
Almost there
I'm done for
Get away from his slaps
Matsumoto vs Tanaka
Street Fighter II
m 0 0 l -25 0 l -25 25 b -8 25 8 25 25 25 b 25 17 25 8 25 0 b 17 0 8 0 0 0
Don't let Honda get any closer
You just need one more hit
You only need one hit to win
Oh shit, watch out!!
Holy crap--
Alright!
Tanaka wins
Ok, ok
You did it
Nice
THIS IS A NO-PROFIT TRANSLATION MADE BY FANS FOR
OTHER FANS. NO COPYRIGHT INFRINGMENT INTENDED.
Translation by Shion | Typeset & editing by Kedomas
fb.com/shionnotsukai | ko-fi.com/shionnotsukai
more episodes @ shionnotsukai.wordpress.com
patreon.com/shionnotsukai | twitter.com/FGRNDNoises
That was your only way
You couldn't let him get any closer