He's the first foreign
talent to do this.
It was quite a challenge for me.
- It must be.
He's very enthusiastic
about this.
I told him "Hamada's very tough so you can hustle him as much as you want".
Look, don't provoke him.
You saw us having a conversatoin with both smiling now, he's a good guy.
Normally, we'll bring
the performer here.
But this time just save it to the show
- Of course.
7 transformation Rules
The performer enters a meeting room.
One who laugh pays 1,000 yen fine.
I'm going to be in backstage directing him today.
Planning Meeting
So which one should we do?
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
Yamazaki Housei
We like to see Endo's "manic potato digging".
Suga Kenji (Producer)
How could I make a digging manic?
Well, you dig and dig
like maniac, I guess.
There got to be many ways to do that.
Shichi henge start!
Peanut
Hot rice cracker
Too hot!(in slangy Japanese)
Peanut
Delicious.
Hot Rice Cracker
Too hot!
babble
How could anyone not laugh?
He make me laugh by
just sitting here.
What a dominating
presence he have!
It's already funny the moment
he steped into this room.
It's about time we get some new blood in our show to replace you guys, don't you think so?
We are just about enough.
We don't need new blood. - Absolutely not.
But, there are so many
talented young comedians...
Morino Ishimatsu(a famous historical play)
We have 8 performances this year.
There are some ticket available (in bumbleheaded Japanese)
Ticket available.
There's no way I'll star in this play.
This thing is bs!
He's breaking up the setup.
Very funny.
So what's that all about?
I couldn't make out what he's saying at first.
- Me neither.
Do you want to do "face-off"?
- Fine with me.
Just a minute, please.
Hello?(in good pronunciation)
Hello?
The connection is bad.
He made all of us pay for every one so far.
- We shouldn't go so easy on him.
It's funnier in good pronunciation.
- Look at these bills!
It's only the 3rd act.
That was 6 years ago isn't it?
- Well, that was...yes, 6 years ago.
Good morning.
Well done!
Why? Don't scare me.
That was hard for you, Hamada.
(sad song)
Sada Masashi
Take a shelter from rain
Oh, this song moves me!
This song moves me!
I managed to hold that one.
Heipo(director)
You shouldn't laugh so hard, Heipo.
Your laughter triggers mine too.
Bob, are you ok?
You drunk too much.
Get a grip!
Here, take this seat.
I...drunk too much.
I drunk too much.
I...drunk too much...again.
He's doing good.
Can you stand up?
I...drunk too
much...again.(make a fluff)
He made a fluff.
I don't have much money left.
Bob and Matsumoto brushing up final act
You mean like your fans?
- No. My fan wouldn't be good.
Peach Boy(old story)
(sound effect of peach
flowing in the river)
Kiji(pheasant)
Are you going to carry on?
So why did you scattered
all the papers?
Sorry.
babble
He scared us.
Everyone, Bob Sapp.
Clear the way for him.
After he got wild he didn't
know what he's doing anymore.
53,000 yen.
Which makes him the
No.1 in the ranking.
He has almost unfair advantage.
All the money goes to a charity
Like when he has this face so close to mine.
Bob Sapp understand intention of this show and generously accepted our offer.
We should offer him a regular spot.
Come to Sanseido studio
next week ok?