Subbed by: Mei.ka~
A battle will determine who can stay calm no matter what happens.
This is the No-Reaction King Tournament.
What a pathetic little voice!!
Endo
Hamada
Housei
Matoba
Matsu-
moto
Owada
Tanaka
The rule are as follows: 3 traps will be activated for each battle.
The winner will be the one who reacts the least.
The one who reigns victorious will be crowned the king.
Last time,
they kept on reacting to cleverly-set up traps!!
Zeebra is working up a sweat!!
So much sweat!
On the other hand...
There've also been strong contenders
who've shown little to no reaction.
And tonight, the no-reaction king will be crowned!!
And the weakest king will also be crowned!!
Housei
Matoba
Owada
It's time for the semifinals in the No-Reaction King Tournament!!
It's a battle between Zeebra and Housei, the only remaining regular.
Man, I really want Yama-chan to do good here.
They'll be checking on the match from a monitor in another room.
I hope so, too.
Yeah, me, too.
Yamasaki's the type to grow as a person while doing this.
Well, all we can do is hope.
He is that kinda person.
That's just who he is.
Hm, I don't really think that's true, but...
Battlefield
Let's go ahead and start the match!
Enter Challengers.
Man, he has to be outta tricks.
He can do it.
Right, right.
Neither of them know when and what traps will activate.
Ah, there are even more traps.
We've got some new stuff again.
They even have the drone!
Oh, there's more of them!
Man, there's a lot of stuff.
What's that?
So much stuff!
Will they be okay?
They look so uneasy!
Get Into Position
And now it starts.
Yup, it's on.
S-somehow...
Giant Murakami
Ichiouka Genki
TN: They're from Yonemura Denjiro Science Production
which is a company that presents science in a fun way.
The Denjiro Army is on stand-by.
Well, that was sudden.
Really.
I see.
Man, I'd hate this.
So the trap this time around is powerful CO2 gas.
Damn, it's gonna spray them real bad.
But it's not like this hasn't happened before.
They also can't hear the other members' voices.
I mean, Yamasaki probably has more experience, but...
Looks like he's balding.
Just a little bit.
What a bald head.
If only they were both balding.
I don't really know who loses here.
Doesn't he look scary?
Seconds until the powerful CO2 gas is activated
Look at how solid their faces are!
Why do we have to wait so long?
They're lookin' good.
seconds
second
Whoa, it's still going!
Oh, he turned his head!
How are you supposed to factor that in?
Right?
That can't be allowed!
Turning your head can't be allowed.
He shouldn't be able to turn his head. No way.
'Cause how're you gonna get good at variety?
That's true.
You just have to take it.
Wait
Hold on now...
He got sprayed so bad.
You know, just by this,
You have to consider how bad the trap's gonna be or you're screwed.
Ah true.
I see.
You have to consider how bad the trap's gonna be or you're screwed.
That's right.
That's true.
'Cause the drone from before...
That drone...
Get Into Position
Ah, that's a solid face right there.
Ah, but,
'Cause of the CO2,
He's been loosing a bit more hair than before.
Look.
Ah, that's true.
There really isn't anything that he can use.
His resources are limited.
Maybe he got a little too much blown in his face.
Now, the seconds trap is the drone.
Ah, it's time.
I'd hate to get the drone.
Owada-san,
Instead of getting surprised, you just laugh.
That's true.
That's a nice face on Yama-chan.
Really solid.
Very nice.
I can kinda see Miyamoto Musashi in his face.
TN: Miyamoto Musashi was a famous swordsman.
You talk too much!
Really,
The glint in his eye is so sharp.
He looks solid!
The way he raises his eyebrows is the best!!
They are up there!
Right?
Zeebra kinda...
He's been Tsuyoshi from Nakagawake this whole time.
TN: Nakagawawake is a comedy duo that consist of two brothers.
C'mon!
He really looks like him!
Ah, I see it.
It's just gonna start up, right?
See, there it is.
Oh, of course they'd get surprised.
Drone Operator
Celebrity Tani+1
I see.
For this, definitely.
I saw that reaction.
Yama-chan's reaction was bigger.
Definitely.
For sure.
It looks like what happened when I went,
But it's probably the same for them.
You think, "Why are they doing this to me?"
And you wanna look somewhere else.
His face is kinda...
Ah, that's right.
Right into his forehead.
That was amazing!!
Zeebra's just been sweating all over!!
All over!
The legendary sweat.
Now that's a minus.
Look!
That was definitely minus a point.
Yeah, minus one for Zeebra.
There it is.
Who knows what they're gonna do to Yama-chan.
But he's fine right now.
True.
He looks like plastic.
Seriously.
He's not moving!!
Not at all!
He's doing great!
But... It's not touching him.
Right.
Ah, there it is!
He totally just smiled!
You can't tell me he wasn't smiling!!
There it is.
Yama-chan kinda...
It keeps on poking him!
I knew it, he -
Ah, it's pulling his hair!
Smack dab in the middle.
seconds
Seconds until the secret joke
It can't get enough of him!
It loves him!
second
Blow to the seat
Housei-san!
Zeebra's amazing!
Both of his hands went up.
Wait
My hair just got eaten!!
This is a nice fight.
Well, it feels like one loss nad one win.
1 more trap left
Hm, that's true.
Sounds about right.
Right?
Yeah, this is a good match.
Definitely.
On to the next one.
Get Into Position
But just now...
They can't let what just happened get to them.
That's right.
That's very important.
The intensity he had just now wasn't really there.
That's true.
So, the next trap is...
The Tesla coil.
Wait, what?
It's a high voltage generator.
That's kinda scary!
It's gonna come out like, "Bzz~!"
Just like, "Bzzz!"
Hm? He kinda looks focused.
Yeah.
He's gotten there.
Yeah, definitely better.
Nice!
Very nice, he's at MAX focus!!
He's ready!
Yup, for sure!
Seconds until the Tesla coil discharges
seconds
second
This would definitely be scary!
This is just straight-up scary!!
Seriously!
This is insane!
Like what was that?
I don't understand!!
End of No-Reaction
Man, that was amazing.
Please make your way to the monitoring room.
Aaah, what was that?
Ah, I was so scared!
Yeah, that was scary!
That was scary!!
That was really scary!
Right?
That was so scary!
Good jog out there!
The first half was really good.
Really, that was great.
I'm sorry, but like the drone...
The propeller ate my hair...
Oh, right.
Nah, you should've expected that.
Well, I didn't!!
Let's play back the match in slow motion.
Both of you... Both of you moved!
That "errr" would be pretty scary.
That's how it ended up.
Ah, right.
The wind from the drone is just so sudden.
That was so lame.
This was...
It hit you pretty hard.
Yeah, it was so strong.
Just this part.
Definitely.
Right?
But Yama-chan did well here.
Very good.
He was just smiling!
He... He really...!
Yeah, you can see it right there!
This was just...
Oh, this part was pretty sketchy.
Yama-chan looks beaten up.
Oh, it's pulling him!
It's eating his hair!
It chased after him knowing he hates losing his hair!!
Someone's losing his temper!
Just watch it!
He hates this so much!
This didn't last for just a "moment".
Zeebra's amazing!!
I don't see it.
He's too good!
These 3 producers will be judging to see who the winner is.
Was the winner Yama-chan of Zeebra?
Please present the verdict!
Blue, blue, blue.
Zeebra!
Congratulations!
At this stage, all the "Gaki" regulars have now been wiped out.
Right!
Matoba and Owada-san.
You know what I think?
That there's a point to this.
Which is?
That Owada-san has to lose!!
Coming up next!
Owada's persistent no-reaction!!
Round 2 in the semifinals:
Matoba Koji vs. Owada Shinya
Get Into Position
It's finally here.
Giant Murakami
Ichiouka Genki
The Denjiro Army is on stand-by.
So it's this one.
With these people, I don't even know what they're gonna take.
This...
That's right, who knows if there're gonna be decoys.
Right, very true.
Wait-
It looks like he's gonna cry.
His eye look like so girly.
It's off.
His face is completely off.
It's so off.
Yup.
It needs to be more intense!
He kinda... Yeah, it's kicked in now.
TN: Margaret is a shojo manga magazine
Those are the eyes you get when you read Margaret.
Definitely!
They look so gentle!
The first trap, the radio-controlled tank,
is about to be activated. However...
There'll be an explosion from the wall. So...
Can they keep up on not reaction?
They also can't hear the other members' voice.
They probably think the CO2's gonna hit them.
They're just waiting for the CO2.
So will it be the CO2? Or the tank?
The tank. If it was me,
I'd probably think it was the tank with the way it'd be facing me.
Yeah, yeah.
Ah, I see.
There's so many...
Right, there's so much to think about.
There're so many things.
Yeah.
So it'd have to be it if it was facing you
Wow!
Alright, we got Owada-san to flinch.
Matoba-kun is amazing.
He's so good!
Wait
They handled that well.
I see...
So this is what they had in mind.
They were so focused before!
Right?
That one got me.
He says that, but he didn't move at all.
Not an inch.
That bald guy...
Why do you have to make fun of him!!
He looks like he's having a hard time.
Like you could just see electricity coming out of his head.
Stop making fun of him!
He's in so much shock.
Let's make fun of him some more.
Stop that!
Then the least you could do is close up on the bald guy!!
What a scene!!
Get Into Position
Will the CO2 ever come?
But those people are still there.
Right.
That's true.
With that said, the next trap is the powerful CO2 gas.
So Owada-san's been uncle-hunted 3 times, huh.
He's a victim of uncle-hunting.
And he still took it 2, 3 times.
Just stop talking!
Seconds until the powerful CO2 gas is activated
seconds
second
Just wait...!
Wait - he didn't react, though.
Yeah, he didn't.
That was a great fight, wasn't it?
It was good!
It was amazing!
So good!
For a second, he looked like Kitaouji Kinya...
TN: Kitaouji Kinya is an actor.
Definitely, I can see it.
Theory: When you spray Owada Shinya with CO2 gas,
he turns into Kitaouji Kinya.
TN: Probably in reference to their other show, Suiyoubi no Downtown,
in which they prove or disprove various theories.
Theory: When you spray Owada Shinya with CO2 gas,
he turns into Kitaouji Kinya.
... He turns into him!
Both have been persistent in not reacting.
Even with the Tesla coil as the last trap...
With barely any kind of reaction, this has turned into a great match.
That's amazing!
That was incredible...
The deciding factor for the match
was the reaction to the wall explosion.
Owada-san kinda...
Yeah, he kinda...
You could see his shoulders go up.
Matoba was able to show off his strength
and has moved onto the finals.
He was a tough opponent.
He was amazing!
Thank you very much!
What were you thinking about back there?
Hm?
Did you just lose yourself?
Yeah.
Were you thinking of other stuff?
No, I just stared straight ahead, yeah.
Sorry, but we can't use this footage.
At last, it's time for the finals.
This is where we'll crown our no-reaction king.
Enter Challengers
I hope they fight it out.
Same here.
This is gonna be a good match.
Yeah.
They did make it this far, so...
They should fare well.
Right.
With the way things have been going,
I think Matoba-kun has the upper hand.
Yeah, I think he should do well.
Get Into Position
So...
They've gone on standby...
It looks like he's staring at the baldness.
Really.
The bald part.
It looks like he's thinking, "He sure is balding, huh."
Like, "This old man's so bald."
I don't need that image in my head when he looks so serious.
Now, the next trap is Ijiri.
TN: Ijiri is a comedian and impressionist.
Pay attention to how he makes his entrance.
It looks like the make-up artist made him really shiny.
Seconds until Ijiri Okada appears
seconds
second
Someone moved there!
Yeah, Zeebra-san moved a little.
That's amazing.
Zeebra definitely moved.
Yeah, he did move.
Matoba didn't move at all.
Matoba-san's a strong contender.
Matoba-san's amazing!
Wait
Who's gonna win?
That hurt so bad!!
Wait, did he get hurt?
It went straight for him.
It hit him!
The fight between these two challengers is on a whole other level.
Although Matoba said he got hurt,
he showed no sign of a reaction. Which means...
When the next one starts,
What if you just hit 'em with a bang after the drum part?
Right.
'Cause they're thinking that they're gonna have to wait.
With a suggestion from Matsumoto, as soon as they
get into position, they'll be hit with flash cotton.
How will the two of them react!?
Get into position.
Of course that'd happen!
But Matoba-san's amazing!
Really!
Ah, Zeebra-san.
Zeebra fell right into the trap!
It got him!
Wait
Well, that was fast!
What twas that just now?!
Caught me off guard.
Me, too.
Matoba's such a strong opponent.
He's so strong!
Even to something like this.
Didn't even react to it.
It's amazing how he didn't react to it.
Once again, they'll be sprayed with powerful
CO2 gas once they get into position.
How will they fare this time?
Get into position.
That was amazing!
There was so much gas!
Well, that didn't go so well.
That was amazing!
His face hasn't even changed.
That's amazing.
Aw man...
That's incredible.
He's the best in Japan!!
Matoba is just too strong...
Usually, it'd end here, but the match isn't over, yet.
The drone will start up and aim for Matoba
in the hopes that we'll get a reaction from him.
This one, huh?
Drone Operator
Celebrity Tani+1.
He jumped a little there.
Not that one!
The wind comes in just like that.
Just smash into Matoba!!
Let's hope it does.
It went to his eye!
This is amazing!
It's comin' for him!
This guy's incredible!
He's too good!
This guy's seriously amazing!
How does he do it?
Right?
This is amazing!
It's been on Matoba for so long now!
Leave it to him to let his "Matoba juices" pour out.
Definitely.
He kinda...
His head is channeling "Ashita no Joe" right now
TN: Ashita no Joe is a boxing manga. Matsumoto's probably
referring to how Matoba's hair curls like the protagonist's.
Seconds until the secret joke
Now...
seconds
second
Well, Zeebra kinda moved a little bit.
Cans drop
He did move.
He couldn't have won.
Wait, what?!
That was amazing.
End of No-Reaction
It was all over me!
Please make your way to the monitoring room.
Did you hear him?!
Man, that was just...
That drone was a pain in the ass!!
I wanted to break it so bad!!
Incredible!
Just what I expected!
That's Matoba for you!
They don't mess around!
I think it's clear that you won!!
You definitely won!
It's just that Zeebra's weaknesses came through.
Yeah.
I'm exhausted...
You're so quiet!
Of course, the result is...
Red, red, red. Matoba Koji!
Thanks!
Thank you!
The very first!
The first no-reaction king is Matoba Koji-san!
I got it! Thank you!
Matsumoto-san, you thought you could seriously take him down.
Right.
I do think that.
Now you have to.
I'd have to or else.
But there's no way.
Yup.
I've been learning a lot from Hamada-san,
And now I've surpassed him and won!!
What the hell are you talking about?
What are you talking about?!
He was too weak for you.
Yeah, definitely.
He's very weak.
So...
The weakest...
Huh?
Should we get on to crowning the weakest now?
If we're talking about the weakest...
Then go ahead.
No way.
Hamada-san and Tanaka-san.
What the hell?!
Sounds good.
No no no,
I swear I'm gonna win!!
Yeah, but...
I'm sorry, but I swear I will!
I mean, it'll be close, but...
What?
Well then...
It has to be perfect.
If it's gonna be like that, then I don't even care anymore!!
Coming up next!
A battle to find the weakest no-reaction king!!
Who will be the weakest no-reaction king?
Tanaka Naoki vs. Hamada Masatoshi
I see...
But they look so weak.
They really do.
What the hell is up with them?
I kinda understand, though.
Seriously.
right?
Not a good start for him already.
He's already scared.
Yeah, he's not ready.
Get Into Position
So, this where they start.
What kinda nerves do they have?
What the hell is that? I've had it with this guy.
Seriously.
What's with his face?
What is that face?
It kinda looks off.
What? That face...
What the... This guy pisses me off!!
Why's his face like that?
He's acting all cute!
He's just like a little girl!
Yeah, seriously...
This isn't what we talked about!! I hate this guy!
Two curveball jokes have been set up in
this match to find the weakest king.
So what kind of reactions will they show us!?
Seconds until the Tesla coil discharges
seconds
second
Whoa~
Did it shock him?
He was like, "Whoa~."
He went, "Whoa~"
Whoa
That was full out!!
Full out!!
Man, that only lasted for, like, 2 minutes, but I could laugh forever.
That was unbelievable.
I wanna take this home with me!
Wait.
That was a full out reaction!
You always have something comin' outta your mouth!!
My apologies.
You were just like, "No!".
Did I?
You did! You went, "No!" like an idiot!
Get Into Position
My heat can't take anymore.
He's in bad shape.
I hate this!
I don't know what face he's trying to make.
What's with the look on his face?
I don't get him.
What d'you think of his face, Matsumoto-san?
I don't get it.
He's so scary, he's turning into a girl!!
It's different.
It's like if a girl had a kid, and then that kid had a kid.
Ah, I see.
I can see that.
Seconds until Ijiri Okada appears
This pisses me off.
He must be having a hard time.
Probably...
seconds
second
Whoa!
Whaa
Who!
Whaaa~
Whoa!
Alright, alright!
"WOW!".
That was just a normal reaction.
They were like, "WOW!".
He's...!
I'd hate this.
He's not even surprised by this.
What is this?
seconds
Seconds until the secret joke
Both of them were hilarious, though.
second
Right?
This is great!
Both of them were so weak.
Isn't this great?!
There ya have it!
Right, right!
That was the weakest king match!
Thank you for being here, everyone!
Thank you!
See you next week!
He's still scared.