Subbed and timed by Outlaws0023
Gaki no Tsukai backstage
Gaki no Tsukai.. as always they're being kids.
Nothing to do, huh?
Hamada Masatoshi
Matsumo Hitoshi
Downtown
Because of the economy?
Yea, yea, yea. That's why we only get water.
Cocorico
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
We do get a lot of water, don't we?
It's gone this far?
Soon we'll only get nuts to eat.
Yamazaki Hosei
It'll never go that far!
So it'll stop at the water?
We're sitting and dreaming, huh?
Good morning.
Gaki Chief
Suga Kenji
So what's the program for today, chief?
We've got a request.
Every summer, there's Niterejanbori, right?
Niterejanbori is a camping festival held by the japanese scouts.
Oh, that's right...
So I thought "why don't we get gaki to take some pictures".
The gaki.. staff.. and members..
But after a lot of thinking...
I reached the conclusion, that Heipo pictures would be the cutest.
Cutest?!
Heipo
He's the image you get in the head when thinking about gaki.
Our theme for today will then be "surprise".
Everytime Heipo get "surprised" you have to take the pictures.
Sekai no Heipo - The worlds Heipo
The always petrified man: Sekai no Heipo
And today we're gonna show you some
of the funniest reaction from him!!
Every time he gets scared, the gaki cast will take pictures of it!!
The place Heipo will have to go to, is written in here.
Wha..what?
I don't like the surprise thing.
Can I read it now?
A noise maker
Was that the surprise?
Go to a café and get something to eat.
That's all?
Yeah, that shouldn't be too hard.
Then there's no need for a surprise, right?
We've already told you it's gonna happen.
It's today's theme.
What are you to this program?
I'm the assistant director!
You've never directed us! Not even once!
Today the gaki team is gonna take pictures
of Heipo at 3 different locations.
First up is the café.
What surprises are waiting?
And how will Heipo react?!
Okay everyone, Heipo will soon arrive.
We've got to do our best!
I really wanna start taking some pictures!
- He is! He is!
He's here?
Photo taking START
Excuse me..
Can I place my order?
Can I?!
You don't say that...
Welcome!
What have you chosen?
- You don't have to use that loud voice!
The waitress's voice is very loud
What are you doing?
1 black tea, please.
Okay, please wait a moment.
Why black tea? He's supposed to eat here.
Noise from the kitchen in...
What is it with this café, it's so wrong.
You seriously can't say that...
Watch him!
If you're going home, then say it!
No way he should.
It's hard to get a picture of
the exact moment he gets surprised.
Noise from the kitchen in...
What's wrong with this shop?!
Waitress happening in...
Here's your tea.
Black teeth
What is that?! Wha...
What kind of café does he normally go to?
What's this?
Tomato juice
It's kinda red...
Oh, it's good. Nothing wrong with it.
Sorry.
- Did he think anything was wrong with a tomato juice?
Excuse me, sir.
A sleepy old man.
Sir?
I don't want to be a bother, but...
Stop fooling around you stupid bastard! Get up!
A waitress with a lot of power
Get up when I say it! Look, look, look! You're
a bother to the other customers.
This is so wrong...
This is difficult, huh?
- Yea.
Surprise in...
That's gotta hurt.
What's wrong with this café?!
What now? Did something happen?
Heipo's instructions
This is almost like bullying.
Let's hear what it says.
Go to the fortune-teller.
- I'll go to the Fortune-teller, then.
More?
He really is a one of a kind.
He looked so~surprised. Unbelievably scared.
is it really possible to get that scared?
I'm in the TV business, but I have no idea.
It feels like I'm taking pictures of an elementary
school class on a school trip.
The pictures they took will be revealed at the end of the show.
Heipo's feeling troubled...
I don't wanna go.
You're already done with the café.
This can't be just as scary...
But I still don't wanna go.
And why did I have to eat something at the café?!
So unnecessary.
I really don't like this.
But in the end, they somehow managed to persuade
the petrified and complaining fool.
Fortune-teller
Location 2
Even more surprises!!
At this place there are waiting many more surprising things for Heipo.
Here he comes.
Excuse me.
What is this place?
Take a seat
Please write your name here.
Electric shock in...
Here?
Why this Ballpoint pen?
I'll try to see you in my crystal ball.
What?
What can you see?
I can se something black.
- What? Black?!
That black object is the girl...
from your future private wedding.
He said something really good!
He laughed.
Now that was a real surprise.
Tha person is 30 years old.
Wait a second.
What's with the face?
So now I would like to show you some pictures from my older visitors.
Uh! I don't want to see it!
Picture of a ghost/spirit
You only see 3 persons on this photo, but...
I can see it! No~!
Actually they're 4.
- I know!
Actually, the girl to the left had a twin sister.
Scary~.
- So they're 4.
Surprise in...
Eh?
- They're 4.
You scared me!
What are you doing?!
Who is that?
No idea.
An unknown person entered!
How can a person you don't know just go in like that?
There's 1 more thing I want to show you.
Take a look at this.
- I really don't want to see it!
Ghost/spirit video
No~! I don't want to see it!
A small group enters an old university with a camera.
I'm really bad with these things.
He really hates this. In a split second
it looked like he was hit by an arrow.
Huh? Looks as if someone has just dropped this.
We haven't dropped anything.
Heipo jumped off his chair even tho nothing happened
What going on here?!
This is making me crazy.
No! I don't wanna watch it!
Once again Heipo got freaked out.
The next place is...
Go to the amusement park and ride the "Wanpakubasu".
What's that?
Some good surprises they made.
Now what?
What is it with him?!
There's no cameras out there, right?
The pictures will be shown in the end of this program.
Next up is the amusement park. The
last chance to get some good shots.
Heipo is now at the amusement park as
instructed to ride the "Wanpakubasu".
He's here.
- All he has to do is the ride the "Wanpakubasu", right?
Then let's just go straight to it and get some good shots.
Even at a cute ride like this, Heipo's got a very surprising reaction.
He really can't take amusement parks.
- What will happen?
I wonder how many years it's been since he's ridden such a thing.
He probably won't look too good up there.
Wanpakubasu
It's as if he's flying!
This is a great chance for some good pictures!
Please stop it.
Scary~!
This is great!
Some great pictures I get.
- Yea, I'm confident in mine too.
A surprise that'll make him scream even louder.
After this
Stop it! Onii-san!
That was some reactions we got.
Next up Heipo's got to but some popcorn.
He's here!
Thank you very much!
Why did he get scared?
Excuse me. Could I get some popcorn?
- Yes, just a second.
Surprise in...
Sorry to make you wait!
"Sukekiyo" is from the japanese movie "Inugamike
no ichizoku" (The Inugami Family)
She turned into "Sukekiyo"
That's good!
This is great!
- But a bit scary, huh?
She's rough!
Why's she spinning around all the time?
That's her way of handing over the popcorn.
Thank you very much.
Oh, the popcorn!
That's some great pictures!
Now what?
Ride the "Sky trip". That impossible!
Many funny things has occurred, but it's not over yet!
This is the last chance for some good pictures.
And at the next ride, Heipo will get a really scary surprise.
How do I do this?
- Just sit right here.
Uwa~ this is impossible!
Eh, scary! Scary!
No, I can't do this! Can't! Can't! Can't!
No! No! No!
How do I do this?
This is gonna take a long time!
Sky trip
Uwa~! Scary! So high!
He's really slow.
- Scary!
Watching this makes me angry!
So high!
- What's he doing? What's high?
Surprise in...
Ain't I going fast?!
Behind you! Oh, that can't be good!
Collision!
Save me!
Stop it!
Stop!
That's kinda scary! It really is.
- (Heipo) Save me
Enough already! Please stop!
I can't take it.
- Is he saying he want him to stop?
As if he wasn't scared enough when he was alone.
But it really was scary.
- And he wasn't able to move.
I felt there were something dangerous going to happen.
He was as strong as 24 people.
He's here!
His face looks so white.
- You're right.
Is there a next place?
- Oh, they saw him!
This looks bad.
Don't lift me!
The students start lifting Heipo
Too high! Too high!
- That's not high!
That's great!
- Pitiful... He's so pitiful
Got some good pictures.
Then where do we go next?
- We'll probably find out soon.
He looks so exhausted.
He looks like someone from "Life".
Next up are the tea cups.
We've got enough pictures by now, right?
I don't think anything will happen here.
What are you doing?
Together!!
Small Tea Cups
This is fine..
- Fine?
I can't do this..
No.. No~
No wait! It's scary!
That's dangerous!
Heipo-chan let's go!
I can't.. can't
That was really dangerous.
Looked like he was about to fall out.
He's feeling so bad he can't move.
Can't help it... it really was funny.
I can't go on.
- He won't move.
It just keep on coming!
Go to the "Bake Yashiki".
Means something like "Disguise mansion"
Looks like he's had enough.
Just before it looked like...
- He wanted to kill someone.
I won't go.
- He's saying he can't even go into a "Bake Yashiki".
I really can't go in there.
I'm going home.
Just go in there!
I can't!
- Just go in!
I can't! No~
- It's not like you're gonna die!
I won't go into such a place.
After this
What's gonna happen at the "Bake Yashiki"!?
Nothing will happen
- Because it's still bright.
Please go in first.
- It's alright, just go.
Hamada, please go in.
- No, I'm taking pictures.
Please let me go.
No~
- Then we'll help you a little.
I can hear some weird sounds.
- Weird sounds? From where?
No, no, no, no!
Please go with me.
- We can't go with you, cause then we wont't get any pictures.
Then get one from the crew to do it.
Let me out!...
He's so strong!
- Please let me out!
Hurry up! Let me out!
"Pinku" is an adult movie genre.
Sadako is from the movie "Rngu" or "The Ring" in english
Outside, a pinku actress has been dressed as Sadako.
How will Heipo's reaction be when he see her?
Scary!
Heipo take a look at her.
- Take a look.
Eh? I think I've met you before.
- What the hell!
Where?!
What's going on?! That can't be right!
Heipo's
Surprise pictures
"Waraereba"
by Ulfuls
Tokikaku waraereba
Anyway, if you laugh
Saigo ni  waraereba
If you're the last to laugh
Nasakenai kaeri michi
The way home becomes shameful
Hahaha to waraereba
Hahaha, so I start laughing
Subete ga umaku iku hazu
Everything is going fine
Sou shinjite iru no
That's what I believe
Naze ka asette
But for some reason I'm in a rush
Gurashite jitabata suru kedo
I'm unsteady, I'm impatient
Tonikaku waraereba
Anyway, if you laugh
Sore demo waraereba
If just you laugh
Kyou ichinichi no owari ni
At the end of the day
Hahaha to waraereba
Hahaha I just want to hear you laugh
Matsumoto and Hamada help me.