Gaki no Tsukai's famous series: Shichi-Henge
In this series we get to see how a true comedian behaves
In a harsh situation in which they can't fail
And today's challenger is...
First time ever on Gaki no Tsukai
Morisanchu's Kurosawa Shichi-Henge!
Not many women charenge this.
Tomochika did it the other day,
but other than that, only Oba-chan has done this.
So this is the first female challenger in a long time.
- She is the 35th person to challenge.
- The 35th challenger.
- I wonder what will happen. I bet she didn't think she would experience this before sex either.
- What are you saying?
Today's star, please come on in.
- You guys are still looking great grade out there.
- All three of you are very good.
- Very good.
- Thank you.
You can tell him if you don't like it.
He does it for no reason.
Here is the ranking list.
What rank are you aiming for?
Who do you want to win against?
But....But.....
- Answer quickly.
- Yes.
If you don't answer quickly, she will be harmed.
Tat's about enough.
Answer quickly.
- Answer quickly.
- That sounded good.
You should be sued.
What is that?
"Heipo invented project: I want to squeeze Nadeshiko Japan's tits."
She's good during the game, don't you think?
Eh!?
Who are you talking about?
Sawa is good.
It's not a matter of good or bad.
That kind of teasing can get you in trouble.
And the word "teasing" isn't a good one either.
This whole part will not be aired.
Then stop writing these things.
I think there are too many planning ideas.
"Let's raise Matsumoto's daughter to be a comedian."
- She has inherited your DNA.
- The public is expecting this.
She's only one year and nine months old.
In other words, let's give her a gifted education.
If I were to put her in an office somewhere, I would put her in Jinrikisha.
I will not put her in Yoshimoto Kogyo.
Why not Yoshimoto?
Is it a problem with the ratio of remuneration?
Her father suffered from that ratio.
I want to do this!
"What if we lock Tanaka in a box?"
I can never do that.
Why?
I would absolutely freak out.
I would not be able to breathe properly.
- So much so that you wouldn't be able to air it?
- Yes, this would be unbroadcastable on TV.
Have you ever been through this?
In another show I was once trapped in a box and driven about 10 km.
At that time, I was so scared, to the point that it probably shouldn't have been broadcasted.
I thought the only thing waiting for me ahead was death.
It was so dangerous that I knew it myself.
But still, how long does she keep us waiting when it's the first one?
- I'm sure she's trying to time it right.
- No way.
- But we have to have a planning meeting.
- Yes.
What took her so long to change into that thing?
She's got a loud voice.
She certainly had a loud voice.
When I saw her profile as she entered this room, she looked like Football Hour's Goto's mom.
Excuse me.
Am I allowed to speak?
Hey, that's mine!
That's my autograph!
You're good!
What the hell are you doing!?
That's not fair!
Stop it!
What the hell are you doing?
That's enough!
Where did you get that?
Welcome Downtown
Matsumoto: Thank you for your kindness.
Where did you get that from?
Hamada: Can I love you?
Matsumoto: I came to see you because I love you.
She's disgusting.
Hamada: I love your eyes.
Matsumoto & Hamada:
I can tell how I feel when I see you.
So now we're in the same youth.
- That’s too long.
- This is nostalgic.
What the hell.
Those were from when you were in the Nichoume Theater.
- Are those her personal items?
- Yes.
- She was corresponding with about 30 Downtown fans at the time.
- Really?
- She did that with the other fans?
- Yes.
I think that's probably when she was able to write those autograph.
I'm left-handed, but she wrote that one right-handed.
She once wrote her name as "Matsumoto Hitoshi" on a test answer sheet and got a zero.
Is it serious!?
She's a strange one.
I'm a pervert, right?
I know you're in trouble.
No...
Use this.
She's crazy.
What did she say to you?
She said to me, "I know you're in trouble."
So I told her "No", and she said, "Use this."
She wanted to be in the mirror with this, didn't she?
I don't understand the story.
She said, "I'm a pervert, right?"
She said that?
You're all grownups, right?
I rub against your body, Go.
I forgot something important, so I'll be back.
I brought a rope.
I would like to play a game with everyone now.
Let's call it the "Rope Game."
Let's start the rope game.
Look, there is a rope.
Here, Hamachan, hold the rope.
Hold, Hold, Hold the rope.
A nice woman passes in front of the grownups.
Lift it once.
Let's find out your limits.
I'll step over here.
Omatagi-san, Omatagi-san.
I'll step from here to here.
Then I'll step over here now.
A nice woman steps over here.
Oh, wait a moment.
I raaaaaaaaaaaise my leg!
- Omatagi-san, Omatagi-san.
Omatagi-san will follow a rope.
- She is an idiot.
I will follow a rope.
Here we go
Lift the rope once.
Lift the rope ooooooonce.
Lift the rope oooooonce.
Lift, Lift, Lift, Lift, Lift, Lift, Lift,
She is an idiot.
Omatagi-san's rope.
Lift, Lift,
Lift the rope oooooonce.
If you Lift the rope too much, it will hurt, so please lower it.
Lower this. Lower this. Lower this.
If you lower this, Omatagi-san won't have anything to step over.
Come on, in that case, let's all work together to hold the rooooooooope!
Omatagi-san!
Hold, Hold, Hold,
Hold the rope.
Give Omatagi-san's Mata(crotch) to you.
He was an adult male.
I have nothing to give you.
I'll give that rope to you guys and you can play with it later.
She is just plain stupid.
- It was vulgar.
- Yeah.
What's "Omatagi-san"?
It's Kasumi.
It's Kasumi Aizawa.
Thank you all for gathering here for me today!
Today I would like to sing a song in front of you all!
Do you all know my song?
Dad, Mom, Grandpa, and Sister.
Today we all made a big hand-rolled sushi.
When I ate it, everything came out of my ass.
Dad, Mom, Gather all my relatives.
Thank you for listening to my song.
Well, I don't know what to do.
I am scared of her.
I don't know what to do.
Look, my hands are redder than I thought.
Okay, I'm going to go sing a song.
It was Kasumi.
She is wayward.
I was scared when she was banging on the wall.
Someone like that came to my house once.
Kasumi-chan?
The police told me, "Just shake her hand."
That's a calm response.
Is that what the responding police told you?
He said, "If you shake her hand, she won't come here anymore."
So I just shook her hand.
She was like a Kasumi-chan.
- She likes this kind of thing.
- Yeah.
You're reckless!
What should I do?
Your head accessory is coming out.
You're not wearing that?
What are you going to do?
What are you doing?!
Why don't you dip it in soy sauce?
She always adds something at the end, doesn't she?
Why did she eat sushi?
This board hit my head as hard as it could.
Even if it was your bad luck, I didn't think it would happen.
- She likes to dance and sing.
- Yeah.
I'm beat.
Guess what.
Please listen to my story about my son.
You know, my son is in a rebellious phase.
He doesn't listen to me at all.
I wasn't there for him when he needed me the most.
Oh, I have a headache.
During such an important time of his life,
So I can't blame him.
My daughter says she's never had a home-cooked meal from you.
You have a daughter, too, don't you?
Your daughter is at a important time, but it's good that her mother is home.
You have a daughter too?
It's not just a lonely mistake.
With you, I could dream it.
It's dirty!
Dirty!
So I would like to get to know my son and daughter from now on.
I would like to share the information I got from you guys today with my son and daughter.
The content has nothing to do with that ass at all.
She just wanted to show her ass.
55 thousand?! That's second place!
You are in second place.
- You beat Bob Sapp.
- Thank you very much!
That last one is not good.
That's the kind of dirty ass you can only see at a beach with no name.
That's the kind of ass you can only see in places where swimming is forbidden.
Originally, that could only be seen in places where swimming was prohibited.