0 0 m -330 -72.25 b -341.875 -73.75 -373.875 -72.25 -370.5 -45.375 b -372.25 -30.625 -340.125 -1.125 -331.75 0 b -318.25 8.5 -313.125 -1.125 -304.75 -2.875 b -294.625 -12.75 -284.5 -16.125 -274.375 -40.875 b -271 -63.75 -292.875 -65.625 -294.625 -67.5 b -308.125 -73.75 -319.875 -72.25 -330 -72.25 m -321.625 -63.75 b -306.375 -67.5 -286.125 -57.625 -289.5 -47.5 b -301.375 -60.375 -311.5 -60.375 -321.625 -63.75 m -407.625 -208.875 b -400.875 -208.875 -343.5 -197.5 -352 -121.75 b -363.75 -73.75 -395.875 -50.625 -406 -45.375 b -411 -43.875 -438 -22.75 -475.125 -57.625 b -483.625 -73.75 -500.5 -92.25 -488.625 -133.125 b -483.625 -149.625 -475.125 -181.375 -444.75 -199.125 b -436.375 -203.875 -422.875 -212.25 -407.625 -208.875 m -255.75 -212.25 b -252.375 -212.25 -211.875 -223.875 -176.5 -162.75 b -171.375 -148 -157.875 -129.625 -166.375 -83.625 b -176.5 -45.375 -193.375 -43.875 -203.5 -40.875 b -211.875 -40.875 -223.75 -30.625 -264.25 -58.875 b -277.75 -70.125 -298 -77.125 -306.375 -123.25 b -304.75 -123.25 -325 -153.25 -282.75 -199.125 b -274.375 -206.125 -265.875 -212.25 -255.75 -212.25 m -411 -157.875 b -458.25 -149.625 -431.25 -98.5 -409.375 -103.75 b -402.625 -103.75 -387.375 -107.125 -384 -129.625 b -389.125 -156.625 -399.25 -154.375 -411 -157.875 m -411 -142.875 b -400.875 -146.5 -395.875 -133.125 -397.5 -129.625 b -397.5 -117 -407.625 -117 -412.75 -117 b -419.5 -118.125 -422.875 -124.875 -421.125 -133.125 b -421.125 -136.5 -417.75 -142.875 -411 -142.875 m -407.625 -136.5 b -412.75 -134.625 -411 -128.5 -407.625 -128.5 b -404.25 -128.5 -400.875 -134.625 -407.625 -136.5 m -244 -157.875 b -281.125 -151.375 -264.25 -100.125 -244 -104.875 b -237.25 -103.75 -220.375 -107.125 -220.375 -136.5 b -225.375 -156.625 -238.875 -157.875 -244 -157.875 m -244 -142.875 b -222 -142.875 -228.75 -117 -240.625 -117 b -244 -115.125 -257.5 -118.125 -254.125 -133.125 b -254.125 -136.5 -252.375 -142.875 -244 -142.875 m -240.625 -136.5 b -245.625 -133.125 -242.25 -126.625 -238.875 -128.5 b -233.875 -129.625 -237.25 -136.5 -240.625 -136.5 m -414.375 -128.5 b -417.75 -128.5 -416.125 -123.25 -414.375 -123.25 b -412.75 -123.25 -411 -128.5 -414.375 -128.5 m -245.625 -126.625 b -249 -126.625 -247.375 -121.75 -245.625 -121.75 b -244 -121.75 -242.25 -126.625 -245.625 -126.625 m -500.5 -238.875 l -156.25 -238.875 l -156.25 95.625 l -500.5 95.625 m -159.625 -235.5 l -497.125 -235.5 l -497.125 92.625 l -159.625 92.625
TPF
Delicious
Delicious!
37 locations in all of Tokyo's 23 districts
Eat at all "Gindako"s to get a million yen!
The challenge to eat in all locations!
Eat at all "Gindakos" to win a million yen!
The challenge to eat at all 37 locations!
As a group, the five must eat a boat of 8 takoyaki balls in each store
Rules are, the group must eat a boat of 8 takoyaki balls in each store
shared amongst the five members!
Anyone else can eat the remaining three!
Each member must eat one
Everyone must at least eat one in each boat
But the remaining three is for anyone!
Finally, if completed, they will be rewarded a million yen!
Clear all 37 locations to get a million yen!
But, if anyone retires
the challenge will end on the spot
Game over when someone retires!
The member to retire first must pay for all of the takoyaki they eat!
The retiree
will pay for the takoyaki they've consumed thus far!
The Second half Start
Yellow
The Second Half Start
Will the group be able to finish!?
Will the gang be able to complete it!?
The thrilling conclusion starts now!
Tofu Panda Fansubs presents:
Down Town's Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Otviss
Patrick &
**Tofupandas.tumblr.com**
**We also have Facebook and Twitter.**
*Support us by following the latest news and info on upcoming projects!*
If you ever see this video being distributed online but not by us, keep in mind that on Youtube individuals may make money off of sharing fansubs like this that are not their own. Please go back and support the original creators. Fansubbing is voluntary and is not meant to generate profit. You can download episodes on our website instead. Thanks for watching!
Proofreader:
Tako, Akane &
Kenny
Translator:
Typesetter:
____________________________________________________________________
Delicious!
Is it?
After four locations have been finished, a suggestion from Matsumoto!
A good pace at the fourth location
Here, Matsumoto makes a suggestion
So
No one's
said they'll eat the remaining three, right?
Not yet, no.
With this, the final person is forced to eat the remaining three takoyakis
The Dreaded "Four at Once" Strategy Starts
Which starts the dreaded "four at once" strategy
Cheese with Roe
Complete
Endo
Green Onion
Hamada
Matsumoto
One Person Must Eat Four
Rectangle
Standard
Tanaka
Teriyaki
Yamasaki
From the 5th location with Tanaka
To the 9th location with Hamada
Everyone has successfully finished their "four -in-one" challenge
Kanamachi Station Front
Koiwapopo
Store No. 9
Store No.10
After a full rotation,
The group arrives at the 10th store!
So Tanaka's
going to be eating four here
How about we stop for once?
The four-at-once rotation
Why?
Can we break this up?
I don't know what you're saying
Well...
Eh?
Give it our all, with everyone
Going back to the first plan
Yes Yes
So everyone eats one each
Yeah, everyone eats at least one
then the remaining three we can discuss
so then...
I think going back to our starting point...
Let's just try going back
Things were more frank back then
Yes they were!
Everyone was saying "Then I'll go!"
Absolutely
You're right
At this point
Would anyone still say "Then I'll go"?
No one would
No, right?
So in the end we have to choose someone to eat 4
It's all about who's eating one and who's digesting the four
Then let's complete a full rotation!
Yes we should
We should!
Are you sure!?
But Tanaka has the biggest bod (body) here
Basically speaking
We have to acknowledge that
I was worried about bringing it up
Me, too
His bod (body) is the biggest
You're the closest thing to a giant here
Even off of looks you can tell
So why are we lumped up together with him
Exactly
Let's go!
We have arrived!
We have to be careful
No one's gonna eat if we don't keep things the way they were
We're gonna start owing each other if we don't stick with the plan
Store No. 10 Kanamachi Station Front
Now at their tenth store, Kanamachi Station Front location
Gindako Menu
Now the group makes the important decision of choosing from the menu
Rectangle
Takoyaki 1 Boat 500 Yen
The Standard
The standard of takoyaki
The Filling
Rectangle
Teritama 1 Boat 600 Yen
A filling alternative, Teritama
Cheese with Roe 1 Boat 600 Yen
Rectangle
The Strong Flavored
With heavy and strong flavors, Cheese with Roe
Finally, with refreshing green onion topping, Negidako
Negidako (Green Onion Topping) 1 Boat 600 Yen
Rectangle
The Refresher
Which one of the four will the men be choosing from?
Can their "Manliness"  be shown through their choices?
Will this choice reveal their "manliness"?
Store No. 10 Kanamachi Station Front
Which one are you gonna go for?
Which flavor?
One Negidako, please
Negidako
Rectangle
The Refresher
One Negidako, please
I don't care
So weak
No matter what you say, I don't care
Here you are
Oh, it's already done
That's suspicious
So everyone eat one each first
I'm just gonna check, there's gonna be four left right?
These onions
This should be a group decision
Maybe I might enjoy this
No, it's delicious
The onions
Delicious, right?
This is good, we're moving forward
How is it?
And then we pour the sauces...
We should go about this quickly like we discussed earlier
It's delicious
Let's go
Negidako's the way to go
Are you good?
Yes
Tanaka can we wait in the car?
Wait, wait
Then we'll stand here
Of course
We won't even look away
A little encouragement
Would be nice
Right
You would go at the same pace whether we do or not
No, no
I will go faster
This is everyone's efforts
Right right
You have to put on the sauce quickly
Alright!
Okay!
Tanaka finishes!
Complete
Great job
On to the next one!
Alucard Kameari
Kanamachi Station Front
Store No. 10
Store No. 11
We've finished up ten stores
And here are the standings
I've eaten 18
Yes
I have eaten 18
So now it's up to Shozo
I'm up next
You can do it
You'll have 20 by the next one
Hitting the 20 mark
Amazing
This one's no good
What do you mean?
This feature's really...
It feels like this every time
Every time
Everyone's going to get so fat
If we keep doing these things
We actually will get fat probably
"I watched Gaki no Tsukai for the first time in a while. What happened?"
Everybody got so fat
What happened to them?
What did happen?
We keep doing these challenges
So true
That's Ryo-san
Oh it is Ryo-san!
"Kochira Katsushika-ku Kameari Kōen Mae Hashutsujo" (Manga Title)
Statue of "Ryotsu Kankichi"
The group passes by the character stature of "Ryo-san" from the manga "Kochi Kame"
At the Kameari station front
Cool!
Whoa
That's impressive
If everyone could follow me
Store No. 11 Alucard Kameari
At the 11th stop, what will Endo order?
Negi-dako, please
Negi-Dako
Rectangle
The Refresher
Yes
One Negidako!
Endo!
Just this once, please
We're back to eating Negidako again!?
I haven't been able to order negidako yet
By myself
Alright just sit here
let's get this over with
Let's eat!
Go ahead
Might as well
Negidako again
Just make it quick
Wow
Would you like any seconds?
We're good, thanks
Don't forget the green onions too
We got more green onions than usual
You could probably finish that
You got it
Let's go Endo
Nice
You can probably go on, can't you?
To the next store
What?
I don't think even he'll be able to do that
That would be difficult
He can't help
But look like Mori Shinichi
And the 20th one is..
Is finished!
Good!
Alright!
Complete
Because it's just that good!
Of course!
You can't start disliking it here!
Next the group is moving to Nishiarai Store
According to the order we have in our current plan, Matsumoto-san is next
Me already!?
Yes
That is absolutely right
I'm sure he already knows what to order
Oh, really?
Are we sure that we want to keep going with this plan?
Yes
Yes please
I agree let's keep going
I kinda understand, though
Let's keep it
At this rate...
Tanaka and I already went so
We've already started the plan
But we could
if Tanaka, Endo, Matsumoto-san, me and Hamada-san went in that order
Nothing would change!
Yes and that's fine
We are a group after all
There's no visual appeal
There's no change in scenery
What do you mean "no visual appeal"?
The people watching
would be like "Eh!?"
"Tanaka's going next now!?"
For the people watching
Right
No No No
We don't have any elements of surprise
Right?
"Gaki" was able
to get this far because of stuff like that
That's true
Also through turning on each other
That's the two mains talking
But we should also...
How about we do rock paper scissors?
Eh!?
Your eyes keep getting bigger today
It's scary
It's for good reason!
Alright! We'll do the four!
Thank you
Are you sure!?
I...
Why are you farting in here?
Why do you have to fart in such a tight space like this
When we first started
this plan
maybe we should reconsider
when the three of us are left to do it
We can't do that for sure
We all have different states of hunger!
Because some of us started eating earlier than others
The "states of hunger"?
WHO'S EVEN HUNGRY?
Store No. 12 Nishiarai Sati
Those takoyakis are starting to hit me
But wait...
What are you thinking of ordering?
That's important
True
We've talked about this a lot
I've been thinking a lot about the Cheese and Roe
Cheese with Roe
Reectangles
The Pack-a-Punch
Teriyaki?
I thought about getting Teriyaki too, but
Rectangle2
Teriyaki
The Filler
That person
just bought it so
What?
That's unrelated!
So I was considering that
That just hit me
"I can't get that now since they bought it already"
What're you saying?
Thinking about the four
going inside me
Are you stupid?
Alright, please
Yes!
Takoyaki it is!
Rectangle
Takoyaki
The Standard
What the hell!
Let's just go with something normal!
This is the second time in a row
That's right!
Let's eat!
Ok, Itadakimasu!
Are you serious!?
These are really cooked!
So that's one
So he's doing four
Indeed
Yes, eating four at this point
That's gotta be rough
Oh, he's doing it!
Matsumoto-san's got it!
That's the pace, Matsumoto-san!
For real?!
Complete
We're going all in on this!
Damn!
Ario Nishiarai
Nishiarai Sati
Store No. 12
Store No. 13
The next location is only 5 minutes away
Along with the takoyaki Matsumoto had
This short trip will make the next location into hell
Zaki-san Zaki-san Zaki-san we're here!
For real?
For real though, huh.
We are for real
What a face
That's quite a face
Store No. 13 Ario Nishiarai
As we arrive at the thirteenth location
Yamasaki goes in to buy
the refresher, negidako
Store No. 13 Ario Nishiarai
Negidako
Rectangle
The Refresher
They meet at a park
Yamasaki's stomach prepares to not fail them
Will they be able to clear it!?
Do what you gotta do!
Complete
Finished!
Amazing!
Alright
We got this
Ario Nishiari
Jujou Ginza
Store No. 13
Store No. 14
Yamazaki proving his manliness
And the next up in the rotation...
Alright Hamada-san
We're counting on you
If you eat 4 here that would be 22.
I give up
You're kidding, right?
The unexpected
Not yet!
My stomach's feelin' really heavy
Mine too
It's just so full
I can even feel it below my stomach
So heavy
Ｉ　ＤＯＮ’Ｔ　ＷＡＮＴ
ＴＯ　ＥＡＴ　ＡＮＯＴＨＥＲ　ＢＩＴＥ
Is what I'd probably say if I were a robot.
This isn't good
Hamada-san
Yes?
Have you decided what you'll order?
Store No. 14        Juujou Ginza
Their legs are feeling heavy, but they arrive at the 14th location!
Store No. 14 Juujou Ginza
Wait, these people are on TV
No we ain't
That's like, so funny
"That's like, so funny"
Next in line!
The Cheese and Roe!
Cheese and Roe
Rectangle
The Pack-a-Punch
He went for it
Wow!
He's so cool!
He did it
He went for the cheese and roe
Going for it now?!
We have to change up the flavor, we keep getting green onion
He's so dirty. So dirty.
He's an old pervert
At this point
Getting cheese and roe at this point,
such an old pervert move.
His true old pervert essence
is coming out
It's hard to pick the right time, huh
Yea, it is hard
I thought it was pretty manly
I thought it was a good choice, but now I'm just an old perv
Are you kidding me?! Cheese and Roe?!
Hold on, hold on
Itadakimasu
Wow, you really are a man for picking this
This is somethin'
Stop messin' around
This really hits you
Ohh
Just one more
Only one left.
Complete
He's completed it.
Incredible!
He did it!
Complete!
That's the second round of 4 pieces-per-person complete
Alright everyone,
Juujou Ginza
Ooyama Happy Road
Store No. 14
Store No. 15
Let's head to the next location!
Let's count up the total
So we've gone to 14 stores so far,
and everyone's eaten either 22 or 23 takoyaki balls.
But since we've gone through everybody twice now,
what should we do about this system?
Do you wanna keep doing the same thing or change it up?
Since we just ate,
Starting with Tanaka, the whole boat 2 times in a row...
One person does 2 stores in a row...
A new plan?
I haven't heard the rest of the plan but
it sounds good to me
That's not right
No way, no way
You mean I have to eat 16 balls?
16 balls at once?
If we go with what Hamada-san just suggested...
There's no way
Hold up,
You're supposed to say "Cocorico will eat as much as they can"
Again with this
Hey
We want to say that, but...
Say "Us two are gonna switch off
every time" right now!!
This again....
It always ends up like this
I was wondering when he was gonna say it
Seriously though
Tell them yourself, Matsumoto-san
You know,
If Shinsuke-Nii were here
he'd actually be pissed at you
I don't know about that,
Shinsuke-san would probably,
He would never
never do that
Alright, how 'bout from now on I eat two balls
Really?
Seriously?
If you guys are gonna insist
Two balls.
Tanaka is tall so
he can eat three
You're tall so you eat 3
Does height really have anything to do with this?
Alright, then please split the other ones between you guys
So Tanaka eats 3, you 2, then 1-1-1
Alright, alright I get it.
I'll eat three!
I'll do 3 and he does 2
But at this point,
when it gets to be too much I'll have to give up,
so if it gets to that point I'll need everyone's help
If you agree to that, then let's do it
Amazing.
This is a good plan
We finally have a good plan
If we didn't decide this it'd still be unsettled
We need everyone else's help...
'If we didn't decide this it'd still be unsettled'
What do you mean
Alright, here we are
We're here, huh
A new plan
Is this a shopping street?
A shopping street?
After being pressured by their senpai,
The plan is 'Endou eats 2, Tanaka eats 3.'
Store No. 15 Ooyama Happy Road
But will it work?
Okay, what's it gonna be?
Store No. 15 Ooyama Happy Road
Tanaka's gonna eat the most, so
Tanaka
Huh, Tanaka?
Where's Tanaka?
Tanaka?!
Huh, Tanaka?
Where's Tanaka?
Tanaka?!
Oh, he scared me, I thought he ran away
I thought he escaped!
Sorry, my microphone fell
I'm really sorry
You scared us
You're gonna eat the most out of any of us, so
you pick.
I think...
What's it gonna be?
I'm thinkin',
the standard.
Rectangle
Takoyaki
The Standard
Just plain?
Yea.
That was a little too casual
*TL Note: He was speaking too informally
Hold on,
Thank you
Here you go
I's so hawt
You were cocorico bombers after all
Yea
A long time ago, yeah
After this,
Not bad.
He did it!
Okay!
He's done it!
Complete
Beautiful!
Well done!
Completed!
Good work
Next is the 16th store, Waseda
which is always crowded with students
Store No. 16 Waseda
Tanaka again orders plain takoyaki, however
Rectangle
Takoyaki
The Standard
his expression soon turns gloomy.
Are you alright,
Tanaka-san?
Because his no one is turning his wind-up key, he eats slow like that
Keep going, keep going
Housei-san
Yama-chan,
help him out!
I'm the one that needs help...
Why?
What?!
Why's that?
Right now,
We've received some troubling news.
After about 5 minutes,
an exam at the university will end,
and an unbelievable amount of students will rush here
Very quickly.
We have to finish this quick, or else
Look, look, look
Time is of the essence!
it's gonna get crazy
Only 5 minutes
Hamada-san looks like
he could eat another one!
Hamada-san should eat it!
Please!
There's not much time!
Completed!
Complete
Alright, we're done!
Let's go to the next store!
8 hours since starting, is this the stomach's limit?
The atmosphere is as heavy as their guts.
We can't even
laugh and talk while we walk right now
Store No. 17 Sanmoru Nakano
After arriving at Nakano, the 17th store awaits!
Rectangle
Takoyaki
The Standard
Here it is
We're they always this big?
Here it is guys
These look really big
Take yours, Yama-chan,
This is my second one
This is my second one, too
Eat it for them, Yama-chan
Please!
Zaki-san
Please.
Hurry up!
This one is Hamada-san's
I just
ate one, idiot!
Please, nii-san
You can give up here, you know?
Everyone's eaten what they're supposed to already.
Exactly.
This is his problem
Right.
You came all this way,
There's courage in giving up, too!!
So, Yama-chan.
What are you gonna do?
Housei-san.
At least
make that look good!
Why did it stick like that?
Why did that happen?
There it is!
Complete
ＹＥＳ!
Completed!
Roppongi
Sanmoru Nakano
Store No. 17
Store No. 18
We're heading out!
It's just that, uhh
There's a big gap between us and Matsumoto-san now
That's true
At this point, 4 balls is a massive difference
Really?
It's not even close
At the next store, does something think
they could eat a full boat?
That's called drastic measures
Then,
If you do it, you'll catch up to us
That's right
You can close the gap
Me, a full boat
A full boat
all at once
at once.
No, I mean,
Not me, but another human here who could eat a full boat.
The only one here is Tanaka.
There's absolutely no way.
Understood, let's do this
Let me do rock paper scissors with Tanaka!!
Me...?
I got it.
Hold on a second...
Why is it always me this time!
If I lose to Tanaka, then I'll do it, but
Tanaka's just not even trying at all, so
No, no, no
I've eaten the most of anyone!
Can we add in
one more person?
I agree with that
I'm okay with that
He's spinning the roulette
Alright
Alright!
Store No. 18 Roppongi
At last, the deciding battle.
Alright
Ready?
Alright, let me put this on
One boat, the 8 ball battle
The 8 Ball Battle!
With three participants
The loser eats a full boat
Is putting the hat on an official rule?
It decides who eats a whole boat, so
Gotta get into gear
Here we go.
Ready?
Rock, paper, scissors shoot!
YES!
YAYY!
1 Boat, 8 Ball Hell
Tanaka!!
Tanaka-san, you lost!
God is watching over us!!
Store No. 18 Roppongi
Alright, let's head over
Let's go!
Eat your whole body weight's worth, Tanaka!!
Rectangle
Takoyaki
The Standard
The boat of hell,
Tanaka chooses the classic standard, plain Takoyaki!
I just got one pair of chopsticks, since you know...
Oh I see! That's right, huh!
There was really no point in
getting out of the car, but whatever
Honestly, yea
Cause we had an agreement
That's right, yes.
There's still 7.5 balls left.
7.5 left.
If we're calculating it, here
That's right
I'm working on it.
We're counting on you here
I will, I know.
Where's the next store?
Next is, uhh
Harajuku
Take us to Harajuku, Tanaka.
Take me down to Harajuku, baby
I really wanna go
It's pretty close, too
This video was brought to you by Tofu Panda Fansubs
It's close by, yes
What are you doing?
You can rest when we go to Harajuku.
He's crying!
What're you gonna do?
I give up...
Give up?!
Huhh?!!
What'dya say?
Give up
Give??
Could you say it for us one more time?
Say it loud and clear, please.
Can I please give up...
The End!
Conquest Failed!!
Tokyo 23 Districts, 37 Stores
It's over!
11,950 Yen (~$110USD) Payed by Tanaka
Total Cost of Takoyaki