Calbee Potato Chips Taste Guess
Part 2!
These chips
Recap
Ah again, they're...
They're rich
They're rich?
Rich?
Consome Double Punch
They could be those plain ones
Could be, could be
I guess I'm lame after all ...
You're cool!
From popular varities,
and limited time special chips
Including some discontinued products,
* Some have ended production
Calbee Chips 72 Varities
specially provided for this game
The 5 will consult together
This is a team effort kiki
A really  bad guess gets a punishment!
You just gotta smell it before anyone huh?
Recap
The one we ate, was, Chicken Salt flavour!
Infinitely Delicious Chicken Salt
Unfortunatley, incorrect!
It was 24, Ibburi-Gakki flavour!
Octopus?
It's a pickle
Oh yeah, it's ibburi-gakko!
It literally can't be anything else
TYPESET BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SENOR_WRISTBAND
Downtown's
Gaki no Tsukai
ya Arahende!
The appearance is a good hint, huh?
Yeah
Let's move on to the next chips
7th flavour
Continuing on, these are the next chips
They look different
They're hard fried
We can distinguish them
7th f
Hard fried, they're hard fried!
Yes
There's a lot of hard fried...
There's a ton of them!
Could be black pepper?
7th flavour
There's not a hint of pepper you absoulte numpty!
There's no black flecks or anything!
Don't make lame jokes!
What black pepper are you seeing here?
Lost all my confidence suddenly...
Hmm?
The taste ...
It's definitely hard fried
I see
The appearance, right?
It's crunchy
Uwahh, I see
But it's definitely,
Yes?
It's not Seaweed from #28,
Edamame Garlic
Seaweed
Wasabi Salt
and it's not Edamame or Wasabi either
#27 Black Pepper - It's not black pepper either
In that case?
Konbu Soy Sauce
It's for sure between 32 and 35
Kyushu Soy Sauce
So you've narrowed it down to 4
Kansai Dashi Soy
Konbu Soy Sauce
Kyushu Soy Sauce
White Shrimp
I think I am not mistaken here
There is no mistake here
Right?
Tanaka-san, and Housei-san agree?
Yes, no mistake
There's no plum taste from 31 either
Kansai Dashi Soy
Konbu Soy
Kyushu Soy Sauce
Plum and Konbu
White Shrimp
What about this Kyushu Soy Sauce?
Or like Kansai Dashi Soy Sauce
text
It has a Kansai taste
The smell is pretty-
Right? a Kyushu smell
It's a deep taste
I see
Kansai?
Kansai Dashi Soy Sauce
or Kyushu?
Kyushu Soy Sauce
You're that confident?
You're confident?
It's between those two right?
32 or 34
Kansai Dashi Soy Sauce
Kyushu Soy Sauce
It's either one
Yeah
34 and 35 are both soy sauce,
just the dashi is different
So it depends whether we can taste dashi
I see
The soy sauce is hard to discern
I see, I see
Kansai...
has a more delicate flavour?
Yeah I agree, it's weaker
Then it's Kyushu?
It feels like Kyushu ...
I think the dashi taste is the sweetness
I see
They're really glaring at you!
That was really cold reaction!
They really don't agree
Exactly
I think it's #35 (Kyushu)
I see
Kyushu ...
It doesn't have that kansai dashi taste
I think this is good
You all agree?
Yup
Then everyone,
yes
are you ready?
The answer please!
Ok
The one we all ate, was, Kyushu Soy Sauce flavour!
Hard Fried Potato
Kyushu Soy Sauce Flavour
Correct!
YEAHASDHAJSKLD !!!!!!
Well done!
We did it!
That was
That was well done
I'm so happy
You narrowed it down first, between 32 and 35
Limited Time Product (China - Shikoku - Kyushu)
This feels great
That was great
Kyushu Soy Sauce
The rich chicken broth brings out the sweetness in the soy sauce
I feel great
8th flavour
Let's continue to these chips
Oh?
These are the next chips
The appearance is a hint again
Right? The pepper
That's a hint
It's pepper, right?
This is pepper
Definitely pepper
The black flecks?
There are black flecks
It's pepper
It's sweet
Sweet, but peppery
Yeah of course
This is pepper
It's pepper for sure
Should we just go for the pepper?
I think pepper is correct
What pepper ones are there?
There's 27 ...
Hard Fried - Black Pepper
It's not hard fried though
It's not hard fried right
So eliminate that
Pepper, pepper
#57
57?
Toyama Black Ramen?
Toyama's Black Ramen Flavour
Black Ramen?
Oh yeah
That black ramen?
Toyama Black Ramen
Toyama Local Delicacy Ramen
Yes
We said it's pepper man
That is pepper ramen
It's pepper flavour ramen
There's no other pepper flavours, huh?
Oh yeah
There's also #24, Rich Pepper Flavour
That's it!
This is the answer
Right?
TN: I think kuro kosho is black pepper (black seasoning)
This is definitely kuro kosho flavour
Right?
Yup, yeah
Are you ready? That was fast.
24 - Rich Black Pepper (Black Seasoning)
If we get this, Yamasaki can regain his reputation
Yes
Understood, are you ready then?
This is definitely 24
Understood, the answer please!
The one we ate, was, Rich Black Pepper flavour
Unfortunately, incorrect!
Eh, it's not this one?
It's not my fault, ok?
Yes that's true but,
Housei-san you should have been more confident
Correct answer?
Toyama's Black Ramen flavour!
SEEE!!!!!!!!!!!!
It was that one!
* Discontinued
Toyama's Black Ramen
MOUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUU!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
It was Toyama Black!
I FUGGIN TOLD YOUUU!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
You said it immediately huh?
You should have pushed for it more
Exactly
You were doubted
Someone doubted me
Who?
Who?!
THIS GUY!
This man destroyed my confidence!
We thought you were gonna get it
Seriously?!
Amazing, you got it
A flavour from one of the 47 Prefectures;
A rich black soup with lots of umami flavour, with a kick from black pepper
That's why it was sweet
Exactly
You said it was sweet at the beginning
Discontinued*
Toyama's Black Ramen
Oh that's why?
I haven't had these ones before
They are tasty
Moving on, these chips
Yes! We got them again!
Hard Fried
Yes, yes, we can distinguish these
Let's get this bread
Sniffing the shit out of them
9th flavour
I almost pinched his head ...
That was close
You might end up smelling his head
Yup! Ok!
I got it!
Thank you
I already got it!
Thank you for the freebie question
Is it that one?
I got it
That one right?
It's that one, or-
Absolutely
Can you all say it together?
Ready, steady, #31
Plum and Salted Konbu
If this is wrong, we're over
Exactly
Endo
Hamada
Hosei
Matsumoto
Tanaka
Definitely
You're ready?
The answer, please!
The one we ate, was, Plum and Salted Konbu flavour!
Plum and Salted Konbu
CORRECT!
Well done!
That was fast!
You guys were quick
I got it from the smell
Oh really?
It's a delicate smell
Right
A lingering taste of konbu and a gentle plum aroma
Hard Fried
Plum and Salted Konbu
A skillfully guessed answer
Next up are these
10th Flavour
These types
These are ruffled, right?
Yeah these are ruffled right?
The shape is different though
Ruffled - Rich Chicken Consome
Ruffled - Salt Flavour
This could be the ruffled salt
Looks like it
Yup
10th flavour
This is that one
*cronch* *cronch*
This is super rich
Is it butter?
Yeah, yeah it is
That was fast
Can I say it?
Matsumoto-san you know it?
This is definitely #23
Rich Potato - Rich Butter Soy Sauce
Rich Butter Soy Sauce?
It's really rich
Matsumoto
Rich Potato - Rich Butter Soy Sauce
It's buttery
It's definitely butter
Right? And it's says rich in the name
"Rich Potato" right?
Matsumoto
Rich Potato - Rich Butter Soy Sauce
This one yeah?
Everyone agrees?
Let's go for this one
The richness I'm tasting is from this
You all agree with this one?
Let's say it
You're ready?
This tempo is good?
The answer, please!
The one we ate, was, Rich Butter Soy Sauce flavour
Rich Potato - Rich Butter Soy Sauce
Unfortunately,
Incorrect!
No way!
Who? Who?
Matsumoto-san is responsible for this tempo
He was pointing at me LOL
Batsu Game
Matsumoto
Hold on hold on hold on
Matsumoto is the impostor
He said "it's definitely this one"
If you guys keep it up we'll all stop talking
We won't stop talking
I'm just guessing!
Your brain,
shid - shup
should I dweep fwy it?
What the hell is he saying?
That hurts!
This hurts more than you think
What the hell was he saying?
Our guess is wrong?
It was incorrect
It was definitely butter
Right?
A chip with a unique width and thickness
Kiwa Jaga Series - Potato Butter
A hint for next time,
Kiwa Jaga - Potato Butter
The quantity is less right? So probably,
The chip bag design is different too
Ah oh yeah it is
I see
Right?
It has that, it's a premium type
Yeah, yeah
Oh I see
So when it's like this, it's a premium type
That makes sense
Like some fancy cheese
That's how rich it tastes?
From now on,
it is no longer a group effort
Let's start off with Tanaka-san
Single Challenger
Tanaka
Ok
Tanaka-san, these are your chips
Go ahead divorced man
Woah you're lucky
This is a lucky question right?
Hold on ...
This is a good one, you're lucky
This is a lucky question
The colour is definitely that one ...
11th flavour
You can definitely narrow it down
This is a good one
It's that one right?
Yeah that one
That's the one that comes to mind
It's definitely that one
You guys can guess without eating?
Yeah, it's definitely that one
It's that one for sure!
Yeah for sure
You're so lucky man
I thought you were gonna guess it right away
Really?
Only Tanaka-san doesn't-
No, no, I got it, I got it
The smell is good right?
Go ahead, Tanaka-san
Go ahead
Please hold on a second
Eh really? I can already say it
You need some time?
Really?
Even though you didn't eat it?
You got it? Really?
Well yeah
I got it
From the smell alone it's gotta be that one
You guys are really confident
It's that one - It's that one
Should I take over?
Endo just take over
Ehhhh I have to take over from you?
You're gonna take over?
I guess I have to
Although you'll be out right away
If I'm incorrect?
Yeah of course
Yeah of course you will
Then which one of us should take over? I already got it
You want to take over?
I want to take over
Tanaka-san's reputation is in the gutter now huh?
Should we do rock paper scissors?
What shall we do?
We can eat it right?
Of course, this is about taking Tanaka's turn
Whoever wins tells him
Wow so lucky
Itadakimasu
You're taking over before the batsu game?
It's a batsu game right away
I have no goddamn idea ...
What the hell man
The taste is totally different?!
Right? It's harder than you think
Seiously?
Potato Chips 72 Flavour Guessing Game
Matsumoto takes over Tanaka's challenge!
Challenger switched
Challenger Switched
It's a batsu-game right away
I have no goddamn idea
What the hell man
It's difficult right?
Seriously?
What should I do now?
You already took his turn
You have to guess it
You wanted to take his turn
This....
It's your fault
I thought it was #61
Shizuoka - Sakura Shrimp
But after I ate it, it was totally different
Challenger Switched
There's this redness in the chips,
So it could be #64
Beni Shoga?
Osaka - Pickled Ginger (Beni Shoga)
Shiga - Beef Steak
This is REALLY hard
It's difficult yes
I got it
This is a hard one
Then Matsumoto-san, the answer please
The one I ate, was, Osaka Pickled Ginger flavour
Osaka Beni Shoga
Unfortunately, BATSU GAME!
Batsu Game!
Matsumoto
You wanted to take over
You took his batsu game
Ta-to, Ta-to
It's Po-ta-to!
What the hell are you making me say?!
What the hell was he saying?
Ehhhhh? I have no idea
Tanaka-san what did you think it was?
Shizuoka - Sakura Shrimp
I thought it was #61
That's what you thought, and the correct answer is exactly that
It was sakura shrimp
Give me my turn back!
That's messed up!
*Discontinued
Shizuoka Sakura Shrimp
What is this turn of events?!
A flavour from one of the 47 prefectures
Enjoy the delicious taste of shrimp from Suruga Bay
Matsumoto's mistake, Shizuoka's Sakura Shrimp Flavour
Endo
Single Challenger
Endo-san gets these chips
These should be immediately guessed
Go ahead man
Don't take up too much time
12th flavour
It's up to him LOL
OK, I'm ready
Already?
That was fast!
#25
This is-
You're ready?
Thick Cut - Wasabi
Thick Cut Wasabi
That was fast
You're good with that?
He's so goddamn handsome
Let's go. The one I ate, was,
Thick Cut, Wasabi flavour
Thick Cut
Wasabi
CORRECT!
Correct!!!!!
Marvelous!
So fast!
As soon as you ate it
Yes exactly
That was cool
* Limited Regions (China, Shikoku, Kyushu)
Wasabi
Thank you very much
That speed...
This was an easy one to guess
Hamada-san's challenge are these chips
Gorilla
Single Challenger
Hamada-san gets these chips
Ah, these could be those ones
Right? I've seen these before
13th flavour
They're those kinds
That type for sure
We can totally take over for you
There's nothing special here at all ...
That can't be true
There's some clue for sure
Ehhh what flavour is this?
This is also a straight away batsu game
Eh what?
Out right away
If your guess is really bad
Ah I see
If you are way off from the right answer
Yes exactly
He's eating the shit out of them
Hard to believe this guy just took a shit
He took a long time shitting, huh?
Took a 10 minute bathroom break
Isn't this the standard lightly salted?
Lightly Salted
At this point
Then are you ready?
Yes, yes
Then Hamada-san, the answer please!
The one I ate, was,
lightly salted flavour
Unfortunately,
incorrect!
Batsu Game
Hamada
Straight away
Hamada-san your guess was way off
way off?
But that ...
Your taste buds are useless
You bloody Potato Baron
That was an amazing sound
Why the hell was he angry?
What was that
You thought it was lightly salted,
it was this Yokohama Tonkatsu Soy Sauce Ramen flavour
I have no goddamn idea
No idea
This was difficult?
Experience the plenitful flavour of Yokohama Tonkatsu Ramen
A flavour from one of the 47 prefectures;
A Kanagawa flavour
Matsumoto's challenge is these chips
Matsumoto
Single Challenger
They look really basic
The appearance yeah
Certainly
Woah amazing
You definitely modified them huh?
We didn't, we really didn't
The staff here, I have no trust for them
14th flavour
They want me to fail
We really didn't modify them, you can even see here afterwards
Oh really?
We did not modify anything
Really?
Then,
I sincerely apologise for my conduct
So honest!
What a supremely decent person!
What a great person!
What flavour could they be...
Uwahhh
UwaHH
It's that one!
He got it?
So that "uwahh" didn't mean you were lost
Yeah exactly
He knows which one
You narrowed it down?
It's, honestly,
how do I say
The debut of potato chips
That's how you feel?
Ah, thank you for this!
It's either Lightly Salted,
Lightly Salted
Or #10, White Soy Sauce
White Soy Sauce
Actually there's no soy sauce flavour, I GOT IT!
Are you ready?
Ok, yes!
The answer, please!
The one I ate was Lightly Salted flavour!
Lightly Salted
He's gonna get this one
Correct!
That was amazing, well done!
That was really cool!
That was amazing
That was great!
Lightly Salted
Potato Chips
The king of flavours, introduced in 1975.
Well done Matsumoto!
Popular for over 40 years!
Well done!
Lightly Salted
You really got it
Hamda-san this is lightly salted
Yeah it's the "debut of potato chips"
Yeah you're right
Even though you said the staff wants you to fail, they gave you the lightly salted!
I offer my sincerest apologies
He's really apologising
I will never drink alcohol again
TN: He's making fun of press conferences where celebrities apologise for getting caught drunk driving
You can still drink alcohol
Feels like it's gonna get harder now
Hosei
Single Challenger
Hosei-san's challenge is these chips
Ah they're hard fried
Oh yeah they are
That's lucky
You got good ones
15th flavour
I got it
I want a good tempo going
They look thick, like that Edwin tag
The thickness right?
15th flavour
That Edwin thing right?
That thing yeah
What a cool expression!
Yama-Chan is taking his time huh
It wasn't a freebie question at all
Taking his time
Yeah
I wanna eat them
I'm not sure exactly, but definitely a garlic taste
You're lucky to get one with that distinguishing taste
Right? Thank you very much!
The one I ate, was, Edamame Garlic flavour
Edamame Garlic
Hard Fried
Which one is that?
#29?
CORRECT!!
Correct!
Well done!
That was a lucky one! Mine tasted like lightly salted
So annoying
He's really feeling it!
Edamame Garlic
Hard Fried
He's tap dancing!
He's tap dancing
Ah, it really is that one!
Tastes just like the real thing
Hamada-san you think so?
Just like the real thing, can really taste the Edamame
Combining the sweet flavour of Edamame and umami of garlic
Hard Fried - Edamame Garlic
Yes
That was fast
The garlic is the biggest hint
That was easy to guess
Tasty
Now they sample the flavours they are curious about
Can we try the Mirei  Biscuit?
Mirei?
#69
Mirie Biscuit
I don't know what Mirei Biscuits are
They're just like normal sweet biscuits
A classic biscuit from Kochi Prefecture
Mirei Biscuit
Really?
Yes
"Mirei Biscuit"
They're kawaii
From Kochi?
Kochi
*Discontinued
Kochi - Mirei Biscuit
There's a ton of them
Right?
Yeah
Makes a nice sound!
Like Champagne!
Champagne?
Like Dom Perignon
Dom Perignon sound
A flavor from one of the 47 prefectures
Mirei Biscuits, popular in Kochi
He is a rich man
Mirei Biscuit
They're sweet
Sweet?
Oh yeah they are
Yeah they are!
These are tasty!
Very good
Yes tasty
They taste like Mirei Biscuits?
Oh yeah they do
These are the sweetest flavour right?
Yes, very sweet
Tasty
Would you like to try #42?
It seems pretty standard though?
Inca Awakening
Ishigaki Salt
It's just salt flavour?
Ishigaki Salt?
Woah what's this?
Luxury Potato Chips
Woahhh
What is this?!
Amazing
Inca Awakening
Ishigaki Salt
It seems pretty standard though?
It's just salt flavour?
Ishigaki Salt?
Woah hold on
Woah what's this?
What is this?!
Amazing
Looks very premium
Yeah
What is "Inca Awakening"?
Inca Awakening is an expensive potato variety
Have a sweet chestnut flavour
Inca's Awakening
Oh I see
They're like gifts
*Limited to Specialty Stores
Inca Awakening - Ishigaki Salt
Woaah
This kind of packaging?
They're like gifts
Yeah like souvenirs
Woah look
They're very different
So thick ( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)
The colour is unique too
These are good, they're like,
very crunchy
And they're thick
Tasty, very tasty
They would make great gifts
Tasty, very crispy
Right?
Yeah
How much are these?
Approx 880 yen (incl tax)
Inca Awakening Isihigaki Salt
Jaga Crispy
Made using Inca Awakening potato variety
These are 880 yen
These are good
These are good?
Yes
What do you wanna eat?
Roasted Manju, #52
Woah Roasted Manju
Gunma - Roasted Manju
Interesting....
Want to try it
This is the package design
Oh like this?
Grilled Manju
Interesting
*Discontinued
Gunma - Grilled Manju
Itadakimasu
Woah very unique
Are they sweet?
Yes
I can really taste the anko
Great smell too
Amazing, the smell is like the real thing
Decently sweet
The sweetness-
Ehh but if I had to guess this one I couldn't
You can taste the anko?
Yeah I can taste the anko
Anko?
A flavour from one of the
ln(2.58131289e20) prefectures
The taste of Gunma; manju roasted with sweet miso sauce (not anko)
Like I said,  I don't taste any anko
I said I didn't
You said you tasted it!
You said it
You said Anko
You thought it was Anko Manju
I said I DON'T taste any anko
Miso?
It's Miso
yeah
It's sweet Miso
I said so!
This deserves a batsu game!
I said it, "It doesn't taste like anko!"
Sorry Matsumoto-san, this is a batsu game!
Batsu Game!
Matsumoto
Who cares! We're not playing the game right now!
There's no helping it
You thought it was-
I said it doesn't taste like anko!
Sorry Matsumoto-san, this is a batsu game!
Who cares! We're not playing the game right now!
There's no helping it
I said it doesn't!
Like c'mon I-
Quiet, quiet
Your head is,
dweet - podado
lyge a dweed podado!
Just speak properly for once!
I see, this kind of taste
It is this taste
Tasty, very tasty
TYPESET BY KEDOMAS
TRANSLATION BY SENOR_WRISTBAND