Subtitles: Zurui
Reunion
[Masao-kun is in danger!]
[If he doesn't get help soon, he could get hurt!]
[Hurry, Miracle Ace!]
Miracle Ace
Mister, it's been a while!
Yes it has
This is the second time you're helping me!
Yes
Thank you!
How did you know I was in trouble?
I was returning from my job
Huh?
Oh, then you heard me... what's wrong Mister?
I'm tired
I had a lot to do today, I'm tired
Oh, your part-time job was tiring?
Yea...
Oh, I thought you could hear my voice with your super hearing
I thought I should go home early
My grandmother is coming home soon
Really?
Yea
We're all going to the buffet
What kind of buffet?
Yeah, we're all going to the buffet
What is that?
Want some?
Candy
Yes
Which hand?
This one!
Thank you
Do you always carry candy?
Yea
It's sweet
You're right
Mister
Yea
You know. I'm always getting bullied
Could you teach me?
What?
Some skill
Ok
I want you to teach me how to defend myself
Like, if someone is going to punch you?
Well... let's see
Try to punch me
Don't bother
Don't come
I'm hitting you, Mister
My punch is hitting you
It's always that way
but somehow I never loose
Only once during middle school did I loose badly
Just in middle school huh?
Yea
Do you think I can win?
I guess you can
You just need courage
Basically
I don't have courage
Yea
I should just try, right?
Yea, that's right
Let's go shall we?
Where are you going?
Huh?
Where are you going now?
You're going to help someone?
I told you. I'm going home, my grandmother is coming
We're all going to eat at the buffet
Which star did you come from Mister?
I told you I can't tell you that!
Bye!
So he's Miracle Ace...
He still has a lot of secrets!
To be continued