Subtitles: Zurui
Today Again
[As I thought, Masao-kun is in danger again!]
[If he doesn't hurry up, they will kidnap Masao-kun!]
[Hurry up and help!]
[Miracle Ace!]
It hurts!
"Mirakuru faito de nagisa no Rock & Roll"
"Mirakuru faito de tokimeki Blue Jeans"
Thank you!
They are bullying you again
I want to die
Don't die
I hate it
You have a difficult problem
By the way...
I have good news
ok?
Yes
I wonder if you should do this...
What is it?
Huh?
Do you want to join Miracle group?
There's something like that?
Yes, there is
Really?
If I join the group, I will become stronger?!
Yes
Really?
Of course, because it's my group
I wonder if I can join?
You will get a monthly magazine
Really?
Yes
Does it cost anything?
Well... it's not like you don't need money
Maybe just a donation
Are there lots of kids like me?
Well, yes I guess you can say that
Kids just like me?
Wow, how many?
To many to count
Let me join too!
You will also get a Miracle Mask
Huh?! Really?!
If you wear it, no one will ever bother you
Really?!
Gimmie!
You want it?
- Yes
I guess it ok
Thank you!
You should told me about this sooner!
There you go
You're just a member, so it's smaller
Now you should be ok
Yes, you should be ok now
Bye
Don't forget about the song!
Ok?
Will I be ok?
"Mirakuru... faito de..."
Ouch! Ouch!
"Mirakuru..."
Miracle Ace!
Ouch! Ouch!
That's Miracle Ace, he still has a lot of secrets!
To be continued