The Future Century
Squadron: The Five Rangai!
His wife called me.
What? I thought you
guys had broken up.
We had. But she found out
about us and went crazy.
What a bitch. It's her fault
that he went for another woman.
Yeah. But she knows
something... Yes.
Evening.
Hi.
Ryoko-chan, I heard that
**(bleeped) gave you a hard time.
It's not easy
to be a singer.
You should kick their asses.
They're just jealous.
Because they are on the wane.
What?
- They are here.
I'm just saying no one as right
to be mean to someone with future.
You can talk to me if you
are in trouble, OK?
They are calling...
- Can't you wait?
Heeelp!
Stop!
Akira Fire!
(from another sketch)
Na-me Neko!
(delinquent young cat)
Gachapin!
(character in kids show)
Pieman!
(also from another sketch)
Snake Police Officer!
(character from their early work)
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
Ladies, run. Now.
- Thank you.
Stop!
You bring back memories.
It's like 5 years ago.
Wait.
Why are you in
those costumes?
One of us is really creepy.
You too bring back old days.
Long time.
They saved that costume?
They send it all the way
from Tokyo Tower.
What the hell
do you think...
You hardly look like
a team!
Don't you remember what you said?
- What did I say?
You said we have to
appeal to kids.
How could he appeal to kids?
How could he?
He does. Don't you see?
This isn't working.
Why?
Yes, you have to appeal kids.
But you have to look like heroes.
I'm sorry.
But you have to fight.
Please.
- No.
Don't shoot.
I'm a wicked cute little snake.
You don't move like
you did in old days.
My ribs. Some of my ribs are missing.
- Don't give me BS.
We can't fight.
- Why?
Because you are
absolutely not 5 Rangai.
I don't give a damn
about 5 Rangai.
I said my some of
my ribs are missing.
If I say one thing you only do that
and fail all other things.
You wanna die?
Hey!
It's... this is not my idea.
So who's idea is this?
- His.
Is this your idea?
Look. He's stepped back.
You don't resist.
We got it.
Forget about fighting.
But what you said wasn't
exactly clear. - Why?
We thought very hard how to
appeal to kids. - I understand that.
But don't forget that you are heroes.
That's rule number one!
So what do you want us
to do?
Just get something
that will make you look like heroes.
If we don't look like it
it's your fault.
Who do you think
you are speaking to!
That's his words.
Just tell me what you want!
- Cool costumes!
Cool costumes so that kids want
to be like you.
I got it.
- Really?
Finally.
It will work.
Make them want
to be like you.
I have an idea.
Just for me.
Just for you? - Yes.
So it's up to the other guys.
I got it too.
- You do?
That's what I've been talking about
from the start. - Thank you.
Make a clean start.
See you next week.
Make them want to be
like you. - Ok.
Nobody want to be like
you now.
We may be little late next week.
- No!
You come here on time!
- We will.
I'm busy.
Goodbye.
I'll do it.
- Ok.
The Future Century Squadron: The Five Rangai!   To be con't.