Subtitles: ZuRUi
Bike
This is kind of nice huh?
DIdn't I tell you so.
It sounds good.
Itao!
Hey.
What are you doing?
Just checking out his new bike.
Who's this?
Him?
He's my friend from middle school, Kurano.
Hey! Who's this?
That's Hamada.
Can I get on it?
Huh?
Can I get on?
Go ahead.
What are you doing here?
Er... um...
Don't do things without tell me.
No, no.
Huh?
It's because I'm here.
It's nothing special.
This feels good.
Right?
It's good huh?
Yea.
Let me borrow it.
Do you have a license?
It doesn't matter!
Hey, cut it out.
Stop it!
I said let me borrow it!
Can you ride?
What's with this guy?
It's none of your business!
Can you ride??
What's it to you!
Ma-kun!
Ma-kun! What are you doing?
Ma-kun! Oh, you're here!
You never came home from shopping!
Oh Itao-san and Yoko are here too.
Did you get potatoes?
Hey!
Yea.
Did you buy potatoes at Sanukiya?
It's right there!
Come home sooner, you know I'm making curry!
You always leave home but never come back.
Here's your 200 yen spending money.
Here!
Not now!
Take it now or never!
Never mind, later!
Hurry take it!
I said later is fine!
I wont give you later.
Ok, give it to me.
What's his name?
Kurano.
Kurano? Oh, Kurano-san I'll give you 50 yen.
Let's go Ma-kun.
Ma-kun let's go!
What are you guys doing? Taking forever!
Let's go!
Come on!