Mitsuru-san
Translation: ZuRUi
It's no good
- Yea
We're messing up on the "shibakuzo" part
Let's try again
Tatsuya!
Practice with us!
Come on!
I don't want to learn that stupid dance
You dummy!
We're members of Hamigakitai right?
Just shut up!
I didn't want to join you guys from the beginning!
What are you saying?  Give me a break!
Yea, what are you saying?
What's with you?!
-What are you doing?
Stop!  Let's practice!
Shut up, idiot!
Not the face!
Stop it!
-Don't hit the face!
Stop it already!
Hey! Hey!
Mitsuru-san!
What are you guys doing?
Tatsuya doesn't want to practice
You need to take your practice seriously!
I don't want to do it!
You idiot!
You will be debuting next month...
You shouldn't be acting like this!
What are you talking about, idiot!
You need to practice seriously!
Idiot, I said I can do it!
I can't do it, I'm leaving
Hold it right there!
What do you want?
What are you doing?
Let's dance!
I'm leaving!
Tatsuya!
-Where are you going!