http://zurui.blogspot.com
Translations: Zurui
Sa-cchan
Good morning!
Good morning
Here you go, good morning
What's up you seem happy
Well... um.. yeah...
Did something happen?
Actually, my wife is expecting again
What?
Really?
How many kids do you have?
You have 2 now right?
Yes
So it will be 3?
No, actually she's having triplets
What?!
Will you be alright?
Yeah, more members means more fun I believe
I know that, but I'm only paying you 1000 yen a day
Can you make it?
Well.. everyday it feels like I'm dying
I'll put more then
Thank you very much
Boss
- Yeah
Actually, I have something to ask you
What?
Actually, I found a new partner
She won't be like the one before
Now it's sexy boom so..
Actually...
I'm thinking to perform a man & woman comedy with her
We're ready to perform and she's here
Is she OK?
Yes!
This time I'm confident
Are you sure? Well if you decided then go ahead
Yes
Are you ready? She's here
She's here?
I'll call her
OK, let's take a look everyone
Thank you, please do
Sa-cchan!
Sa-cchan?
Sa-cchan! Sa-cchan Sa-cchan...
Sa-cchan, this is my boss, Hamada-san, you know him right?
Is that you?
I'm Tanaka Ohyan Sachiko
She is mixed race
Is she?
How old are you?
20...
32?
What do you do?
Do you work?
Well..I used to work in fashion industry
And decided to change you career?
Where did you meet?
Eh..well...on Sadogashima Island
We met
Really?
Well, in this type of business, we worry
about boyfriends. Do you have one?
Do you?
You?
From that night at Sadogashima Island
I'm sorry
You have a wife right?
Yes
Well, whatever
Is it OK if we show you our performance?
Yeah
Sa-cchan lets start
Thank you
Get ready
OK then, presented by Koji and Sachiko
please look at our happy breast performance
Here.. Here.. Here are Sa-cchan's big breasts ♪
Bend like this... and this..
I'm a ghost.. I have a grudge..
What are you doing?
Here... Here.. Here are Sa-cchan's big breasts ♪
Bend like this... and this
Telescope
What are you doing?
Here... Here... Here are Sa-cchan's big breasts ♪
Bend like this..
Mikako Kotani (Synchronized swimmer)
Here... Here... Here... Here..
What the hell are you doing?!
Here are Sa-cchan's big breasts ♪
You are on stage
Hide one... Hide one...
Hey
What are you doing while you are performing
The pitcher threw a ball... and Sa-cchan hit the ball!
Ouch!
Home-run! You did it!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING!?
HEY WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
Stop it already
Who do you think you are?
She didn't even speak
Um... but...
This is not a talk performance
Are you stupid?
Why are you wiping your boobs?
It's coming out..
Hey!
No way!
No way! This is not a talk performance
Eh?!
Old hag
Old hag! You're no good
Stop doing other stuff like wiping while you are performing
What are you doing?
Sa-cchan's nipple!
Hey... wait!
Where's Sa-cchan's nipple? Look for it!
Please look for it...
Wow, found it!
We found it, Saa-chan!
We have to go to the hospital!
Sa-cchan!