The Future Century
Squadron: The Five Rangai!
You know, I haven't got it yet.
- What?
My period. Already a week late.
- Don't tell me it's that jerk.
Don't even think about it.
- I really don't know what to do.
There's not such thing as a happy
life of a single mother.
Yes.
Good evening.
Ryoko-chan, glad to see you again.
We were talking something important.
- Shut up. I need to talk to her.
Ryoko-chan, do you... ouch!
- He's calling you.
Ryoko-chan, do you wanna take a sale?
You don't have tendency
to get seasick, do you?
I said he's calling!
- I know!
It's a deal then. But I must tell you
the ship rock very hard.
It's a date, alright?
- I said he's knocking for you!
Help! Heeeelp!
Stop!
I'm fighting back in tears!
Red Rangai!
Oh, he's gone!
Blue Rangai!
I will go into morning!
Yellow Rangai!
So sad!
Green Rangai!
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
Ladies, run.
Bring it on!
- You are the one to be blamed.
Wait. What happened?
Did he...
When?
What is... a farewell note?
My brother!
You and Pink are brothers?
He's my big brother.
Dear Dokuro-san.
I have no brains to understand
what you say.
I can't figure out what to do.
I don't know which way to go.
So,  Goodbye.
Yours. Pink Fighter.
Bring it... on.
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
What are you doing that for?
You can't make 5 Rangai without him.
Take your seat there.
It was... 4,5 days ago, his brother, Pink...
Wasn't there any of you with him?
Nobody could stop him?
He died because of... HIM!
What's this all about?
- Stop it!
He killed him.
- That's not true!
Dokuro-san aways valued him highly.
I knew he was working hard.
- They were just jealous of him!
They bullied him every night.
- Stop! That's enough!
You're having a split?
Don't listen to what he's saying.
You must be really surprised.
He's so devoted he doesn't know
what he's saying. - I understand that.
Crying and mourning for him
won't get us anywhere.
So we came here, for him.
And we found this very lively man
to put in his place.
We know 4 of us wouldn't work.
What's wrong with 4 of us?
He's so upset.
Please, just fight with us.
- What?
Please.
- No, I can't.
No. I can't hit someone
so dispirited like you guys.
Don't let yourself down so much.
What?
I didn't mean to attack.
Keep your spirit up, ok?
Are you guys alright?
I sense a lot of hostility in his eyes.
I'm sure he'll understand once
we have a talk.
I'm sorry we can't carry on.
We came here just to inform you.
We have to pick ourselves
and start again. - Right.
I promise we'll do everything to
make you satisfied next week.
Don't take it so hard, ok?
I know it's hard but,
don't let yourself down.
It's natural, though.
Take care of yourselves.
- Thank you.
See you.
- Goodbye.
The Future Century Squadron: The Five Rangai!   To be con't.