The Future Century
Squadron: The Five Rangai!
I met the manager.
- What?
The manager? I thought you guys broke up.
- We did, but...
No buts! How can you be so stupid!
- But, he said he wants to see me...
Yes.
Evening.
What's that happy face?
- Hey, don't be a scold.
Ryoko-chan, have you ever clean a angler?
- No, I've never cleaned a wrangler.
Not wrangler, angler.
- Oh, I've never cleaned it neither.
- She's little dumb.
It's pretty difficulty, but taste good.
I'll do it for you next time.
I want to see it, too.
- Why would I show you?!
Heeelp!
Stop!
Nice Boobs!
Big Boobs!
Huge Boobs!
Multiple Boobs!
Spinning Boobs!
Our powers combined!
The Five Boob!
Boob, boob, boob, boob...
- Ladies, run!
1, 2, 3, 4 boob, boob, boob, boob...
Let's bring it!
Wow, you are nuttier than I thought.
What about heroes?
I don't see any.
This, again, is not what I mean by "unite".
There's no trace of Rangai!
This is what you guys come up with by
producing yourselves?
I think, aside from his noise, we are OK.
Stop that!
1, 2, 3, 4, Boob, Boob, Boob, Boob...
Stop! You morons!
Don't spin it
You made me lose my patience.
Who's idea is this? Tell me!
It's Multiple Boobs.
I feel sorry for this, but
please let me explain...
Multiple Boobs! Are you ok?
Damn. We have to get back!
Go, Big Boobs.
Yeah, off course I'll... oh I'm Nice Boob.
What's that?
Damn.
I said don't spin it!
Green Rangai!
Where did boob thing go?
This is crazy. You're never gonna get it
if I go easy on you.
Be that as it may, please just fight us.
This thing really wore us out.
Big Boobs have a fever.
Which one?
- He is.
Now you look ill so suddenly.
Please fight us. I'm begging you.
- No!
Are you ready?
- I said 'no'!
Please. We are really desperate.
1, 2, 3, 4, boob, boob, boob, boob...
- Stop, you lunatics!
Don't you feel ashamed of yourselves?
- Why can't you just say "good job"?
Why can't you say "Kudos! Boob 5"?
- Boob 5?
Yes.
- What happened to "The Five Rangai"?
Well, it's... What happened?
- We are still 5 Rangai at heart.
You don't have to change the name.
- We brought up 5 Rangai.
In my opinion 5 Rangai are still toddlers.
We nurtured them with our milk
We are their mothers.
- Now please.
1, 2, 3, 4...
- Stop!
Get out. You've got it all wrong again.
- Why?
How can you fail to get the meaning
of "unite"? Use your brain just for once.
We don't have any money left.
How could you come up with boobs
by the word "unite"?
Take a hike!
- Ok.
Don't make me say the same
thing over and over.
Goodbye.
- Go, and think!
Just think! Don't spin it!
The Future Century Squadron: The Five Rangai!   To be con't.