Translation/Timing: eChie
Excuse me?
Oh dear..that was not even funny..
What the hell was that?
I am getting pissed.
Darn it...weather forecast does not help at all.
Nah...to tell the truth,
I am in a little hurry, but I need to go to a party.
All of a sudden, it started raining, right?
Well, I can't go to a party when I am like a wet mouse, right?
Now is not the time to be a "a tremendously
handsome guy in rain", right?
Why are you not laughing at all?
You better laugh.
Anyway, I came here to purchase an umbrella today.
Every time I buy one,
I follow 3 rules.
Well...the first rule is..
the umbrella should be well made.
Secondly..it should be light.
and..
CHEAP!!
Damn..you should know it!
What kind of a sales man are you?
Is your head price-numb or something!?
Never mind, it's not important
You understand, right?
Please hurry and get me...well.. anything.
As I have not much time.
I gotta go soon. Make it quick!
Oh..it was great...it started just like a squall.
Give me a break.
yes yes yes...that's it.
Like this...and this...
Don tah-tah-tah don tah-tah-tah
Birds...birds.. birds...♪
Tancho-zuru is...♪
That's why Yako and Miku also are..
Even Nanko-san.
Hey Nanko-san!!
What the hell is that?
Who the hell..
Don't make me do such a stupid thing!
Why an axe!? That's wrong, right!?
Didn't I tell you what I came here for?
Please...
No wonder that you..eh..
your SM queen got tired of you.
Stand up...come on!
Get up!
I am telling you I have no time! Hurry!
I need to go to a party.
I don't care if you lay down like that!
Well...what you call it...you know..
Your recommendation is fine.
Your recommendation.
Even from this shelf is fine!
What?
Bring one soon!
Really..is he sane?
He is pissing me off.
I am all alone..playing with shadows..Chan(Daddy) is..
not coming back yet...Chan...Chan...
Chan-to (Properly) do it!
Chan-to do it!!
You made me embarrassed by this stupid performance.
Stupid stupid and stupid.
As if it was a squall of stupids!
That's enough. This is not even a product.
You just took it from wherever. Did you think I didn't know?
This is wrong! Should be easier to put up.
Good umbrella is easy to put up.
Just bring me ONE!!
Hurry up!
I am not crying because I am sad..
I am rather happy..
Honey..Toshihiko-san did..
He called me Mother for the first time.
Toshihiko-san...Who the HELL IS IT!?
Who is Toshihiko-san?!
Da-da-da-dan Da-da-da-dan!
Entry number 1 Toshihiko-san!
You play Toshihiko-san! Why are you introducing?!
If both of us play moderator, there will be no Toshihiko-san!
You can understand, right?!
Give me a break..
Wrong...wrong...totally wrong!
How can I explain to you..
That's not it...you know?
Well...yes that's it..
Well, Umbrella is good when it's raining,
but it's a bother when sunny.
So I want something compact..
Kasa (Umbrella) is kind of Kasabaru (a hassle
to carry), Kasa is Kasabaru, isn't it?
I bet he is laughing his ass off.
Let me check out his face..
Bring me a folding umbrella!
HURRY UP!!
Folding umbrella!
Cut it out..I am pissed!
You can't sleep on the folded tatami mat ♪
That's why you can't relieve your tired body ♪
It's outtake!
This is not making any sense!
Can you just put it away?
If you didn't, we can't retake!
Nonsense!
Put it away, hurry!
We don't need that. Put it away.
Why can't you understand? Cut it out!
I am not here to play with you!
Right? You are just fooling around.
I really don't have time. Oh, well...please get me that.
The one..you can open with one touch of a button,
when you are carrying baggage.
Right? The one you can just open with one finger.
Hurry up and bring that for me.
YOU HURRY UP!
I'm gotta kill you if you don't rush.
What's wrong?!
Really..
Making me pissed.
Yes yes yes. That is it.
All you have to do is to click on the button!
Aren't I beautiful and sparkling?
I am an attractive woman.
Corner corner at the corner!
Loosen and tighten! Loosen and tighten!
Which is that!
YOU STUPID!
Go to the hell!