Uncle Lizard
Where is he gone...?
Uncle!
Hey!
Sorry about being late
This! Eat!
What's this?
A croquette
Eat!
Are you hungry?
...not so much
Here
Thanks
Don't you have a sauce?
I forgot it
Never mind
All right?
Sorry
Some pour a worcester sauce
Others pour a soy sauce
I like both
I see
You said?
In fact
I didn't say yet
The other day, I got mammy to buy a dog
So
I thought about it later
If I had not told, it's rather good
What does it mean?
Your mother...she won't understand
About what?
If you ask her to have this kind of guy
You?
It's not a problem
It's me who want to have
My child
Sorry, I called you my child
Never mind
After all
When you said that you bought a dog etc.
"It's like as I expected"
You mean, what?
It was disappointing or rather
"This child..."
"too"
Because it's
Well, well
It's mummy
Listen
Since you told that you had a dog
so couldn't have me
"So it's like that for you"
I don't understand
"If you see me as a uncle of a lizard?"
You see me as a lizard
So you have such a idea
That's not!
Probably, you're right
What I want to say,
How can I tell you...
If you think like that,
it'll be impossible
We can't be together
I don't think so
But, you know
You will lose interest
In what? Uncle?
Why!?
At first, you're curious
"Uncle Lizard"
After the summer vacation, you go to school
"There is a uncle lizard at my house!"
Up until now, no problem!
I can picture it
An ant...
I can picture
I'll be pleased
If I find an uncle lizard at my house
Isn't it?
I understand you!
Even uncle understand it
So, I've told you!
But it's only for 1 or 2 days
It's wrong!
You don't want?
To tell the truth,
I think that...
It's the last chance
What's the last chance?
I'd like to become stable and lead a good life
If so, just come at my house!
The problem,
it's how your mother will think of it
None of her business
And!
Me...I don't have a daddy
How the matter concern me?
So I look upon you
Tell me!
What are you waiting?
It's so strange...
Like I expect that you say something
In fact, I already know it vaguely
A little embarrassing
So I look upon you as...
daddy...
Daddy...
It's strange that I say it, but
If we start living together, I'll be so
It's a little awkward that I sell myself
But anyway, daddy
Nice daddy...
I'll be so, fortunately or unfortunately
Oh, yes?
So, it's good!
Yes, but...
It will not go well
No!
I will ask again to mummy
I'll say it!
I'm anxious about one thing
How should I think that
You don't have a daddy?
I doubt it
What does it mean?
After all
It's not good to tell it to you
What? Tell me!
What?
You step on my foot
I'll say something like this!
I'll say when I notice
I have a side like this
Yes
It's not good to say it in front of a child
But it's better to clarify
I say all to you
Uncle say it
You know
Uncle
Will be on intimate terms with your mummy
I don't understand
What means the intimate terms
If you'll be her friend, it's nice
That's not
You know, in brief
For a  long time, I'm not a man
It's bad, I explain badly
Uncle doesn't fulfill his function
Recently
But if I see your mummy, "with her..."
It can happen
Ok, I say it!
You didn't understand
A sexual desire
Sexual desire?
I have a strong sexual desire
You can make friends  with my mummy
Yes, I can
So, that's good
I say it, really
Perfectly
You can
Don't say to others
I am...
Dirty pig