SECRET TALK
My lord
- mh?
I want thou to accept
This offering
Oh well
I never thought you'd be
So interesting!
Shit, I've been found out
Guess I'll just have to end
em both with my katan--
Ah! I forgot my katana
Who art thou?!
I'm an ally
Liar!
Thou art suspicious...
I'm not
But you just said you'll end us---
- Oh no, not at all
I'm actually a fan of yours
A fan?!
So, thou claim not to be suspicious
Yes
Art thou an ally?
- I am!
Then flip 3 times and go woof
Woof!
We can't trust thou yet
Whaaat? Why?
Do the Dog Policeman song
Stray kitten, stray kitten I can see you! ♪
I'm still not sure though
Do Saijo Hideki
It's frustrating, I know ♪
Woooooooow ♪
You want to be spared that badly?
- Yes...