Translations: Zurui
Laying Eggs
Koji-san
- Yes?
Flying to Macau is so fun
Yeah
It will be so much fun with lots of things to do!
Really?
Oh no!
What's wrong Yuuko-chan?
I forgot my passport
As soon as we mention it,
Happening!
- Happening!
By the way Yuuko-chan, take a look
Huh?
The window frame
The window frame?
It's gray
Yes, it really is
Good gray, huh... Especially the top left
Over here?
Yes
Shall we touch there together?
Yes..
Here we go
Koji-san
OK, right?
I really like you
Koji-san! Look!
What happened?
Is this...?
Fish man
But, it's OK Yuuko-chan
Huh?
Fish man is outside
Let's continue
But people are watching...
They don't care
Koji-san!
How is it, Yuuko-chan?
Koji-san
Even though were in a place like this
Koji-san!
What's wrong?
Look!
You stupid!
What are you trying to do!
Yuuko-chan, let's go!
OK!
Hey!
Fish man!
What the hell are you doing?
Give me a break!
"Let me give birth"
I don't care!
What are you doing to my Yuuko-chan!
Hey
You bastard!
Damn it
Die!
I did it, Yuuko-chan!
I did it!!
I killed Fish man!