OPERATION
Scalpel
- Here
Forceps
I had enough
Come on, that's enough
But--
Geez
But you can't
- I had enough
It's taking so long!
But--
But it takes time!
I thought it would be
like, 20 or 30 minutes
But this and that and this...
I'm going now!
You can't
No, I'm going
We're not done yet
But I'm fine, really
I'm going now
I can't let you
Huh?
I still have to---
I said I'm ok
Can you bring me a mirror?
Is this..?
Oh, that's my bag
And here's the mirror
Alright, I can go
- No, you can't!
It's ok
- No, it's not!
I told you I can
It's no ok!
But I have a date today
No way
We're going to Disneyland
to ride jet coasters
You can't ride that!
I told you it's ok, I'm going
You should not--
Don't worry I have this mousse,
I'll be decent enough
Please don't do that!!
It's full of germs!
I told you guys it's fine, geez
Also I think I need... a hat, maybe?
Is it sunny outside?
Yes it's clear weather
You shouldn't do that!
Wait a second, maybe this...
Oh, good! I can go
No you can't, of course you can't!
Sorry but I'm good!
Thanks a bunch!
Wait! Where are you going?!