GAKIFILES SUBS
www.gakifiles.blogspot.com
Facebook: GakiFiles Subs
VIOLENT CLASSROOM
And then... he asked me to forgive him
because he has to lick my shoe.
Hey idiot!
When I do this, you need to give me a cigarette!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
What you doing?
Light!
Give me a light!
Do you really have balls?
The bell saved your life, huh.
what are you doing?
- Sorry!
Good morning everyone.
Before starting class, I have some
information to tell everyone.
Your chronic hemorrhoid got worse?
Yeah that's right, so what.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I have your new friend here.
Transferring from another school,
Hamada Masatoshi-kun.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Hamada.
What's with this guy, looks like he doesn't have any balls!
Hamada-kun if you need any information
ask Shinohara, he is the class president.
Take an empty seat.
What the hell are you doing?
You're pretty brave, huh?
Boss give him a slap!
He has a little small mole right here.
Come here.
Stop it! Stop it you two!
Get over there!
- Yes.
Look at this.
You guys don't interfere with this fight.
Yes boss!
This is how you...
...fight.
Boss!
Wait...
Wait a minute!
Why do you have a winner's face?
Boss!
Wait a minute!
What kind of face is that?
A one vs one fight is...
like this!
Boss! Boss!
What the hell!
You guys help...
You guys don't help me.
Yes boss!
Never mind.
Today...
because of these guys... I'll let it go... but...
Next...
What are you doing?
Boss!
He said not to help.
That was hard.