The Future Century
Squadron: The Five Rangai!
Coming.
Wait. I don't come here
to molest you today.
I come here to meet some people.
-You do?
But why in my apartment?
- Please.
It's 8:30.
They'll be here in any minute.
I'm watching TV.
- I'm sorry.
There's no way around.
I have to attack you.
Otherwise they wouldn't be here.
That's ridiculous!
-Sorry, I have no choice.
Gotcha!
Help!
Stop it!
Red Rangai!
Yellow Rangai!
Green Rangai!
Citrus Rangai!
Citrus!
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
Come on! Run now.
- Thank you.
Hey Citrus!
Yeah.
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
No, you're not.
You are so wrong.
You don't get it!
What hell is this?
-Citrus
You?
Citrus Rangai!
At least you are a Rangai.
You are not even a Rangai.
Right.
Obviously, you weren't listening to
what I said last week, were you?
What? -You heard me.
Red, Yellow, Green,
you guys are OK.
Zip up!
No problem with 3 of you.
What the hell are you doing?
You're the one who said
we need to change. Deal with it.
Who do you think
you are speaking to!
Sit your ass down.
Sit!
All I'm asking is
just doing the job!
We aren't even
near fighting stage.
But you said we shouldn't look
the same last week, right? - I did.
None of us 2 look the same this time.
-You 2 are the same!
2 Citrus!
- No, Citrus and Citrus Rangai.
Ok. Let's forget the fact 2 of you
look like a twins for a moment.
What about the tights?
Hello? What about you?
- Shut up!
Should I wear tights too?
- No, you idiot!
Please just tell me what you want.
-You are all right, Green.
Didn't I tell you that
you shouldn't look the same?
Hey!
What you're saying
is, like...
Citrus Rangai should've
come out first and I last?
That's not what I'm saying!
I'm saying you can't look the same.
That's not what I heard. Your fault.
- Don't give me that sass!
What did I do...
You didn't get it
last week.
You were only pretending.
What? You mean...
I'm the one to be blamed?
Because you are the leader.
Oh, are you the leader?
You are Red.
- He is the leader.
So you are the leader.
Then you have to be Red.
But what about me?
No. I'm talking about...
Are you retarded?
Red is the leader.
That's the rule for this kind of show.
From my experiences,
Red is usually the leader.
And you are not, right?
- No.
So he should be Red.
Then...I should be... Citrus?
Forget Citrus.
So. You're saying
I should be Red?
Exactly.
I haven't told you this because
I don't know how you'd take it, ...
but we intended to
differentiate by our weapons.
Really?
We decided we express ourselves
by using different weapons.
That is true.
Some people seem to like that.
They do?
Why don't you show me
your weapons then?
Let's start with that. - OK.
What you got?
- I have this. A boomerang.
I like this. Not bad.
Not bad at all.
How about you?
An bow.
Why green?
- Same as the leaf.
You?
A heart.
Why green!
Why heart green!
Next!
- Red Rangai.
Green again!
This is insane!
You! Show me.
What the hell is this?
A stick.
I know what it is.
All right! We painted
all our weapons green.
Why do you have to be
such a stinger?
Who do you think
you are talking to!
Why?
No same color!
You broke...
You got something?!
I'm giving you advice.
Differentiate!
You have to think it through again,
or we'll never fight.
This is a waste of time.
I'm talking to you.
Look at me!
No Citrus.
I'm afraid
I can't do that.
This is not a suggestion.
No Citrus!
You can't fight
with this thing on.
You jerk!
Say that again?
You throw this out!
Cut it!
Enough.
Just cut it.
Have a discussion
one more time!
- Stop. You're really hurting Citrus.
The Future Century Squadron: The Five Rangai!   To be con't.