"Emergency Project: Dokkiri Camera"
Matsumoto!
Yes?
Just what shall we do?
A new style of dokkiri camera.
I see.
Today we will get Kouji Higashino.
- He isn't here now, right?
Right.
I believe he should be
here in 10 or 15 minutes.
Is that right?
- Once he gets here...
we will kill him together.
- Yes?
That's rude!
That really would be dokkiri.
Yes!
We're doing an unavoidable dokkiri.
Ah, this is unavoidable?
Unavoidable!
So everyone will help?
- Yes.
- We'll carry out the operation to the T.
- To the T?
Well, Higashino should
be here any minute.
No one gains anything from this.
Please enjoy whatever
dokkiri we are going to do.
Higashino entering CX
- Good morning!
- Konancho Chinese Restaurant...
- That place was cheap!
Umm...
That place...
...it was good food, wasn't it?
The place I went to once?
It's a good place.
Ah, I see. Where the
overhead crosswalk is, right?
Yeah. Just about anything is good idea.
- You should go with your family.
- I will.
Take your daughter. Ah, Matsumoto
is your autograph hanging there?
It's possible!
Anyway, the katayaki noodle is delicious.
Is it?
Speaking of which your head...
...is a katayaki noodle head, isn't it?
It's hot!
Hot!
Dokkiri!
Were you frightened?
Surprised?
"(The New) Dokkiri Camera"
It's not real!
You...
...you really look like katayaka noodles!
Your head!
It's not real!
None of this is real!
Dokkiri!
- He still doesn't get it!
- You don't get it?
- It's not real!
- Not real!
Not real! Not real!
Dokkiri!
Huh?
A big success!
Cameras here and here!
"Big Success"
Good morning. Thank you for this.
Higashino giving an interview
Please have a seat here.
Thank you.
I want to ask you about your
experience in "Gottsu 'A' Kanji".
It's been a month now. How is it?
Your own personal experience I mean.
What did I say before?
You said "I will be tough
and do my best" before.
- I did?
- Yes, you did.
Well, I am being tough...
And I am doing my best...
Speaking of such...
Yes?
Your head, Mr. Higashino...
...is katayaki noodles, you said, right?
...right, right.
Higashi-nori!
Hey, Higashi-nori!
"(The New) Dokkiri Camera"
Dokkiri!
Dokkiri! Look!
You still don't get it!
Surprised?
- Surprised?
- Dokkiri!
Not real!
It's not real, I said!
This is dokkiri!
Luckily it's not real, right!
It's a lie!
This fish sausage is not real too!
This fish sausage here is not real too!
Fish sausage is fish sausage, right?
Not real, it is! Surprised?!
Scared?
He... he's surprised. He's scared.
Ok, a big success!
This went great.
- So surprised.
- Very surprised.
Enough already!
Got you!
You!
When I told you it'd be funny
to do this to me again...
...didn't you say "no chance of that"?!
"Big Success"
Higashino going home by taxi
Coul you open the trunk?
Please open the trunk.
The trunk?
Please get in!
Hold on a second.
We don't need the trunk.
- Are you sure?
Yep, don't need it.
No? Ok, ok.
- Thank you.
- Of course!
The Hotel Yoko in Akasaka, please.
Ok.
Oh!
Your head look like
katayaki noodles, doesn't it?
Huh?!
Wait!
No!
Hurry!
Let's dig in!
- Is it good?
- Yeah! Very good!
- Egg! Egg!
- Egg! Yay!
I'll take this side!
Higashi-nori!
- Higashi-nori!
- Higashino!
- Over here!
- Look! Look!
Dokkiri!
- Dokkiri!
It got on his clothes!
He doesn't get it again
and he still don't get it!
- Dokkiri!
- He still doesn't get it!
Dokkiri! Dokkiri!
See? Camera!
Dokkiri Camera!
- Look! Look!
- Dokkiri Camera!
This egg is not real!
Not real! The egg here!
Dokkiri Camera! Dokkiri Camera!
He's surprised!
- This would surprise you!
- Totally surprise you!
Very surprising!
Ok! A big success!
Look at that!
Your ear is loaded up!
There's so much in your ear!
I mean... you know, this isn't dokkiri!
You guys have learned
the meaning wrong!
- Dokkiri!
This isn't dokkiri! Not dokkiri at all!
Why not?
Scary yakuza. Scared for your life.
That's dokkiri.
What the hell is this supposed to be?!
This is not dokkiri.
- Amazing!
- Not dokkiri...
It's like a facial mask!
Didn't you go home already?
You said you were gonna go play billiards!
Well, anyway...
...look at the camera, give a
peace sign and say "A big success."
You gotta be the last
one to give a peace sign!
Ok! A big success!
Peace!
"Big Success"
Higashino getting to his hotel room
he doesn't notice the camera at all.
I wonder.
He's taking a piss!
I don't wanna hear it.
Psssssss.
He can hear really well.
We're horrible.
He's getting naked!
He's wet.
Katayaki noodles.
We got the hotel staff in on it.
We just gotta give them a call.
Racing around the icy mountain streams.
He's saying, "Racing around the icy mountain streams."
Hey, let's use this when we go.
What would we say?
Look!
What the hell is he doing?
That's scary!
- Yes?
- This is the front desk.
- Sorry to bother you right now.
- That's ok.
We forgot to deliver a message
to you when you checked in.
What was it?
- Yes. Here it is.
- Ok.
Mr. Kouji Higashino's head is
like that of katayaki noodles.
No!
Wait!
This isn't dokkiri!
Higashino's words