Mitsuru-san
Subtitles: ZuRUi
We are...
basically...
ugly!
Why can't our arms follow the rhythm?
Maybe we should quit
-Stupid!
We're a dancing super idol group...
Hamigakitai!
What should we do
-Yea
Tatsuya!
What are you doing, just drinking?
Come and dance with us!
No!
I didn't want to join you guys from the beginning!
What?
-I want to be solo!
If I practice with you guys...
I'll never be popular! What's with that "We're idols" talk!
What?  Don't make fun of us, idiols!
Girls dream about us!
What the hell are you saying?!
Stopt it!
You're no idol!
Stop it, you're killing him!
I told you I don't want join you!
Stop!
I told you to stop!
T..Tatsuya...
Are you ok?
Tatsuya! Tatsuya!
Are you ok?!
He's dead!
What shall we do?
It's true!
-What can we do?!
He's dead
Mitsuru-san!
What did you do?!
Actually...
I...
I hit Tatsuya on the head with this ashtray and killed him...
You shouldn't be doing these stupid things!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, but Tatsuya...
Go and close the window
Check and see if anyone is around
It's clear!
Tatsuya! He's dancing!
Idiot!