Subtitles: Zurui
Miracle Ace
[He suddenly appears out of nowhere to help little kids, it's Miracle Ace]
[Right now, Masao-kun is in trouble!]
[Please come and help! Masked Miracle Ace]
Stop it! Let me go!
Stop!
Miracle Ace!
That was close, huh?
Thank you!
Yes
What is your name?
I'm Misao
Masao?
Yes
How do you write it?
Like this...
Mister, you're strong!
Not really
Mister, you have a lot of equipment, huh
Yea
What is this?
It's not anything special
It's my cigarette case
Tiring...
It's done
Mister, you look really strong to me!
Really?
Mister, is your whole family strong?
My dad... isn't strong
Well, my dad is retired
My older brother is also weak
Really?
Hmmm, my older brother...
well...
he was into track and running
My brother works at the credit union
What?
Toyonaka shinyokinko (Toyonaka Credit Union)
He works there?
Yes
Mister, don't you do any sports?
Not, not really
Mister, I have a favor to ask
When I get bullied...
next time something happens
can you come?
If I'm off that day, I won't come
I work as a waiter in a coffee shop
So if I go there, I can see you?
Yes, well...
Mon, Wed, Fridays I work the early shift
Friday I work all day
Can you give me directions?
Yes, I'll write it down for you later
Really?
Yes
Ok... p..please
Definitely help me
Sure, no problem
Mister, what star did you come from?
I can't tell you that
I can't say
So it's Miracle Ace!
He has a lot of secrets!
To be continued