Translation/Timing: eChie
Excuse me? Sorry to bother you..
Oh dear I am no good, really...
I doubt I am so poor in health.
I haven't been feeling very well.
Well, please listen.. today in fact,
I need to go to a party.
I'm afraid I probably have caught a cold.
And then, you know,
I am ok if I am sick by myself, but..
I shouldn't spread my cold to everybody at the party, right?
If you ask me if it is OK or not,
the answer is definitely not, right?
I really would like to avoid that.
So, what I would like to ask you today is,
What does Doctor do?
Well, in other words, what can you offer me to trust you?
I would say,
Lots of experience,
extraordinary specialized knowledge, and then
some caring and compassion!
You understand it, right? I am here for that!
I am counting on you, OK? You are a doctor, so
please don't disappoint (Gakkari) you patient, OK?
Gakkari, Gakkai (Academic conference) ...
I meant Medical conference.. it should
be understandable enough.
He must be laughing his ass off, so let me check..
Wow, he is thinking about girls!
Wrong. What are you doing! That is wrong!
Give me a break, OK?
I am feeling a chill, I need to do something about this...
All right, please make it quick as I need to go to a party!
Oh dear, in this cold season we tend to fall sick..
Yes yes yes, that's it.
Yes like this and that, and hold this, then..
Don tah-tah-tah, don tah-tah-tah...
Deden-de-den, Deden-de-dede-dedede...
Namamugi-namagome-namatamago
(Japanese  tongue twister)
Nonsense!
I didn't know what I was doing, I didn't even meant do this.
YOU STUPID!
I didn't want to wear such a jacket
at all even if I said I had a chill.
That's wrong. Come on! I don't have much time.
Don't fool me.
I am not here to get the stupid jacket.
How can I say..well you are wrong.
A regular doctor would use.. what you call it..a stethoscope.
You don't even have a stethoscope. That is strange.
Like a regular doctor..please check me with the stethoscope.
I am checking on you, so please check on me, please!
Hurry up and bring your stethoscope. No time!
Well, he is crazy or something..what is he thinking?
Oh, he's back.
Yes yes yes, I hold this and wear this, then...
Alright, alright, alright...
Choshinki (Stethoscope), Choshinki, Jyonan-denki.
"He is pretending to be a president of Jyonan-denki (Jyonan
electronic) who was popular on TV shows in the past".
Totally different. Choshinki and Jyonan-denki
are totally different.
How much does it cost for me to perform like this?
Give me a break! Choshinki and Jyonan-denki
are not even close!
Too awful..you better cut it out already..
Don't get carried away (Choshi-ni-noru)
about Choshinki..Choshinki...
He must be laughing his ass off. Definitely. Let me see.
Yes, he is.
I know you loved my joke. Well, you should end this really.
I am getting pissed, this is not OK.
We had enough for choshinki.
What should I do? Ok, let me explain how I got sick like this.
OK.
Well, it was about 2 weeks ago.
At first, I felt something wrong with my throat.
But I was not taking it seriously and I just had some troches,
But then, my nose started running and my nose..
What are you doing?
Why are you just listening to me?
A regular doctor would be writing down something.
We are not a working youth and a grandma. This
conversation wouldn't help my sickness.
A regular doctor would write down the
process in German or something.
WRITE IT DOWN!
Don't you have a chart? Bring it now!
HURRY UP!! GO!!
What kind of doctor is he? Pissing me off!
Bring a chart!
Yes yes yes, that's it. Like this...and that...
Well...it's been 3 years...since I went into the mountains
alone after I was defeated by Onitsuka..
I won in the spring tournament, and lost in
the winter tournament. If I don't win the next
tournament, it means I lost everything.
Anyway..How can I overcome Onitsuka's
rokkaku-chop? How can I?
Da-da-da-dan Da-da-da-dan
When you beat him up
Nonsense!
Why are you writing down on the chart?
You wrote nothing.
Give me a break! End it!
No wonder your *** and *** got in trouble!
SHUT UP! I don't care if you just met them!
I don't care!
It's your fault! I don't care!
My parents just called me the other day!
Shut up!
No seriously...
That's enough! You are pissing me off!
Alright then...you sit down here! I had enough of this already.
*Roentgen = X-Ray
Let me have a roentgen.. roentgen. Get ready!
I will take it to another doctor, so hurry up!
I really come to the wrong hospital.
This roentgen brings me back my
memories! I used to love it..but..
This is more like Dento-gei (Traditional play).
1,2,3,4
Roentgen Roentgen ♪
Dento-gei Dento-gei ♪
Not even close ♪ To be honest ♪
Bomb A head ♪ Bomb A Head ♪
OK!
Please do not use this, I am very sorry..