Snow Freesia
TRANSLATION BY: SHION
TYPESET & QC BY: KEDOMAS
Good morning, folks
Good morning
- Right now it's 8:30 in Japan
And today, you're gathered here
for the Snow Freesia, as you know
What do you think?
How's this winter?
Let me know what you think, Imada
It snowed...
- Wet snow, mostly, huh?
- That's right
- Snowy days like this are the best
It was a quote from uh...
the late Ii Naosuke
Anyway
Our Snow Freesia it's not just a freezer,
it's a workout machine
For your abs, you knew that?
Just keep that in mind
and you'll forget about your usual freezer
I thought it sounded strange too,
when I first heard it
And now I've had one for over 5 years
You know?
Interesting
- It happens, you know?
Is that so?
- So...
Knoooot!
Here
See? Foxes are interested in this too
They always follow me around
No matter where I am
See?
Ok, let's start from Imada
Let's go
What do you think?
What do you think, Imada?
- Well...
So, how do you wanna open it?
Tell me
Well...
Well, slowly I guess
- Slowly, and...?
So I won't flip it over
- Flip it over and?
That's it
- That's it? Good
Alright
Now, go and make a copy of this
What the...
There's a copy machine inside
Has this anything to do
with the Snow Freesia?
Cm'here, you
Ouch!
What are you doing?!
What the hell?
- What's your problem?
Expect this frequently
If you're here to make stupid jokes,
go home then
I'm sorry
You know damn well
my son died because of this
That's why, now...
Sorry for that, ok?
You reminded me of him
I see...
You look a bit like my son
Is that so?
- I'll write "I look like his son" on your face
You know that?
"I look like"...
"Like his son"
- Are you actually writing it?
See?
Alright then, who's going first?
Can we get inside it?
Of course you can
- Oh, I see
Alright, I'm going first
Very well, we'll start from Imada
You're Imada, right?
- That's me
Alright then, here's the Snow Freesia
- Yeah
And we have 5 balls here
I see... do I have to pick one?
- That's right
Let's see... number 3
- 3? No way, you can't pick that one
This is your first time, right?
- That's right
Let's start with this one, then
- Ok
Here, this is number 1
- Alright
Alright, give it a try
- Do I have to stick my fingers in it?
Trooot!
Alright, let's start
- Yes, please
Get on top
Open the "entration mistion"
at the bottom
- "Entration"?
Yep, open it
Isn't this where you put the veggies?
The hell are you talking about?
- I'm sorry
Why would you put veggies in there?
Well, it looks like...
My son used to say the same,
and now he's dead
You knew that?
- I'm sorry
Alright, so...
Open it up
Nice, now get in
Take a good look, ok?
We're getting through this
Sure
How is it going?
- Well...
Put the "wired tarp" on, please
"Wired tarp"?
The tarp
- Ah! This one
How should I put it?
- Anywhere is fine
Like this
- Ok
Are you ready?
If you open this upper window here
- Yes?
The engine will start to move
- Got it
And that's when you'll start, ok?
- Got it!
Don't joke around
- Yes
Let's go!
Open it up good
- Sure
Alright
Let's go
Ok, ok
See?
It was fun, wasn't it?
Was it?
Y-Yeah...
- It's a blast, right?
I mean... I thought I was going to
slide down a snowy mountain or such...
What was that?
- That's it...
I mean, it did move...
- And?
But it was just that, in the end
"Just that" what?
- I mean, it barely moved
That's what it is
- I see...
It's always been like this,
it's the fixed edition
You know?
What?
I mean, I wanted to experience
the Snow Freesia, I even paid for it
What the...
Show me how it's done
- Do I have to?
That's what you told me, right?
The hell are you talking about?
I've paid for this, you know...
Mr. Noda? Was that it?
Who's that? Are you kidding me?
Huh?
The hell are you sayin'?
You sorta look like him
Calm down, man
But I've paid for it
- Let it go
Screw this
Let's just go
TRANSLATION BY: SHION
TYPESET & QC BY: KEDOMAS