http://zurui.blogspot.com
Translations: eChie
Excuse me?
I'm sorry
Oh, my gosh...
Well..in fact...
I need to go to a party today
I'm in such a trouble
Well
What to say..
I'm not sure this is because of changing seasons
or because of myself
Well..it seems I have caught a cold
This is such a trouble, but
I don't have much time because I need to go to a party
I doubt taking medicine will instantly make me better, but..
better than nothing, right?
This is a real phamacy (*mashi = better than nothing)
Well..something like that happened and..
I am in such a trouble
Hey..Are you listening to me?
What is bad is that
I have the big 3 symptoms of catching cold
Did you get it? What I'm trying to say is..
what the big 3 symptoms of catching cold is
Well... Let's say..
Annoying headache,
Sore throat and..
Looming Chills!
Hurry up!
You are a professional, right!
Hurry up, don't be just listening
You understand it right?
I want to fix my cold to go to a party
I'm in hurry, I don't want to go with this feeling
Yes yes yes
I'm counting on you.
I'm putting myself at ease, so hurry up
Well..This is terrible really..
I'm getting tired
Yes yes yes..That's it
Wear like this..and this
hold this and OK,
Dan-dah-dah-dah...♪
Dah-la-la-la..♪
Got you do, repay me!
Why do I have to be asking you for money back!
What are you making me do?
I said I'm sick! I don't want to move!
I don't want to waste my energy!
What are you thinking?
No wonder somebody wrote "die" on your car bonnet!
Moron!
Hurry up! It didn't make sense at all!
Hurry up!
That's enough
I want to remove my headache..You are making it worse!
You have Bufferin (pain killer), right?
Don't you know Bufferin? Bring
it to me. It works pretty well
Hurry up, moron!
What is he thinking?
I'm getting so tired..
Give me a break!
Yes yes That's a tambourine
Am I beautiful? Fu-fu ♪
Corner corner at the corner! Fu-fu ♪
Anybody stop me!
What are you thinking?
Shut up, moron!
Moron!
It reminds me of my old days!
Da-da-da-da ♪
You can't even do it!
You moron! That's it! Put it away!
That's wrong
You don't seem to understand
Never mind
Ok then
I want to stop my running nose
Please do something about it
You can do that right? Hurry up OK?
I don't have time!
With someone you love...♪
This is someones else's performance!
Why are you looking at me like I'm part of
the audience who applied for the show?
Like "wow, this is how Katsura'san's show is!"
Still got some
That's wrong
That is enough already
Damn you!
DO SOMETHING ABOUT THE CHILLS!
I WANT TO WARM MY BODY, MORON!
Yes yes yes hold these
Raise the red, and do not raise white...♪
Red white red white...♪
Turning around and
Fu-fu-fu ♪
EVEN MORE COLD!
Very cold and plus I got butt cramps!
That's it, Moron!
Die!