Translation: eChie
Under the Stars
Ryoko, here you are.  You'll catch a cold.
What are you doing?
Looking at the stars.
Stars?
I made a promise to my boyfriend.
That every night at this exact time,
we would look at the stars.
It doesn't matter how long we are apart.
We'll be looking at the same stars.
That's what he said.
How romantic.
But tonight, that star isn't here.
Huh?
OK, everyone.  Did you hear?
Yeah.
This is for her and her boyfriend.
We shouldn't fall no matter what! OK!?
Hey you!
I can't hang on, my hands area in the wrong position.
Hey wait, I can't, I can't.
I can't.
I'm shooting.
Come here.
I won't fall!
Wait, wait!
I give up, I give up!
I'm scared, I'm scared!
I'm scared!
It's scary!
Switch to a commercial, hurry!
I can't!
I'm serious!
Hey!