Translations: Zurui
Laying Eggs
It's fun, huh Yuuko-chan?
Yes it is!
Yeah
Look Yuuko-chan, he's a famous steamed bun maker
It's a steamed bun shop
Yes
Yuuko-chan look at the steamed buns
Soft and white
Warm
Just like us
Stop Koji-san!
Shall we touch it?
Yes
Here we go
I love you
Koji-san!
OK, right?
Not here!
It's fine
They know we are in love
Hey! Hey you!
What?
It's you
Fish man!
He's alive!
Hey! You didn't die?
Let me give birth
You're still saying that?
Give me child support payments
What?
Give you?
What the hell are you saying?
You know what, I'm here with Yuuko-chan
in Macau to have fun, don't bother us!
That's right!
That's right, just leave!
You said that you are here in Macau today to have
fun with Yuuko-chan and not to bother you
Huh?
It wont be a fun trip!
I said this trip is not going to be fun
Hey! You're teasing me!
What?
I...
Sign here
Why should I sign anything?
Pull this
What is that?
Pull it out!
Pull it out?
Out of all of these children, I'm going to raise just one
Why are you thinking so negative
Stupid! It has nothing to do with me
These
Hey! Stop!
You know what, you're bothering us!
That's right!
Listen to these children's message!
Close your eyes and listen to these children's message!
Ok, I'll listen..just close my eyes, right?
Hi! I'm Goku!
What are you saying?
You're a Fish man! Fish man!
Not Goku!
You are really...
You should just die
Right?
- Yes!
Don't show me the cross!
You fell for our trick
Yuuko-chan
Oh, where did I put it? I just had it earlier
Hey Fish man!
Take this!
You lied, huh?
Right?
You lied, right?
You said a cross.. but
He's so annoying
Why are you playing tricks!
Don't show me a flashing light!
He's definitely lying
But, Koji-san, look at his guilty face
It could be real this time
Yes
Act like we're going to take a picture
Camera
Flash
This is it
Thank goodness, Koji-san!
This is good!
Hey, Fish man!
Take this
Koji-san
Let's go
OK, let's go
Give me a copy of the photos!