The Future Century
Squadron: The Five Rangai!
You know, the manager said...
he wants to break up with me.
Tha selfish jerk!
I can't stand that ass-hole.
- I understand.
Hey.
Ryoko-chan, do you want me
to give you a shampoo?
Why shampoo?
- Because I'm good at it!
Maybe I'll ley you do it then.
- Don't, Ryoko.
Shut up! It's none of your business.
Come to Aoyama, 3:00, ok? - Don't.
Heeelp!
- Take this!
Stop!
Blue Rangai!
Green Rangai!
Ladies, run, now!
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
Bring it on!
- 5 Rangai will take you on!
Wait. You're too short for 5 Rangai!
Save your breath. Come on!
Let's not go into it now.
But there're only 2 of you!
What happened?
Let's not go into details.
- Don't talk about number.
Wait!
We pull evils of this world!
We pull evils by force of justice!
We are.
After School Electromagnetic Wave Club!
(from another sketch)
Let's have it out, Dokuro-san.
- Let's fight, now!
Stop it, you morons!
We pull evils!
Why are you divided into 2 groups?
You have no business here. Get out!
- Go away.
Before you boot them, look closely
at these guys who have been with you.
Don't you feel anything?
Turn around!
I'm ashamed.
- You'd been with these guys.
I'm disgusted with them. -Hey!
We are doing this in real earnest!
Bring it! Are you ready, South Pole?
- You bet, North Pole.
Fight us, Dokuro-san, fight!
- Stop!
Don't crouch! You're showing it!
Let me explain, please.
- I said don't crouch!
Hey, get a grip!
- We decided we'll try really hard.
But he said he can't forget his brother
and wants to make a new team.
Why did you betrayed us
and joined him?
Because he said he can't make it
by himself alone and he needs me.
And I was tempted by his costume.
Yeah, you always liked exposure.
- Dokuro-san, fight us, not them.
No, fight us. - Wait. You guys had
been in this together till last week.
Why don't you unite as a team?
Then you should come back
to 5 Rangai. - No! No!
You should join us. - No! Hell no!
What Poles can we be?
There couldn't be another Pole.
- They're right, North Pole.
We can find a way if we try.
Listen to me. Unite as 5 Rangai!
I can't. Not with these guys.
- Let me handle this!
Pink Rangai!
What? - Why?
- Don't crouch!
Oh, brother!
- You guys are just naked!
As naked as jaybird!
I thought you are dead.
-  There's a reason for this.
Tell him, Blue.
- That's about 1,2 months ago...
Every week he came here
to get scolded by Dokuro-san.
So we had meetings every week to
discuss what we should do about him.
But they always make excuses, with cold
and part time job. Once there were only 2.
We thought if we go on like this, we'll
fall apart. So he... - I staged this.
So this is your idea.
- Is that true? - Yes.
This is a good opportunity for you
to get together as 5 Rangai again.
Why don't you take this opportunity?
- That's not good!
Why, South Pole? What's troubling you?
- Too late for that.
But what other option do we have?
- Just stick to... it.
To what?
- Electromagnetic Wave Club.
What about all the trouble I had?
I can't fight with you guys
if you're like this now.
All of you got to be in for 5 Rangai.
You got to unite!
I understand. We'll discuss about
how we should start over.
So, please fight Magnectic Wave Club
just for today. - No!
We pull evils!
- Just bring it!
I don't like to fight and watch out for
it not showing at the same time.
Don't worry about that.
- We just cut all corners.
No way I'm gonna fight
with naked guys.
Look, it's good thing he's back.
- Yes.
You should unite as a team.
Start all over again as 5 Rangai.
We'll think about whether we join them
or they join us. - That's your choice.
Sorry, about all this. - Let's fight
next week. Full 5 Rangai vs me.
Sorry about the vulgarity.
- Don't crouch! Hold yourself erect!
Can I go first?
- You are just in the raw!
Goodbye.
- Bye. We'll do it right next time.
Don't forget to unite!
- We won't.
The Future Century Squadron: The Five Rangai!   To be con't.