The Future Century
Squadron: The Five Rangai!
I can't believe the weekend's almost over.
I hate Sunday night. - I hate too.
Maybe I should quit working and
marry someone. - Yeah, that's good idea.
Yes?
- Good evening.
Sorry to bother you again,
but I have to meet people here.
Why does it aways have to be here?
- Because I don't know anywhere else.
Your friend? Hi! What's your name?
- Ryoko.
Ryoko-chan, how old are you?
- 21.
21! You're very young.
- Please stop.
Do you have boyfriend?
- Dokuro-san, he's calling you!
Can we go out? Ouch!
- Dokuro-san, It's for you.
Why do you have to slap my face?
- Dokuro-san, there, he's knocking.
Eat this!
-Ahhh! Heeelp!
Stop!
Red Rangai!
Blue Rangai!
Pink Rangai!
Tiger Mask!
Fuji Land! (amusement park)
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
Ladies run! Now!
- Thank you.
Sit your ass down! Sit! Sit, sit!
You won't get away with this! Not today!
Sit!
Let's just take a good look at you!
Ony by one!
You, who are you supposed to be?
- Blue Rangai!
This is not blue!
Does this look blue to you!?
That's blue and that's blue ant this is...
You! - Red Rangai!
- Why  are you wearing sleeveless top?
Tell me. - This is... more... hip.
Dumb ass.
Hey! - Yes.
What do you think you are? - Pink Rangai!
Why are you acting like a woman?
- Pink Rangai!
You, you don't even come closer.
You are simply out of question.
Let me... - You better find another job.
- Please let me explain.
I may appear to be Tiger Mask.
But I'm Yellow Rangai at heart.
Hey!
Mrs.
You!
This is not even a costume.
No transformation at all.
I definitely have in my mind that...
I should wear something... green.
And... - Uh-huh.
- And this was the best I could find.
I don't need it!
What the hell are you thinking?
You don't look like a hero at all!
you are just a waitress!
But I really tried...
- Don't take my rod.
I don't know what to do anymore.
You're always critical...
You are supposed to be blue.
Zip up!
You came very close this time.
- I did?
If your top isn't sleeveless.
What made you think of taking it off?
I thought this is more...
- You have to protect your skin.
Don't even think about it.
Longer sleeves doesn't improve nothing.
I said I don't need it!
But I really...
- Don't take this!
I'm really at loss what to do.
I can understand what these 3 of you
are trying to do.
Seriously, I think you guys
should dump him.
There has to be 5 of us.
And it's not like I'm not motivated.
I know I don't have what it takes.
I mean, I want to do some other...
You aren't making any sense.
I just don't follow you. But I assume
you have your own idea about a hero.
You have that, don't you?
That's why you're in those costumes, right?
Ok. Come back next week with costumes
tha you think a hero would wear. - Yes.
I promise I won't nag you.
You do it in your way, ok? - Fine.
Let me see what's your
notion of a hero. - Ok.
We'll do this step by step
No need to rush. - I understand.
-  Thank you very much.
You can go now.
Put these away.
We are sorry to cause you trouble.
See you guys next week. 8:30.
- Thank you. - Goodbye
I'll be waiting for you.
Take care.
- I will.
Good night !
- I'm leaving now.
The Future Century Squadron: The Five Rangai!   To be con't.