Subtitles: eChie
Hello!
Excuse me? I'm sorry but..
I got a big event today
Actually I need to go to a party
I don't have much time, but
it will be a casual home party, so
I could just go empty-handed
But, well you know,
to be honest
people around me think that...
I'm very special because I am a foreigner
I could just go empty-handed, but
I want to kind of
meet their expectations
So a small bunch of flowers would be nice
I'm in a hurry
but can you help me?
Can you get something for me? Thank you
Please hurry as I have no time
Well, today is..
Yes tes, that is it
As always
Like this..and that...
Hold this, and then
Don-tah-tah-tah Don-tah-tah-tah
Den-den-den-den Den-dende
Girls in love are
Ban-ban-ban Ban-ban
Tonight with you
Den-den-den........
Jeez, I told you to wake me up!
WHAT IS THAT!
It doesn't make any sense!
There are too many elements!
No center core in this
It was hige-dance in the beginning,
then suddenly there were lyrics
and " I told you to wake me up"
It makes no sense!
Nonsense!
What the hell
Do it right! I'm counting on you
Really..please do it right
You are always fooling me..well
Roses. Roses. Roses are good
Everybody would love roses, right?
Bring some roses
I'll take roses
Yes, roses are good
Please hurry
I'm sorry for you, but
* Bara = Roses  Bara-su = To put the chill on
It seems that I have no other choice
but putting the chill on you
as you went against us, Black tigers
It is too late to beg for your life like that
You know too much about us
You got to know too much
Da-da-da-dan Da-da-da-dan
You know too much!
SHUT UP!
Don't copy what I do!
This is my moment!
You always try to join me!
No wonder Otsuka Nene refused a kissing scene with you!
You stupid! What are you thinking?
Wrong. I said roses!
Why do I have to kill you?
Do you know what is a rose?
Rose!
The one with thorns. Thorns!
Thorns! You understand it right? Bring me some!
Thorns. The one with thorns
Hurry up. I have no time!
He's day-dreaming
Why did you do that, Master?
Master of ceramic art
Why do you say this was a mistake?
We don't understand
Master..I can't go your way any longer
Sorry, I'm going my way
Isn't it wrong
Let's do it right
I came to buy flowers
I don't care about ceramic art
I'm too tired to shout
But
The one thing..
I have to reward you for one thing...
I'm glad, what I was glad about was that...
You were still wearing the wig
That is a great work of you
Really great. If you weren't wearing the wig,
It would be too terrible to look at
This is really
Let me shake hands
You scored a point
This is your kindness
Your kindness
But
Do your business now
Bring some flowers if you are a florist, OK?
Do it right!
Show me that you are a member of society!
Am I right?
Don't fool around!
Don't even think about fooling around...
Tetsuya
WHO THE HELL IS TETSUYA!?
Who is Tetsuya?
Go, hurry!
OK?
Well...never mind
Let's see..what would you know
Something gorgeous and eye-catching, OK?
Are you OK? Alright then
Please hurry
Run! OK?
Make it quick
Damn, I told him I have no time!
Oh boy
What can I do about this?
* They are imitating "Waratte Iitomo"
Being introduced by Hisako Manda
Today's guest is this person, please come in!
Who the hell is it!
It doesn't make any sense!
Do your job, stupid!
I will never ever come again!
Stupid!
Die!