The Future Century
Squadron: The Five Rangai!
By the way, we broke up.
- You did? Good for you.
Yes!
Hey, evening.
Ryoko-chan, do you like low
frequency therapy equipment?
I mean, do you have stiff shoulders?
- Yes I have sometimes.
It's very good for stiff shoulders.
- You don't have stiff shoulders!
I'll give you if you want it.
- Thank you
Ok, I'll bring it next week.
You noisome bitch!
Heeelp!
Stop!
Red Rangai!
Red Rangai Model!
Red Rangai
who has a face in the belly!
Deflowered Red Rangai!
Red Rangai Eater!
Our powers combined!
The Five Rangai!
Ladies, run!
- Thank you.
Hey.
Where are you going?
Take your position.
You are not on this side!
I realized I should rather
be on your side.
No. Go away!
You're not a Rangai! Absolutely not!
Well... - Only you!
That's why I thought
I should be on your side.
This is not what I meant
by "unite".
Our team concept this time is to
offer various kind of Red Rangai.
He's the only one who got it right.
Look how much you've improved
since last week!
I even feel a little hot.
I can call 3 of you Red Rangai.
But not you!
Red Rangai Eater!
That's my point.
This is Red Rangai down here.
And you are not!
Go away!
You guys have got it all wrong.
How can you fight?
Do ku ro.
You don't think
you have a problem, do you?
I think I'm going to get more
fan mail than anyone here.
You! Are you obsessed with
Rangai having sexual aspect?
He's just dirty by nature.
Always bare feet.
I was definitely feeling his skimpy
costumes these days are intolerable.
I'm doing my best. - Pieman's
rating is dropping down like crazy
It's killing me.
Harder I try, lower the rating get.
You have to think it through again.
You've got it all wrong about what I said.
May I?
- Yes.
We don't think... that 5 Rangai
is the only form of heroes.
We would like to make
our own form of heroes.
I mean, we want to produce ourselves
with our own ideas. - I see.
We want to stand on our own feet.
- We like to give it a try.
Please Dokuro-san, let us do it.
Let me remind you first that
you completely blew it this time.
You don't kick me!
What's that for?
You go back to square one!
Think hard one more time! - I will.
Remember to unite as a team.
Also remember you're heroes.
Hey! I'm speaking to you,
look at me!
Goodbye.
- Don't disappoint me next time!
Can you get through?
Look at the way you move.
- You go first, you'll take it longer.
You completely blew it!
What?
Have a think!
- I will.
The Future Century Squadron: The Five Rangai!   To be con't.