Subtitles: Zurui
Mother
Is your mom still here?
She's getting ready to leave
Ok, Ma-kun, I'm going to leave
Ok
Oh! Who are...
Ma-kun who is this person?
It doesn't matter who he is!
Itao, Itao-san?
Yes
Itao-san is handsome
Just never mind!
Do you have a girlfriend Itao-kun?
Yes
Never mind!
Ma-kun can't find a girlfriend
You got nothing on Valentine's day
You're so irritating!
Hurry up and leave!
This face...
Don't touch me!
Leave!
You should be more clean, cut like Itao-kun...
right here...
DON'T TOUCH ME!!
IT'S FINE LIKE THIS!
Scary... oh scary, I'm leaving
Um... Fever!
Because I'm going to see a Kabuki play
I have Kabuki fever!
Who cares, idiot!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING??
What are you doing?
I have to change... Ahhh! Don't peek!
I'm not! Idiot!
Itao-kun isn't peeking
Change clothes somewhere else!
Just don't peek!
It's because you're peeking, it's bad!
I'm gonna kill you!
Hurry up and change!
Oh! So embarrassing!
Hurry change!
I'm really going to kill you!
I'm going to have fun!
Well.. but...
Itao-kun do you have cram school?
Yes, I do
Ma-kun, you should be going to cram school too!
Go to cram school with Itao-kun
You're so irritating!
Irritating, irritating why?
You're mother is just worried about you!
Oh, Itao-san let me give you more tea
Never mind!
I'll kill you!
Don't say such things!
Don't say those things!
Ma-kun don't yell at me in front of your friend!
Hurry go!
I said I'm going!
Let me join you guys!
Let me join you!
I such a lonely mother
What are you saying?
Why are you calling me idiot?
Ma-kun...
Matsubara's son...
Yea
There's something here
Feel it
I'm gonna kill you!!
What are you saying?
I'm leaving, what's with you?
I told you not to yell at me in front of your friend!
Hurry go!
Scary, he's so scary, right?
Don't say those things when Itao-kun is here
Never mind! It doesn't matter, just go!
Well I'm going...
Just gooooo!!
There's...
curry, go and eat it up
I know, I know
Just heat it
I know, I know already!
Share with Itao-kun
I know, hurry go!
It's "Java Curry"
It doesn't matter what brand!
Ok, I'm leaving
Just go
Make yourself at home
You're so irritating...
Such a bother
What is it?
What is it?!
What?
Go!
What are you doing??
It's that time of the month...
I want to eat this one
Just go!!
Oh so scary!
GO!!
I should kill you already!
Hurry go!
How do I look?
It doesn't matter!
Why are you hitting me??
You're so scary!
Let me have a drink
GO!!
Don't forget the curry
I know, just go!
"Vermont Curry"
You said a different brand earlier...