Downtown no
Gottsu ee kanji
Translated by eChie
Song: Kirai Dayo
Performed by: Fairchild
Sung by: YOU
Chotto yakisugita bekon wo
We ate a little overdone bacon
saying it's a bit salty in the morning
sukoshi karai ne tte tabeta asa
At night we had our first fight
Hajimete kenka shita yoru ni
The photo I couldn't tear
Yabure naka tta ano shashin
10 minutes late when we first met
Dea tta koro no chikoku ha 10 pun
I used to prefer to wait for you
Saki ni matteru houga sukida tta
I remember everything
Zenbu oboeteru yo
I can recall
Omoidaseru
Tatta hitotsu no story
The one and only story
But I don't like you, I hate you
Dakedo zenzen kirai daikirai
Even though I won't forget
Wasurenai kedo
Mou kirai daikirai
Yet I don't like you, I hate you
I don't need you now
Imaha iranai
Dakara zenzen kirai daikirai
That's why I don't like you, I hate you
Even though I can't lose
Nakuse nai kedo
Mou kirai daikirai
Yet I don't like you, I hate you
Dare mo iranai
I don't need anyone
I'm sure I don't like you, I hate you
Kitto zenzen kirai daikirai
I gotta go
Mou ikanakucha