Subtitles: Zurui
(Aho = Idiot or Idiotic)
Wait
Stop!!
At last, I found your hide out!
Kentaro, you are good!
Die!!
Now, our roles are reversed!
Now what Kentaro?
(.............)
(..........!)
What... huh?
So are you going to call Aho Aho Man?
Alright?
Aho Aho Man, help me!!
You're an idiot right?
People who say idiot, are idiots
What's with this guy
But we already knew you were coming!
- What??
Pull the lever!
(..........!)
What is she saying, I have no idea!
You will die from hunger in here!
(ho ho ho ho ho ho)
Damn!
Aho Aho Man!
We are stuck in here!
Aho Aho Jacket!
(This summer fashion is
the Aho Aho Jacket...)
Shut up!
That has nothing to do with our situation!
We are stuck in here!
Do something!
Hurry...hurry...hurry!
Aho Aho Dynamite!
(Aho Aho Dynamite will destroy everything
within 1km, and render it useless for 10 yrs)
(This cold be a Nuclear bomb...
no IT IS a Nuclear bomb)
Hey!
What are you doing??
What are you thinking? Bald head!
Everything's a mess
What are you doing!
Do something!
Open it! Do something!
Aho Aho Capsule!
(When Aho Aho Man drinks the Aho Aho
Capsule he sleeps for 1 hour)
Hey wake up! Wake up!
Wake up!
It's ok...
Help! Anybody!
Wake up!
To be continued