Translation: eChie
A worldwide cooking show
Cooking Hatto shite boo!
Cooking Hatto Shite
Ok, first of all.
- Yes.
Our popular regular guest.
Yes. Our guest is Mrs. Cathy Tsukamoto from Shimantogawa cooking school.
Please come in!
Teacher.
Hello.
- Thank you for coming.
Now teacher,
- Yes.
Everyone watching this show is looking
forward to your cooking.
What's today's cuisine?
I'm going to make borscht today.
Oh, borscht?
It's Russian popular cuisine, huh?
Yes it is. Speaking of borscht, it means
one thing in Japan, right?
Yes.
- I think so.
Borscht is a cuisine, right?
Yes.
But in Russia, there are lots of borscht.
Are there?
There are so many kinds of borscht,
so it is kind of confusing.
So it is impossible to make borscht today.
I understand.
I don't like it.
Teacher..Your apron must be surprised.
It didn't listen to me.
It didn't..?
It's annoying huh?
I'm sorry.
That's OK.
You should cut that scene
No no that's fine.
People would think I have bad manners.
- No, no one would.
I will make a dessert today.
- Dessert?
Dessert.
Sounds good. From which country?
Russia.
Oh Russia? It sounds rare.
Yea, please teach us how.
I have a funny story.
Huh?
On my way to come here, I was driving then..
What is it?
- Hilarious.
A hilarious story? I see..
Yes!
Now the crabs...
- Crabs?
Yes, crabs.
Strange to use crabs for dessert huh?
I don't really...
I have never heard.
- Me neither.
I think so. Then I'm going to put fresh cream on the crabs.
Fresh cream?
This is very unique dessert.
Unique? How can you tell that?
What are you looking at?
What makes you decide it's unique or not!
I'm sorry.
Really.
I'm a bit strange today.
I'm sorry.
That's OK.
Apply the fresh cream..
- OK.
He is cheating on me.
Teacher.
I know it.
I'll kill him.
Why men are..
They always cheat on women.
Yea..it is a hard problem.
But I'm sure my husband does.
Oh does he?
He does. What do you think?
It is a hard question. That might be their nature.
Then put the fresh cream on..
Spread it.
OK, I will do that.
Really?
- Yes.
OK, I spread it on the crabs.
This is unique huh?
What makes you think it's unique?
What makes me think..
"No breasts."
Ryoko-chan is shocked.
She must be shocked.
I'm sorry.
No that's fine.
How is it? It's evenly spread on the crab.
Oh no way.. have to hurry.
I need garlic.
Have to hurry?
Yes. They will escape.
OK, I brought garlic.
Hurry! Hurry!
This is a big accident!
I'm so sorry.
Cut out this scene from the show!
No that's OK.
Ryoko-chan must be surprised.
And some lettuce.
Lettuce.
Yes, wrap it with the lettuce.
OK prepare lettuce.
I'm sorry.
- OK.
Here is the lettuce, and the crabs are here.
You know what?
- Yes?
It's really hilarious.
Oh your funny story, teacher?
What?
I'm clumsy.
I came here by car today, and
there were no place to park.
I was waiting for any vacancy.
In fact, you just need to wait.
If you wait huh?
Somebody left.
Then I could park.
Ok, back to the lettuce.
Do you have carrots?
OK, one?
The more the better.
- OK.
OK ryoko-chan, bring them all.
But one is enough for today.
Then smash lettuce with carrot.
- OK.
Lightly.
Do you know why lightly?
You have to remember before getting married.
Hey Ryoko-chan, this is a really important question.
If you can't answer, you might not be able to get married!
Not to break fiber.
Yes that's the answer.
Smash it gently.
Let's smash.
OK, smash gently.
Not to break the fiber.
I won't come back!
OK then, cooking..
Bye.
See you next week.