TRANSLATION: SHION
TYPESET & QC: KEDOMAS
Sky Hanglinger
Good morning, everyone
Good morning
- Thanks as always for being here
So, today you're all here today
to try our Sky Hanglinger
So, how are you feeling about it?
So?
How do you feel about the sky?
I'm looking forward to it
- It's not everyday you fly, right?
Of course not
As they say, "the devils made the land,
but the angels made the sky"
Someone said this before,
and they got beaten up for it
Today you'll soar the sky,
but please, don't think of this as a game
And remember,
"landing is scarier than flying"
Someone said this before,
and they got blackmailed then
But please, don't forget to land
- Yes
Remember: when you're having fun,
you gotta look out for every danger
Ok? Please, remember this
Got it?
- Yes
Let's fly smartly!
- Sure
Alright, each one of you
will fly in turns, one by one
But let me be clear on this:
The first thing that'll happen
once you lift off, is your death
But it's not that bad, you know?
So we have to die for this?
- Yes, that's it
It's going to kill you
But on the brochure, it said it's safe...
It means it's a safe death
Huh? That sounds kind of...
I don't think I can do it
- Come again?
I don't really want to die
What?!
Can't you show us how it's done first?
- No way, I can't
I'm not ready
They haven't arranged
the right model for me, so...
Have you ever done it before?
- Not even once
I mean... can I...
Can I just cancel this?
- Cancel, you say?
He's right, I'd like to cancel it too
Cancel?
- We were thinking the same
Are you quitting?
- We are
Huh, I see...
Can't be helped, then
Alright
Can't we all get our money back?
- Right
Please, give it back
I'm afraid I can't
But when we registered...
- Yeah?
They told us we could ask for a refund if...
- How much was it?
23,000 yen (210$)
- I see
And did you all pay the same amount?
- Yes
Well, I can't refund you
But why?
- Because I've used all your money
I've used every little bit of it
So I can't refund you, what do we do?
So? What now?
Well, you have to refund us
- He's right
Come on, let's fly, don't say that!
That was creepy
Let's fly, come on!
- No way, I don't wanna die
You have two choices, stick with me
or go the hell away
I don't want to do this, I resign,
give me my money back!
I told you I can't
Isn't this a sagi (scam)?
Sagi (herons) can fly, you know
That's not what he...
But I've never flown before
So I'm not a sagi
I'm gonna sue you
We'll contact the police
- You'll sue?
Who are you going to sue?
- You, duh
Huh? What have I done?
- We'll sue you for good
You wanna sue me?
Of course we're gonna sue you
- Me? Sue me?
That's right
- You're going to sue me?
Of course
- And where's your telephone, huh?
Telephone?
I have no idea
- Let's just go
Come on, try it
- No way
I'm gonna die, am I not?
- Yes, of course
But look, I made these salt mounds
as a charm, praying you won't die
Huh?
So I won't die?
- It'd be good if you don't
But I guess you will...
They all died one after another before
If so I'm not riding it
- No one ever complained, though
Of course, they're gone
Come on, don't be like this, man
- Stop it, you're creeping me out
Are you saying I'm creepy?
- I'm not riding that thing
Why not?
Give us a break
- Let's do this, come on
Alright, alright, you won't die,
I promise, now do it
Even if you say so...
- Yeah, so suddenly...
You've been saying we'd die
- We don't trust you
It looks dangerous
- It's fine, come on, let's do it
Don't be like that
Could it be... you were joking before?
About what?
- About dying
No, that part is true, but...
Then I'm not doing it
- Alright, it's a joke, then
So, we're not going to die?
- Let's say it's a joke
"Let's say" what?!
You're not going to die, I swear
Really?
- Yes
It's fine, come here
Let's do this
- Is it safe?
You go first, we'll follow you after
Sit down and put the sky-radar on
Sky radar?
- Yep, the sky radar
Like this
Are you ok?
I warn you, it's so fun sometimes
people never come back from it
So make sure to get back
within 50 minutes
Is he going to fly?
- Of course he is
Can you take the salt mounds away?
No way, if they crumble, you're done for
That's the only thing
I'm relying on for you!
Looks dangerous
- Yes, I...
I don't...
- Alright, let's go
And go!
Welcome back
So, how was it?
Even if you ask me that...
- You flew, right?
I didn't fly at all
- Whaaat?
You saw him flying, right?
Huh?!
He flew, didn't he?
- He didn't move an inch
What the...
Come on guys, he just flew!
He didn't even budge
Let's hear it from him, what do you think?
I mean...
It felt like I was flying for a moment
- See? He did fly!
But he didn't move at all!
That's your personal opinion,
he actually flew!
Cut it out man,
such pranks are so old-fashioned!
Why didn't he fly?
- I told you he just did!
You'll never fly
if you keep on denying he did
Ah, is that so?
Ok, are we going, then?
Let's go to the police station
- Huh?
The police?
And why?
No, wait, really...
Hey, let me go!
TRANSLATION: SHION
TYPESET & QC: KEDOMAS