Sho-ta!
Do you wanna play?
No.
Let's play.
What? - Let's play.
No.
Let's see how much we keep it in the air by hitting
Not now.
Why?
1! - 2, 3, 4, 5!! - Hey!
And this is over!
You, maniac!
So indiscreet.
This is a farewell ceremony!
How could you be so indiscreet?
- I... thought he might enjoy this.
But obviously I shouldn't. No more playing.
I'm sorry. Please go on.
No good.
Be serious!
(Give me a break!)
What? - I was scolded for what you did.
I want to play.
I already told you I can't.
Let's play with this.
Take this! Die!
You damn priest!
Watch how I finish him!
Ouch.
Make a count!
Do you wanna join me?!
Hey! - What the hell do you think...
Hey! - You are the one who started this!
What is the problem with this guy?!
Hey! - Back off.
I'm very sorry.
- What is this lunatic doing here?!
Be serious, OK? - I will. Sorry.
We came here yo say farewell. - Right.
Fooled you! Tour stomach is wide open!
- Fooled you! Tour stomach is wide open!
Hey!
You are totally open to attack!
I can't believe this! - I apologize.
Whyis he here?
Pick it up!
You shouldn't be here! - I'm sorry.
This is a farewell service for God's sake!
- I'm sorry, I will behave. - Please go on.
I'm sorry to have lost my temper.
- It's very understandable.
You do it one more time, I'm out!
- OK, I'm sorry.
You completely messed it up! - So what?
- You got me in a big trouble.
It's so boring. - Just hold your horses.
It's so hot in here. - I understand that, but...
I'm gonna catch fire soon. - Just sit tight.
Let's play. Please. - No way.
No. No.
I can't help loving you!
You freak!
I'm a gay!
Please, priest! Please get back!
You can never get away from me,
you understand?