Subtitles: eChie
Busukko (Ugly Girl) Club
Alright, I'm going.
Take care.
Are you ok by yourself?
Yea, I'm fine.
Well..
Miso soup is in the pot..
Ok, I know. Say hi to your mom.
Ok.
Ok, then.
I'm going.
You got everything?
Yea, I'm fine.
I'll go going then.
Have a safe trip.
Yes.
See you.
Bye.
(Hello, this is Busukko club)
Hello?
(Hi, this is Busukko club)
Well, its my first time calling..
(Ok, how can I help you?)
Well..
It says all girls are around 20 yrs old.
(Yes, all girls are around 20)
And.. it also says "school club activity"...
(Yes)
Is it true?
Oh is that so?
(Yes, don't worry)
And..
If I don't like the girl..
(You can change as many times you want)
Is that so?
(Yes sir)
So.. I'll take the service.
(Thank you very much)
Yes.
(Have a wonderful night)
Haha..yea I hope so.
(Thank you for calling, bye)
Ok..
Secret night entry...? Wow..
Hi!
The door is open!
Hello.
I'm Reona.
Can I come in?
Eh..sorry..
- Huh?
Change.
Change?
Yes, sorry..Change.
Blindfold?
No..
Well..I want "Change"..
Tie me up?
No.. I'm sorry...
Change?
Yes.
Ok, then..may I borrow your phone?
Yes, sure.
Change?
Yes, Change please.
Around 20 yrs old..?
No dream, no hope...
Hello?
Reona.
Change.
Ok..
Yes, I'm sorry.
Ok, then..
She's on her way.
Oh, is she? Thank you.
Sexy..? Exciting...?
Yes!
Please come in!
I am American. Is that ok?
Well, if you want me to speak in
English, I will. I can speak both.
English turns you on?
Well..
Japanese is ok?
Do you want to start?
Eh..
You are cute.
Well, I am sorry but..
I didn't request a foreigner.
Why..
I'm sorry but I am not very good with foreigners.
Oh really..
Let me change.
Change?
I was ready already.
I'm sorry.
Really..
Sorry.
I have no luck today.
Change?
Yes, I'm sorry.
Ok then..
Yea.
Yes!
Excuse me.
Thank you for requesting me.
What?
May I use these slippers?
Shall we take a shower?
Well..
Or just my mouth today?
Shall we get started?
Wait a sec...Eh?
Who are you?
Oh, I am from Busukko club.
What?
You want to release it right? I will do it for you.
Yea, I want to. But...eh...Busukko club?
Certainly yes.
You're an old man..
Can't wait, huh?
No no no...wait!
What's wrong?
No, that's fine. Just let me change.
Eh?
Well.. please change.
Oh... You got me there... You want to change.
Yes.
To be honest, I am upset.
I was changed 4 times today.
Don't be upset.
But sill change, right?
Can't you rethink?
I don't have the feeling at all...
Please.
I can't..
I am a respectable adult with a full time job.
I'm just doing this on the side to make some money to play.
And end up with 4 changes a day.
You keep saying "Change", but ...may
I ask you what is "Change" to you?
Well...
Ok, I am leaving then.
Sorry for the trouble.
Can I tell you one more thing..
If... we didn't meet like this...
Do you think you would have held me?
What!
Here is Mr. Ball!
Get out!
Are you from Busukko club?
Yup.
Go home.
Play ball!
I said to go home!
What the..
Mr Ball is here!
Cut it out and get out of here!
Get out. You guys are all freaks.
Give me a break..
Here is Mr. Ball!
Leave!