Translations: Zurui
Laying Eggs
Today is our wedding day
Yuuko-chan is late
Koji-san!
Yuuko-chan!
I'm sorry
You're late Yuuko-chan!
You look so pretty Yuuko-chan!
Thank you Koji-san
My parents almost found out
Is it OK?
OK, let's start our wedding day
It's just us two
Yes, but can't be helped
Oh, one ring is missing
Koji-san it's under there
OK
Let's have our wedding kiss
It's Fish man
Hey! Where are you Fish man?!
Damn
Where are you?
Hey!
You're bothering us on our wedding day!
Let me give birth
Koji-san
You OK?
I'm OK
- OK?
Don't get married with this strange dressed lady
We couldn't afford anything better,
but you're beautiful Yuuko-chan
I chose it myself!
Hey, leave! Leave now!
What? What is this Wedding day?
This type of wedding... can't beat an "8 peoples" wedding
What are you saying?
What is an "8 peoples" wedding?
Yeah
You're in the way, just leave!
Huh?
Please break up
Hey
Break up with me
When did we ever date?
When did we 2 ever date?
Huh?
I'm going to lie, I'm going to lie from now
You raped me!
You told a lie, right?
Why are you so surprised?
You said you were going to lie, right?
Oh, yeah
It's not "Oh yeah"
Why did you come here? Leave!
What so good about this girl... leave her
What did you say!
OUCH! OUCH! OUCH!
Please stop! Everyone did you see it?!
You're over-reacting
It wasn't anything
Yeah, what are you saying
You're disgusting
... how can he die?
Yeah
Ha.. there's no way you can kill me
Damn
But!
If 2 people love each other in a church
And can forget about their embarrassment
while dancing like an octopus
My ugly self will turn into a skeleton
There you go Yuuko-chan
He will become a skeleton
Do you really think so?
It's OK, dancing like an octopus is
easy, just make your lips like this
Stop!
He's turning into a skeleton
You're right!
OK.. Yuuko-chan.. forget about your embarrassment
Let's do the octopus dance
OK
Let's start
"Octopus, octopus, octopus dance"
"I am an octopus, octopus"
Hey
Why are you taking pictures?
Shouldn't it be a video
Why are you so quiet?
You told us that if we did the Octopus
dance you would turn into a skeleton
You lied!
If you get married to her, what will you do about this baby?
I have nothing to do with that baby
Listen to this child's message!
What's the message?
You both close your eyes and listen to this child's message!
Will I understand if I hear the message?
Yeah
You...
Close your eyes!
Yuuko-chan let's listen to the message
OK
I'm glad (censored)
Hey!
We can't broadcast that kind of language!
Let's go
Wait!
Use the "peeeep" sound!