Murder File: The Long-Armed-Bat-White-Flying-Squirrel
The victim, the long-armed-bat-white-flying-squirrel's time of death...
...was 10 o'clock last night.
A knife in the chest.
I see.
Everything was locked
from the inside.
There's no trace of
the killer's getaway.
A locked room, huh?
Yes.
What else do we know?
The knife was covered with the fingerprints of a ramen shop employee living next door.
That's suspicious.
Detective Hamada!
What's up?
Around 7 o'clock last night...
Yeah?
...the person in apartment
201 next door...
...asked me to ask you if Mr. Long-Armed-Bat-White-Flying-Squirrel and a child were kissing.
They really asked that?
They really asked that.
I made up an answer.
I see.
I just got some new information!
Oh? What's up?
According to the
apartment manager...
...the victim was never in
his room at night time.
So that means...
...the victim was nocturnal?
Yes.
The crime took place in daylight.
So that means...
...he was carried here.
I was told to tell you that.
Who told you that?
I can't tell you that.
I like your style.
- Detective Hamada!
- What's up?
I just learned something amazing.
What's that?
I talked with the head girl at a
snack bar the victim often visited...
...and she seemed disappointed that his arms weren't as long as everyone makes them out to be.
Really?
This is completely
fabricated information...
...apparently the victim said "As
long as I have long arms, I won't
let those bastards do as they like."
That's weird.
Huh?
According to what I heard...
..."It's good to let those
bastards do what they want"...
Apparently the victim said this.
Whichever one it is just
who are "those bastards"?
Who are "those bastards"?
Does it matter?
I want to eat.
Also...
...this is from the
couple living next door.
Yeah?
Apparently the victim sang
one of his hometown songs
in a loud vo ice last night.
What hometown song?
I'm a little bit unsure on that point.
I'd have sex with you.
Can I mention one more thing?
What is it?
According to his coworker...
...the victim apparently said
"If you kill me, lock everything
from the inside and kill me."
That's weird.
According to what I heard...
...he apparently always stressed that
he never did anything like lock things.
Hmm, well we can't know the
layout of the room in this state.
Well, the owner stated it's a 15-tatami mat size when he advertised the room.
Does the owner look suspicious?
No, he moved to
Australia 15 years ago.
He's the prime minister there now.
I knew that.
Inspector!
There's a hidden door over here!
What?!
There's a child inside!
A child?
I'm saying an adult!
Ok.
- Let's take a look.
- Ok.
Please don't!
That's my private thing.
I like your style.
Ok!
At any rate...
...let's start again at step one.
Yeah, but...
...just what happened here?
Hey, me... I'm... I have no clue.
To be continued?