Subtitles: Zurui
(Aho = Idiot or Idiotic)
Before your father died...
...he must have given you the
design of the Megaton Missile.
Don't pretend you
don't know about it.
I don't know anything about it!
If you don't confess you will
be asking for pain, little boy.
Do your worst! I'll never
give it to the likes of you!
Playing dumb, is it?
If that's the case...
then die!
Save me! Aho Aho Man!
Aho Aho Man?
You're really an idiot.
The one who says idiot is the idiot!
What'd you say?!
Aho Aho Man...
...is a super human that
was built by little Kentaro's
father, Professor Zaizen...
...the strongest in
history you might say.
Alright!
Aho Aho Man!
Use the "Aho Aho Hand" on them!
When Aho Aho Man attaches
the "Aho Aho Hand"...
...his punch increases in
strength 10,000 times and
can even blast through steel.
Alright!
Kick!
What the-?
Hey. Hey.
Kick!
Sorry.
What is he doing?
What the hell are you doing?
Why're you using your legs?
You should punch.
Not kick.
Sorry.
Take 'em out!
Come on!
Punch!
Wait! Wait!
Sorry, sorry.
Why are using this hand?
Why are you sniffing it?!
Look at this hand!
What do you see?
Now look at that hand.
You got it?!
You gotta use that hand.
Ow.
What the hell are you doing?!
Just what the-
That's enough from you!
What do you think you're-
Punch!
An awesome punch!
You really are a complete
idiot, aren't you?
To be continued