Note: Every kanji in Japan have at least 2 ways of
being read. The kun-yomi and the on-yumi reading.
FENDING
Usually Kun-yumi is used when the kanji stands alone and
usually on-yumi is used when it's together with another kanji.
We're all ready.. you may start!
Matsumoto is using the on-yumi reading of the kanji's,
so he's actually using the wrong reading and the words he says doesn't have any meaning.
Thank you very much.
Face!
Torso!
Floor!
Heaven!
Warm!
Line.
Car!
Grandchild!
Outside!
Inside!
Floor!
Heaven!
Dark!
Bright!
Heaven!
Wax!
Spring!
Using the kun-yomi. The
on-yomi reading would be "shun"
Thinking.
Sweet!
America?
No!
England?
Italy?
No!
France?
What?
Kun-yomi again. on-yomi would be "ka".
Australia!
Thank you very much!