Company President
TRANSLATION:  SHION
TYPESET & QC:  KEDOMAS
President!
It's about time to begin
Sure
So, as I was saying,
I'm joined by our development team
We'd like to explain you
how our new product works
A new product?
- Yes
Can we?
- Sure
Alright, please, Imasaki
- Sure, let me do it
Here's our new product
- It's a pot!
He says it's a pot
He just said "pot"...
This is a new invention of our company,
the just-press-and-go-pot
Its most peculiar feature
Is the fact it can boil up water
with half the power of a normal pot
Only this one can, right?
That's right
It's an innovative pot, isn't it?
- Of course, it's the first of its kind
It's a complete new pot experience
By using this, you can save
a lot from your electric bill
You can say this pot...
- is the first one of its kind!
...is the first one of its kind!
It is, right?
- It is indeed!
It can halve down the electric bill
you'd pay by using another pot
And of course it works perfectly,
it has no flaws. What do you think?
Mr. President?
Does it hurt?
Come again?
Hurt?
Hurt, you say?
What should?
- That thing, does it?
Does it...
This...
It can hurt
Yes, it does hurt
Let me try it myself
- Sure, please
Please, President
Of course, it depends
on how you use it
Please, Imada, do it
Alright, mr. President,
place your finger over here
Should I put it inside this?
- Yes
It doesn't hurt
We're sorry to hear that
It doesn't hurt?
- Not at all
It didn't...
- Not even a bit
What are you doing?!
- Sorry, I wasn't expecting it...
Just do something about it
So, mr. President...
Come here, Kurano
- Yes
Do it
- Sure
Mr. President, your finger
Ah, do I have to place it here?
- Yes
Please, do it
- Here it goes
Ouch!
- Ah! You said it!
Does it hurt?!
Does it hurt?
- It does, but...
It's not pleasant
I'm sorry for that
- It lacks of stinging pain
Ah, I see... but it hurts, right?
- Of course it does
But it's not good?
- It's not!
Wasn't it?
- Yeah, 'cause... 'cause he pressed it
Sorry for that
- That one doesn't count
YOU, you're next
- Yes
Let's see...
Place your forehead here, President
Here? In this spot?
- Yes
It's kind of...
Too slow
Sorry
- That's not what I wanted
This product, this pot...
- What about it?
Is no good
Is it no good?
- Exactly
It took us 3 years to complete it...
- You gotta do more than that
Got it
Are you stealing your salary or what?
We're sorry to hear that
- I know
It's no good
We got that
- Not good at all
Yes...
- You know, now? What a pot needs
This can't do it
Yes, sorry, Mr. President.
Apologize, everyone!
We're terribly sorry
Alright then
Got it?
- Yes
The pot...
- Yes?
It's not good!
No good
- I understand...
Alright? I'll be waiting
- Sure
Do it
- Mr. President! How's this?
Ouch! Now this is good!
This pot is good!
Is it?!
- We can sell this!
Really?
- Let's launch it
Are you sure?
- Definitely
Can we?
- You bet
Go make more of this!
- This is great news!
There's no time to waste, let's go!
Ouch! This one's good to go too!
What's that?
- This one's good    - Is it?!
Let's bring this one too
We're going---
Ouch!
You're good too!
Come with us, then!
That's all good
This one's pretty good too
Take this thing too!
TRANSLATION:  SHION
TYPESET & QC:  KEDOMAS
Take it or I'll fire you all!
Sorry, Mr. President!