Translation, Timing & Typesetting: GakiNoSuitGuy
Quality Check: John Dread
We will bring you the smiles of children.
Can't wait until summer!
My First Errand - Can't Wait Until Summer Special
Spring Special
My First Errand staff room
The spring special.
That's not something to miss.
Tokoro George
From now on it will get warmer
and the summer is coming.
And they grow up so fast before us.
The smiles of children,
well there are tears too.
Those are all things of passion.
Be sure to watch.
The first smile on our program today comes from the big adventure of the coconut daughter.
1 hour from Toshin by train.
Saitama â— Ogawa City
The first errand is in Saitama Prefecture, Ogawa which overlooks the mountains of Chichibu.
Narrator:
Chikaishi Shinsuke
Today is open school day for parents whose children go to the kindergarten.
Among the mothers and fathers
there is a mother carrying a baby on her back.
5 years old.
Ko
ko
na
Kokona has become serious after becoming an older sister as of last year,
to help her busy mother.
She's so cute.
Mother
The mother is still 22 years old.
She's so young.
That means... if Kokona is 5 years old...
Father. 19 years old.
Mother. 17 years old.
That's right. The mother gave birth to Kokona when she was 17.
Shrine visit
They got married when Kokona was 1 year old.
Wedding
When Kokona was 3, the mother went through her coming-of-age ceremony.
Coming of age
ceremony
Nevermind all that.
Kokona is such a great name. How did she think of it?
When I was pregnant at 17
there was a tanning parlor.
Tan-pa = Tanning parlor
I didn't have a name
and you know the coconut oil that makes a nice smell
Cosmetic coconut oil
and I fell in love with the smell,
Falling in love with coconuts.
so I thought of making her name like coconut.
tsu
Kokona
I thought that coconut would be too strange so I advised my grandparents.
=
Kokona
They suggested to use the characters meaning "Peace at Heart" where the peace is the same as in the Shouwa era.
What a great name you've given her is what people told me.
Kokona
You must surely have given it a lot of thought. Well...
Little brother
Hinata
8 months
old
The baby is a boy.
Today is the first time celebrating Children's Day since his birth.
She wants prove herself for her tiny baby brother, so her mother has asked us to help with her first errand.
- You can go and do it, right?
- Yes
- You can do it, right?
- I can do it.
At the stand ....
Are you listening? Look me in the eyes and listen!!
Mother is serious about this.
This is important.
What will you ask the bus driver when you get on board?
So she's going on a bus.
Excuse me.
Does this bus drive to Ogawa station?
What does she have to buy?
You know they sell small versions of those carp streamers.
For Hinata's Children's Day.
I want you to buy one of them.
Let's keep it a secret from Hinata.
The bus comes twice an hour.
TN: Okara is a residue from tofu making. It's a by-product which gives it certain qualities.
The errand includes donuts and tofu made from Okara in front of the station,
cake and carp streamer cookie from the cake shop
and various items from the grilled meat shop.
Impossible.
That's impossible.
Say it one more time.
- Karaage
- Do you have any Karaage, Bang Bang?
TN: Karaage is fried chicken. Bang Bang is another kind of chicken.
Do you have any Karaage, Bang Bang?
Say it one more time.
- Do you have any Karaage, Bang Bang?
- Ok.
Yes, she can do it.
Don't you cry if you become scared.
What are you saying, mother?
Don't you come back crying from being scared.
This is her method to turn on Kokona's ambition switch.
- Say "thank you" if you ask someone about something.
- Yes.
I might be a bit late. The grill shop is always so slow.
- Don't come back drunk.
- Yes.
An energetic Kokona is dashing forward.
One two, one two, one two.
However...
Mama.
What?
Can I really do it?
At that time even the mother
is wondering if she can do it by herself.
This is the first time for her to go through a first errand. Either for herself or someone else.
Kokona remembers that mother packed her a rice ball.
Holding tightly where her mother has squeezed the rice ball.
Yes, now I've received power.
I can do it!
The bus only comes twice an hour.
Walking to the bus stop usually takes 15 minutes.
She was given 3 times the time to make it there. 45 minutes.
So she is there ahead of time.
There is still 35 minutes until the next bus.
Her mother told her to wait in the shop in front of the bus stop in such a situation.
Hello.
Hello. Is the bus coming today?
Yes, the bus will come.
I'm going shopping by myself.
You are going shopping by yourself? Where are you going?
Just a little bit of pride.
Mom told me I can buy 1 candy item.
Since I have money.
Having spent time shopping the bus might arrive.
- You can cross here.
- Yes, I can cross.
You're already going?
It usually takes time to choose a piece of candy.
But she was only in the shop for 5 minutes.
I wonder if the bus is here soon.
There's still 30 minutes until the bus is coming.
I can't see the bus at all.
It totally isn't there.
There's still time, right?
Still not seeing it.
Not doing anything and just waiting
is the hardest thing for Kokona.
Even after she is done eating the onigiri (rice ball).
It's not coming.
She doesn't understand how slow time passes or how many minutes are left.
The staff is in the same situation.
The shop owner has been watching from inside the shop.
I'm going shopping alone.
By yourself? You're so great.
I was thinking of riding the bus tomorrow. So I came by to check the schedule.
You came to see?
Can you wait a little bit more?
Just wait a little more. Do your best.
Give me some. Nice.
Thank you, sir.
And after waiting a bit more, the bus came.
It's coming, coming.
Hey, Kokona. The bus is coming.
The bus isn't coming.
It's right there.
Kokona is so surprised that it is suddenly there.
Finally. She gets to board it.
The ones who are most relieved are the cameramen.
I can do this!
The bus arrives after 10 minutes.
Much less than the waiting time.
Paying the money just like she was told by her mother...
Thank you.
She said it properly.
The first place she is heading to is...
I must go to the Okara donuts.
In this shop they make various kinds of donuts and
they recently started making Okara donuts.
Excuse me, do you have cheap tofu?
Cheap tofu.
Cheap tofu?
There are all kinds of tofu.
- Yes.
The mother made her get the most common tofu.
These are donuts made from Okara.
These are the ones.
She was told to buy various types.
It's fine.
And when she is done choosing...
She dropped it.
I'm so sorry.
But she isn't getting scolded by the shop attendants.
I will hold it so please take.
Thank you very much, young lady.
Mama said to take 5.
She is letting Kokona do it.
One, two, three, fo-
Kokona is so nervous because of her blunder.
This one looks look.
The shop attendant gives the dejected Kokona
a pink balloon.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
She was so nervous.
Hello.
Please greet people.
That's what she is told by her mother.
Hello.
I'm going shopping by myself.
What? You are shopping by yourself?
Yep.
That's great.
I was at the donut place and now I'm heading for the cake shop.
- Is that so?
- Make sure you take care of yourself.
- Yes. Bye bye.
If you greet people they will be kind to you.
Heading for the cake shop.
Rather than the cake shop she is more concerned about what to buy from the grilled meat shop.
Bang Bang chicken and Yakitori perchance.
Not Yakitori, chicken Tsukune.
Bang Bang chicken...
And Tsukune perchance.
I will do my very best...
I'm starting to get confused.
Bang Bang chicken
Wait?
This is a bus stop she's never seen before.
While she's been saying Bang Bang she's left the trail.
This is the worst.
She's a lost child.
And yet she keeps walking.
Fried chicken...
Bang Bang chicken Tsukune
She remembered Tsukune.
That's what it was. Bang Bang chicken and Tsukune.
Where are you going?
I'm going shopping by myself.
- Shopping? Where to?
- Yep.
The cake shop.
Have you already shopped at the cake shop?
- Not yet.
- Not yet?
Pekochan Cake Shop was that way!
She noticed.
Where was it again?
It was that way!
Yes, it's that way.
This way. Peko. Ca-. Right?
When coming here she always does the usual greeting.
Shake shake shake. He-hello.
She was asked to purchase a polar bear cake and carp streamer cookie.
Polar bear cake, please.
Mr. Best Friend Bear
This one is for Kokona. And then...
And a cookie for her little brother.
Since today is a holiday, the box is Children's Day-themed.
And this one, please.
This too?
Since they are going to grandpa's house, she was told to buy a carp streamer if they have them.
Thankfully it isn't sold out.
I bought it-*bounce*.
Invigorated again, she is now heading for the grilled meat shop.
I wonder if she will remember the song?
Bang Bang chicken Tsukune.
This is the shop she goes to with her family.
I'm shopping by myself.
- You came by yourself?
- Yeah.
What do you want today?
Yes, that song you've been singing.
Bang Bang
Bang Bang for one person.
- Bang Bang meal.
- And...
5 pieces of Kashira.
TN: Kashira is from the tender part of the chicken breast.
5 pieces of Kashira, 1 Bang Bang meal.
And...
The song became a mess.
But she remembers when she ate it.
Which one is round?
It's like a Dango.
Tsukene?
Yes, 5 of those.
Oh, you are shopping?
- By myself.
- Hi, Hina.
Hina, isn't it great that Kokona is shopping by herself?
- Yep, all by myself.
- You came by yourself?
- You can do that?
- Yes, of course I can.
You are walking by yourself?
No, I took the bus.
Ah, Kokona...
Since you came by yourself I will give you a Tsukune.
I don't need one.
Okay, I get it.
What about the fried chicken?
Inside mummy's tummy there is yet another baby.
Yet another? I see.
So that's why your mother isn't drinking alcohol.
She's purchased Bang Bang, Tsukune and Kashira but...
she forgot the first item in the song. Karaage.
She's exhausted from carrying the purchased items.
What? Beer!?
No, no, no. It's juice, of course.
You must be tired.
It's not about being tired,
it was exhausting, I tell ya.
I'm sorry that it took me so long to come.
It was quick, though.
The truth is that it took some time.
Can I complain a bit?
Look, mama drew it for me.
Why?
She drew it so I can go shopping for Hinata and come back.
I can see it.
Hinata, Mama, Kokona.
And the one in her tummy.
I will become the eldest sister of them all.
Customer, don't drink until dawn.
You still have shopping to do.
Are they old geezers?
Do your best, okay?
- Yes.
- Remember to greet your mother from me.
- Okay?
- Thank you.
- Do your best.
- Yes.
- Do your best, okay?
- Do your best.
- Yes.
It's been 2 hours and 20 minutes since she left the house.
It's the 5 o'clock bell.
TN: It signals all over Japan that children should head home for dinner.
At the ♩ bottom of ♪ the mountain ♪ what bell is ringing. 🎶
TN: Loosely based on the song Kanenonaruoka.
Grandpa and grandma's house is the mother's childhood home.
The mother went ahead and is preparing for the celebration.
The mother is making Inari Sushi in the style of carp streamers (koinobori).
This mother can make all kinds of things.
Kokona, you came!
You were able to do it by yourself?
I bought carp streamers for Hinata.
You thought it might be sold out but it was there.
Was it scary? Or was it not scary at all?
Mom...
You were able to do it?
Kokona was able to go shopping.
Hinata, you sure have a fine sister.
I thought that this one is cute so I bought it for Hinata.
Great.
Did you greet Pekochan today?
Yes, I did.
Look at this. Mum did her best and made this.
What do you see?
Can you see carp streamers?
- I do.
- You can see it?
Those are carp streamers.
Amazing.
- Mama, here.
- This is so great.
What about Karaage?
Did you say Karaage?
- I forgot.
- You forgot!
Nevermind. Let's eat next because you did your best.
It's okay, okay.
- Today I did my best, cheers.
- Cheers.
Getting praised by everyone. She did a lot today.
How is it? How, how, how, how?
Just wait, mama. I will praise you in a second.
When you think of spring
all kinds of things seem so shiny.
Moriguchi Hiroko
Singer
And above all the shining smiles of children are unmatchable.
Next up is a bald rebellious kid growing up on an orange orchard.
Blue ocean, blue skies.
Mizaki â— Nango
The sunshine paradise, Miyazaki prefecture.
We've arrived at the city of Nango.
The entire mountainside is all grandpa's orange orchard.
During the harvest all the relatives help out.
Taking in all the sun along with the oranges,
there is a boy who also takes in a lot of sun and is brought up full of energy.
Yuuta. 4 years and
3 months old.
4 year old Yuuta.
Getting the hang of things.
Put it in mother's basket next.
He's sneaking out of chores.
Are you thirsty?
- Tea.
- You haven't worked that much yet.
Yuuta.
He's been ignoring his mother lately.
When it comes to picking oranges it's best to ask grandpa who knows everything about it.
Yuuta.
Please help your mother.
Bringing up a child requires a fight.
The mother will not lose.
It's 10 already.
Yes, it's 10.
Now the errand is about to begin.
- Yes, it's 10 now.
- Okay, let's go home.
It's not time to go home yet.
Let's go drink some tea and then
you can go and make orange juice.
By myself?
Yes, by yourself.
The errand entails heading home and making orange juice.
Putting the oranges he harvested in the bag.
- Remember to make orange juice.
- Yep.
Go home by yourself and make it.
Yes.
For the mother who thinks that he never listens to her
it's a bit unusual how fast he took off.
He left.
He does what he is told. When it comes to it.
I'm so relieved.
Will he come back again?
Yep, he will be back. After finishing his errand.
The mother trusts Yuuta.
I'm so relieved.
She's so overwhelmed by how well-behaved his response was.
He listened to his mother.
You are making me cry as well.
Since this is my first time...
I was a bit uneasy but...
since he left he didn't need to look back even once so...
so... so...
I feel so lonely.
It's too good to be true. I see.
Once he is home there are games and and a TV.
No way he will be back.
Home. ♪
He's humming to himself while unlocking the door.
Scribbles.
They are all the work of Yuuta.
We thought that he would start playing as soon as he got home.
But these are the instruments for making orange juice.
I'm sorry. I was talking nonsense.
He came back to properly do his job.
Things surely change when you become 4.
What? Did you forget something?
He's leaving for something.
Hold up, that face.
Just as I thought.
He found a neighborhood friend.
It's Maro!
The play is escalating.
Where did it go?
What happened to coming back after pressing the juice?
Seems like there will be none of that.
Waiting for 40 minutes.
Poor mom.
He isn't back yet.
It sure takes a long time.
Let's take a break.
He isn't very useful.
I'm worried cause we don't know how he is.
The only one who knows how he is is Maro.
Close to an hour has passed.
- He isn't pressing juice.
- He forgot all about it.
He's back again.
He's playing by himself. I wonder if he will press the juice.
What!? You only came to take your hat?
Your mom is waiting. She is trusting you.
And at that time...
The phone is ringing.
He loves to answer the phone.
Hello.
Yuuta, it's your mother.
Yuuta, how is the juice coming along?
Still.. It's already finished.
Still... Finished??
No way. Really?
For real.
Did you fill it up?
It's full of juice.
It's full? Hurry up and come back, Yuuta.
He's lying.
Yes.
Come back with it. Everyone is waiting.
- Yep.
- Hurry up and bring it with you.
- Yes.
- Yes, I'm counting on you.
The answer was good but...
He said that he has made it.
- He said he's made it?
- Yep.
Since he said he's already made it he better hurry.
Hey, you can't stand on the place where you eat food.
It's onigiri.
Mother has left it for lunch for when they get back.
- Because he ran.
- Yeah, must be hungry.
He started eating it.
Something is different about it.
Yuuta has noticed something.
Yuuta who is afraid of ghosts.
He's never been home alone before.
- What's wrong?
- He's hiding in a cool place.
Oh right! Mom can't yell at me.
It seems he can break higher things as he gets taller.
Amazing.
What? He's taking the water gun.
What about pressing the juice?
Maro, you are in danger. Run away.
Amazing timing.
Perfect timing.
It's as if his mother is watching him.
What?
Hello. Yuuta?
This is your mother.
Hurry up, press the juice and bring it.
Yes.
And what about your protection charm?
The protection charm? It's there.
Do you have it on you?
Yes.
Lies. I can see that you don't have it on.
She can see?
Be sure to wear it.
Yes.
Make sure you're wearing it.
I'm wearing it.
Are you wearing it?
- I'm wearing it.
- You are? Then the orange juice.
You haven't pressed the orange juice yet.
Make sure to do it properly.
Make sure you press it and bring it.
The way he's holding it.
Hurry up. Make it and bring it. Jeez.
What?
He cut her off.
He cut me off.
The otherwise quiet house is now ringing with the scolding echo of the mother.
Can't be helped. Let's do it.
He usually is happy to help make the juice.
That's why the mother has chosen this to be the errand.
He's a child who doesn't do what he doesn't want to. But does the things he loves.
Round and round and round.
He's even putting ice in there.
Putting in the ice.
The mother said to come back with a full container.
It fills up easier because of the ice but...
There's not enough for a full container.
Yep, a couple drops of lemon juice.
One cup of syrup.
The taste is important.
Hey, don't drink all of it.
The volume is small but it's done.
Starting at 10 o'clock, noon has passed now.
I'm late. I'm late.
He finally came.
You brought it with you?
Here you are.
You did it.
Yuuta, did you do it all by yourself?
Yep.
I'm so glad. Thank you, Yuuta.
We were waiting. Grandpa and grandma too.
Hurry up and let's drink some juice.
- I brought everyone.
- You brought everyone?
I wonder if there is enough for everyone.
There's a sample for everyone. Freshly squeezed orange juice.
- Cheers.
Thank you.
The ice has melted just the right amount.
It's delicious, Yuuta.
I've become invigorated.
They went from scolding him to praising him.
Kagoshima    â—     Soo
To an almost unbelievable extent we've managed to track down an errand genius.
- Can you do it?
- Yes.
He's still only 2 years and 9 months old.
Hiroki
2 years
9 months old.
Amazing. Will he manage it?
And what if a car comes?
- Like this.
- Yes, that's right.
The answer is correct but...
- OK? Go and come back.
- Yes.
Bye bye.
Just saying go and come back. Is that all?
This kid can do it. These are the words
that the mothers believes in.
Anyway, she let him wear his
pew-pew sound-making shoes.
Bye bye.
- Bye bye. Take care.
- Will do.
I wonder if he will be fine.
He found something.
It's a long branch.
I've arrived.
Pardon me saying this, but it looks more like a baby pretending to fish than a child.
Maybe I'll skip fishing and go home.
An ambulance.
An ambulance? No that's not right.
He's not far off.
Fire truck.
That's not it, either.
The brain of a 2 year old is looking for the right word.
Police car.
At that age it takes some time to find the right words.
The bus that he loves is passing by but going the opposite way.
It's a bus.
His word finding skills are in top shape now.
While sightseeing Hiroki has managed to walk a lot.
Moreover, heading straight for the goal.
Truth is, he's attempting an errand that's 1 km one-way.
For someone who is 2 years and 9 months old the distance is quite overwhelming.
TN: Satsuma-age is a fried fishcake from Kagoshima, Japan
That's right, the things he was asked to get by his mother are
sweet curry and Bouten which is a kind of Satsuma-age.
He was also asked to buy flowers to offer his grandma's house altar.
Will he manage to remember all those things?
It has taken 23 minutes for him to arrive at the supermarket.
Which amounts to 2.6 kilometers. That's a great deal.
The door opened but...
it closes again.
It's closing. It will close.
Suddenly distracted.
What was it I came here for? The gears in his head are grinding.
Yes, he was able to make the connection.
I'm here for an errand.
He runs!
The 2 year 9 months old started running.
This doesn't look like curry.
He got the Bouten.
I wonder if the currry is next?
"Please give me the sweet kind."
Would be great if he asked as shop attendant.
Where are the flowers?
He's great!
- Where are the flowers?
- The flowers?
He talked!
Follow me.
Next up are the flowers, I see.
Being able to ask for help properly
is an important thing.
He always buys flowers for Buddha.
The flowers he will offer his grandma are chrysanthemum.
He now realizes that he's supposed to get a basket when shopping in the store.
He isn't carrying so much that he needs a basket.
Can you hold it?
I can hold it.
He want's to do it like he always does.
Is that all?
Yes.
He hasn't purchased the curry yet.
- Fine?
- Yep.
- Alright.
587 yen, please.
He's forgotten all about the sweet curry.
With a 1000 yen bill.
Putting it forward.
Thank you for the 1000 yen.
413 yen. Here you go.
Is it okay? Can I put it directly into your bag?
Hiroki will put it in.
He's putting the change and the receipt in by himself.
Yes. Thank you very much.
What a splendid job. Well done.
He forgot the curry but this will be enough.
There is a long way back as well. Do you best.
One more time. The curry.
He remembered.
I forgot the curry.
It just clicked in his head.
He knows the way to the curry mountain.
He just passed it.
What's wrong?
Despite it being right here.
He has no clue after all.
As I thought that he returns to it.
There are all kinds.
Yes, yes, yes. The sweet one.
The sweet one has the same color as Anpanman's nose.
That's what his mother told him.
I see.
He's bought it all and now it's time to return.
The flowers are too long.
The flower petals will drop.
His nose is already dropping.
TN: In Japanese flowers and nose are homonym and nose dropping means that snot is coming out. It's a play on words.
Now it's time to cross the street.
Now it's time to bring out the flag that his mother has made.
That's so nice.
Like magic, the cars stopped for him.
Thanks to the expression of love from his mother.
Such a great idea.
Mother.
Yes?
Mother, I brought a lot.
You brought it and came back.
About the flowers...
Judging by her reaction the flowers seem to be safe.
First, hand over the receipt.
Just like a real man.
Let's show this to father.
Hiroki, take care of it.
Stand up.
2 years 9 months old and his height is 86 centimeters.
Up until there.
Today they will offer new flowers to grandma.
For the sweet curry they will add sweet Kagoshima Satsuma-age.
Father too grew up on this. Just like how grandma made it.
- Let's say it.
- Thank you for this meal.
The father is eating a huge amount.
Isn't it delicious?
Isn't it good, Hiroki?
I got it! I can buy curry if dad isn't feeling well.
Next up we have someone going on an errand for their own birthday.
Let's present a 4 year old girl.
Aichi â— Okazaki
The town of Okazaki where Tokugawa Ieyasu was born.
Eight blocks (haccho) west from there lies Haccho Village, where Haccho Miso was created.
Here in this duplex resides Maruya-san, a Miso factory which has continued to make Haccho Miso for the past 670 years.
This errand is based upon visiting this traditional miso making village.
Today there is yet another kid who will go on their first errand by themselves.
I found it.
Preparation for pork broth-making.
I want to cut the carrots.
Here is Rikako who will turn 4 today.
Rikako.
4 years old.
Overlooking all the children
there is in fact another mother living in this house.
And next is...
To make pork broth, what else is needed?
- Miso?
- Is there miso? Let's have a look.
Here it comes.
There's not enough miso.
- It's true.
- What will you do?
There is some. The pink stuff.
What?
That? That's not it.
This is not good.
The camera is hidden inside a miso box.
This is miso for konjac.
Good one.
Can you go purchase miso?
- Yep.
- I'm sorry to ask you this but...
The miso we use at home is the golden standard red miso.
Haccho miso uses natural fermentation and has a traditional taste.
It takes longer to ferment and is much harder.
The gold red miso that the mother asked for
is easy to use even for the young ones who love haccho miso mixed with rice miso.
- Gold?
- Tell them: "1 kilogram of gold, please."
Did you get it?
If you look for the old man with the beard he will know.
- Okay.
- Yep.
TN: Tebasaki is fried chicken wings with a sweet and savory glaze.
She was also requested to go get the Nagoya famous Tebasaki.
Because there are many people at home she needs three boxes
and golden red miso.
Because she always goes with her mother Rikako will recognize the company owner.
- He's so recognizable.
- Yeah, easy to remember.
- I'm heading out.
- Please do.
- Yes.
- Please use the umbrella properly.
Don't mind. ♪
Tonight there will be a party for Rikako who is turning 4.
Rikako who is walking full of energy suddenly becomes drained from energy.
The thing that has caught Rikako's eye is
how close the river is from below the guard rail.
She is always told that if you let your voice out then you will feel energized again.
- Hello.
- Hello. What an amazing person.
That made her full of energy again.
Hello.
Rikako who is going on her first errand
on her 4th birthday.
She just arrived at the Nagoya famous Tebasaki shop.
I wonder if it is open.
The door opened but it says they are in the middle of preparation.
Excuse me.
Still preparing.
Yes?
I want 3.
What? Mother? Did you come by yourself?
- What about your mother?
- Mom is at home.
- She isn't here? Really?
- Yep.
Please give me 3 boxes.
So 3 chicken wings of Tebasaki.
You will bring 3 home again?
Yes. I have money.
- You do? Take it out.
- Yes.
1312 yen, please.
Okay.
Just for the people who live nearby they sell at noon as an extra service.
Yes, please wait a bit.
Nagoya famous Tebasaki.
Retaining the juiciness of the meat.
They've just finished frying.
Sprinkling them with salt and pepper
and you just can't resist it.
Wait a little more, okay?
I will make you some delicious ones.
While you are waiting won't you try this?
The way to eat them is with your hands.
Take this one.
I see.
Please try and eat it.
Show everyone at home
that this is how you hold and eat it.
That's right. The meat is parting from the bone.
What a polite child. Thank you.
She arrives at the Maruya-san haccho miso factory.
Different from usual she enters from the factory side entrance.
Is there miso here?
If you want miso then there is a mountains worth of it.
She is entering along with the tour group.
She's listening to the explanation with them.
She's listening.
The special thing about haccho miso is the low water amount after compressing it
So cute.
because of how hard we press, squeeze and drain it.
Next up, let me show you around the way for miso creation.
I see. Haccho miso is amazing.
I didn't know that they made this great miso close to our house.
The weight of the rocks is about 4 tons and about 6 tons of miso is inside.
If you were to purchase a bucket of this miso
in a household of 4 people who will drink miso soup once every day
it will take 205 years before you finish drinking it all.
Wow, 205 years?
Please proceed forward.
What? What's ahead?
What is this? What's inside?
An unknown old lady helps her see inside.
What's up with that? There's nothing in there.
Welcome.
She comes to buy with mom all the time, but she just watched.
That was fun. Alright, I've decided.
She's heading for the office where they usually purchase from.
I wonder if the company owner is there.
Today is so slippery.
Because I came by myself.
It's the first time she has come by herself.
It's not an automatic door.
Make sure to close it properly.
Excuse me. 1 kilogram of miso please.
1 kilo of miso?
Yep.
- What kind of miso would you like?
- Haccho miso.
What? Haccho miso!?
Though she was told to purchase Akadashi she must've been inspired by all the talk about haccho miso.
You have 1200 yen and that's not enough.
I will give you the rest as a present, ok?
Golden red miso is only 1000 yen.
Haccho miso is a bit expensive.
She has to put on a hat since they are going into the factory.
Rinako, did you come by yourself?
That's so great of you.
Today is. Since it's Rikako's birthday.
How old will you be?
- 4 years old.
- 4 years old? That's amazing.
So that's why you came to purchase miso?
That's amazing.
Haccho miso, I wonder what kind of
amazing taste it has.
She is licking the miso.
Lifting the lid for the haccho miso.
It's really hard miso, right?
So this is real haccho miso.
There's so much miso.
- A lot?
- Yep.
It's different from usual.
After hearing the explanation she really wants to dig into it.
Yes, we've gathered 1 kilogram.
Since it is your birthday I want to show you what's inside. Do you want to see?
The very special service from the company owner.
They've entered a place that is outside of the tour route.
There is miso inside of those.
There are stones on top.
Is there miso where the stones are place upon?
Yes, inside of there you will find miso.
Is it made from stones?
So those are edible stones?
You can't eat them. Since they are stones.
Rikako, I want to give you a birthday present.
It's small but...
Do you know this?
Are those stones?
Yes, those are stones. This is wood.
Have a look. It's the same thing.
It's the same thing.
It's your birthday present.
I want to see over there.
Her curiosity switch has been turned on.
The type of stone that is placed above the huge bucket.
I can carry it.
Can you, Rikako?
What?
Do you want to try and taste some miso?
It's a sample.
This is the same as the one you are bringing home today.
Haccho miso. For the mother it's a bit too bitter but it has a nice traditional taste.
- Delicious.
- Is it delicious?
That's right.
What is this?
This is red miso...
It's the name of the requested thing.
- I want to eat it.
- You want to eat it? Okay.
- It's delicious.
- Is it? There's also dengaku miso.
TN: Dengaku miso is good for glazing  vegetables and using in oden.
The last one she gets to try on her observation trip is dengaku.
Is it hot?
Is it delicious?
Alright. Let's go.
Thank you very much to the busy company owner.
I want to eat miso once again.
You wan't to eat once again before going home?
I beg your pardon.
She has now sampled all of the miso.
I'm heading home.
- Will you come back again?
- Yeah.
- Take care of yourself.
- Yep. Bye bye. Yes.
For Rikako the taste of haccho miso remains.
The taste she remembers. The taste of her home town.
Obeying the sign.
She will soon be back home.
I purchased it all.
You purchased it?
I even bought the chicken dish.
Tha- what!? You bought!?
Even miso.
Is it heavy?
Welcome home. Come here.
- Aaah, it was so heavy.
- Was it heavy?
I went to the company owner's place and...
I'm totally worn out.
Thank you so much.
You've helped me out.
What is this?
I mistakenly said haccho miso.
You mistakenly said haccho miso?
Is it alright?
I told you gold.
I remembered but haccho miso is alright.
It's delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?
- It's delicious, right?
- Right.
She's so cute.
What's this?
The house of miso.
Oh, so it's the house of miso.
I see. It's the house of miso.
Inside of this there is miso.
Oh, so the miso is inside.
She understands it properly.
Stones.
Everyone has gathered for the 4 year old's party.
Happy birthday dear Rikako. ♪
Happy birthday to you. ♪
Congratulations!
It's pork broth with haccho miso.
This is the miso that I bought.
- Delicious.
- It's delicious.
Isn't it different from usual?
Haccho miso.
- You bought haccho miso?
- This is haccho miso?
The kid who loves the tebasaki.
Higa, you are wrong.
About this thing, you see?
Without grasping it with chopsticks, you just hold it and eat it.
She learned it properly.
If you don't know then let me teach do it for you.
Here?
I will do it for you. Even for Macchan.
Ah, it came out. Is that it?
That's it.
Will you eat Rikako?
Go ahead and eat.
What a great ending.
Seeing the smiles of children and becoming energized.
It surely is a great thing.
The staff is gathering all their energy.
For the June 18th broadcast aimed at Ocean Day.
Let's look forward to the "Summer Big Adventure Special".