My First Errand -
Don't be disheartened baby special.
We are showing this today as a special thing.
To give strength to the disheartened kids.
Miyagi ● Sendai
First off
In east Japan after the great earthquake, Ritsuki was born.
Ritsuki
3 years 5 months
Both his parents are beauticians.
Ritsuki has been independent since birth.
And they made a shop called Avenire which is French for future.
Avenir
How fancy.
Future
They redid the interior after the great earthquake with the help of an acquaintance, Taira-san.
He's also a member in a cheering squad.
Mr. Taira
Filmed in 2016
The father was invited by Taira to join their cheering squad.
From the soft world of a beautician
As a beautician, he comes from a gentle world...
Father
He wants to be regarded as cool by his kids
The reason for the formation of the squad...
(Volunteer force in Miyagi prefecture)
Team Shovel
The "team shovel" which was created during the aftermath of the 2011 tsunami
who brought their support in a time of need.
That's when the group leader Taira thought: "We need some encouragement."
Blue sky cheering squad
That's when he formed the "Blue sky cheering squad".
They will go wherever they've been requested to.
Hospitals, festivals and weddings.
It's because when someone has someone rooting for them, they can show extraordinary strength.
And it's not just the dad. The entire family is putting their heart into the "Blue sky cheering squad".
Ritsuki
Ritsuki's dream is to be part of the blue sky cheering squad.
So he wants to be part of it.
He's always scampering around so his nickname is "scampy".
Like his father he's not good at raising his voice.
"But in order to cheer up others he has to learn to do better."
That's what his parents have decided.
His brother has already gone on an errand alone.
Brother
Ruito
Today is the 6th birthday of his beloved big brother.
And as a secret to celebrate his brother...
the "blue sky cheering squad" will come.
Ah! He has a bruise on his forehead.
Oh no.
He wore his shoes on the wrong foot and started running.
Wonder if brobro will be happy.
Um.
For today Ritsuki will also
be joining the cheering squad.
How nice.
What haircut will he settle on?
He's full of vigor.
So cute.
How cool.
And with this along with Taira and the cheering squad...
His father has prepared clothes for the cheering squad.
Pants and... ah!
There is no jacket.
The important jacket is missing.
You better bring it.
Filmed in 2016.
This is...
Oh no. That's no good.
Since I have to cut the customers' hair...
And we begin...
Ritsuki, can you go?
All by myself?
He's getting it at his home.
Mama is at home so...
I can't do it by myself.
Yes, you can. You've ridden the bus so many times already.
Going by bus?
So he's going by bus.
It's fine.
Just like his dad.
I can't cheer without a jacket.
Ritsuki, don't you want to cheer Ruito?
I do.
But I will feel lonely.
They are both trying to persuade each other through subdued mutterings.
Boys will be boys.
And then...
Dad will give you an encouraging cheer...
His father has become decisive.
Yo!
Heeeeey.
Heee-eeey.
Ri-tsu-kiii.
Now he can do his best.
Aaaand... Hey! Hey!
Ritsuki.
Hey! Hey!
Ri-tsu-kiiiiiiiiii.
His face changed.
Right, really, really....
Yo!
Can you go by yourself?
His tone went down a lil...
Beauty parlor
Home
Nishinakayama
Across the road from the store
he will ride the bus towards Nishinakayama.
Get off on the last stop and get the jacket from his home.
That's tough.
See you.
Off you go.
A father-son that are like peas in a pod.
I will be working then.
The one sending off...
understands how the one being sent-off feels.
Bye bye.
He's hesitating.
Alright. Off he goes.
Oh. He's running.
The bus stop is across the road from the beauty parlor.
His father tried to time it with the bus timetable.
And Ritsuki should make it just in time however...
But looking at the timetable again...
The first bus to arrive will not be the right one.
Oh no.
A bus that won't reach home.
- Oh no.
- No good.
Kitanakayama
Kitanakayama Nishinakayama
Zanezawa eigyoujyo
The next one is going to Zanezawa
but to get home he needs to ride the bus to Nishinakayama.
- That's bad.
- He's definitely gonna board it.
You shouldn't board the next bus.
Of course he can't read the destination on the bus.
Would be good if he asked the driver. But he's not good at letting out his voice.
- Looks bad.
- What will he do?
Excuse me.
Are you heading to Nishinakayama?
Ah, good job!
Nishinakayama?
Yeah.
I'm sorry but I'm not.
Dad, Ritsuki was able to ask loud and clear.
He didn't board it indeed.
He did it.
What a relief.
Truth is that he's been playing "bus pretend" in the bath with his brother.
His brother takes the role of the driver.
And Ritsuki is the passenger.
And he will say: "Going to Nishiyama?"
Excuse me.
Are you going to Nishiyama?
Excuse me. Nishiy...
Please wait.
The bus driver went as far as getting off the bus.
I am going to Nishiyama.
Please touch this thing.
He's going as far to teach him how to ride.
How kind.
Touch here and then sit...
He's even showing him a place to sit.
How kind.
He boarded it.
Filmed in 2016
Just like the bus driver requested.
He's holding on tight to the handrail.
He's nervous.
He isn't scampering around today.
Today he isn't even wearing his shoes on the wrong foot.
That's great.
Needs to go 10 bus stops.
But since it's the last stop he doesn't need to hit the stop button.
He's riding while quietly listening to the driver.
Thank you for riding.
Last stop. Nishinakayama.
This is the last stop.
Please touch here.
He's even teaching him how to disembark.
Thank you very much.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
How remarkable.
He's letting out his voice today.
"After the bus ride I'm counting on you."
That's what his dad said over the phone.
Will he be like: "I want to go back with mom?"
Huh?
Huh? Ricchi what's up?
You see...
I'm busy.
You're busy?
The jacket.
Jacket?  What's up with the jacket?
There it was. Daddy totally forgot it.
Yeah.
He's no good.
He's no good... hahaha
See Ricchi.
Isn't it cool?
Yeah.
It's cool.
His mom, is making sure to encourage Ritsuki.
If it's too big then you should wear your own.
No, it's small.
It's huge.
You can lift your spirits.
Aaaaaah.
Aaa-aaand
Go!
Aa-and
go!
Cheer-ing squad
With the jacket his grandmother made he has powered up.
I clawed you.
Beauty parlor
Choumeigaoka sanchoume nishi
Home
The way back also has five bus routes, so he must ask if the bus will stop near the salon.
Will he be able to say: Choumeigaokasanchoumenishi?
That's difficult.
Hey hey.
One more time, what bus was it again?
Choumeigaokasanchoumenishi
...choumenishi
Did you get it?
Yep.
Off you go.
It will be difficult from this point on.
Do your best.
But in this outfit he will definitely give it his all.
- How cool.
- Amazing. Looks like he's going into battle.
At the crossing there are flags left there.
Ah, he has his own.
He will use his own?
The flag of the cheering squad.
His mother made it by hand.
Amazing.
The scampering Ritsuki is appearing to us like an entirely different person.
For real.
Can he?
Excuse me.
Are you going to Choumeigaoka sanchoume nishi?
He said it.
We go that way. Please board.
He said it properly.
And what he learned before?
To present the card.
This time he was asked to ride behind the driver.
Look look. He's properly holding on to the handrail.
Both his parents said: "Do your best."
And therefor Ritsuku has become more reliable than usual.
It's not the last stop so you better press the button.
The big birthday cake sign is the landmark visible from the bus.
Next is Choumeigaoka Sanchoume West.
There. It's even being announced.
It's there.
There. You better press it.
Did he become sleepy?
Become sleepy?
An old lady is getting off.
How great.
The bus stopped at Choumeigaoka Sanchoume West.
Oh no. You should get off.
Are you not getting off?
What a relief.
Better listen to the driver.
We are at Choumeigaoka Sanchoume West.
Thank you very much.
How great.
He was taught to get off.
Yes. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
How great.
Dad has been starring at the bus stop the entire time.
He's worried.
Daddy. Yahoo.
He's so tiny.
Welcome back.
Daddy, it was there.
Thank you.
You did well while going by yourself.
Were you scared.
Yep.
Were you sad?
But you were able to go by yourself.
Now dad can be part of the Blue Skies Cheering Squad.
Ritsuki.
Thank you.
Cool.
And now they are about to cheer his brother on for his birthday.
Let's make it the best birthday for him.
With squad leader Taira in front Blue Skies have gathered.
Yo.
Seeing the Blue Skies Cheering Squad up close.
Filmed in 2016.
Let's do our best.
It carries a punch.
Yo.
He'll cry.
He's slightly intimidated.
It carries too much of a punch.
Alright. It's beginning now.
The mother is bringing his brother.
The squad leader has deferred dad to be in the center position.
Yo!
Yo.
Ruito 6th year birthday.
What a nice smile
Let's do this.
Heeeeey.
Heeeeeeey.
Ru-iiii-to.
And a...
Hey. Hey. Ruito.
Ruito do your best.
Do your best.
Hey. Yo!
Yo.
Ritsuki and his cherished Blue Skies Cheering Squad
has made a cheer regarding the novel Corona virus.
Blue Skies Cheering Squad
Blue Skies Cheering Squad's
broadcasted cheer
Everyone. We must endure a lot right now.
This is a cheer for everyone who is persevering.
We must endure a lot.
This is a cheer for everyone
who is persevering.
That's right. And we will now broadcast you a video from Ritsuki.
A video from Ritsuki.
Photographer: Mommy.
Are you done changing?
Ritsuki.
Pakari.
In second year of elementary school.
Ritsuki
2nd year elem. school.
He has outgrown the jacket from back then.
How is it? Is it small?
It's small.
Where is it tight?
My arms.
He's 26 cm. taller now.
Pictured: 3 years
and 5 months
He is 120 cm tall and weighs 21 kilograms now.
To not lose to the novel Corona virus
Ruito
4th year
elem. school.
he is going to send a cheer with his brother.
Yo.
We are about to start the cheer for everybody.
Heey.
Eee-ve-ry-body.
Hey hey. Everybody.
Everybody. Let's do our best.
Ooooh!
Thanks for the motivation boost.
Fukui ● Echizen Town
We've arrived at Fukui in the coast of Sea of Japan.
Filmed in 1996.
The owner of this sushi shop is very strict when it comes to serving Echizen crabs as sashimi.
Father
But he has a sweet spot for his eldest son, Iori.
Iori
3 years
6 months old
And Iori knows that quite well.
Iori come here.
This is Iori and his first errand.
Iori. Ask grandpa
for crabs. Get the best one.
That's right. Crabs are counted with the modifier "pai".
'K? Can you do it?
Can you go?
He can't?
Crab fish tank
Grandpa
Shop
400 meters down the same street to get grandpas to take him to the crab fish tank.
That's what the entire errand.
"I told you, I can't go daddy."
Can you go if I hug you once?
His dad is so soft on him.
And then you will go?
His mothers eyes are shining.
Please.
Why can't you go?
Will you get lonely?
Getting lonely?
Mother
The mother is an Echizen woman. She's tough on her husband.
She grabbed him.
Leave him be.
He's not going because you are putting it that way.
You are so soft.
It's beginning. The usual fight.
Fulfill your duty seriously.
Leave him alone if you want him to go.
Hope they will forget all about the errand.
Please leave him be, dad.
You are not allowed to speak.
Now that they went each their own way it means that daddy is coming.
Iori. Go and come back!
His dad changed his way.
There is no one who can go but you Iori.
That's right.
Carry this. Yes.
Iori.
Will you not listen to your father?
That's right. That's right.
You.
Go and come back.
Did you get it?
Alright?
I want you to go.
Carrying him? Isn't that bad, dad?
Treating Iori like a baby.
He's taking him to where his mother can't see.
Ok? I'm begging you.
If you listen to your daddy
I will take you to your favorite place.
Right? Go and get the crabs. Listen to your daddy.
No good dad.
Got it?
This is a test of endurance for the father.
But hey Iori. Dad is different today from his usual self.
He will quit it eventually.
He will come to get him back, right?
Huh? You are still lingering around?
Worried of a grinning mother.
What is she doing?
I will lend you the sword, Iori, since you are a scaredy cat.
You're not strong, are you?
Do you want the sword?
Will you take the sword?
It's Iori's cherished sword.
He will likely grow strong as soon as she gives it to him.
Take the sword. How cool.
Won't you be a man, Iori?
Will you go? Won't you?
I won't. I won't.
TN: They are speaking in a heavy dialect and this time the narrator is mimicking him thus the faint studio laugh.
I will be watching you.
For his first errand his mother must battle it out with him.
I don't wanna.
Only babies want to be held and hold hands.
A baby after all.
His mother withdrew her hands.
If she holds out her hands here he will want to be cuddled even further.
His mother knows that.
The kind smell of his mothers apron.
You will be laughed at by babies like a baby.
But today is different.
Then you can't be a big brother.
It's no good hitting her.
Nor is hugging her.
Or flailing and making a scene.
Go!
I won't let you back in.
Look forward and walk.
While withdrawing her hands his mother thinks of a new strategy.
I...
If you walk over to that electric pole
then I will walk right behind you.
Look forward and walk.
She will make him walk a little more and more by himself.
Ah, you arrived.
And without forgetting to praise him.
Huh? You've walked this far?
Where's home? Iori's home.
You've walked so much.
Go the yellow circle next.
Go.
It's just a bit more until the yellow circle.
Go!
- He's not going.
- Not going.
Go!
Oh, just a bit more.
Your feet are outside of it. Go to the middle .
Alright.
She keeps her promise.
See? I actually came.
Hehe. He has started having fun.
Next... next, go to where that line is...
And like that Iori's mother increased the distance bit by bit.
For his first errand his mother's strategy is necessary.
His grandfather should be at the seashore at this time.
Cross. Iori cross.
Alright. He went.
He's alright now.
Echizen women are strict with their boys.
Brother.
But she's also kind.
Grandpa.
He's running.
Crab. Crab. Crab.
Iori. What's up?
Crab.
I am here to get crabs.
Wow.
Were you told to collect crabs?
Yes, I was.
But for grandpa
it might be a bit difficult.
But you came to grandpa, didn't you?
I'm getting the one in the back.
You will?
Yeah, see.
Like you were told by grandpa, right?
This one is huge.
He grabbed it with his hands.
Aren't you scared?
One crab is 20.000 yen.
He was asked to only bring one crab.
But you can't carry it.
It's fine with just this one.
I don't just want that.
I was told to get many crabs.
TN: The counter for (1) crab (ippai) makes it sound like many (ippai).
One (/Many)? That would mean one.
We better get more crabs.
Otherwise my mom won't be glad.
You want to make her happy?
This one is small.
He intends to bring the biggest ones.
This one is huge.
This one is the biggest one.
An even bigger crab than the previous one.
He's not afraid of the pincers.
As expected from a child of the seashore.
Heave-ho​. Heave-ho.
I bet it's heavy.
Big brother. Big brother.
I wonder if mom will be happy.
He's happy with himself.
Despite crying so much on the way there.
Did he forget it all? Even the thing about the yellow circle.
It's fine. I can go by myself.
It's fine.
As long as Iori has his sword he's someone to be feared.
It's fine. It's fine.
Even the customers are waiting for Iori's crabs.
You came back.
You came back?
He came back.
It took him 5 minutes to walk back.
Welcome back.
You are such a well-behaved boy.
Bring it to dad.
Dad...
said 1 crab so why did you bring 2?
One crab / many?
About the crab
get 1 / many.
Didn't dad say to get many?
What a good boy.
Don't gush all over me, mom.
I am a big brother after all.
They also sent a phone video from Iori's.
Filmed 2020 April 14th
His father has it rough.
Dad
Mom
Because of the novel Corona
at our place
we've had about 300 cancellations from March to April.
I hesitated towards doing my best
despite the bleak outlook.
But now I've decided to put my all towards what I'm doing right now.
I just
don't want to lose this fight.
I don't want to lose to Corona. That's my intention.
Iori is a company worker in Tokyo.
At home in Tokyo
He is 27 and lives alone.
Even though you have a cup.
Haha, that's right.
No no. He has a girlfriend.
She's the one filming.
He washes his hands and gargles as a precaution against Corona.
I am working at home.
And this type of work
is remote work on my computer.
And even today I had meetings where...
When he saw the accounting at his father's shop
he studied accounting at university and now works for a consulting firm.
He's practiced, gotten 6 years of experience, and continued to improve.
Filmed by: Iori
We only get to meet his girlfriend from behind.
My girlfriend is cleaning.
You see...
A messy room is a messy heart.
Yeah.
You look at it constantly and think
Yep.
This is no good. The room is a mess.
A perfect match for Iori.
The mother has decided.
Mother
To create an errand on her day of giving birth.
How surprising.
Ibaraki ● Jyousou city
The city has a large expatriate population from Brazil, and many of the city signs are in both Japanese and Portuguese.
2 months before the expected date.
We met with them at the beginning of the summer.
The mother had a single worry.
Filmed in 1996.
About Hideki who is the middle child of 3.
Who is a kind and easy to comprehend boy.
Hideki
4 years 10 months
As the mother's stomach grows larger,
She's worried he'll become jealous of the attention given to the baby.
And that's why his mother decided
to put him on an errand on the day of the birth.
Hideki
4 years 10 months
Natsuki
1 year 11 months
An errand for the baby.
Something that will change Hideki as a big brother.
And suddenly the contractions began.
"Hideki, your mother is giving it her all so let's all do our best."
That's what his father told him.
And then it happened while the kids were at the pool.
Predicting this his mother made a phone guide.
If you Use this to get to the hospital.
And his father hurried to the hospital from his workplace.
It's the dad. He can't know when the actual birth will take place.
Father
It's a crucial time.
And he asked the kids to jump on a taxi and ride to the hospital.
And that's the errand that his mother thought up.
The kids should be back by now.
Hideki and his little sister Natsuki.
Hello?
Hideki. It's dad. Mom still hasn't given birth...
Yep.
but the baby will be born soon so
can you call a taxi and ride it here?
Yep.
Next to the TV
your mother's maternity health record book can be found.
She forgot her maternity health book.
She needs it while giving birth.
Found it.
Can you bring it with Natsuki?
I can.
Natsuki is still only 1 years old.
Do you know where to find the wallet?
His mother's wallet. They will need money.
It's in her bag.
And then there is a basket. For carrying the baby in.
Yeah.
Natsuki only has to follow along.
Baby basket.
Then call the taxi. I'm relying on you.
Father, son and mother.
This is the beginning of their fight.
This is Hideki's first time calling for a taxi.
Thanks for calling. This is Kantetsu Taxi.
I see.
Please send a taxi.
Alright. We will be there soon.
He was able to call for a taxi.
Hideki is doing it properly.
And closing off the house.
Alright.
- Wow. Remarkable.
- Remarkable.
And he put shoes on his sister Natsuki.
And locked the front door.
We've asked for permission to film from the taxi company
and we've placed cameras in the car.
Thank you very much.
Natsuki is not good with strangers.
Especially old guys. She won't talk with them.
It's fine.
The driver came from the city over.
It's his first time coming to this residence.
We have not told him where to go.
We only asked him to go where the kids tell him to.
Hey, don't cry, Natsuki.
Were are we going?
My mother is
giving birth therefore
both of us are going there.
Which hospital?
It's called Shoujisensei...
Do you know where?
I will teach you.
Thank you.
This is the first time for him to go to this hospital.
Home
Hospital
Hideki has gone to this hospital several times with his mother.
How well does he remember?
At the place called Kobayashi Store
there's a traffic light.
And go straight from there.
Straight ahead?
Ah, I forgot the basket.
The basket for the newborn.
You need to bring the basket?
Oh no.
Then we need to go back and get it, right?
I see. A baby has been born?
Yeah.
It looks like she's about to be born.
That's right. At the hospital...
the mother hasn't given birth yet.
The brother went to bring the basket.
Huh? She's not crying.
Natsuki who is timid towards strangers. s
The basket that will be used when leaving the hospital.
About 13 km to the hospital.
If everything goes well they will be there in 15 minutes.
Alright. Passed the Kobayashi store.
We could also go this way.
Which way?
Straight ahead.
Straight ahead?
Looks like the contractions are getting stronger.
The child will be here soon so please hang in there.s
Huh?
If I continue straight, will we hit it?
That's right.
TN: He meant to say "Un so" (Mhm, that's right), but his nervousness made it sound like "Uso" (I lied). That's why the narrator is asking him if he's alright.
You okay? Hideki.
Should I call them?
Just before the birth.
They are parting now.
The mother insisted on walking there by herself.
Amazing.
Remarkable.
The strong father can't be of any help today.
Turn this way.
Turning this way?
This is a narrow road.
That's right.
But we have to go this way, right?
If we go this way it will be even closer.
I know it all.
Really? They've driven for more than 20 minutes.
They should've been there by now.
I've seen a show on TV about going on errands by yourself.
And after seeing this I wanted to do my best
and that's why I'm doing it.
I see.
We are getting closer.
Is that really the case?
We decided that I first
Rice ball coated with sweetened red beans, soybean flour or sesame​
must go purchase a bald.
A (rice) ball?
A bald.
What's a bald?
A bald is
it's like a coated rice ball.
Who will eat the bald?
Mommy.
Ah, I see. Your mother.
His mother never asked for a rice ball.
The battle has started inside.
His father is nervously moving like the second hand while waiting.
The baby is about to be born.
Despite there not being a moment to spare, Hideki...
We decided that I first
must go purchase a bald.
A (rice) ball?
A bald.
What's a bald?
A bald is
it's like a coated rice ball.
Who will eat the bald?
Mommy.
Ah, I see. Your mother.
Can you wait?
His sister Natsuki has fallen silent.
Can you wait, Natsuki?
Even though he wasn't asked Hideki has decided to purchase rice balls.
It's fine here.
Is it fine here?
It's a shop.
They will have rice balls and dango, you see.
I will be looking after her, then.
Natsuki is not getting off.
Your brother will be back soon, okay?
Natsuki and an old guy.
Only today she has no major problem.
Hideki why are you worried about rice balls at this time?
If you don't hurry then Natsuki will cry.
The driver thought of a topic.
The brother talked about a baby. It would be nice if it was a girl, right?
Then both of you will be able to play.
She's answering a bit.
Excuse me.
Where do you have bald?
Huh? What? Ah, rice balls?
We don't have any rice balls.
They don't have rice balls?
Is it about to happen?
Still? Still?
Just a bit more.
He can't stand it here and there.
My mother is about to give birth
to a baby
and her breasts
need to produce milk
so I am here to purchase bald.
TN: Imitating Hideki he calls them bald on purpose.
That's why he's looking for "bald".
Hideki is kind after all.
Then...
For the baby
milk will come out.
From the breasts...
She will eat it to produce breast milk, right?
Hideki has learned that
when Natsuki was still a baby.
That's what his mother would often say while eating rice balls.
Rice cake stuffed with bean jam
Will daifuku do?
Daifuku. They share the mochi and anko qualities.
He decided to get daifuku instead of rice balls.
Ah... mh... did.
Daddy did? Papa?
Natsuki started talking.
Papa called on the phone.
Ah, I see. That's what he said.
I don't understand it that well.
That'll be 306 yen please.
Alright hurry. You got the daifuku.
I will splish-splash.
What will you splash? The pool?
The bath.
The bath? I see.
He's able to understand.
Will you take a bath?
I might also take a bath.
When I sweat or before sleep.
Did you take one?
Today?
I haven't taken one yet.
How nice.
While Hideki went shopping
the old guy and Natsuki were exchanging pleasantries.
He's back.
Hideki doesn't know about that.
Since your brother wants to get on can you move this way?
Since he...
If the guy says so.
The purchase has been made. Better hurry.
It will say Shouji Hospital
on the sign.
Their father in the hospital.
Not yet.
Huh. Around here?
This is Shouji Hospital.
Sorry for doubting you, Hideki.
40 minutes have passed since they left the house.
And for me...
It will be 5690 Yen.
A 5000 Yen bill.
And then 690 Yen.
Truth be told, it was supposed to be only 2000 Yen.
Thank you very much.
But it's great that they've arrived.
Alright. Don't forget the basket.
And this?
And her?
Natsuki.
You better follow him.
I will go on this.
Papa.
No, I don't want to go.
The old guy is here.
Will you not go to where papa is?
I will go.
You will go?
Then get off.
You can't go if you don't get off.
Don't wanna.
Why?
Here.
Maybe I can help you get off.
Get off with me.
If the old guy says so...
And that.
You can't forget what is good for the breasts.
Their father and mother are waiting.
Hey, Natsuki.
The old guy...
...left?
The bath loving old guy.
Natsuki come here.
Father, just a bit more.
I brought Natsuki.
You managed to do it.
Well done.
Hey. Thank you.
Thank you. Natsuki.
Hey, thank you.
You came.
Was it fine? You did great.
And then...
16:23. Their little sister was born.
Still warm from the birth.
The mother did well too.
With its 4180 gram quite a big baby.
It's a baby.
Natsuki's baby.
My baby.
What's this. It's big.
See right there. A baby. It's so big.
It's my baby.
So tiny.
She's tiny?
She's smaller than me.
Her legs are small.
Natsuki will splash-splash into the bath with her new baby sister.
It's cool inside.
She's cute no matter which way she looks.
With this we will be 4 people.
Mother.
Thank you for enduring the hardships, mother.
Thanks for your hard work.
And you too Hideki.
Hideki is suddenly embarrassed and can't look at his mother.
Go to your mother.
Oh yeah. Better give the mochi.
Yes, the mochi...
Until yesterday he has been jealous of the baby she carried.
Sorry, mother.
You did your best, Hideki, and came in a taxi.
Your mother also did her best.
Everyone, everyone did their best.
Natsuki also did her best.
You bought this?
One is fine.
Can I try it?
It's delicious.
How great.
It's really delicious.
Thank you kindly.
She can use it for her breasts.
The breast milk for both the baby and mother.
Really, thank you.
The former Japanese soccer representative Yoshito Ookubo.
The striker that carries a number 13 on their shirt.
And in the J.League
he has been the top scorer 3 years in a row.
Amazing.
Good morning.
At home he is a kind child rearing papa.
3rd son Touri
And...
Alright.
Your hat.
He waits every day to pick up his 3rd son, Touri.
Filmed in 2016
And when they get home...
The first, second and third son.
He plays with his three sons every day for several hours.
A year prior to that at the Ookubo residence.
A big thing happened.
Rie (wife)
His wife, Rie, had a miscarriage.
And then naturally.
Ookubo and his three sons shaved their heads.
I see.
"Don't worry!" He said in encouragement to his wife.
What a reliable husband.
And since this incident a year has passed.
And the subject of the errand wil be...
Rie
A 4th...
Yes.
- How great.
- Joyous.
I still haven't told people around me.
Even the kids don't know.
Yes, we haven't even told the 3 brothers.
Con-gra-tu-lations.
Ultrasound from week 11
Truth be told, from the complication a year ago
they were told that it might be complicated to become pregnant again.
Kanagawa ● Yokohama
And then on the day of the errand.
They announced to their sons about the coming baby.
Alright. Take a seat.
Papa go first.
Very exciting.
I will announce it.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Aito
Ryokuji
Touri
Are you ready?
YES.
You know that mama has been feeling sick lately.
And the reason for that.
Mama,
inside of her belly
a baby
has appeared.
has appeared. Really.
Touri will be a brother.
- They did it.
- What a celebration.
Amazing.
Why are you sulking.
What's wrong?
He wants to be a big brother
but he has to become a big brother first.
A complicated mental state.
I see. That's what struck him.
Usually he's the spoiled child who clings to his father.
And with the timing of him knowing he will be a big brother
they have thought up an errand for him.
His two brothers have left.
Get up.
Stand here.
Today they will have a home party.
That will absolutely not be enough.
It's not enough meat.
Not enough.
The families of his teammates will amount to 10 people coming.
Pizza and salad won't be sufficient.
They will want meat no matter what since they are pro sports players.
We better have meat.
Wait.
We don't need it.
They haven't reached talks about the errand and he's already opposing it.
They will be 10 people.
- He caught on.
- His face shows he caught on.
Kids like you Touri and...
For the kids this
will be enough but
what will us fathers do?
His father still hasn't said "Touri, go and purchase the meat."
Mama, can't you go and purchase it?
I can't right now. Not feeling too well and everyone is coming in a bit.
Then we better not purchase any.
Huh? Is that the conclusion you've come to?
His father has had enough.
He stopped.
Can I take a rest?
Yes, please do.
Will we make it?
We won't.
Touri, what will you do?
I can't go by myself.
He understood it without being asked.
Wait wait, Touri.
What if you bring Mr. Grasshopper.
Then you won't be alone.
He will go on an errand with a grasshopper?
How about it?
Talk with the grashopper about it. Ask if he wants to join you.
No way that this is all it takes.
Okay.
This grashopp...
Eh? He will go?
With the grasshopper. Both of you go.
- Eh?
- Nice grasshopper.
Tell him to join you.
No way.
As expected. The grasshopper trick didn't work.
Oh no.
If papa and mama join then I can go.
Mama definitely can't.
Yet tears are not forming.
This looks promising.
What should be done, dad?
So... Touri, what will you do now?
You better show it to the new baby.
How about showing them?
"What a cool brother."
"Touri bro, is so cool."ß
Right, Touri?
Yep.
Amazing response.
He stopped crying.
He wants to become a big brother after all.
Here
Sanpachi train is right here.
Sanpachi is a restaurant he often frequents with his teammates.
They will order grilled meat to-go from there.
And how will he order it?
Do you have meat?
Meat.
Will be be able to remember?
Tell them "salted tongue".
Salted tongue.
That's difficult.
5 pieces of salted tongue.
Basil marinated chicken neck.
That is just too much.
Yes, 5 of those.
And what is papa's favorite?
There's still more?
Extremely spicy intestines.
Will he be able to remember that?
Okay?
What's up with that.
Wear this sports shirt.
A tiny nr. 13 shirt.
This one which you got with me the other day.
When he wears this shirt
he will feel as strong as his papa.
His father is writing a message on the good-luck charm.
If you get lonely then look at this.
You-can-do-it.
Touri, you can do it.
And his mother who pretended to fall asleep on the couch will secretly follow him.
You recently went to the cake shop with your mother.
Do you remember the cake your mother ate? The sweet and sour one.
A shortcake.
Can't you purchase one for mama?
Okay.
If the baby is a girl
can you ask them if they havea pink artificial flower.
His dad noticed they sell pink flowers at the cake shop.
What a kind dad.
Then mama will be so delighted.
Off you go.
Cake shop
Home
Yakiniku shop
Take-out at the restaurant: Salted tongue, basil marinated chicken necks and spicy intestines.
At the cake shop a short cake and a flower for his mom.
There's so much.
She will be so delightfully surprised.
Alright, off you go.
Remarkable.
Amazing.
Touri is full of energy.
Alright. Today he's going on an errand by himself.
His father went out.
Don't lose.
He wants to say something.
What now?
What?
Don't lose, Touri.
Eh?
What?
Touri, go!
Eh?
Touri pretends not to hear him and returns.
- Oh no.
- This is on the dad.
What?
Even though he was already on his way.
You were doing great.
You were doing great. How far did you get?
How far did you get?
All the way there.
Amazing. You went all the way there.
We're relying on you.
Touri, do your best.
Alright, this time...
Alright, do your best.
He left.
He left again. Amazing.
Don't lose.
Um.
He's doing totally fine.
Wouldn't it be better if he got back quick?
Got a point there.
He's still peeking out.
See? Now he's heading back.
Papa I'm getting tired.
What?
Don't engage him in a conversation.
See? He returned.
Papa.
What?
I'm getting tired.
He's piling on the excuses.
And what if my butt gets wet?
It won't get wet.
See?
If you hold the umbrella then it won't.
My butt won't get wet.
Yeah, you have a raincoat on.
His butt won't get wet.
Touri, we are relying on you.
Papa can't go so please do it.
Yep.
Do your best, Touri.
Touri, don't lose.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Dad, hurry back.
Touri, see you. Do your best.
Just go. Go.
- And papa, you go too.
- Hurry and go, papa.
Papa is in the way.
He finally went back into the house.
Alright. It will be fine from now on.
What's wrong.
I forgot something.
I don't know the name of the meats.
That's true. Remember the names was a bit too difficult.
Papa.
Huh, what's wrong?
I haven't bought anything yet but...
I don't know.
Let's go outside.
But that's also an excuse.
I want to go with papa.
Papa and...
I can't leave now. Everyone will soon...
I told them that Touri will go and buy the meat.
You are fine.
Say it.
Are you too scared to say it?
Unless papa... can't...
Look. What does it say?
He's just lacking a bit of courage.
I want to go with papa.
What does it say?
Can...
Do it.
His tears stopped.
Touri, you can do it. Do your best.
Ah, he's sucking on his finger.
But his legs...
are moving forward. Take a look.
Alright. Alright.
Touri, do your best.
I want my mama.
He wants his mom.
He's not up for it today.
I don't know.
I have to go defeat the monster.
Monster?
I need to beat it up so you can come back.
It's still there.
I will use the umbrella.
Beat it with an umbrella?
I'm relying on you.
I want to see it.
He wants to see the monster?
What are they even doing?
The monsters. It's calling me.
No no no. It's fine.
So he can speak with the monster over the phone?
Touri, do your best.
Let's defeat it.
- What's up with the pretend.
- He's pretending so hard.
Yep.
Dad, please defeat the monster.
- What was that.
- A phone call from the monster.
Running at full speed.
Alright. He's off.
Dad, isn't there something you must do?
You better go fight the monster.
If he can get past the first intersection, he's all set, dad explained.
We beg of you, Touri. Please go for real this time.
It's fine.
He crossed.
He's so great. He will be fine.
He finally left.
Touri, does he resemble his dad?
Who does Touri ressemble?
Or his mom?
That's me.
Which part?
He can do it but he doesn't have the courage.
Like with me he will worry: Will I be fine?
Ah, it's getting dark outside.
It really is.
In no time the sun has set and it's approaching twilight.
Surely they are worried if Touri is doing fine?
But he seems to remember the directions.
And crossing the street properly.
He really is.
I don't know the name of the meats.
He doesn't know, yeah. His dad's order is too complex.
I don't know.
Salted tongue, basil marinated chicken neck and extremely spicy intestines.
Though he doesn't remember he enters the store.
What will he do?
At the entrance there is a wall of autographs from patrons.
His father is also a regular customer.
What type of meat do you have?
He could also do it like that.
Did you come to buy meat?
He intends to make the waiter cite all the types of meat.
If he hears it he will remember.
Will he notice the three options in between?
The assistant manager who knows his dad well came out.
I will start with the ones that your papa likes.
If it's one of those then say "yeah", okay?
It's starting now.
Basil marinated
chicken neck
Extremely spicy
instestines
Salted tongue
Did he mention "Basil marinated chicken neck?"
He did.
He got the first one right.
Alright. Alright.
And then what else...
What about marinated ribs?
It's a pass.
He didn't get it.
And your father likes salted tongue. Did he bring that up?
He did.
A splendid hit.
There's still more?
The last one is difficult.
Is it sweet? Or spicy? Do you know?
It's spicy.
Great piece of info.
I see.
If it's something your dad likes then... intestines?
He did say that.
He said that.
How splendid.
Is that all?
He got them all right.
For how many people?
So you want 5 of each?
Yep.
He was able to get it out of him.
He remembered the amount.
He's getting 5 of each so they are preparing food for 15 people.
That's amazing.
Touri, do you want to have a drink?
You really did well.
He really did.
He said that there's a monster.
There's a monster? At home?
- There's a monster.
- The scare worked.
Papa will beat up the monster.
He will beat up the monster? Papa?
He was able to grasp the situation.
I see.
Since papa is fighting him then Touri also needs to do his best.
He's so great a peptalk.
It's done cooking now.
Be careful. See you again.
See you again.
How great. He's a nice guy.
Bye bye.
Do your best.
I will.
It started raining.
The rain became more intense. Hurry up and get home.
I must buy cake.
Oh that's right. That's right.
His father asked him to do it as a secret.
For his mother and the baby she's carrying.
How nice.
He better go.
I will leave it here.
His raincoat is drenched from the rain.
Thinking it would be bad to drip in the shop. What a good boy.
He's so thoughtful.
He's only bringing in the wallet.
Welcome.
What?
Huh? What's wrong?
He forgot what type of cake.
What was it again?
Touri needs to psyche himself up for the moment.
Good evening.
Without being prepared...
the shop door opened up to him.
Did you come to buy a cake?
Yep.
What did you come to buy?
He's in trouble.
Short cake.
He suddenly remembered.
The sweet and sour strawberry cake.
Who will eat it?
Mama.
Because she said that she's nauseous...
so she wants something sweet.
Can she eat cake despite not feeling well?
But she's not actually sick.
Yep.
So she's fine.
The lady totally thinks that she's sick.
TN (written): Mama, hurry up and be well. From Touri.
He noticed something.
That thing.
The flowers his dad mentioned.
I will buy this.
This?
It's called preserved flowers.
Flowers that don't wilt.
Since she's carrying a baby.
So you will be a brother.
That's right.
Mom will appreciate it.
I will put it together.
"I will be a big brother."
He is able to properly say goodbye.
While it's all dark
he can still see his father and mother.
Can you see him?
Touri.
Touri isn't crying.
You are so cool.
Are you okay? Is it not heavy?
Mama.
We've been waiting.
I bought the cake.
How amazing.
I bought it.
The goal is his baby that his mother is carrying.
You've become a big brother.
You bought it all?
Thank you.
There's some in this one too?
Mama, flowers.
I also bought flowers.
Where?
At the cake shop.
How admirable.
When the baby is born
both you and the baby can use it.
No one taught him to say that.
Please use it for decoration.
Hug me tight.
Thank you.
I'm home.
His two big brothers have come home.
He was succesful in his errand.
Look. He bought all this.
Amazing.
He also bought flowers for his mom despite not being told to.
Flowers.
Eh?
Now they will be 3 big brothers.
Perfect.
Should we call everyone?
Filmed in 2016.
For the home party
the members of Kawasaki Frontale have arrived.
Kawasaki Frontale (MF=Midfielder, GK=Goalkeeper, DF=Defender)
Arai Shota
Moriya Kentaro
Nakamura Kengo
Noborizato Kyouhei
Taniguchi Shougo
Noborizato Kyohei, Moriya Kantaro, Taniguchi Shougo..
Blessed with all these great team members.
Cheers.
Today's party, is a party for new big brother, Touri.
It's great that they got grilled meat.
Meat for 15 people and it all went down quickly.
Delicious. So good.
Touri Ookubo score a goal
To finish the party they chant to celebrate Touri's victory.
Touri Ookubo Touri from Kawasaki.
The tiny number 13.
We ask of you to always face the goal.
Go go go score. [Sports chant]
Touri and company also sent us some footage.
Filmed in 2020.
Touri
3rd year
elementary school
I did it.
He's now a big brother who is in 3rd year of elementary school.
Oh yeah. And what is the gender of the baby?
Is it a girl this time?
10 years.
14 years.
3 years.
8 years.
Papa. 37 years.
It was a boy.
4 boys and 1 man.
I'm 3 years old.
What kind of little brother is he?
Mischievous rascal but cute.
That's right.
A boy you want to spoil.
So he's exactly like Touri was back then.
Do you like your big brother?
Yep.
Do you like Touri?
He can't stand still.
The mother spends her days laughing and scolding.
Oldest son
Aito (Middle School 3rd year)
I'm the oldest son, Aito.
Second son, Ryokoji.
(Elementary school 5th year)
I'm the second son, Ryokuji.
3rd son. Touri.
(Elementary 3rd year)
I'm Touri from the errand.
And Shiyuu.
4th son. Shiyuu.
(3 years old)
A mischievous rascal but cute.
And about dad?
Might be heartbroken the day they will finally spread their wings.
Nagano ● Ooshikamura
This Spanish mama has lived in Japan since she was 5.
And now she has a cafe at Ooshikamura.
The interior design is made by the musician papa.
Bring it there. The tea.
Taiyou, who's only been allowed to wipe tables.
Taiyou [means Sun]
3 years 2 months
Since he turned 3 years he has been asked to serve the customers.
He did it. His first time doing it.
I will go get it.
Will you eat sweets today?
He can even take their orders.
Corn and... Corn and...
we have soup pulp donuts.
Soy pulp (okara) donuts?
They understood from the "soup pulp".
Soy pulp (okara) is healthy and a popular menu item.
Filmed in 2013.
Listen, listen. About the soy pulp...
we've run out but...
we will make more okara donuts.
Taiyou, go and shop.
Did he get it?
At the tofu shop say: "Okara, please."
By car.
Not by car. By foot.
He wants to go by car.
Not by car.
Can you do it?
Yep.
When you go out...
An insect!
Is he listening properly?
When you finish shopping...
Is he listening?
At the agricultural cooperative...
I want to make salad today so get some Chinese cabbage.
Sure.
You sure? Okay?
After you buy it you can also buy your favorite candy.
Yep-did-it.
Smooch.
Alright. Off you go.
See you.
I love you.
He's going on his errand on a high note.
Agricultural
cooperative
Home
Toufu shop
At the tofu shop used by everyone at Ooshikamura
the okara is said to be different.
Perfect for donuts.
At the agricultural cooperative on the way back he is asked to get Chinese cabbage.
Will he be fine?
I'm tired.
He just left the house.
Just a bit more.
There's still a lot to go.
Just a bit more. Oh yeah!
What's up?
Is he fine?
Meimei's flowers were here.
It's not a goat.
I will give it to Meimei.
His mothers' name is Mei.
Will his mother even be delighted by these leaves?
Arriving at the highly regarded Minoya tofu shop.
He's not getting tofu, though.
He's supposed to say "okara, please".
Here.
We are making soup pulp donuts so...
please.
Yes?
Welcome.
What's wrong?
Soup pulp.. donuts, we are making it
I was told to get soup pulp.
What do you... donuts?
Yep.
Ah.
I see.
Your mom is making her famous soy pulp (okara) donuts.
She understood him.
They are right here.
It's 50 yen per bag.
This?
Yes, this one.
Will this do? Just one?
Um, it's fine.
He has seen the donuts before but never the ingredients.
"Is this really soup pulp?" He wonders.
Is all fine?
I can go.
He didn't even put it in the basket  that he brought all the way here.
Thank you.
Next is the Chinese cabbage.
Put it in the basket.
Oh no, he's heading straight home.
He must be worried if he got the right thing.
They said that this is soup pulp.
Soup pulp?
An old lady from the neighborhood.
Soy pulp.
Otera (temple)?
Okara (soup pulp).
Otara.
Welcome back.
They said that this is it.
They told you this is it?
They said "otara".
O-ka-ra.
Thank you. You did well.
What? It was really this thing?
I did it.
Ah, you forgot one thing. What was it?
The Chinese cabbage.
This.
Ah, for Meimei? Thank you.
Huh? She was pleased.
And then...
At the agricultural cooperative what was it that you needed?
What type of vegetable?
Vegdable.
Ha, which one?
Vegdable
Want me to teach you? Chinese cabbage.
Chinese cabbage.
Chinese cabbage, huh?
Right?
I got it.
Off you go.
- Did he really?
- Really?
He's leaving once again on a high note.
It's a worry.
With the okara...
Go ahead and make donuts.
Let's make them together later.
Yes, I did it!
Today Taiyou is shopping.
He came out on the big street.
Look at his game face.
He needs to cross at this crossing.
What a serious face.
He trained so many times with his mother.
However he passed it.
- Huh? What?
- The other way.
The agricultural cooperative is on the other side.
I should go over there.
You want to cross?
It's the cameraman.
Then you should cross at this crossing.
See? Over there where people cross.
Ah, it's people!
It's people!
He realized midway.
Even a 3 year old person can cross there.
I will cross.
He has arrived at the cooperative agricultural supermarket.
Welcome.
Excuse me...
Chinese cabbage, right?
You came back.
You see...
Meimei told me to buy vegetables.
Is that right?
Which vegetable?
Let's go to the vegetables and have a look.
Going to the vegetable corner.
Which one, I wonder.
This one. Cabbage?
It's not cabbage.
It's different.
She said "vegetable".
What a pickle.
I wonder exactly what your mother said.
Vegetable.
What a pickle.
What is this?
This is mizuna.
It's not mizuna.
Green onion.
It's not green onion.
Is this pumpkin?
Pumpkin.
Tomato.
Yes, tomato.
It's not pumpkin nor tomatoes.
What was it?
It's right there.
This is daikon.
So close!
Below it. Below it.
This is Chinese cabbage.
That's it!
And this one is daikon.
And that's also daikon.
This is mandarin.
He skipped it.
You know so much. It's mandarin.
You don't have vegetables?
We do. Which one are you here for?
They went to the vegetables because of him.
Is it Chinese cabbage?
Though it's right in front of his eyes.
Vegetables.
Then...
Go back to your mother and ask: "Which vegetable was it again?"
Since you don't know go back and ask.
I...
What vegetable did she say?
What type of vegetable.
He couldn't buy vegetables.
Even though his mother was looking forward to it.
Welcome back. Did you buy it?
What type of vegetable was it?
You forgot? Did you say it right?
Vegetable.
Chinese cabbage.
His mother got an idea.
Taiyou, how old are you?
3 years old [san sai].
That's right 3 years.
And you should get? Chinese cabbage [hakusai].
Say it.
100 years old [hyakusai].
Say it once more.
Chinese cabbage.
Once more.
Whether it's 100 years [hyakusai] or Chinese cabbage [hakusai] I'm sure they will understand.
100 years.
Chinese cabbage.
Taiyou, how old are you?
I'm 3 years old.
What type of vegetable will you buy?
Chinese cabbage.
That's right. Amazing.
- What an amazing mother.
- Amazing mother.
Basket. Basket. And the wallet too.
What are you going to buy?
Leafy vegetables [hayasai].
He turned it into leafy vegetables.
Chinese cabbage.
Repeat it on the way.
Chinese cabbage, Chinese cabbage, Chinese cabbage...
Chinese cabbage. Chinese cabbage.
That's right. While he still got it.
- While he still remembers.
- Keep saying it.
Alright, off you go.
I love you.
Don't mix it in.
It's Chinese cabbage.
Chinese cabbage. Chinese cabbage.
Chinese cabbage.
Go and say "Chinese cabbage".
Alright. Off you go.
Chinese cabbage. Chinese cabbage.
That's so good.
Almost Chinese cabbage. [As in: almost 100 years old]
That's the spirit.
Chinese cabbage. Chinese cabbage.
Chinese cabbage.
This time it will surely be fine.
Taiyou is 3 years old.
3 years? What a good boy.
And then... what age?
Did you go and ask?
She said Chinese cabbage.
He did it.
This is Chinese cabbage.
Is it really Chinese cabbage?
Here you go.
Since this is Chinese cabbage.
So this is what Chinese cabbage looks like.
How great that you went and asked.
You are a good boy.
Can you carry it?
This time he puts it in the basket.
Chinese cabbage. Chinese cabbage.
Chinese cabbage is @#!?&...
Yahoo.
Thank you for your hard work.
Chinese cabbage. Chinese cabbage.
No matter his age in the future he will never forget: Chinese cabbage
Chinese cabbage.
Ah! The lady who helped him cross the street.
He exchanged glances with the cameraman.
How old are you now?
Come on. Tell the truth.
I can't tell you.
Can't tell him.
Taiyou is 3 years old.
You are 3 years old?
You are not 100 years old?
Isn't your mother waiting?
It will get dark. Hurry up.
So cute.
He's such a cute kid. Just the best.
I brought it.
You did it? All by yourself?
You are amazing, Taiyou.
You bought this?
What is it called?
Chinese cabbage.
So cute.
You are amazing. Give me a smooch.
Your favorite Chinese cabbage salad.
Shredding the cabbage and sprinkling some Katsuobushi​ on top.
Then add sesame oil and soy sauce and it's done.
Memei's specialty: Chinese cabbage salad.
Bon apetit.
Thank you, Meimei.
Does it suit the taste of a 3 year old?
Taiyou is it tasty?
Tasty.
Meimei, you should eat too.
I might eat later.
As long as you eat this you might get to live to 100 years.
It might be gone by then.
As the cold gains pace by the day
the autumn colors have appeared
It's the height of the autumn colors.
In this town a girl was born.
Kureha
[Autumn colors]
Since she is autumn colored and makes everyone happy they called her Kureha [autumn colors].
She always sticks to her mother and is such a cuddled baby girl.
But when Kureha turned 2
her mother was hospitalized.
It was cervical cancer​.
Her mother rarely came back home.
And in no time she turned into a well-behaved child.
"I don't want to be a burden on mother"....
she suddenly said when she turned 4.
"Mama, if you want me over, just tell me. I'll be right there."
Kureha has said that she can ride the bus and go by herself.
"We will make Kureha do it"
her mother said while thinking up an errand.
But it won't be an easy one.
This is the father.
Filmed in 2013.
He has passed 58 years by a little bit.
I have a leftover.
They are all over each other.
And normally
because of doting on her he ends up buying her anything she desires.
Working hard as a truck driver.
He has to since had his first daughter late in life.
Even the big brother has started to worry about her.
She knows it will be tough but she wants her to do her best.
That's why she's writing her a letter.
As long as papa believes that Kureha will be fine
and he can convey it then Kureha will also say: "Alright".
The father decided to make her bring her onigiri.
Kureha is preparing various things on her own.
This...
You should give it to the bus driver.
She will go by bus.s
This won't be enough, though.
It is enough.
They are using the town-loop bus.
It comes once an hour.
There's 26 minutes until the next bus.
However...
I want to go with papa.
Despite having resolved that she will go by herself.
Then put it in here.
Don't wanna.
Mama is waiting.
Wonder what's wrong?
Mama said if Kureha comes then I will feel better.
But she wants to go with papa after all.
Kureha, please go.
But I can't go by myself.
Yes you can. If it's you, Kureha, then you can do it.
It's fine.
Kureha who knows how to get her way.
This is where he usually caves in and buys her a toy.
It's fine. Since it's you, Kureha, then you can do it.
Come here. I will hug you.
A hug?
Yes. Come here.
It will be fine.
But if papa doesn't come with then I will be lonely.
It's fine.
The more he hugs Kureha, the weaker she becomes.
... Since it's dad, right?
Don't you want to go to your mom?
I do.
You do, don't you?
Then you better do your best.
Deep down she wants to go.
But her tears won't stop.
The bus will come by in a bit.
Maybe she changes her mind if they go outside?
Yes, do your best.
It's fine. It's fine.
But...
I can't stop crying.
You can't stop crying?
Alright.
Only a baby can't cease crying.
It's fine. Okay?
Kureha is no longer a baby.
In the end she didn't get on this bus.
The next bus is in one hour.
Drink a bit of water.
They go back to the house and start over.
But...
He's constantly carrying her around.
Ah, that's true.
He's even making her drink water. Though she's already 4 years old.
The phone is ringing.
The caller is the mom.
Hello?
You aren't constantly carrying her around, right?
It's as if she can see inside the house.
Papa, you better pull yourself together.
Or Kureha won't leave.
The mother wants the father to do it.
Not with kindness
but for him to know that love needs strictness too.
Toughen your heart. Please.
She's scolding him, the dad!
Do you want me to read mama's letter?
The letter from before the errand.
I'm really appreciative of being able to watch the growth and development of Kureha.
Right? So you will go to your mom's by yourself. Right?
It's tough for Kureha and it's tough for papa who must send Kureha out of the house on her own.
It's your first time riding a bus on your own however please pull yourself together.
Mama is saying that she's waiting.
If Kureha doesn't go then she will be lonely.
I will go to the hospital.
Will you ride the bus this time?
Yes?
Kureha, you can do it.
Right?
He decided to take her to the bus stop.
He couldn't stop her tears.
But he's not carrying her.
He must toughen his resolve.
You shouldn't run.
Okay?
Kureha, you can do it. That's what mom said.
It will be fine. Alright.
Just carry me a little bit.
He wants to hold her tight but he fights the feeling.
Do you best, dad.
Lift your spirits.
High five. High five.
Do your best. Do your best. Do your best.
Alright. Bye bye.
Do your best.
He has decided not to turn his face back.
He endures the desire to look back.
Ah, she stopped crying.
For real.
Home
Hospital
Ride the bus for 10 minutes
and the hospital will be right there.
She's on an errand to cheer up her mom.
The bus arrived.
Her expression changed.
For real.
Alright, confirm the destination.
Do you go to Chuuou Hospital?
Yes, we do.
Ooh, she was able to say it.
Remarkable.
To avoid missing her stop she rides behind the driver.
We are taking off. Please be careful.
The dad was right there!
He's waving.
Even though Kureha can't see.
For a moment the dad watches her go.
10 minutes on the bus and it will stop right in front of the hospital.
The errand is onigiri that the father made and the cheer of Kureha's presence.
Filmed in 2013
The hospital is within sight.
Next is Ina Chuuou Hospital.
Alright. Soon she will get to see her mom.
Remarkable.
She can get hugs from her mother.
She's been holding it in the entire time.
Thank you very much.
She has arrived at the hospital.
It's her first time coming here by herself.
The hospital where her mother is.
Mom, she's coming.
Kureha all by herself.
Hello.
Though she doesn't know the nurses.
If she turns here then it will be her mothers' hospital room.
Please knock gently.
She flew in the door.
What?
Kureha.
Did you come by yourself?
Amazing.
And you will go home by yourself.
How great.
She believed in her.
You did your best.
Want to take off your raincoat?
Take off the raincoat
and get an embrace from your mother.
Kureha noticed that the nurse is acting different from usual.
They are really calm.
It's been a while with her mother
But rather than embracing longingly
their conversation is as if they are back home.
I did it like you said.
You brought this? Halloween.
I brought it since mom requested it.
It's Halloween soon.
The mother has borrowed a picture book at the book corner in the hospital.
But... he ate it.
The apple...
There's so much the mother wants to do.
Reading a picture book out loud.
Talk about kindergarten.
And eat onigiri.
These are well made.
I get energized when Kureha comes.
And to energize Kureha
She's giving her a manicure.
Alright.
Now wait a bit.
Time flies when you are having fun.
I will give you a letter.
Did you write a letter? Thank you.
Kureha, did you write it?
She can write?
| \ + [] Δ -| ' /\ | \ + [ Δ -| ' /\
What does it say?
She read it to her mother.
I see.
You wrote: "I hope mama will get better soon."?
Thank you.
Since Kureha came...
Look.
Wow, it...
The mother
has decided not to cry in front of Kureha.
If she does then it will weaken Kureha.
This is a letter.
When you get back home have papa read it for you.
Mama also wrote one.
Do come back again full of vigour.
I have lots of vigour.
Come with all your vigour.
She got the letter from her mother.
And will head home to her father who is waiting.
Bye bye.
Saying their goodbyes at the elevator.
She didn't cry. It really surprised me.
The mother too.
She tried to keep it in.
She was able to do it by herself.
From now on she will be able to go by herself.
The bus departed with Kureha on it.
As she was bestowed energy tears start appearing.
As she has given away energy tears start appearing.
The mother's handling was so kind.
I will do my best.
Since this the mother
recovered so much the nurses were astounded.
Though she was only in there with her mother for 1 hour.
But it's fine.
The story from the picture book continued in her dreams.
Just a bit more and you will pass home.
Close the picture book.
It's the next bus stop.
She's still fast asleep.
Young lady. Young lady. We arrived. We arrived at your home.
What a relief.
Young lady. Wake up.
Right?
We arrived to your home.
Home? Huh?
I was dreaming of my mother.
But the errand wasn't just a dream.
This is the time her father always sleeps so she enters quietly.
Welcome back.
He was pacing restlessly around the room.
You did your best.
I want to give you a letter.
Is it this one?
Um.
The letter. Yes.
The letter that her mother handed her.
Alright.
I will now read mama's letter.
To papa,
Today you believed in Kureha.
Thank you for properly sending her off.
Papa, give this award for the girl doing her best.
It's tough when you have to do what's necessary to fight an illness.
It's tough but I have a family. I have all of you.
That's why I am happy.
Let's enjoy the development of a child together and embark on a happy life.Thank you.
Right? That's what mom wrote.
Right?
Mama has...
This wonderful gold medal. She wants to say "here you go, Kureha".
Wonderful.
Hug me.
You did your best.
Right?
You did your best. You did your best.
Papa is crying.
And she will keep developing. From here on out.
I'm happy that I get to watch her development.
And I want to see much more of it.
That's right.
And has the father developed through this too?
Good girl. Good girl. Good girl.
He hasn't.
It's no good.
It's hot.
Right.
You did well in going to your mother's.
2 weeks later.
The mother who quickly improved was discharged.
Amazing.
How great.
Bringing grandad and grandma to go watch the fall colors.
The sun is shining brightly.
Shizuoka ● Morimachi
In the best region in Japan for tea, Shizuoka.
Where two kids are brought up strong.
Beni
4 years 1 month
Beni who recently turned 4 and
Gen
3 years 9 months
the 4 months younger Gen who is still 3.
Even after kindergarten is over they hang out as the familiar duo.
Even today Gen came to Beni's house to play.
Beni is pouring tea into the container.
We are running out of tea leaves.
But we have to bring it tomorrow.
At the kindergarten they must bring tea in every day.
It's to rinse their mouths.
At this elementary school tea comes out of the faucet.
Amazing.
It's not for drinking. Only rinsing.
Eh. What is this?
Filmed in 2011.
It is said that it helps protect against the common cold and influenza.
As expected from a tea producing region.
They will go buy tea for gargling.
What are you going to purchase?
Tea for gargling.
That's exactly it.
He brings Beni's tea container.
How kind of you.
Home
Tea shop
They are going to buy tea for gargling.
It's the same route as on the way to the kindergarten.
The mothers have found a safe path with no cars.
Uwa, looks like it will be a fun little errand.
Off you go.
Off we go.
The two of them depart in a good mood and friendly.
However...
It's kinda scary.
For some reason tears are forming.
She was overcome with loneliness.
Want to cry?
I want to go back to my mother's.
Where mama is, yeah.
I do want to go.
While saying all that they proceed with smiles.
It will be fine cause I am with you.
Gen is a man. He's reliable.
Continuing down the straight path.
Mr. Sun, don't go away, okay?
It won't go away just yet.
Eh, a quarrel?
But in fact...
Gen's win.
They are playing around.
Oh, I see.
A kappa's leaf.
What's a kappa's leaf.
Since the kappa is coming
this will protect you from getting wet.
A kappa will also come for me.
A kappa's leaf! To be honest this old guy doesn't have a clue.
But it's a good overall feeling.
What's wrong?
Let's eat a rice balls.
They found a place to eat rice balls.
Gen...
Beni has an edamame rice ball.
- How nice.
- Nice.
Delicious.
And Gen has a seaweed rice ball.
And there's kelp mixed with the rice.
They are really relishing it.
Even this old guy wants one now.
Please take care of the litter.
The always kind Gen.
I am going.
Please wait. I'm getting ready.
Their stomachs are full.
And the sun is pleasantly warm.
Which means...
Want to take a break? Right here.
Okay.
Want to lay down?
Lay down?
It feels good to lay down.
This is a post-feast nap.
Mr. Sun didn't go away as promised.
Here we are.
We finally arrived.
Mr. Sun, don't go away, okay?
How nice.
Full of playing around 1 hour and 45 minutes have passed since they left.
We've arrived so it will be fine from now on.
Finally time for the errand.
What type of tea do they need to buy?
Welcome.
One for the lid, please.
Tea leaves.
Gen, nice follow up.
First they get to enjoy a tea sample.
This isn't for gargling.
Since this is first-rate tea.
They appreciate good tea.
Will this one be fine?
No no. No need for first-rate tea.
Tea for gargling.
You need it for gargling?
That's right.
It's tea for gargling that they need to bring to the kindergarten.
For gargling the cheapest one is sufficient.
They help pouring it in the containers.
How old are you?
4 years old.
4 years?
She's a bit proud of it.
And you?
3 years old.
It's a bit frustrating.
The containers are now full to the brim.
Please be careful.
Hurry up and go home.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Sun waited for them.
Today is our first errand.
Huge success.
No no. The errand isn't over until you get home.
I'm tired already.
Yeah.
Their legs started getting heavy.
If they don't hurry home it will start to get dark.
Should we take a break here?
Want to eat Ramune.
Ramune?
They were told to eat it if they started feeling tired. The mothers prepared it.
This is for both of us.
It revitalized them.
Beni, it's dangerous to go there.
If they don't hurry the sun will set.
Mr. Sun is taking his sweet time for the sake of both of them.
I can see it.
The moon is so red.
It's the sun.
The mothers have turned on all the lights in the house and are waiting.
Gen.
I am home!
Welcome back.
They returned safely.
Gen, you have so much strength.
Gen is carrying it.
The kind man, Gen, also reached the goal.
It's been 3 hours and 50 minutes since they left the house.
They did their best without quarreling.
It must've been heavy.
You really did your best.
You've been a great help.
They got the right tea for gargling.
Bacteria is being spat out.
Let's say cheers with our cups.
It's such a nice time when you gargle tea.
This spring they started junior high school and they both sent us a video.
They didn't get to do their elementary school graduations.
Beni
Junior High 1 year
It's bitter.
Even at junior high they still gargle on green tea.
Gen
Junior High 1 year
They always do it when they wash their hands.
It would be nice if life can get back to normal as soon as possible.
Our first errand. Huge success!