Day one in Pattaya, Thailand.
When we have a meal together,
I thought it should be authentic Thai.
I brought something so it doesn't feel like Japan.
Look.
What...?
-Look.
-What is it?
Coriander.
Thai food's all about coriander.
So we should all have coriander.
Why Mr Potato Head?
I borrowed it from my son as a container.
-Seriously?
-Cute.
See? Just by smelling it,
you feel like it's Thailand.
You have a point, I suppose.
And whatever you're doing or eating,
coriander makes it more Thai.
-So I brought it.
-I see.
They only used this once in their whole journey.
Put some coriander.
Oh yeah.
-Nice idea.
-Why not?
That's wrong.
That's not how you give it to him.
Put some more.
Give him some more. Go on.
-That was enough.
-Go on.
No...
So forceful.
How is it?
Doesn't go well with takoyaki.
So bad.
Hamada's Holiday in Thailand.
The six researched Pattaya thoroughly
and gave a presentation to Hamada.
Hamada and company
stayed at Mera Mare Pattaya,
a four-star hotel that opened in 2016.
Located in central Pattaya by Beach Road,
it's ideal for business, leisure, and golf.
In addition to 80 fully-equipped rooms,
it also has gorgeous suites.
This hotel will be the base during this trip.
Whose presentation
did Hamada choose as third place?
Please announce third place.
Third place.
The prize is 1,000 bahts.
That's big.
In third place is...
-Taiki!
-Thank you!
It's definitely good enough.
-Well done.
-Thank you.
It was very Thai.
-Yes.
-I didn't want to go at first.
-To be frank.
-To be frank, I didn't.
I didn't want them near me.
-We were outside a lot.
-Yeah.
It was fun, riding on it.
It lifted him up.
-Beautifully.
-We could never do that in Japan.
-Only in Thailand.
-True.
It was a great picture.
Taiki from "Dorians" wins third place
with this presentation.
Morning, day two of the trip in Pattaya.
Good morning!
Good morning.
-Uh-huh.
-So quiet.
-Hey.
-Huh?
What?
We're filming.
It's started.
Yo!
He's cheerful.
He is.
Good.
-Get over it.
-Like Hitoshi Ueki.
Leave it.
We've not seen much of Thailand.
It's awesome. Let's go see it.
Well yeah, but where?
Taiki's on that duty.
-Leave it to me.
-Thanks, Taiki.
Where are we going?
It's somewhere that's typically Thai.
In my opinion. I have plans, but first...
let's have a go at shooting.
-Shall we go?
-Shooting, huh?
We've all done it before.
Did you bring your own equipment?
-My own what?
-Guns.
Your stuff.
-I'm not allowed.
-You have them?
Nice.
We believed you.
He doesn't have guns.
I don't own any.
Okay, shooting.
Well I came up with a few ideas,
so please decide which one you want.
There's The Million Years Stone Park
and Pattaya Crocodile Farm. A long name.
What we can do is feed crocodiles there.
You can't do that in Japan.
So if you want to feed crocodiles, you go there.
Exactly. Those who want to.
I don't want to.
What's the point in that?
Why would I want to do that?
Why not?
It's exciting to approach them.
They're big.
There's even a show where a man
puts his head in a crocodile's mouth.
I've seen it on TV.
-You have?
-Yeah, a head goes in.
-Like this.
-Yeah, and he just goes "Yay."
They have other animals. Like tigers.
We can go up to them.
Go up to them?
Right next to it.
That's an odd way to explain it.
We can lie next to it.
You know, I looked up Pattaya on Instagram.
-Loads of pics were with tigers.
-Really?
So I know that it's popular.
In Japan, in safari parks,
we're in a car or they're caged.
But Thai people, they just sit next to the tigers.
-Never.
-Never?
I don't trust them. Something will happen.
I see.
-Seshita.
-I'll be there.
I'll attack the tiger.
No, no, no...
Even you couldn't beat a tiger
if it attacks us, Seshita.
Well, I'll be in the middle.
Between him and the tiger?
He's the tiger, I'm Hamada.
And Hamada is petting the tiger, like this.
For photos, I'll just do this.
Considerate.
I'll just vanish.
What if it attacks?
What are you doing?
-Whoa, whoa.
-I'm not a tiger.
Ouch. You're so strong. That really hurt.
Are you the tiger?
Who's the tiger? It's him.
He's only lost against US soldiers in a fight.
-He won against everyone else.
-Impressive.
What else?
I have other plans.
Please listen to me. Of course I do.
He went for the TV.
Well, elephants.
How does that sound?
Surely that's a Thai experience.
Let's ride an elephant.
Ride on it for what?
"For what?"
You go, "I'm on an elephant!"
You would, huh?
But...
That's it?
It's about your emotions?
It's just how you feel.
We'll interact with them too.
OK.
Let's go.
-Elephants.
-Let's go.
Yes. I've already prepared for it.
-Elephant it is.
-Okay.
We're doing it.
-I look forward to it.
-Good plan.
We'll go to the elephants.
They went to a famous elephant spot in Pattaya.
In South Africa, I ate an elephant's trunk.
Really?
It was so hard.
Hard?
They sliced it up and served it to us.
Was it long?
-Yeah, grilled.
-Not rings?
They slice it up.
They steam it and grill it.
You can slice it up.
I asked Naito to eat it first.
He had it and said,
"That's hard!"
An elephant's trunk is hard.
It looks hard.
It won't be tender.
What's it like?
Here we are.
Pattaya Elephant Village.
Okay, let's go inside.
Let's go.
-Elephant Village.
-Are they here?
Yes.
-I smell animals.
-Yeah.
This is very realistic.
-Look at that...
-This must be for something.
Like a show.
They have Thai dance shows here.
There's one.
See? They're just there.
Amazing.
-It's a child.
-Yes.
It looks really happy.
I'm scared.
Pattaya Elephant Village opened in 1973.
Elephants are important workers in Thai jungles.
This place was opened to protect
the ones who became too old...
...or injured and couldn't work any longer.
Here, it is possible to interact with elephants.
They have bananas that we can feed them.
-Please feed the elephant yourselves.
-Feel free to do it.
Look at the size of that snake.
So huge.
It's so surreal.
Wow.
It's overwhelming.
Information overload.
Come on, people.
Feed it.
-Shall we?
-Come on.
It's waiting.
How do I do it?
-It's coming to me.
-Pass it to his trunk.
-Whoa!
-Hurry up.
Sorry.
Get on with it.
He wants it. Come on.
Amazing.
It uses the trunk really well.
It grabs it.
It's quite fun.
And if I put it down?
It'll pick it up.
There.
Amazing.
-Amazing, huh?
-So hard.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
It's my breakfast.
Your stomach can handle anything now.
Thailand suits me.
Sorry.
-You stole the bananas.
-Right?
Use your mouth.
Seshita will use his mouth.
Me?
Nice one, Seshita.
Why me?
Why isn't it Hirai?
It's moldy.
It bothers me.
It's not moldy. It was tasty.
-It was moldy.
-It's fine inside.
That's it.
Smile, or it'll feel nervous.
Animals can tell when you're scared.
What's wrong?
Put it down with your mouth.
Seshita, go closer.
That's it.
Nice photo.
Well done.
It was wonderful.
-Hamada, please, give it a go.
-No thanks.
Hold my hand then.
What's that about?
That's weird.
Please film it nicely.
That's not right.
What are you doing?
I did it.
How was it?
-Good.
-See? It's fun.
-Please touch it.
-No.
Use your hand.
Okay.
-So hard.
-How do you know?
You feel whatever he feels?
I'm the only one who knows
that when you ate the banana,
you got sick.
-I know, man.
-Is that so?
It made him sick.
You felt sick?
The banana did look old.
Yeah, I thought so.
I found out that you can eat insects,
but never an elephant's banana.
Never eat it.
Never.
Okay, now I'd like you all to embark...
...on an elephant journey.
He's hiding.
Where is he?
Where's Hamada?
Hamada?
Yes?
You were here all along.
Here he was.
You disappeared.
I'm here.
-"I'm here."
-Hiding.
Follow me for an elephant ride.
Two people can ride on one elephant together.
This is Thailand.
-Taiki, you go first.
-Okay.
I'll go with Hirai.
Seshita and Iwahashi. Masayoshi alone.
-Good.
-Right?
Let's ride on an elephant.
We're at the right height for it.
I see.
-Cool.
-A happy elephant.
We'll ride on it and go for a little trip.
One question.
How long is the trip?
Around 60 minutes.
Taiki, come back. Come back to us.
Come back.
That was sudden.
So sudden. No violence, please.
60 minutes? Screw that.
I told you this was a journey on an elephant.
Can't we go on a short trip?
I can ask if they can make it short.
Is that possible?
-It's fine.
-Yeah?
Well then, please.
It's fun alone too.
This is quite special.
Very special.
Oh wow.
How is it?
Jeez. What's this?
For your safety.
Amazing.
It's moving.
Wow!
It's scary.
It's wobbly.
Taiki.
It's so high up, Taiki.
Hamada, isn't it awesome?
Too high.
We're riding it.
So amazing.
It's huge.
Unbelievable.
Why don't you smile and wave?
Amazing.
Wow.
This is awesome.
They can even carry Hirai.
I know.
-I wonder how much weight they can carry.
-I'm sure it can handle them.
It's a bumpy ride.
Are you having fun?
It's quite bumpy.
Yeah, it is.
I can't believe how high we are.
What's that?
It's hot.
It's not even that sunny though.
When we're under the sun, right? I get it.
-Amazing.
-It's good to have it.
A Thai aristocrat is among us today.
-With a parasol.
-You know him?
It feels so insecure.
So wobbly.
Elephants rule!
Look, an elephant.
-Awesome, huh?
-Yeah.
I think it's a great attraction.
Makes you feel like you're in Thailand.
-We're going in the water?
-Yeah.
No way. Really?
I wonder how deep it is.
It goes up and down.
There's a monkey.
There is.
-It's water.
-We're going in.
Don't fall over.
This is really scary.
Do elephants ever fall over?
Oh my gosh.
It's deeper than I thought.
-Wow.
-Are we really going in?
-This is quite deep.
-Right?
It's so scary.
Are we OK?
This is dangerous.
It's fun.
The elephants are so deep in water.
-It's scary.
-Impressive.
We're screwed if they trip.
Yes, totally.
This is incredible.
Incredible.
The trunk is out.
Oh yeah.
So it can breathe.
It's breathing like that?
Please, get the parasol.
Have it opened, please.
It won't open.
When did you close it?
-Sorry.
-What was that?
Wow, impressive.
They must be two or three meters tall.
It'll be a disaster if we fall.
The water scares me. What if it falls over?
It is scary.
It might get sick.
Can't do this in Japan.
That was a new experience.
It was the first time for me too.
-Good.
-Thank you.
Wonderful.
Thank you very much.
That was so great.
I enjoyed that.
Taiki. It was totally awesome.
-Thank you.
-Right?
It was fun, huh?
There's more to see.
-Please.
-More elephants?
Masayoshi, how was it?
I enjoyed it, but I think
I'll come back with someone.
Sure, I really hope you do.
Let's go.
More fun experience
you can't experience in Japan.
-Please follow me.
-What is it?
Remember this elephant?
We're friends now. Take a look.
Ready?
I heard that they do this.
Awesome!
Isn't it incredible?
Wow!
That was awesome.
I'd like you to have a go at this.
Whoa, seriously?
-Come on.
-Why?
I want you to try it.
-Are you scared?
-Very scared.
-It's incredible.
-It was quite high.
It's a valuable interaction with an animal.
Please have a go.
-Elephants are very docile, you know?
-Yeah?
It won't bite?
-No, it won't.
-Won't it target me?
First, touch the elephant a bit.
It's hard.
Amazing!
Looked easy.
I was lifted in seconds.
Because I'm light.
-How was it?
-I felt so light.
-It's strong.
-Yeah.
Also because I'm light.
It looked good.
Oh come on. But yeah, incredible.
All of them enjoyed this precious experience
of being wrapped up in an elephant trunk.
I'm falling.
So fast.
It's so high!
Put me down now.
That was high.
-Amazing, huh?
-Yeah!
He's heavy too.
Such a serious face.
-So rigid.
-Your expression!
Why so serious?
You worked out just now.
It worked on my biceps.
Good, let's go now.
I haven't had a go. I want to have a go.
Don't worry.
I want to be wrapped up. Please.
You're having fun.
I'll lift you up then.
You're floating.
That's good enough.
-Same stuff.
-No, it's not.
It's the same.
Tsutsumi of "Dorians" had another
experience with an elephant prepared.
Please gather here, everybody.
We'll have a tug-of-war with an elephant.
I think with this many big men,
we can pull an elephant.
I see.
The rope is ready.
OK.
Let's do this.
I wonder how strong an elephant is.
Don't hold back, OK?
Really?
Hirai should be at the end.
Hamada goes here.
We'll go here.
We'll go towards the end.
Let's do this.
Yeah.
Flip it over.
Don't hold back.
Let's start.
Ready... go!
It's coming.
A little more... that's it.
No way!
We haven't lost yet.
-Come on.
-Stop it. We lost.
Darn it!
-Wow.
-That hurt.
I'm so impressed.
It accelerated so fast.
Come on, Taiki.
There's no way we can win this game.
They said we had a chance
with this many men, you know.
No, no, we had no chance at all.
If the ground was softer,
we could've slid forever.
It was rough with gravel though.
Hirai's butt's burnt.
My butt is burnt.
When we lost the tug-of-war,
we all let go of the rope.
He was still on his butt, not willing to give up yet.
I was impressed.
Then you do it.
You should've done it.
You heard him.
I'll shut up.
Don't, Iwahashi.
-Talk.
-Don't cry.
This is hard.
Who are you talking to? Come on.
Amazing.
It's so rare to interact
with an elephant so up close.
Wasn't it fun? Meeting elephants?
Great!
It's nice to visit places.
I liked being lifted up.
It was good.
I didn't do it.
Why? It was really fun.
You guys wouldn't let me.
I said I wanted to do it.
-Have Seshita do it.
-No.
That's right.
Alright.
It's fun.
Elephant Village is awesome!