Hamada and his juniors are in Pattaya, Thailand.
I brought speakers. Let's listen to music.
Yes, good idea.
Can we play music?
Sure.
-He says OK.
-Thank you.
-Good choice.
-It's "Easy Rider."
It's perfect for a road trip.
Tamio Okuda.
It's a great travel song.
It matches this scenery.
It was used in a travel show.
That's right.
You're singing?
You recorded your voice?
I thought he was singing now.
Me too. You recorded your own voice?
You recorded your own singing?
Yes, I did.
You recorded this?
We want to hear Tamio Okuda's version.
I don't have it.
You don't?
Lousy!
What is this?
It's funny.
It is.
Seriously, what is this?
Unbelievable.
It's like we're on a bus tour, Hirai.
Yes, a bus tour with fans.
What is this?
What's going on?
It's a bus tour.
Hamada's Holiday in Thailand
These six comedians
have researched about Pattaya...
...to pitch fun activities to Hamada.
The group are staying
at the Mera Mare Pattaya,
a four-star hotel that opened in 2016.
Located on Pattaya's Beach Road,
it's ideal for both business and leisure.
It has 80 fully-equipped bedrooms
and luxurious suite rooms.
This hotel was the basecamp for their trip.
Let's see whose choice came in fifth place.
Fifth place.
Everyone, close your eyes
for your name to be called.
There's a cash reward.
Hamada.
Fifth place gets 100 Baht.
Fifth place goes to...
Iwahashi.
Iwahashi is fifth.
It's a good result.
Yes, I'm happy. Thank you.
Aren't you happy?
Well, it's fifth out of six people.
So overall it's a low ranking.
I'm happy, but I'm also...
-Disappointed?
-Disappointed.
But everyone was amazing.
I thought of the best plan I could.
Your presentation were great.
-Really?
-You were.
Really? I'm happy.
There was an unexpected twist,
but that last place felt very Thai.
Very Thai?
Thank you.
It was great.
Then why am I fifth?
The rest was even better.
Everyone's was better?
You weren't bad.
It's tough.
Who are you talking to?
Who's over there?
Don't talk to the staff.
You can't talk to the staff.
Let's see Iwahashi's plan that ranked in fifth.
Iwahashi, go ahead.
Thank you.
So...
You're far away.
I'll stand closer.
Thailand is a hot country, so let's go to a pool.
It's gigantic. I mean it, it's huge.
Really?
There's a 23-meter water slider,
which you slide down
in two seconds.
That's steep!
Two seconds?
It's basically a theme park.
Just like Disneyland,
you can spend the whole day there.
Take a look.
It's enormous.
It's huge.
Hamada, you're not well known here,
so you can let loose.
It would be great for kids.
You can let loose.
Like this.
You're angry?
Nobody was stopping him.
-How about it?
-A pool? I don't know...
It is hot.
We can be kids again.
There are 150 pools,
divided into ten different zones.
What are you saying?
Please explain with words.
Just like aquariums are divided
into themed areas,
the pools are divided into ten categories.
And the ten categories...
Be serious.
It'll be fun.
Can you wear a swimsuit?
No problem. Look at this.
Isn't it big?
I'm carrying four babies.
-Four?
-Four.
Four babies in my belly.
-Four?
-Four.
Three babies, two babies, one baby...
...and four babies.
Cut it out.
Stop it.
Let's go to the pool.
It'll be fun. We should go.
Any other options?
OK, we'll put a pin in this.
I tried Thai food, which is great.
Especially Khao Man Gai.
It's fried rice topped with chicken.
It's popular.
I found the best Khao Man Gai
in all of Thailand.
You can get it with chicken,
or with pork or duck.
A set with soup costs just 100 Baht.
-It's delicious.
-It's cheap.
It's so good, you can eat it even if you're full.
Even if you're stuffed, you'll want to eat.
Keep talking.
Why do you laugh in the middle?
We're listening.
Seriously...
Don't make pit stops.
We're comedians, so it's no fun
if we just go and eat.
Let's draw straws to see who eats what.
That's suspenseful.
There's a varied menu.
Hamada definitely needs to eat
the most popular dish.
So he gets the Khao Man Gai and soup set.
Any objections?
I'll take this.
If he can't eat...
Your plan will be pointless.
Let them draw.
Please pick. It has the menu item you can eat.
Please draw at once.
-Go ahead.
-What about you?
This one's mine.
I get Khao Man Gai, like Hamada. Thanks!
-Inomoto, you get Khao Na Ped, with duck.
-Duck?
It's also popular.
Seshita gets soup only.
Seriously?
The weirdo gets nothing.
I'm Masayoshi.
He's your senior.
"The weirdo gets nothing?"
And Taiki...
This is pork, which some say
is better than the chicken.
And you.
Japanese meal.
What?
You get a rice ball that I got in Japan.
I don't want it!
It's from Haneda Airport.
What is that?
Wait, this expired three days ago.
He can't eat that.
It's fine. I kept it refrigerated.
This is what we're eating.
-Khao Man Gai.
It's delicious.
OK, let's go!
What about us?
Congrats!
It's a miracle!
-You thought he'd say no?
-Absolutely!
Khao Man Gai is the winner.
I was up until four making these.
I'm relieved.
Let's go. Let's eat chicken.
Everyone eats except the weirdo.
That one's good.
Yours too.
You really thought he'd refuse.
I'm so happy!
I could kill someone.
No you can't.
Let's go!
He's so loud, from start to end.
And so, they head out for
the best Khao Man Gai in Thailand.
We're here.
They serve the best Khao Man Gai in Thailand.
It's pretty casual.
It feels very local.
This soup is really good.
It's not too crowded.
Two Khao Man Gai.
Two chicken.
They only have pork and duck.
Only pork and duck?
This is awkward.
Really?
Serious?
Didn't we come for the Khao Man Gai?
No Khao Man Gai?
-It's sold out.
-You're sold out?
He's so unlucky.
Pork is actually the best.
Liar!
The real foodies say pork is actually the best.
Let me explain...
We want to try the basics.
Hamada's card said chicken.
He'll get pork.
I had pork.
You get pork.
-And me?
-Rice ball.
-Nothing.
Will you take pork?
Chicken is the most famous,
but the regulars here say pork is the best.
But you wanted chicken.
I wanted chicken.
Let's go.
Will you at least try the soup?
It's really good.
-Thank you.
-The soup is really good.
The soup...
Is this it?
Seriously?
We went, but they were sold out.
Iwahashi sums up the day...
I'd assumed the staff would have taken care of it.
I should have checked
how much chicken they had left.
This is a true documentary with no fakes.
They didn't have what you presented.
I'm really embarrassed this happened.
I wanted you to try it.
So did we.
What will we do now?
Let's go to a temple to shed our earthly desires.
What's it like?
They have a Buddha that's like this.
It's sleeping?
No, it's not.
I apologize for the confusion.
Let's just go.
Let's go. I'm sorry.
That was really awkward.
Iwahashi had also planned on visiting a temple.
I'll take those.
You want them back?
You had three ideas.
We already decided.
What's your third idea?
Really?
We might have time to go.
Oh yeah. I'm sorry.
So...
-I was rude.
-You were.
Just tell us.
We have time.
I was just so relieved.
There's still time.
I was irritated because
that old man told me to keep talking.
Don't call him "old man."
Thailand is a Buddhist country,
so let's go to a temple.
A temple?
Otherwise it's like going to Disneyland
and not seeing Mickey.
Let's go to Thailand's most popular temple.
There's a golden Buddha, three times the size...
...of the Buddha at Todaiji Temple in Nara.
It's sleeping?
No it's not, and I apologize for the confusion.
-It's not sleeping?
-No, it's sitting.
What does it look like?
Like this.
It's sleeping?
No, it's not.
All the tourists go there.
In Thailand...
Everyone goes there.
-It's a spiritual spot?
-Absolutely.
In Thailand, people know
the day of the week they were born on.
The temple has a Buddha for each day of the week,
and people pray in front of their Buddha.
That Buddha will protect them.
We should go there and pray to our Buddhas,
but we won't know which day to pray for.
-I looked it up!
-Incredible!
Really?
Here we go.
Hamada, you were born on Saturday.
Saturday.
Really?
Please pray to the Saturday Buddha.
Hirai was born on Sunday.
Sunday?
Really? Sunday?
Taiki was born on Sunday.
Sunday for you two.
Masayoshi was born on Friday.
On Friday.
I made a mistake.
Tear that out.
You don't need that.
If it's a mistake, tear it out.
I have my reasons.
Seshita was born on Sunday.
I was born on Saturday.
Like me.
Please remember yours.
What about me?
I have no idea.
What's with you?
And you're my senior.
Look mine up!
I did.
You were born on Friday.
Have you noticed the pattern?
We're all old men.
I'm just kidding.
I was laughing last night. Just kidding.
It was OK until there.
Sorry about that.
We're all born on the weekend.
Yes, so...
Weekend, weekend, weekend!
Weekend, weekend, weekend...
Be quiet!
You're loud.
So we're Team Weekend! Let's go!
Let's go!
-Foreign country people!
-Enough!
That's enough.
Let's go.
Shall we go?
We're all born on the weekend.
Nobody was born Monday to Thursday.
It's a miracle.
If the Khao Man Gai's good, we can go.
Sounds good.
So restaurant first.
Let's go.
But the Khao Man Gai was sold out,
so they head to the temple.
It's huge.
Wow.
I want a photo.
Photography is allowed.
Let's take one from here.
A group photo.
It's three times the size of Nara's Buddha.
I'll take a one.
It's beautiful.
You should join.
I'll take one first, to see how it looks.
A video?
Not a photo?
It was video mode.
Sorry.
A video?
Not a photo?
It was video mode.
Sorry.
Could you take it?
Thank you!
The group arrived at Pattaya's largest temple,
Wat Phra Yai.
Numerous bells line the entrance,
which can be rung
to wash away earthly desires.
Known as "the Big Buddha,"
it's a major tourist site in Pattaya.
This is amazing.
It's a must-see in Thailand.
We're on the snake path.
These mythical snakes are protecting us.
Even from here, it's big.
-It's huge.
-Amazing.
It's the most popular temple
in Thailand for foreign tourists.
It's a holy place, like a Japanese shrine.
Please be respectful.
Look at the size.
That's incredible.
It's not sleeping at all.
I was trying to express this,
but I'm so fat I rolled over.
There are many types.
There's so many.
Look, it's Iwahashi.
They threw something.
Yes, into the belly button.
You can overlook the city from here,
another reason why it's popular.
This is Pattaya City.
Wow.
It's cloudy today.
There's a lot of smog.
That's smog?
They also sell sparrows that you release
to increase your virtue.
That's interesting.
Different countries have different customs.
The Big Buddha is surrounded
by the Buddhas for each day of the week.
Let's see the other Buddhas.
Friday.
Here's the Friday Buddha,
for Masayoshi and Inomoto.
You should pray.
Inomoto.
I want to be more on TV.
I want a documentary made about me.
Not Downtown's show?
Why? I don't get it.
-Saturday and Sunday's Buddha are over here.
-Okay.
Hirai, Taiki and Seshita were born on Sunday.
Go ahead and pray.
Give us more warm-up comedy work.
Likewise.
I hope I become more famous.
-Let's go to the Saturday Buddha.
-Saturday.
That's for me and Hamada.
Let's pray.
Go ahead.
I want to be on more TV shows.
Really, do you mean that?
I'm sure you have enough programs.
Can't you get us on your shows?
Please, master.
You can't be serious.
Not all TV channels like me.
Let's just pray for good health.
Finally, the group prayed to the Big Buddha.
They experienced
the true Buddhist culture of Thailand.
That was great.
It was really amazing.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
It was very Thai.
Yes, it was a very Thai experience. That's nice.
-Back to you.
-Who are you talking to?
There's only us.
Don't talk to the staff.
They listen to more songs recorded by Hirai.
Who is this?
It's perfect.
It's a great song.
It's your song.
It's a bit awkward.
It is, but it's perfect for this hot weather.
Turn it up.
This is a good one.
It's his song.
You're shameless.
The real singer is here.
What an awful singer.
No one wants to hear this.
Are you making fun of me?
He's mimicking you.
It's the way he's singing.
You changed your voice.
You were different in the last song.
What's that?
He's doing the live version.
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
You're teasing him.
He's mocking you.
The actual singer is here. Are you crazy?