Temp:
Shinozuka Rina
How boring.
Hakamada
Law Office
What's going on here?
Attorney:
Hakamada Yukio
Hello, Hakamada Law Offices.
Yes, one moment, please.
Hello, Hakamada Law Office.
Sensei, we've got trouble.
Shinozuka-san, the bread is done baking.
They're croissants.
Never mind the croissants.
We're in a crisis.
What?
Hakamada
Law Office
What's going on?
No one ever lines up at our office,
but now there's a line of people.
Maybe they were lured by
the aroma of my bread.
Of course not!
They're clients.
And phones have been
ringing off the hook.
That can't be what this is.
There's no way a crowd
like this would come here.
Excuse me, coming through.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Wow, what an amazing line!
Looks like it was effective, Kanae-chan.
Maybe so.
Excuse me, I'm the landlord.
Yoshie-san, do you know what's going on?
Let me in first.
Here, take a look at this.
Monthly Publication Monday
Monthly Publication Monday,
hot off the press!
Oh, that's the monthly magazine
with Kanae-san's syndication.
Kanae-chan's manga seems to be
getting quite popular lately, so...
Hakamada's assistant:
Nonomura Kanae
I took advantage of the situation.
Office landlord:
Toyama Yoshie
Look!
"Compensation Lawyer" If you want a divorce and to get compensated, come to the Hakamada Law Office
"If you want a divorce and to get compensated,
come to the Hakamada Law Office."
Divorce Chaser
~Let's Turn Your Tears into Money~
Divorce Chaser Episode 5
Law Office of Hakamada in great peril?
Is that why they're all here?
The advertisement was way
more effective than we thought.
Sensei, you better get started.
Monthly Publication Monday
Rake in lots of compensation fees.
Ah, and I'll bill you for the ad later.
Why didn't you ask me first?
Thank you for waiting!
Who is first in line?
I am.
Please come in.
Excuse me.
Everyone, please wait a while.
I'm sorry.
Please wait.
My name is Hakamada, attorney at law.
I am Otsuka Masayo.
Client:
Otsuka Masayo
I'm a housewife.
What can I do for you today?
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
I can't forgive my husband.
Please relax, and give me the details.
My husband is cheating on me.
He's cheating.
Everyone. Please enjoy while you wait.
What's this?
Bread made by Hakamada-sensei himself.
This is...
Awful.
Sorry, can I have a glass of water?
Me, too.
Oh, yes. Right away.
He's been coming home late lately.
Sometimes after 7 P.M.
Do you consider that to be late?
My husband is a public official,
he works at a government office.
Masayo's husband, public official:
Otsuka Toru
His work always ends at 5:30,
so if he came straight home,
he should be home by 6:30.
But, he comes home at 7:00!
There's a gap of thirty minutes.
Thirty minutes?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
I have instructed my husband to report
to me his daily schedule and whereabouts.
I check his cell phone
history every night.
I have set a GPS inside his briefcase.
I am always informed of his whereabouts.
What an oppressive ball and chain.
It's perfectly normal.
I've been addicted lately to this
foreign drama, where I got the idea from.
Iron Spy Woman Marilyn.
Iron Spy Woman
Marilyn
Commandant X,
thank you for this amazing mission.
That show's getting popular.
The result is this.
I have discovered my husband
is taking a ceramics class.
That's suspicious in itself, isn't it?
So I went to the ceramics class,
and spied on him from outside.
And as I suspected...
The instructor is a woman.
Not only that, the woman's
hands and my husband's hands
repeatedly touched each
other during the class.
Maybe she was showing
him how to mold pottery?
You can teach someone how to mold pottery
without touching each other's hands.
I suppose so...
Anyway, I can't forgive my husband.
You can bill him for gobs
of compensation, right?
When you say he's cheating...
Are you referring to
the touching of hands?
Yes. That's right.
Otsuka-san.
We cannot sue for compensation based on
touching hands with the opposite sex.
Huh?
There must be an illicit affair,
which would be grounds for divorce.
Otherwise it would be impossible
to get approval for compensation.
Can you give me a concrete
definition of "illicit affair"?
Simply put, that would be "sex."
Se-Se-Sex?!
Otsuka-san?
Wouldn't that be grounds
for a death sentence?
Who decided that an illicit
affair has to be sex?
As far as I'm concerned, touching hands
with the opposite sex is illicit.
It has already been determined by law.
It would be difficult to sue for
compensation based on your situation.
You're changing the storyline, then.
The storyline?
This manga character is
you, isn't it, Sensei?
Look what it says here.
Is it a lie?
"There is no compensation
fee I cannot get for you!"
fee I cannot get for you"...
What the heck is this?
Water. Water!
Why did you give us that to eat?
Sensei had good intentions.
Kanae-san, may I see you for a moment?
Oh. Yes!
What is the meaning of this?
This is the main
protagonist's catchphrase.
But I've never said
anything like that.
Well, actually, the other day...
We got the results for
February's reader votes.
You're 9th.
Amazing! I'm in the top ten.
That's no ranking to be happy about.
Editor at Tokiwa Publishing:
Tabata Misato
You're 9th in popularity
out of eleven syndications.
Oh, I see.
If you continue flying
under the radar like this,
you could potentially get canceled.
Canceled?
The reader poll rates your
story contents highly...
but the majority of comments said
the leading character is too plain.
I think he needs to have some kind
of quality that attracts the readers.
An attractive quality?
For example, the protagonist
should have a cool catchphrase.
A catchphrase... for example?
Like, "If you have any sympathy,
give me compensation!"
That one sounds familiar.
Then how about, "I won't die
until I get compensated!"
What kind of situation
would that apply to?
"I'll pay the entire
compensation back to you!"
Why would he pay back the compensation?
You are completely wrong.
What?
Cafe waitress:
Mizutani Sara
"There is no compensation
fee I cannot get for you!"
There is no other suitable
catchphrase for your protagonist.
The manga popularity will rise
with it, there is no mistake.
You applied the waitress's
suggestion literally?
She both seems to be and not be
some kind of spiritual medium.
Don't you think a person like that
would be nothing but suspicious?
But don't you think it's
a pretty good catchphrase?
No, I don't.
"There is no compensation fee I
cannot get for you" isn't good.
A lawyer must not
guarantee specific results.
So that's why there's
a crowd out there...
What's the story, then?
You will get me compensation, won't you?
Based on your situation, I
don't think it's possible.
That means this is false advertisement.
"There is no compensation
fee I cannot get for you!"
I will report this to the
appropriate authorities,
and they will take appropriate measures.
I will contact the publisher
of this manga, as well.
No, no, please don't.
Why not?
Because Sensei can do it!
Huh?
Hakamada-sensei is a professional
in lawsuit compensation.
He will assuredly produce satisfactory
results for you, regardless of the situation.
So, it's true then!
Kanae-san, can I have a word?
A lawyer mustn't guarantee
a specific result.
Sensei, please.
It's a crucial time for me,
my syndication just started.
If some weird claim gets associated
with it, it'll quickly get canceled.
Yes, but...
Even if you can't get compensation,
isn't there some way you
can satisfy the client?
But what's impossible is impossible.
You haven't paid me yet
for last month's work.
Huh?
Me, neither.
I can contact the appropriate authorities
and have them take appropriate measures.
This way, please.
Sensei, this way.
Please be seated.
Um, when can we get legal counsel?
I'm sorry, you will have
to wait a little longer.
I didn't come here to eat
this strange, awful bread.
We should go somewhere else.
One moment, please!
I will introduce you to him right away.
He's still talking to a client.
If the people leave, I paid for
the advertisement for nothing.
We just have to listen to what they've got to say.
That's crazy.
Hakamada-sensei can have
the final word, but
we have divorce experience ourselves.
Yes, but...
Kanae-chan, you have
experience with divorce.
Use it as reference,
and hear them out.
Next in line, please.
This way please.
The rest of you, please wait outside.
Hakamada Law Office
She is cheating on me.
So, I want compensation.
When did she start cheating on you?
Client:
Oyama Takayuki
A friend of mine witnessed it
about two months ago,
and told me about it.
I was told Aya was flirting
and walking with another man.
Takayuki's lover
Inui Aya
This has been going on
for two months now, then?
And that's not all!
My other friends have
seen things, too.
I asked them what they saw, and
it seems she's with different men.
She's not only seeing two,
there are maybe three or four other men!
By the way, are you
planning on divorcing her?
Divorce?
No, we're not even married.
Huh?
I'm only in high school, you know.
High school?
And who is this Aya-san?
She's my girlfriend.
We've been going out for almost a year.
Your girlfriend, I see.
Sensei, our client is here.
Yes, yes. Please have a seat.
Are you sure you want
me to call you "Sensei"?
I might not look it,
but I was once a tutor
for my friend's kid.
So the "Sensei" part isn't false.
Now, what can I do for you?
Client:
Sawada Chiharu
I think my husband is cheating on me.
I see.
What, may I ask, is your
husband's profession?
He's a high school teacher.
Chiharu's husband, high school teacher:
Sawada Shuji
It must fall into the forbidden pattern
of the teacher-student love affair!
No, it's not with a student.
Oh. How boring.
Boring?
Ah, pardon me.
So, who is the partner?
I have a picture.
Two weeks ago I coincidentally
saw my husband in town.
It was at a place far from school.
It bothered me so I followed him.
And there it is.
Where's the partner?
That's the partner.
Rock Hard
School
My husband is addicted to sex clubs.
Sex clubs?
This is horrible.
How long must we wait?
After work, my husband often
brings flowers home for me.
Sounds to me like a nice husband.
What's so nice about him?
He's interested in the young
and cute flower shop girl.
I have witnessed my husband
purchasing flowers once.
He had a lecherous look on his face
while she picked flowers for him.
I counted it, he looked
into her eyes seven times.
That could lead to adultery
in a big way, couldn't it?
Well, I'd say that wouldn't...
One time I saw a tag on
the flowers he brought me.
It said "jealous" on it.
That note was meant to challenge me.
It was a message from
that flower shop girl,
that she is jealous of me and
my husband's relationship.
But, those tags are poetic
descriptions of varieties of flowers...
Oh yes, and another thing.
I inspected his briefcase
the other day,
and there was a handcuff
and eye-mask in it.
My husband is entering
the world of S&M!
Um, Sensei,
I need to ask you a question.
I need your help, too.
Could you please wait a moment?
Over here.
Yes.
Here.
Sensei, aren't you done with her yet?
It might take a while.
Why do you ask?
We didn't want to keep the clients
waiting, so we took to counseling them.
Please don't take that
kind of initiative!
When a person poses to be
a lawyer and gives counsel,
Unauthorized counsel
When a non-lawyer gives legal counsel for the purpose of obtaining fees
it's called unauthorized counsel...
You could get arrested for that.
What? Really?
We were just taking down client
information for you, Sensei.
Can compensation be gotten in
the case of a dating couple?
Do sex clubs fall in the
category of adultery?
Can you get compensated by them?
I don't want to say I can't, but...
Would it be difficult?
Maybe there won't be a monetary payoff?
What, there won't be a monetary payoff?
I wasted time listening to her story.
I feel so stupid.
I'm going home.
Looks like business is booming here.
It might get lots of
requests for investigation.
Freelance Investigator:
Umemoto Kurumi
Sorry to say, but I don't
think you'll be needed.
I'm hungry!
Um...
Sensei! Sensei!
What's the matter?
Why are all of you here?
All of us have the same pain.
I was counseling them.
You can't do that here...
You both have been put through so much.
But don't worry.
Leave it to this Sensei.
He will get you plenty of compensation.
I cannot guarantee results.
"There is no compensation
fee I cannot get for you."
Sensei, please help us!
Let's do our best, Sensei.
Then let me ask you this.
Do you hate your mates?
Do I hate him?
Well, sort of...
Of course I hate her.
I hate him.
Then you are ready to
completely crush them, right?
You are, aren't you?
Yes.
I am.
I need your help.
I acknowledge all of
you are ready, then.
Let's send your hated
mates straight to hell.
Umemoto-san, it's your turn.
Huh?
She is our freelance investigator.
She will do a background
check on your mates.
Is there a fee for investigation?
It is essential for us to
win and get compensated.
But don't worry, the
investigation fee is on me.
Umemoto-san.
Please go capture solid evidence
of adultery, immediately.
Right now?
Can you do it?
What are you talking about.
There is no evidence that I can't find.
Just like Marilyn says,
"There is no evidence
that I can't find."
Marilyn.
There is no rest for the spy woman.
Write a list of suspicious women
your husband got involved with.
Understood.
Sensei, why are you having her do that?
In her case,
it would be difficult to establish proof
of an illicit affair with a specific partner.
So, I will tackle this problem
with the quantity of partners.
In case of a court trial,
the information might prove useful.
There's a possibility that
this will go on trial?
It depends on how your
husband will respond.
But even if it goes to
court, there's no problem.
All I have to do is crush your
husband while others watch.
Understood.
Instructor of the ceramics class
The young wife who's been married for one year at the government-office cafeteria
The woman in miniskirt sitting across him on the train
The high school girl who asked him directions on the street
The female cashier he paid money to at the convenience store
This is only part of what I can
remember, but that's most of it.
Instructor of the ceramics class
The young wife who's been married for one year at the government-office cafeteria
The woman in miniskirt sitting across him on the train
The high school girl who asked him directions on the street
The female cashier he paid money to at the convenience store
"The woman with a child who
sat next to him on the bus"?
Yes. He was pretending
to adore the child
while trying to make
a move on the mother.
That's too brief of an encounter, though.
It's enough.
Huh?
By the way, what is your
husband doing today?
Let's see.
Today is a half-day, so
he's off work at noon.
How convenient.
Let's allow him to do what he wants today.
What? Why?
Aren't you curious to know what
your husband does in his free time?
A relationship of merely "seeing
each other" has no legal protection.
Does that mean you can't
sue for compensation?
Please hear me out.
Even in the case of dating,
if there has been promise
of future marriage,
a compensation lawsuit is possible if
there has been a breach of that promise.
By the way, did the two of
you plan to get married?
No, I'm still in high school.
Huh?
Yes, he's a high school student.
How old are you?
I'm eighteen.
And your partner?
She's nineteen.
She's in vocational school.
Then you're both of the age
to get legally married.
It shouldn't be a problem.
Have the two of you ever
discussed marriage?
Did we ever discuss marriage?
Did you attend someone's
wedding together,
or make mutual promises of marrying
each other, that kind of thing.
She did say she wanted
to get married early.
I think we might've texted
each other about it.
Here it is.
Yay
Hey
What would you do if I said
I wanted to get married?
I'm in high school you know? I can't plan that far ahead (lol)
That's a little weak.
Because it's a one-sided
question that she'd posed...
Is that so?
Oh, then what if I propose to her?
That is something we could try.
Depending on her reply, we could
have it as outstanding evidence.
Isn't that a little unfair?
But, you want give her hell, don't you?
The end will justify the means.
Yes.
Frequenting sex clubs is an
outstandingly illicit affair.
I've had several cases in the past of
compensation lawsuits on those grounds.
Is that so?
By the way...
when is the last time you
had sex with your husband?
Sensei, how could you ask that?
It's often the case that when husbands
begin frequenting sex clubs,
marriages become sexless.
If we can prove his illicit activity of
sex clubs and that your marriage is sexless,
that would beef up the
compensation fee.
When was the last time?
The day before yesterday.
Huh? That's quite recent.
We do it at least twice a week.
That's quite feisty.
In that case, please
recall in fine detail.
For example, ever since he started
frequenting hostess clubs,
foreplay has become sloppy,
or he has become naughtier...
Is there any little change
you can think of?
What's gotten into you, Sensei?
You seem to be enthused all of a sudden.
You were so reluctant at first.
I acknowledge everyone's
willingness to fight.
I'm only responding accordingly.
Um...
Hello, Hakamada speaking.
Masayo's husband:
Otsuka Toru
It's Umemoto.
I'm currently tailing Otsuka
Masayo-san's husband, Toru-san.
He seems to be on his way to the flower
shop, toward his alleged adulterous partner.
Have you captured any
evidence of adultery?
No, not yet.
Even for you, investigating for three
people at once must be difficult.
No.
In season 6 episode 2,
Marilyn did background checks on
eighteen people simultaneously.
Compared to that, this is a cinch.
I'll leave it in your hands.
I've got some noteworthy
information, however,
I sent you an email.
I'm continuing my pursuit.
Hakamada
Law Office
Interim investigation report
"Bread baking correspondence course"
Your item has been shipped
Subject
Umemoto Kurumi
Breadmaker Crafts
Yuasa Pantry
What has my husband been up to?
The GPS is showing
he's all over the map.
It appears he's taking full
advantage of his freedom.
I should have plenty of evidence soon.
I see.
Sensei. I proposed to her like you said.
I appreciate the sentiment,
but you don't have to say that
I've been thinking I want to marry you after all.
She turned me down.
Don't fret.
We have no problem if we have
proof that you want to marry her.
I understand.
Sensei.
Did you find out anything
about my husband?
Please don't worry.
An outstanding investigator is
currently investigating him.
I think we will have
evidence quite soon.
Is that so?
Hakamada
Law Office
Are you here for legal counsel?
Yes.
How long have you been waiting here?
Since 8:30 this morning.
I'm so sorry.
We will get to you right away.
Oh no, I can wait till
the others are finished.
My case isn't a big deal, so...
It's okay, Sensei is just kneading
bread dough right now.
Please come in.
Sensei, we have another client.
Huh?
She has been here since early morning.
Nice to meet you.
Understood, please have a seat.
Please have a seat.
Excuse me.
Client:
Kumagai Setsuko
I've been married to my
husband for fifteen years.
Our marriage had been arranged
by both our parents.
Everyone, please don't eavesdrop.
Lawyers are sworn to client
confidentiality, you know.
Come on, lighten up.
Yoshie-san, when did you come back?
You shouldn't do this.
I live for gossip.
Don't take it away from me, I'll die.
My husband's partner is a friend
of his from back in college.
My husband has introduced me to her,
and I've seen her several times since.
So, when did your
husband's adultery begin?
Probably...
from before we got married.
What?
This is good.
He had been seeing her
before we were married.
It appears the relationship still
continued after our marriage.
Adultery for fifteen years, wow.
This is quite a case.
Maybe it's worth more than
ten million in compensation.
Amazing.
Ten million yen...
Their secret trysts are perhaps
once or twice a month.
His partner has a husband as well.
A double-adultery to boot.
This is a big fish.
Don't lose it, Sensei!
That's enough, really.
So you say, but you're
pulling me so weakly.
You want to eavesdrop, too, don't you?
How much compensation
are you hoping for?
For compensation...
I want nothing.
You do plan to divorce him, correct?
No.
I have no intention of divorcing him.
It's laughable, I know,
but, I love my husband.
My husband is a kind man.
We talk a lot over dinner every day.
We travel a lot together.
I have many fond memories.
If I were to divorce him,
it would be tantamount to
throwing everything away.
Those memories will turn into regret.
I absolutely wouldn't
want that to happen.
What then is it you want, Kumagai-san?
What I want...
is for my husband to stop
seeing the other woman.
That is all.
Understood.
I will send a notice within a few days to
your husband's adulterous partner.
I will state that there are grounds
for lawsuit compensation,
but if the adulterous
relationship were to stop,
compensation will not be pursued.
Since she is married as well,
I'm sure she'd want to
protect her own household.
I will probably get her quick consent.
Sensei, thank you for everything.
You can thank me when
everything works out.
Are you sure you don't
want compensation?
Yes.
Understood.
Everyone, thank you for waiting.
I've made preparation to take a bundle
in compensation from your hateful partners.
Let me explain your respective strategies.
Who should I start with?
Please go ahead of me.
No, I'll wait.
Otsuka-san was here first.
Understood.
Please come with me.
What's the matter with you all?
I think I'm going to give
it a little more thought.
What?
I think I want to do that too, maybe.
Sort of.
Me, too.
But why?
We've got plenty evidence, you know.
These are photos of
Otsuka-san's husband.
When he was freed of his shackles,
he seems to have enjoyed his freedom.
At the flower shop.
At the ceramics class.
There were cute ladies present
in both establishments.
Our investigator spoke
with both those women.
And it seems your husband goes to those
places based on dubious pretexts.
Masayo-san, you and your husband
are having a ten year anniversary, correct?
He's been telling those women,
that he's preparing
secret gifts for you.
At the flower shop,
he said he was going to choose
his own flower bouquet.
At the ceramics class,
he said he was going to make
original his-and-her teacups.
As to the handcuff and eye-mask,
it seems he was going to perform some kind of
magic trick to surprise you on your anniversary.
Supposedly, he wants to show you how
much he appreciates your watching over him.
Pretexts like that are quite common.
It's a way of appealing to
partners, letting them know
they're married, so all
they want is to be lovers.
What a devious husband he is.
Next, Oyama-san.
Our investigator sent these photos.
Huh?
An obstetrics clinic...
Obstetrics Clinic
It seems Aya-san
has a child in her womb.
Huh?
According to investigation, she's
been pregnant for three months.
But, then again, who knows
whose baby it could be.
And it seems she's going
to have the baby.
To save up for raising the child, she
started working at a hostess club.
She's quite dandy, and is popular
with the customers there.
I hear her job is to accompany those
customers out to town, and quite often.
Accompany...
So it seems quite clear now,
that she's been wanting
to marry you for real.
Now, we can easily prove that
she's made a breach of promise.
And Sawada-san, regarding your husband...
He went straightway to the
establishment after school today.
Look how crisp the photo is.
This is sufficient evidence
for illicit activity.
However, there's one thing
I need to let you know.
The establishment your husband went to
was not the sex club on the third floor.
He went to the establishment with
a gay clientele, on the fourth floor.
Gay Bar
Me and My Bro
What?
So that's how it was...
Not only that,
as confirmed by the establishment,
your husband would select a young
man there, who was a former student of his.
They said he was never
there to enjoy himself,
but would talk to the young man,
trying to convince him of things.
They said he was trying to find the
young man another place of employment.
The people at the establishment
find your husband to be a nuisance.
Anyway, who cares why
he goes to that place.
We have this photo, which
is sufficient evidence.
Now, who wants to
start their case first?
I'm going home for today.
Why is that?
Today is our ten-year anniversary.
I should have a present
ready for him, too.
But maybe your husband
didn't get you anything.
It's all a pretext to meet with
those female employees.
He's not that kind of man!
I'm sorry.
I see...
Me, too!
I owe her an apology.
What for?
She's the one that should apologize.
The baby she's carrying... is mine.
You can't know that.
She's been seen with many
different men, hasn't she?
Aya isn't like that!
It's all my fault.
I'm pathetic.
I should've said I wanted to marry her.
She wouldn't have had to
go work at a hostess club.
So I'm...
going to propose to her again!
And of course, I'll look for a job!
I see.
I'll be going home, too.
But why?
The boy who works at that establishment
was an outstanding student.
My husband had high hopes for him.
I think my husband was trying
to free him from the sex industry,
and find him legitimate employment.
No, no.
He's probably a closet homosexual.
That's not possible!
I told you my husband and
I have frequent intercourse.
I said it was the day before
yesterday when we did it last...
But we did it last night, too.
He must be shouldering
concern for his student.
He was more intense with me than usual.
I see.
I know I'm overstepping my bounds,
but all of you are foolish.
You have me as your
legal representative.
There is no compensation
fee I cannot get for you.
Are you all telling me, that you
want something more than money?
Yes.
Yes!
I do.
Understood.
Well, that's that, then.
Hakamada Law Office
I'm back...
Good work, Umemoto-san.
Good job.
That was a lot of work.
Oh yeah, Sensei.
I kept pursuing those targets,
and took these pictures.
Sensei, did you know it was going to
turn out like this from the start?
Of course not.
I just gave everyone the facts.
But, as to how they would
process those facts,
it was entirely up to the clients.
Before you start basking in your glory,
you owe me for the investigations.
Invoice
Huh?
You said you were going to
foot the bill, didn't you?
Well, can you please wait a little?
Why?
You should've made a bundle
with all those clients.
I didn't make any money
from the clients today.
Because counseling is free, right?
Do you realize how much hardship
we're having because of you?
I assure you, I will pay
you at a later date.
Here's the bill for the
ad in the manga mag.
I'll leave this to you, too!
I received an official reply
from your husband's partner.
She consented to the term in the notice,
and will call off her
relationship with him.
Sensei, I am truly sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
I shouldn't have asked a lawyer
to step in to ask for her to call it off.
Well, it's an unusual case,
but there are many ways
I can be of assistance.
I don't know much about these things.
I've asked other lawyers in the
past, and they all turned me down.
You have taken on an
unreasonable request.
I am truly grateful.
Please don't be concerned.
I never turn down anyone
who is truly in need.
Hey, did you drop the catchphrase?
Where he says, "There is no
compensation fee I cannot get for you."
I did.
The protagonist's
catchphrase is now this.
Huh?
"I never turn down anyone
who is truly in need."
I never turn down anyone
who is truly in need.
I think this catchphrase
suits the protagonist better.
I think it's good, too.
Huh?
There can be no other
catchphrase for this protagonist.
She changes what she says
from one minute to the next.
I never turn down anyone
who is truly in need.
Hakamada-sensei's father?
Next episode
Hey Yukio, long time no see.
His client is his long lost father!
They meet again after 30 years...
That person is the most
disreputable person in the world.
Hakamada's younger sister's wish...
My father is being tricked.
To settle the feud between father and child!
Please protect your father!
That man is not my father.
This drama is a work of fiction
Why must you be so obstinate?