Beautician
Nishijima Aoi
Dress shirts, underwear, socks...
Whoops, forgot the toiletries.
Three articles for husbands and wives
1. Living expenses are half and half.
2. No interfering in each other's work.
3. Never forget love and respect.
Business trip
Nagoya branch
Aoi salon
Business trip
Nagoya branch
Aoi salon
Aoi meeting @ Shibuya
Business trip
Nagoya branch
Aoi salon
Aoi dentist
Kohei comes home!
Tokyo arrival 22:00
Aoi salon
Aoi's husband
Hirano Kohei
Careful, careful.
All right, packed.
Ko-chan.
You're all packed.
Oh. Thank you.
Crap, it's this late already?!
Crap!
Here, here.
This business trip
is for five days, right?
Yeah.
I'll make you your favorite
fried shrimp when you get back.
Yeah.
Take care of yourself.
See you.
Have a nice trip.
I better hurry, too.
Office - Tomoya
Mobile
Hello.
What time are you coming home today?
What?
Huh?
Isn't this Kohei-san's—
What are you doing?!
I thought it was a call
from your office.
Who was that—
Crap, the bullet train!
I'm off!
Hey, Ko-chan!
Sorry about that.
My office coworker picked
up my phone by mistake.
Yeah.
I see. How did that go?
It's not too hot?
It's fine.
Um...
I'm so sorry. Pardon me.
5 days later
Aoi salon
Business trip
Nagoya branch
Aoi salon
Aoi dentist
Kohei comes home!
Tokyo arrival 22:00
Aoi salon
The person you have dialed is not available.
Please leave your name and message.
Hello, Ko-chan?
Why aren't you home yet?
You could've at least called
to tell me you'd be late.
See you.
Kohei
Hello.
Where are you?
Aoi, I'm sorry.
Did something happen at work?
Can you come home?
I'm not coming back.
Let's split up.
Huh?!
I'm really sorry.
Hold on a second!
Is it that woman?
Just forget about me!
Wait a second!
Kohei
I'm not coming back.
Let's split up.
Kohei-san.
You forgot this.
Oh, my bad. You saved me.
Thank you.
Say, Kohei-san.
What?
Oh, nothing.
Have a nice day.
You, too.
I'm sorry.
Aoi-san?
Huh?
What's the matter?
You're not quite yourself today.
Hakmada's Assistant
Nonomura Kanae
Did something happen?
Actually...
Hakamada Law Office
Kanae-chan is late today.
She's probably having
her hair done nicely.
Sweet
My Best Hair
Temp
Shinozuka Rina
First a cut, then dyeing.
Oh, and maybe a perm,
and a hair-pack, too.
Office landlord
Toyama Yoshie
All that?
Makes me tired just hearing about it.
It's spring, the time for
a change in your image.
Bound to draw attention
Best of spring hair
The one who really needs
an image change is this guy.
You can say that again.
He said he's growing out his
sideburns or something.
Really?
Sorry I'm late!
Please.
Huh?
I thought you went to beauty salon.
I did. Sensei?
But nothing's changed.
She actually looks worse.
Sensei, I brought a client with me.
Attorney
Hakamada Yukio
I understand now.
Your husband cheated on you,
then decided to separate from you.
So, Aoi-san, what do you plan on doing?
I... just want to know the truth.
What more truth do you need?
He has another woman
and wants to separate.
End of story.
Yoshie-san.
It's spring after all.
People change in spring.
But, we lived together
for two whole years.
Then he calls me
to say goodbye?
I don't understand it.
Do you still feel attached to him?
"Attached," huh?
I just want a proper explanation.
Because if he's dumping
me for that woman,
then, I'll...
Divorce him, and sue
him for compensation?
Yes.
But...
But?
But to divorce...
we'd have to be officially married.
What?
But, you're husband and wife, right?
You've been married for two years...
but not legally married?
You're out of touch.
It's something called
"common-law marriage."
Common-law marriage.
Simply put, it's not an officially
documented marriage.
But... why?
Well...
There's a lot of that nowadays.
Husband and wife can be
independent of each other,
there are no in-laws
they have to endure.
It's quite casual.
A casual marriage...
the end of the world is near.
But if they're not in
an official registry,
can she still sue for compensation?
Forget it.
What a disappointment.
That's too bad.
No, that's not the case.
Then...
Even without legal registration...
you can still receive compensation.
Divorce Chaser
~Let's Turn Your Tears into Money~
Divorce Chaser Episode 9
"Two wives" in a heroic battle!
Ordinarily, common-law marriages have
aspects in common with legal marriages.
In other words, they have the
obligation of mutual cooperation,
Obligation of mutual cooperation
Obligation of mutual fidelity
and the obligation of mutual fidelity.
If we can prove that you two were
living together in common-law marriage,
then it's possible to sue for compensation,
just as if you were legally married.
I see...
But, how can she prove that it
was a common-law marriage?
There are two aspects.
Aspects proving common-law marriage
Number one.
The couple is eventually
planning to register the marriage.
The couple is eventually planning to register the marriage.
Number two.
They are living together
as husband and wife.
They are living together as husband and wife.
Then, yes.
We both planned on getting
legally married,
and we lived together
as husband and wife.
So, we need proof of those things.
Proof?
The most effective proof would be documents
with both your names on them.
For example,
a certificate of residence,
with one of your names
listed as "head of household."
That is, one of you listed as head of household,
Head of Household: Hirano Kohei
Name: Hirano Kohei
Relationship: Self
Head of Household: Hirano Kohei
Name: Nishijima Aoi
Relationship: Wife (unregistered)
and the other listed as
"unregistered wife or husband."
Relationship: Wife (unregistered)
We have separate
certificates of residence.
Then how about an
apartment rental agreement?
Apartment Rental Agreement
Is the rental agreement
in both your names?
Renter name(s): Hirano Kohei
Nishijima Aoi
No.
He moved into the apartment
where I was already living.
I see...
Then, is there anyone who can prove
that you two were husband and wife?
For example, your respective parents,
or friends, or people at work?
I never introduced him to my parents...
I've never met his friends, either.
My husband is always
away on business trips.
There's no proof, then.
You've got no proof whatsoever, then.
Thank you for waiting.
I'm Umemoto, freelance investigator.
Freelance Investigator
Umemoto Kurumi
We weren't waiting, particularly.
Oh?
Didn't I hear you say there's no proof?
I said that.
If you need solid proof,
see Iron Spy Woman: Marilyn,
season 10 episode 9.
Iron Spy Woman
Marilyn
You were careless.
Because the proof is
always in one's memories.
Reflect, and there
you'll find the proof.
Bang!
What?
Where? Where?
It's in my memories?
That's right.
You lived together for
two whole years, right?
Follow your memories, and you'll
definitely find something.
Come to think of it...
Would a photo in a wedding dress
count as proof?
Was there a wedding ceremony?
No, we didn't have a ceremony,
but we wanted a keepsake photo.
That would work as proof.
Also, there's a written pledge.
A written pledge?
Yes.
We wrote down three articles we
pledged to keep as husband and wife.
Three articles for husband and wife
1. Living expenses are half and half.
2. No interfering in each other's work.
3. Never forget love and respect.
We could use that, too.
There's more, isn't there?
In your sweet memories as a couple.
There's a calendar with
both our schedules on it.
That's good.
I also have his-and-hers tea cups.
Okay.
You found them.
In your "sweet memories"!
Anyway, you have to gather
as much evidence as you can.
Yes.
And Umemoto-san,
please investigate the
husband's adultery.
Roger.
Aoi-san.
Hakamada-sensei will help,
I assure you.
Yes.
Come in.
Pardon me.
Done moving yet?
Yes, thank you for your help.
We're having your inaugural ceremony
on a Monday, two weeks from now.
Yes. sir.
Company President
Fujioka Shigeru
You, the young newbie,
were recommended
before all your seniors.
So, get ready for some turbulence.
As we've discussed before,
don't get yourself into any hot water,
No mistakes or any kind of trouble
you need to be rescued from.
I am fully aware of that.
I have risen to my position
thanks to you, President.
Thank you very much.
By the way, Tomomi called me.
She's worried you might cheat on her.
She has nothing to worry about.
I can trust you?
Of course.
Huh?
It's gone.
Why?
The teacups, too.
Gone.
Ko-chan...
The number you have dialed
is not in service.
Please check the number and try again.
I'm sorry.
No.
Please.
All of his things were gone
when I got home from work last night.
All of his things?
What about the evidence?
Do you have any stored
data on your computer?
Oh.
Documents
Finances
Hairstyles (1)
Hairstyles (2)
Photos
Videos
This folder is empty.
How could this happen?
It seems he took more than
just his own belongings.
What do you mean?
Just looking at this room alone,
there's no indication
a husband lived here.
In other words,
Kohei-san erased every
trace of himself from here.
This can't be happening.
Perhaps Kohei-san is
knowledgable about the law.
What?
He took a mitigating course of action,
in order to avoid getting sued by Aoi-san.
That would be my guess.
Ko-chan would do that?
Why?
What now, Sensei?
We can't prove the common-law marriage.
This is going to be difficult.
Umemoto-san?
Things are getting complicated.
Complicated?
Look at this.
I knew it.
So, she's his illicit partner?
No. She's not.
Who is, then?
This woman's name is Hirano Tomomi-san.
She is Hirano Kohei-san's legal spouse.
What?!
Huh?
Which means,
Hirano Kohei-san's illicit partner...
is you, Aoi-san.
Me?
I'm the illicit partner?
Wait a second. What does that mean?
Investigation Report
Kohei-san works at Fuji House Tech,
at the main office in Nagoya.
Employee Profile
Name: Hirano Kohei
Division: Fuji House Tech Nagoya, Main Office
For half of the month,
he would come to
Tokyo on business trips.
"He would come to Tokyo"?
You mean he'd go from Tokyo, right?
No, that's not what I said.
It's the opposite.
On one of these trips to Tokyo,
he met you, Aoi-san,
and entered a common-law
marriage with you.
It started two years ago, right?
Yes.
Subsequently, he met
Tomomi-san in Nagoya,
and got legally married to her.
Name: Tomomi | Wife | Married March 4, 2013
And that was one year ago.
Wife | Married March 4, 2013
But, Aoi-san is his wife...
Is this bigamy?
In addition,
Tomomi-san is the daughter
of the company president.
The president's daughter?
Maybe the marriage paid off.
In two weeks,
he's getting promoted to an executive
position at Fuji House Tech's Tokyo Branch.
I understand.
For the sake of his promotion,
he had to eradicate his double life.
That's why asked you for a separation.
That's how it is.
Good job. You're smart.
Anyway, I have to go now.
This is no longer an issue
of simple adultery.
Are you all right, Aoi-san?
I've been fooled, all this time.
And I believed him.
I can't forgive him.
This is too horrible!
Everyone.
We got a new client.
Her husband is cheating on her,
and she wants to sue him for compensation.
She even has photos taken by a private
detective agency to present as evidence.
You scored.
Two jobs back to back.
I think I can expect rent
payment this month.
Where is the client?
Oh. Whoops.
Please come in!
This way.
Please come in.
Kohei's wife
Hirano Tomomi
She looks familiar.
You.
Are you Nishijima Aoi?
I am, so what?
What was that for?
Take your hands off my husband!
That's my line!
I'm his wife!
How could you be his wife?
You can't be his wife!
This is getting good!
Sensei, you have to stop them!
Please calm down, both of you.
Shut up!
Listen, Ko-chan is...
"Ko-chan"?
Who are you to call him "Ko-chan"?
You're a liar!
You bitch!
Insane hag!
Home wrecker!
Please stop it, both of you!
You're both victims here!
Victims?
Don't lump me in with this woman.
This woman is my Kohei-san's mistress!
I can prove it!
See, now you know.
This woman is a liar.
You've got it wrong.
Aoi-san has been Kohei-san's
common-law wife for two years.
Two years?
Common-law wife?
Kohei-san kept it secret from you,
and married you just the same.
That's a lie.
A lie!
Aoi-san. Tomomi-san.
Show me your left hands.
Left hand?
The same ring?
Aoi-san.
When did Kohei-san give you that ring?
In March, last year.
It wasn't our anniversary or anything.
He just suddenly gave it to me.
What? In March...
That was the same time he
married you, Tomomi-san.
This means Kohei-san
gave two identical rings to both
of you around the same time.
That way he wouldn't have to keep
switching his own matching wedding band,
whether he was in Tokyo or Nagoya.
You two understand now, right?
He was fooling you both.
You are both his victims.
You're wrong. You're wrong!
That ring is just a coincidence.
My surname is Hirano.
I'm in the public registry as his wife.
But how could you prove
that you're his wife?!
Well...
You see?
I am suing this woman for compensation.
Sensei.
Please be my legal representative.
Unfortunately, I cannot do that.
What?
I am Aoi-san's legal representative.
And you want to sue Aoi-san,
if I took you on as a client,
it would be a conflict of interest.
Also, Aoi-san did not know that
Kohei-san was married to you.
So you cannot sue her for compensation.
I can't?
But, Tomomi-san,
if it is Kohei-san you are
suing for compensation,
I can take you on as my client.
Sue Kohei-san?
Yes.
Tomomi-san.
Care to team up with Aoi-san?
What?
You will cooperate with each other,
and be a team.
What?
What are you talking about?
You saw what happened.
That's right. They'll never be a team.
Are you stupid?
Why would I sue Kohei-san?
Forget it.
I don't need a lawyer like you.
I'll talk to my father,
and I'll sue her for compensation.
Sensei.
I know it was an impossible suggestion.
But to prove that
Kohei-san had two wives...
that would have been the best way.
What was I thinking?
I thought we didn't need
to make it official.
When we first started living together,
I once asked Ko-chan,
"What do we do next?"
Then Ko-chan said...
Marriage Registration
I don't want to be legally
bound by a piece of paper.
Who cares about formality? What matters
is how we feel about each other.
I want to live with you forever, Aoi.
What about you, Aoi?
Me, too.
You see? We're already husband and wife.
Husband and wife?
I think of you as my wife.
I would've never imagined
something like this could happen.
We were happy together.
I believed what mattered
was how we felt about each
other, like Ko-chan said.
But, now that I'm in this mess...
I don't have a single thing
to prove I am his wife.
I'm so frustrated...
that I have to suffer like this
because of a lousy piece of paper.
Aoi-san...
Kohei-san.
Were you married to this woman?
Of course not.
I met this woman
at an attorney's office.
What?
Please, tell me the truth.
I'm sorry.
I have slept with her,
just once, before I married you...
I was drunk when it happened.
But it was only once!
She's being following me ever since.
But she was wearing the
same ring I'm wearing.
She must've seen mine, and bought it.
What's this, then?
I went there to ask her
not to follow me any more.
I had to protect my life with you.
So, she was a stalker?
That's right!
She's a stalker!
We'd better report her
to the police, then.
Huh?
Um... let's not do that.
As you know, Tomomi,
I just got promoted, and this
is a crucial time for me.
If this this gets out of hand,
it would be distressing
to your father, as well.
How can you not believe me?
Tomomi.
I've only got one thing to say.
The most precious thing
to me in the world...
is you, Tomomi.
I want to live with you forever.
Don't you feel the same way, Tomomi?
Kohei-san.
I can believe you, right?
Of course you can.
Well...
That was a convincing performance.
So that's how you fool those women.
How rude.
Who are you?
My apologies for the late introduction.
I am Nishijima Aoi-san's legal
representative, Hakamada.
So you're the one that
fed Tomomi those stories.
You are a terrible person.
To think you'd selfishly call off your
common-law marriage with Aoi-san,
all because of a promotion.
Common-law marriage?
Is there any evidence of that?
There isn't.
You destroyed the evidence,
as you well know.
This is ridiculous.
There will be consequences
to what you have done.
But I didn't do anything.
Soon, you will be officially slapped
with a compensation lawsuit.
Like I said, I didn't do anything!
Common-law marriages are certainly
precarious, aren't they?
Yes. I'm thoroughly convinced
they are, thanks to this case.
That's my line!
What?!
Take your hands
off my husband!
But in this episode,
the two women team up, right?
Editor at Tokiwa Publishing
Tabata Misato
That's right.
Can something like that happen?
Well, you see...
There is no other way.
Cafe waitress
Mizutani Sara
I'm the wife. Nice to meet you.
I'm also the wife. Nice to meet you.
Oh no, we can't join hands.
Our hands...
please lend me your hand.
You'd better not see this.
Help!
Somebody stop us!
Hakamada Law Office
Sensei.
I still think it's impossible
for them to team up.
How do you plan to convince Tomomi-san?
I don't know.
All I know is...
I want to help them both.
Kanae-san.
I want to see Aoi-san's
apartment once more.
Huh?
What are you looking for?
I don't know.
What?
Is it possible to perfectly extinguish
every trace of living
together for two years?
What is this?
Oh... that's Haccho miso paste.
I see.
Sensei.
Wait just a second...
That's my underwear drawer.
Oh. I understand.
Sorry...
May I use your bathroom?
Please do.
He's an unusual man.
Oh. Isn't he?
I feel better now.
Sensei, did you find a clue?
I found several.
What?
What do you want from me?
Are you still trying to team
me up with her?
Yes.
I know I'm overstepping my bounds,
but you and she are both victims.
I believe Kohei-san.
I see.
In that case...
let me confirm one last thing.
Confirm?
Concerning the photo you had the
private detective agency take.
That photo was dated March 6, correct?
It was. So what?
That was day that any trace of Kohei-san
vanished from Aoi-san's apartment.
What?
So you're saying Kohei-san
hid the evidence?
The final decision is up to you.
Think about it calmly.
By the way,
I will be presenting your husband with
a compensation lawsuit tomorrow.
It will be at your husband's
office, at 2:00PM.
Oh, there's one more thing.
The toilet paper you use at home.
Is it ultra soft,
two-ply "Happiness"?
It is... so?
Aoi-san. Are you okay?
Yes.
This is your first time seeing
Kohei-san since then, right?
Yes.
Shall we go?
Where's Tomomi-san?
I firmly believe she will show up.
Tomomi-san's not here.
I was afraid of that.
Have fun while you still can.
Well, I'm glad for him.
We'll see how it goes.
I'm counting on you, starting today.
Yes.
Hirano-san.
There are people here to see you.
To see me?
Sorry to interrupt while you're busy.
I have urgent matters
to discuss with you, Hirano-san.
You shouldn't show up
at work, it's indecent.
"Indecent"?
You're in no position
to use that word.
What are you talking about?
Anyway, you'd better leave.
What's going on here?
Nothing, sir.
Come in here.
Take a seat.
What the hell's going on here?
Oh well, this is... um...
I'm glad you're here.
This discussion concerns
your daughter as well, Fujioka-san.
Tomomi? What would be—
Nothing, really.
President, there really is nothing.
Let's hear what you've got to say.
Hirano-san is a bigamist,
one of them by common-law marriage.
Bigamist?
I don't understand. Please explain.
He entered into a common-law marriage
with Nishijima Aoi-san.
He kept it secret,
and married your
daughter, Tomomi-san.
What?
President. This is an outrageous lie.
He took advantage of his
frequent business trips.
One half of the month he spent
with Aoi-san in Tokyo.
And the other half of the month he spent
with Tomomi-san in Nagoya.
He was living a double life.
You have no proof of this
trumped-up nonsense!
I found proof.
What?
This.
What the hell is that?
It's ultra-soft, two-ply "Happiness."
Sorry to ask,
but do you have some kind
of issue with your rear?
What the hell are you talking about?
I used it, too.
It's so soft, it could be addicting.
It costs 800 yen for just four rolls.
It's super-high-quality toilet paper.
It's a two-ply, scented.
It's soft like genuine cotton.
This is ridiculous.
What can you prove with that thing?
You can buy that thing anywhere.
He doesn't use anything else.
The problem here is this.
You have specified this brand
to Aoi-san, to buy nothing else.
And you've made the same specification
to Tomomi-san, haven't you?
That's exactly correct.
We use the same toilet paper at home.
Tomomi.
Tomomi-san.
Kohei-san.
You don't use any other
brand, remember?
You seem to be quite
picky with your things.
For toothpaste, you use...
the one with salt granules.
For socks...
Five-toed ones.
For insect repellant...
Forest Aroma.
Pickled plums?
Dipped in honey.
Miso paste?
Haccho miso!
This kind of familiarity can't be
gleaned from a one-night stand.
It would be impossible to know unless
you've lived together for a long time.
That does prove
that you have been in marriage
relationships with both of them.
They prove nothing...
There was plenty of other evidence.
But you destroyed it all, didn't you?
I did no such thing.
Aoi-san.
What day were Kohei-san's things
taken from your apartment?
March 6th.
So that's what you were
doing in this picture!
Aoi-san.
I'm sorry for the terrible
things I said the other day.
I am, too.
Hirano Kohei-san.
You have wrought serious psychological
anguish on Nishijima Aoi-san.
Hence, you will be sued for five
million yen in compensation.
Compensation Fee Lawsuit
Five mill—
Kohei-san.
I am divorcing you.
Wait a minute—
Hakamada-sensei.
How much can I sue him
for compensation?
For illicit activities,
psychological anguish...
in total, approximately four million yen.
I'll leave it to you.
In that case,
Tomomi-san and Aoi-san's
compensation fees
will total nine million yen.
I don't have that kind of money!
You can use your severance pay.
Huh?
As of today, you are fired.
Huh...
This can't be happening.
I will have Tomomi-san's documents
written and mailed out soon.
Contact my office with
your new mailing address.
Ko-chan, thanks for the two years.
Aoi.
Goodbye.
Wow.
So the husband lost everything.
And what happened to the two wives?
They've formed a friendship
out of mutual commiseration.
Tomomi-san is one of Aoi-san's
beauty salon clients, now.
So, everything worked out
the way Sensei planned?
That's how it went.
I feel better now.
Hey, that's...
I used it once, now I'm addicted.
You should all try it.
But that's a high quality brand.
It's 800 yen for just four rolls.
Expensive!
Hey, Sensei.
You haven't paid your rent,
and you're spending money on this?
You owe me back wages, too!
But this is really amazing!
Are you saying we're less
important than toilet paper?
No...
Just try it once.
You'll see what I mean.
It's addictive.
Ultra soft, two-ply "Happiness."
It gets flushed down
the toilet just the same.
That's true, but...
Next episode
Her mother-in-law is awful.
Come on, get on with it.
It's filthy here.
Suing the mother-in-law for compensation!
It's a pig sty.
I've endured her this long,
After relentless bullying, the wife takes action!
but I've reached my limit.
We can sue the mother-in-law
for compensation, too.
This drama is a work of fiction.