Misaki
Hello?
Go to the cleaners and get my blouse.
Right now?
You'll make it if you run.
Cleaning
White Express
Did you get it?
I ran as fast as I could...
but they had just closed the shutter...
What am I supposed to wear
to tomorrow's dinner party?
I-I understand, I'll get it
first thing in the morning!
You're useless!
The dishes are piled up.
Hey Kanae-chan, are you
getting used to working here?
Office landlord:
Toyama Yoshie
Not at all, yet.
But I'm getting used to killing time.
Hakamada's assistant:
Nonomura Kanae
There's no work to do at all.
Temp:
Shinozuka Rina
There's no appointments
today, either.
Hurry up and play your card.
There, I won.
I didn't hear you say "Uno!"
I said it.
Liar!
The current episode's client:
Ichikawa Tomohiro
I said it!
And I won fair and square.
You're on a winning streak.
Um... this is a law office, right?
A client?
Are you a client?
We've been waiting for you.
Let me get your coat for you.
Please, please, please. This way.
Sit. Sit.
My goodness.
We haven't had a male client in so long.
Is it adultery? Did she cheat on you?
No, I...
Sensei, are you ready?
Yes...
Thank you for waiting.
I am the attorney, Hakamada.
Attorney:
Hakamada Yukio
Sensei, what are you doing? Get tea!
Ah, yes.
I think I'd better go somewhere elseー
There, just relax.
I have work to doー
Please sit down.
I slept well.
I see.
So you're being vexed by a monster wife.
"Monster wife"?
A monster wife. A wife who
changes after the wedding,
and menaces the husband.
Women are stronger than men nowadays.
Compared to women, these men are...
There are many kinds of monster wives.
The visual type, mental type,
and sexual type.
What type is she?
I don't know...
I'm a marketer for a software company.
My wife is a homemaker.
She rarely does anything at the house.
But she has control over finances...
Tomohiro's wife:
Ichikawa Misaki
How long of a shower are you
gonna take? What a waste!
Gas bills aren't cheap, you know?
They cut your pay,
so think before you act.
I'm cutting 5,000 yen from
your allowance starting this month.
W-Wait!
10,000 yen a month isn't enough...
There's no space left for me at home...
She buys nothing but brand-name items...
She goes to spas that cost
hundreds of thousands...
She goes out to lunches at first-rate hotels...
I see... expenditures.
What else?
Is there any domestic violence?
As soon as she loses her temper,
she resorts to violence.
Recently she's learned a new technique:
the roundhouse kick.
I understand.
So, she's the violent-type monster.
I'm at my wit's end.
These days, when I get home from work,
I get intensely anxious...
I get frequent headaches...
Say, never mind that.
What about adultery?
Who's she cheating with?
What?
You know, your wife's lover.
As far as I know, she hasn't been cheating.
What? She hasn't?
Yes.
This is hopeless.
You're right.
Hopeless?
Why is that?
Divorces not based on adultery
can become prolonged.
Plus, it's difficult for a husband
to get compensation from a wife.
It is a fact that women have
an advantage in court.
Is that so?
This is quicksand. Quicksand.
Sensei, drop him.
He doesn't fit the bill, and who
knows if he can get compensated.
No.
We can get paid.
Huh?
Compensation in a lawsuit based on the infliction
of physical and psychological pain.
Domestic violence, moral harassment,
neglect of household duties, expenditures...
We have all the premises
for pursuing a divorce.
Ichikawa-san, you truly
are in pain, correct?
Yes.
In that case,
it is only proper that
we demand compensation.
Divorce Chaser
~Let's Turn Your Tears into Money~
Divorce Chaser Episode 4
The Horror of the Monster Wife!!
Compensation...
If you are ready to demand compensation,
then I will give you my full support.
Hey, what the...
Please help me.
He accepted the client...
I'm done here!
Now that we've agreed,
let's take action.
What would you want to tell
your wife the most right now?
Close your eyes and
imagine your wife's face.
I'm cutting 5,000 yen from
your allowance starting this month.
The dishes are piled up.
Now,
what do you want to say to her?
You're useless!
Don't be ridiculous!
I'm doing the best I can!
That's it!
Let's go with that!
Go and let your wife take those words.
I can't!
This is what you're missing.
Freelance Investigator:
Umemoto Kurumi
"Iron Spy Woman Marilyn"
season 4, episode 11.
It depicts how Marilyn came
to possess a heart of iron.
I'm not running anymore.
I won't run away ever again.
Sensei.
What did you mean when you told him
to let his wife take those words?
It will help him prepare
to fight his wife.
And...
And?
You'll find out shortly.
I'm not running anymore.
I won't run away ever again.
Don't be ridiculous...
I'm...
You're what?
Say it.
I'm... I'm... doing the best I can!
It was amazing how attractive
she must have been...
That's amazing!
Ichikawa-san?
I told her off.
What an incredible monster.
Beautiful.
This is beautiful, Ichikawa-san.
Congratulations.
Diagnosis Report
This, and this.
You knew this would happen, didn't you?
Anyway, now we have proof
of domestic violence.
You've cleared the first hurdle.
Congratulations!
You did it.
Let's move on to the second stage.
What?
There's more?
When you battle a monster,
you must attack its vital points.
Vital points...
You must thoroughly uncover
the facts of your wife's expenditures.
Gather as much evidence as you can.
Purchased items, receipts,
credit card statements...
And savings account ledger
would be helpful, as well.
What are you doing?
I knocked it over by accident
so I'm cleaning it up.
What is important here
is establishing the ratio of your wife's
expenditures to your income.
These things will be evidence
for the expenditures.
Now to find the savings ledger...
620,000 yen?
That's all?
At most, we had about
six million in there.
Six million...
So, she spent it all on this stuff?
Look at all that stuff she bought.
I had no idea we were so depleted.
Could your wife have
another savings account?
I don't think so.
We've closed out our
certificates of deposit, too.
What are you going to do, Sensei?
You can't get any
compensation with this.
That's why I warned you.
If it's not possible, I can
forgo the compensation.
I knew you were acting sneaky lately...
and look what I've found...
You got my ledger and are
talking to a lawyer?
You trying to separate from me?
A woman.
You have a new woman, don't you?
I'm right, aren't I?
This is ridiculous.
Who is the woman?
Help me!
Say it! Confess!
I am not cheating!
I can't breathe!
Sensei.
I know I might be
crossing a line, but...
Your husband isn't cheating on you!
You're the lawyer?
Oh. The bread's ready.
Have some if you'd like.
I won't agree to a separation.
But, if you insist we separate...
I want ten million yen
in compensation.
What a monster.
What is the premise
for the compensation?
Has your husband done something?
Of course. Our marriage is sexless.
None whatsoever, from a long time ago.
This man is useless.
Sensei. I have reason
for divorce, don't I?
Yes. In the case a man is impotent...
I'm not impotent!
I can get it up for anyone but you.
So, you are cheating on me.
Confess! Right now!
Madam, please calm down.
Say it. Get it out. Say it!
Please eat this and calm down.
Disgusting.
What the hell is this?
Anyway, I'll never agree to a divorce.
You, hold on a second!
Shut up!
She said my bagel is disgusting...
Unforgivable.
Ichikawa-san. I will
assuredly get you a divorce,
and compensation, too!
Looks like she pressed the right button.
He's just bitter.
What the hell just came
dashing out of here?
That's the monster.
It finally reared its ugly head.
Is it possible that I'd get billed
for compensation instead?
You weren't cheating on her, were you?
I wouldn't do such a thing,
I'm telling you.
Sensei.
Getting compensation might be
impossible this time around.
That's right. There have no savings.
No.
There is a way.
Huh?
She might have no savings,
but she can't escape the
obligation to make compensation.
What does this mean?
If she has no money,
how would she pay?
Upon the divorce agreement, she simply must
acknowledge the obligation for compensation.
She has ten years to make
the full compensation.
In other words, even if she can't
pay now, after the divorce,
we can demand any income
she earns after the divorce.
Even after ten years,
there can be another hearing,
Compensation Timetable
Normally three years, but can be extended to 10 years
at the time of divorce agreement. (If there is another trial,
it can be prolonged another 10 more years)
at which time, she would be
given another ten years to
make the full compensation.
I see.
Ten years.
What an exhausting thought.
Let that monster suffer for
ten years, for twenty years!
But, this time around,
we're taking a faster route.
How is that?
Ichikawa-san, are you familiar
with property distribution?
No...
Halving of assets on occasion of divorce
is standard practice of property distribution,
regardless of who initiates the divorce.
Half.
Therefore, we deduct the
compensation from this half.
How does that work?
The assets are close
to zero to begin with.
The term "assets" does not
only refer to savings.
Huh?
The biggest asset between you two
is your condominium, correct?
Ah.
So she has an asset!
When the condominium gets sold,
even after the remaining loan is paid off,
there should be some left over.
Half of it is supposed
to go to your wife.
In that case, we take our
compensation from here.
I see.
Compensation can be taken out of the property distribution.  It is essential to elucidate the details carefully in the divorce agreement.
When the other party is a housewife
That might work.
Good job, Sensei!
Well, Ichikawa-san, let's
move on to the next stage.
We have to draft a divorce agreement.
Kanae-san, will you please
help with the drafting?
I will.
Ichikawa-san. We're finally
about to reach the climax.
Yes.
I will leave it in your capable hands.
Oh, yes, there's one more thing.
We need to make a first move.
Kurumi-san.
We need to teach that
selfish monster a lesson.
Make my day, monster.
Thank you. You're all so good.
What do you mean?
You're good, too, Ichikawa-san.
Really.
I know, and I'm even
taking karaoke lessons.
I wonder if I should take classes, too.
But I have tea ceremony and koto lessons...
I'm so busy every day.
I know, right?
Um...
Ichikawa-san, you haven't
touched your drink at all.
That's right. Come on. Let's drink up.
Ichikawa-san, what are
you singing next?
Oh... then, Beyonce.
Beyonce?
I love Beyonce.
I can't wait.
I'm paying for today.
Are you sure, Ichikawa-san?
Thanks. I'll pay the tab next time.
Thanks, bye.
Here's my card.
Thank you very much.
Miss, I'm very sorry.
It appears your card has been declined.
What? That's impossible.
Would you like to pay with cash?
Yes.
Don't worry about it.
I'll pick up the tab today.
Here's my card.
Thank you very much.
Don't worry about it.
Why aren't you answering?
Are you okay?
Thank you. I'm fine.
So, let's keep a log of anything else
that could lead to further disputes.
Yes.
I know how frustrated you must feel.
I was like you, too.
Huh?
I got divorced just recently.
Hakamada-sensei really helped me out.
And now I can look forward to future.
It's all thanks to him.
I see.
He's a strange man, isn't he?
I have an appraisal of
Ichikawa-san's condominium.
In total, it comes out to
35 million yen.
Deducting the loan payback from that,
it comes out to 14 million yen.
Seven million will be paid to your
wife in the property distribution.
That's quite a lot of money.
We will bill her for the entire amount,
for compensation.
Seven million... the entire amount?
You could say she's getting off cheap.
You earned that money with your
blood, sweat, and tears...
but your wife spent
it all for herself.
This amount represents not only that,
but also the great suffering
that you have endured.
So, let's get compensated.
Misaki
Ichikawa-san.
Now, it's time to clearly express
your intent to divorce to your wife.
Yes.
Are you scared?
Well, yes... to be honest.
Your fear will become money.
My fear... will become money...
So, let's announce your intent
to divorce with a smile.
Hakamada
Law Office
I wonder if Ichikawa-san is okay.
Wouldn't it be better for him
to quietly divorce her,
instead of trying to get compensation?
People subjected to domestic violence
and moral harassment for long periods
often come to believe that
they are weak people.
And they have a tendency
to rely on the perpetrators.
I can relate, a little.
What's essential for
Ichikawa-san right now...
is for him to reclaim his former self.
To do that, he must also
demand compensation.
Is all this that so-called
Hakamada's idea?
You put a stop on my card, didn't you?
Do you have any idea
how humiliated I was?
We need to talk.
About what?
So, let's announce your intent
to divorce with a smile.
Please divorce me.
Please.
I would...
like to separate.
Ichikawa-san.
As you said, Sensei,
I told her with a smile.
She said she'll keep me
as her pet until I die.
I see.
But, I feel like I was finally
able to look her in the eyes.
That's the first I've seen you smile.
That's what matters.
Because all I can do is help
you with the legal aspects.
It is you who must fight.
Yes.
We have come here today
to ask your consent in divorcing your
husband, Ichikawa Tomohiro-san.
You guys just don't let up, do you?
Kanae-san.
Misaki-san,
over the past five years,
you have spent five million yen
of your husband's hard-earned money
on expensive brand-name items, beauty treatments,
and extravagant dinners
with your high-society friends.
Not to mention domestic violence...
Diagnosis Report
Verbal abuse...
I'm...
You're what?
Say it.
I'm... I'm doing the best I can!
Who do you think you're
talking to, you piece of trash?
Please, forgive me!
Have you forgotten how to apologize?
Get on your knees and beg.
Demanding that someone get on their knees
against their will can be considered illegal.
If you still insist you're
not the perpetrator
with sufficient reason for divorce,
then we will have to
take matters to court.
Even in court, I assure you, they
will decide in favor of the divorce.
In that case,
you will be billed to compensate your husband's
psychological and physical anguish,
as well as repayment for your personal expenditures.
The total will be seven million yen.
Seven million?
That's impossible!
You saw my bank ledger, didn't you?
Please don't worry.
Here is the appraisal
of this condominium.
Condominium Appraisal Report
Out of the sum you will receive
from the sale of the condominium,
by property distribution,
one half will become yours.
In other words, you are
entitled to one half
of 14 million yen after the divorce,
and paying back the loan.
Therefore, you will be paying
zero out of pocket.
Misaki-san, how lucky for you,
that you won't have to dig
into your own savings.
So, do you agree?
I'll say it again,
I said I won't agree to a divorce!
Stamp and sign this.
Please!
Please set me free!
Absolutely not!
If you will not agree,
then we have no choice
but to take it to court.
However, if it comes down to that,
there will be court fees, attorney fees,
in which case, in all eventuality, your
settlement will be next to nothing.
Are you all right with that?
Do what you want.
Why do you not want to divorce?
You wanted your husband's
attention, didn't you?
We have done some investigating.
Thank you very much.
Um... thank you.
Don't worry. We have to
have each other's backs.
But, it's not easy to associate
with people like that...
All the money in the
world won't be enough.
I know.
Misaki-san, you were lonely.
Since you've moved into
this condominium,
you've had no friends.
On top of that, your husband has
been working overtime until late.
And it was in this situation that
you met the local high-society wives.
It's beautiful.
This? It's from Paris.
From Paris?
Did you go to Paris?
You dropped this.
Oh, thank you!
This is my favorite handkerchief.
Thank you so much.
I'm so glad.
Bye, now.
Wait a moment...
That started the deepening of your
relationship with those women...
However, the money it took to
associate with them was exorbitant.
But you didn't want to leave
your new friends behind...
and you continued seeing them,
though you didn't have the means.
The expenditures became
a matter of course,
but you couldn't stop yourself.
You wanted to confide
in your husband, didn't you?
But instead, your attitude toward
him became increasingly cold...
and kept escalating.
Misaki...
Is that true? Because if it is...
Of course not!
Are you stupid?
What do you know about me, anyway?
Do you think you're some TV detective?
I worked hard...
I...
I wanted you to have a good life.
I said, you're wrong!
Why...
Why didn't you tell me?!
If you were lonely,
why didn't you just say so?!
If keeping up appearances was difficult,
why didn't you speak up?!
Why didn't you tell me?!
I did.
I told you over and over!
Honey, you know...
I don't know if I like
this condominium...
This subject again?
This is an important time for me.
I might get promoted.
I don't have time to move elsewhere.
But, Tomohiro, you see...
Sorry, but let's talk
about it some other time.
Nonetheless, you have vexed your
husband for many long years,
and for that, you will have to pay.
Your guilt is not expunged.
That's enough.
I've had enough of this drama.
If you want a divorce
that badly, it's yours.
Wait.
Honey...
If only I had been more
attentive to you...
Misaki. Let's start over.
I now know, that I'm the one
that turned you into a monster...
...because I kept running away.
Let's start all over again.
I am sorry...
Sensei.
Um... Sensei.
What is it?
You knew this was going
to happen, didn't you?
I think you knew how it
was all going to unfold.
All I did was clean
up the contradictions.
She said she wouldn't divorce,
while saying their marriage was sexless.
She never took off her wedding ring.
Misaki-san was full of contradictions.
Let's go back.
I would've never guessed
you could do that...
there are ways to get compensation
from housewives without income.
I was surprised, too.
Monster wives really
do exist, don't they?
Five years from now,
you will become one.
What? Me?
I feel it.
How rude.
Why would you say that?
Because I can see it.
Huh?
Ouch.
You should be careful.
Well...
Are you saying Hakamada-sensei didn't
get compensation fees this time?
Huh?
Sensei, we're in trouble!
Next episode
There's a line of people out there.
The Hakamada Law Office in great peril?!
My husband is cheating on me.
A controlling wife, traditional man, wrestler woman:
We can't get compensation
for such a minor thing...
Hakamada in a big crisis!!
I will never fail to get compensated!
This drama is a work of fiction
What's going on here?