So, let's move on to today's last request.
Yes! This request comes from the 23 y/o Atachi Ryouhei, a university student living in Osaka.
"Day after day, it continues to be cold outside."
"For this reason, I always keep a pack of instant ramen at hand, and have a special way of eating them when it gets cold."
"I take the freshly made ramen along with the saucepan, and eat it inside a bath tub ..."
"... because by warming my body from both the in- and outside, it truly warms me from within the soul."
"But in doing so, I've come across a strange phenomenon."
"If I eat the ramen while the bottom of the saucepan is submerged in the bath water, the taste becomes sour to the point where I feel a tingling in my mouth."
"As long as the saucepan isn't submerged, the taste remains the same, but it changes once it's in the water."
"Is my tongue playing tricks on me? Detectives, could you try this experience along with me?"
"By the way, it only works with Sapporo Ichiban Shio Ramen!"
Have you had this experience?
Not at all.
When you make ramen ... instant ramen ... you hold the saucepan by the handle.
And you carry it like this.
Now, when you submerge it into hot water and eat from it, you'll experience a tingling sensation.
And when you lift it up again, you'll have the normal Sapporo flavor again. That's what he's saying.
So what is it really like? Take a look.
So I heard that the client's house is a 4-story building.
This is probably it.
Even though it says it's a church.
I'm Detective Maeda with Tantei Knight Scoop.
Please let me in.
So this house is a church?
Ah this is it, right? What a gorgeous church.
Residence on the 4th floor
They really have an actual place of worship in here.
Hard to imagine that a client would live here.
We've made it to the 4th floor ...
Hello! Are you Ryouhei? - Yes!
So you live in a church? - The building is a church, yes.
Was it opened by your parents? - Yes, my dad is a pastor.
Ah, is that so?
We're part of the Protestant Christian Church. - You're ProtestanD?
So how is ... - It's "-tanT"
But I said Protestant? - You said "-tanD" - That's just my voice.
It's "ProtestanT".
ProtestanD? No?
It ends with a "T". Not a soft consonant. - ProtestanD?
It's "ProtestanT". - I said the same thing. - It ends with a "T".
A "T". It's "ProtestanT". - Yes, I get that.
ProtestanD. - No, "ProtestanT". - That's what I'm saying!
Now the real issue
When I eat the ramen, I get a tingling sensation. - From the ramen flavor?
It becomes sour. - Sour? - Yes, that's where the tingling comes from.
So when you hold the saucepan and lift it up ... - Then it's safe.
Just the regular flavor.
And when you put it back in ... - It tingles.
It's like there's an electrical discharge.
Like with the Super Nintendo ... when you would plug it out as a child and lick the power adaptor. - I didn't do anything like that!
When you plug it out ... - Ah, I get it! - It's that kind of flavor!
Ah I get it! So that's how it is? - Just like that!
When I was a student ...
There was this guy called Oshiro, who didn't have a Super Nintendo. He would come over just to do that.
My mom would go: "This is bad, but you can't say anything about it at Oshiro's place."
He would just do it over and over again ...
Yes, just like Oshiro!
We're going to spare you Oshiro's story
You can eat it regularly, but you can also dip it into the bath water and get the tingling sensation. It's a good deal, money-for-value-wise. - Money-for-value?
Two flavors in one!
To be honest, I didn't really want to tell you that. - No matter how much of a good deal it really is.
Ah, there it is! - Here you go.
How nice to be served straight away - aah, I like this style!
Eating the Sapporo Ichiban Shio Ramen normally
Ah you even put some sesame on it!
It's really tasty.
But still ...
... I wasn't feeling cold to begin with.
I see. It's not enough. - It just isn't.
The should eat it once they feel cold ...
So everyone at home will understand it, too. - You're right.
Ah, hello! You're his dad? - Good evening.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you, I'm Atachi.
Hello! - This is a surprise.
This is our current problem. - The thing about eating it in the bath tub?
It's nice that even in your family home, you would allow him ... - I didn't, not even once!
I told him, "Don't eat in the bath!". When I entered the bath after him, there were noodles floating around.
You can't leave noodles floating around! - That was my mistake.
Dad, what do you think? Will the flavor change?
Will it change ... ? I don't think it's possible, even if he says so.
No choice but to test it! - Go ahead.
But dad, you see ... for this experiment ... in fact for any experiment ...
... the accuracy increases the more test persons you have.
That's right. - Right? So this time, to see whether the ramen flavor changes ...
Raise the accuracy of the experiment
No way!
It's so cold!! - No way!
So now ... aaaaah ... there's a strong wind!
The wind is freezing! - Yes, it's really cold!
You can really feel the cold out here.
The three of us ... really, all three of us ...
Cooling down their bodies
... when it becomes really, really bad, we'll head back inside.
All three of us ... ooooooh!
3 minutes pass
Can you still go?
Is this necessary?
Is this necessary just to eat ramen?
5 minutes pass
It's so cold!!!
At this rate we'll get hypothermia.
7 minutes pass
Dad, how are you doing? The wind is too much!
At the next gust of wind! We'll go at the next gust!
It's locked!
Please come in!
Mom opens the door
Get the ramen!
There are only 2 cooking stoves!
Please hold this and wait for now.
It won't open!
Cold, cold, cold, ...
Ah it's warm, it's warm ....
Dad, I'm sorry, there's only enough space for one person! I'm sorry, there's only enough space for one person!
Why can't I fit in there?!
Why can't there be all three of ... - That's all part of the hypothesis we're testing!
That's not what we're testing for!
You can already eat that! Change places with me! Come on, come on, come on!
We need to stir in the flavor ... - Can't you switch places with me already?!
What's with this house?!
It's hot!!
It's so hot!
Man, it's hot.
Hoooot!
How can it be so hot!!
My request didn't include this!!
Let's eat it normally first. What does it taste like?
I ... I can't even tell ...
It's good! - It's good, isn't it?
Now let's put it in the water! Slowly, see what happens!
It's sour! - No way, you gotta be lying!
The taste is really sour! - Are you serious? Really?!
It's sour! - I'll do it, too.
You're not kidding? It's actually sour? - Yes, absolutely!
FOR REAL!!?!
Right? It's really sour, isn't it?!
The taste is actually ... !
All of a sudden, it was so frikkin' sour! - Sour, right?
Are you kidding me?
Switch places with me!
Hot, hot, hot!
At first, normally
The same as always, right? - Now put it in!
My body is really warmed up now!
The same as always.
It's in the sauce pan! - It's different! You're using an enamelled pot!
Try it with this.
How is it?
Kind of sour, isn't it?
Right?! - It's actually kind of sour.
Like electricity? - I'm not sure about that, but definitely sour!
But it's really tasty in here.