Tonight's show is a compilation of clips falling under the theme "Knight Scoop reminds me of ...", and we can't possibly leave out this last category.
"Knight Scoop reminds me of 'Shock Footage'!"
The following 'Shock Footage' would be unthinkable on any show other than Knight Scoop, please take a look.
" ... comes from the 34 y/o Kitamura Takashi, a company employee living in Osaka."
"I haven't had a girlfriend in 34 years."
"I'm not very good-looking, so I was never popular and never had a girl confess her love to me."
"I've already given up on ever getting married."
"I've decided on spending my life alone."
"I have accepted my fate and come to terms with the truth that I will never have a girlfriend."
"But, I'd like to go on a date, even if it was just for one day. The gender doesn't matter."
"Detectives, won't you please go on a date with me?"
It seems he's already waiting over there.
Meeting the client
Kitamura? - Yes!
I'm Takeyama. - I'm Kitamura.
Good to see you.
We're with Tantei Knight Scoop.
Nice to meet you.
So you'd like to go on a date? - Yes!
And whether it's with a man or a woman, ... - It doesn't matter, that's right.
And I am ... - The girlfriend, yes.
Ah, I'm the girlfriend?
How come, in the hopes of getting a date, did you consult the Detectives instead of going marriage hunting?
Ah, I've tried that! It was no use!
I've always wanted to marry, but it's just not possible for me.
Ah, so you've come to think it's not possible? - Yes, so even if it's just one time, a single time, I want to go on a date.
So for this date, the gender doesn't matter to you ... - Not at all!
Not at all! - Not at all?
So even with me ... - Is completely fine!
I'll say it clearly, Takeyama, please, I want to go on a date with you!
You want to go on a date with me? I see.
What should we call each other? - Call me Ta-kun.
Heh? - Call me Ta-kun.
Then I'll be Take-chan? - Yes, Take-chan.
Then, shall we go on a date, Ta-kun? - Yes!
I'm looking forward to it, Take-chan! - So do I. What are we going to do?
Should we climb up there? - Yes, I'd like to go up and see the view.
Hanging gardens
I'm getting nervous. - Ah, when it goes up like that. - You too?
I'm not so good with heights.
More than friends,
Setting
but less than lovers.
Ah is that so? - That's why I'm a bit nervous.
Are you ok?
Yes, I'm ok.
Now that we've come up here, is there something you want to talk about?
Something like how our lives will progress from here on out.
While looking at this view?
Ta-kun, how would you like to live your life?
How I would like to live my life ... ? - What you're thinking of right now.
I do want to get married ...
Why did you say you couldn't do it?
My appearance ...
So your complex about your appearance is the main factor? - Yes.
My head, mostly ... - Your head?
Your hair? - Yes.
But there are plenty of people who are popular, even after becoming bald.
And your head has come a long way, at 34 years old.
Is there somewhere you want to go next?
Not really for me, but you asked for the date, so if there's somewhere you want to go?
Something I ... a photo booth to take pictures!
After you.
Which one should we take?
Ta-kun, you pick!
Here! - It'll take 4?
H-how?
Won't we hold hands?
Won't we?
It's fine, how would you like it?
It's best if you don't go straight for it, but gradually work your way up. - Like this.
Like this ... or more like this ... ? - Nah, well, this won't do.
But if I just held onto here and walked behind ... - No no no no!
But if I ... - NO!
That was scary! You're scaring me if you say it like that!
All of a sudden you became really scary.
I'm getting hungry.
How about Yakiniku? Even if it's still early. - That's fine.
One serving of sirloin ... and one serving of pork rib ...
Can you feed me?
What was it like, being fed for the first time?
It felt good. - It did?
Can I ask you something? - Yes.
You don't have any experiences like that with women?
No I don't.
I mean, I have kissed before.
Where was that?
Like, in Gunma.
In Gunma?
At a hostess club. - A hostess club?
So that was your first kiss then? - I didn't feel anything.
I didn't feel anything.
Because it wasn't with someone I loved.
It felt cold.
I'd like to actually go on a date with a woman.
So even if this was the date now ...
... I'm happy.
You're happy because you've been on a date with me today?
What should we do after our meal?
I'd like to spend a little more time together.
I'd like to have a kiss.
We haven't kissed today.
Me? - It doesn't matter!
Doesn't that matter the most? - It doesn't! It's just about going on a date with me, kissing me, ...
I'm sorry.
But if you do it with me it won't be sincere, and isn't that like your last time?
Also, people will recognize me. "Ah, it's that guy, Takeyama, he went overboard today!"
What about when we held hands?
When we held hands, you thought of it that way? - Of course.
You're being too fast!
Please.
It's ok if it's with you. - It's not!
It's not ok, anyway you look at it.
And we've already done a lot, it'll only cause trouble for this shop.
But at night, this would be a good place!
And don't just decide by yourself "We'll do it"! You're being presumptuous.
Let's do it! - No, not "let's do it"!
Hey!
That was too long!
Thank you. Thank you!
Is the date complete with this?
Yes.
What's become clear to me in that position, is that you've given up too soon!
You hardly have any confidence in yourself!
You've gotten way too worked up about yourself!
You have a good personalty and a nice face, you can definitely find love!
Take care!
Honestly, take care!
Go home! Honestly, go home, this shoot is over!