Subbed by: Otviss
Alright, we're here!
So this next one has
been a very popular attraction since we opened.
The jurassic park ride!
Wow it's coming. Look at this you guys!
Ugh this is one of these
Aaaand it lands!
Wow!
Everyone's laughing
Everyone's smiling aren't they?
We're in it now...
If we go on it will we be smiling like them?
You bet!
Uh so who's going?
Well, all of us and
It's about the talent power isn't it?
You're right.
If you do decide to ride with us today,
There's actually a spot that takes photos
and it'll take one of these of you while riding
Nope. No way.
What do you mean?
Well I mean...
And everyone with a smile on their face
I just thought it would be fun if we were to take a photo like this
Just a little fuuun
We don't know when we'll be photographed though
You can see it coming right?
Yes, you're correct!
Just as you're falling
So even as it's falling it'll turn out well right?
That's right
I'm not really convinced...
Why? You can demonstrate your talent power
You will be fine
Uhm...
I actually thought we were gonna go on the flying dinosaur
So if you compare this to that...
Your feelings must be flying then
No one's gonna laugh at shit like that
Are we doing this?
We'll be done in an instant!
Guess it can't be helped then
Yup let's go!
Let's use our TALENT POWER and take a fun photo!!
I'm not really on board with that though
I'll guide you to the spot
Let's go!
Come on now. Come on!
Nakamura-san! Call on him!
It's scary right??
OH MY GOD MATSUMOTO-SAN!!! ♥
It's not scary, it's not scary
Haha you'll be fine
It's not scary
Since you all came as a family
you will be able to have this great memory in the end
No... Why?
As you could see,
You do get a little wet...
How about some ponchos?
Don't need any!
Okay understood
The hell are you deciding for?
Ugh I can't do this...
It'll be over in an instant
No but,
I'm still reluctant you guys
So I'm thinking the flying dinosaur would be better
Alright, let's go!
No way!
Huh what's wrong?
It was a joke!
A freaking a joke huh?
Charming!
Faces
Talent Power
Ok ok ok! Let's go now!
I'm pumped up!
In the middle?
Ok!
Wow it's all wet!
Yeah it's pretty wet
This is like Villa Villa
Oh it's wet here too
Look here too.
Unavoidable though isn't it
Woah wait, this is all we get?
Oh no this is...
Alright everyone! We're departing!
Look out for dinosaurs and have a great journey!
We're off!
Haha, that was the "Great Journey Boy" right there
Damn this is straight in the middle
Right in the middle!
Yay!
No..
Let's go!
No, this is already bad
Look look! That dinosaur thing is much worse
Nah, The dinosaur is way more...
Woaahh!
That was low
The dinosaur seems better...
Yeah we should've just done the dinosaur
Won't it get better than this?
Knock it off!
We could've gone twice on the dinosaur now
That's impossible you guys
Two times.
Oh shit!
It started talking suddenly...
Keep your face together now
I don't know what you're talking about
Talent power for the photo
We don't know when it's taken though
You know roughly right?
Yeah when it's falling we'll make the faces
Yahoo!
Just riding with the family like this is a little unsettling...
Everyone should be on
This guy's really scared
The dinosaurs are scared too so
Oh there's a baby one too
Enough of this. I'm nervous...
Huh?
What?
We're entering a strange...
This is no good!
It's torn!
You're right! It's torn.
I'm scared...
Ugh no! There's something here
There was something
Where's the person in charge?
I don't like this anymore
WOAH!
Eugh!
What the hell was that?
Look it's here! It's here!
Fall coming up
What is?
Ok use your talent power now for a good photo!
Aahh!
Hahaha!
Woah!
It's cold!
Ouch ouch ouch...
Ouch ouch!
Ouch ouch ouch!
I got so wet!
There's something up with dad
It hurts!
Hahaha!
Wait it hurts!
Ouch!
Haha he sprained it!
He sprained it again!
It hurts!
Did you sprain your shoulder?
Wait it really hurts. What is this?
You were too scared so you stiffed up
Daddy's injured!
He injured his shoulder!
Nakamura-san. He stiffed up and sprained his shoulder.
Hahahaha! Really? Are you okay?
I'm not okay!
It's cause ya stiffed up like that!
Did it get you too nervous?
It actually felt longer than I expected
Did we catch their
talent power?
Your pictures are done
Let's take a look
Okay, here I go
Ta-da
Did we catch their
talent power?
Ta-da
Hahahaha!
Just horrible
Horrible
This is awful!
So the staff
are all looking down not to be on camera.
Just like you!
Show your face stupid!
Dad's getting it!
Yeah you're awesome!
Such a great one!
What a great reaction
I'm like "The scream"
Look at me, I'm not even scared. I'm just like woah!
Not funny in the slightest
Now mommy's just...
Yeah it's crazy. You're honestly just going "Aaah"
It's cause I didn't hear
Let's go to USJ again
Whatchu on about? We told you the photo was coming up