This is the first time
I've felt this bad for the staff
Drunken crab pursuit!
Right now, we're going to a place called "Ieshima"
We can only go by ship
Wow! There's so many people!
Wait there's so many
What the heck
What a sight!
We're currently here at Maurakou
Oh, it's here
So, the place we're headed to right now
is called  "Shimizu no Hama"
Well, you don't wanna walk right?
They have stuff like this?
Oo what's that?
That's perfect!
But the maximum weight capacity is 200kg
And we don't have the budget for 2 cars
Should we ask someone to give us a ride?
You're looking for a driver?
Of course
Won't we eventually get there if we just keep walking?
No we're going the opposite direction.
Ya idiot
O-Over there (SADAKO)
There's a car
A car is coming
Finding someone in a car...
Yeah, might be better
Yeah, let's go with that. Hello
Maybe he's working?
What are you up to?
Ah, I see.. can we fit?
Can we ride with you?
Where are you headed? (DRIVER)
Can the 4 of us go?
To Shimizu
Ah, Shimizu-san (DRIVER)
Is that okay?
Sure, that's okay (DRIVER)
You can all fit (DRIVER)
Are you serious?
Wait you would really lift us?
Yeah, sure why not (DRIVER)
Are you sure? We have 4 people
It doesn't seem like all 4 of us can go.
You think?
軽か
So we gotta split up
Shall we rent one car and have this car go with us?
Oh, that rent-a-car
So then...
Me alone... (SADAKO)
In the rented car?
Ya (SADAKO)
Well, alright
You three go ahead (SADAKO)
Let's do that. Okay, we'll go.
Sorry about that
See you later then, Sadako.
The road is so narrow
Only compacts can go through here
Just barely enough space
Wow, cars are amazing
Right?
Is Shimizu-san pretty popular?
Very popular (DRIVER)
Oh is that so?
You've never had drunken crab have you mommy?
Never had it
I thought so
Honestly, what if it was really bad?
There's no way. Man, you're SO DUMB.
SO. DUMB.
You. You...You're..
SO DUMB!
How many times are you gonna say that
Really. Wait! ...
You're SO. DUMB.
You just wanted to say that
The scenery changed a little
You can shoot a movie here...
It's a very nice atmosphere
Please, come film over here (DRIVER)
Yes, seems like a perfect place to film
Wow this is really nice. Oh, the beach is coming up.
We're almost there maybe
It's there, no?
Where where where?
No, this right-hand side
See, right here
Ahh we're here
We're here?
It's this
This this this
Shimizu-san～
We've arrived
Let's go in here. Is that okay?
This helped us tremendously
We're thankful
We're so thankful
Seriously, sir
Thank you so much
Thank you very much
Sorry to trouble you (DRIVER)
Please, enjoy your time! (DRIVER)
Thank you, good bye!
Mannn
We were saved thanks to him
I wonder if Sadako is here yet
Seems pretty nice
Right? It's very nice
Wahh, I like it
What is this place?! It's SO nice
Hello!
Mama saw this place
We're finally here~
and she truly wanted to try
I saw it on TV and
I thought "I must have this"
Thank you very much (OWNER)
Dreams really do come true
I'm very glad (OWNER)
Very nice
Sadako hasn't arrived yet...
That's fine
That's totally fine
That's ok right?
Master, go ahead and just lock the entrance
Shall we start?
Let's
I feel like having some drinks
Actually,
here at Shimizu-san,
they are very passionate about their sake
They've got 50 varieties!
Sparkling sake piques my interest
Bucu?
Bucu's rosé (OWNER)
Yeah, this one caught my attention
It's sake, but rosé
I've never had anything like that
Let's do it!
Let's drink
Let's
We'll do it
Certainly (OWNER)
Yeah the money...
Plenty!
We have a butt-ton
We're completely covered
So we'll have that, please
I'm SO excited
He seems very passionate
Ugh my fingers smell like octopus!
You were like clenching onto it
What was that all about?
Why all of a sudden...
After you guys left
The person at the shop- ...
Now now.. (OWNER)
Almost like the drunken crab...
This is just a little complimentary dish (OWNER)
What is it?
Oyster marinated in olive oil (OWNER)
Olive oil marinade?
This is beyond freebie level
And then this would be... (OWNER)
It almost makes you want to close one eye. B U C U Bu- (OWNER)
Um, please serve it up immediately
As you wish! Here we go (OWNER)
Nice color! (ONSCREEN)
Rosé. It's really pink
Whaaat is this?
Milky white...
Women would love this kind of color
Ahh it's so good
So good.... wut
First time tasting this flavor
I've never tasted anything like this... wut
Kind of like a cocktail?
I wonder? It's very light
Little bit (thick, viscous, gooey, syrupy.. it's hard to come up with English words describing food without sounding gross)
It's very strange. SO good!
HUUH!?
We're drinking something very special
This would be so popular with the ladies
Thisthisthisthis!
SO DELICIOUS!
For this, I sautéed garlic and chili flakes (OWNER)
Ajillo style. Then after that, I steamed it with some white wine.
Then I marinated that in olive oil and let that sit for about 2 weeks. (OWNER)
There's no bad in any of this
I'M HERE (sadako) ON SCREEN
Right, I am. (OWNER)
You're an otaku, huh?
That's how it is (OWNER)
I just heard something...
What?
Like "nyahsnyaaaaaahnh"
No one...
He's here he's here
He's here! haha
He's already there. Look at him!
It took him SO long
The hell is he doing?
Those kids-
Since they can't shake hands with Matsumoto-san they're settling with Sadako
Master, this sake was so delicious
Thank you very much (OWNER)
I was taken aback
It was heavenly
The prefecture here has a lot of good sake (OWNER)
The sake is amazing too but...
Master, this would be really
good for pasta, no?
Yes, very good with pasta. (OWNER)
Just mixing it in would be good (OWNER)
Just perfect
So start with sake and for the full-course, what would be up first?
Today I would really love for you to have fish (Owner)
So first I think I would like to start with sashimi. (OWNER)
Please, thank you very much
Well we have a stupid amount of money
Seriously, I really don't want him to die...
Just for right now
Just right now
Ahh I'm starving (SADAKO)
Your entrance is like a comedy theater
You come in out of no where "Ahh I'm starviinng!"
You're super late!
No you see, I rented the car right? (SADAKO)
And I rushed over here by myself right? (SADAKO)
Let's cheers first (SADAKO)
We already freaking did it, it's fine
We finished already
Aw man (SADAKO)
We're waiting for the master's next item
Ah. Itadakimasu (SADAKO)
Oh so-rry to keep you waaaaaiting～　(OWNER)
Okay to put it in the front? (OWNER)
Front is good
Please excuse me! (OWNER)
Wwwooww
Master, this is fish from Ieshima?
100% Ieshima local (OWNER)
Wow it's mantis shrimp!!
I've never seen raw mantis shrimp before
Super first experience
Have you had raw mantis shrimp before?
First time. Never had it
First time seeing it with the head (SADAKO)
Ahh, it's completely different from shrimp! Like in-between shrimp and crab.
Like shrimpcrab right?
Yes, absolutely (OWNER)
Shrimpcrab
When there's a good amount, this'll be delicious to do shabu shabu with. (OWNER)
It's super rare
Yes, exactly (OWNER)
This is so good. I've never had something like this.
Yeah what in the world?
What the heck are you thinking about normally?
Just imagining things all day (OWNER)
Imagination
Be careful
The sauce is so good too
I'm still super mesmerized
Yeah I'm still wowed
We haven't even had the main dish yet
Well then, I'll get the next dish ready! (OWNER)
Please, take your time. Excuse me! (Owner)
That blew me away
Didn't think I'd enjoy it this much before getting to the main event.
Right?
Let's play the crab game before the crab comes (SADAKO)
What's the crab game?
You know, (SADAKO)
Toré toré, pichi pichi, kani ryori～ (SADAKO)
the song right? So you take the "ka-ni" part (SADAKO)
and get another 2-letter food item and fill it in. (SADAKO)
Isn't that too easy?
It has to be 2 letters?
2 letter food item (SADAKO)
Then "cuisine~" (SADAKO)
So I'll start first (SADAKO)
We'll go in this order here. 3 2 1! (Sadako)
♬ toré toré, pichi pichi, mame (beans) cuisine~ (SADAKO)
♬ toré toré, pichi pichi, nasu (eggplant) cuisine~
♬ toré toré, pichi pichi, negi (green onion) cuisine~
♬ toré toré, pichi pichi, momo (peach) cuisine~
♬ toré toré, pichi pichi, uma (horse) cuisine~ (Sadako)
♬ toré toré, pichi pichi, ushi (beef) cuisine~
♬ toré toré, pichi pichi, buta (pork) cuisine~
♬ toré toré, pichi pichi, tori (chicken) cuisine~
♬ toré toré, pichi pichi, kaki (oyster) cuisine~ (SADAKO)
WHAT THE FUCK IS SO FUN ABOUT THIS!?
What's so fun!?
But.. Daddy's verse about peach cuisine was so wrong (SADAKO)
What the heck is peach cuisine? (sadako)
Well what's wrong with that
True, peach cuisine is... questionable
Yeah that...
caught me off guard too but, it fits so it'll go on.
What even was that?
♬toré toré, pichi pichi, henna (weird) cuisine~
That's not even 2 letters (it's 3)
Oops, sorry (SADAKO)
Here's the weird food (OWNER)
This is really just a filler between the main dish (OWNER)
Hahahaha!
I really gotta learn more from you
Very strong heart
That's amazing
Your mentality is insane
Oh, what's this?
Sea cucumber?
Please have this with the shredded daikon dish
And please stretch the time with this until the crab is ready (OWNER)
Do ya put it on?
Put it together like this right?
Yeah you can do that, too
Then dip it together and...
He has some funny things to say
SO good!
Very good! Mmm～
What is this?
What could this be
It has a Western taste but, it feels traditionally Japanese as well
Everything here is something I've never tasted before
He's amazing
He's got Impressive culinary skills
If he'd act a little more normal this place would be so popular
Oh! It's here!
It's here!
The drunken crab is here!
Here you go, thank you for waiting (OWNER)
It's huge!
This is what mommy....
Drunken crab
Grill time is 3 hours (OWNER)
Sake marination is 2 hours, with a total of 5 hours (OWNER)
Takes 5 hours to prepare
I can already smell it
It's like steam-grilled
The juices haven't escaped at all (OWNER)
So for this, I'll have them bring out some white rice (OWNER)
Then you get these eggs and put it on top of the rice (OWNER)
it'll change your world (OWNER)
Normally this juice isn't there!
You're going to town on that
It's cause I'm a bad man (OWNER)
Hahaha!
To the crab yeah
A bunch came out! (SADAKO)
Please, feel free to dig in. No need to eat elegantly. (OWNER)
Let's go
IT'S SO GOOD
It's completely different from something like Gejang
It's not so raw like gejang
Wait what, it's so delicious. There's a flavor explosion in my mouth.
Wow it's so good!
No really, what were you thinking?!
100% delicious
It's amazing. This is like shocking
This is the first time I've had blue crab this delicious
The crab juice is completely trapped in (OWNER - screen)
Yeah, that's what it is huh
Then, in this cute lil' rice...
The eggs, yes (OWNER)
This right?
Then pour the juice on top of it (OWNER)
Just drench it directly from above, it's ok (OWNER)
It's egg over rice
And then over here, there's more eggs on the side here
Ooh, you're right. I'll have that in a bit
I'm gonna go jump off that thing
Risotto, risotto
Whaaat?! Ohh my
Delish isn't it!? (OWNER)
Master, this is crazy
I've never had anything like this
What the heck
Your mom has tried amazing food everywhere from filming TV shows
This is the first time I've felt this bad for the staff
I'm sorry... I want to let everyone try this
I'm completely at a loss
At a loss, yeah
While you guys are enjoying the pasta is getting ready right now (OWNER)
Aaaand I'll go ahead and FINISH IT UP FOR YA! (OWNER)
Please go ahead and relax. Just make sure to take your time. (OWNER)
Understood. We know the drill by now
I still can't get into liking him
Even after all he's done for us
He's very funny
I'm super satisfied now
Then we get to have the pasta right?
I wanna come here again
Yes, one more time
Yeah, a 2nd time
Like, for TV work?
Yep
Next week
But we have to say the same exact things we said today
Like to see if we can?
If we can do the same thing?
I need to memorize everything.
Heere it issssss～　(OWNER)
This is the one!?
Are you serious?
Lastly, let me just sear it a little more. (OWNER)
for finishing touches (OWNER)
This pasta takes 2 days to make. (OWNER)
I sautéed onions and garlic for 2 hours, then made a broth with (OWNER)
dried flatfish and mantis shrimp for 5 hours. (Owner)
Because of the searing the juice and the eggs just pour out from the bottom nicely
He's really thinking about Instagram aesthetics
Amazing
You're something else, master
And the innards around this too... (OWNER)
Go for it go for it
Please, go for it
Gogogogoogo
Is that fine? It's okay? (OWNER)
Yes, go right ahead
Now now. Excuse me, there you have it (OWNER)
If you can plate it nicely for us...
It's not nice at all, but alright
Hehehe! (OWNER)
This is just great～
It's just salt and pepper really (OWNER)
Huh?
The rest is from the broth (OWNER)
And in the end I zested some yuzu and myoga
Mmm!!
I want 3 thumbs
3 thumbs?
I don't have enough
Thumbs up isn't enough
It has a sweetness, huh?
Yes, yes, sweet (OWNER)
It's absolutely delicious! Never had this before.
And it's not minced meat
So good!!
Ohhh, it's like this!
Extremely different from what I was imagining.
What was I thinking going on a diet
Delliiicciouss!
Ahh, I'm so glad (OWNER)
to hear that you enjoy it (OWNER)
Very true, isn't it
It's very empowering to see people enjoy your cooking
Yes, my number one source of happiness (OWNER)
Master, thank you so much for entering the culinary industry
I'm really just an amateur with hair (OWNER)
I'm truly thankful
That joke with the hairy crab term is confusing me
Oh no, that's no good (OWNER)
確カニ… わざとやったらすごい
So is this the finale of the full-course?
Actually, normally this would be the end (OWNER)
But I have one more dish for ya! (OWNER)
Special for us?
Just for you all (OWNER)
I don't do this anywhere else. Only today.
Please relax, and enjoy!
It's crab, right?
Crab of some sort
Crab something...
A dessert?
But what could come after this?
I'm feeling a little bashful to show you all this.
First person to discover this place is? (OWNER)
Me
Mommy
And then the one who worked hard to bring us all here? (OWNER)
Daddy
And Dad's favorite dish would be?? (OWNER)
I have a lot. Crab omelet over rice?
Correccctt! (OWNER)
Here, in front of Dad. (OWNER)
Made with blue crab: crab omelette over rice! (OWNER)
I did not think of this
It is thanks to dad after all (OWNER)
It's not really fully chinese, but (OWNER)
it's in the broth.
Go ahead, Mommy
What in the world are you doing?
You should've told usss
Like this?
and like this right?
There's no price on this. Priceless.
Do you like it? (OWNER)
Very delicious
I'm so relieved. Thank you very much (OWNER)
It's delicious you bastard!
Hihihi～ thank you very much...
This especially, I won't make it even if someone asks for it. (OWNER)
It's today's original dish (owner)
You don't make this for other TV shows either right?
No, not at all. I don't make it anywhere. (OWNER)
We'll start a killing match right now
Too good!
Just with crab and eggs...
This is way too scary
I'm scared after eating this
That was fantastic. I'm glad we came to Ieshima.
What a performance
Okay, let's go over the bill
Yes
I forgot about that
Very generous!
Wait no discount
No discount,
and it's still this affordable?
and I totally charged you
for that last one
15,000 per person
That's so..
3.....4....
Very affordable
5.. ok thank you so much
Thank you for the meal
1..2..3..4..5-
So glad we have enough
(笑い)
Was trying to figure out how I should interject
I thought I should probably
go alongfor the counting part