m -89 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 28 l 38 28 l -89 28
300M
Above ground
Steep
Cliff
「Matsumoto family's historical moment」
Most scariest
Thrill
I'm never coming back here to
Abeno
Let's go! "Edge the Harukas" Yay!
Ugh is this for real?
Woah!
Even here my heart is racing
Wow this is amazing
This sucks, It's already very bad
It's all uncovered!
We're climbing so high up..
My head is starting to get dizzy, This is so scary, I can't do this!
Oh wow I totally get it!
This is crazy!
This is amazing!
This is incredible!
Isn't this a cool experience?
Hang on a moment. I can't do this seriously!
What's wrong? What happened?
I'm gonna get sick
I'm getting sick! Oh no, the wind is...!
Alright, Let's do this. 3..2..1!
There's nothing here!
There's nothing here wow!
WOW!
Look there's nothing here, no glass!
This is bad! I CAN'T DO THIS!
I'm serious!
This is so bad, I just can't...
Come on, Open your eyes and watch this!
Yeah it feels super real!
You feel like you're the top of everything...
Wow, It's hard to understand what's happening
It feels like a model city