For more, please visit: http://tofupandas.tumblr.com/matsumotoke
Subbed by: Otviss
Day off
The Matsumoto family's
Do you know what this is?
Wow, it's an electric eel!
It's an electric eel
Woah, you're right!
It's an electric eel however, isn't it amazing?
About 90% of its body is electric
It's internal organs go like this and contract together
I've seen it on video before
Someone tried swimming past a huge electric eel
and then got electrocuted and just fell dead...
How many volts does it give off?
About 800 volts.
800 volts??
You'd die
You'd die definitely
If you happened to step on one you'd die
It's quite crude isn't it?
So we wanted to let you feel
how the very food we give it feels like
when it gets electrocuted
So we created this thing here...
Oh no this is scary... Electricity?
Huh? What is this?
I have nothing but a bad feeling about this
Experience the feeling of
being attacked by an electric eel
Huh? Is it connected to that over there?
Yes it is
It's linked together
If it's 800 volts It's gonna kill us
Well not really, It's obviously...
Lowered?
Yes, You're gonna get to feel the current together.
Why the hell?
Well, that's what it does.
Are we gonna put our hands in the water here?
Well..
Just one person?
there are two openings but
If you were to do it with 2 hands
the current would be too strong, that's why we do one hand only.
Ugh, okay this is way too scary...
This is so bad!
This is seriously bad. We have to decide this by rock-paper-scissors...
the person who loses HAS to freaking to this.
Let's do guppa first and decide from that
Right, decide the teams first? Okay.
It's always you two, haha
Of course, it's always us...
Now we choose a representitive...
I'll go then
Ok, you go
Imma lose for sure! I won't be able to do it
despite going against the boss
Don't worry you can do it
Kenji, go already
Alright, got it!
Alright we know what's gonna happen let's go
YES!!
We did it!
That was close, I was gonna throw paper...
Hang on a second head chief. Are we really okay?
Yeah you're fine!
He says fine but there's no way...
Just like an electric eel's
Mom and
Prey...
Sadako get an electric shock!
m -89 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 28 l 38 28 l -89 28
Put ONE of your hands on the plate down there please
Wow! This is scary
Put it on the plate..
Oh this is so awful...
This kind of thing is just...
THIS IS SO FREAKING SCARY!!
Let's get to it then..
Aah! This is so freaking scary! So scary!
No! no! no! I can't!
I'm not kidding, this is bad
Alright so the food is gonna come out from behind here
Okay, it's dropped
They dropped it now
Oh, it's coming out now
It's looking for it now
It hasn't found it yet
Not yet huh? Is it coming?
Alright not yet, not yet
I can't bare this... I can't bear this
I can't fucking bear this...
Oh, it's found it! It's found it!
AAHHHH!!!
Hahaha! You broke it!
You broke it!
Hahahaha you broke it!
Wow we got the full blow didn't we?
That hurt!
This is...
With this freak over here
This is amazing
This is the first time we see sada like this
It surprised me..
It really did...
I'm so happy we didn't get picked
The head chief definitely gave us a shock
m -89 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 28 l 38 28 l -89 28