"We were each other's first ever friends"
-Mom
Day off
For more, please visit: http://tofupandas.tumblr.com/matsumotoke
The Matsumoto family's
Translated by: Otviss
What do you mean?
We've arrived
Well then, Here we are in Kyobashi
Grand Chateaux from here on?
What are you on about?
Here in Kyobashi
That's right
My memories am I right?
the memories are...
Kyobashi...
Yeah that's right
So in the next place we're going to
there's a former partner of yours waiting
What?
Mom's former acquaintance
When I hear former partner
former partner?
Hamada, ya know?
I naturally think, there's no other than
Huh?
Oh really?
So there's nothing that rings a bell
from ages ago when you did Manzai?
So maybe from my student years?
former partner though
Like grade school
There were definitely some there
What kind of people did you
hang out with then?
Ito
Well, Ito
Ah ah I see, Morioka
There were three of us with a guy "Morioka"
Mom was actually in a trio in the old days
And the name was... "The Koma third branch"
Yeah so around 4th-5th grade
of grade school
Oh?
Yeah..
Mom started doing manzai in 4th grade of grade school
So from what I've heard
That would be before Hamada
Yeah that's right
I was with Ito quite a while but...
Kyobashi and him
definitely don't sound right together...
There you go!
Yes, It's actually someone from the Moriokas
Morioka?
Yes, Morioka
That Morioka though, right?
A partner before Hamada, Morioka
But he didn't speak a word
Ok so, we did have a trio together
Seriously
Then it's meaningless isn't it?
First time he ever spoke was
when he was about 7 years old...
So it was kind of like
the wolf girl?(Manga)
So he didn't speak
even though he was as old as 7?
I'm absolutely serious, go ask the real person
You serious?
It's not just a matter of a couple of years
So how many years has it been? Since you meet
30?
It must be more than 30 years now...
After a time of 30 years, A reunion
He's the eldest son of 6 siblings
You know,
6 siblings.. That's a remarkably large family
Wow
They were ridiculously poor
I mean we were fairly poor too but
that guy was completely beyond poor
Are you serious?
So that Morioka is now
working somewhere in this vicinity?
What kind of store do you think it is?
Yes,
Somehow, him doing something at a food
and drink place sounds right to me
In any case, because he was always...
Because he was ALWAYS so hungry
He could eat anytime
That's why?
So now that he's older, I feel like
he would want to continue
doing something
with food that's very laidback like that
You remember don'tcha?
Anyhow, Morioka has
for 12 years, independently been
the owner of this here
The owner boss
Wow, that Morioka huh?
Hang on a second, this is high class
Here it is, "Kamon"
Amazing
Is that Morioka?
You saw Morioka?
Ah he's laughing
Are you Morioka!?
Haha, He's laughing
We found Morioka
Well let's get going then
Hmm?
Let's go
You Morioka?
Good evening
It's freaking Morioka
Good evening, nice to meet you
Likewise
Huh? Is this your wife?
Yes
Hello there, nice to meet you!
Wow!
I'm Matsumoto
This is amazing...
We totally get Morioka
He looks so kind
So, did he tell you
Yes he did
anything about me?
He was talking crap about me right?
What did he say?
A little bit
So he said something
Yes
You're the owner of this place right?
He really is the owner though!
More or less... yeah
I mean, Morioka
being the owner here
The fact that we're having a
a normal conversation is so surprising
He seriously didn't speak a word
That's right, He still doesn't
talk to people he doesn't know
Here's a little thing we heard from before
Morioka,
Up until you were 7 years old
you didn't speak at all
Is that true?
You didn't speak at all right?
That's saying too much...
You were late with talking...
So that's how it was
The oldest of 6 siblings right?
Huh? 7 people!?
Seven actually...
7 people? You increased to 7 huh?
14 years younger..
You got one more?
That's just amazing
Wow..
Here's someone with a lot of legends
He's a remarkable person
Morioka...
Haha, it's not like that..
I'm going to enjoy listening to those
Let's do that and calm down for a moment
Let's sit down, shall we?
A talk with the legendary former partner
Funny and exciting memories
Chinese Cuisine:
Kamon
As expected, you wanted to manage a food place I see
Cause you were constantly hungry
Is that really true?
Yes it is..
In those days ya know
Tanaka Kakuei was the prime minister
Yeah yeah
Mom: Matsumoto
Morioka
And I was taking my dog for a walk in the park
And then, since Morioka
lived adjacent to that park
And from afar
And their dad was SO poor
and kind of hot headed
I seriously heard this:
So when I was walking the dog
Tanaka, you freaking idiot!
To the prime minister? The prime minister at the time?
Yeah, Morioka's dad completely shaken
let out a cry like that..
Because they were so poor?
Hahaha!
Then my dog just went "ooooh"
That was its response?
That was the reaction?
But right? It happened right?
Hiroshi Morioka.
His dad was called that.
After that, we heard "Hiroshi, you fool!"
From the two Itos and him
Hiroshi, you fool
Did they really
say that?
And then
my dad got seriously angry
Every time they saw his face
His dad was really mad at us
They uttered "Hiroshi, hiroshi"
That sure is funny
Yeah, His dad was kind of messed up
Hiroshi Morioka
He brought out a bunch of porn mags
When we went to play at his house
Huh? For you kids? But you were in grade school right?
Yeah
Yeah he just threw them on the table
You were shown porn mags?
He said I can't deal with these anymore
I think it was during spring cleaning or something
So he threw them in a bonfire
"This one I don't need, this neither..."
And we kids were looking at this
Ah, I haven't finished watching this one yet
What happened with him anyway?
He's healthy...
Huh!? He's still alive? Wow
He's still well
That idiot...
Please stop
Morioka's reaction
Seriously?
is as if he's dead
I'm completely dead now
My wife isn't saying anything so
Like in an instant
Right?
I guess so, you're fully alive though..
I wonder what happened for a moment there
Saying "I wonder what happened for a moment"
These are the things this boring ass
is saying, after all
Come on, you just met him after all this time
35 years
How long has it been?
35 years huh, when exactly was the last time?
At Osaka station..
Oh we met?
At that disgusting under passage right?
Yeah, exactly
The manzai contest... Imamiya
Really?
So kind of in the middle of that. On your way home
And at that time
Wow, we met at an amazing place then
Your partner Hamada, cried out in a loud voice
"Morioka!"... at like the grounds there...
What are you saying? Who the hell is this?
What in the world...
Forget about that,
He cried out your name and you didnt know what he was saying?
When he saw Morioka
that's what he had to say, in a whoosh
Hamada's body just had to
When he saw him
his body just went Morioka!
Anyhow, he's a super kind guy
Aren't you?
We totally understand that
When you look at him, you understand
Yeah
He's never been angry right?
Yeah, that's right
A bit of a poor talker
I can't imagine that
But we understand
Exactly
He doesn't get that angry
I kind of
want to eat something Morioka has made
Let's eat!
So...
First of all, what is it?
How about your recommendation?
Ah, there ya go, Mapo Tofu
My recommendation would be Mapo Tofu
I never thought I'd be eating Morioka's
Mapo Tofu...
I didn't think it would happen
I've heard he worked his way up to be a head chef
And then 12 years ago
Wow..
He became independent
You worked hard didn't you...
That's incredible
It is, it is
Yeah, it really is
Is Yumi in good health?
Is everybody..
Yeah, everyone is...
Well, his little sister
Who is that? Yumi
Everyone is healthy huh? That's amazing
They are all well
There's Yoshitaka, Yumi
Ah, Kouji
And Kouji
Masako
Eiko
Kazuo
and Kazuo
And then at the very end Yoshiyuki
Yoshiyuki
So maybe Kouji?
Yoshiyuki...
The third one
Yeah the third one
That dude
was always taking persimmons!
From the neighbourhood?
Hahaha
Cause ya didn't have anything to eat
You know what,
There was a persimmon tree
next to the Dobu River
And there, like the tree was
It was too crooked?
how should I say, bending down
No no no, it was like...
The tree was like in a complete arch,
What do you call that?
You couldn't really tell at first glance
And then, Kouji was like holding on to the tree
Whaaa!
And as his back was almost
He munched on the persimmons
touching the river
Like a bear! He was a bear!
That's how bears eat
Cause he was hungry
Hah, because he was hungry?
They didn't have a choice
Have you met any
other peeps from Amagasaki?
Uhm...
One time... uh... the guy from the meat shop
Yamazato?
I went to him one time when... uhm..
they were closing
And uh then...
we went and kept them some company
But after that,
We had them all stay for dinner here
Your talking is completely hopeless
His talking is hopeless
There's no mistaking there
You know, It's because
he didn't speak until he was 7
Hahahaha
You're strict, I'm just a common guy
Hey!
Ooooh!
Mapo Tofu
Wow!
You can put some peppers on to your liking
Eating Mapo Tofu that Morioka has made...
Wow, this is amazing
It's...
Please eat up
It looks delicious
Wah, it really does
This is really professional, Morioka
Hmm?
I've been trying hard to figure it out
"Figured out" Mapo Tofu though
You're not the one to have
That's the chinese
Ah, so that's what he meant
The taste though, It's Morioka's take on it
Digging in...
Mmm!
It's delicious!
Thank you
Wow, that's delish!
It's delicious but
also has a "originality" to it
It's like different to
Yummy!
Way off
normal Mapo Tofu
He's saying that because he has worked hard
It's completely different
to figure out the perfect combination
Isn't your wife's support a little sloppy?
I especially praise his cooking
huh, whats going on?
At first the spicyness isn't so noticeable
It's delicious, the sweetness
What is this magic?
It's delightful
The sweetness is delightful
And the peppers...
If you put on some peppers
The tang changes again
Yes, exactly that
This is freaking good
It's good, the originality
is really prominent
Eat up everyone
This really is good
Shall we go for one more thing?
Yeah?
Yes
It was called the "Koma third branch" right?
Spinning top
What was it now?
So the third koma branch was
Yes, that's right
The manzai group
the name of the trio, yeah
Do you remember any sketches?
I told you, he doesn't speak
Anyway, Ito was...
He was called the "Iron spin top"
Iron top
Iron, wood...
and I was called the "wood spin top"
Wood top
Then naturally, Morioka was
was called the "plastic spin top"
Plastic top
The most boring one
The plastic spin top?
The simple guy huh
A simple guy
Iron top
Plastic top
Wood top
Such an unimportant guy
The cheap one
Haha, That's right
The wife is laughing like crazy
We had like songs too right?
However...
Songs?
The song of the "Spin top third division"
You don't remember? You cold hearted jerk
and iron is always smiling♬
♬The wood top is so kind
♬And the plastic top is so poor♬
Hahahaha!
Am I right? Morioka, you must remember
Hearing it now,
But I can't say I remember anything
I remembered a little bit
You sure do remember a lot
How come is it
that you, such a quiet guy
joined Matsumoto's group?
It was always us 3 together...
Through grade and middle school
Yeah we were somehow together
And we often went to Ito's
house and play...
Listen, Morioka was not a guy who
shared his feelings a lot
So you were tagging along, right?
Uhm...
Lonely?
Well, I was lonely so...
I'm gonna cry
Tears might be coming out at any moment
Well regarding that...
What's up with that? Suddenly...
Us 3 did manzai quite often
Where did you guys perform manzai?
and we were killing it too
Well at like, christmas meetings
and when there were other various assemblies
and because we did manzai in our own special way
we often killed it
At times, me and Ito
do we even need Morioka?
were often thinking
Because it was only the two of us who thought out the sketches
Iron top
Plastic top
Wood top
and sometimes only us two speaking
So Morioka didn't do much
and we thought let's do it without him then
That one time we did it without him
Wow!
was a complete disaster, we bombed
So at that time, we thought "We DO need him"
With this type of "Morioka" being with us
Ah, I see
We figured out the balance
It was very brash
Me and Ito always wanted to mess around with each other
I get it
and we were just freaking wasting time
Isn't noticing that in 4th grade
amazing?
Very harsh
Yeah it is
So Morioka made it important
around that
Because of the balance
Yeah, exactly
Wow, that's interesting
If that didn't happen
You probably wouldn't have made it would you
Exactly, that you're right.
Morioka, are you even listening?
Yes sir, I'm listening
"Yes sir"
Why the hell are you being so polite?
It's like you guys are brothers...
Morioka is just...
Classmates, right?
It's because you're former partners
Yeah he's a good guy though right?
Right?
Yes.. he is
Hey, your wife is saying kind things about you
I'm glad all siblings are alive and happy
Absolutely
It sure is good
It's a little...
What's up with this atmosphere?
Anything you remember,
Don't you have any memories of
Matsumoto?
Plenty of them
Morioka, did you like me?
Oh, that's a good one
I liked you from the start...
To begin with
Really? I thought I was disliked though
I don't think you remember but,
When we were in kindergarden...
Together yeah, and I had to hop off midstream
Yeah we were in kindergarden together
And then at the kindergarden's...
He just said he had to hop off kindergarden,
Completely cause of economic reasons..
Isn't that amazing?
Well I guess that's how it was
Right, Morioka?
So I quit midstream... and then I
the school gate
was always waiting outside
And then,
I heard macchan call for me
And then..kind of..from there
we started talking..
Huh?
That's the first
I don't really get it but,
You can call it the first time we started hanging out
It feels like I'm starting to cry
Makes you want to cry all of a sudden right?
Oh, here it is!
Wow, that looks amazing
Right after the story; "Shhuuwaa"
This looks so delicious!
So you...
You remember something like that?
One doesn't really have many
memories from kindergarden
Was that the earliest memory you have?
That voice, calling for me
Yeah the earliest...
Made me very happy...
That's why I have no trouble remembering it now
I think of it sometimes
So that's how it is, I guess I did do that.
You think of it sometimes?
I guess I did that...
Remarkable
Calling out for me..
What a great story
Morioka might actually be
my first ever friend
Am i right?
It was like that for him
and same for me
We were in the same class
all the way from grade school to 6th grade so...
It's unbelievable we were in the same class
Yeah yeah yeah
Me and Hamada never ended up in
the same class. Not even once
It was a wonder.
There were only 3 classes you know
Especially during 4th and 5th grade
What an amazing story
Exactly
We became 2 classes right?
Despite that,
Me and Hamada didn't end up in the same one
unfortunately. However, with Morioka
we were ALWAYS together
But if you add it all up
we've probably talked for 20 minutes all together
It must have been longer
That's short! Shorter than now
A lot longer...
You remember a lot
It's fried seafood rice
Morioka, What is this?
Fried rice (Scorched rice)
My thinking is just different
You're obsessed with it
Oh wow
Delicious
You've done well Morioka
So good
Hahaha
You've done very well
It's seriously what I think, You've done well
It's crazy good
It's really good!
So you can make stuff like this, huh!
The fried rice is also delicious
Cause he's a master chef
Yeah
Matsumoto's girlfriends...
So how about,
Do you know any
moments when he had one?
3rd year of middle school, in the recording room
Oh that's right
You were also in that club right?
So yeah, when I was
in the recording room
You guys together, Hamada and yourself
went in there and
told me to go out for a moment
And said, we're gonna do some confessing
Confessing?
Soon after
the girls came in and they were "confessing"...
Huh?
What the?
Hm?
Then after a few minutes they came out
and when I asked how it went
I could tell on their faces that
they were blushing and then
they both told me "I guess it was okay!"
Seriously,
couldn't you tell that story a little better?
We want to talk about things
appropriate for the episode though
It was like a double date
Yeah so,
With Hamada...That's
actually related to that park ya know
Oh right! Your first kiss
The Amagasaki one
That's some amazing history
Wow
Uhm yes.. around that time
You were kind of a late bloomer right?
I actually did date some girls though
however,
HUH!?
No I wasn't hiding it but...
So you were hiding it?
It was a senior from the same broadcasting club
Wait!
Did you know about this?
You didn't know?
Dang he's a player...
Morioka, were you really?
So freaking much
Oh so this is from middle school
This is from the middle school years
Wow, it's well kept
I also have this in my house but
Wow,
I don't really look in it
So the, broadcasting club
Ah the club
It's right here, the broadcasting club
Ito, Myself and Hamada here
Oh wow
So the, broadcasting club
It's right here, the broadcasting club
Ah the club
Ito, Myself and Hamada here
Oh wow
And here's Hayashi-sensei
who was in charge of Hamada
And during the 3rd year
Right right
When we had to start worrying about our
high school applications
This teacher here went to Hamada
and said "you should worry about brushing your teeth instead"
High school is out of your league,
you hobo
Are you really taking care of your hygiene properly?
Hahaha!
What does that mean?
What kind of inspection is that?
Anyway,
Morioka's personality is really shining through isn't it
Just like you told us, It's really...
Really showing through
When everybody were done with
their snacks and threw them away
You picked them up again and ate them didn't you
This has been really successful
It was really delicious
With this good food,
Thank you
and that you got to meet him after all this time
How about taking a commemorative photo
Let's do it
The long-awaited...
Alright I'm taking one,
wow, that peace sign...
Okay, going now, smile!
That was a good one!
Oh my
Definitely
This time was good
and iron is always smiling
♬The wood top is so kind
...And the plastic top is so poor♬
Let's head to drunken crab island!
Next time