Mom got taken away!
Day off
For more, please visit: http://tofupandas.tumblr.com/matsumotoke
The Matsumoto family's
Translated by: Otviss
Hey, what the hell are we actually doing today?
No no no...
He said it!
Because it's getting a little warmer now
Yeah
Oh..
We are going to go to
How many stations are there again?
all of the Osaka circle line stations in this series
Beyond 10 stations by now?
Shouldn't it be
So it's 10 stops now huh?
Yes
Most of the major routes
Yeah it links to
So, this time it's..
Nishikujo
This again..
I know about kujo though,
cause I used to live there
So it's next to that?
Yes, right next to it
I wonder how it is now though
Nishikujo is pretty much
in between Hanshin and JR so,
there are plenty of stuff under the elevated rail
I really do like areas under elevated rail
So let's enjoy ourselves
It's only 3 stops from Osaka station
so It's still within the central city area
And after US(Universal studios) also set up there
It has changed a lot
Oh really?
The entrance is right there so..
So how about we just go there?
Haha no no..
I wanna go!
US doesn't count as within the circle line so
Why is this show
so interested in like
all the freaking time?
taking us to remote areas
Hahaha!
Nishikujo is not a remote area though!
It's not a remote area..
We are never ever taken to places like
Universal studios or the Abeno Harukas
Do you want to go there?
I do!
Heck, if you say that, let's go then...
Jet coaster though right?
You wouldn't go on
Ah, the one at Universal studios?
Yes
What the hell is that?
What would you think about back drops?
A thing that goes backwards
Why the hell would you want us to do something like that
We debuted to go forward
not backwards
Yeah we've always been going forward!
Calm down you guys...
You're too vigorous!
So this time they
aren't gonna cut us off at
10.000 yen again right?
Actually, this time
Let's set that limit then
the prices are kind of cheap so
Shall we?
Yes, let's
10.000 Yen!
Limit at:
Matsumoto family budget
m -89 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 28 l 38 28 l -89 28
Oh, and since there
Okay, lets go then!
Are so many
little shops lined up this time
We gotta be self-disciplined
and look for like...
Huh?
Shops with originality
Well there are
plenty of shops competing
What you on about?
to stand out
Moody geezers around...
There's gonna be lots of
Let's look for some good grub shall we not!?
Well, despite that
He's kind annoying now
This is,
Kind of pissing me off yeah
Thanks!
This is the map we prepared
This is the so called "Gourmet town"
under the elevated rail in Nishikujo
Exactly
Hmm, There's a tunnel alley it seems
Hmm..
You can't talk about Nishikujo,
without mentioning the keyword "Gourmet"
Everytime we do these things
Gourmet huh?
there's always a way to tell
of the places we go to
the local speciality
So if we use this "Gourmet" keyword
but this time it's not so evident.
Yeah
what exactly would that mean
What in the world is "Harami 9" right?
Wow...
It's definitely Harami(skirt steak) but
Skirt steak...
like what do they do with the
That's why, I want you to
look at this map and
Clam grab grilling...
solve the mystery
I want to try that!
It makes you wanna try it right?
Just in what way will
they prepare it for you?
The clams that you take...
Yeah but the clams,
This is seriously messed up but
When I hear "clam grab grilling"
I imagine they grill the clams
while you're still holding them in your hand
Hey, is that gonna happen?
You guys be careful alright?
Are they gonna grill them in my hand?
You sure are taking it literally
They are definitely not...
Let's go find out if
actually grill them in your hand
That's what it's all about today
If they grill it or not... what the?
Why are you staring at me for?
I kinda felt you bombed with that joke
Listen, Udon..
Udon no Hentai(Obsession)!
What is... Right?
I wonder what that means?
Udon no Hentai (Pervert)
Does that mean they are gonna
do rope bondage with the udon noodles?
Wow, that's harsh
It's no good if we don't stop filming
We definitely have to cut it there..
Hahaha..
Those would give a lot of strength for sure!
We're not..
Yeah? What is that..
You definitely do
You get curious
Here's one that's ridiculous
Which one?
"Great taste, Great entertainment? - A brothers bar"
Great entertainment...
That's just too exhausting
It's probably a
Store the Nakagawa brothers have been to
The Nakagawa brothers...
You got it
Those dudes
are in Yoshimoto you know
I wonder what that means.
I guess
we're going to find out right?
9:1 dream rice bowl
What the?
What is 9:1 right?
"Magic flour, Hachimi?"
Huh?
Not ichimi, not shichimi, but hachimi huh?
Firstly, which one are we starting with?
Hmm..
Ah, what about the clams?
We going there?
The ones you grab and get grilled?
Yeah the clams are kind of...
And get grilled? Yeah, we don't
know if they're gonna grill 'em like that yet though
I love clams
We don't know that
Ah, its probably like you get to
grab them yourselves right?
Yeah maybe, cause I'm imagining
they grill only the ones...
You manage to grab,
am I right?
Oh! So how bout we make a game
out of the one who
WOULDN'T THAT BE INTERESTING!?
manages to grab the most.
Come on, I was just saying!
I wanna see the face
I'm not failing!
of a failing comedian
I'm not messing around!
Alright, got it
Let's go!
We're going to Nishikujo!
We've arrived!
Well then, we're here in Nishikujo
Couldn't we pick a place
It's kind of amazing
with a bit more sun?
It's cold
It's shining in the completely wrong place
Look up there please
There's the elevated JR(Japanese railway)
And then Hanshin(Electric rail) as well
Oh! I see I see..
That's how it is yeah
Exactly
It's really convenient
Seems like a very nice and convenient station
You said it.
I see
Namba is in walking distance as well
It's kind of nice isn't it?
Nishikujo is freaking nice
I wonder why we
haven't been here before huh?
It's because of the circle line..
Well..
Hahaha..
We didn't know about any weird
planning like that. Since when?
I've said it so many times now
Yes but for how long has
Constantly!
has the camera been rolling though?
Huh!?
Yes, constantly!
I didn't know about that
They've always been on!?
The two camera men.
They were here weren't they?
They've been here all the time.
Wow you're right!
I'm a big fan of these guys now
They were here from the start
Hahaha!
Why would they film a fan?
Let's get going then!
to the clam grab grill!
Grabbing some clams...
I'm really hungry
It's here?
It's in the under rail passage
Kenji, I'm freaking hungry
The clam grab grilling
There's also the Udon transformation place
Yeah, if that name gave us so good vibes
from there, no?
maybe we should start
"Gold town"!
Wow, the entrance is really cool!
This is cool!
Woah!
Nishikujo parlor
This is good!
This is really... Oh wow, what's this?
If we find a good place
along the way let's go there
Sure thing
Why is..
Hm?
Is this really the right way?
Must be here. There's no other path
This isn't a dead end?
Wow...
Oh, we're out again!
What the hell's the matter with you
But...
Ugh..
But..
Clams, where ya at!?
No the.. It's...
This is all there is
This is all there is, ya know
You're right..
It's definitely on the outside
Maybe this way, huh?
This place is certainly...
Interesting
Yeah, it's nice
Sure is
Wow, they're already drinking
From lunch time
They are drinking like crazy
There are gramps who drink during
lunch time for sure
Kenji, I said I was hungry
Knight Scoop!
Look, It's the bicycle from
Ah.
Haha, you got it instantly.
The one at the back right?
Why is that always there by the way?
It's a part of the set
It's constantly there though
Yeah it is.. and uhm
a horse too
and a horse yeah
Oh, here's another one!
Perhaps it's here?
There are tons of 'em!
Look, Hormon!
"Yamato charcoal grilled hormon"
I guess that sounds good
However, the shop
Kenji mentioned...
ADD TEXT ( DONE)
Uh, There's a monster!
Huh? A monster?
Oh crap!
Wait, are we okay?
No no no I don't want too, it's scary!
Oh come on, we're fine
Flip it over it for me!
Flip it over,
Hahaha..
It's just a normal frog you guys
The frog is standing on two legs!
What the? This is so off-putting
Ah, look here!
It's cause there's a frog shop here
Ah, that's why
What the hell is that anyway, Frog shop
Didn't know there were shops like that
My gosh, this is so creepy
Huh? What?
Odds and ends shop
No that's not...
Huh?
Mommy!
Mom!
Hey, Mom!
Mommy!
He's being kidnapped!
Mom's being kidnapped!
Hey, Mommy!
This is bad, this is bad!
Here please..
Mom is being taken away
Mommy, stop! This is not good at all!
Ah!!
Huh!?
But, he's kidnapped..
Oh wow, Tamura Kenji! ♥
No no no, this is our mom!
They kidnapped my mommy!
They took my mom away...
It's locked!
What's this all about?
Eh!?
Oh no...
Tamura Kenji decided to join us, everyone!
Mom, what are you doing?
What the hell?
Finally, we took them here
Mommy....
Mommy, what's all this?
We brought them, everyone
What are you doing?
I don't know a bloody thing
What's going on here?
What's this all about?
Wow, I'm so happy!
It's karaoke!
There are snacks even..
Hm? Did you say something?
♬After so many times, so many times
Please, we apologize but...
I have no idea what's going on
This situation...
Wait, you mean mine?
She's really good
Who's song is this?
Sorry but, I just heard my
father comes here often.
Hahahahahaha!!
I apologize
Woah, this surprised me!
Huh?
Is this for real?
Thank you so much for coming. Thank you!
That really surprised me
Don't worry, I'm under your care,
I'll try to behave.
I'll behave
Uh.. yes, thank you thank you.
Thank you very much...
You're so cool ♥
I also just found out, This is my
Son's friend's grandmother.
The world really is small!
What is this place, I'm at loss for words.
"Karaoke snack" right?
"Karaoke snack"
Please sing a song!
Please sing once, one song only
Please..
Otherwise we're not getting outta here
That's messed up, It feels too weird
Just one song please!
We just started filming...
We'll start with one song..
We'll start with one? No this...
1 Song!
From dad
The matsumoto family:
m -89 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 28 l 38 28 l -89 28
A representation of his dad!
He's gonna sing to represent his dad
To represent
my Dad?
I can't figure out who works here and who are customers...
The two over there are the owners
Wow I can't believe it..
"Kimi wa habara yori utsukushii"
Go daddy!
Thank you very much..
His dad always
sings this one
Wow, thats really...
Thank you so much everyone!
Thank you, thank you.
Thanks everyone
We have to go now
Let's get going
Sorry for intruding
Thanks for having us.
This was truly remarkable,
Please take care of my dad
next time he's here
Thank you for coming!
Thank you.
Sorry for intruding like this..
Thank you very much
Thank you
That was just...
That was shocking
Absolutely amazing..
What in the world just happened
That was seriously scary
the moment I came through that curtain
My heart was racing from
Yeah that curtain was scary for sure
I guess kidnapping is a real thing
I guess that was some real customer service, huh
That really surprised me, I'm
disoriented once again
Did we walk too far?
Huh? I'm telling you is this way
Clam grab grilling...
Well you could say,
I was already grabbed and
ready for more
But ya didn't get grilled
But it was close, It felt like we
were all being grilled in there
Are we really going back here?
Yeah, I guess here..
Alright, going back then..
We haven't found a single shop yet
Ah, but this is kinda...
Look at the sign over there
"Number 18 OK Road"
Ah...
Number 18 OK?
Ya bet
Huh? Is this right?
This is not within reach at all.
I'm freaking hungry!
We haven't been to a single place,
Eh!?
IT'S HERE! LOOK!
Which one?
You're right! It says it right there
One time for 200 yen! That's cheap!
Ah crap!
Let's do it!
So we can only do it once huh? Uhm so...
Hello there
Hello
Are ya doing clam grab grilling here?
Yes we are
Really? We finally found it
How about mom goes first..
Who's gonna go then?
My fingers are too short
Mine aren't such a big deal either
Yours are way too short
How about you?
You've got boring ass hands
My hands are big, yeah
Yeah I guess Kenji..
Alright, alright...
If you could do it with both of your hands...
For 200 Yen!?
We can do it with both!?
This hospitality is over the top!
Eh, so how am I..
I just do like this?
Not like that no,
grab them from above please
Wow, it's packed full
Can we do it with one hand each?
That's completely fine
Hey, mommy
One hand each
Yeah
Both of ya grab with the
strength of each hand and then you
push your hands together
so that you can take the ones in between too
Wow you really know
how to do this, huh?
Ah I gotcha!
So I do this so we can combine..
Okay and then...
We're gonna get some in between
cause we can only do it once right?
Let's go lets go!
This is gonna work out perfectly
Can ya do it?
So first...
Shit thats cold
Yes it is
It's not gonna work
No no, if you do it like that
Yes yes yes exactly! The ones in between too!
Oooh!
Exactly like that!
Faster faster! And then down in the bowl!
Yay!
You did it!
This is what we took!
We managed to grab quite a lot didn't we?
This what ya managed?
Very clever
Alright then!
You think we're good?
It's a lot
We did it.
And then you're gonna prepare it
for us right here right?
We did it, guys
Yes, exactly
Let's go
Let's head in
Hello
A hidden pub under the elevation
Rare cuisine
"Kameman"
Lots of fun events!
Yoshimoto comedians
also come here often
Oh wow
they do all kinds
You're right
Saikoro steak. one time for 780 yen
I wanna do that～
If ya throw a 6 you get 300grams!
If you win you get 10% off
They have Oaiso rock, paper, scissors too
Why don't you try it?
Wow!
Wow this made me happy
What's this about like, is this
Yeah like..
a gambling themed store?
How do you want the clams prepared?
Alcohol steamed or butter fried
This should definitely...
Wow
I mean we can only pick
one or the other right?
Half and half is...
Half and half
Alright we'll do half and half then
Okay? Really?
Don't forget this is only 200 yen, we have money left
Now I'm happy
You're absolutely right, this is cheap!
"Kameman"
9800 Yen
Clam grab for 200 Yen
Left:
m -13 37 l 2 37 l 3 18 l 2 -4 l -2 -23 l -68 -25 l -86 -25 l -86 39 l -86 37 l -33 37
Today we have a limit of 10.000 yen so..
Yeah
We're kind of using the money wisely I think
Yeah, you're right
Do you want to do the steak dice?
Are we okay with that?
Steak dice as well
780yen for one time
If ya throw a 6 we get 600grams
Let's do it!
This one isn't good, 50 grams see?
Yeah if you throw a one we'll give you 50 grams of meat.
Even if we pay 780yen?
Yes, the price for competing..
Let's do it then
Let's go
Since me and Kenji
did the clams last time
Alright, I'll do my best
We'll let you do it this time
Hey, she's even
bringing you something
Hey it's Cee-lo!
Yeah
It feels like the
bad luck from last year
Is not quite gone
It's definitely still there
The dice is letting me start from one though
Wow...
So you're saying it won't show?
Yes it won't
If you were to be speculative right?
It definitely won't show, let's go
Okay here it comes
300 would be amazing
Alright!
5!
That's good!
If it was my turn then maybe...
Then for comparison
What the hell? That's no good!
If I'd done it
we would have had great success!
I'm glad you did it this time
That was risky
We were lucky
Really close
That was close for sure!
How embarassing～
We are noticing your clumsiness
"Kameman"
9020 Yen
Clam grab for 200 Yen
Saikoro steak for 780 Yen
Left:
m -13 37 l 2 37 l 3 18 l 2 -4 l -2 -23 l -68 -25 l -86 -25 l -86 39 l -86 37 l -33 37
200g certainly is big
We did it though
Should we have some drinks?
Yeah for sure, let's drink
And now, if we win
Rock-paper-scissors
We get 10% off
You're right
That's awesome actually
What's up with this store?
How about a "Free Jack Highball"?
Huh?
A what?
Oh, "Freezing"
Cause it's chilled
It's "freezing"
Japanese-style
They have 和 high ball too
That's nice
Zero sugar, Zero purines, not sweet
Me too!
Should I get this maybe...
4 和 high balls from wheat liqour please
和 high ball is good
"Kameman"
7340 Yen
Clam grab for 200 Yen
Saikoro steak for 780 Yen
和 high ball x 4 for 1680 Yen
Left:
m -13 37 l 2 37 l 3 18 l 2 -4 l -2 -23 l -68 -25 l -86 -25 l -86 39 l -86 37 l -33 37
Okay!
I'm glad we
didn't go to that Udon shop
I'm happy we have that ahead of us
Yeah I guess so
Did we...
I want to go to the Udon place too
How do we find that place then?
Well since
It's going to be easy to find the others
we found this place now so
Cause now we're in the "Number 18 OK" right?
What I really wouldn't
want is going by
Exactly
that karaoke bar...
Never ever in my life again
There's a possibility
We're gonna pick that one again
This is the entrance to the Number 18 OK so...
Oh I see, I got it...
Alright, I got it now
Here you are, sorry to have kept you waiting
Thank you very much!
Yay!
Cheers!
Delicious
Wow, that's delicious
It's really not sweet at all
Right? This is good
I can drink tons of these
This is good!
This is good for yer body
Yoshimoto people coming here right?
You get a lot of
Yes, we get plenty actually
Who was the first one that came here?
We had Yoshida Yutaka here...
Well first...
And then Matsura Shinya as well
Oh really? Yoshida?
Wow
People say this place is good
and they keep on coming do they?
Wow, all of them are new comedians
Bon appetit, Alcohol steamed clams
Oh it's here!
Alcohol steamed clams
Wait, this is half?
Wow, it smells amazing
So this is what we.. huh?
There are some green onions in there
There are some "Field mustard flowers" as well
Wow...
Field mustard huh?
Field mustard..
Wow, this truly is amazing
You can put the shells in here..
Thank you very much.
The staff are certainly friendly aren't they...
Absolutely..
Ooh! This broth is nice!
Oh wow, this broth is so nice
Right?
As a savoury food this is a 100 points from me
This is delicious!
The best!
The clams are also nice and chewy
Huh!?
Why the hell are you
No, Its cause
Scooping into the trash bowl
Mom put
shells in
How embarassing～
my bowl already...
His clumsiness is too obvious
Yes
Sorry for intruding, here is the
butter fry version
Butter fried clams
Huh? Did we order this?
Wow
This is a 100 yen ya know
I'd love to make pasta with that
This juice is great...
I'd love to mix this
With this?
Wow..
and that together
Clams are truly amazing...
It would be great
This broth is just perfection.
I'm beaten, this is delicious
Very
Hmm...
This place is truly great
This place must be crushed in the evenings right?
Crushed?
Yeah, packed!
You mean packed right?
It's okay you didn't get it
Packed?
This guy is the strange one
Ah okay, Thank you
Yeah it's okay you didn't get "crushed"
I can't imagine anything else
But during these hours
there aren't that many though
This place is cheap too
Yeah
Here's the saikoro steak..
Very sorry for the wait,
Exactly, cause he threw a five..
It's cause dad threw a five...
780 yen!
Hang on, for 700 we..
Here's the saikoro steak..
Very sorry for the wait,
Exactly, cause he threw a five..
It's cause dad threw a five...
780 yen!
Hang on, for 700 we..
This is a lot!
Saikoro steak 780 Yen (200g)
Hmm?
Is this for real?
Oh this...
Should we lower this maybe...
So tender..
Is it?
This is crazy tender you guys...
Is it really?
Wow that's tender
This is amazing, what meat is this?
This is so tender!
It's a little stiff... Isn't it thigh meat?
It's tender!
This is freaking delicious...
This is some luxury meat right here..
Yeah the taste of lean meat..
Wow, this is just amazing
This is remarkable,
truly delicate...
Mmm!
The sauce is good too!
Uhuh
Yeah you're right
Right?
Yup!
Wanna do rock-paper-scissors!?
Yeah let's go!
If we win we turn the 2790yen
Let's do it
That's...
to 2390yen
400 yen! That's about one of these
So.. you for the clams and steak..
Huh? For real?
Let's order
Let's do it. Win okay?
Pick the staff member of your liking..
We get to do it with whoever I want?
Yes
Sadako, who you gonna pick?
Well obviously, the good who looks unlucky
That person!
That's reckless! Get outta here!
You are the hopeless one!
That's the boss yer talking to
How unexpected...
Seriously, knock it off..
There's no one as lame as you
What the hell is wrong with you?
I thought we
were were supposed to
enjoy ourselves
with the cute staff
Only one try!
Sadako vs Owner
Serious Rock-paper-scissors
m -89 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 -43 l 38 28 l 38 28 l -89 28
That's the real boss you were talking to
If you win we pay 2390 yen
Because it's a 400 yen difference
you better win!
Rock-paper...
If you win we pay 2390 yen
Wanna do rock-paper-scissors!?
Because it's a 400 yen difference
you better win!
Rock-paper-scissors!
That was a cheap win..
We won and made it cheaper
Yay I did it!
This is big. This piece here..
We certainly got off cheap!
Hey big bro! I actually contributed
something to the family for the first time!!
A calling! Perverted udon
Next time