Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Kazutoyo Koyabu, Tamura Kenji and Morita
This is the semi-annual everyone's theories special!
The Three Musketeers have the honor of gathering today
-Really?
Who gave you this name?
We are known as the Three Musketeers of Order and Comedy
Just the three of you?
It's the three of us. This time Morita is a newcomer
-Yes
Individual Morita
-Enough!
Don't mention that
Who has been replaced?
It seems to be changed many times
-The position often changes
For example, Kasuga, Kojima.
-Yes, yes
Kasuga can't show his face on TV anymore, right?
That's not the case
He should not be willing to show his face
If he was an individual it'd be over for him
Indeed
So who wants to be the first?
Let me take the lead, please.
-Wow, this guy's voice is loud enough
To open is a sharp and incomparable theory
I hope to meet everyone's expectations
The theory I bring this time is
If you run into your mother on the street but are treated with indifference, you will gradually think it's a stranger who looks like them
A long title
Good point, good point
This can happen?
This kind of thing usually does not happen, but we want to see what happens if it does
When I talk to my father, he doesn't change his look at all
That's something else, don't bring it up
Stop it, okay?
This may indeed be the case from an age perspective
He's already not listening
What are you talking about!?
"Not listening"
You're so insensitive!
No, it's like he's just saying the same thing all the time
If you run into your mother on the street but are treated with indifference, you will gradually think it's a stranger who looks like them
Assisting us this time is
Panther Ogata's mother, Meiko Ogata
Her son is being interviewed by a fake magazine
To make mom look more like a stranger
She wears clothes she would not normally wear
Already in a different category
And takes position in front of the building where her son is
Ogata, what are you going to do?
What will happen?
It's pretty scary
Even with the glasses, it's hard to tell
Ogata completely directly fails to notice her
After all, it's a different look
Due to the result, we retest
This time in front of Yoshimoto's head office, she's in position without her glasses
The result
Here we go, here we go
Here we go!
Should notice this time
This dress...
He's noticed!
What are you doing?
-Eh, eh?
Eh?
-Eh?
You're my mum, right?
What?
-You're my mom, right?
Why?
You have the wrong person
No, no, no. You're my mother.
-No, no, no, what?
Who are you shouting "mum" at?
Eh?
-Eh?
I don't know you.
-What the hell is going on?
Eh?
-Eh?
I'm just waiting for a friend here
What?
-You have the wrong person, right?
Eh?
-Eh?
I really don't get it.
-Stop, stop, stop.
You are definitely my mother!
Why?
You're definitely my mother.
-No, no...i'm not
Eh?
-Eh?
I'm meeting a friend
They haven't come yet, so i've been waiting here
No no no
Wait a minute...
You are my mother, right? Is that wrong?
Big mistake. I don't even know you
Her acting skills are explosive
You are definitely my mother!
Absolutely.
-No...no, i'm not. I don't know you
No, you're definitely my mother.
-I said no!
You're my mother!
-What are you doing?
Why are you being like this? It's too strange and rude, right?
One hundred percent.
-I said no. How rude!
I'm rude?
-Yes, you're rude
How is it possible to find two people so alike
I have never seen such a shameless person
You are definitely my mother, I can't be wrong
It's so weird
Starting to be a bit suspicious
Are you telling the truth? Where are you from?
Where am I from? I'm from Iwate
Not Miyagi?
-No.
Then maybe our ancestors are connected
We are definitely relatives, no doubt about it
Relatives!
He actually took the bait?
What is your last name?
Fujiwara
-Fujiwara?
My last name is Ogata
It's not Ogata?
-No.
Can this kind of thing can happen?
I'm so sorry.
-Yeah
Ah, the phone is not the same
You must have made a mistake...
But isn't it just too similar?
Similar, like, super similar
I've never seen a dress like this either
Are you sure you're not my mother?
-I'm sure
I always go out dressed like this
I can't believe this is happening...
Sorry about that.
-Yeah
In summary
Consecutive denials will lead to the person being assumed to be someone else
In the end, he really gave up
He really thought it was another person
Really took the bait!
The mother worked very hard
Controlled her accent
Stayed close to standard language and spoke in a different way than usual
Not even a single smile
Aside from this I have many over theories for everyone
Please enjoy the following few all together
The rest of the theories selected by Koyabu are...
If the string on the pull-to-heat beef tongue lunch box is actually a party cracker, you won't even notice it
Another long one
This time, under the guise of a special test program meeting
Ganbare Luya
What is a special test program?
For a tasting session, what was put in front of them was
Special Beef Tongue Pull-ring Bento
What is the result?
Then please eat first
-Okay
Must be delicious when it's hot
A little scared
Look at Mahiru's face!
This was all for this reaction!
The next theory selected by Koyabu is
Do pachinko parlor clerks spend their days off playing pachinko
The investigation begins
How long have you worked at the pachinko parlor?
Been doing this since I started college
About 12 years now
What do you do on your days off?
I play pachinko
Does it make people forget reality?
Once you're addicted, it is like you're instantly in another world
There are times to win and times to lose
These moments are what make you forget about everyday life
It's just too fun
To deal with the hard life of working at a pachinko parlor
You can use pachinko to forget about it
What do you do on your day off?
On rest days I play pachinko
When on a break I will definitely go to play pachinko
Absolutely? 100%?
-Yes, almost always
What do you do on your day off?
I play pachinko
What time from?
As soon as the store opens
What do you do on your day off?
I usually play online games
-Online games?
We surveyed the days off of 62 pachinko parlor workers
In the lead was Pachinko
What's more
I also play on work days
I play pachinko before work
After work and I go back to playing pachinko, that's it
If i'm on the morning shift, I'll go to play after occasionally
So once pachinko is over, you move onto pachinko
An endless loop of pachinko
It's not just the days off, but even the weekdays
There are many people who play pachinko before and after work
After having fun in pachinko...
-After you've had fun, you go to work in pachinko
Basically I spend about 300 days or more a year on it
In the pachinko store?
-Yes
The next theory selected by Koyabu is
When calling someone to check the answer to an argument, and your opinion is correct, the first thing you will say after hanging up the phone is, "See?"
I told you!
So, Tsuneida will set-up the verification
How do you set this up?
By targetting his senior
And so
Komen is a junior high school graduate, right?
They say he's a junior high school graduate
He actually graduated from high school
No... junior high school graduate, right?
-He's not a junior high school graduate
Eh, really?
-Yeah
Eh? No way!
A debate begins
I want to make sure, seriously
Hello? Sorry to trouble you, Komen
Tsuneida is wondering...
We're both drinking
And he's talking nonsense
He says you're a junior high school graduate, but you're a high school graduate, right?
Right?
As Komen is actually a high school graduate
Will he say "See!"?
Okay, sorry
You were saying?
The next theory selected by Koyabu is
At the moment of crossing the finish line when winning the marathon, no runner will not raise their hands high in the air
To verify, we investigated the winning moments of Olympic gold medalists across all generations
First, the 2016 Olympic Games in Rio de Janeiro
Hands up!
Next is the women's race
Sure enough, they also lifted
Basically, they will
Then came the London 2012 Olympics
2008 Beijing Olympics
Next also
Two consecutive gold medals
Finally Takahashi wins the gold medal
Into the glorious final sprint now
The olympic gold medalist arrives at the finish line
Now Yegorova crosses the finish line
Arriving at the end
However, there were also less subtle players
Leaving the 10th win at the Olympics Breakthrough finish
Carlos Lupis now crosses the finish line
John Benoit of the United States crosses the finish line
Aside from the women's marathon standing race
Which was not included in the TBS broadcast, all the gold medalists raised their hands
What an old image!
Ah, raised his hands!
What a thin rope
Do you want to lift it? Do you want to lift it?
No lift
The final theory selected by Koyabu is
The hairstyle that appears most in lyrics is the ponytail
Flat hair
Braids
Bomb hair
Long hair
2x ponytail
The results of the 10th to 6th place are as follows
Next, we will publish the 5th to 2nd place at once
Today is also full of energy, a big bang
Drape yourself in a bachelor's suit and add an flat top
Bald headed Taro, under the sun
Short-haired me showing a smile
Slightly to the left perm
Finally, in the top spot is
Ponytail shake shake shake
A long way ahead!
Ponytail with 102 songs
Is a distant first
I see.
-Yes
Yoshida, what do you think?
Aren't Pachinko's clerks tired of being like that all the time?
They stay where they work all the time, don't they?
Yoshida, you watch the news even on your days off, right?
The concept is the same
That's not the right way to put it, is it?
I wanna know her opinion
In that case, is it true that the news anchors do not watch the news during their breaks?
Well, as an entertainer
I watch variety shows and also go see live shows at the theatre
Newscasts are not just about reading the news
If you think in this way, should people who grow rice on the farm eat bread?
What are you mad about?
Let's explore this in a theory
Next is a theory selected by Tamura Kenji
Have you ever played VR?
Sure.
-You have?
Yes, I think so
It's really awesome now
It's like another world
So its feels very real
So, I brought this theory
If you wake up in a VR world, you would be super surprised
What?
Sounds tough
How can you do it?
Yeah
First you need to put it on
It isn't easy
That thing is pretty heavy
And it is important for the person not to wake up
But this program has a king of not waking up if he falls asleep
Could it be...
Everyone's favorite monster
He once got home drunk and went under his bed
And fell asleep straight away
You can put it on, right? If it's that guy.
-Should be doable
Get him drunk and go home
And put it on before he sobers up
What happens when Kuro-chan wakes up in the morning to find himself in a different world
If you wake up in a VR world, you would be super surprised
So
My most recommended pubs
Start!
We start with this fake plan of drinking and talking
And so
Iwawawaaaa~
Ah, smells good!
Too close!
As usual, Kuro-chan drinks at a high speed
Then I will touch you
And follows up with sexual harassment in front of the camera as usual
You're really cute, Irina!
Ah, cute, like...
Whoa, today may be interesting
Another, please
-Good
The more he drinks, the stronger the result
How much are you drinking?
Drinking loads
I want to go out with you and I want to have sex too
But... but that's not what I mean
Completely drunk
And
Danger danger!
Wall-to-wall
Really, I... I really think you are cute
I know
Careful
Monstrous as per usual
Bye bye
Irina... I... like Irina
Irina
-Ok
Preparation complete
Is there any other ending like this?
The location shoot?
It's over
Is it over?
Yes, please put on your shoes
He's farting
A man who doesn't drink like an adult in his 40s
Is stuffed into a cab
And forced to return home
Later, he arrives home
Irina
He immediately lays down on his bed
And falls asleep in a flash
So
Here we go, here we go
No need to wear the costume, right?
Finally, the VR equipment is brought it
Really can't wake up
Putting it on so early?
Who knows when he'll wake up
By the way, the VR Kuro-chan will see is this
An image of standing in a high place
The next thing to do would have been to wait until the morning but
Even if you know it's VR you'd still be afraid
As it will be more difficult to distinguish between virtual and reality in a drunken state
We wake him up immediately
However
He doesn't wake up at all
So the final resort was used
Sincere effort is expended to get him on his feet
So
Finally he's a little sober
The VR experience begins
What is this? A construction site?
What?
What what what what?
What? There's a bell. There's a bell
Bell, what? What's going on?
What's happening?
What is this?
Where is this?
Where? Where? Where? Where?
A ferris wheel!
Where? What's going on?
Like this, Kuro-chan has completely entered the VR world
But because he doesn't look down much he isn't that scared
At this point, the plan changes
And the image is replaced with a sexy one
Who?
Seriously, who is this? Very cute
He wants to touch
What is this? What?
What?
Who is it?
Change of clothes? Who?
What what what?
Really wants to touch
What is this?
Wait, the clothes...
Watching so intently
Looking at the ass
Crazyily looking at the ass
Constantly at this angle
He's watching!
Suddenly looking at the face now
And then
Seducing me? Seducing me?
So scary
He pounced!
It hurts. What's wrong?
Ow ow ow!
He just tried to jump on her!
So painful
What? What is this?
What's going on now?
Pay attention to me!
You're not seducing me?
This, what, what is this, what?
Hey, what...
Completely inaccessible
What what what?
Hey, are you not seducing me?
What? What is this?
Don't say goodbye!
What's going on now?
What? What's happening? What?
Wait a sec
Wait, where did you go?
Then
Finally realised
What is this?
Where's Irina?
Irina?
This is my home
What's going on?
A dream?
In summaryA dreamlike VR experience
Haven't seen him for so long but he's still amazing
Really a monster
Usually this isn't the sort of approach you should use to get close to a woman
It's like a cartoon
So scary!
Ow ow ow
Lupin the 3rd in action
That jumping method!
Lupin's jumping method when only wearing underwear
Here are more theories selected by Tamura Kenji
The next is
If you get super mad, any living creature can feel your anger
Mammals like dogs or cats can certainly understand anger
So we investigate with a reptile
This time we use a turtle approaching food
Behind the food, an expression of anger with full force
Will it cause the turtle to stop?
Start!
Don't fucking come this way!
Putting on such a disgusting face
Don't approach me with that face
If you come here i'll wrap you up in this green vegetable and eat you!
I won't forgive even a turtle!
Oi, get the hell back!
If you come any closer
I'll beat you so hard you'll never reach land again
You bald bastard!
Hey, I told you not to get close!
Hey, don't come any closer!
Hey, I told you not to come any closer!
Oi, are you fucking listening to me?
Get the fuck out of here. Stop fucking around!
The next theory selected by Tamura Kenji is
Bulldogs with spiky collars do not actually exist
Do young people know this?
The studded collar was made famous by cartoons and BULL-DOG SAUCE
To put it bluntly, it's a cliche
And may even hurt the dog itself
So, surely no bulldog actually wears it
But after starting a investigation
We received a sighting in Osaka
So
We visit the family
Hello
Sorry
We hear you have a pit bull with a spiky collar
Ah, yes
Really?
Want to see it? Come on up
That's her. That's the kid
Yes, there is
This dog wears the owner's homemade collar
Why do you want it to wear this studded collar?
Looks good
Bulldogs have been wearing these collars for a long time
The bulldog's name
Comes from the fact that they were bred to fight with bulls
So why would they need to wear a studded collar?
To protect the neck
The neck is the weakest place of the dog
So this protects the neck when the dogs fight
It's protective gear
With the spiky collar
Will it not prick the dog?
It's okay, it's okay to be bitten and pricked
The skin is soft
Is that so?
-Yes
There is elasticity so it is soft and fluffy like this
Just like this
Really? I see
Don't get bitten!
By the way, the master's skin is not so soft
As bloodshed has occurred after being jumped often
The next theory selected by Tamura Kenji is
People who buy crossword books have no immediate plans for after
We monitored a bookstore for 3 days
Too malicious
Not many sales
Did it take 3 days?
Finally, we found a purchaser
And so
We are a TBS program
What did you just buy?
Logic
Puzzle
Can I ask you something?
Do you have plans after this?
Yes
What plans?
Going to KFC
For lunch?
-Yes.
And after that?
Nothing
So... you're free?
Well, a bit
The last theory selected by Tamura Kenji is
Can Hikomaro make a bad dish look good?
A treasure chest!
Known for his unique performance
Hikomaru is one of the pioneers of food commentary
But, will he express the feeling that something is unpalatable?
So
This dish was prepared by
Here we go again
Working man!
Wake up
Hey, what what what?
Let's go
Where to?
You'll know when you get there
What is this Antonio Inoki "You'll understand when you go. Thank you."
Let's go
Did he ever say that?
So, with Kuro-chan, who has finally sobered up
Is this a metaphor you use if you just woke up?
So impolite
He arrives at the kitchen studio
Where?
What is it?
Now, Kuro-chan, please cook a dish in a blindfolded state
Huh?
Wait, I don't cook
Haven't done it in over 10 years
Don't you think it's strange to be blindfolded?
Despite saying this, he starts cooking blindfolded straight away
Stir-fried vegetables
I think it's a carrot
Kuro-chan recognizes ingredients and spices by touch and taste
Soy sauce
The hygiene level is a bit...
What are you doing?
Yeah, he doesn't know
Can only taste test
This is probably olive oil
Wait, this stuff does not seem to be drinkable
Afterwards, he boldly cuts vegetables
And carefully sautés them in a pan
Impressive he got this far
Talented!
However
Pepper
Is it in?
I can't tell if any has gone in or not
The finished dish is this
OPEN
What's this smell?
The vegetables are a mess
To be frank, it's more feed than a dish
So, the food review begins
Here we go
So hard
See? It's raw
These fried vegetables are past it
This is the Lehman Shock of the vegetable world
※Lehman Shock: An important trigger for the outbreak of the 2008 U.S. financial crisis
The collapse has already occurred
2nd try
Ah, a nice sound
Wow, what is this?
Too much pepper
Pepper's solo concert
This...
Horses won't even eat it
A horse won't eat it, it's just not good
A complete acrobatic troupe of food waste
In summary
The difficulty of eating was very well conveyed
As expected
Very impressive
What do you think, Sho?
The bulldog
Had the feeling of wanting to protect the public's impression
I think it's interesting
Our old CD covers were similar
We had bats with spikes on them
We made them
Everyone felt depressed
Using such a thing to hit was someone would be just despicable
You'd have to have brain issues to use it
The type that, instead of beating people up
Wouldn't dare to actually stand up to other people
What have you learned?
Next are the theories chosen by Morita
So, I'll be finishing things
Okay, got it.
-Go for it!
The last of The Three Musketeers
No need for this name
As the last of the Three Musketeers of the Order and-
It's the "Three Musketeers of Order and Comedy"
Enough already!
There's business issues related to this
What business, you're an indivdiual!
Individuals can also be members of the Three Musketeers!
It's "The Individual Three Musketeers"
The Three Musketeers, my, Takei Juso and TrumpMan
That's it. The theory I chose for everyone are as follows
Does throwing a tantrum work for adults?
Eh?
-Eh?
Children do it to their parents
Will it work if parents do it to their children?
Does throwing a tantrum work for adults?
It's like this
What kind of content is it?
-Yeah
The verification is Nakagawa Paradise's father-son pair
Currently, the thing the son wants the most is Nintendo's LABO
Upon entering the store
The father will begin to pout "I really don't want to buy it after all,"
Welcome
Ah, is this it?
Is this it?
-Yeah
How much is it?
How does it work?
This is too expensive
I thought it would be cheaper
Daddy doesn't want to buy it
Won't buy, won't buy, hate it hate it hate it
Won't but it! I absolutely won't buy it!
He's throwing a tantrum!
No! I won't buy it!
I'll never buy it!
Ok, get up
I don't want to get up, I don't want to get up
Don't want to buy, don't want to get up!
A calm response to his father's strange actions
Rintaro acts like an adult
I hate it, I hate it, Rintaro, I hate it, I hate it!
You'll think Dad has become strange, right?
Forget it
He gives up so easily
Okay?
-Yeah
Forget it
-Thank you
You're great
Don't you want it?
-I want it
Is it okay if we don't buy it?
-Fine by me
You are really cute
Such a good boy, really
For the very good boy Rintaro
The program team gave him the Nintendo LABO as a gift after revealing the project
I see
Children are afraid of such an outcome
Standing there the whole time, suddenly
He had that "forget it" expression
Literally that "enough" face
It was literally like that
A dead face
To buy that thing in the end
It's really not in line with this show, I hate it
Isn't it nice?
Not needed
Absolutely not needed, its annoying
We must do away with hope, do away with it!
It won't be edited out, even if you say so
Don't throw a tantrum at the producer!
Even a tantrum won't lead to editing it out!
That part will be used!
The next theory chosen by Morita is
Its impossible to avoid drawing wrinkles on portraits of Matsuo Bannai
Speaking of Matsuo Bannai
The deep, deep lines are his characteristic
Is it possible for this feature to be overlooked?
First, we investigate a portrait store
It's painted
Sure enough, he drew very obvious lines
Very similar
What is the key point?
The wrinkles
There is an impression of wrinkles
Then, in other portrait stores, too
A lot of wrinkles
Okay, this is it
Of course, portraits emphasize the lines
So, the investigation hits the street
Where are the key points?
Lines
A simpler depiction of the mouth, ears, and wrinkles
However, it is quite similar
Indeed
And after that too
The wrinkles
Wrinkles
Ah, that, that, wrinkles, wrinkles
Indeed, whenever drawing Matsuo, wrinkles will be included
Lines here
Wrinkles?
-Wrinkles
Among them, a man with an artist's style
Seems talented at drawing
No wrinkles
And many parts aren't drawn
Pretty creepy
This isn't a good example
Many other people's drawings had more lines than yours
That... mine...
I don't want to focus on other people's weaknesses
Wouldn't that be in bad taste?
Weird guy
The next theory selected by Morita is
A good quote
Don't judge someone by their weaknesses
The example sentences for "kill" in the kanji exercise book used by elementary school students are all "kill/hold your breath"
Because it's a bad word
Indeed
"Hold your breath"
There you go
"Hold your breath like that"
"Hold your breath without moving"
Next, in the poop practice series
Why this?
"Hold your breath at night and poop"
What? That's...
Next, this kanji character exercise
"Kill the bugs"
Also
Bit scary
"Kill pests"
So the results of the survey are
There are 10 books that used it in terms of breath and 6 for killing bugs
The next theory selected by Morita is
People with the name "Hotei" (a folkloric deity monk called Cloth Sack) all have related nicknames
The investigation begins
Hello?
I'm sorry, is this the home of Hotei?
Yes, I'm Hotei
We explained this was for a TV interview and got permission
Although rather sudden
Have you ever had a nickname?
Nickname?
Yes
Can you tell me what your nickname is?
Potato
Potato？
Yes Potato
The next theory selected by Morita is
Ask why!
A "strong" word for people in their 20s is "Zero" and "Kobayashi" for people over 60 years old
So, first of all, we surveyed people in their 20s
What comes to mind when you think of "strong"?
Strong Zero
-Wine
What comes to mind when you think of "strong"?
Strong Zero
-Zero
What comes to mind when you think of "strong"?
Zero
-Certainly Strong Zero
What comes to mind when you think of "strong"?
Strong
Strong Zero
-Strong Zero
It's good value for money, high alcohol content
The penetration rate for the 20-something age group is quite impressive
93% of the 68 people responded as expected
In other words, 63 people replied "Zero"
Zero answers for Kobayashi
You don't have to use zero here
Do you know Strong Kobayashi?
No, who is that?
Then the next survey of people over 60 years old
Strong
-Eh?
The word "strong"...
Strong
-Strong?
Is there anything you can think of from this word?
Strong Kobayashi, right?
Strong？
Ah, I don't know, I can't think of anything
Strong
-Eh?
What's that?
Although there were people that answered Kobayashi
A large section of this group does not respond to foreign words like "strong"
"Strong ",  do you know what that means?
-No
Do you know the meaning of Strong?
-No.
Have you heard of "Strong Kobayashi"?
-Yeah
He knows!
The next theory selected by Morita is
If you sneak some change into the hood of someone's hoodie, they won't know it's there until it's 10,000 yen or so
10,000 coins must be pretty heavy
This verification actually took place at the same time during last week's episode
It was carried out in secret
It was done?
The target was...
The last to come in, Panther's Ogata
Who quickly took off his hoodie
It's cold. Absolutely
It's not cold at all...
-I think it's better not to take it off
First, the main project to make him laugh was focused on
Stop!
Stop it!
What?
Then, after achieving success
Is it hot?
Fujimoto forces him to put on a hooded sweater
And the coin verification begins
So handsome
-So handsome!
Put a lot in!
What is this?
Due to having drunk a lot
The setters boldly put coins in
Beer. One more
Beer, please, a lot more
Despite touching his hood, Ogata fails to notice
I'm drunk! I'm drunk!
So, we will reveal the main plan first
When drinking something, like, "poof"
Oh
It was unexpectedly difficult to confirm
Spat it out!
-Eh?
Did that
Did you all do it together?
-We all did it together
So many
What a mess!
Such a mess
What is this?
I'm a little confused
Horita, what do you think?
I think drunken Hollywood Zakoshi is super cute
Such a smiley face
He's not very good at drinking
And that Hotei, why is he called "Potato"?
I still really want to know why "Potato"
It seems a further investigation is needed
An unexpectedly interesting answer
He seemed to think its more normal than it is
It wasn't "What's your nickname? I was called potato"
But "I'm Potato"
So? Why?
Even if they say it in such a way, you should still ask why
If they answer this plainly I guess you'd be afraid to ask why
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03