Timers: Phantom, IngloriousBee, Riddell Translators: Babystand, Zebestt, TheYuriken
m 0 0  l 1800 0  1800 140  0 140
WDT Project
Let's get started with another Wednesday Downtown. Welcome everyone.
Yes, thank you
Shall we begin?
Everyone please welcome our first presenter
Yasuko Mitsuura from Oasis
You're usually over there
Yes, this is my first time on this side
Good evening, thank you for having me
Today it's just, really?
Do I have to dig into this?
It's bound to bring out the worst in women.
Really?
Really. It really is.
You're really pushing it, huh?
The theory I've brought is this-
Theory: If a profile picture has two girls
it belongs to the cute one
That's harsh...
It's heartless~
I think that might be possible
I think it is
Talents can be really bad
Yes, talents and models-
don't seem to be as bad about it
But just look at what they put in their blog posts.
They ask me for a picture to post saying "I worked with Mitsuura-san!"
So they take it-
Then they upload it.
When I go to check it, I'm shocked!
They look absolutely stunning while I stand there with my eyes half-shut
What is with that?
It was like she was thinking "Well as long as I look good".
It's scary, truly.
How about you two?
I think a lot of my friends are similar.
They ask for a picture but-
They only look at themselves
Right?
I think it's best that if you ask for a photo,
you should let them take it for you
I think this is something only moderately cute girls do
Real cute girls have real cute friends
That fastball came out of nowhere-
right into my face
KERPOW, right?
I'm speechless
That's quite an opinion
She just went over your theory with her own
Coming up-
Does the profile picture belong to the cuter girl?
After that-
Can you bunt a home run?
We put it to the test...
...using 300 km/h balls from a pitching machine
Then, can you play telephone game with various genres?
The theory that you are not considered a professional unless you have a perfect knowledge about your signature act
We're investigating the theory that if a profile picture has two girls-
it belongs to the cute one
I wonder if this will end up being true?
First, we searched for girls that have a profile picture with their friend in it
Then we asked nearby boys which is cuter
Finally we'll find out which one is the real owner
Will it be the cute one?
This was the first photo we found
A profile picture with friends, ages 25 and 22
Could you please tell us which of the girls in this photo is cuter?
The left
The one on the left is cutest
Left
The left one?
Yeah
With 3 votes to 0, the streets have chosen the girl on the left
So which one does the profile picture belong to?
Thank you for helping
They got her to come out
What will it be?
Ah, of course it is
It was the cute one
She's cuter in the picture
Why did you use a pair photo here?
You shouldn't say that
To show off my looks
What exactly do you mean by that?
It's her best angle right?
First of all, it's a pretty good photo
But it didn't look very glamorous with me alone
And photo alone doesn't look as cheerful so
"I'm in it with a friend"
"I look pretty"
Those 2 things are-
what I consider
when I decide
By the way, which of you is more popular?
Well, she's younger so she gets more attention
Really?
That's embarrassing
I'm pathetic
She insists she didn't use her friend as a fashion accessory
Around how many guys have asked you out, total?
I haven't been counting, really
Do you have a rough estimate?
It doesn't have to be exact.
Probably around 40 or 50
Isn't that a lot?
Moving on
This pair photo
I think the one on the right is cuter
I also prefer the girl on the right
I also think the girl in center frame is cute
The judgment on the streets is "right"
This is just bad
Sure enough
They're correct after all
This one was also the cuter girl
With this there's a sense that
"Oh, they're such good friends!"
So, good friends
But a selfie kind of screams-
"I'm obsessed with myself"
Next
These two
I'll go with the left one
I also think the left is cuter
I also say left
The decision is the girl on the left,
but usually the profile picture should belong-
to the person in the middle
It could be
Excuse me
Of course
It's the girl on the left
That's freaky~
Although the rate of cute girls using pictures is high,
most of the pair photos we found didn't have much difference in cuteness
Do you think many women-
use pair photos with someone much less attractive?
It somehow exudes the sense that she is obviously cuter
Then, there's-
This pair photo
Could you please pick the cuter girl?
Oh okay
The right one, yo
The one in white, right?
Yeah, that's right
The right
The one in white?
Yes.
The left one
Left?
Without the purikura effect,
I think the girl on the right is going to look worse
This is the first time the decision has split 2-1
So which one is the owner?
Ah, there she is. She's coming.
Hello
Excuse me, we're from Wednesday Downtown
And so-
We're not sure which girl this is
Which one?
In the purikura machine...
...I pick the cutest one...
from those that we took
Somehow, the purikura created this totally distorted picture of the girl on the right
At this point
It seems less about cuteness
And more about the effects used
Our next photo is this
I think the left is cuter
The left one
By some stroke of fate we ran into this man
Excuse me, excuse me
Haven't you been on TV before?
Have you been on TV?
Yes, I have
Wednesday Downtown
Yes
We're shooting Wednesday Downtown now
Oh really?
That's right, this man is-
Back from spring
the one we met when we were looking for fish-faces
The hippo-face man
What do you do for a living?
Construction worker
Construction?
Yes
You know, I was scouted by a comedy agent
Right now I'm, uh, uh,
I'm doing extra work in comedy productions
Thank you for helping with that theory
Oh yeah, no trouble
What are you doing today?
Well, I have the day off
I go back to work tomorrow night
Sitting in my room all day would be boring
So you're going to Shibuya?
Yeah, that's right
I spend a lot of time in Shibuya when I have a break
Have there been any consequences?
People greet me a lot
If I go to Ikebukoro-
People will even come up-
and ask to take a photo with me
Oh, hello
We ask him, one of our many friends, who is cuter
The left one, yeah?
However, this photo belongs to the girl on the right
And this is what the girl on the left looks like
The purikura effect completely changed them both
And our final photo
The right one
The blond? Interesting
Left
The decision of the street is...
Oh really?
...the woman on the left 2vs1 however...
Sorry, hello
Please come over here
The result is...
Based on the colour of the hair...
...it seems that she is the one on the right
I get why she took it from a high angle
Why did you use a pair shot for your icon?
When you take selfies, I end up touching it up...
...using filters and such
But I get the "You look nothing like that" response a lot
"You look nothing like that"
Stop it!
When I'm alone...
...I get told "That's fraud!" a lot as well
"That's fraud"
With that, the cute one is the user of the photo but...
...profile pictures and reality don't match up
It's amazing, you can't just trust the photos...
...that's the only thing we get from this
It's incredible...
...it makes that much of a difference
Wouldn't it be good to be like "No purikura!"?
In the end, if you just use purikura, from a male perspective...
...they all look cute but if you open the lid...
Wouldn't she end up alone if she continues like this?
Wouldn't it be hard for her to find someone?
I think that's saying too much
Since we had good girls that accepted to do the interview right?
Yes yes, they were open about it so...
But didn't you just think "that's a completely different person"
But, I really thought that her heart was beautiful
No way!?
He said so many thing while watching the video though
Right?
The ones that accepted to go on tv were all lovely people, personality wise
Right the ones that did yes
It's like, uhm...
...we're in an age where small jokes like that wouldn't make them super angry
Next we have the corner where we present and investigate theories from around the world
Viewers' Theory Corner
Tonight's presenter is
It's Tamura Kenji!
Thanks for having me!
The hell is that?
Your hair is crazy
You noticed?
No I mean it's weird...
Did you get a perm or something?
I got a perm...
...and I ended up leaving it...
...and it was pretty funny
We were like "We did it!" with the make-up artist...
"We got a good one"
...and I came in like this
But it wasn't that funny afterall was it?
No it wasn't
It wasn't?
Let's move on. Here is the first theory!
Theory: You can play the Telephone Game with puppets
What do you mean?
You might think to yourself "Hmm?"
The Telephone Game is where you say something to the next person's ear and it goes around...
...however, not using any speech...
...we got professionals of expression together...
...and we made them play the Telephone Game. That's the theory
You mean like drawings and stuff?
Yes exactly
Shall we have a look?
We've got the puppeteer
And a portrait artist
Latte Artist
I think that it'll definitely stop at the latte artist
Can they even make anything more than a panda?
And there's the condescension!
That's not ok
That's no good
That'll piss people off for sure
"Nothing more than a panda?"
We're experienced in that
We are!
How did you experience it?
The cymbal theory, cymbal
People were really pissed off at me for making fun of the cymbal guy
Right?
Yeah!
We're investigating the theory that you can play the Telephone Game with puppets
With that, this time...
we will have these six pros from different genres, including the puppeteer
communicate an idea using just their proficiencies
If the theme that was given by Announcer Kuniyama
manages to go through to Announcer Yoshida at the end
we will have proven the theory.
Oh the first one is drawing as expected
The theme is this
Antonio Inoki hitting a homerun
This is impossible!
Are you ready?
Yes
With that, please get started on your craft
At first, we start with the portrait artist
How long does it usually take for you to draw one picture?
Usually, if it's just the face, I draw in a bout 10 minutes
About 10 minutes
Are you confident in yourself?
Uuhmm, yeah...
...I want them to at least understand the person, since it's a portrait
Fifteen minutes since the start,
The end result is here
This is really important
Yes, something like this...
Where are the important points exactly?
The points are
you'd have to understand that it's "this person"
So the red scarf
and that you can see his satisfaction with the homerun
I see
Yeah you can see the point being given too
I kind of tried to squeeze it all in
And when she shows it to the pantomime...
Wouldn't it be okay with a pantomime?
Alright!
Did you understand what it was?
I did
Uhm, Mr. Inoki is...
...in a game of baseball...
...hitting a homerun
With that, the Telephone Pantomime begins
It's not that funny
Wouldn't he get it?
She brings up the characteristic chin with her hand movements...
...1, 2, 3...
...Da! movement...
...to relay that it's Inoki
And then...
She's pretty good
She brings the pose again huh?
Are you alright?
Yes
Next is latte art
This is where we might have problems
What are you exactly doing?
I'm first building the silhouette...
...with that the contour?
Right, this is chocolate sauce, to draw on the details
15 minutes passed working on their craft
I'm done
This is...
What did you draw?
This is the scene of Antonio Inoki hitting a homerun
Why did you divide it to two cups?
If you draw things too small...
Oh my god, I'm sorry...
...the portrait would end up unrecognizable, since the canvas is so small
...so I thought about increasing the canvases
Since the chin is very characteristic...
...and also his red towel. I wanted to show that it's Antonio Inoki...
...to make them understand
And drawing the ball flying away...
...on my second cup
I'm hoping that this is understandable by the next person
I see
The puppeteer, seeing this work of art...
Antonio Inoki is...
...playing baseball
That's your answer correct?
Yes
That is what you understood
Yes, it is
The homerun aspect of the question was lost at this point
This could comeback somehow
Please start explaining the theme to the next person
Here also, we get the hand movements to show the chin...
...trying to do the "Da!" but...
Da!
She forgot the "3"
Also...
Is it a bit tough?
It's like a bunt
Okay
What did the fifth person get from the puppet's movements
Please show it
It ended up like this
A batter looking to hit
a very fast ball
With the puppet, we completely lost Inoki
But by some miracle, the homerun idea came back
Let's make another miracle and get Inoki back!
The balloon artist seeing this
Would he've been able to make Inoki with balloons anyway?
Do you have a clear image in your head?
I'll be thinking about it while making it
After 20 minutes of hard work
Yes, I'm done
What are you trying to convey?
A batter trying to hit a fastball
This is amazing though...
Basically I wanted to depict the motion of a fast thrown ball
by creating this spiral thing.
The face looks a bit like Downtown's Matsumoto.
It's true they look alike...
Yes, this is just something I did for fun...
For the sake of fun,
the Matsumoto element appeared into the sequence.
Yeah but...
He thought too much about the show.
As a result...
He really did.
Nice to meet you!
Balloons right?
Yoshida should get it at once....
However...
Yes, I got it.
The ring shoes and the pants are definitely saying Inoki!
Announcer Yoshida, please tell us your answer!
Is it so?
Yeah
A blond
baseball player
hits
a flying ball
with a bat.
Unfortunately, this is wrong!
And with that, the elements "Inoki" and "homerun" disappear,
It would end up like this...
the element of Matsumoto also wasn't mentioned.
This is embarrassing isn't it.
And so, a second try after some changes...
It definitely can be done
This time they discussed an approach that should result in success.
They should change the order
Yeah right?
The marionette is the point here...
And the outcome...
The first half consists of the illustrating artists,
Is that so...
and the more difficult genres are put towards the end.
And so the second phrase is...
Tricky!
A gorilla that failed the exams.
The second phrase is...
That's tricky!
A gorilla that failed the exams.
The phrase...
First, what the portrait artist created...
They don't even take exams
Cute...
This is the large gorilla realizing...
the exam part is shown through the sakura
but since it's a fail the sakura petals have fallen.
This is difficult!
But this wouldn't be enough to understand,
so I show that his exam number is missing from the pass list.
I see...
The latte artist who sees this...
A gorilla that failed the exams.
100 points!
This one's good!
Yeah he is great!
And so, this illustration is recreated with latte art.
This is amazing!!
The latte artist is definitely underrated...
And the collage artist that saw this...
Yeah we were making fun of him
Playing sevens (card game)...
monkey!
A missed interpretation.
Why??
Why sevens??
And by creating that collage...
What is he doing?
He missed clues like the sakura petals...
Next, the balloon artist...
The sakura...
It's a monkey playing card games
He got this correct, however
So it turned into a monkey...
But he made it very well
It's great, though
Yeah, indeed
The pantomime who saw this...
A gorilla that plays sevens
The point where he finds seven!
Somehow, "gorilla" comes back into the sequence...
The gorilla part is correct.
A gorilla playing cards.
Gorilla was correct.
But this as gorilla...
Equally far from both a gorilla and playing cards...
the japanese style marionette is struggling fruitlessly.
How will that work?
A gorilla....
This is on point!
sits down after an act of intimidation...
and eats...
a banana.
What the hell is this!
Unfortunately, it's a miss!
It's the paper guy's fault
And so the conclusion is, the telephone game is difficult.
Well yeah...
It was pretty close right?
It was...
But the latte artist was great right?
He was!
He was amazing right...
...Kawakita-san?
I sincerely apologise.
Aren't ya going to Harajuku?
It was really amazing!
It really was,
and even more it being in colour.
Yeah, exactly.
However, I didn't hear anything about using two cups...
Are you upset because there was no reaction to that guy making your face?
It's not that...
So let's move on to the next theory! The theory is as follows:
The theory that one should have a perfect knowledge of their signature act or are not considered a professional.
What could that mean...
Well there might be several acts that someone possesses, however, if money is made out of one signature act,
then you really need to have perfect knowledge of that specific act,
otherwise it is not good.
In other words,
for example Degawa-san the comedian
has an act called "the nose crayfish".
If that's the case then do you know the shishimai (lion dance) perfectly?
Well that is obvious Hamada-san!
Bringing it up regularly...
It is so obvious...
I really feel obliged towards it
Since when does this tradition exist?
Right, right
Is that a japanese thing to begin with?
Yeah, who started doing it...
Is it from Chinatown?
Who started doing it first?
If you say it at once like that then I can't answer!
I do have the answer but if I am told suddenly like that...
WHY??
I panicked. I really panic.
Then I will answer only one question.
Your signature act...
Only one?
The question from Harry-kun
To begin with, please tell us if it's a japanese thing.
I've heard...
that it has been brought from China.
It exists in China too, right?
So how long ago did it come to Japan?
You mean how many years ago?
Well yeah historically.
Do you gain anything from knowing that?
Well it's about this theory now...
Read the title!
It's there!
You are not considered a professional unless you have a perfect knowledge about your signature act.
So this time
we have invited comedians who
rely on either props or phrases as their signature act.
To prevent complications, we invited them over for a fake project.
We then ask them ten questions regarding their signature acts.
If all questions are answered correctly the theory is confirmed.
Oh I see...
The first contestant is..
Nice to meet you!
Nagano-san!
Nice to be h...
Comedian Nagano.
What was his thing?
When you think about this man...
Right, it was Rassen...
I simply....
LIKE RASSEN!!!
A repeated calling of Rassen (a painter) during his act.
Does he have an understanding about Rassen?
He's says it alot too
Nagano-san...
you like Rassen right?
I like him!
Isn't that so?
I LOVE HIM!
I LIKE RASSEN!!!!!!!
...and with this
Rassen quiz!!!!
This will be entertaining!
Huh?
Let's see the first question
Well he was caught by surprise so...
Please take a look at this
Which of these paintings is made by Rassen?
It's difficult!
Please answer with A, B or C.
Only one is rassen
Ah, I got this one!
Yes, Nagano-san?
That's it right?
Simply because
I have seen this painting
That's correct!
Do you own any of Rassen's paintings?
I bought some, yeah
I was made to buy.. I bou... yes I have bought
I have bought, yes
During a show he purchased a 620.000 yen painting
He got the correct answer!
And with this...
continuing the Rassen quiz, here is the next question:
Who is Rassen?
Eee, is he gonna know this?
He knows this doesn't he?
Somehow....
it's very easy for me
Last year I actually met Rassen
Are you ready?
Naganosan? B!
He actually knows this
Why did you choose B?
I said I met him!
Correct!
See!?
Congratulations!
In this case, he met with Rassen during work, so he got the answer.
Well he said he met him
Here is the next question:
What thing related to Rassen does NOT exist?
A: An amusement park attraction, Ocean Rassen The Ride
B: A pachinko place, CR Rassen World.
C: A game software, Rassen Art Collection.
What is that?
It's starting to get a bit difficult...
Eh, two exist? Yes.
The two really exist.
Ah so the two exist.
So two are real..
Naganosan?
So the amusement park attraction doesn't exist.
No I don't think it does.
It does sound real though.
You are correct!
Yeeesss!!!!
The pachinko place "CR Rassen World" opened in 2006.
And who played there...
I don't know that...
The first game software of the Rassen Art collection is the digital jigsaw puzzle.
Who knows that!
I see...
Somehow this man...
"I LIKE RASSEN!!!"
whether that's true or not...
he is naturally very strong in the Rassen quiz.
Amazing !
Let's roll to the next question.
Where was Rassen born?
A: Hawaii
...It is right?
B: California
C: Australia
Nagano-san
Hawaii!
I think for Rassen...
the majority of the paintings
are inspired by sea.
Nagano-san
Unfortunately, it's the wrong answer.
The correct answer is B: California
Unfortunately it was a miss and therefore you will receive a punishment.
HEY NAGANOOOO!!!!
You son of a bitch, you like Rassen right?
That hurt!
Isn't that so?
You like Rassen?
Typical Aja Kong...
WHAT IS THIS??
What the hell is this you're supposed to like Rassen!
I'm seriously scared!
Say it properly that you like Rassen!
I LIKE RASSEN!!!!!!
What is this?
Unfortunately Nagano failed on the fourth question.
And the next  challenger is...
But I think he really tried.
Nice to meet you!!
Gorgeous!
Suddenly his face changed...
Mada tasukaru, ma tasukaru, ma tasukaru (We'll be saved, we'll be saved)!!
Madagasukaru (Madagascar)!!
The one who everyday points at that island...
Madagascar, but how much does he really know about it?
You really picked a good one here
Gorgeous you are always mentioning
a country-island on the African coast
That's how it came!
MADAGASCAR!!
And with that...
I know about it naturally- Madagascar quiz!!
Do you have a good knowledge of Madagascar?
Well yes I make sure to point at it correctly everytime.
Well at least he knows where it is located.
So the first question is:
Which of these is Madagascar?
He should be able to answer this.
I think I can answer this.
He points at it so he should know.
Gorgeous-san?
I even looked and pointed at it earlier.
Unfortunately it is incorrect!
You're joking! You're joking
A is...
It's B...
Taiwan
That's a joke!
Please check with your own eyes the shape of it
Gorgeous are you serious...
This was not good.
THIIIIIIIS...
Here is Madagascar! Oh you're right...
Even the first one was difficult...
OI GORGEOUS!
Their make up matches
WHAT'S THIS!?
MADAGASCAR!
Why the hell don't you know. Find it on the first try your idiot!
GET IT RIGHT!
Her voice is loud...
You look at it a lot don't ya?
yes...
Apologise to Madagascar!
Sorry...Saipan! THIIIIIIS....
Let him do his thing
And the third challenger is...
This is bad!
Mao's collar quiz with Hattori Yukio (historian).
...but not this time...
HEYYYYYYY!!
Huh?
Where is Hattori sensei?
Aja Kong please take a seat.
Aa, that's what it means!
She got lured...
So that's how it is?...
AJA KONG!!!!
When you think of Aja you think of a tin drum
When you think of a tin drum you think of Aja
I naturally know about it- the ittokan(Tin drum) quiz!
There's no way she knows anything about it
How long have you wrestled with the ittokan?
Around 25-26 years.
All this time together.
To you the ittokan is a very valuable signature item right?
It's kinda like me and the shishimai...
Yeah of course it's something more than a signature item.
It's my best partner.
Her feelings for the ittokan are like me and the shishimai...
Let's move on
What is the official name of the ittokan?
A: 16-litre drum
B: 18-litre drum, C:20-litre drum
So that's what it means
Kong-san please.
B
18-litre drum.
Because itto (volume unit)...
is 18 litres right?
That is correct!
See?
I at least know the meaning of itto!!
Here is the next question:
Among the uses of the ittokan, which is the most common?
A: paint
B: food oil
This must be it!
C: soy sauce
I thought it was soy...
Isn't it B?
But there are so many uses...
Is it okay to put soy sauce in it?
Well to me soy sauce is the most useful.
Interesting...
If it's oil it will be sticky inside.
It wasn't oil..
and for the juniors it will be difficult to remove.
She's really thinking about this.
Kongsan?
This is probably A: paint.
In the old days it might have been soy sauce,
but lately it's not very common, before I would go to soba restaurants to get soy drums,, however
lately soba restaurants are not using soy drums.
So the supply is very limited.
Unfortunately...
The correct answer is B: food oil
Oil huh...
But oil is not going away even if you wash it!
You can't use the oil ones
It's not a question whether it's easy to clean..
You have no clue about the ittokan do you?!
Who do ya think you're talking to?!
I don't want to be lectured about the drum by someone who has never used it!!
And so, even though she has no perfect knowledge of the drum,
Aja's feelings towards it were certainly communicated.
Everyone failed didn't they?
Well Nagano got three questions right.
However we could also have answered the first and second questions...
Lately, you've consistently been bad man..
It's true, if you think about it.
Since you came out it's like...
You don't even confirm your theories and still go "thanks for the hard work"...
Huh, am I being scolded right now?
Will you keep appearing?
How about you take the night bus?
Huh, after 24 years in the industry, will I start taking the night bus?
Do you take the green car (first class train wagon)?
Well I have had the opportunity to be in a green car...
Well this appearance is not worth the green car...
You can take "kodama" (plain wagon)
Still better than the bus!
Much better than bus anyway.
I am Tamura Kenji, the person doing that is Moriwaki Kenji(comedian).
There you go trash talking about others too...
NO NO It's true! Moriwaki Kenji
gets on the green car but pays the ticket back and gets on the kodama!
I really am telling the truth!
Here comes the next presenter, welcome!!
It's Tanaka from the Ungirls!
Pleased to meet you!!
Well...this time I thought I will present a theory...
The theory this time...
...seriously what is it?
Why are you looking at me all the time!?
I thought of you as a mate!
As a mate right?
He is one right?
Feels like you guys are plants that live in the same tank!
I am doing this for a long time so cut me some slack!
Actually, you sort of feel like the same food as well...
About the theory, in old times
there was a game called "Moero! professional baseball", do you remember?
Nintendo?
You remember it?
When you talk about this game, what comes up is
that the foreign players' strength settings are so high
that even if they bunt, it ends up being a homerun.
If you hit the ball nicely...
Yes, that's correct.
So this time I brought this:
The theory that if you bunt a ball with a speed of 300 km/h you will still get a home run!
What do you think about this?
Shouldn't be possible!
Not possible!
It won't be able to increase height.
It will just go straight and will not reach the seats...
It will not achieve an arched course...
But this is OK, because
you think that if you don't swing upwards you won't get a homerun
but truth is if you hit it horizontally,
if the hit is good it will go flying.
I see.
Because if it's just..
If you hit right above the center the angle can be certainly confirmed.
What a creepy way of explaining!
This is unfair!!
It's OK we understood you.
If you say so then it becomes so!
If a ball comes from a pitching machine at 300 km/h, then a homerun will be achieved even with a bunt.
The legendary 1980's Nintendo game
I don't quite know about this...
I wasn't even born then.
"Moero! professional baseball"
You're not born yet
the bunt homerun.
This was a bunt just now!
It went over 130 metres!
This was a success just now.
The games in the 80's man...
And so, making this bunt homerun a reality
is this machine with a pitching speed of 300 km/h.
That's scary!!
I get goosebumps
Previously, the challenge taken by ex-professional baseball player Yamasaki Takeshi...
Right right, he appeared before.
Last time was not successful but...
This is very scary!
You can't even see the ball...
That's how you'd end up
There's nothing but laugh.
I didn't see it. It went BAM!
and with all the smoke...
As seen,
If this is the pitching speed,
Isn't it amazing, scary!
there is no chance of a bunt home run.
This is a nice theory
In order to back this experiment scientifically,
we asked the science fiction investigator Yanagita Rikao.
That's an amazing name.
Fiction...
The question is whether it's possible to achieve a bunt homerun.
Given that the bat is securely fixed,
the ball could fly 122 metres according to the calculation.
When the bat is fixed, then the balls speed after impact
equals the ball's initial speed times the ball's elasticity coefficient.
In this case the ball's resistance is approximately 0.42.
So 300 times 0.42 equals 126 km as the ball's speed after impact.
If the ball has a speed of 126 km, then it
can result in a 122 metre homerun.
And on the day of the experiment,
Just like Rikao sensei suggested,
A metal base was fixated on the batter's box.
I hope this works.
And this time, prepared exclusively for the show,
is this 300km/h pitching machine.
Rikao sensei is also on the scene.
And with that, the preparations are completed.
Will it be possible to achieve a bunt homerun
with this 300km /h pitching machine?
Why that face!?
It's a good face.
Will it be possible to achieve a bunt homerun
with this 300km /h pitching machine?
First of, a wooden bat was fixed.
And a memorable first try!
Ready!
What came off? Ah, the arm...
It came off on the first try...
Something seems to have gotten in...
Not even close...
That's a dead ball right?
The ball was pitched
That was it!
Going straight towards Hamada's armpit, it just ripped the arm off.
At the sight of this, the expectations of a homerun are rising.
The ball's speed during this pitch was 304 km/h.
After adjusting the ball's course, the experiment continues.
Ready!
On the second try?
Gaining a great height, the ball passes the net.
If this is the case...
Maybe it is possible after all.
We need another 5 millimetres.
5 millimetres yeah?
However, the next pitch...
Ready!
It broke!
It came off..
It's like the wig came off...
It broke off!
It did...
Not tolerating the ball's massive speed,
the bat just broke.
It's an uncommon way of breaking.
That's right.
Normally it grazes through
and cuts the wood.
But this just snapped off.
It got ripped instead.
The bat may have snapped, but the bunt was successful.
And so this time a metal bat was prepared.
and the experiment resumed.
With an unbreakable metal bat, a bunt homerun should be possible.
Ready!
It hit a good spot
Where is the ball?
It reached second base...
In case Rikao sensei miss calculated...
we examined the pitch using slow motion.
It bent so much!
It does yeah.
The bat just warps like rubber under the ball's high speed,
and it just absorbed its force.
With the unexpected turn of events, Rikao sensei checks his calculations...
Quit him already...
He looks very cool.
In order to make the impossible possible,
his answer is...
The answer is!
If we use tennis balls
Use tennis balls!
It started getting weird this theory!
Will a bunt homerun be accomplished with tennis balls?
In order to achieve homerun, the answer that Rikao sensei gave is...
Tennis balls.
You considered the tennis ball's heaviness?
Yes that's right.
Compared to a baseball, the tennis ball has a greater elasticity coefficient,
so that will make the ball fly easier.
So you think it's possible?
I think it's possible.
Moreover, to achieve bunt homerun, the pitching machine was moved closer to the batter,
and the tennis balls' proneness to slow down was covered.
According to calculations, this will achieve a pitching distance 3 times higher.
At last, will that result in the bunt homerun we have been dreaming?
The time of the fateful result is here!
Ready!
A pitch that was completely covered on camera
Has science accomplished a bunt homerun?
Ready!
Hmm...
It's not flying at all
A second base...
And to conclude, a bunt homerun is only a game thing.
TANAKA!!
I apologise!
What the hell?
It concluded so suddenly..
What is this?
Emm what is this?
I am very sorry, everything i said before was gibberish...
This V (sounds B in Japanese), didn't even result in a band...
I don't like this...
But you can't help this!!!
That doll was mistreated as well...
I really felt bad for my partner.
Next week
Check out our Facebook and Website for more Wednesday Downtown! This video was subbed by a community run project called the Wednesday Downtown project. Thanks for watching!
m 0 0  l 1800 0  1800 158  0 158
The theory that the funny skits in pretty girls' phone are not funny at all,
The name of this ingredient is that we find in fukujinzuke (pickles),
is not known by anyone.
Also, is you reverse a prank multiple times, you end up losing confidence.
And finally, we investigate the theory of the worst speaker in pro-wrestling, Maeda Akira.