Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Lets get on with our first presenter please.
Anyone there?
It's Viking's Kotouge
Hello everyone, hello everyone
No collar person
The correct term is collarless shirt
I yearn to teach
To put it this way, all humans are collarless
Humans all over the world!
-Get on with it!
He's the one thats wrong but i'm annoying.
A collarless person can talk so much!
-Please continue
Today I bring you an annual project, please take a look.
The 2021 Prank Review
It‘s here
-That's right
It's that time of year again.
Since 2014,
That was the first
-Yes it was
This is the eight time!
This is the show's longest running... ongoing project
Breathe!
Almost there
I missed my chance to breathe
The most frequently performed project in the program
-Really getting old
Can't you speak without having to take a breath?
-I was short of breath
So, this is the annual project to see who was pranked the most last year
And a snow mountain balloon taro competition
2021 Celebrity Ranking
First at joint 10th...
3JI NO HEROINE's Kanade and JOY with 7 times
So many pranks
-Yeah
The next two both appeared 8 times
Jungle Pocket's Kobu and Panther's Ogata
I thought it'd be higher
2018 Prank「Fake Navigation Voice Recording」
Turn right after 1000km
After 1000km
Turn right after 10,000km
2019 Prank「Dish names at a fake yakitori restaurant」
Work it out already!
Excuse me, your electric car
Electric car？
-Excuse me
Delicious
-Thank you
Your Nagabuchi
Nagabuchi?
Top-ranked for 3 consecutive years, Ogata drops to No. 7 in 2021
You'd normally realise, right?
The next three people appeared the same number of times
Who is it?
Sakai, Tsuda and Nadal
Yeah, he has loads
Less than before?
Can you tell me something interesting about when you played soccer?
-OK
2020 Prank「Video recorded in advance for a long-distance meeting」
Funny stories from the soccer team
Pre-recorded video
What is it? Huh?
Just played a video
An interesting story
The King of 2020 has failed to achieve a winning streak
Next is a 10-time tie for 2nd
Yamauchi and Kawai
Unexpected
Bitter citrus fruit…
The first Johnny's finalist since 2014
Johnny's, great!
At the top of the list is...
Who can surpass these two?
Oda with 12 appearences
This time, he is awarded the title of King of 2021
Yeah, so it's Oda this time
The generations go by so quickly
-Yeah
Komiya is no longer on the list
Now, its time to get down to business
-Yeah
Oda was pranked so many time this year
So he must be pretty sensitive to the whole thing by now
So, this week we did seven pranks on Oda
Then we challenged him to tell us what they were
You also did it, right?
-Yeah
I was waiting for the traffic light after work from Nagoya
2015 Prank
When the American car that should have been in my house drove past me
Shipped all the way from Tokyo
The staff drove on the expressway to Nagoya
-Awesome!
It's car theft!
Indeed, indeed
One day in December...
Definitely a tiring week
Exhausting
Oda is notified of the results
You came first in the celebrity prank ranking of 2021
Huh? First?
-First
What the hell?
First place?
-That's right
That was scary
Oda's very scary sometimes
I'm always questioning if things are pranks
Probably because i've been messed with too much
And so the plan is put into action
Everything feels like a prank
Can Oda determine the 7 pranks performed in a whole week of pranks?
I think I can probably tell
I won't miss the small details
I've been here too much
I'm too suspicious
To narrow it down to 7...
There are often Assistant Directors who rush in from the corridor
I have to react "Oh!" even when I've seen it, just do something
They're really everywhere
Arrangements for the extremely sensitive Oda are as follows
Heightened sensitivity
Someone bangs on the wall after shouting occurs at a location shoot
Koga Ken sings the BGM in a Cafe
Realistic
The number of followers round a Z-list celebrity is ridiculous
Wear a police chief's uniform for one day from the moment of leaving the house
He really became a chief?
The entire meeting staff are over 190cm tall
That's tall!
The first appearance of Ado is a fake
Wake up without being woken up
The last one's like Ikyo's question
For one week, a camera remains close to Oda to shoot the 7 pranks
After one week, he is asked to guess which of the things that happened around him were pranks
After one week
Excuse me
What hat are you wearing!?
Good morning
How much confidence do you have?
I have complete confidence
I have a definitive answer in my mind
There are 7 that I am sure of
If it was 6 or 8, then it'd be different
I'm sure it's seven, and you've arranged for seven, right?
-Correct
I have confidence and also feel a little embarrassed
I'm serious
I apologise
I am really serious
Can you work out the last one?
I think i'm good to go
What does he think is the first prank?
If this isn't a prank then its a problem
Being the Chief of Police of Shinjuku Police Station for a day
The night before my manager gave us police uniforms
And told us to wear it to work tomorrow
This is the police chief costume you will wear tomorrow
Put it on before you go out tomorrow
Later you'll be in a taxi prepared by the police station
Put it on in the morning, OK?
Now way! Aren't I on "Love it!"
Wear this before "Love it!"
Then switch to the clothes prepared at "Love it!"
Just wear this uniform for the journey
What do you mean?
Start when leaving the house?
That's right, start when leaving the house
-Why?
So you'll be a police chief for a day
It definitely felt ridiculous
She explained to me that it was because I was going to be a police chief for a day
We had a little argument
Even the police chief changes into their uniform at the station
This is what I said
He talks like my dad
She said: "No, this is the rule for the police chief on their first day"
I genuinely didn't bring my own clothes, the uniform was my clothes for the day
I thought this is definitely wrong
I just couldn't understand it
So weird
Police chief, police chief!
So weird!
This is killing me
Seriously
Too interesting
I saw it on the news
-He was really a police chief for a day
Really?
Did he really work as a police chief for a day?
Seriously
What a mess
I was laughed at by everyone when I entered TBS
If he came in like that you'd definitely laugh
What is this, a drama?
Koga Ken was also wearing a uniform for some reason
It was also Koga Ken's first day as a police chief
So,
Koga Ken too
Good morning
Left the house as a police chief
Actually turned up wearing it
Naturally, Koga Ken knows the setup
What did they tell you?
They just... just gave it to me
When?
Gave it to me yesterday
I thought we'd be taking pictures from the morning
Constantly asking questions to tell if it's a prank
Where, here?
-Yeah
Couldn't we just shoot and change here?
Something was definetely wrong
Very perceptive
When I was on a location shoot,
I was in a room in a big 6-floor apartment
And in the room next door there was "BANG"
Like someone was saying I was being too loud
An impressive one to come up with
It's not easy
It could happen
Get get get get get your spirit up
You're demoralizing me!
-That hurts!
I'm hurt inside, too, asshole, it's your fault!
Scary!
This is pretty real
-Yeah
Next door?
There's someone living there?
Move over there a little
There
Hey, is someone living there?
I didn't say a word from that point on
Yeah, okay
By the way
-Not good, not good
There's a load of subway stations close to here
Not only Musashi Kosugi, but also Moto Sumiyoshi
It's like "King's Brunch"
I thought this is not something you'd usually expect
I'm sure i'd scream if it was me
It's impossible for the staff to not consider something like this
Indeed
There are people living next to where we're shooting
If it wasn't for the prank I wouldn't have gone there on location
So far, Oda has gotten all the questions right
I was working with Misono
I've collaborated with loads of people
We discussed the cooperation plan
At the time, she was surrounded by an unnatural number of people
7-8 people
He realised!
OK, thank you
Can you two wait for a moment, please?
-OK
Poor Misono
It would be weird to see so many
Where did this Misono come from?
I'm very happy we can collaborate
Yes I'm also very touched
You'd definitely be able to tell
Misono's hair was in two colors
Was there one person for each color?
This person in charge of this color and another for the other color?
The makeup was setup in such a way?
Why would it be setup like this?
With an agent on hand
Then I was introduced to Koga Ken
Too awesome
I said we have to cooperate!
You'd definitely laugh
I especially like that one part
I really want to collaborate on it
First on the oil pipe
That song was so good, I was amazed
Thank you
You'd definetly laugh
-Yeah
What is the guy on the end doing?
I couldn't stop myself from laughing
I tried really hard to hold it in, but I just couldn't
There was just way too many people
I also asked my agent "Isn't this weird?"
She said: "Maybe musicians are all like that"
"EXILE are also like that"
There's no way you can use EXILE as a reference for Misono
So that was it
Pretty good
-Not bad
There was a pre-taping meeting for a show
Just like this
There was about 4 staff members
Everyone was gigantic
That's good
-Not bad
So it is possible to get them all right
-Possibly
Probably about 190CM
Thank you
-Thank  you
Let's take a picture to finish
He realized at this moment
I'll take the picture
I'll take it
-OK
OK, let's start with a smile
Over 190cm!
So stressful!
OK, cheese!
I might not realize
OK, all good
Next an angry face
It's still possible
Very good, very good
There's a lot of tall people these days
-Yeah loads
I hope we can make a good show
Definitely
Lets cooperate well together
So far, Oda has gotten 4 right in a row
Impressive
Can he achieve the first perfect score?
First...
A report in a music program
Ado who sang "Urusei"
Would you realize if you hadn't seen her before?
It was Ado's first appearance on that program
I was the only person who'd met her before the show
Although she's a bit out of my league
I react to things,
It's my job to react to things that happen
So I went to the studio to see Ado
The recording studio is over there
I want to see the imposter
Can we go, is it ok to go now?
Let's go
It's there, right?
The set is a behind the scene's look at Ado's first live appearence on the show
She's a teenager, right?
Doing VTR requires me to look around and at the camera
It was an impostor, right?
How'd he know?
Can you look at the camera now?
Eh, really?
It's the first time her face is shown
So here we go!
Oda, please start by shouting "Ado!"
Countdown, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Ado!
What a gentle face...
It took a lot of effort to control myself
Being gentle is easy
Even if i'm shaken inside, I won't show it
That feeling
-Yeah
She's already a housewife, right?
Whoa, suuuuuper gentle-looking
Who decided on this lady?
Not what I expected at all
I said "Not what I expected at all"
But I didn't say "she's more mature than I expected"
This sort of thing shouldn't be said
Ado's age was announced to the public as 19
The fake Ado that Oda was faced with was 47 years old
But she doesn't look 47
Ha?
If the other person couldn't hear me i'm sure I would have said a lot
What a reaction
I would have said "who's the middle-aged woman?"
But even thought it wasn't Ado it'd still be pretty rude
Oda's still got two left to get a perfect score
Impressive
-Impressive, right?
He can probably can get a perfect score
Coffee shop BGM
After work a taxi was arranged for me
The driver was an African dude
I even asked for his name, it was definitely a prank
Is there any more to this?
Rare
The driver was called Masonga and he was from Tanzania
It's really rare to see an African dude driving a taxi
Seriously?
He drove really normally
I asked him his name just to check
How come he took that taxi on that day?
I also asked him "Have you been in Japan long?"
This could also happen
He was a good driver, also knew the best routes to take
And so, Oda gives his first incorrect answer
Now let's see the true face of Masonga
Where would you like to go?
Really rare
The program staff conducted an investigation based on Oda's description
He was very quick to agree to an interview
Hinomaru Transportation
The last prank identified by Oda was...
It does seem like a prank
"Love it!" graduation prank
The new year's live broadcast wasn't discussed with me in advance
Kawashima suddenly made an announcement
"Today, Oda is gradauting from "Love It!" for a role in a morning drama!"
I hadn't heard anything about this before
Today he's graduating from "Love It!"
Huh? I had no idea!
How come?
Really? Really?
-Seriously
Wait a second, is this for real?
It's over, you're starring in "Come Come Everybody"
-Yeah, yeah
Starting next week, right?
-Ah, but-
I don't have the morning drama every day,
And there's also times when you don't appear
So I thought this must be a prank
For weeks now...
Isn't there a connection between these shows?
Ano's appearence
It seemed possible
It went on for several weeks
So, the results are shown above
You got 5 correct
That's impossible, impossible
I don't think its possible I got anything wrong, which ones were wrong?
Seriously? No way!
Which one do you think?
I'm unsure...
Oh, the police chief thing was definitely a prank!
Correct
Right?
-Yeah
Ado was a prank
-Yeah, a prank
Be confident
That was close! That was close!
The "Love It!" graudation was a prank
No
OI!!!!
Tragic! The graduation is real!
No?
Why do I have to suffer a double blow?
The remaining 3 correct answers were then stated
Masonga was real?
God, I knew I should have asked more questions
We then asked him to see if there was anything else suspicious that could have been a prank
The ones I just listed were "high suspicion", I also have a few "moderate suspicion"
Only the road in front of my house is iced over like a ice skating rink
We don't know anything about that
This really can't be done
A man at Kyoto Station wanted me to do a questionnaire
He asked me how old I am, I said i'm 43
Afterwards he said "Thank you"
I wondered if such surveys are still a thing
Why just ask someone's age?
Indeed, indeed
Look's like he doesn't have the right answer
So, we revealed the remaining two pranks
Goodbye Sunday Followed by Monday Take a Break on Tuesday
Who's heard of this before?
Feedback was basically 0
Didn't hear
-Didn't hear it
Does it ring a bell?
-It does
This is Koga Ken's "Goodbye Sunday"
H-h-h-how, w-what?
What happened? What did you do?
Did you have a meeting at a cafe during this period?
-Yeah
The BGM was this song
Tough!
Next is the last one
The last one is scary
You stayed at Osaka Hotel, right?
-Right
Did you sleep well?
Yeah I slept really well
Good morning
Wake up prank without waking up anyone
What are you talking about?
W-w-what's going on?
You'd definitely have this reaction
Ijiri didn't know what kind of emotion to feel
He really went in but didn't wake him up
It's not easy for Ijiri to not wake him up
Came in? Came in? Really?
-Yeah
It must be a lie, right? '
-No, it happened
It's scary to think about
It's a little scary
Why do they look so much alike?
He's wearing his hat!
He's the worst!
He drank it, he drank it!
Drinking an unopened one
Luckily I didn't drink it
Really?
After that he stayed in Oda's room for 10 minutes
10 minutes?
He's so close
He didn't realise?
-Terrifying
Good night
For the first time, Ijiri exited the room without waking up the pranked individual
What the hell?
Ijiri's pranks are all the same
I really want to see it
Awesome
It's too much
-OK OK
He just got two wrong, what do you think Matsumoto?
Ah, I thought he'd be able to get them all correct
But its impressive he realised the banging on the wall
Indeed
-It's very like to happen
What do you think Matsumura?
The two incorrect ones did seem a lot like pranks
I've really never such an African taxi driver
It was a tense week for him
He doubted everything
-Even ice in front of his door
Taking a picture, it's time to take a picture, right?
It was an unfunny experience for everyone
And the fact that the color of his sweatshirt matched the wall behind him was very upsetting
Unpleasant to look at?
-Yes
Let's welcome the next presenter
Okano Yoichi!
Hello everyone
Thanks for having me
Your second time here
Yes, I was called to come in such a short period of time twice
Very impressive
There's a reason for that
Originally Audrey's Kasuga was supposed to come
But he tested positive for COVID-19
I saw on the news
Oh really?
So an immediate search took place for a negative person
That's me
-No, no
Are you a negative person?
I am a negative person
There are still a lot of negative people, right?
No, there wasn't any negative people available for tomorrow
Oh really?
Negative tomorrow
So i'll perform well today also
You can do it
Before we get into, please watch this VTR
OK
Balloonist Taro
Why did he suddenly turn up
Can you do it? That's awesome
Nostalgic
I've seen it
Must admit i've seen it
This staff member
-They're all out
Why do we have to see this again
The hand is stretching out from the inside
Please just watch
Get it, get it!
It'll definitely break
What we've just seen is Balloon Taro
Balloon Taro
Do you know him Matsumoto?
I've seen him a few times
How about you, Niiyama?
I know him, i've seen him on VTRs
Oh really?
-That's right
Today, we bring you a theory related to Balloon Taro, please take a look
Snow Mountain Balloon Taro Competition
What?
Snow mountain?
It's literally what it says in the title
What does a Balloon Taro competition even mean?
Simply put, we will see what happens when you go down a snow mountain dressed as Balloon Taro
In that shape?
Loads of people dressed up as Balloon Taro?
-Correct
To see if you can win against Balloon Taro?
Is Balloon Taro going to participate?
Well, let's see what will happen
I'm not looking forward to it at all
Just look forward to it!
Snow Mountain Balloon Taro Competition!
Loads of people
All 8 of the participants, including Balloon Taro himself, are nude comedians
Here we go, the man himself!
I'd like to ask everyone what it feels like to be inside the ball
Nude apart from a pair of tights
Yeah, a pair of tights
A pair of tights but very warm
The sun's light is shining,
So there's a greenhouse effect, it's warm
Very hot
-Very nice!
This is a race down a snow mountain dressed as Balloon Taro
Rupturing of the balloon is an instant elimination
Ah, so it is
That'd be too bad!
Only the first few finishers can advance to the next stage
There will be three matches to decide the final winner
So, what does Balloon Taro himself think of the competition?
To put it bluntly, its rabbit hopping
So it depends on how far you can hop
It's physical strength
It's really uncomfortable to wait like this
-Yeah, the feet...
I really want this to start already
The first stage is 200m
That's quite a long distance
To start, a 15° slope used by intermediate skiers
That's scary
Look's pretty steep
There are also wavy areas in between
Ah, scary scary scary
This is a tough track
This could be part of the winter olympics
The first 4 to finish will advance to the next stage
And so, the first stage begins
On your mark, get set...
Balloon Taro should be pretty good
The first one ahead is Seshita
Ah, so tough
But Zakoshi comes up with side
Is this OK?
-It's fine, it's allowed
The green balloon wearing a black hat,
Looks like it's gonna break
Looks really easy to break
Zakoshi is sliding down at a very fast pace
Clever
Suprisingly he can use his brain
Ah! But his hat has fallen off
Looks like an apple!
He transformed into an apple!
On the other side, Kasuga and Akira 100%, both in red, are behind
In this way, Zakoshi didn't jump
Looks like Yogibo
Instead, he slid down like a sled and opened up a huge gap between the rest
So fast!
So far!
Seeing this, the others decided to take a similar approach
The same trick
Come on, Ono!
All of the participants are either sliding or rolling down the slope
But Zakoshi has stopped
Oh yeah
Because it's flattened out
Oh really
-Yeah
This is a very unexpected race!
Can't slide the whole way
But at this point,
Ow, ow, ow, ow
It's going to break?
It broke!
This is where Seshita's ballon breaks!
30 seconds after the start of the first stage, Seshita's ballon breaks
Must be cold
-Really cold!
And...
My back hurts!
Ono's balloon has also broken
And Zakoshi is unaffected, retaining a beautiful hold on first place
This is a Zakoshi branded humidifier, right?
Ono's balloon has also broken
From here to the middle of the preliminary round is the wavy area.
Zakoshi is impressive
Super fast
Strength is pretty high
Now in second place, the oldest contest at 53, Balloon Taro!
But he's fighting a tiring battle against the ups and downs
The creator doesn't want to lose
Now, Okano's balloon has shrunk
Has his journey come to an end?
That's bad
He's been overtaken
But he's desperately trying to stop Jun-ichi Davidson
The air's leaking
It's like that is it?
It can leak
Okano's become so small!
So it can leak...
Suddenly from behind, Akira catches up with a forward roll!
The current ranking is shown above
First is Zakoshi
And last is Audrey's Kasuga, the man whose very proud of his strength and physique
Who will be the first to reach the finish line?
Such hard work
But as all of the participants are over 40 years old, have their reached their limit?
The participant stopping at this point is obvious
I didn't expect them to all be so enthusiastic
Here we see Kasuga catching up from the rear
In front, Akira 100%'s balloon suddenly bursts!
Akira 100%'s balloon suddenly bursts
Cover up with the pan, quickly!
Ow, ow, ow, ow
Now 3, 4 and 5 are all stuck in a ditch
And now Balloon Taro has caught up with Zakoshi to steal first place
Their strength has...
Awesome!
This is just the preliminary round!?
-Yeah
But Zakoshi refuses to be defeated and overtakes
Now in last place, Okano is entombed within the balloon and falls
But the air has already...
So difficult without the air
The balloon is completed deflated and resembles Tutankhamen!
As his movement is restricted can he get up?
Will he be able to get up?
What can you do
No, he can't get up!
He can't get up
Can't stand up
And now his balloon bursts and he's the fourth person to be eliminated
Can't believe you got eliminated in the first round!
And now he's fleeing as if being chased by a mountain spirit!
What are you talking about?
What an analogy!
At the other end, Zakoshi, who is temporarily ahead, loses the lead to Balloon Taro
Such a skillful use of the balloon
And keeps the lead as he finally reaches the finish line
Awesome!
It'd be really bad if it exploded here
The end is in sight for Balloon Taro
Definetly exhausted
Ah be careful
With the last ounce of his strength, Balloon Taro is the first to cross the finish line
Hurry!
He has won the first match exquisitely!
Hoping to also finish, Zakoshi is once again sitting down and sliding
He's got the hang of it
It's downhill here, too
A good slide for his final sprint
He's like something that floated downstream in a story
Looks like he's praying for his sins
And he uses his head to finish
And Zakoshi finishes second to advance to the next stage!
That's some hard work!
Seriously hard work
So tiring
Hey, which place?
-2nd!
Ah pretty good
Just behind in 3rd place is Kasuga
Catching up!
Kasuga has been jumping!
Later, Jun-ichi Davidson also reached the end
Before he was clearly last
Even if it breaks it doesn't matter I guess
So, these four participants advance to the second stage
2nd match
I see
Are these four OK?
My legs are so sore I can barely stand
You get super sweaty inside the balloon
The people watching probably can't even tell how tiring it is
To begin with, Zakoshi was ahead but ultimately can in 2nd
I was sliding as soon as the starting gun even went off
I didn't even push off, I just slid
But second is still pretty good
I swooshed!
What the hell?
The first person whose balloon broke was Seshita, right?
-Yes
After being overtaken by Zakoshi I thought i'd slide down too
But I tried to stand up and pulled too tight so it burst
Standing up?
-Yes, it didn't work out
PIN——CH
Next is the second stage
That chat didn't go too well
The 150-m forest road course is almost all uphill
It is more physically demanding than the 1st course
More tiring than the first one?
The first 2 out of 4 players will advance to the final
The stamina of these people is really impressive
So tough
Please take your positions.
What will happen?
Get ready!
The tough 2nd stage now begins
Whoa, awesome!
Oh, like this?
Is it okay to make your opponent fall?
Totally fine
Is it necessary to wear the hat?
Not necessary
Zakoshi drops his hat the same as last time
Here sliding is impossible due to an incline
Danger, danger!
It's going to break!
Suddenly, Kasuga has stopped
Lost his balance?
Even used a drone for this
It's difficult to get up
Kasgua is standing!
The competition is incredibly intense!
This part is really all about stamina
Kasuga shakes off the three from the outside and comes to 1st
20 meters from the starting point, Kasuga escapes in a watery melee
Good, good, good
This'll work
The back three are still huddled together
Looks exhausting
Especiall since its the 2nd stage
But Zakoshi and Balloon Taro both suddenly catch up
And this is only the semi-finals
Yeah
Ah, he's down
Does he want to roll?
-Where'd he go?
Jun-ichi is a bit far off
Thigs have reached their limit, right?
Is Jun-ichi losing his strength?
Definetly sore
Back must hurt too
Zakoshi enters the final 50m
2nd is Kasuga followed by Balloon Taro
Zakoshi's pretty strong
Balloon Taro!
He's dead!
Wait, he's falling!
No way!
Very good
He's dead, right?
Kasuga actually pushed Balloon Taro off the track
Surely this shouldn't be done
Dangerous!
Halted!
The balloon seems to have burst
Those branches are dangerous
Ah, watch out, watch out!
Ah he can't get up
You can do it!
Don't give up!
Trying to grab the tree to get back on the track, he fails
It can't be helped
Kasuga sure is a formidable opponent
Kasuga's evil!
Balloon Taro is eliminated
He's down
And Zakoshi is the first to reach the finish line
Zakoshi has really good stamina
There's only one spot left to advance to the final
Zakoshi's balloon doesn't even leak
Kasuga is almost at the end
Or will Jun-ichi Davidson make a miraculous comeback?
Oh, is there a chance?
At this point,
What's going on?
Jun-ichi suddenly self-destructs, throwing himself off the track
Therefore,
Kasuga successfully reaches the finish line and advances to the final stage
Looked pretty easy
So energetic!
What happened with Jun-ichi?
I can't do it
And so, these are the two participants advancing to the final
What a pity
What a shame
As expected, right?
Snow Mountain Balloon Taro Competition Final!
It's already night
It's night
Swooosh——!
What is this?
It seems to be snowing
Finalists
It's finally the final
The time is 8:00 p.m and the temperature 8 degrees below zero
Freezing
8 degrees below zero
The final stage, in extreme cold, is a 70m course
Isn't the angle a bit too extreme?
Not good, and it's winter
And almost all of it is a 30° slope, which makes for a very dangerous course.
Really impressive
Dangerous!
It's practically a cliff!
It's really impressive, it looks good
You may not really understand just by watching,
But from this angle it just looks like a cliff
What are you laughing at?
Snow Mountain Balloon Taro Competition - who will win become the first champion?
Is underwear necessary for this?
It'd be dangerous to not
How could that be broadcast?
They're at a snow mountain so they are frozen and shrunken
-Very true
Probably can't see it
The Snow Mountain Balloon Taro Competition final is upon us!
On your mark, get set...
-How will it go?
The race begins
Will red or green be the winner?
This is bad, this is bad!
Scary, scary
This would definitely happen
Ah, it burst!
Of course!
It's dangerous for the staff too
This doesn't have to be Kasuga and Zakoshi
Face down
Terrible, terrible
They caught a naked old man
No, it burst!
Even though it burst
-Scary, scary!
Who won?
I can't see anything!
-So scary!
Too fast!
Who won?
The results were unclear to all
I can't see, I can't see Kasuga anymore
The winner is, of course, Zakoshi, who reaches the finish line first
Therefore,
The winner of the competition is Zakoshi!
Swoosh——!
This game was much more exciting than expected
It was really fast!
By the time i'd come back to my senses, it'd already burst
I really only just came back to my senses
And a bit damp
-Yes
A bit of a Koshino Junko vibe
Zakoshi sent the staff flying
If he wasn't caught he'd have flown into the building below
You can't control yourself here?
I tried to brake
Like I was trying to brake in the car
Thankfully it didn't burst at the point
It was very fast
After the start I bounced a few times
Then the ground just disappeared
Bounce bounce bounce then straight down
It was like falling into a trap
After the ground disappeared, my head also dropped
The brakes just...
Slip, slip, slip, slip
To sum up
The first Snow Mountain Balloon Taro Competition led to 0 injuries
Everyone wins
Very good, very good
So what do you think after watching, Matsumoto?
I apologize for not being interested initially
It was extremely enjoyable
I watched with great interest
Of course, when watching the video it's tough to gauge the speed,
In real life it was incredibly fast
-Yes
The fastest thing I've seen this year
At the scene was it funny to see that sense of speed?
I could barely even smile
I didn't know whether to laugh or not
"So dangerous, so dangerous"
Everyone was shocked
In the last stage, was it even necessary for people to be involved?
Indeed, anyone could have done it
Even a wardrobe would be fine
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03!