Suiyoubi No Downtown starts once more, thank you all for being here.
Let's kick things off with our first presenter, this person!
Hello everyone! - It's Jinnai Tomonori!
A question for you all!
3 years ago we did a project at Kuro-chan's place.
The "theory that a person could live under Kuro-chan's bed". Do you remember that? - Yes!
Quite a shocking project. - Indeed.
Back then we weren't exposed for 1.5 days, 39 hours! - Right.
At some point the hiding person had to go to the toilet ...
... where he did his business, but at the fear of getting exposed by the noise he didn't flush.
In the morning Kuro-chan saw his dump and he got exposed because of that.
It's probably scarier to find someone's dump than a person.
He might've thought he forgot to flush himself! -Like he had some kind of memory disorder!
But it didn't look like the shape he normally produces.
"I couldn't have made that", I know what you mean. - You do?!
Well this time our project takes us to Kuro-chan's home once more!
"Hide for money - at Kuro-chan's home"
Indeed! - "Hide for money"?
Kuro-chan actually moved to a new place on this show recently!
It's a lot more spacious than his last place.
What we did is to hide 10 TV personalities in his home while he was away. - 10?!
Wow! - Once Kuro-chan came home, ...
... we observed to see how long it'd take him to find them all.
Did he by chance figure it out after finding 10 people's worth of shit?
Not one of them would flush?!
You're about to witness "Hide for money - at Kuro-chan's home"!
Moreover, there's a segment about kids with a long way to school that's not covered in this fansub!
Hide for money - at Kuro-chan's home.
This time is all about hiding yourself at Kuro-chan's place!
We've gathered 10 TV personalities who seem like they might be good at hiding!
What's Takahashi Minami doing in a lineup like this?
I'm actually quite good friends with Kuro-chan, so that's the reason I'm here!
I'm also here as a friend. - We're both here for that reason!
Including these two, who are Kuro-chan's friends, ...
... everyone's average height is 158cm!
They're all quite short!
10 contestants who've all cleared their PCR tests!
The biggest light weight of all of them is ...
Me, Seiga! I weigh 39kg, ...
... so I want to make the most of that and do my best! Count on me!
He has a face that could beat Inada (Naoki).
Meanwhile, the home owner Kuro-chan ...
Q: Describe your life in a few words.
K: "From now on"
Doing some kind of interview?
He's taking part in a fake interview.
What kind of answer is "from now on"?! - Seriously.
And so the contestants head into Kuro-chan's place that's been equipped with 19 hidden cameras.
What's that supposed to mean? "From now on".
Still messy as always!
- That even his new place would turn out like this.
Everyone, please hide!
By the way, the contestants will earn 10 yen for each second of hiding until they're found!
Kuro-chan will arrive in an hour, so please hide before then!
That's his NEW place?!
- Clean the place! - It's filthy!
The toilet is filthy!
This place is ... - A mess!
He really doesn't change.
I'm thinking of hiding among all this cardboard. It seems like a blind spot.
And so he hides by ripping a hole into the cardboard boxes that have been sitting here since Kuro-chan moved in.
Looks pretty good! - Right?
Pretty good spot.
They say "it's hard to see what's under your nose".
The closest place would be here, right? Since he'll sit there.
If I hide back here ...
... I'll be able to know what he's up to, because I'm so close!
That could work in my favor.
I've got this one in the bag! Money, here I come!
Ah, very good!
One by one, each of them decides on their hiding spot.
It starts when Kuro-chan gets back, so please do your best!
Under the sink, under the bed ... - The apartment isn't so bad.
Quite spacious!
And then ... the home owner returns.
"Hide for money - at Kuro-chan's place" starts!
Clean up, dammit!
- Yes, it's a new place!
As soon as he gets home, he starts digging into the bento he got at his shoot ...
... as well as a convenience store meal. It's double portions for him.
And then ...
"Breakfast & lunch in one! Grated yam soba & onion soup!"
That's not true!
"Living the healthy life-dashiiiiin~!"
He just can't stop lying!
He doesn't mention the yakiniku bento, and falls back into the habit of lying in his tweets.
He also doesn't notice the contestant who's hidden only 2m from where he sits.
He's moving around! - This is bad!
Kuro-chan is fully immersed in his bento.
He doesn't notice!
- How's he so carefree?
But then ...
The curtain moves in an unnatural way.
And then ...
Now he's noticed it!
But you wouldn't expect someone to be there!
Kuro-chan sensed that something was off.
And in that moment ... !
What? Some kind of noise?
A big mistake - he dropped his phone!
What's wrong with you? - Bad move, Wes-P.
- He just dropped his phone?
Those thighs piss me off!
Not one milimeter of thigh gap!
Kuro-chan instinctively takes a step back.
He seems frightened. - Yes, he can't speak!
He's not even asking "Who's there?".
Although he's frightened, he slowly comes closer.
It moved again!
He wanted a blind spot, but it's no use.
Ah, I knew it!! There's someone there!
After 15min 26sec, Wes-P has been secured.
Wes-P, that was no good. - Big blunder on your part.
Eh, who are you?!
Ugh, so soon ... - "So soon", what's that supposed to mean?!
Shit. - Eh, what are you on about?!
Nice to meet you. - Uhm, you too ... ?
Oh man ... - What is this?!
Why's someone in my home I don't even know?! - This sucks.
It ended so soon. - What's that supposed to mean?!
Why were you here anyway?! HEY?! - So frustrating.
W-who was that?!
Some dude I don't know was here!
What kinda prank is this? Huh?
Are you with Wednesday('s Downtown)?!
But hang on, he just left!
Wes-P, unrecognized by Kuro-chan, is headed for ...
... a jail up on the roof of the building.
Eh, what is this? Is it over? Hey!!
Come out for the reveal already! What is this?!
I don't get what's going on! Come and do the reveal!
But our "Hide for money" has only just begun.
There's no way we'd reveal it this early on.
10 minutes pass.
And then ...
Perhaps he thought there were hints behind the curtains?
Kuro-chan investigates all the curtains.
Ah, this is bad!
And then ...
The cardboard!
Eh! There's someone here! Right?! There totally is!!
Right? Who are you?!
Uwah, I knew it! There IS someone! Who are you?!
BICSMALLN's Chiro has been secured.
Hang on, you're that Choro guy, right?
Choro? His name's Chiro!
Kuro-chan isn't very familiar with entertainers.
How many are there?! Are there still more?!
And so at last he sets out on his journey as ... hunter!
If he's going like this, he'll search under the bed next.
And then ...
Ah, there's someone!! I knew it!! Right there!
Who are you?! - Ugh, I figured I'd be fine here.
Once he knew something was up, he was bound to search there.
What are you on about?!
Shit, that was so soon ...
What are you cursing for?!
I really thought I could pull it off.
What's your point, seriously?!
And with this, Kuro-chan follows the contestant.
And what he finds is ...
Eh ... ?
Wh-what are you doing?!
What is this? What are you guys doing here?!
Was this especially set up for Kuro-chan? - Yes, just for him!
While the hunter has left his post ...
I need to stretch myself a little ... !
Is Takamina doing fine?
I'm a bit thirsty.
Maybe I'll help myself to some water. This one still looks sealed, so I guess it's fine.
Is that really ok?
- He'll come back!
The contestants use the time to catch a breather!
But this is the roof of my building!
Are you doing "Run for money"?
You are, right?
Enough already! I figured it out, enough!
What's wrong with you?!
At last Kuro-chan figured out that this is a parody of "Run of money".
He's back! - This is bad!
Oh, who's there?!
What are you doing?
- What's wrong with that guy?
Who are you?! I know you're there! I found you!
Ah, shit.
He was being too reckless!
You're doing "Run for money", right? - Ugh, shit.
How terrifying would it have been if he'd found Seiga first.
At this point, 1 hour has passed since the project began.
Only the 6 people seen here still remain.
But then ...
My manager gave me this earlier, what is it?
He said "Use it at your next job". So he wants me to wear it?
That's right. For his "next job", ...
... in other words, for THIS job, he was given a black suit just like the one hunters wear.
I should wear this, right? Right?
Are there still more?!
Kuro-chan changes his clothes as he keeps voicing complaints about everything.
Now put on these sunglasses ...
Why'd you wear them at home?
There's even a camera attached on the side!
I really look like a hunter!
A unique kind of hunter.
A hunter he may be, albeit more reminiscent of Umibozu from City Hunter.
How many are there? I guess I gotta search for them?
I'll find you! I will!
He's found 4 already. - But he doesn't know how many are left.
I already caught this one.
Next would be ...
This would be the main room, right?
Here, my walk-in closet.
Eh, what's that? Did something fall off the rack?
I found you! I totally did!
What the hell!
Gimme a break! - It's Makino Suteteko!
I was sure you wouldn't find me! - You're number 5!
Whatever. - I found you-shiiiyo!
Having found 5 people, Kuro-chan does ...
That should be everyone, right?
That was easy-peasy.
Ok~! The staff just needs to show up now.
I got all 5, bingo~!
No part of him thinks there'd be 10 people hidden in total.
He mistakenly thinks 5 would be a nice round number.
With that, his search comes to an end.
Clean up the place! - Seriously.
Someone save us. - Someone, please!
That's right!
If someone can rescue the members on the roof without being caught by Kuro-chan ...
... they can earn a bonus of 50 000 yen, as an extra rule!
And so this man, who was hiding on the veranda, is making his move.
Alright, I'll head up to save them!
Chance is coming for us!
He enters the apartment from the veranda via the window, ...
He'll find you like this, isn't this dangerous?
... and heads to the roof.
Oh, he made it!
Ah, Chance is here! Chance has come!
Thank you~!
However, only 1 person can be rescued at a time!
Please save me! - Please save me!
He worked hard at King Of Conte, so I'll pick Sakai! - Ah, thank you!
Come out! - Come back for us as well!
With this, Chance Oshiro earns a 50 000 yen bonus!
Unnoticed by an inattentive Kuro-chan, Chance makes it back out to the veranda.
The veranda seems dangerous.
Sakai also ...
... heads back underneath the bed, thinking there's no way he'd search the same place twice.
Is the staff still not coming out? Hey!
Ah! Another phone?!
Eh? Is there someone there?
Eh, wasn't there a sound just now? Is there someone?
Where was it? I heard some kind of bang.
I think it was back here!
Sakai turned Kuro-chan's hunter switch back on!
And then ...
There's someone!!
He got Chance caught with that!
Sakai repays his rescue from the roof by getting him caught.
Are there still more of you?!
With this, Kuro-chan realizes there are more than 5 people, ...
... and he resumes his search.
There's someone! - Kyah~! - Who's screaming?!
Eh, Takamina?!
Why'd you have to find me?!
What-, wait ... why is Takamina in my home? - Seriously, why?! You're so cruel!
I don't get what's going on but you can't just come in here with a bunch of comedians!
After that ...
Uwah! Another one!
You found me ... - Ah, it's Yabe!
Screw you! - You can't say that to the home owner!
Screw you! - You can't speak badly of people!!
You make me sick! - Don't say that!!
[These subs are brought to you voluntarily, without the support of any of the sponsors listed up there]
3 hours have passed since we started.
The 3 listed here still remain.
Sakai is doing well! - You'd think he'd be out by now.
I'll look around the kitchen.
As Kuro-chan appears to investigate the kitchen ...
... the man under the bed makes his move.
He's coming out? - Something he wants to do?
In order to prepare for the long term, ...
... he grabs a blanket, pillow, ...
Gotta check the smell.
... potato chips, gummi candy, and ...
Those make noise!! - He's gonna come!
It's so cold!
He even grabs some warm clothes!
Much warmer~!
And then ...
Koishida? - Yeah?
Right now I think you can grab anything you need.
Sure seems like it.
Ah, he was there?
After gaining this information from his neighbor Sakai ...
... Koishida emerges from his closet for the first time in 3 hours!
Was that a noise just now?
Was there a noise? Hey, is someone there?!
It really turned into "Run for money"! - Hide quickly!
Hey, where are you? Where?
There was a noise just now!
He'll be found like that!
I'm sure there was a noise, it was pretty loud!
It's wide open!
But it's a small closet, it seems unlikely someone would be in there.
Did I leave it half open like this?
It feels somewhat warm ...
Found you! I got you!
Oh, come on! - I found you~!
Are you Koishida?
Sorry, Sumire!
They got your (Sumire's) dad. - Daddy!
And so only 2 remain.
Moreover, since it's past 4 pm ...
I don't have much time before my next job, so ...
... I need to change and leave! Got it? I gotta go!
Kuro-chan might be going somewhere, but the project will continue until everyone is caught.
Damn, my apartment's all messy now!
It was messy from the start!
Have fun at work!
Here the remaining two can catch a breather at last. But ...
You're here, right?! - Woah, he's back!
Eh, that's scary!
You're here, right? I know you are!
The way he goes about it is scary! - Hey, hey, hey!
You're here, right?
Getting dangerous ... !
I really gotta go, you know?
I do have to go, even though I'm not sure I really have work tonight.
But I'm short on time, so I'll head out now!
What was that?
Did he leave?
This time he really left, right?
No, wait a bit more!
He left, right? Then so will I. Here I go.
Uwah! - Thank gosh it's you.
Thank goodness.
He really did leave, right? - Yeah!
And then ...
I think he might not be back for another 3 hours. - 3 hours?!
That's according to Kikuchi, who works with Kuro-chan every day.
We're basically free to do anything for these 3 hours.
And so ...
Shall we order food?
Hello ... ?
They order pizza.
Wow, this is great!
They fill their stomachs to prepare themselves for the long haul.
You sure he won't come back?
Meanwhile, on the roof.
I actually have work after this, so ... - Eh?
Takahashi Minami, the only TV personality here who's actually in demand, retires from the game.
Now 3 hours have passed since Kuro-chan left for his work.
Let's get back to it again. Thanks for everything!
They head back like employees staying at a business hotel on a work trip.
Each of them goes back to their old position.
The bath ... - He'll be found for sure!
It's tight around my stomach, I ate too much!
This bath is actually quite pleasant.
The bath's dangerous, Kikuchi!
He's even got manga.
He hasn't even searched it yet.
7 hours since the start.
They've gotten fairly used to their life in hiding.
But then ...
He's back!
Very slowly.
The home owner returns, on tiptoes like a burglar!
At his own home! - I get how he feels though.
And then ...
I'm back, hear me?! I'm back!!
Why's he announcing himself?
Hm, where are you? Where might you be? I'm back! Did you wait for me?
He startled me ... - Did I startle you?!
I'm back! The home owner has returned!
Hey there~!
I came back dashing once my broadcast was over! Hear me?
"Dashing"
Where are you? Let's put an end to this alright?
Seriously, where are you? Where?!
Scary! - Why's he so agitated?
We really need to end this now! Seriously!
If we don't end this soon I'm gonna lose my freaking mind!
In a complete reversal from the cat burglar style he showed at first ...
... Kuro-chan runs around from room to room in a bizarre state.
Once I wear this I'll be in hunter mode!
There are still more left, aren't there?!
He once again picks up his search!
The bath's dangerous!
There's still a place I haven't searched yet.
This is bad, he'll come in here ... - A place I haven't searched~!
You're in trouble!
And then ...
Who's in here?
Uwah, shit! - Kikuchi? Eh, Kikuchi?!
Wanwan-nyannyan's Kikuchi is secured after 7h 12min.
Now I've found everyone, right? All 10?
I've found everyone! ALL TEN OF THEM!!!!
Of course Kuro-chan doesn't know about the rescue rule.
He's convinced this means it's over.
He's just casually eating something.
The staff still won't show for some reason.
In that case ... I've gotten all sweaty, so I'll take a bath.
He's taking a bath. That's my chance!
He's in the bath!
Zero privacy!
Taking this chance, Sakai goes and ...
Sakai's coming! - He'll rescue us, right?
Aaaah, nice!
Who are you picking?
Chance! To repay you for earlier!
Sweet! - I'm still in the game because of you!
To thank him for rescuing him once, he rescues Chance.
Kuro-chan is defenseless as he's still occupied with shower time.
While he's busy, they both make their way back to the apartment.
As their hiding spots, they pick ...
That was Takahashi Minami's spot!
Chance heads into the closet Takahashi Minami was hiding in earlier.
It smells like Minami~!
What are you talking about?
Sakai on the other hand heads back underneath the bed.
I rescued Chance!
9h 30min have passed since the start of this project.
I'm about to get ready for bed after this ...
... so is the staff really not gonna show up?
Ah, wait! Isn't everyone on the roof still?
They'll be exposed! Oh-oh.
I'll go up there and ask them!
Ah, no one's there!
Eh ... ?
He must think it's over.
Eh? They're gone?
Did they all go home? What's the meaning of this?
As a matter of fact ...
... when Chance was rescued the scheduled time for the shoot was already exceeded ...
... so the group on the roof dissolved and left.
Does this mean it's over?
There's no one here, right? Did they go home?
Where are they going with this? Why does no one tell me stuff, seriously.
At this point Kuro-chan is convinced the shoot is over.
Hence, he switches to off-time mode.
Tonari No Totoro, Totoro~!
He might be relaxing in the living room.
This makes me remember the time I got bullied in Amagasaki.
I'd get locked up in narrow spaces like this.
I've been confined like this before.
I also remember ... a murder ... happening right before my eyes.
What are you talking about?!
10h 30min since the start.
As Kuro-chan is convinced the project is over ...
Welcome to my evening routine, the Kuro-chan livestream~!
He starts livestreaming on TikTok.
"You look like Cromartie", aah it's a homerun to be compared to a Giants player!
"Your face is too close", are you shy of faces?
"Shiro-chan", wrong, it's "Kuro"!
Who'd wanna watch Kuro-chan?!
"What are you into lately?". I'm too embarrassed to tell, but thanks for the flowers and heart-piipii~! Baby-tappii~!
Kuro-chan, stop talking ...
Is he crying?!
Kuro-chan ...
This hellish livestream continues for 40 minutes.
"Hell". - Well they're not wrong.
"You're a baby", that's how my parents see me. Baboo~!
"I like a guy who's just like you". You shouldn't like anyone apart from me!
His fast talking is making me insane.
It's like a cult leader chanting spells.
Chance's stress is hitting its limits.
This would make anyone go insane. - The stress of the narrow place is getting to him!
Kuro-chan, shut up already! Phwgh!!!
Tomorrow, do you ... - Shut up, Kuro-chan!!
Hm?
Some kind of noise.
Tomorrow, do you ... - Shut up, Kuro-chan!!
Hm?
You'll be caught! - This is scary!
This must be scary for his viewers.
This is bad!
A major blunder by Chance!
His voice reached Kuro-chan in the room next door.
Scary! - Especially for his viewers.
Sorry, my bad, it was nothing-dashiiin~!
Thanks for the gift, Kagetora!
One of the comments says "Wednesday's Downtown".
Then, as he ends the livestream ...
Thank you-dashiiin~!
There really was a noise just now!
Is there still someone there? Huh?
There was a noise, right?
Ah! Who are you? Who?!
Eh, aren't you Chance Oshiro?!
Ugh, sorry ...
Why are you here a second time?!
Eh wait, so it was never over? It's not over at all?
It's not over at all?!
This is bad, now I'm the only one left.
What's this about? This was your second time, wasn't it?!
Please tell me there's no one left!
There still is someone~!
And so, just to be sure, he checks every place for a second time.
This is impossible.
If they can revive, I'm stuck in an infinite loop!
He doesn't check under the bed ...
I'm going to bed!
And then ...
Kuro-chan retires for the night.
With this, Sakai has entered a time where he can focus entirely on increasing his prize money!
However, 30 minutes later ...
Sakai has fallen asleep.
You're kidding! - It's a bunk bed of hell!
What kind of image is this? - How can he sleep there?!
For one hour, they both sleep soundly, snoring both above and below the bed.
Is he serious? - What is this?!
Eh?
That must be scary! - It might've sounded like his own snoring at first!
Scary ... ?
Eh?
Snoring?
How can you sleep there, Sakai?!
You've gotta be kidding me.
There's someone there! Hang on, what's this about?!
Isn't that Sakai?!
You're back again?!
Wake up! Go home! Leave!
What the hell?!
Am I ... am I at Kuro-chan's place? - Of course!
Why ... ? Oh, I see.
Wh- ... what are you on about?!
I was scared!
You snored like crazy!
I was seriously scared!
You snored just as loud!!
I can't get out ... - Get out! You got under there yourself, didn't you?
And I found you once before!
What the hell, leave already!!
You're noisy! - Don't tell me that, it's MY home!
You're noisy! - What's the matter with this guy?!
I just woke up, I'm in a bad mood!
And so, after a recorded 13 hours and 13 minutes, ...
... Sakai wins 402 180 yen!
This ends this tremendous project. What did you think?
What surprised me ...
... is how there are actually people who tip Kuro-chan in his livestream. - There are!
He had like hundreds of rose gifts. - Right!
Sumire, your thoughts?
I think if it had been me, I would've fainted! - Since you sleep alone? - Yeah!
Unfortunately they caught Koishida straight away. - Yes, my dad got caught right away!
What about Matsumoto?
They should've added Yaguchi as a contestant. - With the closet and all.
[Referring to an incident where Yaguchi Marika cheated on her husband and hid her lover in a closet when he returned]