Timers: Shiratohaki, Beatrice, Phantom, IngloriousBee Translators: Natsume, Zebestt, Jump4r, Tamaio
m 0 0  l 1800 0  1800 140  0 140
WDT Project
Welcome to Wednesday Downtown everybody!
Let's go ! Here is our first presenter, please come in
It's Giraffe's Kawashima Akira
Pleased to meet you
What a nice boy
I'm a giraffe thanks for having me
My theory concerns dogs
How many of you own a dog?
I own one but I keep him at my parent's home
What breed is it?
A mixed breed from a Chihuahua and a Papillon.
It's a small dog right
Indeed
What is his name?
Seimei
Wow such a "Japanese" name
Seimei as in "life"...?
Yes
So, the Japanese word for "life"
Indeed
It wasn't me who gave it
But, everyone is alive though right?
Don't say such things
Here is my theory concerning dogs
Theory: "Could you recognize your own dog, even if other people are walking him"
Oh I see !
It's not like you're looking for your dog
Outside, other people will be walking them
You could immediately recognize Peru, right
Because he had no more fur
Yeah he had no fur because he smelled so bad
I would instantly recognize him
In the end, he died wearing my sweater
After this, will entertainers recognize their own dogs?
He looks like him !
Moreover,
If you introduce the strangest person from your acquaintance, you finally reach a hoarders house
Current hits you once per minute : Current Domino
And then,
Avoid five kinds of punishments, Rhythm Challenge
Memorize the order of punishments and aim for efficiency
Theory: "Could you recognize your own dog, even if other people are walking him"
With that said,
Entertainers, who are dogs lovers, are called out to a fake program
I wonder.. It seems difficult to notice
In the middle of the film location, look at the 3 situations where they encounter their pet dogs:
1) Dogs passing by in front of them
2) Passing right by their sides
3) Contact between the dog and the owner
If not noticed by the end, the theory is off
I see
The first target is...
Will he get it?
Gusuman!
Gushiken Yoko
And the dog, a white Boxer called Gusuman
it's a breed of dog, which has quite a distinctive appearance
The fake show consists of a health check data
1) Measuring the heart rate
2) Walking 1km
First, the dog is passing by in front of them while they measure the heart rate
Let's relax a bit
Will he notice Gusuman ?
Here he is !
It's good right?
Perfect eye contact
This he noticed
This is perfect
Gusuman is also looking at him
Gusuman noticed him
He is watching him
Gusuman without a doubt noticed his owner
Although Gushiken...
I'm really curious about that dog
Eh? This one ?
I owned one like that
Is this a toy?
Isn't it a Miniature Pinscher ?
Unbelievable
It is.
Really?
Are you serious?
Miracle
He was curious about a dog that he owned in the past
Are you serious Gushiken ?
Then, while walking, the dog will pass by the side
Let's slowly walk 1 km
Alright, lets go!
The walking starts
and then...
The amount of food
in this way
He's so looking at dogs
It's bad to get overweight
A miniature ? Wasn't it a poodle?
As expected, he reacts at dogs
Finally, Gusuman's entrance
Oh, it's a boxer !
Amazing, it's a boxer
Are you serious?
He has a a boxer
Unbelievable
Amazing
Huh?
Right now, I just..
That was without a doubt a boxer
It's definitely Gusuman
There are people who have dogs around here huh
I want too see it one more time
It isn't good
Gushiken can't hide his excitement for the rare breed of boxers, but
Eeh he didn't get it
He didn't notice
he doesn't recognize his own dog
What about when they make direct contact
This he has to understand
Gushiken is left alone
Sorry, Gushiken-san
Yes
Is it ok if I shake your hand?
This is a boxer
You know boxer dogs?
You know what
Do you know mine?
Eh
Amazing, why?
Hose, do you like him?
Do you know mine?
They're the same
Wait a moment
Did he notice?
He looks like Gusuman
It's the real one
You're saying Gusuman
He looks like him
Wait a bit
Maybe this is my Gusuman?
He noticed !
He is similar ?
What the hell is this?
Isn't it Gusuman
As expected, he noticed
"What the hell is this"
Revealing the prank
How did you notice?
The size of the ears
There aren't many like that
He got it after all
This morning I took a walk around 7am
With Gusuman?
We separated with good feelings
What is this?
Because of the location, I had a good feeling
What the heck is with good feelings
If he makes contact, he notices
The following dog lover entertainer is...
We're happy to have you here Sugi-chan
Absolutely, happy to be here
Sugi-chan
His dog is a toy poodle called Puchi (3 years old)
Even this time, while visibly walking by
He doesn't notice at all
Even in the next part,
That's fast !
Yeah it was all over
Hm, Huh?
He's so similar to mine
Puchi
That didn't do, I'm just a stranger
Puchi !
He isn't looking, I'm mistaken then
He really looks like mine
But as an owner, I can't pass by without stopping
Cause it's Chiba
It's just like... mine
Even the size
But mine might be prettier after all
he's more cute
He was suspicious, but
he thought it couldn't be possible
Which means, once again with the last confrontation
Sugi-chan ?
Yes
Are you the person from before?
This gotta be puchi, he looks so much like him
Is it ok if I shake your hand?
Yeah no problem
Thank you
Thank you very much
Puchi Puchi Puchi ?
He looks so much like him!
Do you have a toy poodle too?
Yes exactly
Eeh, what color is yours?
Same color
Furthermore,
and when I touch him he has the same tension as mine
Just now, he seemed tense when I touched him
How old is yours?
Puchi?
Look ! He's so angry
This isn't safe!
Puchi has the same way of being angry
when he looks at me,
Why?
THIS IS PUCHI !
What is he angry about?
He's not calming down at all
He looks at his owner and get angry
Puchi is so angry
Sugi-chan also noticed his dog
Why?
As expected, if they make direct contact, they immediately recognize their own dog
Then, our last target is this person
Welcome Ikko
Hello
Ikko
It's this type of Ikko huh
And his dog is a 5 year old Chihuahua, Peko
It'll be easy to notice
Indeed
This time, he also doesn't notice with the "passing by" pattern.
How cute
Furthermore, even the "Passing right by" is failed
So cute~
Isn't it the one from before?
He doesn't get it
As expected, he didn't notice his own dog, however...
Sorry,
I didn't say it earlier, but is it ok if I shake your hand?
You like it
So cuuute
For real?
Do you like poko?
He's called poko?
Yes
Poko~
He's happy
Why is it doing that? Going "Gnnn~"
He always does that sound
Poko~~
You like Chihuahuas?
Until now, I have owned many generations of Chihuahuas
So, now you have a chihuahua too?
But, the way of barking is exactly the same
Like yours?
Eh, what color is he?
It's this exact...
He's happy~
What did he notice?
Something...
The odor
The odor?
He said Woo Woo
It's just like mine
Yes
Also quite doubtful about the unique purring
Come on
Cheese~
Until the very end he didn't ask : "isn't it mine?"
We don't need to say it, it's a perfect proof of our theory
really...
As a matter of fact, this dog is Peko
Oooooh, no way
He didn't notice
Which proves,
Ikko didn't notice
What was that, at the end
What the hell
The way Sugi-chan raises his dog is..
Is that alright?
That's a problem isn't it
If you put a camera in his house, he might do a bunch of stuff
It was unbelievable
What was that?
The way he said "He has the same way of being angry" was scary
Next presenter is this person, please come out!
Hello!
Jinnai Tomonori
Long time no see
So this time, my theory concerns "linking groups together"
We have done this 2 times in the past
Theory: "with a 6 people chain, you can finally get anyone's phone number"
And the second one: If you keep introducing the most interesting person
from your acquaintances, you will end up at Matsumoto Hitoshi"
This second time, they finally reached Matsumoto
It was super scary
Indeed, also this time, I thought about this
Theory: "If you introduce the strangest person from your acquaintances,
you finally reach a hoarders house"
No way!
It'd be quite a thing if it did!
How this will go?
It's possible
Until now, we've tried to reach Matsumoto, but this time it's a hoarder's house
but there's also a possibility we might reach Matsumoto again
It would be amazing if I lived in a garbage house
Eeeh this is amazing
But maybe...
On that subject, someone living in a hoarder's house is not necessarily strange,
he might have reasons for it
but indeed, they seem to be quite a lot of strange people
In the previous tour of that show, when I was looking for locations of garbage houses
I became quite close to those people
But the first impression was... It was all over the place!
That's the house, but what about the person?
Those people were also untidy
Talking about garbage houses, what do you think Seiji-san?
What are ya saying!?
Whose face is all over the place?
Everything is where it should be you idiot!
There isn't even space for stepping
There's plenty!
Theory: "If you introduce the strangest person from your acquaintances, you finally reach a hoarder's house"
With that said, from the people waiting around
In Shibuya?
we look for the first strange person
Then immediately
He doesn't have an umbrella
There are plenty of people like this in Shibuya
In the heavy rain, a man with strange movements
No umbrella...
Then, let's try to talk to him
Because you were walking in the rain without umbrella
I wonder why
It's because I really like Shibuya's rain
You like the rain in Shibuya?
Yeah
I like urban rain
This guy...
As expected, seems like a strange person
have you ever been called strange?
Strange? Mmh indeed
Gross
His laugh is so irritating
Kind of gross yeah
The first person of the link is
Oshima Kan (20 years old)
Could you introduce us to the strangest person from your acquaintances?
Alright, so cause I'm into dancing
I have a lot of gay acquaintances, they are people who really bring attention to themselves
Quite far gone people
Immediately getting an appointment with this person
Later, heading to the meeting place
Good evening
Are you Fujimoto?
Yes
Here is the "quite far gone gay", Fujimoto Kota (19 years old)
Do you recognize yourself as being strange?
No I think I'm quite normal
I often get called strange though
I don't think I really have anything weird
if I wouldn't dance I probably would be a normal person
What the hell is he doing?
Weird
In appearance, he doesn't have much self-awareness
Eeeh
He's weird
Oooh Ryou
Terrible
What are you doing?
His friends are amazing
What is this
What in the world
Unexpectedly, hugs and kisses from friends in the street
Is this what they call "Shibuya people"?
As expected, he wasn't normal
I see
Who is the strangest person from Fujimoto's acquaintances?
The person I'm thinking about when you say strange is a dancer called Rechiko
Again a dancer?
It's not that she drinks alcohol but
Although there are people around, she goes like " Yiaaah"
Do you mean an excited person?
She's really an idiot
This time once again, a dancer
I don't get a "hoarder" vibe from this
With that, we head to Rechiko's location
Excuse me, are you Rechiko?
Yes
Incredible
It's Wednesday Downtown
I'm Rechiko, nice to meet you
Unbelievable
The third person of the link, Esaka Reiko (19 years old)
Wow
Rechiko
Esaka Reiko
I'm Rechiko, Poi poi pi
Macchan, Hamachan I'm watching you
Poi poi poi~
Do you think you're considered strange?
I wonder, I think I'm a frank human being
Once again, not much self-awareness, but
when asked what her latest strange behavior was...
When I was at an event in Tokyo, I was standing in the back
I was really frustrated
I bought biscuits and was thinking of eating them
I wanted to eat them but,
Somehow felt I wanted to throw them at something
Without permission, I went 'Waaah" and then
with all my might I threw them "WHAM". It's the kind of story that spins your head
Rechiko who was supposed to be dancing in the background
she jumps to the center as she pleases and it resulted in her throwing biscuits
She gets forcefully pushed to the backstage
She's talking about that?
So who is the weirdest person this...
...rebel Rechiko knows?
Rechiko is amazing
There's this drag queen that's probably the most extreme ever...
...and his name is Katoken
Another drag queen dancer
with the name Katoken
He is
He really is too much
Too loud
We go on to the next person
Since it's Katoken (name means lot of health)
Hellooo~
This is Katoken : Katou Kenta, 19 years old
However
I really love doing weird movements
Like this...
and "NAANII~". I always do these
Oh I get it
His name he was positive but...
He's skilled
...he wasn't that loud as aforementioned
The next person we were introduced to was...
Saitou Tsukiho, 17 y.o
Oh she's young
It's really weird though, is it okay?
She was gonna do her trademark funny face but...
3-2-1
It's not much is it
I've been told it's scary
However...
3-2-1-Go!
...Rechiko's was much stronger
This girl is weird as hell
There's this person called Daisuke...
...who wears makeup everyday, he's in drag
There are alot of drag queens
It's only drag queens
Now, on to the next drag queen dancer
That's strong
He's kinda cool though
This is Fujiwara Daisuke, 21 y.o
I liked being called "creep" but also...
...there are mothers who tell their kids "don't look"
But one of the reasons I do it is that that makes me feel good
Who is the weirdest person this Daisuke knows?
He's a DJ
Is he a man?
He's male yes, he has one...
We're not going towards a hoarder house at all
We finally leave the dancer zone to a DJ
But unfortunately, even though we tried reaching this man
We couldn't set up a meeting cause of lack of communication
That means we start once more from the first person
Oh you went to Kitasenju! It's a good place for this
I get cold if this part (of my hair) is missing
No way that's true
If there is (hair), my neck gets warm
There aren't really weirder people than my cute self, yeah
Since my cute self is pretty extreme
I'm the best, at the top, the king
I really want to see this guys house
We couldn't really get to the second person
Will he act like that if you ask him about his house?
However...
Yeah if we can't get to the second person it won't work
This is a program called Wednesday Downtown...
...we were looking for a weird person
A weird person...
We kind of decided from your appearance...
Ones from 20+ years ago
We talked with this man with a unique appearance
I've been doing work as an extra
So having an outfit that was a bit out there could work...
You're an extra though
With that, this extra who wants to stand out is...
Sakamoto, 47 y.o, is the person we'll do our restart with.
Why do you have earphones on?
It's completely fine don't worry
Amongst this Sakamoto's acquaintances...
I feel like we're on to something here
...the one who's the weirdest is...
I wonder where we'll go
The street musician Yamaguchi Motochika, 30 y.o
And the person Yamaguchi is introducing us to is...
This girl called The Fullbody-Tights Singer Chaki
She's is Osaka
Osaka?
Yes
That means, to Osaka...
But,
The Fullbody-Tights Singer Chaki was...
...a common sensed person with an over the top expression
With that we understand that the real weird people are...
...the ones who look completely normal on the outside
The next person we got introduced to was Yamamoto
At first, he looks quite normal, however...
He looks really normal
In the future, I want to get assassinated
I want to die by assassination
Really?
My friends dream is to get a demonstration going because of that
One person...
One person told me "Ok then I'll kill you"
We have an agreement with that person
I'm serious
This guy is crazy af
That's insane
The person Yamamoto introduced us to is...
They scream about love in front of HEP
Always
They're only yelling out stuff like "I love everybody!"
What is this person's job?
A monk
Oh he's a monk?
Yeah
But, we couldn't get a hold of that monk
Since they're weird
Our second chain got cut off at 4 people
Since everyone's weird you can't reach them normally
We're not really going anywhere
So it won't work...
At this rate, we won't reach a hoarder's house, so...
Ah we came back to Kitasenju
...We've decided to start from a person of higher age
I'm a first class architect
Oh really
It's in the fine details
Oh is it
No, if you don't do it properly
You don't need a close up!
Your small mistakes will become huge
This person who doesn't allow small mishaps
Ooi Takashi, 71 y.o, introduced us to...
This cyropractor with a strong first impression, Tanaka
Haven't we come close?
Then, with Tanaka's introduction,
The hairdresser Ookuma's weirdest acquaintance,
Ah it got better a bit...
Oh he's stylish
Takeda from Takeda Motor Vehicles
Lots of car parts hanging around everywhere
It's quite a sight
It's so dirty
Wait, it's dirty?
It's dirty as hell
From a normal person point of view, it could be considered as trash
He's really stylish
Yep
He is isn't he?
Trash
We've finally come to a place that smells of trash
Getting closer to a hoarder palace very suddenly
That means, we go to Takeda Motor Vehicles quickly
Hello
Yo
This is the owner of the said hoarder palace
Takeda Hifumi, 64 y.o
We get a closer look at his place of work
We come to a place that you wouldn't think was open for business...
...full of random car parts scattered everywhere
Most of it has been here for many years
These are products?
Yes
They're products to me
They can be used so I keep'em
It can all be sold so I have'em
It's the one from before
Yes it's the one I did
I look at all of it and choose
A line we've heard somewhere else
It's a pinch if you say those things
Also, when we get a look at the offices...
No space to walk or stand,
The state of hoarder's palace
I think of myself as fond of cleanliness but...
With that,
It's quite easy to reach a hoarder's den of a small scale
A small scale right?
Yes on the light side, we reached it on the 4th person
There were really weird ones like "I want to get assassinated"
"I have an agreement"
What's wrong with that person?
In Osaka...
The "crazy af" guy
The really crazy...
He was serious too
The dancers strong hug and kiss...
...was like the one Jenkins* got
*It's a reference to a meeting between an abductee and his Japanese wife
After he got off the plane
Yeah after he got off
Nobody got it...
It's nostalgic
Nobody in the audience got it
Nobody knows what you're talking about
It's an old reference
It's like this please watch
Next up is the corner that verifies various theories from around the world
"Viewer's theory corner"
Tonight's presenters are
It's Chidori!
We're Chidori! We'll be in your care
Okay let's start "Everybody's theories"
We've done various mixed rule games
Yeah you have haven't you
This time...
...we've come with a new mix. You know batsu games right?
Variety TV's classic
It's the theory that if you mixed those batsu games with something else it'd be quite interesting to watch
We've come with a new suggestion to variety Tv
What do you mean?
Let's just look at the title, here it is
Batsu x Rhythm Game
A game like the Yamanote line* game
*It's a rhythm game inspired by the Yamanote metro line in Tokyo
Rhythm games like that exist right?
If various punishments would come at that rhythm...
...would you be able to get away from them in time
You know the Yamanote line right?
It's quite simple isn't it?
You say the thing that was th... glast person said that before
You're harsh
The Hamada Police is real harsh!
thglast?
Thglast??
There's no way I would be saying stuff like that at this moment
Yeah he said it
You said thglast..
You're really damn harsh!
You won't go easy on me huh?
I can't, can't, I don't like that no
You will not?
I will not!
You say the thing that the person before you said...
The person before you...
...and add your own.
It's the one where you have to memorize it all
Will you not do it once everybody?
Can you do it? We'll test it out
It's from here to there right?
Let's start with Daigo, and go all the way to Hamada, If you guys can
There's no way Hamada gets to play...
I'd like you to try though
He has the toughest part
Yes yes..
Let's start with vegetables
Alright, vegetables.
The topic is vegetables. From Daigo, let's start the Yamanote Line Game
Pan-pan
Cabbage
Cabbage - Lettuce
Cabbage - Lettuce - Carrots
Cabbage - Lettuce - Carrots - Bok Choy
Cabbage - Lettuce - Carrots - Bok Choy - Komatsuna
Cabbage - Lettuce - Carrots - Bok Choy - Komatsuna - Lettuce
Hey!!
Hold on!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING!?
You wrapped it with lettuce!
Bok Choy!
He wrapped it!
You made Chinese food!!
He sure did wrap it.
Punishment x Rhythm Game
In this game, the player stands in this box
And tries to avoid 5 types of punishments dealt in time with the music.
Oh that's amazing!
Moreover, each punishment is chosen by lottery, and is added up one by one
so that the players must memorize each punishment in order.
Oh noo
The participants taking on the challenge are these three
It's a dodging game.
I see...
Let's try... 15 punishments.
Eh?
That's impossible...
15?
15 is impossible.
There's no way.
If you fail mid-way you have to start again.
Wooow
Woooow
It's always this bullshit with them
Always
With that, let's have Kasuga choose the first punishment
A bamboo sword
What's with that
Bamboo sword
Hold on, if it comes here...
That machine looks scary..
Hold on
Uh, well if you come here you'll understand but
I can see the whole machine
That does seem scary
The harisen... it's scary over here
That's terrifying!
and I can hear the noises from the Harisen and the volleyball machine
Ok, I'm ready
Start anytime
Maru?
Quick
Was there only one beat?
That was faster than I expected
Isn't this dangerous?
You should be ready by the second 'thump'
I see...
Volleyball
Ohhhh
Oooh nice
Ok ok perfect perfect
Ready set go
Washbowl
So, down
Go down once, back up, and then down again.
The washbowl isn't a separate item
Just remembering "down down" is ok.
Ah that's right, "down down", that works
Oh, that's interesting
Let's remember by commands
Just remember the commands
That's right, by movement commands
Too early!
Oh amazing!
This looks fun!
Did you make it? Barely?
I did it right
I stood up right?
He had to stand up once
Mhmm
Bamboo stick
Jump
Down-down-jump
The commands
So early!
You're too early
Sorry
So early!
Ahh... my heart is pumping
Way too early
Yes, you need a good memory
but if you don't have a good sense of rhythm, you can't clear this game
Net
It hit me a bit
Nothing you can do about that
He's safe right?
Yeah yeah
That's hot...
He did it He did it
He's got it
Noo!
Why did you jump there?
What are you doing?
What are you even doing?
And after that
Ouch!
Slow!
You bastard!
The opposite!
Nakaoka keeps dragging the team
He went for it!
Already 1 hour has passed since the start
You really have to memorize them all
Down down, then jump
Nice
Komiya clears 6 in a row! A new record!
Next, Kasuga also...
He's not looking at anything!
A bit suspicious, but he still clears.
But Nakaoka...
Next, Nakaoka challenges 8 punishment in a row
He's pretty bad
Down-Side-Down
Down-Jump-Down-Down-Jump
This is hard...
He's in unknown territory
Alright, let's do this
He's still not jumping when supposed to
Oh god
I can't bear to watch
Ahh please
No more
This guy is really pissing me off
His glasses!
2 hours since the start, the 16th game
Oh, they've gone all the way to 12!
Amazing!
Kasuga, amazing!
Wow
Wow!
Woooow!
Kasuga finally passes the 12 punishment barrier
Well he does have good stamina
Afterwards, Nakaoka has to clear 13 punishments
Will he be able to connect to Komiya
I hope he doesn't jump at the washbowl again
No way!
What what what
The volleyball...
Shocking...
Are you ok?
This guy's really pissing me off
Once again the streak is stopped by Nakaoka
He really can't do this
Ayyyy
Slowly, he seems to be getting the hang of it
Still, there seems to be a barrier at 11 penalties, and the record has not been improved
It's been 3 hours and 50 minutes since the beginning
They've done it for 4 hours?
But next...
Kasuga clears 12 punishments
Amazing
As expected
Wasn't the volleyball too close?
That first volleyball almost hit me!
And then, Nakaoka challenges the fated 13 punishments!
Let's go!
Oh he took off his glasses
Ok ok
Oh no!
Good work
Ohhh close
Keep it up
He did it!
Safe safe safe
He's awakened!
Ok ok ok
It's over it's over
I never want to do that again
You're the best
Komiya also clears 14 punishments
In the end, complete victory is entrusted to this man
The result is...
You're ok!
So fast
Nice nice
Nice
No way!
Kasuga!
Aaaaahh
Noo!
With that, our participants were able to clear 14 punishments in a 4-hour battle
Ah that was...
They couldn't succeed?
Mhmm
But it was pretty interesting
It was a good try
What did you think Matsumoto?
I think there's no way I couldn't do this
He said it!
He really said it!
Yeah, well even now...
Now?
I've already memorized it
No way
You memorized it while watching, right?
Right, right!
That's impossible
Let's do it, Matsumoto san
Of course! You can even set a blowtorch up
Yoshimoto won't allow that!
Well, there's one more mix!
And here comes the next one.
Punishment X domino show
Now this is interesting
What?
And here come our two clueless challengers
Viking
They appear every week
Nishimura san, what's wrong with your eyes?
That's right, his eyes...
They were swollen when I woke up
Sorry
What the hell happened?
So intriguing
As always, Nishimura being a weird guy
He's so creepy
Where did he sleep?
They will have to face a 1000 dominoes challenge
However, there's a special rule: an electric current will flow once a minute
EH?
EH??
An electric current?
Every minute, right?
Whaaat
Don't be stupid...
Similar to last week's
Aaah, I don't like this
No way, no way, no...
Kotoge san, do you feel confident about this?
Well, I...
Some time ago, I set up a domino show in another TV program
I see
So I'm sure I'm better than this guy over here
But I'm pretty good at electricity so...
So when it comes to that...
What the hell do you mean?
There's no such thing as "good at electricity"
How did you know?
So if I manage to endure...
How did you know you were "good at electricity"?
And that's my only...
...chance of winning
Aaaaah
Wait a sec
They can't see the timer
The first shock...
Is that so?
So these two don't know
Oh, I see
Hey
How much distance
I'm really scared of the first shock
The distance...
Between dominoes
Well, you should separate them a little bit more
Ah, they can't topple?.....Oh, they can.
Wow, the "once per minute" rule...
It's scary, huh?
It is indeed
is really freaking me out
He wants to know how's the shock
Right, so as to test its strength
What should I do?
He can't stand shocks, right?
It's coming, isn't it? In a minute
Is it coming?
He's waiting for the first one
How strong will it be?
So scary...
But the other guy's totally fine
I think I can't do this
Well, after all, it's Nishimura
If I don't know how strong it will be...
Nishimura is totally oblivious
Wow, this is something. I...
I'm scared
Ah, it's coming
He's laughing
Are you waiting for the first one?
AAAH
That was strong!
This is impossible!
No way I can do this!
No way!
This is impossible!
This is scary!
I think I can't do this...
You were setting them!
Keeping track of the time on your own
and predicting the coming shocks.
That's the key to success
Yeah, but...
I'm too scared to set the pieces
Nishimura didn't even flinch
I can't...
I just...
It's just impossible!
I can't do this
This is so tough...
Why, you're setting the pieces just fine!
Leaving "Good at electricity" Nishimura aside,
Kotoge can't even set the pieces properly
Out of all the WDT challenges, this is the craziest
That depends on who you ask right?
Why don't you shut the hell up
However, after enduring several shocks...
Oh, isn't he getting used to it?
Instead of predicting the next shocks...
They've just grown used to them
A mastered technique!
It has been one and a half hour since the start
They have grown used to the electricity, but...
...this happens
AaAAAA
Wow this is bad
That can happen, huh?
He lost the progress...
What a fool
Surprisingly, Nishimura rebuilt it quickly
and caught up again with Kotoge. But then...
Wait! Wait!
Didn't even get a shock!
Oh, it stopped there
Might be the difference in experience
After all the progress, he ends up toppling them without even getting shocked
On the other hand, Kotoge...
It usually comes after setting 10-15 pieces
Each minute
No way
Yes
So when the time comes, I'm ready
They seem to finally be able to time the shocks
However...
Ah, it's coming
Careful!
Wow!
AAAH
WOoow!
It hurts!!
All the progress gone!
Noooo
NO NO NO NO
That sucks!!
That's the worst!
That is terrible
That's the worst
So depressing
They toppled, huh?
"They toppled, huh?"
That's awful
They toppled so beautifully
Since you're good at this...
..they toppled so beautifully, no?
I see
He's something
They spend a total of 5 hours and 30 minutes
5 hours and 30 minutes!!
but they couldn't clear the domino challenge
I see...
Wow
They were so close though
Yeah, they were!
They couldn't clear it...
That was something
What about this one, Matsumoto san?
Piece of cake, I'd say
What a liar
He must be kidding
So you can do it, right?
I think so, yeah
No, you only have the power to refuse it
If we were to begin right now
I see, huh
I see
If the staff prepared the challenge right now...
That's right
If they brought it now
He'd be like: "You really thought I meant it?"
Check out our Facebook and Website for more Wednesday Downtown! This video was subbed by a community run project called the Wednesday Downtown Project. Thanks for watching!
m 0 0  l 1800 0  1800 158  0 158
Next week: If professionals did teacher impressions, students would die of laughter "theory"
And also!
"The stronger the tsukkomi is, the funnier it gets" theory
"People won't notice if a famous song with changed lyrics is played in a store" theory
And finally, "When you're holding a urine sample, you become powerless" theory