Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Who is it?
Hello everyone
It's Jinnai Tomonori!
Has everyone heard of the phrase "set phrase"?
So have you ever had the experience of being set up?
What happened exactly?
At a handshake event, a fan came over and said they were meeting me for the first time
So I said "nice to meet you" but was then told "it's not the first time we've met"
Wow, that's bad
Have you ever been trapped in a conversation?
Those guys from Weekly Magazine
I thought I was talking to them about something they already knew, so I confessed everything
After saying that, the guys actually looked surprised with a "is that so" look
I didn't know how far the other side had investigated
After that, I had to give a press conference and get a divorce
That's enough from you
※In 2009, the day after he filed for divorce, he held a press conference and admitted that the reason for his divorce was that he was having an affair with multiple women
Don't mention that, Junior, it was 10 years ago
It happens
So, the theory I bring you this time is:
"Is there anything you have to say to me?" If you're told this, you'll likely say something that's unnecessary
I see
-That's scary
I think we all think the same thing in that we'd definitely say something
In this case, for example
If you go to Hamada's lounge and are told this line by Hamada
You'll probably be interrogated for more than 2 hours
Why!?
No, no, that's if Hamada's getting told off by his wife
He'll confess until the sea runs dry
He'll just keep going
Later
Will they really say unnecessary things?
And
Connecting Udo's overuse of "Sorry" with Amano's daily life
Will either notice the connection?
And, if the pitcher and first baseman are magicians
Can they use a hidden ball to get batters out one by one?
"Is there anything you have to say to me?" If you're told this, you'll like something that's unnecessary
The initial pair is Impulse
This guy won't listen anyway
Definitely
I can't really imagine what will happen
It's a little scary... truly
So...
If he confesses to a crime or something, it's over for us
I'm quite nervous as the pranker
After calling out his partner under the pretext of "we need to discuss something," the verification begins
What's going on?
Is there anything you haven't told me yet?
So believable
Something I haven't told you?
There's something I haven't been told, right?
Something that needs to be said?
The autograph thing?
Eh?
Autograph
-Autograph?
That...
I was requested to sign our autograph
So I signed your name as well
So cute
Because it was requested...
That doesn't matter
That doesn't matter at all!
That's not what i'm referring to
He laughed!
Ah...the gym?
Eh?
The gym
What about the gym?
I lost 2KG of weight after exercise?
Had a slight change in body size
No, why would I call you out because of this?
You lost 7KG when you were forced out of the business because of the scandal
I wouldn't call you out today to talk about losing 2KG
Well, yes, yes, that's right...
Although I could say it
"It's like this" can also be said
I think it's better to let you confess yourself
Impressive
Western...Western restaurant thing?
Eh, what? What Western restaurant?
I want to open a western restaurant
Gotta get a health permit
Seems like the kind of thing that would actually happen
An interesting pursuit
His look suits a Western restaurant
Eh? Western food...
Since i've been back at work I've wanted to open a Western restaurant
It has become an interrogation
Although forced to talk
All he gives are useless updates
Explosive announcements seem to be few
After that too
Is it about preparing to study abroad in summer?
Want to open a cooking channel on Youtube?
Debt...debt?
Hair regrowth?
Dad...that I was beaten by my dad?
The small material keeps on coming
Even telling a story like "I was beaten up by my father" is unbelievable for someone over 40 years old
Originally this guy is bad
It's not that
Eh...
After saying "it's not that" repeatedly
If I say "It's this" then that's the end of it
I need to hear the words
-Um...
If it doesn't come directly from you
I won't be in the mood to help you
Things that I should say to you...
The last thing he squeezes out after thinking incredibly hard is...
That...
The encounter
What encounter? Go on
Let's see if it's right
Signed up for the dating app that thing?
Already laughing
Laughing so obviously!
Don't laugh!
It's really funny though
Never had the opportunity to find an attractive...
Is this it? Eh, is it?
Did you register under your real name?
No, it says "42-year-old company employee"
Did you upload photos?
-No, I didn't
But if you don't show your face, it's a little bit...
It'll eventually end in...
When we meet, it'll be "You're Teshita, right?"
Is this something that will cause you problems?
No, these kinds of things don't matter at all
So, we reveal the truth
What?
These familiar faces will make you understand
Wednesday?
Indeed
What just happened?
What's happening?
Did I do something?
After conveying the theory
Don't air the thing about the dating app thing!
How are the results of the dating app
Nothing at all
The guy who "earns 150 thousand a year at the age of 42" has no chance at all, right?
Next is
A survey of seniors and juniors who usually have a good relationship
And so
TKO's Kinoshita-san seems pretty bad
Really stingy
And Yukio's brain is a bit wrong, right?
From what Matsushita says
This guy keeps talking about it
They're obviously trying hard but still being told they don't get it
I don't understand why he doesn't understand
We all work very hard
Really? What about Otake?
Nadal who does not stop badmouthing his seniors
Will soon be faced with the statement
Nadal, do you have something to say to me
No no
There is
Something I have to tell you?
Is it about LUMINE? LUMINE
Talking about your Heroshow segment?
Talking about our segment?
They've been doing the same thing for 18 years
"It's always the same, and the people listening to it remember it", something like that
I think someone said that
Who said that?
Who said it...
Anthony did
Anthony?
Immediately betrayed the man
Is it really what Anthony said?
"It's always Heroshow"
Anthony? He was looking down on it?
Funny... funny damage
What does funny damage mean?
I didn't understand either
I've already heard about that, to be honest
It reached my ears
Don't eat the mushrooms
Finished it in one bite!
I told you not to eat mushrooms
I really do not know what you are talking about
I haven't done anything
I really do not want to be the one to say it, Nadal
Eh...the private work thing?
I really don't want to take private work, but I can barely afford to eat
How often do you do it?
Not that often
This golden week, there are "Golden Private Shows" and such
You can live well if you don't take private work
Although I hate to say this
ZAKO said this
He said "Why is private work dark?"
I said "Yeah"
He replied "When the darkness is gone, the light comes"
What the hell?
Don't do private work, you're on TV after all
Yes, I'm sorry
But its not this... private work does not matter what
So
What is it?
X？
Eh?
This is bad
Not good not good
So we disclose the truth
That face!
Always staring!
A good bad expression
Wait a minute Fujimoto
A lot of good info came out
I also said the X thing
Look at his eyes
What is this thing?
What day of the week is it?
Wed... Wednesday Downtown
Seriously?
Don't be like this, seriously
FUJIWARA's Heroshow segment
It's being looked down on
By Anthony and you
No...that's what everyone says
What do you mean "everyone says so"?
Next is also a senior and junior who have a good relationship in private
What about the master-disciple relationship?
Recently I heard some bad rumors
Is there something you're not telling me
Eh...
Bento? The bento thing?
Bento...ah, bento...ah
Bento?
I took the bento?
Who?
Me
Who's?
Yours
From the lounge?
Yes
You took my bento from the lounge?
Yes, I'm sorry
Is it this?
How can it be this?
I went with various people...
I have worked in various places with different people and done it there
Bento thief?
Yes... yes
I've done it to loads of my seniors
Who? Your seniors?
Viking's Nishimura and a few others
What's wrong with you?
Who? Viking's Nishimura
Nishimura
But this doesn't constitute a crime, right?
I didn't say anything about crime in the first place
But isn't this something that everyone knows
I don't care about the bento
That? The thing with the AV actress?
Eh?
Having dinner with the AV actress?
My wife realised
Eh?
Kumomoto... I told her it was your fault
And now my wife is wary of you
You've overthinking it
As a liaison with an AV actress is exposed...
Kumomot's reputation is unexpectedly brought into question
Yeah, this'll happen
And there's more
Macau?
Eh?
-Macau?
Macau?
In Macau...
The thing about that woman?
Eh? Woman from Macau?
Was I there?
You were there
We went together, right?
Don't don't
No no no
With both about to suffer, the verification is brought to an end
This...
Due to the damage it will bring to Kumomot's reputation, please cut this out
That's reasonable, right?
Kumomoto's wife... right?
I'm sorry, Kumomoto's
I'm so sorry
Last is Morita who will be questioning his junior
You two have something to talk about
Eh, what? What? What? What? What?
So i'm leaving
Wait a bit
It doesn't matter if he's here?
First of all, it's just us two
First? What do you mean, first?
Eh, what? What? What? What? What?
Is there anything you have to say to me?
Something I have to say?
Hmm
No there isn't
There must be something you have you say to me
I don't understand your reply at all
I already know
What kind of interrogation is this?
It's not like that
Not "not like that"
If you know, then say it
I want to hear it from your own mouth
What are you angry about?
I am completely confused about what is going on here
The atmosphere is getting interesting
What exactly do you want to hear?
I already know
If you know then just say it
I want you to hear it from your own mouth!
But there's nothing, I've said nothing
I already know!
Then say it!
You just keep saying "I know, I know!"
Unlike the previous three groups, this group does not have a particularly obvious senior-junior relationship
Thus, the scene turns into an argument
We have set up a personal office
It is absolutely necessary to understand each other. It is not possible for us not to share things, right?
Since it's such an important thing, just say it
Why do you refuse to say it?
Say it, or do you not know anything?
What do you really want to hear?
That is, with
Don't just say "you know", it won't get the conversation going
What do you hope to achieve with this type of set phrase?
It's not a "set phrase"
Then just come with some evidence and say "what is this?"
You've gotta do both
It's because i'm not doing that that you don't want to do it
What do you want to do then?
If you confessed from the start I wouldn't be angry
What, is it a business thing?
Eh?
What? Business?
Yeah, business? Yes
So it's that!
Well... I took on jobs and so on...
I went alone and did a hosting gig
I didn't tell the company that I did it
Eh, the company?
Is that not it?
He took the bait in the end in such a typical manner
The duo and their manager are the only three people in their company
And thus engage in a private business-focused exchange
Morita, who couldn't hide his shakiness in the face of such a real betrayal
This is not the same as ordinary private work
Yeah, because it's personal
Eh? What? You took a job?
Isn't that the thing?
It's also a bit related to this
I don't think this is what you were referring to
It's not about this, is it?
What about the pay?
How much did you get?
Basically just pocket money
We're supposed to share half of everything!
You take a share of all my solo work
That's because it's all on the firm's books, so it can't be helped
Then isn't it wrong to do it outside of the company?
How much did you take? Enough is enough
Just say how much you've taken, and don't worry about the rest
How much did you get paid?
Eh...
20？
You didn't talk about it with Yamane?
I didn't, so i'm sorry, but this is beside the point
This is obviously not what you wanted to ask about
Saying this out loud means i've already half lost!
It's not a loss
It is because of the way you are talking
A half-loss
No, no, no.
-A half loss means you still have another half
No no no
You just said half of it
-Wait, wait, wait, it's just one
It's not because there are two halves that you say "half lost"
Something needs to be cut into two halves to have lost half of it
Do you have something you need to say?
Huh?
You also have something to say to me, don't you?
Suddenly, an unanticipated counterattack is launched
Like you said, it has to come out of your own mouth
No, really
That's enough out of you!
Don't do this!
This question is too annoying
So, what about that? In Fukuoka?
Huh?
When was it?
You took a job at the beginning of the year, right?
At that time, we agreed to go to dinner with our clients
Only you said stuff like "I've got something later"
You're the only one who didn't show up, saying "I'm going home"
Yes, I said, "I'm not feeling well, I'm going home."
Bad health but you actually went out, right?
Huh?
You were in bad health but you went out?
What do you mean "huh"?
You went out at that time right
No I didn't
I already know!
No no no no
That's enough. Don't go on like this!
You went out
-Huh?
One of the girls sent me a private message
No, no, no, no, no, wait, wait
No, no, no, wait
I know!
No, I'm talking about you
I already know about it!
What?
I got a private message from Fukuoka!
"I work at a hostess club", like that, and you went there
That's enough, that's enough!
This topic is closed
It's weird you don't wanna talk about yourself
I'm tired, i'm tired
I'm the one that's tired!
I'm really tired
And so, we reveal the truth
What is this?
What? What? What? What? What? What? What? Enough, i'm tired
What's going on?
I don't get what's going on
Eh? You, eh?
What is this all about?
You...
No, it's you, isn't it?
You did something, didn't you?
It's strange for you to ask me "what's going on?"
So what is going on?
Isn't it you?
Due to the counterattack, Morita thinks that he has been counter-pranked
A trick, right? No?
I knew nothing of it
So what is this?
What kind of magic is this?
I don't know!
In summary
this a theory that no one benefits from
Very explosive
This is bad
Yeah, no good
It became like an Obon Kobon event
The way of quarrelling
I'm relieved about Teshita
Each reveal was quite cute
Wants to run a Western restaurant and stuff like that
I'm cheering him on
Let's welcome the next presenter
Zun's Iio!
First time seeing you
Matsumoto, I've been here two or three times already
Hamada, what has happened to him?
What theories have you brought so far?
5 years ago, Udo's good nature is insane
Oh yeah
What was particularly unusual about that verification
Was Udo's various apologies
He was sorry for everything.
-He apologized for everything
"I'm sorry for almost hitting you"
No one even noticed
-Indeed
Last summer, I sat in front of the air conditioner
Udo passed between me and the air conditioner
Then he turned around and said
"Sorry about blocking the cold air from the air conditioner for a moment, Iio"
In this regard, we have brought this project
Kyaeen's One-day Electric Linked Life
One-day Electric Linked Life
Every time Udo says "sorry"
Amano will receive a shock of electricity
This is pretty bad
-It's awful
The question is, can Amano solve the mystery?
And stop the shocks
Again, this is the type of project that benefits no one
So, the one being shocked is Amano
However, the source of the current
Has been previously explored
This is the issue
Yes, yes, yes
Sorry, please take care of me
Udo's mantra: "Sorry"
At that time, to co-stars, staff and even agents
He apologized like crazy and talked endlessly
In this schedule
Will Amano be able to detect the linkage and stop the current?
So, at 10:00 a.m., it starts with
Artiste Navigation Yeah!
Using the Sunshine Shopping Building in Ikebukuro as a stage
Emotional Udo's trip begins!
Before you know it
Have you been to Sunshine City?
I was just here not long ago
There's a planetarium.
-Oh, oh, planetarium
I remember, Amano he...
He worked as a planetarium narrator
I think it was here in Ikebukuro Sunshine
If not then sorry
It only takes 5 minutes and reaching the topic of Amano for him to say sorry for the first time
So, Amano, who is called out for a fake meeting
Will taste his first shot of electricity
Ow ow ow ow!
His meat is hanging out
A naughty peek at the belly
Ow!
What's going on?
This is scary...
Amano, confused by the sudden electric current
Is suddenly greeted by the program staff
What the hell is this?
We are Wednesday Downtown
It hurts. Did you guys just do that?
-Yes
What what what what what what, what a bunch of weirdos you are!
What the...what the hell? What are you verifying?
Faced with an unaccustomed trick, it takes a while for Amano to get in the mood
Subsequently, he is fitted with an electrical device
Then
So cute, so cute
Sorry, can I ask you a personal question?
Idiot, idiot!
Too... sorry, really
It hurts. It hurts a lot!
What kind of experiment is this? Can't you tell me?
Of course, it is impossible to reveal the details at this stage
Instead, we tell him to enjoy his day to the fullest
Next, some more meetings take place
So the meetings...all have to be held in this state?
-Yes
Why?
Even though the meetings were fake, we carried on as usual
This will be troublesome for others, its not good
Thus begins Kyaeen's electric linked day
Once again
Sorry, are there any special events today?
Ah, yes yes yes
Sorry
Sorry, really, sorry
Sorry, taking up your time
Thank you very much, sorry
Excuse me
Are you okay?
-I'm okay
The conversation at the service desk alone involved 7 apologies
Next...
Sorry, what type of guy do you like?
Sorry, this
-Ow!
Really, sorry
Ahhh I can't stand it... why is it still going on!
Even during a break from location shooting
Thanks, sorry
I'm really sorry, thank you
For making you go to the trouble of putting black honey all over it, i'm really sorry
Sorry...
Sorry, thanks very much
An endless barrage!
Udo's sorry meter climbs sharply
While the staff wait for Udo to use the toilet
Ah, this kind of time...
He'll surely say it
Ah, are you waiting for me?
-Yes
Oh i'm very sorry, sorry
Sorry, really, sorry
You had to wait so long, sorry, sorry
For me, really, sorry...
Sorry sorry sorry sorry
An 11-sorry explosion
It hasn't stopped yet. It hasn't stopped yet
So far, shooting time has lasted for 2 hours
And the sorry count is up to 150
Amano's next job is
I'm Takayanagi
-I'm Amano
Please advise me
A fake location shooting with the full assistance of the "King's Brunch" crew
Complete with a host and costumes
It's impossible to distinguish from the real thing
King's Brunch Shopper!
Let's introduce our guests!
Hiroyuki Amano!
This is the second time you've participated
I remember...always remember that...
I bought a lot of things that time
At that time Yuuka was here
Er... Yuka- gave me an amulent... sorry
Then let's get started!
Let's go!
Amano has been haunted by eerie feelings since the beginning of the show
Thank you, and I apolgize for making you wait so long
Sorry, thank you
Look at that look on the clerk's face.
-Completely stunned
The one just now was delicious, sorry, I didn't even thank you for it
Thank you very much, sorry
Sorry, I just want to buy something I didn't get
Sorry, really, sorry
…Yes
I said a bunch of inexplicable, really sorry everyone
I apologize, really, sorry
At this point, the filming ends
Next
A banned word?
Once I say that word I'm...
Amano fails to consider that someone else may be involved
Finally, Amano will join Udo's location shoot
Can he detect the link and stop the current or not?
5:00 p.m. The stage is changed to the shopping street of Takanouji Temple
The shoot continues towards the store where Amano is waiting
So
Hello, wow so delicious, look
Ah sorry
Sorry, really
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
When Amano takes his 393th shock of the day
Huh?
-Hey, wait a minute
Isn't this Amano? Great!
I'm waiting for you guys!
I'm so happy, Amano.
-All of a sudden the enthusiasm is high
That's great, Amano. You're so cute.
-Cute? I'm your partner, right?
As soon as I came up, I saw Amano, so warm, so warm
A pair of 49 year-olds
Udo doesn't even know that his dear Amano is being mercilessly destroyed by his own mantra
Sorry, it's really cute
Wait a minute, what's going on here?
Next
Here you go then.
-Is that okay? Really? Sorry, thanks
What are you doing? What's the point?
What I'm trying to say is...
-Do you want to pay?
I was going to say, "So there's 1,000 yen"
Udo doesn't particularly notice that someone is continuously screaming
On the other hand, Amano fails to notice the connection
Are you a couple?
No
-Oh no?
I really thought you guys were, sorry
Sorry sorry sorry
What are you doing? What is "ay"?
Scared, right? Sorry
Huh?  -It's okay.
Can I ask you what kind of man is your type?
Udo!
-The first time!
Thank you so much!
Thank you very much, sorry
I am so happy
OK OK OK let's go
After these 4 consecutive shots, Amano begins to notice something
Then
Sorry
What are you doing?
We are strolling around Takanouji
I heard that the sashimi here is very good.
-Yes
Could you please... Store Manager, sorry
Let's have a taste
Sure
Wait a minute...
At this moment he finally senses something
Please have a taste!
Dried bamboo shoots and barbecued pork
-This much is no longer considered a tasting, right?
If you can, please.
Come on, Udo
Ah, sorry
This is a little scary
Are you okay?
-That was close
Why do you look like a figure skater
Oh I thought this was a sign
Excuse me
Back to the camera, sorry
What? Do you want to practice boxing?
-No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Are you dodging before you throw a punch?
-Wait a minute
Will you shut up for a second?
Anyway, don't talk to me.
-Why?
Do you need anything else?
-Sorry
Finally?
This excellent barbecue...
I'm already convinced
I've suffered all day because of you
-Sorry
What?
-This is it!
After 8 and a half hours since the start of the verification, after 461 currents
Amano finally correctly identifies the source
So we disclose the project here
Thank you for your hard work
After explaining the project to both of them
Huh? That location shoot was actually...
It won't be broadcast
Ah... it was just for "sorry"？
Please stop!
I've had this thing on since this morning
How many apologies have you made?
Did you apologize continuously and incessantly?
-No
What a lie!
I guess I did
-You did, right?
I thought the machine was going berserk
How many times in total?
The total is now 462 times
462 times, each time the feeling was as bad as the last!
Each impact was like first love
So it has come to this
Okay, OK
That's all for today's shoot. Thank you very much.
-Thanks
Help me dismantle it!
Removal of the current device takes place finally after 9 hours
But
Really sorry, thank you very much
Sorry
Sorry, Mr. Driver
Stop stop stop pain pain pain pain pain pain
Ouch... ouch...
That guy is apologizing in some damn place again. It hurts!
By the way, if the total current of this day is accumulated
It is just over one shot from a taser
Surpassed the taser
What do you think?
-Very impressive
The phrase "I'm sorry for making you have you put the black honey on it" is simply...
He applies the same amount every time, right?
Probably like a tiny little bottle
If he doesn't finish it, he'll say, "I'm sorry I didn't finish the honey."
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Taking Downtown as an example, it's the same as Hamada saying "I'll kill you"
If I was electrocuted every time he said it i'd be a mess
The first sentence of the segment would be "I'll kill you"
Next is everybody's theories
Tonight's presenter is
Kamaitachi!
This is our first time, please take care of us
So...
No, these two people have been rehearsing for a very long time
Backstage?
Yes
Matsumoto, please don't say that
So I was wondering what they'd say
We were just confirming the content
-That's it
Please never say we were practicing or anything like that
No no no no
You didn't practice for ages?
People will be concerned to hear we had to practice such a simple thing
We all expect a bit of chat after they come out, right?
We were really just confirming the details of the process
We aren't holding back a big move
Indeed
How... did this opening become so stifled?
It's super hard to get such an opening
Everyone, let me ask you a question
What are your impressions of "magicians"?
Dexterous
Good with their hands and stuff
Very good at hiding things
Yeah
So, the theory we bring today is this
If the pitcher and first baseman are magicians, they can use a hidden ball to get the opponent out one by one
I see
Should work
The fielder hides the ball
The moment the runner leaves the base
He uses this ball to get the runner out of the game
A trick play
It's like this
So to put it in perspective
A magician will hide it cleverly
As if holding it over here
But it's not. It's this hand that's holding it.
-Awesome
Impressive
That's how it'll work
That's great, but I hate it
Why? Why?
Great and annoying
While I write he does not anything else other than practice magic
Don't say such things!
So his current level of magic is super high
I go drinking with a magician
Regularly?
Yes, many times
Once we went to a business meeting with a magician.
-Stop it!
To potentially enter the magic business, instead of being comedians
Eh what? It's not funny, don't bring up this kind of thing
This is the part that you were rehearsing, right?
This sequence
So...this is it
No, no, no
Are you here to bring shame to the king of conte?
We won
Here we go again
It's not like that, think about it, the depth of the work is completely different
If the pitcher and first baseman are magicians, they can use a hidden ball to get the opponent out one by one
This time, we used the phrase "1 million dollars if you succeed in stealing a base in front of a former professional baseball catcher"
Thus, this fake project attracted several performers known for their running ability
So
With the cooperation of the former Hanshin's catcher, Kano
※狩Keisuke Kano: Hanshin Tigers catcher from '01 to '17, most stolen bases in the Central League in '09
What do you think of using a hidden ball?
How can I put it
It would be too bad to be finished by this
Even if you are criticized for being careless, there is no way to refute
Have you ever experienced it?
Not really
It would definitely start a fight
"What are you doing?" and so on
I've never seen it
A hidden ball that is extremely difficult to see on the court
There have only been four successful ones in baseball history in the last 15 years
So, there are still some
It is a trick play that is very rare
So, these experts in slight of hand are brought in
And should be able to get people out
1 million for successful base stealing in front of the former professional baseball catcher
So the first challenger is Bobby Ologun
The initial target is Bobby Ologun, a regular in such sports projects
After a good warm-up
Everyone, let's stop Bobby's 1 million
Enemy?
So, the verification begins
First, a magician with pitching experience holds the ball and sets up a stationary position
Seeing this, Bobby boldly pulls away
Really>
By the way, although they are magicians
They are forbidden to use two balls to complete the hidden ball out
I see
No dirty tricks
At this time
I don't think so
Indeed
But the distance is so big
A handkerchief?
Yes, the thing handed to the pitcher was
A rolled-up handkerchief
You wouldn't notice
But Bobby completely missed it
So
This will be over soon, right?
Out!
Bobby failed to steal a base
Totally out!
OK, well played
Challenge failed
Blocked successfully
Why?
You held the ball and threw it to him
That's wasn't a ball, it was a handkerchief
It was a handkerchief
Is this okay?
What the hell?
You didn't confirm where the ball was
Who was holding what
Do you usually throw handkerchiefs?
Can you throw a handkerchief at the Tokyo Dome?
There used to be a "Handkerchief Prince"
※Yuuki Saito: In 2006, Saito's high school division reached the Koshien Summer Conference. His valiant appearance and the way he wiped his sweat with a neatly folded handkerchief on the pitcher's mound caused a media frenzy and the name "Handkerchief Prince" became popular. He only accumulated 15 wins in 8 years of his career as of the 19th season.
Took it out of his pocket like this
Saito, right?
-Yes, the same thing.
The pitcher was sweating and handed a handkerchief to him at first base
So
The next target is
Giants Sakamoto player's impersonation artist Honzaka
※akamoto Isato: The current captain of the Yomiuri Giants joined the Giants in 2007. On May 1, 2019, he hit the first home run of the NPB order and era at Tokyo Dome.
Really similar!
He belonged to the baseball team as a student
Very true
So similar
Will he notice the hidden ball?
Sakamoto is this short?
The result is...
After holding the same position as before
Just as a sec
Under the guise of a strategy meeting
And the fielders gather on the mound
Give the ball to first base
And on the pitcher's glove is something commonly found in magic
A dove
Okay?
Open again
Sorry, let's start
After returning to their respective positions, the game resumes
The pitcher gives Honzaka a quick glance at the ball-like object
Not surprisingly, the distance between the base bag and the distance...
Wow!
Out!
Thank you, OK OK
Thank you
At this time, the plan is revealed
No success
Yes... ah
The last is the man that has a 10-second record for the 100 meters
Dante Carver
For this verification a similar approach is used
Again the players gather on the mound
Where is the ball?
Out!
Thank you
Seriously?
In summary
Regardless of whether it's allowed or not, its impossible to avoid
What do you think?
Not very interesting
So direct?
No, it's fun
Get rid of this VTR
Wait, Matsumoto, its our first appearance
-Magic
It's not called magic, it's post magic
Post
Post magic
It's not post magic!
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03